(Do you remember the Family Package Project?)
(It was the 1st global project of 2018 on Running Man.)
(Depending on their 4-week missions, their fates divided.)
(4 special members joined them on this special project.)
(And four races unfolded with these members.)
(The roulette of their fates was completed while playing dirty.)
(The Luxury Package got Switzerland. The Shuddering Package, the UK.)
(And one snap determined...)
(the different fates of the 12 members.)
(Switzerland: Jong Kook, Jin Young, Haha, Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Han Na)
(UK: Jae Seok, So Min, Sang Yeob, Seok Jin, Da Hee, and Kwang Soo)
(And at last,)
(6 members of the Luxury Package went to Zermatt, Switzerland.)
(But was there more to this luxurious trip?)
(5 members of the Shuddering Package went to wing walk with heavy feet.)
(What on earth happened to them?)
(June 9, the day of the Luxury Package members' departure)
- Hello. - Are you all ready?
- I can't. - You can't ski? It's all set up.
No, I can't.
- Jong Kook can teach you. - The story is all set up.
- Jong Kook, I like the members. - Goodness.
- My goodness. - No one pulls absurd stunts here.
- I like this group. - The group is fun to have fun with.
Jong Kook, without you, everyone will pull ridiculous stunts.
(Don't get the wrong idea.)
- They're a group of jokers. - Ridiculous stunts...
- I warned them in advance. - You did?
- Jong Kook said this to me. - I told her not to be ambitious.
"Jin Young, don't be ambitious to get a lot of airtime."
- "Let's take this easy." - Right.
- "The scenery will be great." - Exactly.
- They promised to kiss... - Hey, they have to air...
- on the Alps. - No, listen.
(She adds a spoonful of a ridiculous story.)
No, listen. The natural landscape is too pretty not to air on TV.
We won't be on TV longer because we desperately try harder.
- You're desperately trying now. - No, that's not true.
- Jong Kook. - It's already started. It began.
- I ask because I'm curious. - This is so weird.
How many black outfits...
(Do you like me or something?)
- What? - Do you keep buying them?
- This is a misunderstanding. - I get that it is.
Don't get the wrong idea. I always liked black.
- You always liked black? - Yes, I did.
- I'll research your past clips. - I can't...
- Look into every clip. - I can't stand next to them.
- We can never stay together. - I'm getting a headache.
- I suddenly have a headache. - Come here. It's not balanced.
- Look at him. - He was thinking about me.
- You matched yours to mine. - Right.
I wanted to have an easy time during those five days.
Why do you always rebel against me when you're not with me?
- Rebel? What do you mean? - You do when I'm not with you.
When I rebel against you in your presence, you'll hit me.
(Do you need to ask?)
- If I do, you'd hit me. - When I'm not with you,
you do that. That's why people get the wrong idea. I don't hit people.
I didn't know Jong Kook watched our shows.
- That's how he is. - It's the final episode of...
the Family Package Project. We'll depart for Switzerland today.
(They'll head to Switzerland.)
- Let's go! Let's go! - I didn't know I'd be on this trip.
- It was hard filming all the shows. - Right.
- We need to relax. We ought to. - It will be paradise.
Zermatt, which you will be heading to, is chosen...
as 1 of the 50 destinations to visit before you die.
It was ranked first as the place to visit by the Swiss if...
- they could visit only one place. - Really?
In Zermatt, you will be skiing during summer.
- That had been my dream. - Skiing during summer.
- How is it possible during summer? - I can't believe this.
- You'll have cheese fondue. - Cheese fondue.
- Fondue. - You'll sleep at the hotel...
with the highest observatory in Europe.
(This is their 3rd stop on their itinerary.)
(Really? This is amazing!)
This is my dream.
- You didn't know about that. - What? No, I did.
- You knew about the observatory? - No, I didn't.
- Gosh. They look like... - Then what dream?
- You two look like a couple. - Isn't that right?
You definitely didn't know about it. Stop forcing those reactions.
His hand feels awkward. It's hard to let his hand rest on my shoulder.
- Right? - Why?
And the theme of the Luxury Package is...
- Do Everything You Want to Do. - This is insane.
(Do Everything You Want to Do)
You can add activities you'd like to do to the itinerary.
You will be able to do every activity you choose.
(We will let you do every activity you choose.)
- You. You'll be a famous director. - We can use SBS' budget?
Please bring in the board.
(The itinerary is beyond luxurious.)
- There are a lot. - We must visit there.
- Gosh. - Look at all the food.
- Look at that. - The veal sausages look good.
- Yes, they look delicious. - Skiing there would be awesome.
- How many can we choose? - As many as you want.
You can discuss among yourselves and choose as many as you want.
- This is incredible. - To be honest...
You know this Heli-skiing?
(They can get off the helicopter anywhere and ski on the Alps.)
(During this activity of the nature, they can ski at 4,000m altitude.)
- My gosh, that's my dream. - I went there 20 years ago.
- You did? Did you ski there? - I stayed there for two weeks.
- No, I didn't have enough money. - Really?
- Seriously? - It's expensive.
To those who enjoy skiing or snowboarding,
it's a dream.
It used to be my dream.
Jin Young can't ski.
(Jin Young can't ski.)
Jong Kook, you can carry her in your arms, right?
- Carry her on your back. - Carry her on your back.
I am telling you.
I can tie her to my waist.
Fine. Go ahead and choose that option.
Look. It's not like you are completely disinterested, JK.
(Look. It's not like you are completely disinterested, JK.)
- JK. - JK.
- JK. - Stop calling me JK.
(JK is a cute nickname.)
Let's choose heli-skiing.
- I agree. We have to try it. - We have to try it.
- Let's try heli-skiing. - Look at that.
How about this one?
- Paragliding. - How about paragliding?
Paragliding.
- Let's go look at the sheep. - I know. This is so cute.
You know,
we can see sheep in Korea.
- Let's go see them. - These sheep have black faces.
You can paint the Korean ones.
Let's go over to this side.
It's time to choose the food.
- The Michelin Guide. - This one.
- Mediterranean cuisine. - It looks delicious.
- It looks delicious. Look at it. - Mediterranean cuisine.
What's Mediterranean cuisine?
It's a cuisine of the Mediterranean Sea.
- What does that mean? - East, Yellow, or Mediterranean.
The sea that is close to Switzerland is Mediterranean Sea.
East, Yellow, or Mediterranean Sea.
It must be expensive.
- It's the best. - It's luxurious.
Jin Young, this one is for you.
Stargazing at an observatory.
(Stargaze at an observatory with JK.)
- We can stargaze anywhere. - That star is your star
That star is my star
(They are ridiculous.)
When you sang those words, his heart fluttered.
- JK's heart fluttered. - JK.
It's not like you are completely disinterested, JK.
Did she order you to do this?
- Maybe the production crew did. - I got paid.
Did you get paid?
I got paid by Jin Young.
You are pretty funny.
Let's do it.
- Sure. - Let's stargaze at an observatory.
You chose the tours.
Now, I will give you the real rules of the Luxury Package tour.
- Are there rules? - Real rules?
Gosh, you are being annoying again.
Luxury Package shouldn't have any rules.
During the duration of your trip,
you have to finish the chosen tours to return to Korea.
As for the additional tours you have chosen,
you will pay the expenses.
You will pay the expenses.
- That's just wrong. - Don't be like that.
- Don't be like that. - That lying...
Heli-skiing is expensive.
It will cost thousands of dollars.
You should have listened to women.
- We suggested looking at the sheep. - We suggested looking at the sheep.
Seriously.
The black-faced sheep.
The flights, hotels,
and the basics will be paid by the production crew.
Isn't this robbery?
- Isn't this robbery? - This is extortion.
They are basically telling us to pay for this trip.
- We can't do this. - This restaurant must be expensive.
It must cost 300 dollars per person to eat there.
Who pays for the additional tours...
will be decided by a vote and Half and Half Roulette.
(A vote and Half and Half Roulette)
- This is worse. - Don't spin the roulette.
Firstly,
you will have a secret vote per each tour.
After enjoying the tour, the ballot box will be opened.
The members whose names are in it...
will get written on the roulette instead of the production crew.
Then the one person who gets chosen will pay.
The production crew might get chosen too.
Our names are bound to show up in the ballot box.
- This is scary. - If no one writes the name,
the chance is half and half between the members and the crew.
We will have a chance if we join forces.
- That's right. - We will have a chance.
I already see three traitors.
No, no.
- I won't write anyone's name. - I am conscientious.
- You are bound to backstab us. - I don't do that around Jong Kook.
I won't... I won't write anyone's name.
Sure.
Before you return to Korea,
there will be the Last Refund Chance for those who paid for the tours.
Last Refund Chance?
Please bring in the board.
Can we get our money back?
We become thankful of such chances.
Can we get a refund?
- Hey, hey. - What is this?
(What?)
(What are these?)
I got goosebumps as soon as I saw the board.
Okay, I will get a refund.
- What is "a refund"? - You get your money back.
(You can't beat Se Chan's naivete.)
You get your money back.
You remember these, right?
These are the three activities for the Shuddering Package.
(3 activities for the Shuddering Package)
(Cable car bungee jumping from the height of 134m)
(A form of triathlon at a rough canyon, canyoning)
(The longest suspension bridge that is 494m long and 85m high)
These are the three activities for the Shuddering Package.
If you try one of the activities,
you will get a full refund.
(If they try one of the activities, they get a full refund.)
These activities are really scary.
I can't bungee jump.
I am going to lie down on the bed...
upon arrival.
This isn't the Luxury Package.
Let's promise not to vote for each other...
- before we worry about these. - That's right.
- Seriously. - That's right.
Let's use the production crew's money.
That's right.
The least we can do is say that we'll do so.
(He has zero trust in them.)
In any case, this is nice. The members are nice as well.
This is nice.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Let's see if their friendship lasts.)
Let's film a video.
- We are going to Switzerland. - We are going to Switzerland.
This is lovely.
My goodness, you aren't wearing any makeup.
This is a celebrity's bare face.
- Look at Ji Hyo's face. - Since I have to sleep,
I washed my face and got ready to go to bed.
- Are you going to Switzerland? - Yes.
How luxurious!
We will have...
- the Luxury Package in Switzerland. - Let's go.
- Fondue. - Fondue.
- Switzerland. - We are going there.
- What is this? - A sheet mask.
Is this you?
(Ji Hyo puts on a sheet mask as soon as she boards the plane.)
You put this on your face.
Like that?
- You put this on your face. - Then you sleep.
(Se Chan begins to take care of his skin.)
- Look at this. - What is that?
- It's Ji Hyo's sheet mask. - Really?
- I want to try it. - Try it.
(We are handsome men.)
(It's time for them to fall asleep.)
(Drawing)
(I am done.)
(He is satisfied.)
(The three sisters are busy chatting.)
(He glances at them.)
(Haha finds his childhood innocence and approaches Ji Hyo.)
(He gives her the packet he scribbled on.)
It's nice.
(Excited to hear him compliment on her product,)
(she takes a picture with the packet he scribbled on.)
(My mission is complete.)
(About 10 minutes pass.)
(For goodness' sake.)
What is this?
(Flustered)
(For goodness' sake.)
What is this?
(Let's see how the immature Team Luxury fares.)
I feel like we are going to a battlefield.
I feel horrible.
- Hello. - For goodness' sake.
- Hello. - It's not fun to be at the airport.
I have never felt good...
about going to the airport while shooting Running Man.
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
- He is about to drop dead. - I got an IV injection yesterday.
He looks like he is headed for the netherworld.
I was surprised to see his face.
You know, it has been a while...
- since we saw Da Hee. - It has been a while.
- She became prettier. - That's right.
She became more stylish.
The hat changed her looks.
Kwang Soo, why didn't you finish tucking in your shirt?
- No, this is... - What is this?
What are you pointing at?
(Watch where you point.)
What are you doing?
The two of you should be apart from each other.
Gosh, you always stay close and bicker.
- He is very sensitive today. - I know.
- He is sensitive. - Did you miss Da Hee?
That came out of nowhere.
- Maybe you missed Da Hee. - To be honest,
- I thought about contacting Da Hee. - Why didn't you?
- She might have misunderstood. - I asked him yesterday,
and he said that she might think he is making a move on her.
I realized that I would be annoyed...
whether she misunderstands or not.
That's why I didn't contact her.
Good job.
Did you gain weight?
- What? - Did you gain weight?
You can't wing walk if you weigh over 78kg.
I ate a lot these days,
but there is only so much weight you can gain.
I gained weight up to 77kg.
- You just needed to go a bit more. - 1kg.
Then I suddenly had...
- You had a struggle. - I had a struggle...
and ended up losing 5kg.
Now, I weigh 72kg.
- You just needed to gain 3kg. - I know.
I won't be able to wing walk...
- if there is a weight restriction. - You can't do it if you weigh 80kg.
I weigh 80kg.
(I weigh 80kg.)
Really?
- Do you weigh 80kg? - Do you weigh 80kg?
Why is no one telling her to stop lying?
(There is no way she weighs that much.)
Why does everyone think it's plausible?
- I thought it might be plausible. - You know, Da Hee is...
- No one's saying anything. - She's tall.
- Da Hee is very tall. - I'm tall.
How much do you weigh?
- I weigh 70kg. - You don't weigh a lot.
Sang Yeob wants to be a regular member of Running Man.
He is very ambitious.
He says...
he can do anything...
the production crew asks.
I always tell the production crew...
that I can come fully dressed up...
if they tell me an hour ahead.
(I can come fully dressed up if they tell me an hour ahead.)
(He is a prepared man.)
In the beginning, the production crew liked that.
Now, they find it burdensome.
You are too enthusiastic.
When you got out of the car, the staff went,
"What is wrong with him?"
(It's fun to slander.)
For the finale of the Running Man Family Package Project,
you will leave for the UK for the Shuddering Package.
(It's the day they leave for the UK for the Shuddering Package.)
(It's finally here.)
(Wing walking, an unprecedented and extreme experience)
(It starts now.)
How do you feel?
(How do you feel about going to the UK?)
We just talked about it.
- We've been talking about... - What do you mean?
- how we felt for 30 minutes. - Talk about how we feel?
Do I have to curse again?
(Are you teasing us?)
All of you got quite sensitive.
As you're about to travel far,
- there are two gifts for you. - Gifts?
(Two special gifts)
Let's open the first gift box.
They're real gifts.
Who prepared it?
(It's the first gift.)
- What are they? - What are they?
(Special Pirate Roulette Game made from clay)
Look at the characters.
It's Pirate Roulette Game.
A Running Man fan sent Pirate Roulette Games...
- that she made with a letter. - She made them herself?
- Herself? - Really?
- It's Seok Jin. - This is me.
- It's Seok Jin. - It is.
"To Running Man members,"
"I'm a huge fan of Running Man. I'm Cho Yeon Woo."
"I've been watching the show since I was 12."
"It's been 8 years, and I'm 20."
- Really? - That's cute.
"When I was in middle school, I made name tags..."
"to play Name Tag Elimination."
"You work very hard."
"You often play Pirate Roulette Game these days,"
"so I made Running Man characters with clay."
"I planned to make Grasshopper Jae Seok and Penguin Haha."
"However, I ran out of clay, so I made an impala."
(However, I ran out of clay, so I made an impala.)
(It's an unexpected impala.)
To make the penguin,
it requires more clay.
I was very happy at first.
He had no choice.
- I can understand. - He had no choice.
He still made it, so I'm thankful.
"P.S. Se Chan and So Min who joined recently are great."
"Sincerely, your big fan, Yeon Woo"
- Thank you. - Thank you, Yeon Woo.
- We'd like to thank Yeon Woo again. - We thank you.
She made them so well.
Is this another gift?
Open them at the same time.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- 3. - 3.
- What is it? - It's a grasshopper and a frog.
- It's a frog. - It's a frog.
So Min.
- It's a frog. - Did another fan make them?
(So Min loves it.)
It's so cute.
It's a frog.
- "I love you, I'm sorry, thanks." - "I love you, I'm sorry, thanks.
"Hello, I'm Luxurious Yang Se Chan."
- What? - How's the weather in the UK?
"The weather is perfect for wing walking."
"If I had gone there, I'd ride it for you. It's unfortunate."
"Be safe and enjoy the ride."
"Luxurious Se Chan."
(Se Chan is such a brat.)
(Wait until we come back.)
Yang Se Chan.
There's one more thing.
Sang Yeob and Da Hee haven't signed the oath yet.
Please sign the oath.
(It's time to sign the oath.)
Please read the oath...
and sign it.
- Write in English. - Write it in capital letters.
Wait, is this what I write?
Sang Yeob is prepared for the ride.
You weigh 70kg, which is perfect.
It's perfect.
Do we just sign here?
She weighs less than I do.
- What? - Stop lying.
I'm not.
- Do you weigh 52kg? - Yes.
You only weigh that much?
- She weighs 53kg. - She's lean.
No, I don't.
- You wrote 53kg. - Aren't you in the 40s range?
So Min weighs 53kg.
Da Hee sounded very mean.
Really?
Listen to Da Hee.
There's no point in lying. You'll be weighed before the ride.
It's better to be honest.
- Will we be weighed? - Yes.
It's for safety reasons.
(She changes her number.)
Are you changing the 10th digit?
You don't have to ride it then.
You can be exempt.
Stop it.
Why are you erasing it?
- She erased it several times. - Why are you erasing it?
- What are you doing, Da Hee? - Do you weigh 56kg?
- I was... - Just write 60kg to be safe.
(Her final weight is 56kg.)
Before you travel to the UK,
- we have bad news for you. - What is it?
Wing walking ride operates a limited number of times...
per day.
(There's a limit to wing walking rides.)
Among you...
(The number of rides is limited.)
- only three will ride it. - Okay.
(Only 3 members will wing walk.)
- That's unfortunate. - That's half of us.
- That's half of us. - Okay.
- We have a 50-percent chance. - Okay.
This is what we prepared for Shuddering Package in the UK.
It's called Unlucky of the Unlucky. Here are the rules.
(Unlucky of the Unlucky)
It's a total of four rounds.
Penalty badges will be distributed based on the results.
We have badges today.
Based on the number of penalty badges,
the size of Pirate Roulette at the final race will change.
(Pirate Roulette size changes.)
The 1st and 2nd place get 24 slots.
The 3rd and 4th place get 16 slots.
The 5th and 6th place get 8 slots in Pirate Roulette Game.
You play in the order of the last to first.
(The game is played in the order of the last to first.)
The 1st 3 losers get on the wing walking ride.
(The 1st 3 losers get on the wing walking ride.)
(You're at a disadvantage the more badges you have.)
Kwang Soo.
It doesn't matter whether you're first or last place.
Even if you get 100 slots in Pirate Roulette Game,
- The pirate will pop. - you always lose.
- I was startled by him. - He always loses.
Even our trip to the UK is worrisome.
Here's the mission to determine the ranking.
It's called Hard Suitcase.
(Hard Suitcase)
- Each of you brought a suitcase. - Yes.
Do you see a line of white tape?
That's the starting line.
Push your suitcase to the line. The ranking will be determined...
by how close your suitcase gets to the line.
(The last three receive penalty badges.)
- It's similar to curling. - Of course.
Okay.
- Seok Jin will start. - Okay.
- Do we only get one chance? - That's right.
(Seok Jin, Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, So Min, Sang Yeob, and Da Hee)
The penalty is the penalty badge.
(You get a badge when your suitcase is the farthest from the line.)
- That's good. - He did well.
(Pushing)
(Sliding)
(Where will Seok Jin's suitcase stop?)
Don't go farther.
It went far.
(It's hard to tell whether it's close or far.)
- That's not bad. - It's considered good.
If you push it toward the corner, it'll be closer than Seok Jin's.
- You're right. - Right?
- Here's what I will do. - Okay, Sang Yeob.
I'll push mine toward Seok Jin's and move it farther.
- Okay. - Here I go.
- That's right. - It's not as easy as you think.
- Let's go. - The direction is good.
- That's good. - It's turning.
Let's go.
(Sliding)
(It's turning.)
(It's closer to the line than Seok Jin's.)
- He did well. - That's good.
(He's in a daze.)
That's good.
(Sang Yeob is in 1st place.)
Good job.
(That was a good strategy.)
- Next is So Min. - This is how it starts.
Next is So Min.
I bet she won't do well.
- Her suitcase will get on the line. - She won't do well.
(How will So Min do?)
That was too weak. You're last.
(Sliding slowly)
(That was too weak. You're last.)
- So Min is last. - You made it turn back.
(She does a horrible job as everyone expected.)
- So Min and I are similar. - Her suitcase turned back.
We're bad at serious games.
- She's at a disadvantage. - She's good at practice games.
(She's only good at practicing.)
- I feel too pressured. - That's good.
The suitcase moved like a boomerang.
(Current ranking is Sang Yeob, Seok Jin, and So Min.)
- Move forward. - What is he doing?
- He's concentrating. - Move forward.
(Jae Seok is bad at serious games. He's the fourth player.)
(How far will his suitcase go?)
- It's going well. - Don't push mine away.
It passed mine. It went far.
(His suitcase stops far from the line.)
Oh, no.
I'm second place.
Jae Seok is last.
(Currently, he's last place.)
My goodness.
He's so bad at playing games.
Next is Kwang Soo.
(Current ranking is Sang Yeob, Seok Jin, So Min, and Jae Seok.)
(Okay, I got this.)
(Where will Kwang Soo's suitcase go?)
It's not moving as much as I thought.
- It's moving. - It's not bad.
(Sliding)
It's moving.
- It's going far. - Wait.
(It passes the line.)
- Wait. - It's moving.
- What? - It's moving.
(Sliding)
(It moves out of range.)
- Where is it going? - It's out.
It's out.
- What happened? - It's out.
- What? - It's out.
- This is considered out. - How?
- It's out. - It's on the line.
- It's not a line. - It's on the line.
The line stops here.
- It's on the line. - It stops here.
- It's up to the camera. - Here's the line.
- It's up to the camera. - What?
- I'll move the camera. - Come back to your senses.
- What do you mean? - It's up to the camera.
- What senses? - The line ends at the camera.
- That's nonsense. - It's on the line.
Listen, your suitcase even passed the lighting.
What's the purpose of the lighting?
We're filming up to here.
I'm important, not the lighting.
Ask the lighting director.
Listen, sir.
- You placed the lighting here... - Can't you move it?
because you didn't intend to film beyond this point, right?
- Right. - See?
Where does the framework end for the camera?
- In front of the camera. - "In front of the camera".
(The film framework is up to where the camera is.)
- It's out. - What's wrong with him?
- Stop it. - What are you doing?
He's very experienced.
How long have you been a director?
- It's been 10 years. - 10 years? See?
He has 10 years of experience.
He's worked longer than you.
- I've worked for 10 years. - Stop lying.
The first time I saw you was five years ago.
- Five years? - What are you talking about?
- It's my 9th year on Running Man. - What?
- Was I a ghost for four years? - I don't know.
I met you five years ago.
Stop it, Kwang Soo.
(It's Kwang Soo's fault.)
Does Kwang Soo get another chance, or is he disqualified?
He's disqualified.
"Disqualified"?
How am I disqualified?
He's disqualified.
You placed last.
Ask the lighting director.
- Do you think he disqualified? - Please, sir.
Does he get to play, or is he disqualified?
(Director, does he play again or is he disqualified?)
Please, sir.
- He's disqualified. - Okay.
(He answers right away.)
What is he?
(Is he a referee for the World Cup?)
Okay, just wait and see.
Are you really going to be this harsh? Okay.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
(It's the last player, Da Hee's turn.)
- I'll push Sang Yeob's away. - What's wrong with you?
- Good. - I'll push Sang Yeob's away.
Da Hee, push it away. Or push Seok Jin's away.
I know how to make it turn.
Are you a good pool player?
(Yes, I'm Da Hee, a pool player.)
I mean...
(The dark horse pushes her suitcase.)
Unbelievable.
(Grinning)
(It approaches the suitcase in the best spot.)
- Go. - It's going out.
My goodness.
- She's disqualified! - She's disqualified!
- It's going out. - My goodness.
(Her true skills are revealed.)
(Why did it end up next to Kwang Soo's?)
- You're out! - Red card!
- Red card! - Hey.
I'm not out.
- I think these two will lose. - They ended up next to each other.
I think you two will end up wing-walking.
- How could this happen? - I almost hit...
- I was right on the line. - Sang Yeob's.
Mine was already out, and she pushed it away.
Yours attracted Da Hee's like a magnet.
(Kwang Soo has 3 badges, Da Hee 2, and Jae Seok 1.)
You already have three badges? You'll definitely lose.
Even if I have to wing walk, I'll make sure Jae Seok does it too.
I don't know what kinds of games we'll be playing,
but I'll make sure you end up on the wing...
by all means.
By all means.
- Let's get it! - Let's go!
(Kwang Soo has 3 badges, Da Hee 2, and Jae Seok 1.)
I feel a bit relieved now.
Kwang Soo, you already have so many badges.
Jae Seok, I just realized...
which path I should take in the UK.
The only path you can take leads to wing walking.
And seeing ghosts.
No. I think you're on the same path as me.
(Let's see.)
(After 12 hours of flight, they arrive in the UK.)
- We're in the UK. Thank you. - Take the flowers.
Thank you. They knew we were coming.
They've been waiting for us?
We often hear words of concern from our fans at airports.
- A fan just said, "Don't pass out." - What did she say?
- Really? - Yes.
(Don't pass out while wing walking.)
We might.
Why can't you just let us enjoy our trip?
(Gloomy)
I hate when Seok Jin does this.
You heard what Seok Jin said on the flight, right?
- What did I say? - "Guys."
- "There's no way I'll wing walk." - "No matter what you guys say."
And on camera, he says,
"I'm nervous to death."
(He changes his attitude.)
What are you doing?
I think the UK is the right place for me.
- The air is so nice here. - You said that in Mongolia too.
They're smoking right there. What are you talking about?
(They're smoking right there. What are you talking about?)
(It's a smoking area.)
We're walking right past a smoking area.
- What are you talking about? - Did you hear what he said?
"I have no idea where I am right now."
- "Am I in Sangam?" - I did say that.
- Everyone. - Yes.
We're in London now.
London.
We were welcomed by so many fans.
We appreciate it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We love Running Man.)
(I'm so popular.)
Thank you.
(Thank you.)
- Lee Kwang Soo, Lee Kwang Soo - Lee Kwang Soo, Lee Kwang Soo
(Sad versus happy)
(Thank you.)
- Lee Kwang Soo - Not Jee Seok Jin?
We're in London now.
The wing walking place...
and the ghost castle is in Oxford.
We'll go there by car.
I didn't want to visit the UK like this.
Where should we go now?
- Let's get on the bus. - Okay. Let's go!
- Let's go! - Is wing walking fun?
This is better.
Da Hee, right now or later?
- Later. - I'm all swollen up.
We look like newlyweds.
- Right? - Yes.
What?
- You don't look like newlyweds. - Not at all.
- Newlyweds, my foot. - You look like colleagues.
What are you doing right now?
- You said you were sick of him. - You were sick of Sang Yeob.
He looks more handsome in the UK.
When my swelling goes down tomorrow, I'll look awesome.
His well-defined, facial features suit the UK.
- Da Hee. - My goodness.
- Jeon So Min, Jeon So Min - So Min.
(Shy)
- So Min. - So Min.
What's happening on your honeymoon?
- What's going on? - You're on your honeymoon.
- Lee Da Hee, Lee Da Hee - Da Hee.
- Da Hee. - Da Hee.
- You should be grateful. - Thank you.
- Lee Da Hee - Lee Da Hee
- Lee Sang Yeob... - Lee Sang Uk?
- Lee Sa Yeob? - What's his name?
- Lee Sa? - Lee Sang Yo?
They're trying to remember Sang Yeob's name.
- They're discussing. - They're talking about it.
- Lee Sang Yeob, Lee Sang Yeob - Lee Sang Yeob, Lee Sang Yeob
(Thank you, guys.)
After shouting Da Hee's name,
they were not sure.
(Sang Yeob?)
- "Lee Sang Uk?" - There was a discussion.
It was silent for a moment.
(It feels good to be in the UK.)
- Let's go. - It's 4am in Seoul,
- but I don't feel tired. - Right.
I feel okay for some reason.
Da Hee got some sleep on the flight.
- I did. - Right?
- Sang Yeob slept too. - You snored.
I didn't.
I thought it was a tiger.
Da Hee, you snored.
It's okay.
- It's okay. - It was really you?
(It was really you?)
I didn't snore. I never do.
I sleep quietly like a baby.
What are you talking about?
- Like a baby? - What are you talking about?
- My nickname is Baby. - Baby?
I heard you snore.
- What are you talking about? - I sleep quietly like a baby.
You slept like a baby tiger.
What?
I see words I know everywhere. "Short-stay car park".
- You know what it means, right? - Temporary stay.
English is not difficult.
- Look. "Emergency exit". - If it's not difficult,
why were you so quiet at the immigration desk earlier?
The officer kept talking, but you didn't say anything.
Look around. Don't be afraid of English.
If you're so good at English,
why did you say, "Coffee pot, come on"?
(Why did you say, "Coffee pot, come on"?)
- Why did you say that? - "Coffee pot, come on"?
- "Coffee pot, come on." - It just...
- slipped my mind. - Why did you do that?
It's like a foreigner saying,
"Come here, coffee pot," in Korean.
- "Come on." - And they brought it to you.
- "Come on." - They understood...
- what you meant. - "Coffee pot, come on."
"Come here, coffee pot."
Tonight, you'll be staying...
- at an ordinary hotel. - Will it be an ordinary place?
- Tomorrow, at the ghost castle. - Why are you doing this to us?
I completely forgot about it.
What if Seok Jin wakes up in the morning...
and suddenly sounds like a baby?
(What if he becomes possessed by a baby ghost?)
What should I do then?
(It might really happen.)
In the early 90s, on SBS,
a TV show had a Japanese hypnotist as a guest.
Seok Jin stroked a shoe as if it were a cat under hypnosis.
- Really? - I was under hypnosis.
- Is there a video? - Were you hypnotized?
(This is the video of Seok Jin under hypnosis 20 years ago.)
(How is your dog right now?)
(He seems hungry.)
(Comedian Kim Ji Sun)
(I feel sorry for him.)
(Seok Jin was hypnotized by a world-renowned hypnotist.)
I was hypnotized for real.
- Really? - You weren't pretending?
- He wasn't. - It was for real.
- He was hypnotized. - That's incredible.
I watched it on TV and laughed a lot.
Yong Man and I wondered...
whether Seok Jin put on a show to become a star...
- or if it was for real. - He was pretending.
(Has Seok Jin always been like this?)
But Seok Jin does fall for those things easily.
I do.
He does.
Is it because you focus easily?
- It's the opposite. - It means you're weak.
(It means you're weak.)
(You brats.)
In 15 minutes, we'll stop by at a rest area.
Would you like to play a game to give someone a badge?
- I'm good at it. - Timing game.
- I have nothing to lose. - One badge?
That's right.
If two people say a number at the same time, they both lose.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Just one round. - Timing game.
I'm going to say, "one".
- I'm going to say, "1". - I'm going to say, "1".
- I'm serious. - I don't want a badge.
- I'm going to say, "1". - I'm going to say, "2".
- I'm going to say, "1". - I'm going to say, "1".
Ready. You have to raise your hand too.
- Let's go. - Ready. Set. Go.
- 1. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
(Seok Jin was waiting for the right moment.)
(He shouts the last number out loud.)
(I tried to be quick.)
- Gosh. - My pain went away.
- I thought I'd lose. - So did I.
You guys have such great teamwork.
He said, "six," so confidently.
Fine. You guys want to take advantage of me?
- What are you talking about? - What are you talking about?
Okay.
- We didn't take advantage. - The game doesn't require thinking.
- What did we do wrong? - Let's play once more.
Okay, I understand.
(Seok Jin gets a penalty badge.)
(They finally arrive in Zurich after 17 hours of flight.)
The weather is great.
- The weather is so beautiful. - It's unbelievable.
It's so cool.
- Who said that it's cold here? - Thank goodness.
- It's summer. - The weather is amazing.
- Okay! - The weather is incredible.
It's amazing.
There's not an inch of fine dust.
- The air is different. - I can see everything.
We heard top secret information.
Are we riding a train?
It took about a day to get here.
That's right.
I wouldn't be surprised if we're in Brazil.
You have so many bugs on you, Ji Hyo.
- It's because of the color. - It's because we couldn't shower.
- I didn't get a chance to shower. - Can we please wash?
This is the Luxury Package.
- You're in Zurich, Switzerland. - Right.
You're in Zurich, Switzerland.
Do we have to do that?
- That's fake. - It's fake.
Really?
- We're in Zurich, Switzerland. - Why don't we...
- play along? - Just do it, Jong Kook.
- Let's do it. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Screaming in joy)
In 1, 2, 3.
(They scream in joy while waving their arms.)
- This is great. - I'm excited.
(We can't believe that we're in Switzerland.)
- Is this a drama? - Luxurious Switzerland.
We're filming a drama.
Everyone.
You finally arrived in Zurich, Switzerland.
We almost got in trouble while passing immigration customs.
- What happened? - Jin Young looked different.
(Jin Young looked different from her photo.)
- He said... - He looked at my passport photo.
He looked confused.
I asked him if I looked different.
What did I say?
- "Face upgrade". - "Upgrade".
(The simple answer was face upgrade.)
"Face upgrade".
- Seriously. - He let me go.
He let her pass immediately.
He thought that she was bold.
At least she's honest.
Let's go to the train station.
- Okay, let's go. - Let's go.
- Are we going to a train station? - Let's go.
Let's go.
(The city's life and culture can be found at train stations.)
Is this the train station?
Okay, it's a railway.
- Jin Young. - Yes?
Will you keep looking around?
I'm in a foreign country. I don't look around in Seoul.
It looks similar to Cheongnyangni Station, Line One.
It seems like Seoul Station.
- The ambiance is similar. - Doesn't it?
- It's here. - Is that it? It arrived.
There's a place to put luggage.
(It's a second-story train.)
Be careful on your right.
(They climb up to the 2nd floor.)
It's amazing.
(There's a lounge with a couch.)
- Goodness. - This is incredible.
This must be a romantic train.
- This is great. - It's romantic.
- It's romantic. - It's beautiful compared to the UK.
- Right. - We have better members too.
This is a place for lovers to visit.
- Do you want to sit here? - This is great.
- It's okay. - Two of you are perfect.
(Jin Young and Jong Kook are perfect together.)
Your outfits are also similar.
You make a perfect couple.
- Shall I change seats? - It's too fake.
- It's uncomfortable. - Stop it.
- Don't be fake. - It's fake.
Let's act naturally.
The most unnatural thing is the fact that I'm sitting here.
You're always together.
No, that spot is perfect for your shirt color.
(Hot pink is uncomfortable.)
Since it's romantic, let's get romantic.
- Okay. - How do you mean?
Let's switch partners.
- Why do we have to? - Partners?
Do we even have any?
- You don't like your partner. - He doesn't.
You don't like me?
She's better than her.
(Han Na is better than Ji Hyo who's like family.)
- How about Han Na? - Ji Hyo is...
I prefer Han Na.
- He should be Han Na's partner. - Would that be better?
She's like my sister.
Let's go to the restaurant cart for a meal.
We should be romantic on the train.
- We should act. - It's a romantic train.
It's the first time that we met. I have nothing.
I'll be someone with a strong personality.
- "A strong personality"? - Yes.
(Three male members move first.)
- This is great. - Okay.
(Will they find romance in the restaurant cart?)
It's perfect for a date.
It's like a date.
Since it's hot, let's order something expensive and cool.
- Okay. - That sounds good.
(He pulls out his hair.)
Pull it out.
- You look good. - Right?
- They're here. - They're here.
(The first shy woman to enter is Ji Hyo.)
(Hello, boys.)
(The 1st woman makes a move.)
"Hot Swiss Classics".
I'll get a salad.
(I knew it.)
(Se Chan is the only one she can trust.)
(Yawning)
(He yawns all of a sudden.)
(How could you?)
(The members are heartless to their own members.)
I'll choose...
(What is Ji Hyo's final choice?)
(Tapping)
Okay.
You look handsome with one eye covered.
(This handsome man is mine.)
He's the type of men she likes.
You look better with your hair back.
I found my partner.
(Next up is Han Na.)
Goodness.
Why do you have bangs?
(My name is Haha.)
Why are you pretending to be handsome?
You're here.
(Rolling up his sleeve)
(Will it attract Han Na?)
(It's possible.)
- I came to join you. - Okay.
(I came to join you.)
What's with your arm?
- What? Do I look masculine? - What are you doing?
(In the end, my partner must be...)
- Hello, honey. - Hello.
Who's buying the meal?
Let's eat first.
- Let's eat. - Let's enjoy it.
I have enough money, so order expensive dishes.
Shall we order three dishes?
- Order 4. We'll have 2 each. - "Order 4"?
- "Swiss beef with fried onions". - That sounds good. Order that.
Let's order one salad. It'll be refreshing.
Can you order some kimchi?
- Kimchi? - Yes.
Then I'll order...
- gamjatang. - "Gamjatang"?
- Gamjatang with bones. - With bones?
(The restaurant waiter arrives.)
- This one? - Is it okay?
- That's okay. - One Caesar salad...
- and one beef. - Okay.
One multi-vitamin juice, please.
- Han Na is amazing. - Thank you.
Finished.
(He feels dispirited.)
It's basic English.
It's difficult.
(She's too good for him.)
Here's your salad.
- That was fast. Thank you. - Thank you.
Here you go.
Try some, Han Na.
- You ordered it. - Is it macaroni?
- What's this? - It's beef.
(Six men and women start their meals.)
It looks delicious.
It's so delicious that I'll pass out.
(He passes out due to embarrassment.)
(The food is delicious, and the view is beautiful.)
I hope tomorrow's weather will be like today.
(One more hour of transfer will bring them to Zermatt.)
It's pretty here. Look.
Look at the ceiling.
- This is great. - It's pretty.
(They're impressed.)
- We are - We only say hello.
- In Switzerland - In Switzerland
The train is moving.
(They've been traveling for 21 hours.)
I feel so much better.
- Enjoy it as much as possible. - Until now, I didn't feel...
- like we were in Switzerland. - I know.
Now it feels like Switzerland.
- It's so beautiful. - Look at the view.
There's a waterfall.
This is our life.
Where is the water coming from?
This is amazing.
- It's nature. - Look at that.
It's a romantic ride.
(This is a romantic ride.)
(Impressed)
This is insane.
It's a bridge.
You say that you like me
(They're about to face their harsh fates.)
(This bus is heading to Oxford.)
It's "Y" by Freestyle. I love this song.
- Whose song is it? - It's "Y" by Freestyle.
- It was my background music. - This one?
- It was mine too. - Me too.
It was the most popular song on Cyworld at that time.
("Y" by Freestyle is a popular, sentimental song.)
(She goes back to that time and feeling.)
The background of my homepage was snowing with this song.
(A snowing homepage)
It was snowing in the background.
My character had a hairstyle...
I wrote this on the main page.
"Three things that we can't hide".
"Cold, cough,"
"and love".
Goodness, he's blushing.
- "Cold, cough, and love". - "Love".
What are the three things you can't hide?
Me?
Farting.
No way, Da Hee.
It's fatsia.
- Fatsia? - Fatsia?
No.
Yours are fart, sound, and smell.
- No way. - Three things that you can't hide.
Fart, sound, and smell.
Please get ready.
We're having a good time. What now?
- Wait. - Goodness.
They're mission bags.
What are they?
- Wait a minute. - Da Hee.
There's money inside.
- It's from the Brazil World Cup. - What's this?
- There's money. - Can we look?
It's 10 euros.
- Aren't you hungry? - Yes.
We're at a resting area in the UK.
Order a takeout that you'd like to eat.
Bring the takeout outside, and eat together.
- Okay. - It's not a mission, right?
- You must get a takeout. - A takeout?
It's a takeout.
Do we get a takeout?
It doesn't matter what it is. You can buy snacks.
Okay.
- Let's get it. - Let's get it.
(They go to a resting area for food.)
What should I eat for dinner?
I want to eat something new.
Something unique.
- There's a food court. - It's really big.
There are many choices.
The UK is great.
- Gosh, what's that? - What is that?
What's this?
- Roast pork? - Pork?
- It's pork? - Yes.
What are you going to eat?
(What are you going to eat, Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo?)
We're looking around first.
- Hi. - Hello.
(Smiling)
- That looks tasty. - What's that flirtatious smile?
What did you just do?
I've never seen you smile like that before.
(You're supposed to smile when you speak English.)
I'm so embarrassed.
Be quiet.
(Jae Seok stops at a Mexican place.)
They have nachos and burritos.
I want a burrito.
(I want a burrito.)
I'm worried about something.
He's not going to just give me a burrito.
- He'll ask you questions, right? - It'll be...
If he starts to ask me many questions,
it'll be hard.
But you've been here before.
Of course. Don't worry.
Excuse me. Two.
(Jae Seok orders.)
- No more chicken. - No more?
(He goes through the steps confidently.)
Yes. Cheese.
Sour cream?
- Sour cream? - Yes, please.
(His burrito is done.)
It's done.
(Relieved)
Is this... Pork?
(Seok Jin gets pork.)
That's pork skin, right?
I want to try it.
That's nice.
Is that on Youtube?
- You... - Youtube?
Youtube? Yes.
What's your name?
What is your name then?
Write it down, please.
- Big Nose. - Write it down.
- I might have a look. - Yes, yes.
(Does he want to write to me?)
I should write down my name then. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
- "Jee Seok Jin"? - Yes, Mr. Jee.
- Jee. - Yes.
(Mr. Jee becomes an internet star.)
(They're done getting food.)
(Outdoor eating area)
You can eat...
your food now.
Can we share our food?
As you wish.
Kwang Soo, is that all you got?
What did you get?
I just got some fruits.
Why did you get only fruits?
I went for quantity rather than quality.
(A pack of sushi rolls)
(It's Shuddering Package, but they get to enjoy a meal.)
Gosh.
(That was tasty.)
I really enjoyed it.
I love this.
(Have some desserts.)
- Are you done eating? - Yes.
To determine who will be excluded from wing walking,
carry out the second mission, Eat to Fly.
(Eat to Fly)
- Eat to Fly? - What?
We're done eating.
We asked you...
to get takeout.
You'll fold airplanes using your food wrappers and fly them.
Three people whose airplanes fly the shortest distance...
will get 3, 2, and 1 badges respectively.
All I have is aluminum foil.
(The bottom three will get penalty badges.)
(All I have is aluminum foil.)
Look.
You should have told me before I crumpled it.
It's all crumpled up now.
What is this?
(While trying to reduce trash, he shortened his life.)
You have to make it look at least somewhat like an airplane.
- What about... - Hold on.
(How can you make this look like an airplane?)
I don't have any wrappers.
(Kwang Soo is dumbfounded by the unexpected mission.)
I don't have anything.
- Gosh. - Hold on.
You can use scissors and tape if you want.
I mean...
I don't even have a plastic bag.
- You should have asked for it. - I don't even have a plastic bag.
(You should have asked.)
What will Kwang Soo do?
Look at mine.
So Min has an advantage.
I have this too.
(She has a paper bag and a thick paper tray.)
I only have aluminum foil.
Gosh, we've been...
(We've been cracking up a lot.)
We've been cracking up a lot in the UK.
- Hold on. - In the UK.
Seok Jin just said,
"My bladder will burst."
(Seok Jin just said, "My bladder will burst.")
Is it okay? Can it air?
Are you feeling okay?
- I heard it clearly. - Me too.
Do you want to pee?
Why did you say that?
I said, "We've been cracking up a lot."
- You said, "bladder". - Hey.
- "My bladder will burst." - Not my bladder.
- You said, "bladder". - I said, "We've been cracking up."
Is there something wrong with your ears?
Replay it. I heard, "My bladder will burst."
(Let's replay the video.)
My bladder will burst.
"We've been cracking up a lot."
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok heard it right.)
- My goodness. - Gosh!
It's torn.
Yours looks okay.
Mine is torn into pieces.
- What happened? - I tore it.
(It's her habit.)
- This tape won't stick. - Okay, okay.
It keeps slipping.
Let me try.
What am I going to do?
This is a perfect airplane.
This is a perfect airplane. Everyone.
I have the best material, so I'm going to...
That looks amazing.
I'm going to add Kwang Soo on the wing.
- That's incredible. - I'm serious. I'm doing this.
You never know who will win...
even though my wrapper has rice on it.
(You never know who will win.)
We won't know until we fly them.
It has to look like an airplane.
It looks like an airplane!
These are wings.
That's not an airplane.
Don't use tape. It's not going to work.
Wait and see.
(Jae Seok's aluminum foil is folded into a plane.)
It looks okay, right?
That looks like an airplane.
I even added...
Kwang Soo on the wing.
(Kwang Soo will be wing walking.)
Why did you do that?
- Kwang Soo, fly. - Sang Yeob did a good job.
- It won't fly. - It won't fly.
I can't even practice. It'd destroy my plane.
Right?
No one can practice!
Can you clean up here? What are you doing?
- What? - What are you doing?
(Da Hee does her best to the end.)
(She focuses on her work while everyone else is laughing.)
- Seok Jin. - Seriously.
(She builds the frame with her chopsticks.)
(She makes sure the wings are balanced.)
You have to get the tail and the wings right.
(She fixes the tail and the wings carefully.)
(Will Da Hee's aluminum foil airplane fly?)
We all have something that looks like an airplane.
Please.
- The rest of us should step back. - Okay.
(Seok Jin used his styrofoam box.)
- Fly. - You stepped on the line.
You stepped on the line.
You're being so strict.
- If you do it again, you're out. - You'll be out.
Please.
(Please fly far.)
(It falls.)
It didn't go far.
(Seok Jin's airplane falls near the starting line.)
It didn't go that far.
- Next up is Sang Yeob. - Me?
I think yours will fly far.
- It doesn't seem to fly well. - Sang Yeob even used...
chopsticks.
(He made his airplane stable by using his wooden chopsticks.)
Let's go.
(Fly to Korea.)
- Okay! - What?
I win.
- Sang Yeob. - Sang Yeob.
No. You should measure from the tail.
You're supposed to measure from the tail.
In all games... What's that called?
- What? - The jumping...
Get some sleep.
Give me the car key.
Seok Jin needs to sleep.
- You mean neolttwigi? - The jump...
- Neolttwigi? - You measure backwards.
That's the right way.
Sang Yeob wins.
- I'm in first place for now. - It didn't...
Next up is So Min.
That's a perfect airplane.
I'm looking forward.
(So Min used her chicken pie bag.)
- I hope it'll turn back. - Please.
It'll turn back.
Love will come back.
Love will come back!
(Come back here!)
- It went far. - It went pretty far.
(Flying)
(It ended up half a step ahead of Seok Jin's and Sang Yeob's.)
She's in first place for now.
- Please step back. - She's in first place.
It didn't fly as far as I expected. I did better while practicing.
Please step back.
(The fourth player, Jae Seok's turn)
This aluminum foil airplane...
- might fly far. - It might...
- fly far. - You never know.
Fling it to the ground.
(Good luck, burrito wrapper airplane.)
- Fling it to the ground. - Even...
Jae Seok's airplane is ugly.
Look at that plane.
See?
Look at that.
(Is it to wish Jae Seok good luck?)
Fling it to the ground.
As a kid, I entered a glider competition.
(You never know who will win.)
(Jae Seok is ready to fly his aluminum foil airplane.)
Fling it to the ground.
(He only has to get past the others to avoid getting a badge.)
Fling it... Yes!
- He flung it. - He flung it.
(Glider Yu, fling it down!)
He's definitely at the bottom.
It's even torn.
Who is up next?
- Me. - Da Hee.
(Another aluminum foil airplane)
Da Hee's looks good.
I even won a prize at a paragliding competition.
- What does that have to do with... - I know how planes work.
What does paragliding have to do with this?
I mean hang gliding.
Hang gliding has nothing to do with paper airplanes either.
- Anyway, just watch. - Okay.
I won't say anything more.
You're very talkative.
- I'm confident about this. - You're confident?
- What are you confident about? - We just made planes with foil.
- Why is she confident? - Hey.
I think she ironed the foil.
- It's really straight. - I made the best of the worst.
But it did seem impossible to make one.
I have to throw it like this from here, right? Just like this?
From here, throw it like this.
- Like this. Like throwing a dart. - Throw it like you would a dart.
In other words, you can't throw it like this.
- You threw it like this though. - By the way...
- You're talking crazy. - Seok Jin.
- If you do, you're slamming it. - Hurry. We have to hurry.
- Kwang Soo's plane is melting. - Hey, Kwang Soo's...
- One of the wings fell. It fell. - Hurry.
I'll do it now.
(After a slight commotion, it's time for Da Hee's plane to fly.)
(Flying)
What? What was that?
(As it drew a beautiful parabola, the plane flew far.)
(My gosh, that's amazing.)
What was that?
- See? It can fly. - The drawing paper works, I guess.
- She did a great job. - I'm in third place.
(Sang Yeob, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok could get badges.)
- Next up is Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo's plane is about to depart.)
- It'll fly far due to its weight. - Play fair.
(Since it's heavy, the fruit peel might fly far.)
- Let's be fair. I'll hold this. - Okay.
- You can't extend your arm... - Okay, okay. I won't.
- Hold on. - It can't go down.
- That's why I have to block here. - If you throw it, it'll fly far.
- Why are you always harsh on me? - Yours...
It's because yours has the highest chance.
- You might cheat. - If you throw, it'll fly far.
- I'll block here. - You can go as low as this.
- Move just my arm? This is allowed? - Yes. I'll hold his arm right here.
- I'll block him here. - The angle should look like this.
- Then how can I fly my plane? - I'll cover here.
If everyone blocks me, how can I fly mine?
- But this is necessary. - Keep the right angle.
- Just use your wrist. - How can I fly it like this?
I made mine with aluminum foil.
- But this is... - You can do this. Try it.
- I'll hold Kwang Soo's body. - Your feet can't go over here.
- Wait. Let me try it without you. - Sure, sure.
- If it's off, you can adjust it. - Okay, okay. That sounds fair.
- Yours can fly only once. - If you don't think it's fair.
- Your plane can fly only once. - It will break.
I think you'll have to throw it out right away.
(If his fruit plane flies...)
(and passes Sang Yeob's plane, he won't get a badge.)
(It's his practice round. What's the result?)
I think you'll have to throw it out right away.
(If his fruit plane flies...)
(and passes Sang Yeob's plane, he won't get a badge.)
(It's his practice round. What's the result?)
- Hey. Hey. - See? Look at that.
(It's almost throwing the tangerine.)
- I can't throw it like this? - What was that?
- This isn't allowed? - You threw the plane.
- This is unacceptable. - If you do that...
- No. No! - This is unacceptable.
(Slipping)
(As he slips, he falls on the fruit plane.)
- No! - I slipped on it.
My plane!
- Hey, I slipped on the banana peel. - No, no.
- My plane. - It was the banana peel.
- I'm sorry. - You have to fly yours now.
- I slipped on the banana peel. - This is annoying.
- Okay, okay. Hold on. - Poor Kwang Soo.
- I'll do it. - Hold him.
- He'll throw it. It'll go far. - I didn't do it on purpose.
- It'll fly better. It's flat. - I'm still going to do it.
- It will fly better. - Get ready.
Start.
(To be fair, everyone holds his arm as he uses his wrist to fly it.)
(Will the flattened plane fly well with just a snap of his wrist?)
(Falling)
(It plummets straight down to where his feet are.)
- He's in last place. - It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gets 3. Jae Seok gets 2. And Seok Jin gets 1.)
- There's nothing you can do. - It didn't cross the line.
Why did you buy the fruits?
(Kwang Soo has 6 badges, Jae Seok, 3, Seok Jin, 2, and Da Hee, 2.)
(They finally arrive at Zermatt Station.)
- We're here. - This is making my heart race.
- My heart is racing fast. - A meeting point.
(It's a mountain village which is located at 1,620m altitude.)
(It's the Mecca of winter sports near Switzerland-Italy border.)
Everyone, you have arrived at the cleanest village in Switzerland,
Zermatt, where Matterhorn is enclosed.
(Welcome to the clean village, Zermatt.)
- The air is so fresh. - This feels different.
- It's different. - It's different indeed.
- There's no fine dust. - It's the definition of nature.
I'll tell you the first stop on the itinerary of the Luxury Package.
For the 1st stop of your itinerary, you'll enjoy it at 3,100m altitude.
- It's the observatory. - An observatory?
The fondue and the hotel are part of the itinerary.
(No need to calculate the fee.)
Fondue.
(On top of an authentic Swiss fondue meal with the scenery at 3,100m,)
(they'll stay at the hotel, closest to the sky on a starlit night.)
(This is awesome.)
- And as for the added activities, - This is amazing.
we'll calculate the fees for the mountain railway...
and the extra food after your meal.
One of the staff members will be wearing the ballot box.
We'll head out to ride the mountain railway train.
- Okay! - Okay.
I'm so relieved to be in Switzerland, not the UK.
- I agree. - I'm so happy.
The UK... Gosh.
- Look to the left. - My gosh.
(Is this scenery real?)
It doesn't look real. It doesn't. I can't believe this.
Everything looks like computer graphics.
- Gosh, look. - That's it. That's it.
- That's it. - Matterhorn.
- We'll see without the clouds. - Everyone, look at this.
- Gosh, this is out of this world. - That's Matterhorn?
- If the clouds moved only a bit. - Hey, after seeing that, I bet...
- there must be a spot for photos. - Hey, do you want to see this?
Seriously. This is amazing.
It's a shame to admire it with only my eyes.
To admire it with your eyes, your eyes are too small.
(To admire it with your eyes, your eyes are too small.)
- Open your eyes wider. - No.
But once it's in my eyes, it can't get out. It can't get out.
- Look at the peak there. - It can't escape.
- Someone's paragliding on the left. - Where? Where?
- Look on your left. - My gosh, that person is flying.
(You can paraglide while admiring the view of the Matterhorn.)
(They can't help but sing a song.)
Why are you singing about the ocean when we're at a mountain?
(You're dazzling)
(My body has the tingling sensation)
I thought that this kind of vibe reminded me of something.
- I just remembered. - What is it?
- It feels like "Flaming Youth". - Right?
(The Youth are excited in Switzerland.)
- I was going to mention that. - "Flaming Youth".
It feels like we're sitting around in the old house.
(You must've felt excited just like me.)
I see the snow. But we have...
- the windows open. - Are you reminded of someone?
(Does the beautiful snow remind you of someone?)
- Someone you want to bring here. - 1, 2, 3.
- Me? I do have someone in mind. - Who is it?
(Who is the lady he wants to bring to this romantic snowfield?)
(Anticipating)
I should bring my mother here.
(Come on. Your mother?)
(Jong Kook is a dutiful son. This is why he can't get married.)
Everyone, you're going to get off at Gornergrat Station...
- which is situated at 3,100m. - Okay.
- I'm so glad to be here. - I agree. I'm so glad.
Let's get off.
- This is so beautiful. - This is Switzerland.
(My goodness, this is Switzerland.)
What a beauty.
- Seriously. This is magnificent. - Gosh.
Hey, let's take a photo. 1, 2, 3.
("Flying on Matterhorn")
- 1 more time. - 1, 2, 3.
(We're on cloud nine since we're Team Luxury.)
This is incredible.
Running Man is...
- suitable for viewers over 12. - Suitable for viewers over 12.
(They film the TV rating notice.)
(Team UK, head over here while you wing walk!)
- I got hungry so quickly. - Me too.
It's so interesting. I keep eating, but I'm still hungry.
Everyone, the first stop on your itinerary is...
the observatory package at 3,100m altitude.
We'll provide the fondue and the hotel as part of your itinerary.
We'll calculate the fees for the mountain railway train...
- and the additional food you added. - Yes, we'll do that.
Even if you're paying for the food, you can't eat it right away.
You can only eat the food if you complete your given mission.
- We have a mission. - It's different from what I heard.
(There is a mission.)
I'll tell you the mission that will earn you additional food.
In Switzerland, the people play a game called, "Zwanzgerle".
You must throw coins and stick them into boiled eggs.
You have to stick it in the shell?
You have to stick it in.
One of you will throw a coin into the boiled egg on the team's behalf.
If you succeed on your first try,
- we'll provide you with every dish. - Then Jong Kook should do this.
But someone might be better at throwing than me.
Se Chan might excel at throwing.
If you fail, you can take one dish off the menu and try again.
Can we practice?
- Shouldn't we practice once? - Once?
- You can practice once each. - We don't know how it's like.
Like this?
(The coin has to stick in the egg.)
(Throwing)
I'm sorry.
(He throws the coin at Ji Hyo.)
- Do you have a grudge against me? - No, I don't. I'm sorry.
This is difficult.
(Se Chan's coin hits the egg but doesn't penetrate it.)
It's so thick, Jong Kook.
Let me see. I'll give it a try.
(I'll give it a try.)
- It doesn't stick. - Jong Kook.
- It keeps breaking. - It keeps on falling apart.
(He's never done this before. Can he do it?)
(The coin disappeared.)
It went in.
(The coin has to stick to the egg, but it's stuck in the middle.)
It's so deep.
I mean, you can't see the coin.
- Goodness. - Look closely.
(Watch this miracle.)
(It's like the coin came from the egg.)
Jong Kook did it. We'll start.
It's stuck in here.
We won't practice.
Start.
- His power is no joke. - Take this.
I shouldn't feel pressured.
- You can do it. Focus. - Good luck.
Let's see.
(If he succeeds, the entire menu is free.)
(He succeeded during the practice. Can he do it now too?)
He did it.
(He makes no mistakes.)
- All right. - There's no other way.
I stayed still, and the coin got stuck.
- Jong Kook. - There's no other way.
- Can we check? - What is he supposed to do?
What now?
- How are you going to take this? - There's no time. Please eat.
Eat what you ordered.
Thank you for the meal.
- This is the Luxury Package. - Oh, my.
They look so good.
Look at this.
(The dried beef contains the romance of the highlands of Switzerland.)
- This is so good. - The lamb is so good.
All right.
Fondue is here.
The fondue is boiling.
Do we dip this?
You went in really deep. Good job.
- This is so good. - The lamb is so good.
Cheese.
- Cheese. - Do you want to do cheese cheers?
- Cheese cheers. - Cheese cheers.
- Love shot. - This reminds me of Seok Jin.
Try the lamb.
(They taste the fondue through a love shot.)
- This is so good. - The lamb is so good.
The lamb is great.
Try it.
(Jong Kook gobbles down the food.)
You dip this...
- and lift it up. - This is such a luxury.
(They're happy to be in the Luxury Package.)
I have to use the restroom.
I'm full.
(Is Se Chan excusing himself from the table?)
(It looks like he's going inside to look for a restroom.)
(Is nobody here?)
(If your name is in the ballot box,)
(your name gets added to the roulette.)
(If you get picked on the roulette, you must pay the additional cost.)
(You can pay, Han Na.)
(If only he votes, there's a good chance Han Na will get selected.)
(But there's no way that's the case.)
(Haha is writing somebody's name down too.)
Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes, it was so good. - It was great.
- It was so good. - Look at your cap.
The additional expense for this trip...
Right.
It totals to 523 dollars.
(It includes the mountain railway and their meal.)
As you see, the ballot box is full.
(We're family.)
I wonder who it is.
(It wasn't just me.)
(If you get selected, your name gets written down.)
- Here are the voting results. - Okay.
First.
It's on paper.
- Han Na. - Okay. Write it.
- Haha. - What?
Your pupils.
- Why? - It wasn't me. Write her name down.
- They moved six times. - No, it wasn't me.
Next.
Who is it?
It's on an egg. Han Na.
Really?
- You two are mean. - It wasn't us. What are you saying?
It has to be you two.
Next.
Who is it?
(Is there more?)
It's on a chocolate wrapper.
Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan)
- Se Chan. - Oh, dear.
What did I do?
Okay.
Hold on. I'll wait.
Really, you guys?
I'll vote.
(Se Chan wrote Han Na's name, and she wrote his.)
Next is on a leaf.
- Here. - When did they do that?
(It's on a leaf.)
Se Chan.
(Se Chan's name is on the leaf.)
(He has 2 votes.)
I wonder who they are.
Next...
- is Se Chan. - What?
What? Wait.
1, 2, 3. Jong Kook wrote my name too.
(With 3 votes, Se Chan leads the poll.)
(Ji Hyo listened to Han Na and voted for Se Chan.)
(Jin Young took a leaf...)
(and voted for Se Chan too.)
(You can pay, Se Chan.)
- Who has the most votes? - Can I spin the roulette?
- Se Chan. - Sure.
- I won't feel as bad. - Hold on.
You never know.
(Se Chan gets 4 spaces, Han Na gets 3, and Haha gets 2.)
(People who didn't get voted take 1 space each.)
Han Na and I are almost equal, right?
(Se Chan spins the fateful roulette that will cost 523 dollars.)
- I'll go. - You never know.
(Han Na with three spaces?)
(Se Chan with four spaces? Or Haha with two spaces?)
It's Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
(He only had one space, but he gets picked.)
That was awesome.
I had a feeling you would pay.
(Why me?)
Jong Kook, please write down 523 dollars in your bankbook.
You got so lucky, Se Chan.
- 500... - He's a lucky guy.
- 20... - We used so much of his money.
- Three. - Let's use his money.
(He gets unlucky and has to pay 523 dollars.)
The hotel feels...
so stable. It feels like a family home.
- It feels like a family home. - I'm not sure.
Look at my hair. It's flat.
What's wrong with your hair?
Did you draw that on with a marker?
I didn't wash my hair for 24 hours.
- Mine's flat too. - My hair is itchy.
- Look at his too. - What's this?
He took it off, and it smells like lamb.
(Seok Jin smells like lamb.)
- Stop lying. - I'm serious.
- You can't smell it. - You smell like lamb.
- I can tell. - Let me see.
- Stop lying. I don't smell. - Really?
- Oh, gosh. - I'm serious.
(He can smell lamb.)
Stop lying.
His face turned red.
- His face turned red. - Smell it.
- Smell it. - Don't do it.
Take your caps off and smell yourselves.
- I don't smell. - I don't think...
(Sniffing)
- I don't smell at all. - She kept on scratching her head.
That's my habit.
- I don't smell. - That's your habit?
- Smell her. - Try it, Kwang Soo.
- I don't smell. - I'll be honest.
Okay. I don't smell.
(He's shocked.)
It's because I just scratched.
I don't smell, Jae Seok.
- That's not possible. - Jae Seok.
- People smell. - I really don't.
- I usually don't smell. - Why do we have to do this?
I don't want to smell it anymore.
You're too aggressive, so I don't want to.
Try here.
Da Hee, I'm serious. It kind of smelled like poop.
What?
I'll be objective.
- Don't try to fool around. - I won't lie.
- Be serious. - Okay.
(Goodness)
(What is this smell?)
I was serious.
Da Hee, why do you think you don't smell?
I wasn't joking.
I don't smell.
- People smell. - Da Hee.
- People smell. - Why do you think you don't?
My skin smells good...
- like a baby's. - No.
Why would you smell like a baby? You're 35.
Why do you think you're a baby?
- Take your caps off. - Why?
Let's be natural. Don't try to be fake on TV.
Is this natural?
- Is this natural? - Don't touch your hair.
- Don't touch your hair, So Min. - I can't tell.
- Don't touch your hair. - Do I smell?
My hair usually doesn't smell.
Oh, my gosh.
- I don't smell. - What do you mean?
You can't smell yourself.
You don't know because it's yourself.
Jae Seok is touching his hair.
(Did you see him?)
- I saw him. - You saw him, right?
- I had a gap, so I put it together. - Hey.
You know how handsome men touch their hair after showering?
(That's what it looked like.)
(He was full of confidence.)
That's what he did.
(He's confident for nothing.)
Goodness.
(He saw that.)
- It's late now. - Right.
You have to go to bed for wing walking tomorrow.
(It's 11:30pm right now.)
(Who will be the 3 people to wing walk?)
This mission will be for 30 minutes.
Here's the third mission before going to bed.
It's called Your Silence.
(The third mission is Your Silence.)
You have to stay in the same room and be silent for 30 minutes.
(You can't make a sound for 30 minutes.)
Whenever you make a sound, you receive a penalty.
At the end of 30 minutes, 3 people with the most penalties...
will get the badges.
(3 people will get the wing walking badges.)
We just don't make a sound, right?
- I'm sure they'll try to interfere. - We'll start...
now.
(30 minutes of silence starts now.)
(Let's put our caps back on.)
(All right.)
(Slapping)
(Seok Jin attacks with his cap.)
(Okay.)
(Pushing)
(Jae Seok starts pinching Seok Jin's thigh.)
(He makes a sound.)
Seok Jin is out.
(We'll see once I get back.)
(This is why it's difficult.)
(Seok Jin gets directed to the penalty room.)
What is the penalty?
(What is the penalty?)
(Everybody is still quiet.)
(I'm going to the restroom.)
(Stepping)
(He steps on Kwang Soo's foot.)
(Kwang Soo just made a sound.)
Kwang Soo is out.
(Me?)
(She's about to laugh.)
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
(Me? Fine.)
(You scared me.)
(I already have 6.)
(Okay.)
(Kwang Soo goes to the penalty room as well.)
(Should I try something on him?)
(She tickles him.)
(Laughing)
Jae Seok is out. Da Hee is out.
- What? - She laughed.
I thought it was just three people.
(She didn't understand the rules.)
(She thought only 3 people would get penalties.)
You just spoke.
- What's going on? - It goes on for 30 minutes.
(You need to be silent for 30 minutes.)
Wasn't it just for three people?
(Da Hee and Jae Seok leave.)
What is this?
(We did well.)
(What?)
(We did really good.)
(He cracks up.)
(Here he is.)
(He's back.)
(It's a landmine of laughter.)
(Sang Yeob gets the penalty.)
(They both laugh.)
(As a penalty, you get funny face paintings.)
That one's bad.
(She tries to hold it.)
(I think I just saw something terrible.)
(I have to take a picture of this.)
(So Min is having fun.)
(Go away.)
(Laughing)
(Do I look that funny?)
(Look at this.)
(This is the class of laughter mine.)
(Kwang Soo is back too.)
(He looks silly.)
(Look at this, Kwang Soo.)
(What is it?)
(Laughing)
(It's Seok Jin Attack.)
(As soon as you see the picture, it makes you laugh.)
(Kwang Soo gets the penalty as soon as he comes back.)
(Goodness)
(I can't stop laughing at it.)
(How is it? Show me.)
(She makes a sound.)
(She tries to hold it in.)
(Exploding)
(It's Seok Jin Attack round 2.)
Look at this.
I have to show it to everybody.
What do I do?
(Do I look that funny?)
Go.
(So Min gets the penalty as well from Seok Jin Attack.)
(He's left alone.)
(He's here.)
(Jae Seok has a pointy nose.)
(That one's intense.)
(I went inside, and they made my nose pointy.)
(I have to take a picture of this.)
(He can't help but turn on his camera.)
(He looks haughty.)
(They have the best looks on Running Man.)
(If somebody comes in, let's attack them with the picture.)
(Da Hee is back as well.)
(She's a man with red cheeks.)
(I won't laugh this time.)
(Is Da Hee back?)
(Jae Seok, our picture looks too funny.)
(I can hold it in.)
(She makes a sound.)
(She can't.)
(I have to hold it in.)
- Da Hee is out. - You're out.
What?
What's this? What's wrong with Jae Seok?
- Da Hee is back. - Oh, gosh.
Why? What did you see?
(She laughs too easily. It's almost automatic.)
- I can't do this. - You're sweating.
I can't do this.
I'll make them laugh.
(She paints her own face.)
I have to make them laugh.
I have to send them away.
(Seok Jin is making the staff laugh.)
(It's a double laughter mine.)
(How is it? It's good, right?)
(Let's make the others laugh with this.)
(This is their new target.)
(It's the silly man with a unibrow.)
(Kwang Soo,)
(look at this.)
(He attacks with a silly dance.)
(He barely survives.)
(Do you want to see this then?)
(This is the stronger 2nd attack.)
(Trembling)
(He's about to explode.)
(The picture is right in front of him.)
(He tries not to look.)
(He manages to control himself.)
(He's good.)
(That was close.)
(What is wrong with you two?)
(He controlled himself,)
(but So Min is here.)
(She's Hong Doo Kkae's wife.)
(He bursts out laughing.)
(He laughs out loud.)
(Jae Seok gets the penalty again.)
(He cracks up.)
(Laughter is contagious.)
(She thinks he looks funny too.)
So Min is out.
I have to show him the picture. There's a funny one.
Was this necessary?
I can't laugh. I can't.
(Jae Seok and So Min both enter the penalty room.)
(We survived.)
(Let's be good. I have 2 badges.)
(I have 6.)
(She leaves the penalty room again.)
(Sighing)
(She wasn't able to...)
(hold in her laughter so far.)
(I'm going to control myself and overcome it this time.)
(She's determined.)
(Giggling)
(It's automatic again.)
(Hold it in. I can do it.)
(Da Hee, do you want to see this?)
(This is a challenge for her.)
(This is her biggest crisis.)
(She makes a sound.)
(She laughs again.)
(She's about to cry.)
I can't do this.
(This picture is very effective.)
(A cute, drunk man...)
(and Hong Doo Kkae's wife with glasses are here.)
(Let's take a selfie.)
(Say cheese.)
(They attack each other...)
(and try to...)
(hold their laughter in.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E406 Running Man
"Switzerland and the UK"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(I can't.)
(What's that?)
(He got plastic surgeries on his nose and eyes.)
(It's a laughter attack.)
(This is the worst crisis for them since the start of the mission.)
(He's happy and proud.)
(Calm yourselves. Let's take a selfie.)
(Thanks to calm Sang Yeob, they take a selfie.)
(They pose like models.)
(We're wing walking tomorrow.)
(Look here, Jae Seok.)
(What are we doing?)
(They're trying to take a group photo.)
(Giggling)
(That was an unexpected attack.)
Why are you standing next to me? Why were you there?
(Why were you standing there?)
(He's happy.)
(Peeking)
(Giggling)
(He cracks up.)
Kwang Soo is out.
(Go, Kwang Soo.)
(I'm going to pretend like I can't see anything.)
Take him away.
Go. This is not fair.
(His face is not fair.)
He has to erase that and start all over again.
(The storm passes by.)
(He checks his handsome face.)
(Let's give Jae Seok another penalty.)
(She removes the tape.)
(That was unexpected.)
(Groaning)
That was good.
(Was it that painful?)
(Jae Seok gets another penalty.)
Hey.
You almost ripped my nose out.
I can't believe her.
(The handsome man who lost his nose goes to the penalty room again.)
(Meanwhile, in the penalty room)
(Kwang Soo finishes receiving a nose job as well.)
(Kwang Soo's nose is taped like Jae Seok's.)
(So Min finds her new target.)
(Why don't you sit down for a second?)
(Why?)
(Shouting)
(They succeed in removing his nose bridge.)
(Kwang Soo ends up making a noise as soon as he comes back.)
(They can't believe they did it again.)
(I want to stop going to the penalty room.)
(When the atmosphere is calm,)
(the one who can't stop laughing comes in.)
(I refuse to laugh this time.)
(Let's go make her laugh.)
(So Min attacks with a picture.)
(She suddenly collapses.)
(Da Hee trips over a bag because her eyes are shut.)
(Da Hee, take a look.)
(They surround her.)
(Peeking)
(Laughing)
(It has begun.)
My goodness.
Hey, I am out of ideas now.
Hey.
She is out.
(Peek-a-boo)
(What do you think of my trash can hat?)
(Laughing)
(That's a nice reaction.)
I don't know what to do. I won't do this. I won't do this.
Gosh, I hate So Min.
The game has ended.
- Okay. - The game has ended.
It's over.
(Your Silence finally ends.)
- I barely suppressed my laughter. - The game has ended.
That was incredible.
(Why aren't they coming out?)
(The avatar version of Kwang Soo counterattacks.)
I have to take a picture. I have to take a picture.
This is incredible.
- You are too late. It's over. - Is it over?
(What are you saying?)
- Why is it over? - It's over.
Why is it over?
- It's over. - It's not over.
- No. - Is it over?
- Is it really over? - It's over. Look over here.
- Look over here. - Let's take a picture together.
Let's take a picture together.
- Is it over? - It's over.
Is it over?
(The handsome man also finds out that the game is over.)
Why did it end so soon?
(Disappointed)
I mean...
- You look scary. - Look at this.
(My makeup is funny.)
(Is it over?)
This is too much.
- I will announce the results. - I went in two times.
- Da Hee... - She went in five times.
- She went in a lot. - She has many badges now.
We don't know how this will end.
Kwang Soo went in four times.
(Kwang Soo gets 2 badges.)
Even if I get many badges, there is no hope for you.
I can't tell how you are feeling.
- I am making an angry face. - Let me see your face.
- You don't look angry. - I am angry.
He's in a good mood.
- I think he is in a good mood. - Am I second to last?
Can't you hold in your laughter?
You are worse. You went away the most often.
(She's an automatic laughing machine.)
You really can't hold in your laughter.
This is too much.
Even a little snort...
was counted as a sound.
I once got dragged away because I farted.
- He deserved it. - I once got dragged away...
- because my stomach grumbled. - Her stomach grumbled.
(So this is Running Man.)
The person who will receive one badge...
for going to the penalty room three times is Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok gets 1 badge.)
- My goodness. - This is ridiculous.
I don't know why we are doing this in the UK.
- I am in tears. - I didn't know I would do this.
I laughed so much today.
Kwang Soo, are you angry right now?
- Right now? - I can't tell his current mood.
I am smiling right now.
(I guess you can't see it.)
(Unlike his angry expression,)
(you can see his teeth.)
How are you feeling? Are you in a good mood?
- This is hilarious. - What do you think?
- Put yourself in my shoes. - Your expression is...
Nothing good happened today. Why would I be in a good mood?
I ended up with eight badges and blue paint on my face.
I can't believe you.
Look at you.
(I know you had a hard day.)
(Ripping)
(He removes Jae Seok's nose bridge.)
My nose is gone. My nose is gone, right?
My nose is gone, right? Is it bleeding?
My nose is gone. I felt it.
- Isn't that your nose? - My nose is gone.
- My goodness. - My nose is gone.
My nose got ripped off. Look at the tape.
Are you smiling?
- I am smiling. - I think he is smiling.
I am smiling.
Now, Round Three came to an end.
Tomorrow morning, we will have Round Four.
Would that be necessary? It's over for Kwang Soo.
(It's over for Kwang Soo.)
- No one can beat him. - Tell Kwang Soo to rest tomorrow.
- He has so many badges. - How many badges do you have?
- How many badges do you have? - Eight.
(Kwang Soo is at the very bottom after getting 8 badges in 1 day.)
- Stay cool-headed. - He's really unlucky.
If we don't wrap up soon, Kwang Soo's skin will be blue...
- even after he washes his face. - You're right.
His face is really blue.
This paint might not come off.
I want to laugh, but I can't.
The paint hardened. It really did.
Let's wrap up quickly for Kwang Soo.
Please go to your rooms and rest.
(The 3 people who will wing walk will be revealed next week.)
(It's time for skiing.)
(Let's go and ski.)
(They dreamed of skiing on the Alps.)
(However)
(What is going on?)
(It will be over if we get hit by lightning.)
(The luxurious trip encounters an unexpected hardship.)
(An emergency meeting is held.)
(What will become of Team Luxury?)
(They can't run away.)
(They can't avoid it.)
(The last mission to choose 3 people)
(Finally)
(The worst penalty in the history of variety programs shows itself.)
(The unfortunate member climbs onto the wing.)
(The penalty shocks everyone.)
(Who will be the 3 people to climb onto the wing?)
(The Unfinished War)