- Don't do that. It's the new year. - Hello.
- Hello. Happy New Year. - Hi.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
- His outfits are improving. - He's all dressed up.
Gosh, no, no. Stop it. You're making me blush.
(Come on. Don't make me blush now.)
- This is embarrassing. - Doesn't he...
- look great? - It's hot in here.
(Jae Seok shows up next.)
- What's going on? - Jae Seok.
- A shearling jacket. - I wore a shearling jacket.
- Happy New Year! - Happy New Year!
You look like pickled radish!
Pickled radish!
- Pickled radish! - I don't look like pickled radish.
You do. You look like you jumped out of gimbap.
You called me Jaws Bar at Entertainment Awards.
Now, you call me pickled radish.
For goodness' sake.
(She goes from Jaws Bar to pickled radish.)
- Se Chan dressed up today. - No, I didn't.
- Stop it, So Min. - Look at his ankles.
My goodness.
Se Chan, your ankles will ache when you get old.
- You will get arthritis. - It's okay.
Your ankles will ache.
I am only 33 years old.
You deserve a beating.
I am 38 years old now. It's a disaster.
- Are you 38 years old? - Yes.
You are pushing 40!
(You are pushing 40!)
(Song Ji Hyo, a woman who is pushing 40)
Ji Hyo.
(They exchange blessings to start the year.)
You are pushing 40.
- No one will think she is 38. - Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year! - Happy New Year!
What are you doing?
Every day is a festival.
- Happy New Year! - Jae Seok.
- Why did you take off the jacket? - What happened?
- Hurry up, and bring the jacket. - I was startled...
- when I looked in the mirror. - Why?
The shoulders were too much.
(The earlier outfit was too much.)
I wanted to talk about it during the opening! Why did you change?
(5 minutes ago, Jae Seok entered for the 1st time)
(Power shoulders)
(He looked like he just played a game of rugby.)
Don't say anything before the opening.
He figured it out on his own.
- Really? - He had an instinct.
So Min was forced to look like a high school student.
A flashback. A flashback.
A flashback.
In dramas, main characters are sometimes forced...
to look like high school students.
- That's right. - She is trying to look young.
- A flashback. - She went too far back in the past.
- That's right. - That's the impression I got.
It makes it impossible for you to enjoy the drama.
I thought her hair was dried herring.
(Is this hair or herring?)
Seriously.
- Why did you wear Hyun Woo's coat? - I didn't.
(Hyun Woo is his son.)
It's not his.
He wants to look cute.
- Isn't it Hyun Woo's? - It's his wife's.
- Is it your wife's? - No, it's not.
The winner of Top Excellence Award wants to look cute.
I asked my stylist to bring clothes that will make me look young...
- and this happened. - In any case,
Seok Jin won Top Excellence Award.
Congratulations.
(We congratulate Seok Jin on winning Top Excellence Award.)
Running Man, Jee Seok Jin.
(Last year, "Entertainment Awards")
(Seok Jin did it!)
It is thanks to you...
that I am where I am.
I will run to the best of my abilities. Thank you.
(I will run to the best of my abilities.)
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- His diligence and effort paid off. - You're right.
It's all thanks to the dear members.
There is no use in saying much as this won't air until later.
You want to say "These jerks" instead, right?
(You want to say "These jerks" instead, right?)
"These jerks".
(What's the story behind "These jerks"?)
Thank you.
Seok Jin and I...
left the get-together early after "Entertainment Awards".
(At a get-together after "Entertainment Awards",)
(Seok Jin picked up the tab and left.)
How much is the total?
(He looked very manly.)
- It's not very expensive. - Thank you for the food.
Seok Jin and I left early because we had work the next day.
As he exited the restaurant, he said,
"I can't believe these jerks."
(I can't believe these jerks.)
(Did you really say that?)
Really?
The total...
was quite expensive.
You know,
I had never seen people order takeout...
at a barbecue restaurant.
(He reveals how he truly felt.)
You told us to do that.
Did you see Jae Seok?
- He took a lot of pork belly. - 12 servings.
(He took a lot of pork belly.)
(He really ordered meat to go.)
12 servings.
(12 servings of pork belly)
(He ordered an entire pig to go.)
You told me to order meat to go.
In any case,
it's a happy occasion.
So Min won the Rookie Award.
(She won the Rookie Award.)
Kwang Soo and So Min won the Best Couple Award.
- The Best Couple Award. - Yes.
Running Man, Jeon So Min. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
(She received the honor of winning the Rookie Award.)
My goodness. I am sorry.
- I mean... - It's okay.
I love you. Thank you.
Lee Kwang Soo and Jeon So Min couple.
(Kwang Soo and So Min won the Best Couple Award.)
He is a mature man.
Aren't you glad I said that?
We are a bit more than colleagues.
So Min won three awards.
- You are right. - So Min won three awards.
I shamelessly made Seok Jin pick up the tab.
- It's okay. - On that day,
I thought Jae Seok would help me.
Jae Seok suddenly stood up and said,
"Is Seok Jin the only one who received an award?"
Then everyone said,
- "Jeon So Min! Jeon So Min!" - That's right.
"However,"
"who won the Top Excellence Award?"
- "Jee Seok Jin! Jee Seok Jin!" - "Jee Seok Jin! Jee Seok Jin!"
(The answer is obvious.)
(Jee Seok Jin! Jee Seok Jin!)
You can order takeout today!
- Jee Seok Jin! Jee Seok Jin! - Jee Seok Jin! Jee Seok Jin!
Seok Jin thinks we are joking.
(I can't believe these jerks.)
That night, I talked in my sleep.
"Jee Seok Jin! Jee Seok Jin!"
- My voice went hoarse. - Mine did, too.
The person who got drunk the most...
was Park Na Rae.
(The person who got drunk the most was Park Na Rae.)
(Drunk Park Na Rae)
Why was she there?
(Park Na Rae was invited to the get-together.)
(The owner of Na Rae Bar...)
(enjoyed the get-together to the fullest.)
She was completely drunk.
She had a get-together for an award she received the day before...
- with Running Man. - She's too much.
- Seriously. - She enjoyed herself.
She didn't drink at first. When I asked why she wasn't drinking,
she said, "It will be unbecoming if I get drunk here."
At the end, when I asked if she is okay,
she gave me the finger.
(Na Rae showed them the epitome of drunkenness.)
She was completely drunk.
I feel like Na Rae should visit the show.
- She should. - That's right.
Today,
we will welcome the New Year by renewing Running Man.
We will have a race to determine who will be in the TV rating notice.
- TV rating notice. - TV rating notice.
It is shown in the beginning of the show.
(This is TV rating notice.)
- It's shown every week. - Yes.
The winner of today's race...
will be the director of the TV rating notice...
and freely decide what to show in five seconds.
(The winner of the race can direct the 5-second TV rating notice.)
- Alone? - The new TV rating notice...
will be aired for a month.
- A month? - Yes.
Then you can be the main member.
- For an example, - I will try my best to win.
I can stand at the front and have the others in the back...
- if I am the director. - You will have free rein.
If I win, I will make Jae Seok wear that jacket.
(I'm going to make him wear that jacket.)
(Power shoulders)
- For goodness' sake. - We didn't get to make fun of him.
- He can do that, right? - If I say,
"Kwang Soo, stand naked," does he have to follow?
(If I say, "Kwang Soo, stand naked," does he have to follow?)
He can take off his top.
This show is for 12 years and older.
- 12 years and older. - What's wrong with you?
I can't stand naked and say,
"This show is for 12 years and older."
So Min, this show is for 12 years and older.
There's a rumor that our rating is changing because of you.
Running Man almost became a pay-per-view show because of you.
This show won't get aired...
with that kind of TV rating notice.
As a result, the winner will make a storyboard...
of the TV rating notice you want to see...
and give a presentation.
(What will the winner want to do?)
What should I do?
- Can we use the water bomb? - You can use anything.
- Can we film it anywhere? - Yes.
Let's go to Nevis Swing again.
(Let's go to Nevis Swing again.)
- I will film in Korea. - Don't do that.
As I say, "Running Man is for 12 years and older,"
the rest of you will be on Nevis Swing. Okay.
(Is that how you're going to be?)
My mind is set.
(Peeking)
- We will be at a zoo. - Look at his drawing!
We will be at a zoo.
(Is this Jae Seok's zoo?)
You are worse than Ji Ho, your son.
Ji Ho is can draw better than me.
- "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals". - I also have big plans.
Should So Min be...
a frog or a parrot?
Should So Min be a frog?
Make her upper body a frog's and her lower body a parrot's.
- What? - That would be scary.
- It's like a collaboration. - That would be scary.
Just you wait.
My goodness.
I am worried about what So Min will do.
What kind of an animal is Se Chan?
I am a bear, right?
(A cute bear?)
You aren't a bear.
- I am strong. - You are fish.
- You aren't a bear. - You are fish.
Catfish.
Catfish?
- I am not catfish! - Se Chan.
We don't have any fish.
A catfish suits you.
- A catfish is a good one. - Hold on.
Kwang Soo is a giraffe.
(Walking over)
Hold on. Let me take a look.
- Let me see how it looks. - Draw feelers.
(Which one is the real catfish?)
You are a catfish.
- It's a permanent marker. - It's a permanent marker.
- It's an oil-based marker. - It's a permanent marker.
(It's an oil-based marker.)
Do you want me to walk around like this all day?
I am sorry.
You look like a catfish.
- Jae Seok, do something. - I am sorry.
(Seok Jin gets up.)
I can't do anything about it.
(Rubbing)
You can't erase it with an eraser.
It's working.
(He gets a more realistic mustache.)
- Come on! - He became Woong's father.
It's Woong's father!
I guess there are things you can't erase with an eraser.
Are you acting this way because you won an award?
(Are you acting this way because you won an award?)
For goodness' sake.
Okay, so he's a catfish.
(It's funny, right?)
They will let us do this.
(They carefully make a storyboard for their 5 seconds.)
I can be a king.
Then I will do...
I will go to the fish market.
(My imagination will become real.)
This is...
like a dream. The thought of directing this scene...
- makes me so excited. - Seok Jin.
You won't be able to do it.
(You won't be able to do it.)
(The chance is slimmer than winning a lottery.)
Wait, and see.
That's why I am not curious about your idea.
There is a twist. It's five seconds.
(They can't wait to see whose idea will win.)
- Is the current one five seconds? - Yes.
- This isn't easy. - Seok Jin gets...
the most amount of screen time in the TV rating notice.
(He attacks with a fact.)
(Say that again, you jerk.)
Seriously.
- It's five seconds. - Excuse me?
5 seconds is long for him. He usually appears for 4 seconds.
- Se Chan, you're laughing too loud. - It's funny.
(Meanwhile, the high-schooler, So Min is...)
(letting her imagination run wild.)
So Min, what are you drawing?
I'm drawing an underwater scene.
But I can't come up with anything cruel.
Why would you come up with something cruel?
- What's with you? - Don't do that.
Or...
I'll make Jae Seok and Jong Kook kiss.
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook will kiss?)
Gosh.
This show is for the ages of 12 and over.
Please remember that.
(Disappointed)
My goodness.
Kwang Soo, why did you draw water bombs in the background?
You saw it right.
He doesn't realize he'll get hit with the water too.
(Are you talking about these water bombs?)
Fine, in my animal kingdom,
there will be a water bomb above just the giraffe.
I like that.
Okay. You're not wearing anything in my drawing.
- What? - Nothing under that green jacket.
I'll remove the water bomb.
All right. Then I'll give you clothes.
Okay. That sounds good.
(I like Kwang Soo's idea.)
Please present your ideas.
Mine is called...
Running Man's Sea Story.
"Running Man's Sea Story"?
(Running Man's Sea Story)
- Sea Story is dangerous. - It's the name of an adult game.
(Even the title is problematic.)
Why did she give it such a name?
- Everything she does... - Running Man Under the Sea.
Kwang Soo is seaweed.
(Kwang Soo is seaweed.)
Make me into a living creature.
- I want to be a living creature. - That's nice.
- I like that. - I want to be able to move.
He'll be standing on ice, wearing green tights.
Please make sure his underwear lines don't show.
- So Min. - He'll be painted green all over.
I would like you to make...
his outfit moist.
As you expected, Se Chan will be a catfish.
Please prepare some mud.
- He'll be lying in mud. - Mud?
- I hope she won't win. - Se Chan will...
be covered in mud.
I think Se Chan will look cute.
Wearing all that costume, we'll appear for 0.1 seconds.
As Ji Hyo is a girl...
Ji Hyo will be a red carp.
I want her costume to be covered with spangles.
Don't be just nice to Ji Hyo.
So Min!
Ji Hyo should look pretty.
She's happy she can wear spangles.
(She's happy.)
Spangles are nice.
Jong Kook will be a rock.
(Jong Kook will be a rock.)
(I'm a rock?)
Like Gollum...
Jong Kook doesn't expect much from you.
I want his costume to have a hole here.
Hey, we can't do that on a show for 12 and over.
- His chest and belly should show. - We can't show our skin.
- He'll be a rock. - Why...
Why do you decide how much skin I should show?
Like this.
Celebrities are sensitive about showing their skin.
Seok Jin will be sticking to Jong Kook's shoulder.
- Me? - Yes.
- He's a sea urchin. - Can you show all that?
- In five seconds? - We have only five seconds.
Everyone will appear at the same time.
Seok Jin will have to curl up.
His arms and legs should be inside the costume.
- I have to curl up? - Like this.
- I'm a sea urchin? - Yes, you have to curl up.
Make Seok Jin a part of a picture puzzle.
- Will there be a prize? - Haha will...
be an octopus spitting ink.
I was too nice.
- Mine is too nice too. - Give us five more minutes.
- Give us 5 more minutes. - Give us 10 more.
- No. - Mine is too nice.
Also, look at Jae Seok.
He's an anchovy.
(Jae Seok is an anchovy.)
- What are you talking about? - It suits him.
So Min is good at casting.
He looks like an anchovy.
His costume has to be very tight.
It has to be really tight, so he looks very thin.
I can't have the shape of an anchovy.
The anchovy will be very tiny.
(Tiny?)
Why do you keep making me tiny?
Hey!
(Last fall, in the sweet potato field)
(Jae Seok's is tiny.)
(Hey, say it properly.)
(His nickname became Small Jae Seok.)
Why do you make me tiny?
- Small Jae Seok. - Hey!
It's Small Jae Seok.
You did it in the chili pepper field too.
(He's angry.)
I mean...
Small Jae Seok.
- Hold on. - It was a sweet potato field.
- A chili pepper field? - What's with him?
- It wasn't a chili pepper field. - Did you just admit it?
- This is an inferiority complex. - No, it's not that.
(I'm sure of it.)
- No, I don't! - He feels inferior.
So Min...
Small Jae Seok. Gosh.
He's famous.
- He's famous? - Really?
Everyone in this field knows.
What?
(You are watching storyboards that are fit for those 12 and over.)
- Has the word spread? - Yes.
I'll walk by, saying, "Running Man is for 12 and over."
(I'll just walk by.)
What?
There's still two more seconds.
Then you'll just spit some ink.
(Octopus Haha will wrap it up.)
You can have two seconds to yourself.
How much ink will he have to spit?
Please write, "12",
with ink.
Why am I not unhappy?
That was creative.
He's happy he can appear for two seconds.
It wasn't bad.
(Someone is furious.)
So Min, you shouldn't be a frog.
That'd be too comfortable.
- This is not okay. - I shouldn't have gone first.
It wasn't a good idea.
(I shouldn't have gone first.)
You might not see it well.
Let me explain.
The title is, "There's a lot to Learn from Running Man".
(There's a lot to Learn from Running Man.)
I want to shoot it at Myeongjeong Hall in Changgyeong Palace.
- I know that place. - I want to shoot there.
I'll be the king,
and the others will carry my palanquin.
In the opening scene,
we'll show Seok Jin's trophy.
And Seok Jin will smash it.
(Seok Jin will smash his own trophy.)
- My trophy? - "I don't deserve this!"
(I don't deserve this!)
This is not mine!
- It's okay. - He even treated us to dinner.
- I like that. - And...
The servant who fans the king...
will be Jong Kook.
- He'll be shirtless. - Hold on.
(Jong Kook will be shirtless.)
- Why am I always shirtless? - This show is for 12 and over.
Jong Kook is shirtless in every scenario.
- You have no choice. - I can't.
Let's avoid going shirtless.
Haha, Seok Jin, and Kwang Soo...
will be horses.
- They'll pull the palanquin. - Goodness.
- I'm a horse? - Here comes the climax.
I'll whip the horses, saying, "Let's go watch Running Man."
The horses will say, "Running Man is for 12 and over."
That's it.
It's not bad, is it?
Who will be whipped?
Someone popular should be whipped.
You're right.
- So I chose Jae Seok. - Nice.
(As Jae Seok is popular, he'll be whipped.)
I like that.
Okay. That was nice.
(Will Se Chan's dream come true?)
Ji Hyo.
I think mine is the simplest and the most straightforward.
- What is it? - We'll be using our bodies.
(Use Your Bodies)
This looks simple, but these letters are made of humans.
- It's us. - Are they bodies?
(Those letters are us?)
Use a drone camera or something.
- 1, 2... - With our bodies?
- Yes, with our bodies. - Really?
- Wearing tights? - Yes.
Now that I think of it,
maybe our faces should be covered too.
(Our faces should be covered too.)
Then why does it have to be us?
We don't have to do it.
Hire some extras.
- Hire people. - No.
We'll show them...
how well we can work together even without...
- seeing each other's face. - It has a message.
What message?
- Does that make sense? - It can be fun.
Does that make sense?
- I don't want to do this. - This really is for 12 and over.
- Everything we do is a penalty. - This is not okay.
- This wasn't the intention. - Let's have one normal scenario.
It's not supposed to be like this.
I'm not going to make Jong Kook take off his shirt.
- That's right. - Everyone will be equal.
- Everyone will be equal. - Exactly. You're so nice.
(You're so nice.)
What is this? Are you guys together?
Is there something going on?
Why do you say she's nice?
She is nice.
(They've been suspicious since the fortune-telling.)
You're nice.
At the end, we'll all do our symbolic pose.
We'll do the running pose.
I'll say, "Running Man is for 12 and over."
I like it.
I like the idea. It has a message.
It's touching.
I hate that it'll be shot at a gym.
- It's "Healthy Running Man". - I like the title.
These are treadmills.
(Healthy Running Man)
You drew yourself so cute.
That's not how your hair looks.
(It's too cute.)
I'm cute.
It's simple. I'll be holding a 12 sign.
I'll say, "Running Man is for 12 and over," looking cute.
The rest will be running at full speed.
(The others will be running at full speed.)
We have to start again if we fall, right?
Yes.
(We can't do that.)
So Min will be holding 12kg dumbbells.
She'll hold it in each hand.
It's for ages 12 and over.
Members will dress up as Young Gu.
What are you talking about?
(Dressing up as Young Gu is necessary.)
What about Kwang Soo?
- He doesn't need to dress up. - I see.
- Why not? - You already look like him.
I'm going to dress up too.
- I'm jealous of you, Kwang Soo. - I'm going to dress up.
- I'm jealous of you. - I'm going to dress up.
It's simple. This is running backwards.
- Backwards? - Everyone's back is turned.
The faces aren't visible.
Why would we dress up as Young Gu?
There's no reason.
(There's no reason behind dressing up.)
Why would we do a makeup when we don't face the camera?
We'll dress up anyway.
That's terrible.
- We show the back of our heads. - This is upsetting.
I think I was too nice.
Why did your storyboard change?
- It keeps changing. - Mine is...
very simple, and there won't be any suffering.
It's called "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals".
You'll play animals.
(Yu Jae Seok and the Animals)
I stand in the front.
I stand in front of the camera.
Jong Kook will either dress up as a cat on a stove...
- Jong Kook? - That's cute.
Seok Jin dresses up as an impala with a trophy on his head.
(Seok Jin has a trophy on his head.)
- He's a unicorn. - A unicorn?
- Pardon? - It's a unicorn.
He's an impala who received the Top Excellence Award.
- That's good. - And...
So Min was a frog, but I changed it.
She'll be a parrot on a perch.
She'll be on an actual perch with a thin bar.
(It's a perch with a thin bar.)
- It won't be easy to balance. - It's impossible.
So Min has to keep her balance.
She has to hold the bar with her feet.
Can you do it?
You have to hold the bar...
with your feet like this.
So Min has to hold onto the perch like a bird.
(She must stand on the perch.)
She needs to practice.
Lastly, I'll come out.
When I shout, "Running Man," you express age 12.
- With our body? - Yes.
How?
It's like Ji Hyo's.
Did you just make that up?
No, I didn't.
You just made it up.
- Where is it written? - Come on.
- It was my original idea. - Stop applying others' ideas.
- I didn't. - Why would we do it?
- The animals will make 12. - How?
You have to come up with how.
We can't express 12.
How is it possible?
As a human being, I don't know. The animals...
- The animals... - You're the director.
How could you not know?
The animals will work together...
- How can animals make 12? - to show 12.
Just do it!
- How? - Just do it.
- All right. - How can we make 12?
I'll start up a fight.
(He'll start up a fight?)
What?
- What did you say? - I'll start up a fight.
You must show age 12.
Then I'll say, "Viewers of 12 years and older".
Take a look. Stop making things up.
That's all I have.
I changed the storyboard a little.
- Especially... - You changed a lot.
My idea was a beautiful birthday.
My title is "A Birthday in Seok Jin's World is Age 12".
(A Birthday in Seok Jin's World is Age 12)
- That's my title. - What is it?
It means age 12.
(It has no other meaning.)
- It's sensible. - It doesn't make sense.
What doesn't?
What about animals expressing age 12?
- It makes sense. - Nothing makes sense here.
What is "A Birthday in Seok Jin's World is Age 12"?
If you're 12 years old, you should dress up as one.
You should dress up as a child.
- Me? - According to your title...
- You're 12 years old. - I'm just me.
- No. - You're 12 years old.
You should put rouge on your cheeks and forehead.
Why would I? This is up to me.
(This is my storyboard.)
- It's because of the title. - You can't tell me what to do.
- Seok Jin, listen. - You can't change it.
The title is "A Birthday in Seok Jin's World is Age 12".
That means you're 12 years old.
- Okay, I'll accept that. - Okay.
(He acts cool.)
- I'll accept one idea. - That's right.
I'll accept one.
You'll need a lot of Botox.
- I'm swollen from laser treatment. - Botox.
(He's swollen from a laser treatment.)
- Next is... - What?
Did you get a laser treatment?
I said that he'll need a lot of Botox.
He responded, "I got a laser treatment."
(Seok Jin's response is "I got a laser treatment.")
I got a laser treatment.
- Goodness. - What is he talking about?
- Se Chan used to be a human being, - Human?
but he dresses up as Gollum.
(He changes Se Chan to Gollum.)
- Gollum? - He washes my feet.
Gollum is an old character. Not many people know about it.
It's too old.
That's what I want.
(This is my idea.)
Children of age 12 won't know.
I won't accept more than one suggestion.
- I only accept the makeup. - Okay.
Next, So Min...
used to be a dancer that the king adores.
- That's a good role. - However, I changed it.
- To what? - She'll be an actor.
- She's reborn. - What kind of actress?
(Seok Jin changed her role.)
As the Joker.
It's a role that I like.
She'll dress up as the Joker.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
The time setting is during Joseon Dynasty.
- The Joker shouldn't come out. - Of course.
It's not realistic.
The Joker comes out, and Rome comes out.
- Seok Jin. - Everything is included. It's okay.
Why are you nitpicking my idea?
- Kwang Soo. - Mine is very simple.
As you can see, my title is...
"2018 Start Afresh".
As you can see in the picture, water bombs are installed.
So Min wears Young Gu wig.
- Why? - Makeup is simple too.
- Jong Kook... - Why am I Young Gu?
wears a sleeveless shirt and tights. He's dressed.
Jae Seok wears no makeup except his green jacket.
(Jae Seok's costume is his green jacket.)
Bring that jacket. Joo Eun, you have to take it.
What's wrong?
- What about the jacket? - It was the funniest.
I don't believe this.
All members will get water bombed.
A clean-looking Kwang Soo appears.
Present the age ratings, and frame out.
All I say is "Viewers".
- Who says age 12? - That's done by...
- He added it. - each member.
(Each member says it.)
Members say each syllable, "Running Man is Age 12."
Seok Jin is in Daegu. Jae Seok is in Busan.
Jong Kook is in Gwangju. Haha is in Haenam.
He's lost his mind.
- Stop playing. - Goodness.
The members getting a water bomb...
won't be aired.
- What's the point... - After the water bomb...
- of water bomb when it isn't aired? - That's right.
- I think it'll be fun. - Seriously.
(There's no other reason.)
- That's cruel. - I'd feel satisfied.
What kind of idea is that?
They'll be on camera after the water bomb.
Viewers.
- My goodness. - I put everything together.
- Okay. - That's all I have.
My original idea was something cute.
My original idea was...
"Cute Running Man's Seafood Market".
- That's a good idea. - Everyone's costume was nice.
As we walk and chitchat,
I wanted to make it pretty.
You changed it.
The more I listened to you, the angrier I got.
I completely changed it.
This is in one frame. It's a TV screen.
(Running Man's Age Rating)
It's a PSA that viewers of Running Man must be over age 12.
It's a storyboard. The first scene is...
Seok Jin who is smoking an electronic cigarette.
- It's age 12 years or older. - Is that okay?
Right. It's a public advertisement.
Next is Jae Seok watching pornography.
- Come on. - Ji Hyo is cursing while drunk.
Next is Kwang Soo and So Min who are fighting.
Se Chan writes bad comments on Seok Jin and So Min.
Next is Jong Kook being a bully.
These scenes are shown for one second.
Will you cross them out?
Then I tear them all and jump out of the screen.
Then I say, "No, Running Man is for age 12 years or older."
That's it.
(Haha denounces the bad actions of adults.)
That's complete nonsense.
- It's simple. - It's nonsense.
If you look carefully,
water bombs are installed everywhere.
After being aired for 1 second, they get a water bomb for 0.5 second.
Then I come out of the screen.
- Come out of the screen, my foot. - I do.
Put ink inside Jae Seok's water bomb.
(Haha won't tolerate Jae Seok.)
There's also mud.
My goodness.
- There's also mud. - There's nothing good.
- It's hard to decide. - There's nothing good.
Will the idea that wins first place...
be aired for one month?
It'll be aired 8 times including Part 1 and 2.
- That's amazing. - I want to win first place today.
- Really? - I'm being serious.
Jae Seok can't win today...
- I want to win. - unless we want to suffer.
There are ones who shouldn't win.
I think Ji Hyo's is the worst. Our faces won't be shown.
- Ji Hyo's is easy. - How can we make 12?
It's not about being simple.
There's nothing wrong with Ji Hyo's.
(There's nothing wrong with hers.)
- Are you in a relationship? - Will you act as a couple?
What's going on?
There's not much to do for Ji Hyo's.
- All we do is dress up. - I wasn't going to say it.
I wasn't going to say it, but why are you together so often?
What do you mean?
You were together during the get-together.
- Are you in a relationship? - They're suspicious.
Will I lose all my money?
- Lose what? - I bet all of my money...
that they aren't in a relationship.
(Last Christmas, a romance began between Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
(Seok Jin bet all of his money that they aren't in a relationship.)
I want Seok Jin's money.
Someone wrote that he wants to see me penniless.
(I want to see Seok Jin penniless.)
- If you two are dating... - I'll add one more.
If they date...
Seok Jin will be penniless.
He wanted them to be in a relationship.
Seok Jin won't dress up as an impala.
I'll make him penniless instead.
(Seok Jin turns into a penniless man instead.)
Today's race to select the winner is called...
The mission to win the TV rating notice is War of R Ddakji.
(War of R Ddakji)
- "R Ddakiji"? - "R Ddakiji"?
Ddakji?
- I'm good at that game. - Why are we playing that?
The member with the most ddakjis will win the race...
and become the director of the clip.
- I have to win this. - Everyone will be...
given 20 ddakjis to start.
Depending on the success of your mission,
you may be given more or forced to hand in your ddakjis.
- Let me hand them out first. - Okay.
- Look at this. - Give this to Se Chan.
This is for Kwang Soo.
- There are names on them. - Our ddakjis are in here too.
Goodness, these are real ddakjis.
My gosh. These used to come with snacks.
- These are the ones. - These are nice.
- Goodness. - These are nice.
If there are any extras, can you give me some?
- These look amazing. - We wore a lot of costumes.
We did all sorts of things.
Seok Jin...
must not have done much.
(But it seems Seok Jin must not have done much.)
You used only three pictures for the rest of his ddakjis...
while other members have about five photos.
Exactly.
- I don't think I can get married. - Did you do that?
I can't get married now.
(This photo from last August will fend men off.)
Gosh, So Min.
Gosh, her photos are so funny.
(My goodness. Why did I do that?)
I see. This is how I look like. Goodness.
Haha has the oddest one among us.
- His ddakjis... - All of mine are weird.
This one. I really hate this one.
- This photo. Seriously. - Haha.
Haha, you look like a loser.
(Your face looks like a loser's.)
"A loser"?
(I respect his loser face.)
Haha.
Now, I'll tell you the rules.
The first mission is...
Battle of 12.
(The 1st mission is Battle of 12.)
You will make 4 teams of 2.
Each team will invite guests who are related to the number, 12.
When you win the given challenge,
you will obtain R Ddakjis.
There are four keywords for guests you must invite.
You will make a team with the member who chose the same keyword.
You will personally invite guests who fit the description.
The battle will 2 to 1.
The members who win the battle will earn 20 R Ddakjis.
We have to invite guests? We have to do that?
Before you begin your mission,
let us reveal the keywords related to the number 12.
- Should we all choose one? - Yes.
(2 members with the same keyword will make 1 team.)
(The partner they choose will play an important role today.)
Should I stay away from hardcore members like Kwang Soo?
- Is this the keyword? - Yes.
(The partner they choose will play an important role today.)
"A celebrity with a 12-year age gap"?
(Jae Seok and So Min are a team.)
"A celebrity who was born in December".
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook are a team.)
My gosh, mine is hard.
(A celebrity who lives in the area at the 12th bus stop)
"Celebrity whose debut was 12 years ago".
(Kwang Soo and Haha are a team.)
- It's going to be a long day. - Ji Hyo.
- Did you get the same one? - Goodness!
- We played a similar one before. - Yes, we did.
- Seriously. - He introduced a wrong person.
(Kwang Soo was exhausted then.)
(Haha supposedly gave him the number for Yu Seung Woo, the singer.)
(Haha gave him the number to "help" Kwang Soo last April.)
(Kwang Soo went to meet Seung Woo with a leery feeling of gratitude.)
(However, "Lee" Seung Woo showed up.)
(This was how the Tricky and Cunning Brotherhood was forged.)
- He gave me a wrong number. - I gave him a different Seung Woo.
(The brotherhood is reunited. He's already feeling tired.)
I had to shave on that day too.
Everyone, you will move to your designated vehicle for each team.
You can continue your discussion there.
All right.
(The mission for each team)
- So Min. - Yes, Jae Seok?
- I researched a while ago. - Yes?
A celebrity who is 12 years older than me is...
Lee Gyeong Gyu.
- I see. Lee Gyeong Gyu. - We have a 12-year age gap.
Or another celebrity is Chon Ho Jin who won the Grand Award.
(He won the Grand Award from KBS.)
I have never met him in person.
- Really? - I've never had the pleasure.
I only met him in passing.
But I was never properly introduced to him.
- I've never worked with him before. - I'd like to meet him too.
How old is 12 years older than your age?
It's 35 years old.
(It's 35 years old.)
- That's 12 years older than you? - Yes.
(But she was born in 1986.)
- 35 is 12 years older than you? - Yes.
Wait, no. It's 45 years old.
- Don't you think that's too much. - I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
Do you think you're in high school today?
People who are 12 years younger than you are...
- 35 years old. - That's right.
People who are 12 years older than me are 45.
What year were they born?
(Who are some celebrities that are 12 years older than So Min?)
This celebrity is 45 years old.
(That's right!)
- That celebrity? - Yes.
- Isn't that celebrity busy? - Hold on.
- Do you have the number? - That celebrity's phone number...
is the only one I know among celebrities we mentioned so far.
(Jae Seok has ties with this popular celebrity?)
(We are on our way to meet you now!)
First off, let's get moving.
We'll go to Gangnam Station first.
First off,
- we'll give you two stickers. - Okay.
What are the stickers for?
Put one of the stickers on your body,
and think about whether you want to put the other sticker...
- on the guest or not. - We can put it anywhere?
Yes, you can put anywhere on the guest's body.
I can think about this and put it on when I want to, correct?
Whoever puts the sticker on the guest within five minutes...
will get to team up with the guest.
After finding out the mission,
if you believe teaming up with each other is better,
you don't have to put the sticker on the guest.
So Min, think about this then.
It might be better if we don't put this on the guest.
You and I can partner up and win the game.
It's better to win 20 ddakjis.
But only first place matters.
(Winning them together doesn't do me any good.)
You have a point, but...
Then why don't you help me?
My plan is better than yours.
I think...
Well,
I really want to see you in the anchovy costume.
(I'm sorry. I really want to see you in the anchovy costume.)
Hey.
I also want to see you on the perch.
I want you to...
perch on that rod. Mark my words.
Small Jae Seok, Small Jae Seok.
(Her teasing is on repeat.)
My goodness, have you gone mad?
Seriously. This isn't a double entendre.
- I have never... - But you do mean that.
Anyway, stop trying to cause misunderstandings.
Then I will make you a whale.
Stop it!
Stop bringing that up.
This doesn't suit the program.
What are you talking about? You don't want to be an anchovy...
- Just stop talking. - or a whale. What do you want?
Just drop this.
Then what will you be in the sea?
I told you to stop.
This is exactly why you cannot win this mission.
Don't win today.
I'll win today. Unbelievable.
(Will her story come true?)
Well, I looked up celebrities...
born in December.
- There were so many. - Daniel was born in December.
(He was born on December 10.)
- Should I call Daniel? - I really like him.
I love him too.
- Psy was born in December too. - Psy?
-Hey, Kye Sang was born in December. - Yes?
- Kye Sang was born in December. - Hey!
- Yoon Kye Sang. - Let's meet him.
I watched "The Outlaws" like crazy.
He was born in December.
(The leading role in the hit move, "The Outlaws" last year)
(Yoon Kye Sang played the role of his lifetime, Jang Chen.)
Why don't you send him a text first?
- "Kye Sang, it's Seok Jin." - You want me to do it?
No, I don't want to do it.
I have never met him in person though.
- Seok Jin. - What?
You won the Top Excellence Award.
Regardless of my award,
- I can't do this. - Right now,
- you're the recipient of the award. - But still...
- I freeze in front of famous stars. - Seok Jin.
Come on. Give him a call. You said you'll do it.
- I'll give you the number. Come on. - Let's give it a shot.
He's not picking up.
He might not answer an unknown number.
- Hello? - Yes?
Is this Mr. Yoon Kye Sang?
(He's careful.)
- Yes, this is he. - Hey.
(Kye Sang answers the phone!)
He picked up.
- I'm sorry. - Kye Sang!
This is Jee Seok Jin from Running Man.
Oh, hello.
- I'm sorry to call you like this. - Kye Sang.
We called just in case, but you answered our call.
I'm sorry, Kye Sang. This is Jong Kook.
- Oh, hello. - Have you been well?
I'm sorry, Jang Chen.
What are you doing now?
I just finished working out.
- I see. - Now, I'm on my way home.
- Were you at the gym? - Yes.
Well, you know...
I feel so bad for asking you this.
We have to meet with a celebrity who was born in December.
- I see. - Yes, but...
Don't feel like you have to say yes.
It's probably not possible for us to meet...
with you since you're not ready now, right?
(Can we come meet you now?)
(Will their spur-of-the-moment meeting be accomplished?)
Right now, I'm naked though.
- You're naked? My apologies. - I see.
(He's naked since he has to take a shower after his workout.)
I'm so sorry, Kye Sang.
- I feel so bad. I'm really sorry. - So he is...
I'm sorry to ask you this, but...
can you say one of your famous lines?
(He has many famous lines that contributed to the film's success.)
(Which one will he say?)
I came here to collect my money. Why should I care about that?
(He sounds fierce.)
(Goodness! He perfectly reenacts the scene.)
I came here to collect my money. Why should I care about that?
(He's true to his nickname, Kye Sang, the almighty!)
- Kye Sang. - But...
Thank you so much for this.
Sorry to point this out, but did you say the line naked?
(Sorry to point this out, but did you say the line naked?)
I bet people are looking at him in the locker room.
You were about to take a shower.
I apologize for asking you to do this,
but I'm sure your fans appreciate this.
Happy New Year, Kye Sang. Thank you.
- Happy New Year. - Sure, sure.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Bye.
Who can we meet?
- Celebrities born in December... - Seok Jin.
The one I can think on top of my head is...
He was born in December.
It's Jang Hyuk.
(Jang Hyuk, Jong Kook's best friend)
- He was born in December. - Don't you talk to him regularly?
- Yes, I do. We are close. - Right.
- Let me give him a call. - Yes, call him.
- Great. - He's filming a drama now.
Right. That's true.
So I have to see if he's available or not.
- Let's give it a try. - Wait a second.
- Hey, Jong Kook. - Hey, Hyuk.
- Are you in a shoot now? - "Hey, Jong Kook."
Yes, I'm waiting for my scene now.
- Is that so? We are now... - I like him.
- filming Running Man. - Yes? I see.
Our mission is to find a celebrity who was born in December.
- In December? - Yes.
- So I was thinking if I could... - That's right.
go visit you and film us playing a game.
But it would be hard since you're filming a drama now, right?
(I know you're filming now, but can you meet with us briefly?)
- If... - If you come here,
I'm in no matter what. We have each other's back.
Right.
(If you come here, I'm in no matter what. We have each other's back.)
- He's so cool. - Thank you so much, Hyuk.
All right then. I'll see you there.
By the way, what will I be doing?
(He's nervous.)
We don't know yet.
- We don't know either. - It's a game.
Running Man makes me worried.
It'll be okay.
You don't have to worry.
I'm supposed to be charismatic.
(Please remember.)
(He's playing a charismatic lawyer.)
I know that.
We'll protect your charisma.
All right.
- Okay. - Okay.
(They'll visit Hyuk in Songdo.)
I'll tell you what you need to do...
- with Hyuk. - Now?
- Now? - Right now?
Okay.
Let's see. 1, 2, 3.
"Blowing..."
(Blow up 10 plastic bottles with your nose.)
He has to blow up plastic bottles with his nose?
I'm sorry, Hyuk.
I'm sorry.
He said, "Running Man makes me worried."
Gosh.
I'm so sorry.
Can't you give us another one?
Didn't you hear him?
- Exactly. He was worried. - He's supposed to be charismatic.
Let's do another one.
- Give us another one. - He can't do this.
Let's go. Where's the bus stop? Do we have to go down?
There's one there, and there's another one there.
We have to go 12 stops.
We'll go 12 stops and look for someone who lives there.
If we can't find anyone, we'll come back 12 stops...
and find someone here.
(They'll move 12 stops back.)
- Here? - Yes.
No one said we can't do that. We'll move 12 stops...
and look there first.
- All right. Let's go wherever. - Let's go.
We don't know which bus will come first.
- This one goes to Yeongdeungpo. - Yeongdeungpo?
This goes to Gayang-dong.
Gayang-dong.
(It might become a long journey depending on the bus.)
The first bus is arriving.
- The color is... - It's blue.
(They have to get on the bus and go 12 stops.)
- It's bus number 602. - It's 602.
(The bus they must ride is bus number 602.)
- Let's get on the bus. - Let's go.
- Hello. - Hello.
(They get on the bus.)
Hold on. We're...
(They check the route.)
Where are we now?
(Which stop will they get off at?)
Chungjeongno Station.
(There are many newspaper companies and government offices.)
Are there celebrities that come from this area?
(Will there be any celebrities around there?)
There's none.
Let's go there first. If I remember correctly,
there are many media companies around there.
We might find some celebrities.
I used to come to Sinchon a lot.
We're passing by Sinchon.
When I was younger,
- this place was so popular. - It was.
I even received a few casting offers in this area.
I got some business cards.
(The legendary street casting)
Really?
Did you debut after getting business cards?
I did.
- Really? - Yes.
(Ji Hyo used to receive a lot of business cards.)
I can't believe I'm with a person who debuted after getting a card.
It's true. I debuted after getting a business card.
- This brings back memories. - It's nice.
Ewha Womans University is nice too. It would've been great...
- to come here. - You're right.
(Meanwhile)
I have an exhausting partner today.
I wanted to take it easy today.
- Gosh, today is... - Goodness.
I really wanted to do well in today's game.
It's going to be ugly.
- Let's not do that again. - Seriously.
- Let's play fair. - Don't get cute.
- Don't be too mean. - It depends on you.
Let's not even start it.
Let's play fair.
- It's a promise. - Seriously.
Let's show them what fair play is.
We learned everything from you.
(Haha is the legendary betrayer.)
Who do you think we learned it from?
You learned it too well.
- Learn only good things. - You amaze me.
(Teacher versus student)
- It's true. - You're unbelievable.
We have to choose the right partner.
- Someone who debuted 12 years ago. - 12 years.
Someone who debuted 12 years ago...
Let's do this. Let's start over.
You and me...
I really want to win.
I love my scenario.
- Haha. - Yes?
If I win, I'll take out your water bomb.
(If I win, I'll take out your water bomb.)
(Tempting)
Kwang Soo usually...
- keeps his promises. - I promise.
I'll take yours out.
(Trust me.)
When I say, "Running Man is for 12 and over..."
"12 and over".
- Can I say, "and over"? - You can say, "12".
(You can say, "12".)
12?
Okay.
- Keep your promise. - "Running Man is for..."
- "12..." - "and over."
Can I say something else?
It sounds weird.
(It doesn't sound nice.)
All right.
- You can say, "for 12 and over". - Okay.
- "Running Man is..." - "For 12 and over."
(Running Man is for 12 and over.)
It doesn't sound right.
That part is too important.
You start.
- "Running Man is..." - "For 12 and over."
- Like this? - It was nice.
- I'll keep my promise. - Thank you.
I'll remove your water bomb.
I found Lee Sang Yeob.
He was on Running Man recently, right?
He debuted in 2007.
Really?
(This is his 12th year.)
(He recently did funny impressions on Running Man.)
It's not a bad idea, is it? He even won an award recently.
That's right.
We should call him and congratulate him.
It's Sang Yeob.
Hello.
(He's curt.)
Hello, this is Running Man. We're Haha...
And Kwang Soo.
- Hi, Sang Yeob. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
(Gentle)
Hi. It's nice to speak to you.
His voice changed instantly.
- Nice to hear from you. - It gave me goosebumps.
What's your blood type?
(Random)
(Why is he asking that question?)
It's B.
- That's right. You were chosen... - Yes.
as the blood-type B star of 2017.
Wait.
(The blood-type B star of 2017?)
(What?)
Congratulations...
- on getting chosen. - on getting chosen.
(Congratulations)
Congratulations.
The competition was fierce among blood-type B stars.
- Really? - You got second place,
and Jae Seok got third place.
(Both of them are telling lies so skillfully.)
Are you shooting right now?
- We are. - You are?
We're visiting our favorite guests.
And you were chosen as the star of 2017.
We have a prize for you.
(We have a prize for you.)
- Do you have time? - I can come to you.
- Is that okay? - Should we meet halfway?
Should we do that?
We'll be having tteokbokki in Hongdae. Can you come there?
- All right. - You have to hurry.
- Okay. - It's my treat.
We even have a trophy.
(They're even lying about a trophy.)
- Anyway, I'll see you there. - Okay.
- See you there. - But...
you have to hurry.
- Okay. - Thank you. I love you.
See you soon. Bye.
Don't ever do this to me.
- Let me explain. - Don't do this to me.
It's because of you.
- You played along so well. - Don't do this to me.
- I couldn't stop lying. - Haha is scary.
If our careers fail,
- we could con someone together. - Let's do that.
Let's con Seok Jin.
- We have to. - Okay.
How are we going to make a trophy?
(How are we going to keep our promise?)
Let me tell you what the game is about.
(The game is revealed.)
"Three Choices".
"You'll make three choices at a cafe."
"If you make the same choice, you succeed."
"The team that succeeds twice first will win."
- What does that mean? - I don't understand.
If we're choosing, it means that this is a roulette.
Yes. We'll explain the details later.
The team that wins two points first will win.
You'll compete 2 to 1, so your victory lies with your partner.
That means you have a better chance if you're two people.
(It's better to have a guest.)
(Look at him.)
Hey.
- I can't do this with you. - What?
Don't do that.
Your face says everything.
Please explain the situation with the subtitles.
- Who made it more obvious? - Haha.
Let's stick together. There are many games left.
(Don't betray me.)
I never said I wouldn't.
Let's stick together.
(Thinking)
- Look at him. - Let's take it easy.
- Let's play fair. - Seriously.
I'm already tired.
(He wants us to stick together?)
Hey, give it to me.
(Give your sticker to me.)
You don't need it anyway.
Can we choose one another?
- Yes. - It's between us.
- Let's exchange the stickers. - Sure.
Do we really need to do this?
- What? - It's like you don't trust me.
- I do. - I...
Why wouldn't I trust you?
- You lost it? - Where is it?
(You lost it?)
It was here before.
(Your sticker suddenly disappeared?)
Can you give me one more?
Hey.
(Forget it.)
What's with him? He's tiring me out.
Fine, let's go our separate ways.
- You're... - Haha.
- That's not it. - You're...
That's not why. Let's exchange.
- What's wrong with you? - Let's exchange.
I didn't know it was here. Let's exchange.
- Just do it. - I'm angry,
so I'll keep all.
(They're sneaky traitors.)
Wait a minute.
- What do you mean? - Let me keep them.
Don't you trust me?
I think I'm angry at you.
Don't talk to me for a while.
Come on, Haha. Fine.
(Team Jae Seok and So Min)
Here's the mission.
What is it?
Your mission is called...
Karaoke of 12.
- Karaoke? - What's that?
You'll take turns singing.
The person with the higher score wins.
The winner will get 20 ddakjis.
(They exchange a look of competitiveness.)
Jae Seok, let's sing together.
You don't sing well.
I sing well.
What can you sing?
I sang with Kim Dong Wan in the past.
- Kim Dong Wan? - Kim Dong Wan of Shinhwa.
- Dong Wan? - Yes.
Sing the song.
It's been a long time, so I forgot, but I added harmony.
- No way. - Look it up.
You'll find it on the internet.
- Really? - Yes.
- Did you sing with him? - Yes.
I trained to be a singer in high school.
- But I was a faceless singer. - Really?
(She was a faceless singer.)
- It was popular back then. - "Faceless singer"?
The producer told me to stay as a faceless singer...
and an actress, and then to reveal my identity later.
I worked with him,
but the producer ran away to Japan because I had no talent.
Your relationships always end that way.
It's the other person who runs away.
I was quite surprised.
- There it is. - Right?
(He presses play.)
That's my voice.
Which part?
(She hums.)
The female voice.
Do you hear the harmony?
When will your part start?
This is my part.
(It's been a long time)
(I feel free at this moment)
That's me.
(For those who may be flustered...)
("He Starlight" by Kim Dong Wan featuring Jeon So Min)
My part starts again.
Listen closely.
(The times when I walked alone)
It's me.
(Aren't I a good singer?)
Did you add the harmony?
Sing it again.
The times when I walked alone
(He hits her.)
(Stop playing around)
That's so fake.
There's no sincerity in your voice.
(She lacks sincerity.)
- Do you know what? - What?
It's a song called "Doll" by Shin Hye Sung and Lee Jee Hoon.
- Yes. - It's the epitome of harmony.
People sing it at the karaoke.
Will you add harmony while I sing it?
Do I have to?
(So Min considers it the epitome of harmony.)
(Will So Min and Jae Seok sing such a sweet song?)
I'll miss you
It cannot be helped
(Here's my high note.)
When I'm exhausted from crying for so long
I'll look for you
(She gives up.)
When will you sing in harmony?
You sing horribly.
I'm singing in low pitch for the background bass.
I can sing "Spring" in harmony very well.
Can you sing it? I'm good at singing it in harmony.
Really? I'll try again.
Start.
In deep mountains
- Stop it. - There's a spring
- That's not in harmony. - Who drinks from there?
Stop it.
Stop it already.
Stop it. Goodness.
That's enough.
- Stop singing. - It's harmony.
- Jae Seok. - Just stop it.
Try it again.
I'll sing in harmony instead. This is how you do it.
You sing like this to add harmony.
Start.
In deep mountains, there's a spring
Who drinks from there?
(They sing harmoniously as they play with notes.)
Destroying eyes
Those are not the lyrics.
(What did you say?)
(Something seems terribly wrong.)
What are you singing?
What kind of lyrics are those?
What are you?
(They arrive in Gangnam.)
What are some other songs?
(They select songs while waiting.)
I should sing "Darling".
That's a good one.
(Knocking)
(The guest is 45 years old.)
(It's a star who will shine this year.)
(He also has amazing singing skills.)
(Who is today's special guest who has it all?)
That's a good one.
(Knocking)
(The guest is 45 years old.)
(It's a star who will shine this year.)
(He also has amazing singing skills.)
(Who is today's special guest who has it all?)
Young Chul.
The one who will...
shine in 2018 is me.
(The most popular comedian singer, Kim Young Chul)
- Hello, Young Chul. - Come here.
Did you bring an English newspaper on purpose?
I always read the newspaper.
It's in English.
- I always read the news. - Where did you get it?
There's an English newspaper in his bag.
Stop it.
There's his wallet too.
He has so much cash.
Stop it. He just arrived.
You take out his wallet as soon as he arrives.
- Is that her habit? - No.
Put the newspaper back in.
Thank you, Young Chul.
I was really surprised.
Why?
This is why I thought you called me.
What?
Did you hear what happened at the Entertainment Awards Ceremony?
- What? - Am I regular?
(She sticks a team sticker.)
What does R mean?
Does it stand for regular?
- Did I become a regular member? - What did you do?
- Am I a regular member now? - What did you do?
Are you selecting another member?
So Min and Young Chul will be a team.
(So Min and Young Chul versus Jae Seok)
Jae Seok will be on his own.
- Did you do something wrong? - So Min.
(Just wait, and see.)
(Their singing competition starts.)
All I have to do is score higher.
(So Min and Young Chul's average score versus Jae Seok's score)
(She clicks her tongue.)
Hello. 1, 2.
Microphone testing, 1, 2, thank you.
What did you say?
(She prepares a lot for her bad singing skills.)
Is this a warm-up?
(They warm up first.)
Go.
("Ring" has an unforgettable melody.)
(He exaggerates his dance moves from the start.)
(Excited)
(It's a crazy dance.)
So Min.
(She turns.)
What was that?
(She pokes.)
(She does a finish.)
(Jae Seok loves this type of dance.)
(They remember the steps.)
I can also make a whirlwind.
(She spins.)
It's a whirlwind.
(It's So Min's whirlwind dance.)
Gosh, I'm dizzy.
(What is Young Chul score?)
- It's 100. - I never sang it at a karaoke.
- You got 100. - It's 100.
- So Min's dance was good. - Isn't it charming?
(More than Young Chul's singing...)
- 1, 2. - You have to move forward.
You can also do it this way.
(She mimics various creatures.)
(I'll practice that dance.)
Let's see.
Does the competition start?
Yes, we'll each sing a song.
We'll take the average of your scores...
and compare it to mine.
I'm nervous.
Young Chul scored high.
"Ring".
(She gets energy from Young Chul.)
- Are we starting? - Yes.
She'll start. Singing in Jin Young's version is good.
(The winner gets 20 ddakjis.)
(How much will So Min score?)
So Min.
(She transforms.)
(Ring)
(He gets up.)
(The old men can't resist dancing.)
(Her singing is rather stable in the beginning.)
(I'm your older sister)
(She reaches the climax as she sings passionately.)
(Get ready.)
(Ring)
(They waited for this part.)
Let's go
(Spinning)
(She's out of breath.)
(They're out of breath,)
(but they can't stop dancing.)
(The past 4 minutes felt like 4 hours.)
(It's time to reveal the score.)
- What is her score? - Please.
(Panting)
(From the middle, she gave up on singing and focused on dancing.)
What is my score?
85. It's 85.
(Compared to her singing skill, 85 percent is generous.)
- 85 percent? - Is that good?
- Is it not bad? - We needed to get over 90.
(Jae Seok and Young Chul are left. What will they get?)
- Here? - Please have a seat.
(Haha and Kwang Soo are going to meet Sang Yeob.)
Let's make a paper award.
(They make a paper award from a blank paper.)
Do you want to make it?
- Do you want to draw? I'll make it. - Okay.
(It's a Blood Type B Star Award, so they are very sincere.)
You can do it comfortably.
(He's creating a prestigious-looking trophy from the drama awards.)
This is so sloppy.
(Award ceremonies are about the sincerity, not the awards.)
- It's all about the heart. - I know.
But that's really bad.
Look at yours.
I have no time. I'm almost done.
(It's entirely handmade.)
I'm almost done.
This is really bad.
Doesn't it look pretty nice?
(It's a water bottle trophy.)
It's pretty good.
(He gets up.)
Isn't this nice?
It is, right?
Blood Type B Star Award.
(This award is presented for your talent and wit on Running Man.)
Haha.
That looks good.
- He might cry. - Right?
(It's a more prestigious-looking trophy decorated with a wreath.)
Put on a sticker.
(Sang Yeob will be happy, right?)
This came off.
(Let's see.)
Hold on.
- When did it come off? - I'm missing this.
Am I not supposed to have it on me?
Come on.
(We're both experts. Why are you doing this?)
- Don't do this. - It really came off.
Do I not need it? If not...
He's a bit strange.
Get up.
I'm serious.
I don't have it.
I'm serious. I don't have it.
If you don't have it,
you need another one...
to be on the same team as other people with the same color.
It's his fault that he lost it.
(Where is it?)
Are you going to put it on?
It must be here somewhere. Where is it?
(It must be here. Where is it?)
Come here.
I really don't have it.
You punk.
(He discovers the trick.)
Do you want to die?
I don't have it.
(Do you want to die?)
- What's that? There it is. - My gosh.
Goodness.
- Do you think I did it? - Never mind.
Don't talk.
- It fell, so I sat on it. - It's okay.
- Haha. - I'm not talking to him.
- You're mistaken. I sat on it. - I won't talk to him.
I didn't know I sat on it.
You...
I'm truly innocent.
You are...
(Goodness)
You are such a weird guy.
Aren't you going to give me your sticker?
(You promised.)
Why would I give you mine?
He's here. Sang Yeob is here.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Hello. - Congratulations.
Congratulations.
(Congratulations, Sang Yeob.)
(What is going on?)
"Congratulations."
"Blood Type B Star Award".
"Best Top Three".
"Lee Sang Yeob".
"This award is presented..."
"for your talent and wit on Running Man".
"From members of Running Man, 2018".
(Singing)
Let's take a picture.
(The tricksters get into position for a picture.)
Turn.
Long time, no see.
(They try to take Sang Yeob away.)
I stuck it on him!
(He sticks the team sticker.)
(Kwang Soo's sticker)
I stuck it on him. I did it first.
Haha...
Haha did something.
He knew I was going to stick the sticker,
so he put my sticker on himself.
He is...
- a dirty human being. - When did you see it?
- He's a dirty human being. - When did you see it?
(What was Haha's strategy that Kwang Soo found out?)
(Kwang Soo is going to betray me anyway.)
(Sly)
(He took off his own sticker...)
(and put on Kwang Soo's sticker.)
(Even if Kwang Soo betrayed him first,)
(Sang Yeob would have been on Haha's team.)
- He's a dirty human being. - When did you see it?
What's going on?
Is Kwang Soo's sticker on Sang Yeob?
- Yes. - He tricked me.
Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo are on the same team.
- Yes. - Haha is on his own.
(I'm on my own.)
Oh, gosh.
- Congratulations, Sang Yeob. - Thank you.
Congratulations.
(How could you do this to me?)
- You are... - No, Haha.
Think about it.
I'm guilty too.
Let's ask Sang Yeob to show us.
He can do impressions of people.
After Kim Hak Do...
After Kim Hak Do and Jeong Jong Chul, he's the best.
It's true.
That's the order.
He has a new impression.
- That day, So Min did... - Oh, right.
"I have two bullets."
(There was an impression battle during the filming.)
I have two bullets.
(It's an impression of Lee Jung Jae on "Assassination".)
(He strongly expresses injustice.)
I was impressed, so I worked on it.
I'm sorry, Jung Jae.
(How is Sang Yeob's impression of Jung Jae on "Assassination"?)
"I have two bullets."
Goodness.
"I picked these guys,"
"Your Honor."
He's trying so hard.
(This is the class of the Grand Award recipient.)
- There are so many people watching. - Excuse us.
Isn't he great?
- Isn't he good? - Thank you.
It was Lee Jung Jae.
Please say a few words in Jang Hyuk's voice.
I think he'll be good.
Thank you.
(They're amazed.)
I didn't know I was going to get such a great award.
Thank you. "Un Nyun"!
(The line from "The Slave Hunters" is always funny.)
I'm sorry, sir.
Thank you.
That was so similar.
(Actor Lee Sang Yeob works hard to develop more impressions.)
- This is the first game. - I don't 'know what to do.
The three of you can order a drink each...
and give your credit cards to the barista.
If your card is chosen, you lose.
Yes. Really?
What's going on?
(If there are two members in your team, the chance doubles.)
Then is it better to have more people?
Isn't it a disadvantage to have more?
(It's more disadvantageous to have more people.)
(I tried hard to get Sang Yeob on my team.)
Isn't it better to have more people?
Gosh, this is great.
It's a great game.
This one's really good.
(They learn a lesson on virtue and vice.)
This is so much fun.
I have two cards.
- Yes. - Stop it.
He doesn't care about winning.
- He doesn't care. - I have one.
I have one.
Hold on.
I don't know what to do. I just got here.
This is mine, and this is Kwang Soo's.
(They mix up their credit cards.)
(Haha, Sang Yeob, Kwang Soo)
Let's go.
(The game of random chance begins.)
There are three cards.
- Let's have something sweet. - Yes.
Let's have a cake.
Let's see. I want Sang Yeob to order.
- Me? - Yes. I want to buy you something.
Do you want to take the order from Jang Hyuk,
- Jung Woo Sung, or Lee Jung Jae? - Jung Woo Sung.
- Jung Woo Sung. - Okay.
Can I have a tiramisu first?
He does it right away.
He doesn't say no.
He's the same.
Drinks? What about drinks?
Order drinks in Jang Hyuk's voice.
Jang Hyuk.
- Can I have iced Americano? - Me too.
Can I have three iced Americano?
That came out of nowhere.
That's it.
We have to pay.
(It's time to pay. The barista chooses the loser.)
Here you go. Please choose what you like.
- You can choose any. - Choose any.
(Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob have a 66.66-percent chance...)
(while Haha has a 33.33-percent chance.)
- You can choose any. - Choose any.
(It's Haha's.)
It's his.
(There are so many twists in this race.)
We have two cards.
We had two.
We won.
That was totally unexpected.
(As a twist, Haha loses.)
The first game is over. Haha got chosen, so he loses.
(The first game is over.)
What do we do? We are here for Jang Hyuk.
- My gosh. - I feel bad.
- Right? - This game...
- He's so charismatic. - Right?
You can't make him play that game.
What plastic bottle?
- Aren't there other games? - They're friends of 20 years.
There are other games too.
They have a friendship to preserve.
- You know the rules, right? - Yes.
If you don't put the sticker on him, you two are a team.
Let's be on the same team.
From now on,
- you have to decide in 5 minutes. - 5 minutes?
- Okay. - Time's up once I blow the whistle.
He's in the middle of a drama, and he has a charismatic role.
He's so charismatic.
Hyuk.
(It's Hyuk.)
- He's so charismatic. - Hyuk.
(It's the charismatic actor, Jang Hyuk.)
You sounded worried.
I overheard you...
- on the phone. - You were worried.
You were worried about being on our show because of your current role.
When I come on shows that involve my friends,
I know I have to embarrass myself.
So... I'm...
I'm just going to go with it.
He's not like this. He'll never do this on other shows.
- I know. - He has standards of his own.
When he sees us...
When I see Cha Tae Hyun, Kim Jong Kook, and Hong Kyung In,
I give it all.
Right. Thank you so much. We came here,
- but we're bothering you. - I feel bad.
- He's doing so well. - That's right.
- You're in the middle of a drama. - Right.
You need to take a break. We are sorry.
- Sorry. - It's all right.
It's cold, so let's hurry.
- Yes. - All right.
- It's over? - It's been five minutes.
- It's over? - Time's up?
We were asking how he was doing.
That doesn't count.
It's too bad,
but Hyuk is on his own.
Seok Jin and Jong Kook are on the same team.
No way.
What do we have to do?
- Goodness. - Let me explain.
It's a game. It's 2 versus 1.
Here's the game you'll be playing.
- It's simple. - We will explain.
We asked for a different game.
(I have to play that game?)
We asked.
We asked for another game.
- We asked. - We tried...
to change it.
- We asked. - They said they didn't have any.
- We asked. We're so sorry. - We didn't want to do it.
I felt so bad. You're my friend.
This game is called Snort of 12.
I have to blow this with my nose?
I told you. We tried.
We asked for a different game.
- We tried for an hour. - We asked for another one.
- We asked for a different one. - We tried many times.
- We did. Sorry. - We asked for another one.
Why don't you just recruit me? I'll just be a regular.
- I'll be a regular. - Please.
We need a contract.
The rules are simple.
Breathe into the plastic bottles with your nose,
and the team that unflattens the bottles first wins.
(1, 2, 3, 4)
He's counting.
(He did.)
Don't you need to blow your nose?
I do.
Just in case. Thank you.
Let's get clean first.
It's like getting rid of last year's germs.
I'm so sorry, Hyuk. We won't take long.
I'm sorry,
- Top Excellence Award winner. - You two were the winners.
We're both Top Excellence Award winners. I'm sorry.
Let me repeat. We tried to negotiate for an hour.
- Let's unflatten this a little. - Jong Kook said...
his friend has a charismatic role.
Let's help him a little. They're too tight.
No, no.
- We have to do this properly. - It has to be fair?
- Let's crush ours. - Okay.
- This... - Let's do that.
- Let's crush them a lot. - Okay.
(He doesn't try.)
Let's crush them.
You're pretending like you're crushing them.
- I'll do it. - I thought...
- he was crushing them. - No.
- You're faking it. - I did it.
I really did it.
Ours are so crushed.
- Get ready. - Let's do this.
(Hyuk has to beat the other two with his nose muscles.)
Do this. It doesn't take long.
Ready.
Set...
(Will Hyuk give it his best and win the mission?)
(He unflattens it in one try.)
(He sweeps it with his large lung capacity.)
(Meanwhile...)
(He's barely doing anything.)
This is not working. How is he doing this?
Hurry up!
How do you do this?
(Hyuk is faster than the other two.)
(They're doing two at a time and are catching up.)
This is not working.
(He runs out of energy.)
Next.
How many did he do? My snot is coming out.
(This match is unpredictable.)
(It's over.)
My gosh.
(Giggling)
- Good job. - Was I funny?
- Was that fun? - Hyuk.
(He cares more about being funny than his appearance.)
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's totally okay.
That was so funny.
You tried your best.
Thanks so much.
There's one of Hyuk's that's not unflatten properly,
so Seok Jin and Jong Kook win.
(They win 20 ddakjis.)
Sorry.
- He tried his best. - He did.
- Did you see his face? - Excuse me.
I couldn't do it because I was laughing.
If it's really bad, please blur it out.
- They'll do a good job. - I'm acting as a lawyer.
It'll be fine.
On my sixth bottle, I turned a bit pale.
(He cares more about winning than the friendship.)
- So I switched nostrils. - You turned pale?
- You switched nostrils? - I was doing this side,
and I couldn't keep it up, so I switched.
(He got dizzy,)
(so he switched to the other nostril.)
There's a request from the Running Man fans.
Lee Sang Yeob did an impression of you.
He got popular for saying, "Un Nyun".
"Un Nyun!"
(The fans wanted to see the original version.)
Can we see the original?
- Did you see it? - Did you?
- Did you see it on Running Man? - That line...
- is not supposed to be like that. - Then?
What is it?
He did it really weirdly.
- Really? - It looked weird.
Show us the original.
(How does the original do it?)
"Un Nyun". Like this.
- Was that it? - Yes.
- Is this the original? - Yes.
It's the same.
(These two...)
(are not that different.)
(It's the same.)
"Un Nyun".
Maybe I speak and hear differently.
Perhaps.
We're finally here.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan are by Sangam SBS Prism Tower.)
- She's here. - Is that her?
The lights are on.
(They're waiting for their guest.)
(Only top stars drive this car.)
(Who's inside the car?)
- Na Rae. - Oh, dear.
(It's Park Na Rae, the star of entertainment awards.)
Na Rae.
- Na Rae. - Na Rae.
- What's going on? - Na Rae.
(What happened among them?)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We're in trouble. This is going nowhere.
(They stopped at a bus station.)
- It's here. - Let's go there.
(Sangam was 12 stations away.)
- Let's go. - Go.
("Comedy Big League" was being filmed today.)
- Let's go there. - They're in Sangam.
Hold on.
(He's called Na Rae.)
- Hello? - Na Rae.
- Yes? - Where are you?
I'm on my way.
- During our team dinner, - Yes.
you made a big mess, so we have to talk.
I'll be in the parking lot we always park in.
See you later.
Really?
Have some tangerines.
Na Rae.
Are you sober now?
Are you okay?
I'm going to court. What's going on?
Let's talk about that later.
Put on a microphone.
What's going on?
Why am I putting this on? I have to go in.
- I need my jacket. - Give us 10 minutes.
- 10 minutes? - It'll only take 10 minutes.
You need to dress like a celebrity.
Here it is.
You didn't disappoint us with that color.
Why are we all wearing only primary colors?
- This is tangerine. - Tangerine? I see.
- We're doing a mission. - Okay.
Can you spare 10 minutes for us? Let's go to SBS.
What mission is this?
- It's so simple. - Really?
I don't think you are sober yet.
I don't think you are.
- That night was intense. - Na Rae.
- This is really simple. - It's simple.
(Are there stones on a dish with a cup on the bottom?)
- Explain. - We hold this...
and throw it up. If all five stones go in the cup, you win.
- It's over once you do it 1st. - You have 5 chances.
But you're on your own.
- What? - You're by yourself.
You're on your own.
But there's a condition.
If you get five in the cup first,
you win a big prize.
- Really? - Yes.
This is not just for fun.
We have to do this.
- We have to win. - We have to get this.
Our lives depend on this, Se Chan.
- This better be worth our time. - I know.
Ready.
(This is their first step toward winning.)
Set...
(Flipping)
Okay.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan get 2 at a time.)
- Okay. - Hold on.
- We only have one left. - Ji Hyo.
Take a breath.
(Meanwhile for Na Rae...)
My gosh. Why is this not working?
(Sighing)
Ji Hyo, take a breath.
We're almost done.
Oh, dear. Na Rae.
- You still have shaky hands. - Wait.
(She has unexplained shaky hands.)
You have a tremor,
- so you can't do it. - Move over.
(Flying)
- Stop drinking. - Goodness.
Running Man is rated 12A.
- She's so funny. - Na Rae, we're done.
- You are? - We have one left.
We have one left.
- Okay. - There you go.
All right. Get ready, Ji Hyo.
- Okay. - Go, Ji Hyo.
- My goodness. - Ji Hyo, hurry up.
Ji Hyo, Na Rae got the hang of it.
Na Rae got the hang of it.
Na Rae got the hang of it. You need to hurry up.
- Okay. - Hurry up.
Okay!
(She comes from behind and wins.)
(This must be how the hare looked after losing to the tortoise.)
You should have picked up the stones for me.
Woman-who-is-pushing-40, what are you doing?
I ran around the room because of you.
You should have picked up the stones for me.
Hold on. How did you do so well toward the end?
My hands began to shake in a rhythmical way.
(My hands began to shake in a rhythmical way.)
(Rhythmical)
Na Rae got the hang of it. This is a disaster.
Okay. We will give Na Rae a gift.
Na Rae, your appearance on Running Man...
earned you a gift.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Hold on.
- Running Man gives you tangerines. - Hold on.
- It matches your outfit. - They match.
Please take these tangerines. I hope you have a good shoot today.
Hold on. These tangerines look familiar.
How did they come back to me?
You know,
- life is a circle. - That's right.
- Bye. Thank you. - Good luck.
- All right. - Bye.
Good luck. Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
(Thank you for coming despite your busy schedule, Na Rae.)
The one with the Rookie Award.
- All right. - It's hot.
(So Min's score is 85.)
I will go next.
Which song will you sing?
I will sing "Darling".
He lives young, right?
I was going to sing "Flower" by Jang Yun Jung.
- That's a good idea. - Let's stick to trot.
(I must win.)
(A backup dancer interferes.)
(Stepping)
(He tries his best to concentrate.)
(She grabs the attention.)
(He is annoyed.)
(So Min's dance makes Jae Seok impatient.)
What is going on?
(He takes off his clothes one by one.)
(Darling)
(You)
(Jae Seok's performance gets edited to meet TV guidelines.)
(Jae Seok's "Darling" receives a score of 83.)
- Thank goodness. - We did it.
Jae Seok, why are you so bad at singing?
How are we two points apart when he sang so terribly?
So Min, the key wasn't high.
- He just can't sing. - Don't be ridiculous.
(It's So Min's fault.)
If you score 82, it's a tie. If you score 81, you lose.
Young Chul, help me.
Don't worry. It will be game over once I sing this song.
Young Chul.
- "Flower" by Jang Yun Jung. - All right.
- That's good. - Don't lower the key.
The current key is for women.
The key was high for Taeyang's song, too.
(His score needs to be 81 or less for Jae Seok to win.)
I lowered the key since it was for women.
(I have to do something.)
(Grabbing)
(He blocks the microphone...)
(and tickles Young Chul.)
(He attacks like an immature child.)
What are you doing?
Move.
(Don't pester Young Chul.)
(Following)
(Young Chul, focus on singing.)
(What are you doing?)
(She attacks viciously.)
(A match that began with betrayal becomes a fistfight.)
(Grabbing)
(Pulling)
(As the fight becomes more fierce,)
(the singing contest loses its original meaning.)
(She anesthetizes him.)
(As Jae Seok gets anesthetized,)
(Young Chul's steps turn sadder.)
For goodness' sake. Come here.
They will take all of my screen time.
Let go.
(Both the singer and the listeners are in tatters.)
(Young Chul's song is over.)
Let's see it.
(It's time to check the score.)
(If the score is 81 or less, Jae Seok wins.)
(If the score is 82 or more, So Min and Young Chul win.)
The score, please.
99! Give me a big hand.
(So Min and Young Chul win.)
(Young Chul is the king of karaoke machines.)
I am a singer.
"Are you the king of singers?" I am a singer.
Good job, Young Chul.
(So Min debuts successfully as a singer.)
So Min will receive 20 ddakjis.
(Meanwhile, Haha and Kwang Soo...)
It's coming.
- Thank you for the dessert. - Thank you.
Their dessert is popular.
- Thank you. - My goodness.
- Thank you. - Sang Yeob, it's good to see you.
- Seriously. Congratulations. - I missed you.
- I really missed you. - I missed you.
Thank you.
(They enjoy a coffee break with Sang Yeob.)
Even the ice looks splendid.
I know.
What did you do yesterday?
I went home after the awards ceremony.
You were really happy, right?
- Congratulations. - Seriously.
I was so happy...
that I drank a lot.
You drank.
The occasion called for it.
When you called me,
- I was getting scolded by my mom. - Really?
That's why I picked up right away. "Hello?"
That's why you picked up.
He answered a call from an unknown number.
I would have even answered a spam call about loans...
at that moment.
Had a loan shark called me, I would have gone, "Hello?"
That's hilarious.
He is good.
I love Sang Yeob. I love him.
That goes without saying.
You seem busy these days.
(He suddenly talks to Kwang Soo.)
- Me? - Never mind.
Sang Yeob...
Sang Yeob is so refreshing.
He is like lemon tart. He is so refreshing.
Something is different...
- about him. - You hurt my feelings.
Why did you clench your fist?
- He is really different. - My feelings are hurt.
(A star with blood type B, a star who is wanted as a member)
I will give you the mission now as you may be required to wait.
This is the second mission.
If Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob win, the game ends.
- It's game over, right? - Yes.
(If Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob win, the game ends.)
This is your second choice.
Once the mission begins,
(Choice of 12, Round 2)
you win if the customer who walks into the cafe...
orders the menu you chose.
Please pick a menu before the mission begins.
(You win the mission...)
(by correctly guessing the menu the first customer will order.)
(If either Sang Yeob or Kwang Soo gets it right,)
(Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo win.)
- We should choose differently. - We have an advantage.
- We do. - We have an advantage.
I made up my mind.
Since there are a lot of female customers,
I will choose hot latte.
Since it's cold, I will choose hot chocolate.
Women like hot chocolate.
You can't change your choice after you say it.
Then I will also choose hot latte.
Why don't the two of you play Dreadful Pirate?
You want to ruin my chance.
- I will choose a different one. - Which one?
I will choose hot Americano.
(Hot Americano, Hot chocolate, Hot latte)
Kwang Soo drives me crazy.
I am playing clean and fair today.
- I am serious. - You are playing fair?
Of course, I am.
Okay. Let's take this to the end. We don't know what will happen.
(They wait for a customer.)
We just need to wait until the next customer comes.
- We should talk. - I see.
This is how a variety show works.
(5 minutes pass.)
(10 minutes pass.)
(20 minutes pass.)
(No customer comes.)
(Rustling)
Sung Yong, I need to go to the restroom.
Do you need to use the restroom?
I am okay. I am okay.
- Do you need to go? - I will be back soon.
(Another 5 minutes pass.)
(The shoot resumes.)
You will go with the menus you chose.
- Yes. - Of course.
I still don't know why I am here.
Where is the trophy?
- Here. - There you go.
(He remembers he was invited as a star with blood type B.)
There you go.
It's an important award.
Lets' play rock-paper-scissors. I want to see my fortune.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha wins alone by playing rock.)
What?
Two scissors.
(Two scissors.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins.)
He ended up winning.
He drives me crazy.
I am in a good mood today.
Me too.
By the way,
I take back my words about removing the water bomb.
(I take back my words about removing the water bomb.)
- What? - I said I'd remove it before.
You can't take back your words.
I just did.
(It's too late.)
Okay.
- A customer is here. - Hold on.
(A customer comes in.)
(A customer comes in after 30 minutes of waiting.)
Hot Americano, please.
(He orders Haha's choice, hot Americano.)
Hey.
(Something is strange.)
Are you drinking it here?
It's to go.
(Why is Kwang Soo upset?)
(What?)
(Who is he?)
(He made people laugh on the show.)
(He was a character who was as pure as snow.)
(Haha's best friend, Park Geun Sik)
(No matter which mission he gets...)
(Rice and seasoning)
(With his pure brain,)
(he made his presence known.)
(Did Haha's friend, Geun Sik,)
(visit the cafe by chance?)
Hold on.
(My gosh. I know what's happening now.)
(What on earth happened?)
(10 minutes ago)
Hey, let's go to the restroom.
(Haha said that he was going to the restroom.)
(But why is he coming back without using the restroom?)
Hey, Kwang Soo... Hey, hey.
Hey, where are you now?
I'm pooping.
- You're pooping? - Yes.
Can you come here right now and do a mission with me?
We are in Hongdae.
Come and just say, "Hot Americano, please."
I'll treat you to coffee.
I'll send you the address. Stop pooping, and come right away.
- Okay. - Come as quickly as you can.
(Exactly 5 minutes later...)
- He's here. - Wait.
- Hot Americano, please. - Hold on.
Hey.
(He pretends that he doesn't see the camera.)
Hot Americano, please.
Are you drinking it here?
It's to go.
- Hey. - What?
(He pretends to be surprised.)
Hey, Geun Sik, what brings you here?
- Hey. - I came here for a cup of coffee.
My gosh, why are you here?
- Gosh. - Long time, no see.
- What is this? - This is Lee Sang Yeob, the actor.
- Oh, my. Hello. - Are you serious?
- Hey, long time, no see. - Hello.
Hey, Happy New Year.
- Hey, Haha. - You can't do this. Hold on.
- You ordered hot Americano, right? - Yes.
I need to wake up.
What did the customer who just walked in order?
Hot Americano.
(He's brazen.)
- What is this? - What do you mean?
Are we going to play dirty?
Is it ready?
- Seriously? - Let me pay for this.
No, no. Let me pay for this.
- Why don't you take a seat? - Seriously?
But seriously, why are you here?
- I needed coffee. - I can't believe this.
Where are you coming from?
I was at home. I'm on my way to...
He said he always comes to this cafe.
I'm a regular here.
I was sitting there...
and thought how someone could look so alike.
(That's what he thought initially.)
Okay, fine. Fine.
(He enjoys his Americano on a Monday afternoon.)
Fine. We're going all the way today.
- Let's duke this out. - Hey.
But it was hilarious. As soon as he walked in,
I asked if it was him, and he said,
"Hot Americano, please."
(Let's play this dirty then.)
Okay, okay.
Didn't I come really quickly though?
- It took me about three minutes. - Are you serious?
Yes, you were quick.
This is so funny.
- I don't know what the last one is. - Geun Sik, you are the best.
Thank you.
- Why are you thanking me? - Have a good day.
- I'm a fan! - What's wrong?
- No, he said the line. - Thank you.
- Have a good day. - See you around.
Please take your seats, and we'll do the last game.
- Okay, okay. I still have a shot. - All right.
- When did you call him? - I won five now.
I feel nervous all of a sudden now.
- He may have more air time than me. - No, no.
Don't you worry.
- He might have more air time. - No, don't worry.
(With the score, 1 to 1, it's the last round.)
- We have to win. - Then for this game,
I might have an advantage.
You don't know that. This is an important one.
- The last choice for Choice of 12. - Please.
A tape has been attached on the floor of this cafe.
- It's near the entrance. - Okay.
Guess the customer's foot over the line.
Choice 1, right foot. Choice 2, left foot.
Choice Three, the customer steps on the line.
(With which foot will the customer pass the line?)
Hold on. Please read the choices again.
Choice 1, right foot. Choice 2, left foot. Choice 3,
- the customer steps on the line. - My gosh. This is too hard.
We are at an advantage.
"The customer steps on the line."
- "The customer steps on the line." - Okay.
Whatever you choose, we'll win.
- Right foot. - Right foot.
"The customer steps on the line."
- Haha, stop it now. - Wait.
Whom do you keep calling?
- Geun Sik, don't go yet. - What are you doing?
- Geun Sik. - What's wrong with this guy?
Geun Sik, don't leave yet.
- What's gotten into you? - All right, all right.
- Okay. - Gosh, that was hilarious.
"The customer steps on the line."
Most people are right-footed, so when they see the line,
they will be compelled to use their right foot.
- Did you choose Choice Three? - Yes.
Whoever wins will get to take Choice Three.
Whoever loses will have to take the left foot.
- I don't want to lose now. - Usually...
Haha, I'm sorry.
- I mean it. - People usually step on the line.
(When he walks in a natural manner, does he end up...)
(stepping on the line?)
This is bound to happen.
This is a given. Seriously.
- Whatever happens, that's a given. - You...
Did you come in with your right foot?
I came in with my right foot first.
Welcome. Please come in.
- Are you guys filming here? - You can come in. Please come in.
I can come in?
Come in.
Don't try to calculate which foot to use now.
(Hesitating)
(Just come in.)
Don't think about it.
- How do we do that? - No, no.
Whatever happens, people will step on it.
- My gosh. - I agree.
- Okay. - That is the right choice.
(Will the next customer step on it like Kwang Soo's prediction?)
- They have to just cross the line. - Okay!
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha: left foot, Kwang Soo: on the line)
- Then I get the left foot. - Yes.
- Okay. - All right.
I'm almost there!
If I win this game, it's a miracle. It will be incredible.
Haha, it's either the customer steps on it or uses the right foot.
- Your chance is slim. - That's right.
To be honest, I'm not even nervous.
(All they need to do is wait for the next customer.)
He's coming in. He's coming.
- Customers are here. - Customers are here.
(At this moment, two guys walk into the cafe.)
(At this point, he will either use his left foot or step on the line.)
Customers are here.
(Who will be the victor?)
(Shortly)
(The last story with Eccentric Master)
(Living with the master still surprises them.)
(His preferences are unapproachable and incomprehensible.)
(What have I just eaten?)
(And above all,)
(the master delivers a heavy blow.)
Your minds are...
("All the Butlers" is coming up soon.)
He's coming in. He's coming.
- Customers are here. - Customers are here.
(At this moment, two guys walk into the cafe.)
(At this point, he will either use his left foot or step on the line.)
Customers are here.
(Who will be the victor?)
(He stepped on the line!)
(Just as Kwang Soo predicted, he steps on the line.)
(He's in despair.)
(Justice is served!)
- Hello. - Welcome.
The third choice is...
stepping on the line.
(Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob win in the end.)
(Yes! This is going to be my year!)
(He's frustrated and can't believe what just happened.)
Kwang Soo, who won the mission, will be given 20 ddakjis.
And Sang Yeob...
will receive a small gift that we've prepared.
That's right. You deserve this gift.
Usually, stepping on the line means you are out.
(He holds a grudge.)
(This wraps up the mission with ddakjis.)
(However, the battle for TV rating notice begins now!)
(Next week)
(It's not over until it's over?)
(The war isn't over. It's a team match now!)
(Are you still clueless? It's an individual match in the end.)
I have to win by all means.
(They will only get 5 seconds.)
(Their unprecedented passion to become the center of the clip)
(Or is it their energy?)
Let's go, my story under the sea!
(And)
(Finally, their imagination...)
(comes true.)
(Which member will win?)