- What's this? - We're going inside a house.
Is this "All The Butlers"?
- What's this? - Is it a restaurant?
Is it really a restaurant?
- It must be a restaurant. - It's nice.
We usually open the show in the yard. This is refreshing.
- I'll put your shoes up here. - Thank you.
(Is the shoot inside a restaurant?)
Gosh, what's that? Wait.
- What is it from the start? - What is it?
There's food during the opening.
- What's going on? - This is amazing.
- This is nice. - What's going on?
They're treating us well for a reason.
- Are we eating already? - No way.
What's going on? I feel pressured.
- What is it? - What's all this?
Can we eat?
(Come here, So Min.)
- Do we eat? - What's going on here?
(Sit next to Jong Kook.)
- What shall we do? - Everyone.
You must be hungry since it's lunch time.
- Yes. - Yes.
Our shoots have been difficult these days.
We prepared a special opening for you.
- Right. - What's going on?
- You'll start with a meal. - This is weird. I don't like it.
Do we get to eat for free?
- There's even deodeok. - Jong Kook.
There's no water. I'll bring some.
The texture of the deodeok is amazing.
I haven't had hot rice in a long time.
It's strange that no one is putting dried laver on their face.
Now that we're allowed to eat as much as we want,
- I can't eat. - Just eat.
- Do we have to dance? - Just enjoy it.
This is how Seok Jin eats.
- Do you know what he just said? - What?
If we came here alone without cameras,
he'd say, "There's a lot of food, but nothing seems appetizing."
(He's eating for the camera.)
That's what he'd say.
He complains no matter what the menu is.
Exactly.
I wonder I love jellyfish so much.
(He forgets about the shoot and eats with gusto.)
Jellyfish is delicious.
They're writing something.
(Staff members are writing something.)
- What are they writing? - What's going on?
- What is it? - Come on.
- What are you writing? - I don't care. I'm going to eat.
- I don't care. Just eat. - How can they write...
right in front of us?
They brought something to write on.
I'm trying not to care, but as soon as I noticed that they're writing,
I can only eat what I already ate.
I'm eating deodeok.
Tofu is delicious.
- Tofu? - Tofu with kimchi is excellent.
(So Min gives him a flower.)
- It's a flower. - It's in front of you.
- Why are you giving it to me? - Just because.
- To me? Thank you. - Yes.
- What are you doing, So Min? - What is it?
What is it all of a sudden?
- I'm sitting next to him. - Out of the blue?
She likes to do things out of the blue.
- Hey, what are you doing? - I'm sorry.
(Crashing)
- What is it? - Is it a mission?
- Is it a mission? - Why did you do that?
It's because it was too far.
- You're being rude. - Wait, Jae Seok. It was too far.
- It was too far. - Did you get an instruction?
- What's going on? - I was only eating.
Why did you give me a flower? It's strange.
- Did they give you an order? - No.
(Their suspicious meal continues.)
Can we get more braised ribs?
I ate too much.
Is everyone done eating?
Excuse me, is there nurungji?
- No. - Wait a minute.
I want some more braised ribs, but I ate too much.
(A man stares at Seok Jin who goes to ask for nurungji.)
- To be honest, I want soup. - Me too.
- How about this? - Why isn't there any nurungji?
(What?)
What?
What happened? What did you do?
- What? - What's with the look?
(He's caught hiding something.)
Seok Jin, what's with the look?
- What is it? - Make up an excuse for yourself.
Make up an excuse for yourself.
- I went to the restroom. - With your rice bowl?
(Did he go to the restroom with his rice bowl?)
This is what he did as he came back in.
(He mumbles to himself awkwardly.)
What was that about?
This is a failure. I don't know what it is.
- Wait. Jong Kook. - This is a failure.
- He went to the restroom, - Seriously.
but he said, "I'll go and eat."
He went this way instead of that way.
He came back in while talking to himself.
If it's Seok Jin,
let's shoot again tomorrow.
(If Seok Jin is the spy, let's shoot again tomorrow.)
- What's going on? - Tell us.
- You thought it was me last time. - I know.
I can be strange at times.
(I can be strange at times.)
That's why.
What he said was very strange.
I acted normal,
but you thought I was being strange.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- I don't think so. - Why are you blushing?
Also, his rice bowl is empty.
Why do you keep picking up your chopsticks?
(Everything that he does seems suspicious.)
- Why are you picking them up? - Listen.
It's because you're cornering me.
(It's because you're cornering me.)
- I was only being normal. - Seok Jin.
- Aren't you full? - I am.
- Put down your chopsticks. - No.
I want some ribs.
(The suspicious meal is over.)
(They come out to the garden for the official opening.)
If you're afraid...
(They head to the shoe rack to go outside.)
(He looks around.)
Didn't Ji Hyo put my shoes on the rack?
(Didn't Ji Hyo put my shoes on the rack?)
- Where are your shoes? - Are they missing?
(My shoes are missing.)
Was it a mission to hide my shoes?
Are your shoes missing? Weren't they next to mine?
Ji Hyo put them up earlier.
(Jong Kook's shoes were on the shoe rack when they went inside.)
(After their meal, his shoes disappeared into thin air.)
Ji Hyo put them up earlier.
- Seok Jin. Where did you put them? - Yes?
(It must be you.)
- Mine were on the ground. - I don't know.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
- How would I know that? - Where did you put my shoes?
- He's the culprit. - Seok Jin.
- How would I know that? - What did you do with my shoes?
- It's over. Done, done, done. - Seok Jin.
The culprit is...
- Jee Seok Jin! - Jee Seok Jin!
- I didn't. Why do you suspect me? - Where did you put my shoes?
- Hold on. This is... - Goodness, it's me again.
Hold on a second. Attention. Everyone, what's going on?
"Attention"?
How can you say that? Some are older than you.
- That was a bit rude. - You gave me a flower.
- What's going on? - That's a bit rough.
Do you want me to be rough on you?
No, no.
Step aside, Jae Seok.
Where did my shoes go?
- Right now, - Who did it?
- Jong Kook's shoes disappeared. - Yes.
Today, someone has a grudge against Jong Kook and stole his shoes.
For today's race, you must catch the petty thief.
(Catch the Petty Thief)
His shoes?
(Who is the thief that stole Jong Kook's shoes?)
The thief who stole his shoes...
is among you.
- It's Seok Jin. It's too obvious. - My gosh.
(One member in particular seems very suspicious.)
It's Seok Jin.
Let's come back here tomorrow. We'll film it again tomorrow.
It's not me.
Gosh, this is crazy. They're suspecting me again.
- What is this? - Didn't you fail?
All right. The winners of four missions...
will be provided with photos of the petty thief's body parts.
(Winners will receive photo hints.)
If we get the photo of his nose, it's over.
(Is this a definite clue?)
If the members unanimously apprehend the petty thief...
in the final voting, the victory will go to the members.
And you'll be given a present.
And the petty thief will receive the water bomb penalty.
If you fail to apprehend the petty thief,
everyone except for the petty thief will face the penalty.
And the petty thief will receive the present.
First off, we'll give you a pair of shoes.
- But you know what? - My gosh.
Do we have to play the race even if we know who it is?
- Who is it? - Goodness.
- That's the trick. That's the trap. - This is easy.
Wait, but there might be more than one petty thief.
- Why are we standing like this? - Think about it.
(Are we standing in groups?)
- It really wasn't me. - What did you say?
(Petty and suspicious members are in a group together.)
- That's not what I meant. - What's your problem?
- What are you insinuating? - There's an expression for that.
- What's wrong with you? - Let me explain.
- What's his problem? - You were together as a group.
- Hey. - So Min's flower was so random.
Everyone didn't say anything about that.
I only gave it to you because you were sitting next to me.
- That's why you gave me the flower? - Yes. It went well with red.
- That's why you gave me the flower? - Yes. You go well with red.
- As soon as we all sat down, - Listen.
you were trying to sit next to me. That was really weird.
- You usually avoid me. - I tried to avoid sitting there.
(Don't get the wrong idea.)
I wasn't trying to sit there.
- Really? You were avoiding me? - He thought the opposite.
- Really? - Now, he misunderstood.
- Hey, you passed now. - Okay, I understand that.
Gosh, those two sycophants are standing right next to him.
Goodness, you annoying punks.
- I can't believe them. - "Mom's..."
- "Mom's..." - "Diary".
What? "Mom's Diary"?
- I bet one of them is the thief. - Seriously.
(There's no way my boys would do that.)
The 1st hint is at stake during this 1st mission.
Let me tell you the rules of Squid Ink Shower.
(Squid Ink Shower)
- What is that? - What's that? We just started.
Form 4 groups of 2.
It will be 2 against 2.
The teams will freely choose to play either offense or defense.
The teams playing defense will put a basket on their heads.
Their goal is to pick the water balloons from the opposing teams...
instead of squid ink balloons.
The opposing teams will throw the balloons.
If it's water, you'll win the game, but if it's squid ink, you'll lose.
- Gosh, this is hard. - Goodness.
This will be a tournament mission.
On top of the photo hint for the petty thief,
you'll be given a chance to pick...
four members to test their identities.
(They'll be given a chance to pick 4 members to test their identities.)
- 4 members? Gosh. - 4 members?
- One of them will be the thief. - They'll give us yes or no answers.
1 of the 4 will be the thief.
- Seok Jin will be chosen then. - How many are there?
(Tournament bracket: Jae Seok and Ji Hyo versus Kwang Soo and Se Chan)
- Ji Hyo. - Anyway, get Kwang Soo.
- I want to take these shoes off. - By the way,
black water might flow down even if Seok Jin got water.
The black hair spray?
Doesn't it mean he failed? It has to count as a failure.
If that happens, Seok Jin might not advance.
- We'll start. - We're starting.
Okay.
They can just wear raincoats, so only their faces will get wet.
- That's right. That would be funny. - Getting their faces wet is funny.
Now that we saw you guys play...
(It was edited out since it wasn't funny.)
- We realized... That's right. - Our team lost, right?
To be honest,
- getting clothes wet isn't funny. - That's true.
That would be funnier,
but I wonder if Haha would be okay with that.
- I'm okay with that. - Haha is generous, so it's okay.
Besides, he has to be okay with that on his own.
And it's not that important right now.
Leave him alone. He can sort it out alone.
The important thing is that we must catch the shoe thief.
- I forgot about that. - Right.
(I forget about that.)
(What?)
Come on, Seok Jin.
- Stop acting innocent. - That was our mission.
It would've been better if he didn't say that.
- That's not the thief's focus. - Right, right.
- Right. I forgot about that. - Right.
- Let's get them. Got that? - Okay.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo must stay away from the squid ink balloon.)
I'm sure of it. I bet Kwang Soo has the squid ink balloon.
They know which one they're holding.
It has to be him.
(It's time to choose the balloon.)
What do you think about Se Chan's?
Should we go with Se Chan's? Let's go with his.
(Let's go with Se Chan's balloon.)
Yang Se Chan's.
(Yang Se Chan's)
(Surprised)
- Did we start? - Yes.
- We choose Se Chan's. - But we...
- We have to mix... - Se Chan's.
- Don't switch them. - We weren't ready yet.
Hey, we already chose the balloon.
- No, we weren't ready. - Hey.
- We picked Se Chan's. - No, because...
- Hey, we chose Se Chan's. - We didn't switch...
- Wait, wait. - We already made our decision.
- No, we weren't ready yet. - We already said his name.
- We weren't ready then. - We weren't ready.
- Wait. We have to mix them up. - We already said Se Chan's name.
Goodness, those petty thieves.
They're so small-minded.
Gosh, they're so petty.
Aren't they? They should steal some shoes at least, right?
(Aren't they? They should steal some shoes at least, right?)
- What? - Right?
(What? Are you talking to me?)
They should be gutsy enough to steal shoes.
No.
Hey, forget about that.
If you want to win, forget about them.
I must think about my shoes to catch the petty thief.
No, you ought to let that go.
- We're going to go with that. - Bring us new balloons.
- What are you doing? - We'll go with that.
- We'll do it with new ones. - What are you doing?
- This is unbelievable. - No, listen.
Is this just water?
(Changing balloons on the sly)
Shouldn't you check the balloons?
- What if they're both squid ink? - If they're both squid ink,
they have to get the water bomb penalty.
To have a fair match, this is what we're going to do.
Both balloons might be squid ink. After you pick a balloon,
- should they get the other one? - Should we do that?
Why do we have to do that?
I swear. Both balloons aren't squid ink.
- Why would we get the other one? - I swear. Both aren't squid ink.
- Listen up. - Don't come. Stop getting close.
Why didn't you let us go with the one we chose earlier?
- The balloons weren't mixed up. - We weren't ready.
- You should've said, "start". - You should've said it loud.
"Start."
No, listen.
- "Start." See? It was loud. - That's not fair.
- We don't know either. - We don't know.
Is that so?
Se Chan's.
(Lowering right away)
- Kwang Soo's. - Kwang Soo's.
(Oh, no.)
You had to choose on the count of three.
- Choose on the count of three. - Kwang Soo's.
Jae Seok was merely saying his name.
- That's right. Start. - I had the final say in it.
- Kwang Soo's. - Great, Kwang Soo's.
Are you ready now?
They're doing it.
(They hold Kwang Soo's balloon without any trickery.)
I don't know about this. I really don't.
- It's water. It has to be water. - Kwang Soo, we're not ready.
- I'll give you one more chance. - Kwang Soo's.
- Kwang Soo's. - Kwang Soo's.
- Can you give us one more chance? - Kwang Soo's.
- Kwang Soo's. - I'm really going to throw it.
- Yes. - Okay.
- It's water. It's water. - Nice.
(Fine, get the balloons.)
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo successfully figure out the water balloon.)
Why did you make that face?
What do you mean?
They figured it out because you lowered the basket right away.
Gosh, this guy is a mess.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo acquire 1 point.)
Look at the difference in height for the basket. Look.
Se Chan, isn't it too high for you?
(The pair seems off-balance.)
- No towels around your necks? - Se Chan will get the most of it.
- Let's switch places. - Should we wrap our necks?
- What? - Should we wrap our necks?
We're going to start right away.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo go to get their balloons.)
You little runt.
(Jong Kook is wrapping the towel around his neck.)
Gosh, Jong Kook. This must be what it means to have two sides.
He was nicely wrapping the towel around Se Chan's neck...
as he curses at him at the same time.
Gosh, I can't figure him out.
- I can't say anything. He's nice. - Right.
- His actions are nice, - But he says harsh words.
but he said a mean curse word.
- He's sweet and scary. - That's right.
All right.
- Ji Hyo's? - It's Jae Seok's.
- Jae Seok's? - Yes.
Jae Seok's.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan choose Jae Seok's balloon.)
Okay.
Don't switch.
- Gosh. - My gosh.
(Popping)
- Come on! - It popped.
It popped.
(What are you doing?)
- Hey, it just popped. - What will you do now?
- Come on, what was that? - It just popped.
- I didn't pop it. - How will he pay for this?
- It popped. - We'll side with them.
- There's nothing we can do. - That can't happen.
- When will this game end then? - It popped.
- Gosh, this... - You'll let this slide?
- Be careful. - I'll hold it.
- "Be careful"? - Are you serious?
- I guess there was a thorn. - What nonsense.
- Your hands aren't thorny. - There are no thorns here.
I didn't do it.
- Jae Seok, be careful. - We're serious.
- I'm serious. - Promise that you'll be careful.
- Yes, I promise to be careful. - Okay.
What are we going to do? What is this?
- I'm sorry. - Just forgive him.
- I'm sorry. - Forgive him this once.
He was the most surprised.
I was just turning around. I can't believe this happened.
(Gosh, he's playing innocent.)
I can pop yours too.
- I'll explode if you do it again. - Be careful.
They wouldn't switch, right?
- They'll feel conscious of it. - Look.
(Wouldn't it be Jae Seok's?)
- Jae Seok's. - Jae Seok's.
I won't let you slide this time. I clearly warned you.
(It's hard to read Jae Seok and Ji Hyo's faces.)
I'll kick you.
What is it?
- You have no choice. Throw it. - I must throw it.
You can't do it again.
(If it's the squid ink, Jae Seok and Ji Hyo wins.)
(Did Kwang Soo and Se Chan choose the right balloon?)
(The unlucky ones deserve the squid ink.)
- Didn't you guys put on the hood? - Come on.
Why didn't you put on the hood?
(Why didn't you put on the hood?)
They took off the hoods when they were complaining...
and never put them back on.
- Were we supposed to put them on? - Yes.
- We have hoods? - Why would we wear raincoats?
- We do? - Yes.
Why would we wear raincoats otherwise?
Kwang Soo's face...
- His eyebrows are connected. - You look South American.
South American?
You look handsome.
- You do. - Right.
- You should do this all the time. - Why do you look happy?
- You should do this all the time. - You look great.
I like it.
(Will he be the prince of South America?)
- Jae Seok and Ji Hyo... - Okay.
- won a hint about the culprit. - Share it with us.
- You can share it with others. - Show us too.
- Show us. - Show us.
We shouldn't share it with you.
- Let us see it first. - Take a look.
What's this?
(The culprit's ankles)
(It looks like a man.)
(Is the thief among the male members?)
You can share it with others if you want.
Please choose four candidates.
When you choose candidates,
choose those who never went outside...
and Seok Jin.
- You think so? - Then you'll know.
- Don't choose Haha. - Who stayed inside?
- I stayed inside. - I went outside.
(Haha and So Min stayed inside.)
- I stayed inside. - I stayed inside.
- I went outside. - He went outside.
I went to get water.
But Ji Hyo stayed in our sight.
We saw her get water.
- Ji Hyo, me, and So Min. - I was in your sight too.
- I was in your sight too. - That's true.
But we can't trust him.
Why not?
- We just can't. - I...
These four would be good.
Seok Jin has to be included.
- We have to choose him. - We have to.
- Seok Jin, So Min, - Haha.
- Haha, and Ji Hyo. - But...
(Seok Jin, So Min, Haha, and Ji Hyo)
(Is the thief among these 4?)
Who are the four candidates?
- Go up. - Me?
- Of course. - Of course.
- "Me?" - You're...
You're the prime candidate.
- Of course, you should go up. - Gosh, this is frustrating.
The thief...
is...
(Seok Jin is the most suspicious, and the other three aren't.)
(The thief is...)
- Among these four. - Congratulations.
(The thief is among these four.)
- Now we can be... - It's 100 percent.
- I'm 100 percent sure. - Goodbye
(Congratulations. Seok Jin is definitely the thief.)
It's 100 percent.
- Try to suspect the other three. - It's 100 percent.
Exclude me.
- All right. - This is the last advice...
- I can give to you. - I get it.
(Is Seok Jin really the thief?)
Shouldn't we suspect all four candidates?
Not just Seok Jin...
(Everyone is thinking about the result.)
- What are you thinking about? - What?
(What are you thinking about?)
What's on your mind?
I was thinking I should work hard.
He's restless.
- Just return Jong Kook's shoes. - He's immersed in thoughts.
If I was Seok Jin,
I'd tell Jong Kook the truth ask for his forgiveness.
- Me too. - Hey! I'm not the thief!
This has happened before, right?
I deny it, but they don't believe me.
You even came to get the ribs.
- You were giving them to me. - You'd normally...
stay where you are.
You wouldn't come to us.
He doesn't usually move.
He never does.
- This is so stressful. - Seok Jin is definitely the thief.
This is so unfair.
This is happening again.
I'll give you another mission.
It's Three Car Games.
(3 Car Games)
Are we playing games in the car?
If everyone passes...
all three missions,
you'll be given three hints.
- Three? - That's awesome.
If everyone passes the missions?
- I'll prove my innocence. - Okay.
The first mission is the mouth gag game.
- Mouth gag? - Mouth gag?
- Are we putting on mouth gags? - Mouth gag?
Everyone has to blow bubbles while wearing a mouth gag...
within 30 seconds.
That sounds hard.
Gosh, we're playing such a strange game in the car.
We have to wear a bib too?
7 or 8?
One for each.
One for each?
Oh, my goodness.
Everything I say sounds weird, right?
- You sound really weird. - Stop suspecting me.
Stop suspecting me.
"What is a mouth gag?"
Give Seok Jin a break.
- Stop it. - Jong Kook.
We understand you, but you should give him a break.
He keeps saying weird things.
I'm okay.
"What is a mouth gag?"
What do you mean?
Just stay quiet.
(Laughing)
How do you put this on?
(Like this)
You're good at everything.
You're even good at putting on a mouth gag.
- It's too big! - It's too big!
(It's hard to even put on.)
- It's too big! - Let's hurry up.
I'm drooling.
(They'll go from So Min to Se Chan.)
Let's start from So Min. Ready.
(Start)
(So Min succeeds.)
Okay.
It's hard.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
(Fail)
It's not working.
You're stalling.
- You're stalling. - There you go.
- That was intentional, wasn't it? - No.
(Struggling)
- I succeeded, right? - Yes.
(Haha succeeds with 10 seconds left.)
(Blowing)
- There you go. - There you go.
(It's Se Chan's turn with 3 seconds left.)
(If he succeeds, they'll win a hint.)
(Will he succeed?)
Se Chan.
There you go.
(Se Chan.)
(As soon as Jong Kook calls him, he succeeds.)
- Success! - Success!
Is it a success?
It's so funny.
Se Chan was struggling,
but as soon as he heard, "Se Chan",
he succeeded right away.
How did you do that?
Here goes the first hint.
- Hold on. - This is the culprit?
It's a silhouette?
It's an arm under an umbrella.
It's an arm.
(The thief's elbow under a rainbow umbrella)
It looks like Se Chan's arm.
It looks like Se Chan.
Se Chan has a lot of moles on his arm.
- There are no moles in the picture. - No.
Just above the elbow,
there is a black spot.
- Let me see. - Isn't it just dirt?
- I have a mole. - I have a mole too.
Let me see.
(Jong Kook is checking everyone's elbow.)
- Let me see. - Everyone has a mole?
(How does Seok Jin's elbow look?)
- It's him. - It's him.
(It's him.)
(It's me?)
- What did you see? - What?
- What's there? - You have a spot.
What are you talking about?
- Let's just stop. - Goodness.
It's Seok Jin.
(Every piece of evidence points to Seok Jin.)
- I look back... - "I look back?"
What does that mean?
- Don't look back - Don't look back
- Gosh, it's driving me crazy. - Don't
- Regret - Regret
They're framing me.
(Do better next time.)
Let's start the second mission.
It's Random Five Second Talk.
(Random 5 Second Talk)
You'll be given a random question about another member.
You have to give 3 answers within 5 seconds.
- Okay. - Okay.
- It sounds hard. - Can you give us an example?
Let's say the question is "What are Jae Seok's strengths?"...
and I answer, "He is nice. He is a good host."
"He is handsome." Does "He is handsome" not count?
- It could count. - It's too farfetched.
It could count.
- It's too farfetched. - Did you say it's too farfetched?
- It could count. - Then we'd just fail.
Why would we fail with that?
- It's like saying I'm tall. - Exactly.
It should count.
Being handsome is subjective.
You have to give 3 answers within 5 seconds.
Kwang Soo will answer a question about So Min.
Ready, start.
When is So Min prettiest?
Right now, yesterday, and the day before yesterday.
(Right now, yesterday, and the day before yesterday.)
(What?)
(Just say, "Every day.")
- So Min is touched. - That was nice.
When is So Min happiest?
Right now, yesterday, and the day before yesterday.
What?
(Right now, yesterday, and the day before yesterday.)
- What? - Good job.
- It makes sense. - That was clever.
What do you want to give So Min as a gift?
Money, cigarettes...
- What? - Hold on.
He can give her...
whatever he wants.
She doesn't smoke, but...
- All right. - Stop it.
You failed.
(Running Man abides by the regulations.)
- Gosh. - What's wrong?
Gosh. You're too much.
(I'll get you back, Kwang Soo.)
It's Haha's turn now.
You'll answer questions about Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook? - Yes.
Why?
Can't I answer questions about someone easier?
No one is easier than me, you brat.
You're right.
- You brat, good luck. - Start.
What makes Jong Kook smile biggest?
Exercise, a shower after exercise, and food after exercise.
(Exercise, a shower after exercise, and food after exercise.)
Why does Jong Kook visit LA so often?
His girlfriend, his ex-girlfriend,
and his daughter.
His daughter?
(His daughter)
(He has a daughter in LA?)
It's an exclusive! Jong Kook has a daughter!
My daughter?
You have a daughter in the US?
She got into USC.
- Really? - Yes.
She's a good student.
What is Jong Kook most scared of?
His daughter, his girlfriend, and his ex-girlfriend.
(All the answers include his girlfriends and daughter.)
- Success! - Success!
It was perfect.
- It was amazing. - I'm sorry.
- I was just kidding. - It was perfect.
Just kidding.
- I was just doing my best. - Good job.
I didn't know I was a fool for my daughter.
He's a fool for his daughter.
Gosh, I kind of wish I had a daughter now.
(I kind of wish I had a daughter now.)
- Jong Kook. - What do you mean?
People will be searching for "Jong Kook's daughter".
- "A fool for his daughter". - "A fool for his daughter".
I want a daughter.
Maybe he really has one.
- Do you have one? - What are you talking about?
- What if you have one... - Give him his shoes back.
- Give them back. - I don't have his shoes.
- Give them back. - Next question.
- Jae Seok, this is about Seok Jin. - Seok Jin?
It's the problematic guy.
- You're the problematic guy. - Get ready, set, go.
When was Seok Jin most helpful as the oldest member?
(Considering)
- Hold on. - Hey, answer him.
(Fail)
Answer him. Yesterday, today, and the day before yesterday.
Answer him.
My bad. I didn't know you'd start like that.
(I got it wrong from the beginning.)
- What does that mean? - He'll go to the next question.
- Next question. - Let's move on.
Let's go again. Get ready, set, go.
What are Seok Jin's charms as a man?
Tell him.
Confidence, courage, and sense of justice.
This is too hard.
This is harder than an exam.
- Why is this game so hard? - That was too hard.
He said he has a sense of justice.
- I have three. - These questions are hard.
So far, only Haha has succeeded.
- Really? - That was too hard.
- I couldn't even say a word. - Ji Hyo, yours is about Haha.
Haha?
Get ready, set, go.
What are some other jobs that suit Haha?
(What are some other jobs that suit Haha?)
She needs... Hold on.
- She needs a pause. - Hold on.
Hold on. Why is mine so hard?
- How's that hard? - That came out of nowhere.
(There are so many occupations out there.)
Fashion designer, lawyer, and doctor.
I thought this was a practice game. It was that easy.
(She's the worst in quizzes.)
- Seok Jin. - Yes.
Get ready, set, go. What are Jae Seok's habits?
He picks his nose...
He's acting weird. He's so weird.
- He doesn't have habits. - This is weird.
Let's give him a turn at the end.
- That looked so intentional. - No way. He has no habits.
This is the last game.
It's English 3, 6, 9.
(The last mission is English 3, 6, 9.)
I can't speak English. I'm bad.
- 1, 2. - 1, 2, 3.
- 4, 5. - 4, 5.
- 6. - You clap twice on 6.
- We can't even do this in Korean. - We can't.
- This is so hard. - How do you pronounce eight?
- It's "eight". - "Eight".
You also say, "fifteen" and "fifty".
There are some people who can't go beyond that.
I'll be done at 10.
- Really? - We can't even reach 20.
- Let's start with you, Seok Jin. - Okay, let's go this way.
- Is Jae Seok last? - Yes. Let's go.
3, 6, 9. Start.
- 3, 6, 9. - 3, 6, 9.
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
- 5. - 5.
(Six)
- 7. - 7.
- 8. - 8.
(Nine)
10. What was that?
(10. What was that?)
- That was so weird. - Is this all just a show?
- What was that? - What if there are two people?
(Maybe it's Seok Jin and Jong Kook.)
Why would you get English wrong?
No, this is difficult in Korean too. It's more difficult in English.
It might be two people. We have to consider that possibility.
That was weird, Jong Kook.
(He made an unreasonable mistake. Is something going on?)
We failed. Can you give us another chance?
- Do you want one last chance? - Yes.
- We'll switch the order. - Let's go the opposite way.
- Okay. - This is easy.
- Start. - Start.
- 3, 6, 9. - 3, 6, 9.
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
- 5. - 5.
- 7. - 7.
- 8. - 8.
- It's 8. - It's 8.
(Clapping)
- Stop it. - It's eight.
- This is all just a show. - What was that?
I pronounce English the proper way,
so I got confused.
- That was so obvious. - Jong Kook.
He might have plotted something with Seok Jin.
But there's no motive.
- Why not? Tricking the others. - What's the motive?
Me?
- Is that possible? - When you plot something,
there's always an assistant.
- Because people can get suspicious. - To confuse people.
That doesn't make me feel good. I'm not an assistant.
- I mean you have roles. - Don't you know me?
- Your role today. - Seok Jin,
it's not because you want to do it.
- I'm not an assistant. - You're the worker.
Let's ask Jong Kook to go on the platform.
- Me? - We have to try it.
- Me? Why me? - That was so weird.
- You're weird too. - We're suspecting you.
I wasn't sure before, but I'm pretty certain now.
Go ahead. I don't care.
(Go ahead. I don't care.)
- Don't say that. - I have nothing to say.
Don't say that. We're going to try it. Please.
- Go ahead. - "Go ahead."
"I don't care."
(He copies Jong Kook.)
- You sound similar to him. - Oh, gosh.
Did I say it like that?
Let's do an impression of him. "Go ahead."
- "Go ahead." - "I don't care."
(What are the identities of these two suspects?)
- This is so pretty. - Where are we?
It's a garden. It's pretty.
- We haven't been here before. - This is pretty.
- Is this it? - It's pretty.
What is this?
What's wrong with these shoes? My feet are getting wet.
- Those are water shoes. - Are they?
(It's for going in the water.)
My feet are getting soaked. Goodness.
- Seok Jin, - These shoes.
why did you wear socks with water shoes?
- How can you be funny with shoes? - My feet are getting soaked.
Stop stealing shoes and stop being funny with shoes.
- Oh, gosh. - There's a reason.
He's ready to take the water bomb penalty.
- He's really funny these days. - I agree.
- Oh, gosh. - He's humorous using everything.
He makes people laugh with the most random things.
- He planned it ahead of time. - He's incredible.
Wear the shoes you stole from me.
(If your feet are soaked, wear the shoes you stole from me.)
Wear those.
- I have many pairs at home. - You were so obvious.
- Gosh. - Say it if you're jealous.
Once his feet get soaked, he'll disappear.
He'll go where he hid Jong Kook's shoes.
This mission is called Shoe Bag Toss.
(Shoe Bag Toss)
The person who throws the bag farthest will get a hint.
- Okay. - I see.
The winner gets two hints.
- That's great. - Okay.
You have all eight items in your bags right now,
so they're very heavy.
You'll be able to throw them far once they become lighter.
Here's your chance to make your bags lighter.
You'll put these pants on and dance to the music.
Once I blow the whistle, you have to stick the words...
that are spelled correctly on your butt. We'll let you...
take out the items that are spelled right.
- Okay. - Let's get the hints.
- All right. Music. - There's a dumbbell.
- It can't be too light. - Cue the music.
(Up and down)
(So Min looks at the words while doing her fancy footwork.)
So Min, show them.
(Shake it.)
(Running Man is in love with So Min's dance.)
This is my favorite move.
That's not how you do it.
(They must find the words that are spelled correctly.)
So Min, spread them out.
It changed.
I want to dance like Bo Ra.
- She's so good. - This.
(Bo Ra's dance heated up Running Man.)
(Bo Ra's dance?)
Isn't this it?
(She does a wave.)
That wasn't it.
It's this.
(Bo Ra didn't do that, but he's close.)
(Bo Ra's dance is easy.)
Twerking.
- That's so dirty. - What are you doing?
(Stop twerking.)
(He gets punished with a kick.)
Twerking.
(While everybody is dancing, Seok Jin...)
(searches for the words and finds "beans".)
(He finds it and dances on it.)
(I'll hide it and stick it on myself.)
(Whistle)
(Pushing)
(Seok Jin gets flung away.)
(They are after "beans" too.)
- 10, 9, 8, - That was mine.
- 7, 6... - That was mine.
- I can't give up rice. - Five,
- 4, 3, - Where is it?
- 2, 1. - I can't give up rice.
(It's over.)
It's good.
- It's all good. - I got nothing.
- I got nothing. - I got rice.
Seok Jin was stepping on it, so I was watching him.
- You pushed me. - Let's go.
Let's check them.
"Gam". "Ssyal". "Sal".
- You have none. Move. - I have none?
- Move, thief. - Me.
(Come on.)
- You have "beans". - I got one.
- "Billiard balls". - "Slippers".
- Slippers. - Billiard balls.
"Dumbbells".
You have "beans".
You have "dumbbells" too. "Seaweed".
Haha got so many.
(He got the most.)
- Okay! - We have the results.
- Jae Seok, you can take out rice. - That's it?
- That was good though. It's 3kg. - You took out a lot. It's heavy.
- Kwang Soo, you took out beans. - Rice.
- I took out rice too. - You did?
- No, it's just beans. - When?
- It was "ssom". Was it "sap"? - It was "sap".
You didn't get rice.
Did you get rice?
- Yes. - He didn't.
- No. - He didn't get it.
Everybody is saying no, but only you're saying yes.
Maybe it was somebody else's.
- That could be. - Is this a prank?
(He thinks it's unfair.)
It's not.
Nobody saw it?
Pranks are only for stars.
(He's kidding.)
Why would you say that?
What's wrong?
Someone might play a prank on me.
(Actually Kwang Soo...)
- Kwang Soo. - He has a lot.
- He has rice. - He has rice.
(He did have rice.)
- Rice. - Okay.
Is it really?
I got rid of it.
Kwang Soo got rid of it.
Kwang Soo.
- What? - Don't cry.
(He gets teary.)
Tell us if you got rid of it.
- Kwang Soo really got rid of it. - Take it out then.
He really did. He's crying.
He's about to cry.
- Did you get rid of rice? - Are you sure?
I definitely did, but everyone denies it.
I have no idea now.
- He really got rid of it. - I definitely did.
- It was beans. - We'll count it.
We'll take out rice and beans for Kwang Soo.
Forget it.
(He's upset.)
If he didn't get rid of it, he's cheating.
You can punish him next week.
You have beans, so make yourself some rice with beans.
(Eat some rice with beans if you're lying.)
If...
Will you make a big deal out of it?
- He already is. - Will you?
Let's say we took rice out for Kwang Soo.
If we find out next week that Kwang Soo didn't get rid of rice,
make him carry 20kg of rice next week.
- Let's do that. - Will you do it or not?
I give up.
Why?
If not, give 20kg of rice to every staff member.
- Why would I do that? - Do it.
Why would I do that all of a sudden?
- Next week... - You should do that.
- Take out rice, beans, and weights. - Take them out.
- You ruined everyone's mood now. - I'm sorry.
(You ruined everyone's mood.)
(Did I?)
- I'm sorry. - What have you done?
I'm sorry.
Whether you got rid of rice or not isn't important.
Look at all the staff members.
I'm sorry.
(He apologizes.)
(Teasing Kwang Soo is fun.)
- You can do it. - We'll do better.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(He's speechless.)
- I'm sorry. - You can do it.
- We'll do better. - Let's go.
Let's wrap it up. Take out rice from Kwang Soo.
In that case, don't take it out.
- Take it out. - Don't take out the rice.
Just take it out.
We'll make him carry it.
That's right. It would be funny.
(Who got rid of what)
- Do we throw it here? - Yes.
It looks light.
This will be possible.
(It's time to throw their shoe bag.)
- It's extremely heavy. - Mine is light.
- It's quite heavy. - It's extremely heavy.
This is perfect.
I can't throw this.
Who will start?
Let's start with the one with the heaviest bag.
Mine is the heaviest.
Start with Seok Jin.
- May I throw it like this? - Yes.
- You can throw it however you want. - It might go farther if it's heavy.
Throw it like this.
Like that?
(It must stay within the left line.)
If you think about it,
we're all suffering because of Seok Jin's sticky fingers.
(He blames Seok Jin again.)
Hey, it isn't me.
What if he has shoes inside his bag?
No way.
Shall I start?
You only get once chance.
Move forward.
You got it.
(Throwing)
(He throws it quite well.)
It went far.
(It was a nice throw.)
- It didn't make a difference. - Next is So Min.
(Seok Jin's record is 6m.)
It's so heavy.
Look at Se Chan.
(It's Haha's turn who has the lightest bag.)
Haha's bag is light.
(He's full of confidence.)
It's Bruce Lee.
His bag is so light.
It's perfect to throw.
He'll throw it far.
He has potential.
(He goes for first place that will give him two hints.)
(Where far will Haha's bag travel?)
(Flying)
- Out. - It's out.
(It's so light that it goes out.)
(How did it go that far?)
It's out.
(He places last because his bag goes too far.)
- Is it out? - Out.
You were in first place.
(Haha is eliminated.)
- Does the first place get hints? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo throws his bag without beans or rice.)
It'd be funny if he hits his face with it.
I know.
(It'd be funny if he hits his face with it.)
- He almost got tempted. - What?
He got tempted.
He might hit himself while swinging it.
- Here I go. - Okay.
(After the controversy over rice...)
You can do it, Kwang Soo.
(He goes for 2 hints.)
(It flies off lightly without rice.)
Goodness.
(It travels far.)
(Currently, he's the winner.)
- Did he get rid of rice? - Did he really get rid of rice?
Do you have to win?
It's for the hint.
Jong Kook's bag will go far.
I don't know how I should throw it.
(They suspect that Jong Kook is putting on a show.)
(If it's true, he'll work hard to keep the hints to himself.)
(He becomes the winner without breaking a sweat.)
(He throws a 5kg bag the farthest.)
This isn't fun.
(Come on.)
Come on.
- "This isn't fun"? - It isn't fun at all.
I'm the winner.
- What? - Why isn't it fun?
- It isn't fun at all. - What do you mean?
- It went far. - It's not fun.
It was thrown like Thor's hammer.
Put back the rice in my bag.
Jong Kook is the winner, and he gets the hints.
May I see it?
- No. - I'll discuss with you.
- I'll discuss with you. - Let me look at it first.
- Let me see it. - Share it with us.
This is...
My goodness.
(The ankles of the thief who's leaving the restaurant)
Pull up your pants. Mine are thick.
- Wait, like this? - Pull down the socks.
Seok Jin's ankles are thin.
- Are they thin? - Look.
Wait, there's no hair on the legs.
- Wait. - It's Seok Jin.
- I got him. - I have a lot of hair.
What do you mean I have no hair?
- I have a lot of hair. - He doesn't.
- I have a lot of hair. Look. - He doesn't.
He has no hair at all.
(His leg is clean without any hair.)
(There's no hair at all.)
I thought it was the leg of a newborn.
- We got him. - We caught the thief.
He has no hair.
Get his water bomb penalty ready.
Look at my hair.
(Isn't this a lot?)
It's Seok Jin.
Poor Seok Jin.
Why did you do it?
Even you'll find it strange.
Isn't it like looking at the mirror?
Let me see it.
- It's definitely Seok Jin. - It's not me.
Here's your second hint.
(The petty thief's hand holding a shoe)
Who is that?
Whose hand is that?
(He shares the hint with everyone.)
It's definitely a man.
- It's not a woman. - It's definitely a man.
You never know, so check the women.
It's definitely a man's hand.
Ji Hyo has manly hands.
It looks like a man's hand.
- Let me see. - Look at Ji Hyo's hand.
(The shape is similar, but her hand is thinner.)
Her hand is too thin.
- Let's see So Min's hand. - It's a man's hand.
It looks like hers.
- No, it's not hers. - It's not her either.
- This is... - It depends on the angle.
It's hard to tell whether it's a man or a woman.
- It's him. - Give it to him.
(It's Seok Jin.)
(Jong Kook suspects Seok Jin again.)
(It's definitely suspicious now.)
(After losing his shoes, he only suspects Seok Jin.)
(Is it a plot between the two of them?)
- It looks similar to his. - The elbow would make it easy.
Let's go to the place where the last hint is.
It's the last hint.
It's the last mission.
- It's a punching machine. - Punching machine?
Does it give a lot of advantage to Jong Kook?
Isn't this mission for Jong Kook?
- Come on. - Jong Kook is good at it.
Can we do this later?
I'd like to punch the thief when we find him.
(He wants to punch the thief instead of the machine.)
- That means... - Punch the face?
Won't the water bomb penalty be enough?
Why are we using that machine now?
- You know this, right? - What?
- The culprit is around the scene. - Right.
Seok Jin has been next to Jong Kook all day.
- He's been next to me all day. - That's true.
(They've been next to each other since this morning.)
I'll share the hint.
This is the final mission...
in which you can win a determining hint.
Here are the rules for Life is One Shot.
If you know the answer to the question,
you get to hit the punching machine.
The number of the 100th digit of your punching score...
will be your answer.
- What? - It's hard to understand.
Let's say your score was 350 points.
Then your answer will be choice number three.
(The answer is choice number 3.)
- I see. - You have to punch well.
Punching as hard as possible isn't the answer.
- You have to try. - We never know.
You lose your chance when your answer is wrong.
The winner gets two hints.
(The winner gets 2 hints.)
2nd, 3rd, and 4th place get one hint.
This is important.
How many choices are there?
Won't the answers be the last numbers?
I can score from 700 to 800 points.
Why are you posing like that?
- Did you hurt your wrist? - No.
- Yes? - Did you hurt yourself?
Those who are good at punching...
(This is how they pose.)
- What? - What?
People like me throw short punches.
Why are you hiding it?
You seem scared because you've never done it.
The choices start from number three.
The question is easy. It's easily seen in everyday life.
In the word tangsuyuk,
what does tang mean?
What does tang mean?
Tang.
Number three, fried.
- I know. - I know.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan raise their hand.)
- May I try it right away? - Yes.
- It means fried. - Fried.
Can't we hear the rest?
The score must be in the 300s.
- Is it tang? - Yes.
Press the button.
(He presses the start button.)
(Why isn't it moving?)
- Jae Seok. - Jae Seok.
- You have to punch it. - Haven't you done it before?
He's never played with the punching machine.
This is a speaker.
- This is a speaker. - He's such an amateur.
Why did you hit the speaker?
- It's embarrassing that... - You're out.
- I'm competing with you. - There's the button.
For punchers like me...
Does it have to be a three-digit number?
- It has to be in the 300s. - In the 300s.
It plays music.
That's right.
(He dances to the music.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(He does the popular So Min's dance.)
Dance with him.
I'm addicted to So Min's dance.
(So Min's dance is addicting.)
I can't bear to watch him. It's terrible.
The score should be in the 300s.
(He gives a try.)
(Jae Seok's answer is number 3.)
(Jae Seok's score should be in the 300s.)
That's too weak.
It's 300 points.
(His score goes into the 300s.)
- It was too strong. - It went over.
It's going over 600 points.
(His score is 728 points.)
- His score is 728 points. - It came out to be 728 points?
- It's 728 points. - Did I score that high?
No way.
It's hard to get a score in the 300s.
Fail.
Let's hear all the options.
Here are the options.
- Number three, "to fry". - Okay.
Number four, "to look like a gun".
Number five, "to dip in the sauce".
Number six, "thick sauce".
Number seven, "soup".
(Everything makes sense.)
Number eight, "sweet".
(I know.)
So Min.
So Min, which number?
- Number seven. - What was number seven?
- "Soup". - "Soup"?
Number seven.
(So Min aims for a score in the 700s.)
(Punch)
That was strong.
- I hope it goes over 700 points. - It'll be in the 500s.
- It's over 700 points. - It's still going up.
It's perfect.
- It's over 700 points. - It's perfect.
(740 points)
It's 740 points. It must be the right answer.
Number seven, "soup".
(Is "soup" the right answer?)
- Me. - It's wrong?
It must be number eight.
You shouldn't punch it too hard.
- It'll go over 900 points. - You should punch it hard.
Number eight, "sweet".
- Even So Min went over 700 points. - Number eight, "sweet".
(Haha aims for a score in the 800s.)
That was too strong.
(His punch was very strong.)
- It was too strong. - No.
- It'll be too high. - No.
His punch was...
(It can't go over a score in the 800s.)
It's hard to go over 800 points.
We won't be able to give the right answer.
- It has to be stronger. - We can't.
He did his best.
His punch is so weak.
It's so weak.
Number eight, "sweet".
You should punch it even harder.
Okay.
That was nice. He definitely succeeded.
(Se Chan punches it as hard as he can.)
- You did a good job. - I hope it'll go over 800 points.
I hope it goes over 900 points.
It's in the 800s.
842 points.
(His score is in the 800s.)
- Okay. - What was your answer?
Number eight, "sweet".
(Is "sweet" the right answer?)
Okay!
It means "sweet"?
You have to punch it the right way too.
It was "sweet".
You need to punch it hard.
It was number eight.
(Who will win the hint?)
Here goes the second question.
"This" can include a lot more information than a barcode.
It's a two-dimensional matrix code...
and called QR code.
QR stands for "something response".
- Quantity. - What does Q stand for?
Quan.
Number three, "question".
Number four, "quiet".
Number five, "quick".
Number six, "quantity".
Number seven, "quarter".
Number eight, "quality".
- Number nine, "quest". - It must be "quality".
- It must be number 9. - Number 9, "quest".
- It's number nine. - "Quest"?
But we can't go over 900 points.
Number nine, "quest".
It's definitely number nine.
They must want us to get more than 900 points.
Okay.
Can I use my legs?
- It doesn't matter. - Which number?
- It doesn't matter? - You're going to kick it?
You'll hurt yourself. Just use your fist.
(Stop being ridiculous.)
I don't want you to hurt yourself again.
He keeps acting up.
With a flying knee...
You almost hit your own head.
Gosh.
Can I do a turning kick?
- Gosh. Stop being absurd. - That's absurd.
- You'll hurt yourself. - Absurd?
You'll hurt yourself. Calm down.
I'll do this.
All right.
- Whatever. - Let me show you.
Let's do something sitting down next week.
(To get 900 points, Jae Seok prepares to do a knee kick.)
(How strong will it be?)
(Moaning)
Gosh. What was that?
(The results are just what everyone was expecting.)
- What did you do? - What was that?
- What was that? - What did you do?
A man should be able to go over 900 points. It's 634 points.
(He fails with 634 points.)
Fail.
It's number nine.
Are you sure it's number nine?
- It's number nine. - "Quest response"...
- makes sense. - We didn't have number nine before.
You should analyze the question.
"Quantity" sounds cool.
- It sounds cool. - I want to try "quick".
(Practicing)
(Seok Jin is doing his best.)
Look what Seok Jin is doing.
(Look what Seok Jin is doing.)
What does "quantity" mean?
Why isn't anyone watching Seok Jin?
(Seok Jin pretends to be okay.)
I hope some cameras are shooting me.
(Seok Jin is ready to aim for 900 points.)
It's better to use your elbow.
(He almost missed it.)
Gosh.
- I feel sorry for you. - Please be careful.
You'll hurt your shoulders.
(Seok Jin fails with 592 points.)
- Which number? - I want to try "quantity".
- Go for it. - Try it.
Number six.
- No. Number nine. - Like a man.
- It must be number 9. - Number 9, "quest".
- You have to go for it. - You should go for it regardless.
Of course.
Gosh, stop being ridiculous.
(What are you doing?)
You should push it.
Are you going to use that hand?
I've seen this a lot since my school days.
Bad fighters try many different positions.
- Like this. - Good fighters...
- Run from behind. - Good fighters...
like Jong Kook need only one position.
(Good fighters need only one position.)
Here we go.
Gosh, you must've gotten beaten up a lot.
- That was nice. - That was strong.
(He punched hard.)
- That was strong. - That was strong.
700? 800?
- 817 points. - Even though it was that hard?
- Should we push it harder? - It's so hard.
No. You just have to punch it hard.
Jong Kook.
(It's finally his turn.)
I'll try number nine.
Number nine...
It'd be funny if he fails.
- That'd feel so good. - Right.
You have a point.
Is that how you do it?
Aren't you going to hold your hand with the other hand?
- No. - Why...
Why are you doing that?
Use your both hands.
- Leave me alone. - That's how you do it.
- What? - Be careful.
Be careful.
His punch would knock you out.
(He aims for 900 points with only 1 hand.)
(Will his fist get a score in the 900s?)
(Punch)
- Gosh. - Your arm.
I'm okay.
(He hit it a bit low.)
(The door of the machine opens up.)
- It was hit a bit low. - I'm okay.
(His score is...)
It didn't go over 900 points.
(He fails with 834 points.)
(Even Jong Kook failed to go over 900 points.)
It's okay.
- Is it my turn? - Yes.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
I choose number five.
- Number five. - "Quick".
It's the only word you know.
(What did he say?)
"Quick service".
I know what it means too. It means fast.
It's not like that.
The code is supposed to be quick.
- She has a point. - It makes sense.
- Number five... - I think it'll be fine.
It'll be in the 500s.
- It's too high. - It's 650 points.
This machine is weird.
Don't you use the word "quest"...
when you play games?
Move.
What are you doing?
(What are you doing?)
- What? - Do you want to try?
What?
- Get lost. - What?
- Who are you? - You brat.
- What? - Gosh.
Get out of my way.
- Move. - Move.
Gosh, these cowards.
Move.
(Cotton fist versus honey fist)
My answer is...
Choose number nine if you're a man.
- Number five, "quick". - Hey.
- You're so low. - I was going to choose it anyway.
- I was going to choose it. - Okay.
I was debating between number 5 and number 9.
- I was going to choose it. - Try it.
(Will Kwang Soo get a score in the 500s?)
- That was too weak. - It'll be in the 500s.
- It's too weak. - It'll be enough.
It was that weak before too. Look at that.
- Okay. - 507 points. Number 5, "quick".
(Number 5, "quick")
Number five, "quick".
Okay!
(Correct)
- See? - It was right.
How did you know?
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo was right.)
- It's supposed to be quick. - That's right.
- It's quick. - QR codes are fast.
I can't believe it.
Here goes the next question.
One of the most famous 19th-century German philosophers,
Friedrich Nietzsche, said this once.
Friedrich.
"Marriage is a long 'This'".
- Okay. - What is "This"?
Seok Jin is a marriage expert.
I'm an expert.
I think I know.
What are you doing?
Hold on.
Number 3, "conversation". Number 4, "voyage".
Number 7, "sigh". Number 8, "fight".
- I've heard about it. - "Grave" isn't one of the answers?
(Why isn't "grave" one of the answers?)
- Why is it a grave? - Seok Jin.
What do you mean?
(There should be "grave".)
It's usually among the possible answers, but it's missing.
I know this right away.
- Move over. - Why is he at the front?
(I'm first.)
- I lined up. - I was here first.
- Why does he keep cutting? - What was that?
I lined up.
Move over when I tell you nicely.
I'm going to do my move.
Hey, Protruding Lips. Move.
(You're being noisy.)
(Let's see. Did you say, "Protruding Lips"?)
Move over when I tell you nicely.
I'd rather not use my fist.
(Look at these people.)
Come if you want to fight.
(Come if you want to fight.)
So Min, go.
(So Min is enough. She's in the same weight division.)
(Is it just you?)
Hold on. Sir.
(Or were you looking for me?)
- Not you, sir. - You told me to come out.
- Not you. - My elbows.
- What are you doing? - Me too.
If those two fight, I'll let my nephew join in.
He's two right now. I want to let him fight.
(Once he starts walking, it's doable.)
- My nephew... - Stop it.
- I suggest my mom. - Stop it.
(Jae Seok gets moved to the end.)
"Sigh" seems likely too.
It's "sigh" or "fight". It can't be number six.
(He's certain.)
- I think it's "conversation". - It's a paradise,
but it doesn't last long. It is paradise.
- Seok Jin, is it temporary? - Yes.
- It doesn't last. - When is it a paradise?
- It doesn't last. - When does it end?
There are moments in the middle.
- That's right. - How can you live without them?
- It's like a desert in the oasis. - That's true.
(It's like a desert in the oasis.)
- I mean an oasis... - What did you say?
(It's an oasis in the desert.)
- What did you say? - It's an oasis in the desert.
- I think it's "conversation". - It's a rest station on a highway.
There are moments of paradise in between.
I think it's "conversation". Hold on.
Why is he here?
(Why is he here?)
(Didn't he get caught cutting the line and had to move?)
I thought I was mistaken.
(He got caught cutting in 3 minutes ago.)
(He moved back slowly.)
Number four. I thought it was "voyage".
(He slipped in halfway.)
(Great. That was smooth.)
Hey, why are you standing here?
I'm always in front of Seok Jin.
- Why? Move back. - Come here.
- I... - Why are you standing there?
Seok Jin was always behind me.
- You can't do that. - That was earlier.
You two should move back then.
- Oh, gosh. What are you doing? - Why me?
- He's always behind me. - Gosh.
- That was weird. He was here. - Why?
- This is weird. - Kwang Soo.
- Answer. Number seven, "sigh". - "Sigh".
You have to get 700 points. It has to be strong.
(Punching)
- That's enough. You'll get it. - You'll get over 700 points.
- It's 800. - Is it?
- Move. - You have no excuse, right?
Goodness. It feels good though.
(He's happy he got over 800 points.)
Number three, "conversation".
(Friedrich Nietzsche said this once. "Marriage is a long 'This'".)
That's good. It will start with three.
(So Min is weak, so she aims for 300 points.)
Number three?
Number three, "conversation".
"Marriage is a long conversation."
It's wrong.
(It's correct.)
It's right.
- Do you have so much to say? - I was at the end.
You talk it out and love each other.
There's not much to talk about.
From the fifth year, you don't talk much.
That's odd. Long conversations?
("Marriage is a long conversation." So Min takes 1 point.)
- Here's the last question. - Okay.
The Chinese character "Soo" is made up of three components.
- What does it mean? - Three components?
Number three, "rock-paper-scissors".
Number four, "let's go".
Number five, "collaboration".
Number 6, "division of labor". Number 7, "love triangle".
Number 8, "pickpocketing". Number 9, "gloves".
(What does the Chinese character "Soo" mean?)
It's number three, "rock-paper-scissors".
"Rock-paper-scissors".
(Tapping)
(The machine didn't know it was punched.)
- I didn't do it. - You did.
- Move. - Move.
You did it.
Number three is not easy.
Doesn't number five sound okay? "Collaboration"?
Number five, "collaboration".
(Punching)
- Was it too hard? - That was too weak.
- He got it. - 547 points.
- "Collaboration". - How's this possible?
Your answer is "collaboration".
- It's wrong. - Oh, gosh.
- I... - That wasn't it.
(Oh, gosh.)
Why do you sound so sad?
- You guessed anyways. - What do you mean?
Jae Seok gets it wrong every time,
and he always gets sad. I find it funny.
He's always like, "That wasn't it."
He tricks me every time. I feel like he knows.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
I'll go with number four, "let's go".
(He hesitated.)
- "Let's go"? - It can't be.
That's farfetched.
- That doesn't sound right. - Hey.
It's kind of tricky.
He's so dumb.
I wasn't going to say this.
- That wasn't nice. - I'm sorry.
- I hesitated too. - I'm sorry.
They made it 2,000 years ago. Will they say,
"let's go"?
(Let's go.)
What's that?
(Teasing)
China took on English early.
Hey, you never know.
Maybe it means something different.
I think it's "rock-paper-scissors".
I think Seok Jin...
- never got a question right. - It's important to try.
- True. - He's positive.
- He's so positive. - He turned very positive.
- Number four, "let's go". - It might mean something.
I'll go.
- It's too weak. - He got it.
It's over 500. I did this, yet it's over 500 points.
- You have to hit it. - That didn't work.
Punch it. It's "rock-paper-scissors".
Answer. Number four, "let's go".
Wait. You said I was dumb.
- You said I was dumb. - Jong Kook said it might be right.
You're so funny. You said I was dumb.
That's not nice. You said I was dumb.
It's not "let's go", but it probably means that.
I didn't think about that.
Number four, "let's go".
(Kwang Soo wants a score in the 400s.)
This won't work.
- He got it. - Okay. It's 417 points.
(He tries answer number 4 with 417 points.)
If this is the answer, I'd be shocked.
Number four, "let's go".
(Will Kwang Soo steal the answer again?)
- It's wrong. Think about it. - No way.
You're so dumb.
You're so dumb. Number four, "let's go"?
- Maybe it's something similar. - You're so dumb.
- How dumb. - Gosh, Jong Kook said it could be.
How dumb.
Is Seok Jin supposed to be there?
(What?)
(Seok Jin cuts in the line and gets caught.)
(He's shameless.)
- What are you doing here? - Jae Seok is always in front of me.
(He's confident.)
- Move. - Move, both of you.
- You're not there. - What are you talking about?
- Move. What are you doing there? - What's wrong?
- Move. - He's ridiculous.
- Seok Jin. - He's right.
- He's always behind me. - It was So Min.
Right. I forgot too. That was so natural.
What's wrong? Jae Seok is always before me.
It's "gloves" or "rock-paper-scissors".
Wait. Is he supposed to be there?
(Is this his turn?)
Is he supposed to be there?
(He stood in line, and it's finally his turn.)
- Is this right? - I'm not sure.
What are you talking about?
- Move. - Move.
- I don't know. Move. - Hey! You're crazy.
- Why are you not saying anything? - It's So Min's turn.
- I waited. - He was before me.
I stood in line. So Min.
I stood in line and got here, right?
- I don't remember. - Move.
(I don't remember.)
(Move back, old man.)
- Move. - This is right.
(I don't remember anything.)
- My gosh. - This is right.
- You have to move. - I'm speechless.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin reunite at the back of the line.)
- Ji Hyo mentioned something. - Try "love triangle".
It might be "pickpocketing" because you use hands.
There are many "hands" in the character.
It could be "pickpocketing".
I'll go with number eight, "pickpocketing".
- You'll get it. - He got it.
- Okay, that's good. It's 822. - 822 points.
Number eight, "pickpocketing".
If Se Chan is right, he wins.
There was no pickpocketing in the old days.
- No, that's not it. - It makes sense.
Okay!
(Number 8, "pickpocketing" is correct.)
(It was "pickpocketing"?)
- See? - Thank you, Ji Hyo.
You use your hands, so it's "pickpocketing"?
- She got all the questions right. - She did.
- She told me. - She's the queen of quizzes.
- She's the queen. - She is.
Ji Hyo.
(Thank you, Ji Hyo.)
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, he wins with two points.)
Se Chan got two questions right, so he wins.
He'll take two hints.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo,
So Min, you got one question right. Please come forward.
- There's something for us too. - There must be.
- Maybe we get 1 hint. - I get 2.
Oh, gosh.
(1st and 2nd place get to see the 1st hint.)
- It's a hand. - It's a female.
- It's a female. - It's a woman's hand?
- That's right. - It's a woman's hand.
There's something here.
There's something on the wrist.
(Is the thief one of the ladies?)
- There's something. - Let's see, So Min.
- So Min. - She didn't want to show me.
Oh, dear. It's the same.
- It's her. - Is it her?
It has to be her.
(They start thinking she's the thief.)
It's her.
- It's not me. - Did we test her earlier?
- Let me see. - We did.
- Let's see. - It's So Min.
That's why she gave me a flower.
Is it So Min?
(Kwang Soo is surprised by something.)
It must be her.
Is it you?
- Our signatures were on the wall. - What?
- Our signatures are attached. - I know. Hurry.
("Our signatures"?)
(At a cafe near the opening site an hour before the shoot)
(Someone tall approaches one hour before the shoot.)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Is it Kwang Soo?)
There's a reason why we called you earlier.
You'll play an important role today.
You'll be the petty thief.
I like that it's an important role,
but what kind of name is that?
Before I tell you a hidden rule,
there's a member who will accompany you.
Is it a guest?
(Is there a guest?)
(Another petty thief comes in.)
Hello.
(The second petty thief is Se Chan.)
- Hello. - I'm not alone.
What? Why are you here?
It could be nerve-racking if I were alone,
but I'm confident with another person.
- Is it the two of us? - We're petty thieves.
Really?
Being a petty thief doesn't fit me.
- I steal big things. - I don't think...
the title is important.
(They resemble the thieves from "Home Alone".)
What's going on?
- What? - What?
- Hello. - Hello, Jae Seok.
What brings you here?
- Jae Seok, you shouldn't be here. - What?
He seems like a petty thief.
I think all of us are.
Are all of us thieves?
Now I understand. All the pieces are coming together.
We don't have time.
So Min, what are you doing?
(All 7 members are petty thieves.)
The official rule is...
catching the petty thief.
This is a special prepared for those...
who couldn't defeat Jong Kook no matter what.
It's 7 against 1, Catch Kim Jong Kook.
- That's offensive. - It's offensive.
- That's offensive. - It's offensive. It's 7 against 1.
- 7 against 1 is too much. - I know.
I wouldn't feel good even if we won.
You're looking down on us.
- Winning won't worth anything. - It'd be obvious.
All of you must hide the fact that you're thieves.
During the final vote, only Jong Kook's vote will be effective.
Unless Jong Kook figures all of you out,
Jong Kook will get the water bomb penalty.
You'll get a pair of shoes with a design of your choice.
A design of our choice?
It'd be funny to see Jong Kook get the water bomb penalty.
However, if Jong Kook figures it out,
only Jong Kook will get a new pair of shoes.
All of you will get the water bomb penalty.
- One will be flogged by Jong Kook. - Flogged?
We have to make Jong Kook like us.
- We already chose our leader. - Who?
It's Seok Jin.
- He's the eldest. - He is.
- It's obvious. - Me?
What you must steal is Jong Kook's shoes.
- What? - What?
His shoes?
As soon as we start the show,
you will enjoy a meal together.
While you're eating, steal Jong Kook's shoes.
Hide the shoes in the assigned vehicle without being caught.
- Are we a team? - Yes.
Isn't that too easy?
However, you must steal 1 by 1 in a relay.
(They must steal in a relay.)
One person picks up Jong Kook's shoes from the floor.
Then he puts them on the top shelf.
The next person moves them one shelf down.
The last person moves them to the vehicle.
(The seventh person moves the shoes to the car.)
- We'll definitely be caught. - Definitely.
We'll be caught from the start.
Jong Kook will pressure us.
Keep a poker face.
You'd better be careful, Seok Jin.
Gosh, I'm already stressed out.
Get ready for an additional shoot.
We'll be caught during the opening.
(The hidden mission starts.)
- What's this? - Is it a restaurant?
We usually open the show in the yard. This is refreshing.
I'll put your shoes up here.
Thank you.
(He suspects nothing.)
Put them here.
(Haha puts his shoes on the top shelf.)
(So Min moves them one shelf down.)
There's no water. I'll bring some.
I'll bring some water.
(Ji Hyo successfully moves them down.)
Does anyone want more rice?
- I do. - Give it to me.
- Excuse me. - Just a little.
(The fourth member, Se Chan succeeds.)
(The 5th and 6th petty thieves succeed.)
(I think we'll easily succeed.)
(Only Seok Jin remains.)
- Is there nurungji? - Ask.
Tell me to go when I call the waitress.
- Is there nurungji? - Really? Thank you.
Go get it, Seok Jin.
Wait.
(He looks for the waitress while pretending to be angry.)
(Why is he getting nurungji all of a sudden?)
Am I the last one?
Where's the car?
(Seok Jin is excited to be the last thief.)
Am I the last?
When did the others go?
I didn't know that I was the last one.
Do I put them here?
(The petty thieves succeed in stealing his shoes.)
(The petty thieves' fight for hints starts.)
(What does the photo of the ankles really mean?)
(Whose ankles are these?)
(It's the eldest petty thief, Seok Jin.)
(There's another big secret.)
(The other shoes indicate that there are six other thieves.)
(Whose elbow is it under the umbrella?)
(It's Se Chan.)
(7 colors indicate 7 petty thieves.)
(Who's holding the white shoe?)
(It's Kwang Soo.)
(These indicate six other thieves.)
(Whose female hand is it that is signing?)
(It's Ji Hyo.)
(7 frames of signature indicate 7 thieves.)
(Jong Kook sees the signature hint.)
Gosh, So Min. Give it to me.
- Our signatures are attached. - What?
- Our signatures are attached. - I know.
(What should we do?)
Why are you crumpling it up? Why are you trying to eat it?
It must be So Min.
(Is So Min also a petty thief?)
- Let me see your foot. - I'm not it.
Let me see your foot.
All of our signatures are in the hint.
All of our signatures are in it.
I'll give another hint to Se Chan.
(Se Chan gets an additional hint.)
(It looks like So Min's eye.)
(A silhouette of six other thieves is reflected in the eye.)
The hint tells almost all.
- May I show it to everyone? - Can't I see it?
- It's up to you. - We can see it.
Wait, come here.
- Wait a minute. - I can see it, can't I?
- You can show it to me. - No, wait.
- You go away. - What about me?
You can look. Wait.
(What kind of hint is it?)
Wait, you come here.
- The two of you wait. - Why?
(He pretends not to be a thief.)
- Let's take a look. - Let's see.
- Gosh. - What's this?
It's So Min's eye.
- Let's see. Don't come near. - It's not me.
- It's So Min. - It has a double eyelid.
- It's definitely So Min. - You have double eyelids.
It's definitely So Min.
- There are shadows inside. - Right.
I see some shadows.
Isn't there a silhouette?
(What? Se Chan. What are you doing?)
There is.
(He tells Jong Kook about a silhouette.)
- The thief has double eyelids. - It's So Min.
It's not my eye.
(Let me think.)
Kwang Soo.
(Mumbling)
(What's going on?)
It's a woman's eye.
(We're shown in the eye.)
It's So Min.
(Is that really us?)
(Se Chan makes a mistake without knowing that it was a hint.)
- Wait a minute. What's this? - Let me see it.
(Jong Kook seems to realize something.)
(Did Jong Kook figure it out?)
It's definitely So Min.
It's not me.
It's So Min.
I don't think it's one person.
(The suspect from the hints keep changing.)
(There are several people who acted suspiciously.)
(Jong Kook notices something strange.)
(Will Jong Kook find out about all 7 thieves?)
Everyone, it's time to vote.
- I'll start. - You'll vote in order.
Right now?
(Jong Kook wins if Jong Kook votes for all 7.)
- Are you done? - Are you already done?
Are you getting ready to sleep?
(Let me think.)
(Why are there other shoes in the photo?)
Who's next?
It's Se Chan.
(They hurry with their voting.)
(He stares.)
What do you think?
I'm not sure about you.
(He starts to count.)
(Wait, how many of us are there?)
(There are 8 members.)
(There are only 7 shoes in the photo.)
(What's this number?)
(Nervous.)
(They remain silent.)
Why aren't you making a deduction?
Wait.
How could you?
(Wait, how could you?)
Isn't the answer obvious?
What?
We should make a deduction.
- It's obviously Seok Jin. - It could be So Min.
There's something strange going on here.
No one is talking.
- What do you mean? - Seriously.
This has never happened before.
You know why?
When I was making a deduction,
I said that it's either one or all.
(The culprit is one or all of them.)
(A while ago when they were in the van)
(Seok Jin was the most likely suspect.)
There's only one thing I can come up with.
- What? - It's either you or everybody.
(It's either you or everybody.)
It's either you or everybody.
(Is he human or a ghost?)
Either everybody is in it or it's just you.
It's everybody excluding me.
I said it's one person or all.
(Jong Kook is interrogating.)
We picked out a few.
- Who? - And...
- Hold on. Who are you thinking? - You're mad, so I can't think.
- Who is it? - So Min and Seok Jin.
- Who is it? - So Min.
- What? - So Min.
What about Seok Jin?
I don't think it's him. If you're thinking about the foot,
- you should look again. - I don't know. I'm going in.
(He tries to escape reality.)
Why are you stuttering? What's wrong?
You keep... He makes you do that.
(He keeps on interrogating.)
Even if we don't do anything, you make people like that.
- Where are you going, Kwang Soo? - He makes you do that.
(Where are you going, tall guy?)
- There's somebody in there. - I'm going to line up.
Come here, So Min. Come back.
- I'm going to line up. - Stand here.
Why aren't you saying anything? Why aren't you figuring it out?
- We have an idea. - I did.
We already know. The eye and the elbow.
We usually talk about who it is.
We usually whisper to each other.
That's normal for us,
but nobody is talking right now.
Wait. This is a middle school senior with the juniors.
I mean...
- We already know who it is. - That's not it.
He won't let me go.
Isn't this so strange?
We're about to vote, so we should be noisy.
I'm the only one talking.
You lost your shoes. Why are you yelling at us?
You should have taken care of your shoes.
What is wrong with you?
- You yell at us for helping you. - This is driving me nuts.
To be honest, we don't care about your shoes getting lost.
I don't know. Just vote.
Can I go?
Why is it like this? Why...
I'm sure it's Seok Jin.
Gosh, he's so skeptical. Look at him.
I'm not skeptical. This is so strange.
Once he gets married, he'll come home and say,
"What's wrong with this house?"
(That's frightening.)
"There's nothing wrong, honey."
- "Why, honey?" - "There's nothing wrong, honey."
- "What is it now, Dad?" - "There's nothing wrong, honey."
- "I'm home." - Me?
- "Why, Dad?" - When did I do that?
"You don't talk about me at all."
("You don't talk about me at all.")
- "What's wrong?" - Listen.
- "Why aren't you welcoming me?" - Let me say this.
If I say that, there must be something wrong in the house.
- Really? - There has to be.
I... Oh, gosh.
(That's pressuring his family.)
Fine. I had a hunch in the beginning.
- I'll trust it. - Okay.
(He trusts his instincts and votes.)
(Who will Jong Kook vote for?)
(Sighing)
(What?)
(He takes his cap off.)
(They turn in their phones and clothes so that they don't get wet.)
(This is how they accept the penalty.)
How many boxers do I have to carry?
(He's mad.)
I...
get stressed over these things.
(Will Jong Kook give them the penalty?)
(He'll trust his instincts.)
(Hesitating)
(I choose you.)
Okay.
I think it might be me and So Min.
I'll prepare myself.
It'll hurt to get flogged when you're soaked.
That's true.
Do we get flogged?
(What?)
- Why do we get flogged? - Do we get flogged?
- Why do we get flogged? - Aren't there sticks?
What? Why do we get flogged?
- There were sticks. - They just carry them around.
Just in case?
(Let's see.)
I don't know.
(He gives up.)
(Do better.)
Just in case? Why do we get flogged?
Did you say that because there were sticks?
(I don't know. I'm getting dizzy.)
Here are the voting results.
(If Jong Kook votes for everybody, they'll get the water bomb penalty.)
If the thief gets caught,
he or she will get the water bomb penalty,
and the other members will get a prize.
If the thief does not get caught, the thief will get the prize,
and the other members will get the water bomb penalty.
(It's up to Detective Jong Kook.)
One...
two...
(What will happen to the 7 thieves?)
Three.
(Here are the results.)
(Was Jong Kook certain that there were 7 thieves?)
Three.
(Splashing)
(He catches the 7 petty thieves.)
It's cold.
(Goodness)
What was that?
I was right.
(Yes, I was right.)
(His instinct was...)
(Stamping)
(There were 7 thieves.)
I was right.
(He rounds up the petty thieves.)
Stop laughing.
(Are you happy for winning 7 to 1?)
This isn't fun at all!
- This isn't fun. - This isn't even slightly fun.
I was right.
I told you he'll get it.
- Yes. - Who was that for?
Let's do eight people next time. Join us, Chul Min.
You should join us too.
I told you this wouldn't work.
How did you know?
To tell you the truth,
I thought it was over from the beginning.
Me too.
I knew he'd guess.
He's good at deducing,
but we're really bad too.
We didn't say a word near the end.
We were so intimidated.
Our teamwork wasn't great.
It was you.
There is an additional penalty.
One petty thief will get flogged by Jong Kook.
Let's do rack-paper-scissors.
- "Rack-paper-scissors". - "Rack-paper-scissors".
(Let's do "rack-paper-scissors".)
- "Rack-paper-scissors". - What's that?
- Where's that from? - What's that?
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - You can do that.
People who has the same gesture as Jong Kook stays behind.
- That sounds good. - Okay.
I'll do it here.
Rock-paper-scissors
(The last person remaining will get the penalty.)
(Jong Kook has scissors, Ji Hyo has rock, and So Min has paper.)
Goodness.
No way!
(Ji Hyo and So Min survive. The rest are still playing.)
I'm relieved.
- I'm relieved. - Who survived?
- Really? - Goodness.
- Why did you throw out "scissors"? - You usually do "rock".
We're all...
You usually do "rock".
I'm so mad.
Why didn't you do "rock"?
- Ready. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jong Kook has paper, and Haha has scissors.)
Okay!
(He's saved.)
(The rest still remain.)
No way!
What are you doing?
Please save me.
Please. Stop reading my mind!
What's wrong?
- I'm not. - What's wrong with you?
Let's do this.
- Please. - This is driving me nuts.
Let's decide fast.
- We have to decide. - Please.
All right. I'll do it.
Rock-paper...
(Rock-paper...)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Scissors
(Se Chan has paper, and the rest have scissors.)
(What about Jong Kook?)
(He chooses paper.)
Yes!
(Goodness)
(Congratulations, Se Chan.)
(Surprisingly, they survive.)
How did this happen? Us three.
(Let's start the penalty with Jong Kook.)
You're his favorite pupil.
(Sighing)
It's going to be so painful.
You're really bad too.
(He thought about it.)
In what aspects?
I take care of you.
Se Chan has to get hit and get his act together.
- I agree. - What did I do?
It's like this.
This, right?
Here?
- That hurts. - Here?
(That hurts.)
- Hold on. - Did it hurt?
- Did it hurt? - Yes.
I can't watch.
I can't make a mistake,
so I have to aim here.
I'm going to do this.
(Hitting)
(He did it.)
(Beautiful form)
(Nice shot)
(That sounds like firewood being chopped.)
(Hitting)
(It makes him go after Jong Kook.)
- That looks painful. - It does.
Why? Did it hurt?
(This is a lovely bromance.)
Did you think it wouldn't?
(Do you think it was sweet?)
Jong Kook is the winner.
Congratulations.
(The race ended earlier than expected.)
(A week later)
Hello.
Why do you keep winning the polls?
- What? - Why?
You win everything.
"The star who will do fine without laws."
(What's the law?)
Why did he get first place?
You are first place too.
- For what? - What?
You upload things the fastest.
(You upload on social media the fastest.)
Do you mean the picture I took with Tom?
Why did you upload the picture...
you took with Tom Cruise?
Isn't that why we took the pictures? Why didn't you upload it?
- Tom Cruise is going to sue you. - Why?
(Be careful.)
- Did he say that? - Yes.
Tom is mad,
because you're not good friends, but you posted the picture...
without his permission.
He said this on his way out.
"Please keep it to yourself."
(Please keep it to yourself.)
- "Keep it to yourself." - You heard him, right?
- You heard him. - "Keep it to yourself."
- "Keep it to yourself." - "Keep it to yourself."
- You heard him, right? - "Keep it to yourself."
How did he say that?
- He knows everything. - That's not possible.
- He's been to Korea nine times. - Right.
- Do you think he can't say that? - That's right.
He said, "Please keep it to yourself."
He said this to me.
(What did Tom Cruise say to you?)
"Please post it."
- Seok Jin. - What's wrong with you?
(Gosh, Seok Jin.)
(Their smiles are gone.)
What was that?
Come on, Seok Jin.
- Come on, Seok Jin. - "Upload it"?
- See? No one is laughing. - Exactly.
(See? No one is laughing.)
(Doctor Yu brought it back to life.)
I wasn't trying to make you laugh.
People laugh when they can relate.
I'll see how long you'll survive. I'll be watching you.
As of today, our show has been running for eight years now.
And the eight of you will join today's race,
- Get Your Number Eights. - What?
My fortune?
(Do you mean, "my fortune"?)
- My fortune? - It's a pun with the number eight.
Through your given missions,
you must acquire the number eight.
3 members that acquire 8 of the particular number 1st...
- will advance to the final round. - Only three members?
And only 1 of the 3 members will become the ultimate winner.
The final winner will be given an incredible privilege.
What's the privilege?
(What is the privilege?)
The privilege is that the winner can change...
the name and the profile photo of Running Man's members...
on the biggest search engine in Korea for eight days.
(The winner gets complete control for 8 days.)
(The privilege to change their profiles is amazing.)
- What? - For seven days?
For example, for Seok Jin's profile, I can put a photo of his nose.
I can just update his nickname on it. Is that really possible?
Yes, as long as they aren't curse words or distasteful photos.
- So I can't use curse words? - Of course not.
(Darn it.)
(I had a good one in mind. What a shame.)
- Do you think that's allowed? - All right.
- He hasn't learned his lesson. - I was confirming what he said.
I'm sorry.
(Bowing down)
- Get a grip, Kwang Soo. Focus. - Be careful.
- Be careful. Stay focused. - I'm sorry.
Before we start the race,
you'll come up with the drafts how you want to change...
the members' profiles.
- To tell you the truth, I can... - Okay.
- just use the existing photos. - You'll change the name?
- The names will be important. - That's right. Exactly.
For Seok Jin, I'll change his name to "Earthworm".
(Because it rhymes with his last name?)
That's so childish.
Then if people look me up, there will be an earthworm?
- Earthworm. - Earthworm.
I'm going to go with chicken breast for Jong Kook.
- Chicken breast for Jong Kook. - That's good.
- Chicken breast. - Hey, we're like...
- kids coming up with nicknames. - Right.
I'll go with Small-minded for Jong Kook.
- "Small-minded". - He sounds like a kid.
- Small-minded. - What should I name Haha?
- Haha? - How about Status Laundering?
(Status Laundering?)
- Status Laundering? - He totally laundered his past.
(Laughing)
- "Status Laundering"? - Okay. For Jong Kook,
I'm going to go with Yoon Eun Hye.
(Yoon Eun Hye, "A Man")
(The drafts for the profiles turn into bickering matches.)
Gosh, isn't that too much?
For Jong Kook, I'll go with "He Bites When Petted".
(Watch out for Jong Kook, the dog.)
Hey, that's mine.
"He Bites When Petted".
I'm going to use that for him. "Beware: Stay Away".
(She'll add this too.)
- Kwang Soo. - Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- Frog. - It's hard to pick one for him.
If you give me a good one, I'll return the favor.
- If it's decent... - Then I would like to...
- have a deal. - Is there a nickname you want?
- Do you want something like Prince? - Prince?
- No, I'll be embarrassed. - Actually, it sounds sarcastic.
- That's more insulting. - Why?
I got it. I'm going to name Kwang Soo as Fish.
(Out of all names, he'll go with Fish?)
- Fish. - Fish?
- You do look like a fish too. - Right.
- Rockfish. - What... Rockfish?
- Fish. - Rockfish.
- People look up fish a lot now. - Right.
Kwang Soo can be one of them. I'm making you famous.
(He's talking nonsense.)
- It'll raise your status, you know. - That's right.
I'll get more points with the photo of a fish?
- Or Song Joong Ki's Friend. - Oh, right.
(Or I'll go with Song Joong Ki's Friend.)
- Oh, right. That's a good one. - Song Joong Ki's Friend.
- That's great. - I'm really going to do this then.
Or I'll go with Freeze, Song Joong Ki.
Why would you say that?
(I hate that even more! What is that?)
- Freeze, Song Joong Ki? - Why not?
- Freeze, Song Joong Ki. - Why would I tell him to freeze?
You'll catch up with him soon, so "Freeze, Song Joong Ki".
We'll use the photo with the gun.
I'll name So Min Farter.
- Don't do that. - It's cute.
That's good. That's a cute one.
- No, I don't fart. - That's a cute one.
I don't fart.
- I don't. - Lady Kwang Soo is good too.
- No, no. Jae Seok, please. Don't. - Or what about Pooping So Min?
No, that's... I'll take Pooping So Min over Lady Kwang Soo.
(Gosh, whatever.)
- Pooping So Min. - Or I'll take Farting Bug.
Hey, Farting Bug is better than Lady Kwang Soo?
Farting Bug is better than Lady Kwang Soo.
- Unbelievable. - That's a better choice.
I'll rather go with Farting Bug.
What did you put down for Jae Seok?
- I put down Ugly Man for Jae Seok. - Jae Seok...
(He didn't mean that literally, right?)
- I gave him a good one. - Hey.
- Are you serious? - I mean, it could mean...
- I mean... - Goodness.
I put down Small Jae Seok for Jae Seok's name.
Hey, what are you doing?
(Small Jae Seok)
(What did you say?)
- Yours is similar to mine. - What's yours?
What do you mean by Small Jae Seok?
- Hey, I saw it. I did! - Listen.
- Have you gone mad? - "Small Jae Seok".
I'll leave the rest to your imagination. Small Jae Seok.
- You can't let people do that. - He's small?
For Jae Seok, I'll just put a period.
(He's as small as a period.)
Hey, you stay out of this.
- He's small. - They're unbelievable.
I can't believe you wrote, "Small Jae Seok".
- That's neat. - I see. Is that how you'll play it?
(How will the race end?)
(The race to acquire the number 8 begins at last.)
(Special backups have been dispatched for the war.)
(Sung Dong Il, a sure bet to make movies hits)
(Shin Hae Sun, the queen of TV ratings)
Gosh, it's Mamamoo.
(Jang Do Yeon and Mamamoo)
(Are you sure this is Running Man?)
(With these special guests,)
(they will eat,)
(show slapstick comedies,)
(and throw the ultimate party of variety shows.)
(If you cheat,)
(you'll get a beating.)
(You deserve a beating.)
(And the final mission where the number 8 is at stake)
(An octagon ring unfolds before their eyes.)
(They betray and plot to win the numbers.)
(Can they change their fortunes to good ones...)
(or ruin them?)
(It's their last chance to change their fortunes.)
(What will happen to these eight members?)
(Protect Your Names)