(Last week)
(Film a new TV rating notice for the new year, 2018!)
(The winner will have the chance to direct the TV rating notice.)
(The new TV rating notice, which will air for a month,)
(was at stake for the last week's dirty and cruel race.)
(In the midst of tricks, some succeeded and some failed.)
(They obtained R Ddakjis depending on the results of the race.)
(And)
(The final round will depend on the R Ddakjis they have obtained.)
(It's their last chance to be the director of TV rating notice.)
(Which member will be in the limelight of the TV rating notice?)
(Storyboards of each member)
(The last mission will determine the director of TV rating notice.)
- What is this? - What's all this?
Do we need to bet again?
Is this what we're doing today?
(The set is quite cutting edge.)
- What's happening today? - My gosh.
This looks so cool.
The set looks fancy.
(Which member will win the notice?)
Did you guys know this about So Min?
She told me that when she was either in high school or college,
she always sang this specific song when her time was up.
My parents are really strict.
I couldn't stay out late. I had to go home when it was midnight.
I always sang this song when I was leaving the karaoke.
Which song? Sing the chorus.
("Good Time" by Cleo)
(I want to spend the night, but I need my parents' permission)
- You must've been with a guy. - So...
- She was with a guy back then. - That's why...
- I hated that she sang that song. - She sang it for the guy.
- She must've sounded cute though. - That sounds about right.
The guy must have enjoyed it though.
- She was singing it for him. - She only picked songs like that.
- Gosh. You know what I mean? - It is annoying.
"Blue Rain".
Where are Seok Jin and Jong Kook?
Right now, Seok Jin and Jong Kook...
are on their way here. The previous mission took longer than expected.
- It's rush hour now. - I know.
Se Chan must film another show, so we must wrap up by seven here.
That means all three of them are out of the race.
Including me?
- You must go film the show. - I can participate longer.
You have to go.
So for the following mission, Seok Jin and Jong Kook will...
bet through the phone remotely.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
- Wait. - Cutting edge of the 21st century.
- This is so funny. - The show of the 21st century.
- When we start the game, - Okay.
- you will participate remotely. - I got it.
- Okay. - Okay.
Actually, we have to be there to feel the moment.
- That's right. - That's kind of disappointing.
(What is the final mission?)
You can acquire R Ddakjis as many as you bet.
It's a 4-on-4 mission, Along with Mistrust.
(Betting mission, Along with Mistrust)
- It's a team match. - It's 4-on-4.
Teach me how to play.
There will be four rounds.
Come up with a list of players after reading keywords for each round.
Bet on your team's victory or loss for each game without disclosing it.
If you win the bet, you will acquire the number of ddakjis you've bet.
If you lose, you will forfeit the number of ddakjis you've bet.
(They will either win or lose ddakjis.)
However, if you bet on your team's victory,
and your team does win the game,
then you will be given double the number of ddakjis you've bet.
- Double? That's a lot. - On our team?
- I'm going to bet all in. - Me too, Jae Seok.
- Let's go with Team Nevis. - Yes, let's do that.
- Take Team Australia or... - We'll go with Team New Zealand.
- Is that what you want? - Our pride is at stake then.
- I'm going to take this seriously. - Fine. Okay.
(Keywords are quiz, draw of luck, 1-on-1 match, and challenge.)
We must win this round.
- That's right. We came this far. - Here...
- You should come this way. - My gosh, I'm so exhausted.
You know what's at stake on this round, right?
(Everyone, you'd better get ready.)
- Of course. - Five seconds.
- Right. - Five seconds for the notice.
(The winner will be the director.)
I won't be able to win. I don't have a lot.
All right, everyone. The first game is...
- a quiz. - Okay.
Jae Seok and Haha. Please come up to the front.
My gosh, in this team, I'm the smart one.
He's the smartest one in our team.
- That's why we feel so sad. - My gosh.
- I can't do it. - This is unbelievable.
Well, this might not test us about our common knowledge.
I might be able to win.
- That's true. - We don't know what it's about.
We are going to start now.
- Whoever solves 2 questions 1st... - Is it over then?
- will win. - Should we bet first?
Now, you will place your bets.
(The betting begins!)
(They must bet on their member's victory or loss.)
(They will win the same number ddakjis they bet.)
(If they bet on the victory and win, they will earn double the amount.)
I have to be smart about this. It's an individual match in the end.
- It's an individual match. - My gosh.
Do you have 20? How many do you have?
- I have 38. - Write the number of ddakjis.
(Currently, So Min and Kwang Soo are in 3rd and 4th place.)
- Jae Seok is going to do well. - If I win...
- I bet he's going to win. - This game...
(Contemplating)
I think Jae Seok is going to win.
What? Why are you betting so many?
I have to beat you.
(Is that how you're going to play?)
(Thinking)
If I bet on my loss...
(I must win the bet.)
The first game is a quiz.
- Quiz. - Which members are playing?
- Jae Seok from Team Australia. - Okay.
Haha from Team New Zealand.
(It's almost like David versus Goliath.)
Jae Seok will win if this is a quiz.
It's the same chance that I win rock-paper-scissors 10 times...
- in a row against you. - That's right.
- Cover your bet. Don't change it. - Okay.
(8 of them finish betting.)
I will give you the first question.
It's an open-ended question.
- On archery targets, what is... - This is really hard.
the color of the spot for 10 points, the highest points a player can win?
(What's the color of the spot for 10 points in archery?)
I know the answer, but I'll keep quiet.
- Jae Seok knows a lot about sports. - Yes, he does.
- Try to think it over. - Isn't this too easy?
Really, Haha? Do you know the answer?
This is too easy. Everyone knows unless you're an idiot.
Exactly. This is too easy.
All right. Show your answers. 1, 2, 3.
(What are their answers?)
Which color did you write?
(Jae Seok wrote, "yellow", and Haha wrote, "cobalt blue".)
My gosh, "cobalt blue"?
(I know where he's going with this. He has bet on his loss.)
- What? - This is wrong?
What are you talking about? Why would you write, "cobalt blue"?
The answer is...
- yellow. - That's right.
How could you get this wrong?
(Kwang Soo and So Min are cheering.)
(But they are happy too?)
- Isn't this too easy? - I knew it.
- Jae Seok. Please! - Please!
We'll present you the next question.
When someone disturbs or gets in the way of something...
that seems promising or has potential to be successful,
we say that he or she is "spoiling" the situation.
From what is the term derived?
My gosh, it's so hard.
(From what is the term, "spoil" derived?)
It's vinegar.
It's not a candle. It's not, right?
A long time ago, I knew...
(From what is the term, "spoil" derived?)
(On the other hand, Haha writes his answer with confidence.)
I learned this before.
This is crazy.
I knew it, but I can't remember it now.
No, Jae Seok. You must remember it.
- I can't remember this. - Show your answers.
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3.
I can't remember this.
No way. Did I say the right answer?
- I saw this somewhere. - Jae Seok...
wrote, "vinegar" for his answer.
Are you sure you don't remember?
(My gosh! He wrote, "vinegar"!)
- I can't remember it. - Haha wrote, "My gosh, it's crazy."
(My gosh, it's crazy.)
Haha wrote, "My gosh, it's crazy."
(Look at that guy. That guy is crazy indeed.)
- Oh, this is crazy - Oh, my.
I learned this a long time ago, but it was such a long time ago.
The term, "spoil" derives from...
(If vinegar is correct, the 1st round is over with Jae Seok's win.)
(In that case, his teammates can obtain double what they have bet.)
The term, "spoil" derives from...
vinegar.
(Vinegar is correct.)
(It derives from vinegar as too much vinegar can spoil the food.)
Jae Seok.
- Yu Jae Seok! - Yu Jae Seok!
Yu Jae Seok!
(Wait. The word really derives from "vinegar"?)
- Jae Seok. - My gosh.
What a bummer. I should've bet more.
You're so smart, Jae Seok. How did you know that?
He has never let me down! Never!
My gosh, Jae Seok is so cool.
1, 2, 3. Show us your bets.
I bet five on my winning.
(Jae Seok bet 5, and Haha bet 20.)
- Jae Seok, you'll receive 10. - My gosh.
(10 R Ddakjis go to Jae Seok.)
- You bet 23, right? - Yes.
46 R Ddakjis go to Kwang Soo.
42 R Ddakjis go to So Min.
- I also guessed correctly. - How many R Ddakjis did you bet?
- 20. - 20.
Since your guess is correct, you get 20 R Ddakjis.
Se Chan gets four R Ddakjis. Ji Hyo, how many did you bet?
- 3. - You get 3 R Ddakjis.
Jae Seok wins the first round.
(Meanwhile, at the site of the remote betting...)
Both of you won R Ddakjis.
- I should have bet 20. - I get 20 R Ddakjis.
I didn't occur to me sooner.
It's hard to stay updated at a distance.
(Jong Kook gets 10 R Ddakjis and Seok Jin gets 20 R Ddakjis.)
(The current rankings: Seok Jin, Jong Kook, So Min,)
(Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, Haha, Jae Seok, Se Chan)
(The current rankings: Kwang Soo, So Min, Seok Jin,)
(Jong Kook, Haha, Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Se Chan)
With 81 R Ddakjis, Kwang Soo is leading.
He has one more R Ddakji than So Min.
What was the title of your storyboard?
("2018 Start Afresh", directed by Kwang Soo)
(The members get water bombed in 8 provinces of Korea.)
We can't let that happen.
- We must stop him. - We must stop Kwang Soo.
So Min's "Running Man's Sea Story" is close behind.
("Running Man's Sea Story", directed by So Min)
(The members star in her show as fish, seaweed, rock, etc.)
That's dangerous.
My storyboard is good.
The next mission is a game of chance.
The representatives are So Min and Ji Hyo.
You choose between odd and even.
I will go all in. I have no other choice.
- Odd or even? - Odd.
Please let it be even.
It's even.
(So Min wins.)
(Jae Seok hits the jackpot.)
"Yu Jae Seok and the Animals" is in first place.
"Yu Jae Seok and the Animals".
("Yu Jae Seok and the Animals", directed by Jae Seok)
(Other members play various animals in humiliating costumes...)
(and make Jae Seok shine.)
It's the worst!
Please.
We need to stop Jae Seok.
I am in second place.
(Haha's "Man out of a Comic Book" is in 2nd place.)
I could still win.
- It's still in the top three. - You need to win.
- Let's go. - Okay.
You need to win no matter what.
- You can win, right? - This is my last chance.
- I only have one R Ddakji. - Me, too.
- Do you have one R Ddakji? - Yes, I do.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan end up losing everything.)
Ji Hyo and I are the same.
This mission is a 1-on-1 match.
Before that, Jong Kook and Seok Jin will join...
- since they have arrived. - Welcome.
Did you win?
I bet 20 R Ddakjis on you losing.
The two of you fell far in the rankings.
- Doing it from a distance... - It made you lose your touch.
- It made me lose my touch. - Of course it did.
In this 1-on-1 mission,
you will kick trays with your feet.
Jump high and kick both trays with your feet spread apart.
The one who kicks the trays higher wins.
(Kwang Soo versus Se Chan)
He has long legs.
Kwang Soo, show us a kick.
Show us a kick.
- I am much taller than him. - That's right.
I can just raise my legs and touch the trays.
Kwang Soo could fail on purpose.
You know,
I can't trust Kwang Soo.
What is he writing? What are you writing?
Kwang Soo, you will do your best, right?
Of course. I have to win.
- If I win, I get twice the amount. - That's right.
I will bet on Kwang Soo's win.
- He gets twice the amount that way. - Kwang Soo. What did you write?
Is it win or lose?
I have to bet on winning.
- Tell us. - I have to bet on winning.
- Look me in the eye. - His pants...
- are too thick. - Is it win or lose?
(They are, right?)
Kwang Soo.
Play with your underwear on.
I can't trust him.
(He takes off his pants.)
He has a point.
(He takes off his pants in front of the camera.)
He needs to win to get twice the R Ddakjis he bet.
(I love your passion, Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, you are working hard.
Now, the staff members...
are unfazed.
He is like a grandpa.
(It comes very normally now.)
Please place a bet.
Bet your R Ddakjis on whether or not your team will win.
(I have to win.)
We have to take this to the end.
(Jumping)
- His jump was low. - He can't jump.
(His lousy jump makes people change their bets.)
- His jump was low. - He is stiff.
He is stiff.
(It's a practice.)
This isn't an easy task.
Se Chan.
Try jumping.
- How? - Jump with your feet apart.
(He is far below the trays.)
His jump was lower.
- Seok Jin. - I will bet on Kwang Soo.
- Don't be fooled. - I will bet on Kwang Soo.
- May I practice once? - No.
Can I practice? Do I have to go right away?
I want to do it without the trays over here.
- I will face this way. - Try it.
(Panting)
Kwang Soo wants to win.
Does it hurt?
(Sniffling)
- This is... - Kwang Soo.
- What? - You fell on the floor.
(You are in pain, right?)
(Grunting)
(He pushed the mat and fell on the floor.)
(I landed on my back onto the floor, right?)
Don't you feel a nosebleed coming?
- I can't breathe. - You must be in pain.
He can't breathe.
Why did I fall on the floor?
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
- What? - You fell on the floor.
(Get it together, Kwang Soo.)
- You fool. - Don't you feel a nosebleed coming?
- Don't you taste blood? - You are fine.
(The match begins in earnest.)
- Let's go. - Is Se Chan going first?
- Yes, I am going first. - Please flip over the board.
- This is hard. - This is hard.
Here I go.
We will have a few rounds.
(Since he has no chance of placing 1st,)
(Se Chan has no reason to lose on purpose.)
(Can Se Chan succeed in the 1st round?)
He failed. He failed.
(He jumped pretty high,)
(but his left foot didn't touch the tray.)
- He failed. He failed. - He failed.
Kwang Soo, you will win if you succeed.
- It won't be easy for Kwang Soo. - Didn't my feet touch the trays?
- Good luck. - If I fall backwards as I kick...
- I will succeed if I do that. - You will succeed.
- You can do it, Kwang Soo. - You can do it.
You can do it.
Here I go.
He is going to fail.
No, he wants to do well.
Do it seriously.
(The fate of this round depends on Kwang Soo.)
(Can Kwang Soo succeed?)
(Kwang Soo does it again.)
(He jumps slightly, so he won't touch it.)
He failed.
I can't believe him!
It could be a part of his plan.
It's not easy...
- to kick the trays with both feet. - That's not the case.
He must have bet on losing.
- It's neither win nor lose. - Both of them lost.
- They did, right? - It's a failure.
In this case,
there is neither a winner nor a loser.
(Now, there is neither a winner nor a loser.)
Is that the case?
Kwang Soo...
bet everything on losing.
I will take the number of R Ddakjis...
everyone bet.
Are you taking it from all of us?
Yes, I am.
- Thank goodness I bet 5. - I also bet 5.
Thank goodness. I bet one.
I bet one.
Will you take it from all of us?
(Is that how the rules work?)
How many did Kwang Soo bet?
Did you bet on winning or losing?
- I bet on losing. - Show us your board.
- I bet on losing. - What did you write?
- I took off my pants... - What did he write?
- to bet on losing. - What did he write?
He bet 15 on losing.
- You are less than human! - It's not like that.
People bet their R Ddakjis on you.
He didn't bet 15, but 45.
- 45. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - You are less than human!
- It's not like that. - You are less than human!
Why do the rules work that way?
- For goodness' sake. - 45.
You failed, Kwang Soo.
(The current rankings: Jae Seok, Haha, Kwang Soo,)
(So Min, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Se Chan)
(Jong Kook, Seok Jin, So Min, Ji Hyo, Se Chan)
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo took a big loss.
You shouldn't have been so greedy.
I didn't think you would fail!
I couldn't do it.
Jae Seok is in first place.
"Yu Jae Seok and the Animals" is in first place.
- We have to stop it. - We can't let that happen.
- We have to stop it. - We will be dressed up as animals.
Haha's "Man out of a Comic Book" is on the second place.
- It's a good one. - If you win this round,
yours will get chosen.
Should I go all in?
This is the final round.
The representatives for this round are...
Seok Jin and Jong Kook.
The mission is...
Dibidibidip.
(Dibidibidip)
I don't know how it will go.
It doesn't go as you wish.
- This one... - I don't know how it will go.
I don't have a choice but to bet on winning.
I will bet on winning.
It will give us more R Ddakjis.
(A lot of members go all in.)
Look. This is my only chance.
(Jae Seok goes all in despite being in 1st place.)
He went all in. What is going on?
You're going to go all in too.
I might lose.
Right? I might lose.
Seok Jin will go first.
Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Haha will defend.
Do you want me to win?
- You have to win. - I have to win.
The outcome depends on the number of times you hold out.
The number of times I hold out.
- Ji Hyo. - I am done if Seok Jin loses.
- Hang in there. - Nevis Swing! Let's go!
- Let's go. - Nevis Swing.
- Nevis... - In 1, 2, 3. Swing!
- He has to win. - He has to win.
- Winning is good. - Seok Jin.
Eliminate her right away.
- Eliminate her right away. - All right.
Let's begin.
Dibidibidip.
(He eliminates her in one try.)
Okay.
He really beat her in one try.
Dibidibidip.
Okay!
(He eliminates 2 people in 2 turns.)
(This is incredible.)
(Sighing)
(Seok Jin is ready to eliminate...)
(3 people in 3 turns.)
(Can Seok Jin's third attack go as well?)
(He is stopped.)
Okay. He did it.
(He eliminates everyone in four turns.)
(He screams in excitement.)
- Dibidibidip. - Okay.
(What happened?)
(He wins after four tries.)
Are you next?
He wins in four tries.
(Thanks to Seok Jin, Jae Seok is more likely to win.)
Listen, Jae Seok.
- Go easy on me during your shoot. - Okay.
Make me look nice.
If he defeats everyone...
Gosh, you're terrible.
(Haha)
It's over if he defeats all at once.
That's correct.
(Haha's fate depends on Jong Kook.)
(He's close to winning.)
Let's start.
- You can do it. - If Jong Kook...
defeats all of them,
it'll be very surprising.
Kim Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook. - Kim Jong Kook.
- Nevis. - Kim Jong Kook.
Nevis.
Let's do it.
Goodness.
It won't be easy.
Shall I start?
Here I go.
(Will Haha's belief in Jong Kook help him win?)
Dibidibidip.
Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. - Why?
I...
Did you bet on your loss?
(Did he bet on his loss?)
- He did. - Kwang Soo.
(I was supposed to lose.)
Do I win if I defend once more?
Do this next, Jong Kook.
(Remember this, Kwang Soo.)
That would be cheating.
Dibidibidip.
(Gosh, I fell for it.)
(That seemed natural.)
Do a fake one.
So Min, you must win.
You have to win.
Dibidibidip.
(Jong Kook was blocked once.)
I really want to win.
(This round determines the winner.)
- It's for a month. - It'd be great.
Dibidibidip.
(She blocks him.)
She blocked him.
Dibidibidip.
(Jong Kook loses.)
It's over.
(Jae Seok's victory is confirmed.)
I'm in complete darkness.
- It's over. - But...
I'm not happy...
because I don't want to become a parrot.
I won.
It's the animal kingdom.
(The winner is "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals".)
The winning TV rating notice is...
"Yu Jae Seok and the Animals".
What far do I go to dress up as a catfish?
- Pardon? - To dress up.
- I will... - How do I dress up as a giraffe?
discuss with the staff in detail.
I'll make it happen.
It's called "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals".
You'll simply dress up as animals.
(He prepares in detail.)
(There are new shocking characters.)
(The terrible reality of "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals")
(Jae Seok's shooting of TV rating notice is coming up soon.)
Everyone did a good job during the shoot.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - This is upsetting.
Let's do it one more time.
Let's do it again after one month.
I realized how seriously I must play.
No way.
I gave them good roles, but they're upset.
You must be hungry since we started early.
- That's right. - We're hungry.
We prepared Monday Tasting Session...
where you can eat whatever menu you want.
(Monday Tasting Session?)
- This is necessary. - I'm so excited.
We haven't done it in a long time.
(It's a delicious gift from the staff.)
(Common lunch dishes...)
(are all in one place.)
Gukbap sounds good.
Vietnamese spring rolls?
Steak?
I want gukbap.
What I want now is gukbap.
- What's this? - Among the dishes,
select the one that you'd like to eat.
Okay.
- Really? - One dish we want?
I want jjajangmyeon.
(Jae Seok chooses jjajangmyeon.)
I want this one.
Goodness.
- I want Vietnamese spring rolls. - Get out of my way.
You move.
- Mine is steak. - Mine is Vietnamese spring rolls.
Is that so? Mine is steak.
(Each member picks a dish.)
Did you pick a dish?
- Yes. - Yes.
With the name of the dish,
each of you will jump...
on the box.
Four of them are filled with ice water.
The other four are safe.
The menus chosen by those who fall into the ice water are eliminated.
The menus chosen by the ones who are safe...
are the menus you will eat.
(They can only try the menus chosen by the 4 surviving members.)
Really?
(Only half of the chosen dishes can be eaten.)
Please stand next to the box of your choice.
- Is yours 7? - Shall I pick 4?
I'll take four.
I'll take one.
The menus of the members who falls into the water will be eliminated.
(If you fall, say goodbye to your menu.)
I want some chicken.
I want gukbap.
(Chicken)
Please.
Okay.
1, 2, 3.
(Se Chan's steak is out.)
Goodness.
I knew it.
Pork cutlet.
(Jjajangmyeon and pork cutlet are safe.)
Let's go.
I knew it.
(Vietnamese spring rolls are out.)
Who's next?
(Chicken is out.)
- 1, 2, 3. - 3.
(Pork belly barbecue is safe.)
That's great, Jong Kook.
I'm hungry.
Shall we jump at the same time?
- At the same time? - Three dishes are safe.
(One of them is safe.)
Please. What's yours?
- Tangsuyuk. - Tangsuyuk?
Jjajangmyeon is safe, right?
- Yes. - That's right.
- They'll jump together. - No.
They're similar.
One.
Two.
(Gukbap and tangsuyuk)
- Two. - Get a shot of Ji Hyo's face.
He said to get a shot of her face.
Is it me?
You can't tell each other.
That makes it obvious.
My goodness.
You can't do that, Director.
(Don't make it so obvious.)
Let's go. 1, 2, 3.
It's Ji Hyo. No, it's not.
Is it me?
(Contrary to everyone's prediction, Haha is eliminated.)
(She gets tangsuyuk.)
Is it me?
(He gets fooled.)
(The broken box reminds him.)
I jumped too confidently.
I'm in complete darkness.
The four dishes that you chose are...
jjajangmyeon, pork belly, tangsuyuk, and pork cutlet...
for today.
For Monday Tasting Session,
today's real race is...
(Today's real race is...)
It's called Someone's Bad Luck.
- What do you mean? - Happiness with 10 Dollars?
Within five hours,
you must eat all four dishes...
- with 10 dollars. - What?
You must eat all four dishes...
(All with 10 dollars?)
All of them?
If you go over time...
or fail to eat all the dishes with 10 dollars,
everyone will be penalized.
What is he talking about?
- Only use 10 dollars? - All 8 of us?
Don't you know how much one jjajangmyeon is?
What about tangsuyuk?
During the race,
the member who doesn't get to eat...
receives a Bad Luck Badge.
If you clear the mission,
the one with the most Bad Luck Badges places last.
The one who comes in last chooses another member...
to be penalized together.
Again?
(Two members are penalized.)
For 2018, the year of dog, the penalty is...
walking 10,000 steps with a dog penalty suit on.
(Walking 10,000 steps with a dog penalty suit on)
- 10,000 steps? - The penalty is taking...
10,000 steps.
Here's 10 dollars.
How can we eat 4 dishes with 10 dollars?
We must go to cheap restaurants.
We should search the cheapest restaurants.
- We don't have time. - Let's hurry.
Let's go.
(Happiness with 10 Dollars race starts.)
(Where should we go first?)
Wait, where should we go?
(The timer is on.)
- The time started. - Right.
There goes the time.
(Time limit is 5 hours.)
Where should we go first?
Let's eat jjajangmyeon first.
- Jjajangmyeon? - Let's do that.
Jjajangmyeon.
(They must find a cheap place to eat.)
- Let's go. - Machine jjajangmyeon.
- A cheap restaurant... - Let's go here.
I found jjajangmyeon that costs a dollar.
- A dollar? - Yes.
(Jjajangmyeon is a dollar?)
It costs a dollar.
- Where is it? - In Gunpo.
Let's go.
Are we going to Gunpo?
- Let's go. It's only a dollar. - Isn't it too far?
There's enough gas in the car.
There's enough gas.
We should go there.
There's tangsuyuk for 1.5 dollars in Gangseo-gu.
- 1.5 dollars? - It's 1.5 dollars in Gangseo-gu.
- Let's go to Gunpo. - Hey.
Let's go to Gunpo first.
Why are you angry?
Let's eat jjajangmyeon.
Why are you so angry?
Let's go now.
- Their break time starts at 3pm. - Let's go.
Let's go to Gunpo.
(No one can stop Jae Seok from eating jjajangmyeon.)
Let me call the restaurant first.
Let's call first.
We don't have time, so call in the car.
Why is Jae Seok so angry?
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Close the door.
(Close the door?)
I'm going to Gunpo, so get in another van.
- What? - Wait for me.
- What's wrong? - Hurry. We don't have time.
- Goodness. - We have time.
Let's get in.
- I'll sit in the back. - Goodness.
Why are you so impatient?
Hurry up. We don't have time.
Goodness.
Jae Seok, it's in Gunpo.
(No one can stop Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok is so into it.
- What's the number? - I have to go, Bo Pil.
Please put on your seat belt.
I have to go, Bo Pil.
Is it really a dollar in Anyang?
How can they make profit?
There's a place that sells pork cutlet for a dollar in Sanbon.
- What? - We can go after Gunpo.
Let's eat everything there.
- Is it okay if we go? - Yes.
It's in Sanbon.
(They head to the jjajangmyeon restaurant.)
Jjajangmyeon will be delicious.
- Gosh, I'm so hungry. - It'll be delicious.
I like green peas in jjajangmyeon.
Fried egg with jjajangmyeon is good too.
- I agree. - Right.
I like ground beef jjajangmyeon.
It's with ground beef.
- It's fun to pick out the beef. - It's expensive.
It's expensive though.
Seok Jin, how much was jjajangmyeon when you were little?
(Seok Jin vaguely remembers how it tasted 40 years.)
- How much... - Five cents?
I'd say 30 cents.
- 30 cents. - I don't remember.
They had to go to China if they wanted jjajangmyeon.
That's not true.
They had to go to China.
It was the Korean Empire period.
They had to travel to Tang Dynasty.
Tang Dynasty?
Tang Dynasty envoys would bring jjajangmyeon...
when they were visiting our king.
Exactly.
You used brass coins, right?
I did.
You did?
He used Joseon coins.
Joseon coins...
(Have you ever seen secret royal inspectors?)
Have you ever seen secret royal inspectors?
Have you ever seen horse badges?
One of my school friends became a secret royal inspector.
One of your school friends?
One of my school friends...
He used to be such a troublemaker,
but he became a secret royal inspector.
(He passed the 17th-century state exam.)
I didn't know he became one.
Weren't you taken during the Manchu War of 1636?
I worked as a Japanese interpreter.
(He even interpreted.)
It's the Qing Dynasty, not Japan.
It is?
One of the Qing commanders was Japanese.
Were there really dinosaurs?
- What? - Were there really dinosaurs?
Did you evolve from a monkey?
Bipedalism.
(Are you taking it that far?)
Can you handle this one too?
Back then, my back didn't ache.
My back became bad when I started walking on two legs.
(He'll soon remember the time he was an ameba.)
(From Seoul to Gunpo)
I wonder how one-dollar jjajangmyeon tastes.
This place was going to close down.
That's why they started selling jjajangmyeon for one dollar.
- But... - It became popular?
It became so popular, and they're still in business.
(Their one-dollar jjajangmyeon became a hit.)
That's incredible.
(Mouth-watering)
I think we're almost there.
Can't you use GPS?
- It's in that building. - Are we here?
- I found it. "Free jjajangmyeon". - Okay.
It's that place.
- "5-dollar tangsuyuk". - "5-dollar tangsuyuk".
- We found it! - Tangsuyuk costs five dollars?
- Awesome. - One-dollar jjajangmyeon?
Is there really one-dollar jjajangmyeon?
Can they get any profit?
Running Man members are about to taste one-dollar jjajangmyeon.
My mouth is watering.
Smell it. It smells so good. Ji Hyo, it smells great.
This costs only one dollar?
Hello.
- Can we order? - Does it really cost one dollar?
Excuse me.
Is it okay if we shoot in the corner?
- Sure. - Is it okay?
Thank you.
(Jjajangmyeon, 1 dollar)
Does it really cost only one dollar?
It's incredible.
Let's just eat as much as we want here.
Happiness with 10 Dollars. We're at the first restaurant now.
Order one portion,
and pay for it.
Before we start,
let's decide how many people will eat here...
by playing a game.
Choose one customer here.
The number of bills the customer has...
will determine how many people will eat.
Each member will randomly draw...
a number.
The result will determine who will eat here.
Those who don't get to eat here...
will get a Bad Luck Badge.
If the customer has eight bills, everyone gets to eat?
The bigger your number is, the lower your chance is.
I guess up to three people will eat.
If the customer has one bill, will only one person eat?
Yes.
Eight would be the worst.
(Smaller numbers are better.)
Let's see.
I want one.
(Who will lucky and choose a low number?)
Please.
This.
- Seok Jin, turn your spoon around. - I haven't seen mine.
It's five.
- Can I try again? - It's over.
It's my turn.
I doubt it's eight.
(Jae Seok's turn)
- Four. - It's not bad.
- Three. - Three.
Three.
My turn.
Eight.
(Haha picked 8.)
I'm in complete darkness.
It's true. You've been very unlucky these days.
Here we go.
(Kwang Soo's turn)
Six.
4, 5, 6.
1, 2, 3 are left.
Seven is left too.
Let's turn them around at the same time. 1, 2, 3.
(1, 2, and 7 are left.)
It's seven.
(So Min: 1, Ji Hyo: 2)
Yes.
It's seven.
- Choose one customer now. - The lady.
Hold on. Let's look around.
They must be friends.
- There's a lady over there too. - Choose the lady.
- This lady? - Yes.
- Because... - Could we see...
how many bills you have?
Mothers usually use credit cards. It's students that use...
No, it's not like that.
- Are you sure? - Because...
Just sit down.
Be quiet.
The number of bills in her wallet.
- Just the bills? - Yes.
(The number of bills will determine how many members can eat.)
(Who will get to eat?)
one...
(Two bills)
She must use credit cards.
- Thank you. - It's 11 dollars.
- Thank you. - She must use credit cards.
(She usually uses credit cards.)
Who will get to eat?
Just those two will eat.
I wanted jjajangmyeon.
(We get to eat.)
Could Kwang Soo have been right about students?
Do you have any bills?
How many do you have?
In your wallet.
Wait.
(A lot)
- Gosh. - I knew it.
He has more than 10.
What did I say?
(Kwang Soo is speechless.)
(We should have listened to him.)
What did I tell you?
Students use cash.
You have a lot of cash.
(Disappointed)
Kid, are you going to eat that?
- Stop it. - Gosh.
Don't do that.
- You shouldn't leave any food. - Be quiet.
Stop it.
Be quiet.
Those who don't get to eat will receive a Bad Luck Badge.
My goodness.
(Bad Luck Badges)
Two bowls of jjajangmyeon are served.
- Gosh. - So Min and Ji Hyo.
(They're for So Min and Ji Hyo.)
Like this?
Two bowls are served.
Even though we paid for one portion?
(One-dollar jjajangmyeon for So Min and Ji Hyo)
- We could have all eaten. - Exactly.
We could have all eaten.
I thought we were going to share one bowl.
- Let me mix it for you. - Can I get chili powder?
- So did I. - After we're done shooting,
come back here.
- It looks so tasty. - You can eat then.
- I want it so badly. - Jjajangmyeon...
She's eating it.
Eat it with pickled radish.
- The slurping sound. - Does it taste good?
It looks tasty.
(It's driving me crazy.)
- It tastes really good. - I can't believe...
it costs only one dollar.
- It doesn't taste cheap. - There's enough sauce too.
- It's just right. - It's sweet and spicy.
Guys.
(It's sweet and spicy.)
(I'm happy I'm so lucky.)
We came all the way to Gunpo. Can't we...
Call your friends.
Guys, why don't we order one more bowl?
- Don't do that. - Can we do that?
If you really want to eat,
- pay another dollar... - Are we going to draw again?
Are we drawing again?
The one who draws one will get to eat.
- One? - Okay.
I want one.
Let's draw one at the same time.
- Draw one. - Let's do it together.
Please.
- At the same time. - Please.
I'm not sure if I'll be lucky.
Please. Just this once.
Hold on.
What did you pick?
- What's your number? - Six.
We're 6 people, and I picked 6.
That was close. Two.
- The rest... - I still have a chance.
- It's your turn. - Turn it around.
You know how much I love jjajangmyeon, right?
Please.
I want my number to change to one.
Jae Seok chose this place.
(I want my number to change to one.)
What are you doing?
- Five. - I still have a chance.
(Jae Seok is eliminated.)
I have a chance.
I actually don't want it that much.
- Could it be Jong Kook? - Let me eat.
I have a feeling it's Jong Kook.
Should Jong Kook wait?
The two of us should go first. You go first.
(Kwang Soo checks his number.)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
Could it be Jong Kook?
(It's either Haha or Jong Kook.)
It's either of these two.
- Jong Kook... - But...
(Please let me eat.)
- Jjajangmyeon... - Should I go first?
Hold on.
(Please let me eat.)
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(Shouting)
(Haha is exhilarated.)
(Haha surpassed the darkness and picked 1.)
(My goodness.)
Haha.
Thank you.
Whatever. I'll just eat it.
Hey.
You're breaking the rules.
Pay another dollar and try again.
No.
If you run out of time,
- Right. - everyone will be penalized.
Let's hurry.
It looks like more than one serving.
My gosh, this is amazing.
(Slurping)
I really want to eat it.
(It's driving him crazy as he can hear and see the noodles.)
- Doesn't it look really delicious? - Yes, indeed.
I will let you have a bite if you take my badge.
(Haha, the strategist, makes a sweet deal.)
- My gosh, that's really tempting. - Goodness.
- I will give you this much. - My gosh, you...
I will feed you this much.
- If you take this. - Dear me.
5, 4...
We have to go to four places.
(I can't stop thinking about the slurping sound.)
(Will someone be tempted to accept this deal?)
- I'm in! - Okay.
(Kwang Soo, the lover of jjajangmyeon, is in.)
(He's a slave to his desire.)
- I'll give you the Bad Luck Badge. - You can't...
- skimp on the food. - Okay.
(I should've gone for it.)
Gosh, that looks so tasty.
- All right. - Let me taste it.
- Hey, here it is. - Give him a lot.
- I'm going to give you a lot. - Okay.
- Here you go. 1, 2, 3. - My gosh.
I really want to eat jjajangmyeon.
(Eating someone else's food is the tastiest.)
(I'm not going to watch this.)
- Whose badge is that now? - Can't we give it to other people?
- We need to go to the next place. - Right.
- Let's have pork belly. - What's next?
- Let's eat pork belly next. - Yes, let's do that.
There's a thin pork belly place near Bucheon Station.
- It's open 24 hours. - Let's go.
Let's go to Bucheon.
- You must order one serving. - Let's get going first.
It is cheap.
(The number of Bad Luck Badges for each member)
- We'll have pork belly next. - That sounds good too.
I'm going to put rice, a piece of pork belly,
garlic with gochujang on top of the lettuce.
I'm going to eat it with salt.
- I'm so hungry. - We must eat it with rice.
I think we're almost there.
- We are 3.7km away. - All right.
(Humming)
We got here faster than I thought.
(Seok Jin starts humming all of a sudden.)
(Glancing)
(Singing)
What was the name of the song?
(He makes a trumpet sound.)
- What? - That was good.
- I was surprised with myself too. - Hey, that sounded really cool.
Let's try that again.
(They suddenly form an a capella group.)
(So Min joins in too.)
What is that?
(Drop the beat.)
Hey, we sound great.
(Their questionable song continues.)
(It's caught between being a noise and a song.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo is enjoying the song in her dreams.)
How could Ji Hyo sleep in this commotion?
Is she sleeping? My gosh, Ji Hyo is sleeping?
(It must have been the tasty jjajangmyeon.)
- We are here. We arrived. - We're at the restaurant.
- Jae Seok, it's this one here. - This is it.
Let's eat!
- Let's eat! - It's 2 dollars and 50 cents.
- No way. - This is the place.
- Look. It's open 24 hours. - It's 2 dollars and 50 cents.
How could it be only 2 dollars and 50 cents?
My gosh, thin pork belly. I love it.
- It's only 2 dollars and 50 cents? - Hello.
- Has the owner gone mad? - My gosh.
- It's only 2 dollars and 50 cents? - Yes.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
I'm sorry to ask this,
but could we film in this restaurant?
- Would it be okay? - Sure.
- Thank you, ma'am. - We'll film only on this side.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
My gosh, the owner seems really good-natured.
(The cameras are set up quickly to film at the corner.)
We're rolling.
- You've arrived now. - Yes, we have.
This time, you won't have to choose a number.
- All of you might be able to eat. - Okay!
- Awesome. - What is the mission?
For this mission,
you'll choose either odd or even.
How are we going to play that?
Whoever correctly guesses whether the number of spoons...
and chopsticks is odd or even will get to eat.
- This is an individual game. - Right.
- I can shake this, right? - Yes, you can.
Of course.
- It sounds like there are a lot. - The chopsticks are in there too.
Hey, Jae Seok, what do you think?
(I can pick the opposite of his choice.)
I'll choose the opposite.
- I'll go last. - No, tell us.
- I want to pick the opposite. - Let's choose the same answer.
What do you think, So Min?
I'll go with odd.
- Me too. - Odd?
- Odd? - Then I'll go with even.
Even, odd, even.
Hey, everyone. What about this?
If you think it's odd, go that side. Come here if you think it's even.
- That was clever. - Okay.
My gosh, we picked different choices. This is bad.
- Which side is for even? - This side.
This side is for even, and that side is for odd.
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Seok Jin, and Kwang Soo choose odd.)
- I'll count one by one. - All right.
Okay.
- Odd. - Okay.
Don't play any tricks now.
- Don't play tricks. - You think so lowly of me.
- Even. - Even.
- Let's all say it. Odd. - Odd!
That's great.
- Even! - Even!
- Odd! - Odd!
Hey, this is making me so nervous.
- Odd. We're almost there. - We are almost done.
(Does he have 1 or 2 spoons left?)
He has more.
- There are two left. - It looks like there are more.
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Seok Jin, and Kwang Soo chose odd.)
(Jae Seok, Haha, Se Chan, and So Min chose even.)
Gosh, there are two left.
(Fidgeting)
Wait, why are you putting the spoon between your bottom?
- Why are you doing that? - No, this is the last one.
(I only have one left. There's an even number of them.)
Odd!
- Yes! - Hold on.
(He finds a deeply hidden spoon.)
- Hey. - All right. It's odd.
(He fails to hide a spoon.)
- Don't join Jae Seok. Then you win. - Seriously?
I wasn't even expecting to win.
(The losing members will receive Bad Luck Badges.)
- Four servings of pork belly. - My gosh, Jae Seok.
They have to get the badges too, right?
(The number of Bad Luck Badges for each member)
(The thin pork belly is being grilled on the pan.)
- My goodness. - Oh, my. Can you hear it sizzling?
- It looks good, Seok Jin. - This is amazing.
Don't grill them. You have to stir-fry them.
- Right. That's the way to go. - Stop teasing us.
- The oil seeps out. - You're right.
- Cook kimchi too. - We can cook kimchi with it.
(I'd give anything to eat that.)
(This is like a torture for members who lost.)
My goodness. Look at this.
Seriously? You're not good at cooking pork melly.
- Seriously. - "Pork melly"?
- I bet you want to eat this. - You don't know how to cook it.
- Move aside. - Are you trying to eat this?
No, no. Let me cook it for you.
- No, that's all right. - Come on.
- Why are you hitting me? - There's no need.
- What's wrong with you? - Let me cook it for you.
- Why would you cook it for us? - Come on. Move aside.
- Hey, eat up. - My goodness.
- Are you serious? - Why are you doing this?
This is how you ought to do it.
- Unbelievable. - Hey, hold on. Hey.
(His hands are swifter than their eyes.)
- Get it. - Wait.
There's a fight going on over there.
(They are searching and seizing the hidden pork belly.)
(Screaming in pain)
I researched a lot about this while watching TV.
(He's always improving as he watches the shows.)
I studied a lot about you.
- He's bleeding! - My gosh!
Hey.
(Shall we enjoy our meal now?)
- I got to taste one. - He ate one in the end.
I ate it.
(Place the piece of meat, a bit of doenjang,)
(and seasoned, sliced spring onions.)
- It's true. - Haha.
(This is the pork belly that brings joy to Ji Hyo.)
I gave you half of my jjajangmyeon.
(The meat impresses him right away.)
I will buy someone's Bad Luck Badge.
I'm going to trade one.
(Haha and Se Chan get a bite and take the badge.)
- That's good. - Why are you doing this?
- You're going to take my badge. - Okay.
- No, you can't do that. - I can't help myself.
(It's a good deal for Kwang Soo since he has two badges.)
I sold my badge to him. I gave it back to him.
(Se Chan and Haha receive 1 more badge.)
- Give him your badge. - Come on, do it.
- Yes, give one to Jae Seok. - Give it to Jae Seok.
(Should I try getting rid of mine too?)
- Everyone. - Hey.
I will give this to whoever takes my badge.
No, no. Forget it.
(No, no. Forget it.)
- Gosh, he's so annoying. - Forget it.
Why would I take his badge?
- Why would I do that? - Give him your badge.
- The price was very reasonable, - Right.
- but the meat was fresh. - It was very delicious.
- Which food will you try next? - I didn't even get to eat a lot.
- Tangsuyuk in Mok-dong. - Let's eat pork cutlet.
- Shouldn't we eat tangsuyuk? - Did you find a place?
- Tangsuyuk! - It's time for tangsuyuk.
- Tangsuyuk. - It's cheap.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I have to eat tangsuyuk.
- We don't have much time left. - We're running out of time.
If we don't finish on time, all of us will face the punishment.
- Exactly. - That's right.
It's going to be evening rush hour soon.
- There will be a lot of traffic. - Precisely.
- So we must hurry. - Luckily,
tangsuyuk and pork cutlet restaurants are nearby.
I must eat tangsuyuk. Seriously. That's only fair.
I'll choose tangsuyuk over pork cutlet.
Let me have tangsuyuk.
Tangsuyuk must be delicious too.
Strangely, we are only eating pork today.
- That's right. - If I eat tangsuyuk...
(She sounds happy.)
(Eat ulmyeon in sadness, eat jjajangmyeon when you're annoyed)
I'm annoyed, so be quiet.
(I'm starving right now.)
(She stubbornly sings the song.)
(Tangsuyuk)
- Tangsuyuk - Tangsuyuk
My goodness.
If I don't get to eat tangsuyuk,
it won't be pretty then.
I don't think you will be able to eat pork cutlet either.
- Jae Seok can't eat that either. - Right?
- Hey, Se Chan. - Yes?
Se Chan, you'd better watch your tongue.
- It's either me or you. - Today, I'm...
I'm really on the edge today.
I have a feeling that Jae Seok will go back on an empty stomach.
(Look at that joker.)
This is driving me crazy.
- Hey, we're here. - Yes, we are.
- We are only 400m away. - There's a college here?
We are almost there.
Besides, since we don't have much time, we must hurry.
When we get there, we'll finish the game quickly.
We'll move things along really fast.
My gosh, I can't believe we actually found this place and came.
- My gosh. - That's pork cutlet!
- It's only two dollars! - That looks good.
Goodness, let's get pork cutlet.
(There's a pork cutlet restaurant next to the tangsuyuk restaurant.)
Hey, the pork cutlet costs only two dollars. We'll be done then.
(How amazing!)
- It's right next to each other. - It's next to the other restaurant.
They are next to each other.
- We will accomplish our mission. - This is incredible.
- This is the tangsuyuk place. - This is it.
- Here it is. - 1 dollar and 50 cents!
This must be the place.
Hey, a bowl of anchovy noodles is only a dollar.
(Tangsuyuk, 1 dollar and 50 cents)
We can walk to the next restaurant after this.
They are right next to each other.
How could this be possible?
- Excuse me, could we film in here? - Yes.
- Could we film in here? - Would you be okay with that?
- Is that all right with you? - Thank you.
All right. Thank you.
- Is it only 1 dollar and 50 cents? - Hello.
- Is that so? - We'll have some while we shoot.
- We're sorry. - Thank you.
- My gosh, this is amazing. - I see.
(Which members will get to eat?)
Thank you.
I'm surprised that we found this place and actually came here.
- "1 dollar and 50 cents"? - How could it be so cheap?
It's crispy and savory.
Freshly-fried tangsuyuk costs only 1 dollar and 50 cents.
(It's only 1 dollar and 50 cents!)
I'm jealous of people who live in the neighborhood.
Students must come here often.
It's perfect for students.
It's not only for students.
(How many will enjoy tangsuyuk?)
I hope we all get to eat it.
Here's the next mission.
- There are four in the kitchen. - Right.
Ask one of them for their age.
The number of members that corresponds to the first digit of...
their age will get to eat.
The 10th digit?
No, the first digit.
- If it's 31, 1 gets to eat. - 1 person gets to eat.
(It depends on their age.)
We must select someone in their late 20s or 30s.
We can all eat if the age is 28.
What if it's zero like 30?
No one gets to eat.
We're in trouble.
Choose a number.
We should choose the early digits.
It's difficult.
Pick one, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo starts.)
I'll eat tangsuyuk no matter what.
What's your number?
1, 2, 3.
(Which number did he pick?)
(He gets number 8.)
(We knew it.)
He was so determined to eat.
(Why does it always happen to me?)
I bet you won't get to eat.
That's hilarious.
Who's next?
I want to eat something.
1, 2, 3.
(Se Chan gets 7.)
- 7. - 7.
What is it?
- 7. - In 2, 3.
(So Min gets 5.)
- Five. - Ji Hyo?
- 4. - She gets 4.
I'm next. In 2, 3.
- Mine is 6. - It's 6.
(Haha gets number 6.)
- We'll get... - They're 1, 2, 3.
- We're 1, 2, 3. - We'll eat no matter what.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
I got two.
- Am I 1? - 3.
(Seok Jin is 3, Jae Seok is 2, Jong Kook is 1.)
He doesn't even like it.
He doesn't even want any.
I got number one.
I was only thinking about their age.
I didn't care which number I would pick,
but it turned out to be one.
Jong Kook is good at guessing the age.
Let's pick one person.
If it's 28, all of us get to eat.
I bet the owner is 28.
- The person on the right. - They could be...
31 years old.
Pick the woman in the middle.
Let's pick the one in the middle.
She seems 27 years old.
(She appears to be 27.)
She's in her early 20s.
- She's in her early 20s. - She's in her early or mid 20s.
I pick the man on the left.
(He seems to be in the late 20s or 30s.)
- Let's pick the one on the right. - It could be...
- Could he be in his 30s? - By the way,
I'm sorry for barging in like this.
We apologize.
Which person shall we pick?
Let's pick the woman.
The one in the middle.
- I agree. - Me too.
- Me too. - Do you want to choose?
Based on majority vote, you choose the woman.
(They pick the woman.)
How old are you?
- Is she in her early 20s? - How old are you?
(Tangsuyuk depends on her age.)
If it's 28, all of us get to eat.
How old are you?
(How old could she be?)
I'm 33 years old.
(She's in her early 30s.)
See? She's 33.
(Four members fail to eat.)
She's as old as you.
Does Jae Seok get to eat?
(The three get to eat.)
We're the first three.
- We're the first three. - Does he get to eat?
It's the three of us.
(33 years is the best age.)
She looks very young.
- I thought you were in your teens. - I thought she was 26.
(Did you think I was in my late 20s?)
What about the man on the right?
- Pardon? - I'm 37 years old.
(He's 37 years old. That was close.)
We should have picked him.
(He could have gotten his first meal.)
How old are you?
- I'm 19 years old. - 19?
(You should have picked me.)
- He's 19. - 19?
- Is he 19 years old? - 19?
- He's a senior in high school. - Who?
(He could have made everyone eat.)
He's a senior in high school.
He's 19 years old!
(He wasn't 33 years old!)
I had a chance to eat too.
You picked her.
I said to pick the man!
I told you that he looked young.
I told you that he seemed young.
Even I could have eaten.
- Anyway, we get to eat. - Let's eat.
I already have two badges.
I had nothing to eat for hours.
(Each of them gets a badge.)
For how many people is it?
- It's for 1 person. - 1 person?
- Is it this much? - Really?
It's a lot.
- It's freshly fried. - Right.
- Really? - It smells amazing.
The portion is generous.
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you.
(He takes a bite.)
(It only costs 1.5 dollars.)
Is it delicious?
It's very good.
- It only costs 1.5 dollars. - It's really delicious.
(They're about to pass out.)
It's really delicious.
Give me a piece.
I gave you some.
I'm so tired.
(He's desperate.)
- It's because I'm tired. - Bring your dish.
Look at my eyes.
(They complain about hunger.)
Look at Haha.
(Will So Min get a bite?)
No, it's okay.
- It's really good. - It's okay.
(Did she really refuse?)
It's okay.
(Is she refusing a bite?)
(So Min loves to steal other people's food.)
It's really good.
- What's going on? - What's happening?
What's going on?
- What's happening? - What's going on?
(The other table gets tangsuyuk.)
That's not right.
It's because...
(You didn't know, did you?)
- The pork cutlet is... - What are you doing?
What's going on?
You should win to eat.
Pork cutlet costs 2.5 dollars.
We have enough money to eat it.
- What are you doing? - What's going on?
If we spend more, imagine what will happen to you.
(He's about to choke.)
I'm about to choke.
You're not some gangster.
I'm just informing them.
(He gives him a warning.)
He's drinking the sauce.
(He's so hungry that he drinks the sauce.)
- Hey. - It's because I'm really hungry.
Wait a minute.
- Se Chan is very hungry. - It's because I like it.
It's delicious.
Were you that hungry?
Still, you shouldn't drink the sauce.
It's delicious.
- Let's eat pork cutlet. - Let's go.
Let's go. Shall we go next door?
- It's right next door. - It's two dollars.
- Is it right next door? - Yes.
- Thank you. - Let's go.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We thank the staff.)
It's right next door.
- We have 2 dollars and 50 cents. - That's great.
(They take their time.)
Wait.
Is it closed?
(We're on break.)
- We're in trouble. - Why?
- It's closed. - The restaurant is closed.
Is it closed?
(We're on break.)
- We're in trouble. - Why?
- It's closed. - The restaurant is closed.
- Why did you eat? - Wait.
(This is bad news.)
(The pork cutlet restaurant was next door to the tangsuyuk place.)
(They took their time as they were certain to clear the mission.)
It's their break time.
- Right now? - They're preparing.
Why did you eat without thinking?
(They only have 2.5 dollars left.)
- It's because of Se Chan. - Didn't you read it?
Where's the two-dollar place?
Find it now.
- Isn't it in Mokdong? - Goodness.
- Where was it? - Where is it?
- I saw it. - This is terrible.
- Didn't you read it? - It's in Hongdae.
Let's go to Hongdae.
- Let's go. - Let's go to Hongdae.
Let's hurry.
- There's one. - Let's just go.
I'll scold you in the car.
Let's go.
- Is it 2.5 dollars? - Yes.
How could you act out of whim?
I saw how flustered Se Chan was.
(They head to Hongdae.)
I was so surprised.
Where is it in Hongdae?
Call the restaurant.
- Where is it in Hongdae? - It can't be more than 2.5 dollars.
We almost got in trouble.
No, we're already in trouble.
We don't have time.
Turn on the light.
How much time do we have?
(They have 40 minutes left.)
How much is the place?
- It's 2.5 dollars. - Are you sure?
- Yes. - If it's 50 cents more...
(They fail if it's more than 2.5 dollars.)
If it's 2.8 or 2.9 dollars,
- it's over. - What is it?
- Is it more expensive? - There's a 1.9-dollar one.
- Where? - It's in Hongdae.
Really? Let's go.
- Is it in Hongdae? - Is it an old price?
The blog post was written...
- It's this year. - It was posted...
- No, it's last year. - in September 2017.
- It's served with kkakdugi. - That's great.
I want some kkakdugi.
(They head for the pork cutlet.)
(They arrive at the restaurant in 25 minutes.)
Even noodles cost three dollars.
(Is this the place?)
How can pork cutlet cost 1.9 dollars?
- It's the main street. - It's true.
Is it okay to shoot?
Is it okay?
Is it okay to shoot here?
There's fish cake soup too.
- We're here to eat pork cutlets. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Does your pork cutlet cost...
Does it really cost a dollar and 90 cents?
The members have found pork cutlets...
that cost a dollar and 90 cents per portion.
How lucky they are.
(They're so lucky.)
The owners must be out of their minds.
Is it even possible?
Does it really cost only a dollar and 90 cents?
- Do we just get pork cutlets? - Yes.
- That's okay. - That's okay.
They must get no profit.
Noodles cost more than pork cutlets.
(Their pork cutlets cost a dollar less than the noodles.)
Curry pork cutlet with sauce costs exactly 2 dollars and 50 cents.
(Curry pork cutlet with sauce)
Guys, you have to draw a number.
- Here we go. - Let's do this.
If I fail this time too, I'll have starved all day.
Jong Kook isn't...
- desperate. - I'm not.
You shouldn't be desperate if you want to win.
Draw a number...
1, 2, 3.
- 3. - Mine must be 1.
- 1, 2, 3. - Unbelievable.
- I can't believe it. - I picked two.
1 of the 2...
(If they're lucky, everyone will get to eat.)
I'm so happy.
You'll roll an eight-sided dice.
The number will determine how many can eat?
(They'll roll an eight-sided dice.)
That's correct.
Ma'am, please roll the dice.
Are you ready?
- Ready... - You can do this.
- Please. - We want an eight.
Please do a good job.
- We want an eight. - Please.
Throw it high.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
(They're hungry, and some of them will be penalized soon.)
(The owner will determine who will get pork cutlets.)
- Wow, two. - Okay.
(Only 2 people can eat.)
- Okay. - Two people can eat.
I haven't eaten anything.
- What number do you have? - I haven't eaten anything.
Four.
- My number is five. - I haven't eaten anything.
Too bad.
- We can order curry pork cutlets. - Okay.
- Two curry pork cutlets? - Yes.
- Two? - Yes.
We have to move to another place.
- Okay. - Okay.
I haven't eaten anything.
Is that even possible?
- Pork cutlets have arrived. - Thank you.
(They'll enjoy the pork cutlets in a park.)
Thank you.
Two-dollar pork cutlets.
- They're freshly fried. - Pork cutlets.
- Oh, my. - Look at that.
This costs two dollars?
Let me try a piece first.
- Okay. - Go ahead.
Let's try it.
(Impressed)
- It looks tasty. - It's steaming.
Does it taste like curry?
- It tastes good. - It tastes good.
- It's driving me crazy. - Can I try the sauce?
Se Chan, come here.
Okay. I'll be right there.
- Here. - Thank you.
(Jong Kook shares his food with others.)
Thank you.
(I picked it up on the street.)
Aren't you going to eat?
Eat.
The one who has accumulated the most Bad Luck Badges...
is Se Chan.
He'll choose one member who will be penalized with him.
You know what the penalty is.
You have to take 10,000 steps in dog costumes.
You can only walk straight.
(They'll walk the crowded Hongdae street...)
(in these costumes.)
Se Chan, please put this headband on a member.
(This is hard.)
I'll put it on from behind.
(The Nevis Swing trio and Jae Seok have been excluded.)
I've been penalized so many times.
One...
(The candidates are Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and So Min.)
Two...
(One of them will take 10,000 steps in a dog costume.)
Three.
(Who will wear the costume that symbolizes the Year of the Dog?)
(So Min)
(Se Chan, you brat.)
Good. It's a good choice.
I was hoping he'd choose So Min.
So Min has never done anything like this.
You should try wearing tights. So Min.
I had to walk next to Kwang Soo when he was wearing a rooster costume.
(It's no big deal.)
That's right.
- Yes. - In the Year of the Rooster.
Our youngest members will be penalized.
It's been decided.
(It even starts to snow.)
- It's snowing. - It's freezing.
(The dogs,)
(Se Chan, and So Min are on the street.)
It's like "A Dog of Flanders".
- You look cute. - You look great.
I love it.
I'd love to try it.
Are you sure? Do you want to switch?
- I'd love to try it. - It's freezing.
- So Min, this is amazing. - You look great.
It's hilarious.
- It's snowing. - Guys.
We'll give you step counters.
If you take 5,000 steps for real, you'll have to walk 2.5km.
- 2.5km? - So just shake your step counter...
while you walk until it says you've taken 5,000 steps.
- Shake it while you walk. - Shake your step counter.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
We'll see you next week.
See you next week.
(We'll see you next week.)
- Can we go home? - Bye.
Se Chan and So Min, bye.
- Bye! - Bye!
Se Chan, wait and see.
I'll get back at you.
- I'll get back at you next week. - You look great.
(See you next week.)
Bye!
- We have to walk 2.5km? - Yes.
Guys, be careful.
- There you go. - Come here.
- You're doing great. - Don't fight.
- That's my boy. - You're doing a good job.
- That's my boy. - Look at that.
What's happening?
(People are surprised to see them.)
Don't take pictures.
(Embarrassed)
I'm so embarrassed.
Se Chan, I'm so embarrassed.
(They became stars on social media that day.)
(It's Running Man again.)
Hello, I'm Yang Se Hyung.
(Lying)
- Hello, I'm Song Ji Hyo. - This is Jeon So Min.
I'm Song Ji Hyo. Hello.
(Sorry. We had no choice.)
Why are we doing this in Hongdae on a snowy evening?
You and me...
(I'm sorry, So Min.)
So Min, we're almost done. We'll walk to Hapjeong-dong.
(They might walk all the way to Hapjeong-dong.)
(They're shaking their step counters.)
I'm done!
(Finally!)
- You're lying. - I'm serious.
I'm done.
Okay.
You're finished.
Both of you are finished.
- You can go home now. - Let's go home!
Let's go. Thank you.
Bye.
You can see it on TV at 4:50pm on Sunday. Thank you.
(Now, "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals" will be revealed.)
Please watch Running Man.
I'm so embarrassed.
(Now, "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals" will be revealed.)
(The shooting starts early in the morning.)
It's pretty.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
I see all the costumes are ready.
I love this. It's perfect.
Kwang Soo is just a giraffe?
I should have made him do something else.
What a shame.
I didn't pay so much attention to Kwang Soo.
(They start preparing in the waiting room.)
(Other members arrive.)
- What are you doing here? - Good morning.
- Good morning. - Is today the day?
Look at those costumes.
Is there a catfish costume?
(Everything is set for you.)
What is this?
(The costumes have been prepared according to Jae Seok's plan.)
- This is Seok Jin's. - Yours is here.
This is mine? What am I?
- What are you? - What am I?
You look like a kid. What am I?
- You look like a kid. What am I? - You're Toshio.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
- Why do you look so neat? - I won't...
do anything.
(Haha's role is...)
You'll be Toshio.
(Toshio)
(Toshio is a baby ghost from the movie, "Ju-On".)
What?
(Jae Seok put a lot of thought into it.)
You said you wanted to be something funny.
You said you were tired of penguins.
Is this mine?
What? Yes. It's a catfish.
This doesn't look like a catfish.
I know. What happened?
I'm a man.
(Why does a catfish need a bra?)
Haha, good morning. Are you Toshio?
- Good morning. - Good morning.
- Your costume is cute. - Go to the next room.
Se Chan, will you be a mermaid?
I'm supposed to be a catfish. I'm not sure.
Why would a catfish wear a bra?
Are you a female catfish?
- Are you female? - Yes. I'm a female catfish.
(He's given up.)
(They have to wear costumes Jae Seok assigned to them.)
It's going to be cold.
It looks more like a mermaid.
It does.
(The silver costume looks garish.)
I'm a man.
Good morning.
- Seok Jin is here. - Good morning.
- Seok Jin, you'll be a beggar. - What?
(You'll be a beggar.)
- What? - You'll be a beggar.
A beggar? Why am I a beggar?
A beggar? Good morning.
- Okay. - A beggar.
Why am I a beggar?
Are you a beggar?
What is this?
(Why am I a beggar?)
(He bet all his money that Jong Kook and Ji Hyo weren't together.)
(Many viewers said they wanted to see him broke.)
(Jae Seok decided to grant their wish.)
I'm a beggar? What are you?
A catfish.
(He's no better.)
I'm a female catfish.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
It's so noisy.
(Jong Kook comes in.)
Hello.
- Hello. - He's here.
- Jong Kook... - Your costume is a cat.
- I'm a cat. - It's pink.
- It's cute. - It is.
I like cute things.
It's cute.
I'm a cat.
- I'm glad you like it. - It's cute.
It looks like you're shooting a finance commercial.
- I tried to look normal. - It's like a finance commercial.
You look trustworthy.
(Ji Hyo arrives.)
What's this?
No way.
(Goodness)
(This can't be.)
Ji Hyo, that's you.
- Am I No-Face? - Yes, you are.
- I'm No-Face? - Yes.
- What is wrong with you? - Aren't you happy?
You're No-Face.
(No-Face is a character in Japanese animation.)
(It has an oval face with dark eye makeup.)
- You need to... - What's this?
do makeup like No-Face, okay?
You're No-Face. I thought hard...
to make you look funny and settled on this.
- You're No-Face. - Seriously.
- She's No-Face. - No way.
I had no idea.
I'm a man. Why do I have to dress as a woman?
- You're here. - Just do it.
- Hey. - Just do it.
(He makes everybody laugh.)
What are you supposed to be?
I'm supposed to be a catfish.
Why do I look like a cutlassfish?
You're a female catfish. Why are your shoulders so wide?
Hey.
You don't need to put any makeup on.
You look like a catfish.
You do.
(He already looks like a catfish with his face alone.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Come on over, Kwang Soo. - Hello.
- Hi, Haha. - Hi.
- Kwang Soo. - Get changed, giraffe.
- Kwang Soo... - What's this?
needs some makeup too.
That's you today.
- That's me? - How do I put this on?
Yes, it's you.
Hurry, Kwang Soo.
If you don't want to do it, you can win.
- Okay. - Sure.
Let's play another round.
- All right. - What?
It looks good.
You look so scary.
Is this Toshio?
Am I just a person next to the homeless person?
It looks good.
What's this? Goodness.
- It's good. Good. - Where are you?
Let's play another round.
Just another round.
I'm so mad.
(He gets up.)
How tall am I?
I'm too tall.
You have to put makeup on. Sit down.
That's so cool.
Let's do another round.
(He still wants to play another round.)
Another round. I mean it. Please?
I just remembered what I could dress Jae Seok as.
I can't say it now because he may not do it.
Let's play another round.
- Am I an alien? - One more time.
I'm not a catfish.
- You can't. - Let's play another round.
Why am I female?
Why am I female? Why?
What's this?
I have a fear of heights.
(Shaking)
(He's wobbly.)
Can you catch Kwang Soo in the camera?
You have to.
Ji Hyo likes her No-Face costume.
It's a giraffe.
I'm not a giraffe.
He ate it.
Everybody is happy.
It looked like I was feeding a real giraffe.
Eat, giraffe.
Who told you to win?
(It's a giraffe that eats gimbap.)
The giraffe almost ate my hand.
- Let me ask you for a favor. - What is it?
Can you change the lightbulb?
You're going to fall.
I'm relieved.
They're so happy.
I knew they'd like it.
(While they have fun,)
(the set is being prepared.)
("Yu Jae Seok and the Animals", directed by Jae Seok)
(How will the set look?)
- It's because I'm wearing this. - Really?
It's because of this.
Seok Jin is naturally funny.
- He's totally transformed. - The makeup was done perfectly.
Thank you.
(He's a homeless person.)
What?
It doesn't look like you put makeup on.
- Gosh. - I'm serious.
Of course, this is my makeup.
Did you see what he did?
- "Gosh". - You punk.
"You punk".
(The trophy goes in the can.)
I need to find it.
It's Top Excellence Award.
Gosh.
Jee Seok Jin of Running Man.
(He received the award last month.)
(It's the irony of fate.)
Why is my nose runny?
Do homeless people have runny noses?
- I don't think so. - It's cold.
Why do I have a runny nose?
And...
we haven't started yet,
so don't run around too much. Stay still.
- Okay? - I'm not running around.
- I'm staying still. - Don't run around.
(Fidgeting)
And Seok Jin.
Stop looking for cameras. Stay still.
My feet are frozen.
You're a parrot.
Thank you.
(At that moment)
- You look great. - That looks great, Ji Hyo.
(Ta-da)
- Leave it that way. - Leave it.
She looks great.
Don't touch her.
It looks perfect.
It does?
(She looks exactly like No-Face. The actress has transformed.)
Aren't you happy with it?
It'll help you get new roles.
(She can act more characters now.)
(She puts the costume on.)
(She claps for herself.)
(She's put on many costumes before,)
(but this one is the best.)
(She comes in.)
You scared me.
- I was startled. - You look great, Ji Hyo.
- That scared me. - It's No-Face.
- Goodness. - You really scared me.
(She has everybody's attention.)
It looks great.
- This is so funny. - Ji Hyo.
Kwang Soo looks cool.
- Who? - Kwang Soo.
He looks like a character from "Cats".
I do look cool. I like this.
For his nose...
Can you let...
- Se Chan do this? - Do this.
- Let him do it. - It's okay.
- Would you like to try? - Ma'am.
Don't give up on me. Please.
Do this for the nose.
(Leave me to it.)
- Is that white? - Yes.
I'll do the outline.
- Why? Just do it. - No, this is right.
(Let me see.)
(It goes like this.)
All right. You have to do that on the nose.
- This is meticulous. - Right.
- See? It's better. - That's good.
You are happy about it.
Aren't you happy it looks good?
- This is it. - Right?
That's what we want.
(The expert and Se Chan work passionately together.)
(The giraffe makeup is complete.)
Thank you.
(He gets up.)
(Sighing)
(He puts the giraffe head on.)
You've never been a giraffe to this level, right?
You're a perfect giraffe.
- He looks great. - You never did it to this level.
He thinks Kwang Soo looks great.
(He looks biologically giraffe.)
Can you do it up to here?
Let's take a picture.
How am I supposed to do this?
You're not in the screen.
- I can't do anything else. - Hold on.
- Wait. - I can't do this.
I'm coming down.
Come down.
Let's take...
(Collapsing)
Are you all right?
(It's dangerous to stand on two feet.)
Are you okay? Be careful.
Be careful.
Be careful, Kwang Soo. Are you okay?
I just bungee jumped.
That was so scary.
(He's petrified.)
Who did that?
Don't take pictures.
Don't try to take pictures.
I wanted to commemorate...
My phone is broken.
- Is it okay? - It's broken.
Why did you do this?
- Is it okay? - This is all I had, and it's gone.
- Goodness. - Is it okay?
- I lost everything. - Seok Jin.
- His phone is broken. - It is.
It won't work.
(So Min, the parrot, shows up.)
(She's an angry parrot.)
I'm angry.
It looks great.
- I like the parrot. - She's a parrot.
Look at the giraffe.
Are you a giraffe or a lion? What are you?
- He's a giraffe. - How could you?
- I can knock you out. - How is he a lion?
(This looks like "Fantastic Beasts".)
- You look like a duck. - She's a parrot.
(The angry parrot terrorizes the giraffe.)
Stop it.
She kicked him.
(He can't move by himself.)
I can't move.
(I was born human.)
What's this? What did I do?
(Who is this giraffe in the mirror?)
- Put your shoes on, Jong Kook. - I have shoes?
I'm sorry, but I wasn't trying to make you look cute.
I'm so cute.
I love this.
- Gosh... - He loves it.
(He's supposed to be a cat, but he looks like Tiger Mask.)
(The members are ready to go.)
I think we are all ready. Let's get moving.
- Okay, let's go. - Let's go to the set.
Let's finish this fast.
- Hold onto him. Stop eating. - Seok Jin.
You have to hold him. He can't walk on his own.
You've never been a giraffe to this level, right?
(Kwang Soo is a perfect giraffe today.)
She's a parrot on a roost.
(Jong Kook is a muscular cat.)
He can be a cat on top of a fireplace.
Seok Jin needs to hold an empty can.
(Se Chan is a catfish, and Seok Jin is a beggar.)
(Ji Hyo is No-Face, and Haha is Toshio.)
No-Face looks great.
("Yu Jae Seok and the Animals")
- This is yours. - I caught a cat.
(They're in the studio.)
What's that?
It looks like we're doing a performance.
This looks like a performance.
Who does this for a TV rating notice?
Who does a TV rating notice like this?
Why is one shoulder lower than the other?
Haha is a bit taller.
(My crutches are of different heights.)
It's high.
Everybody.
(He's the main guy today.)
So Min, go on the roost.
You are the only one who looks nice.
(She fits in 200 percent.)
So Min.
You look like a real bird.
That's so funny.
I'll put you into places.
(I'm a real bird.)
The giraffe goes at the back.
Where?
Move over.
(He's slow.)
(He's a sad animal with a long torso.)
- In front of that? - That's good.
- Turn around. - Stop going. Turn.
(He takes forever.)
- And the cat... - Okay.
is next to the parrot.
- Go next to the parrot. - Here?
- Here? - Yes.
That's a good seat.
It's good. I'm in the middle.
Move. Go away.
She's too into her role.
Let me see.
(He's not into his character yet.)
(She isn't either.)
(He isn't.)
You have to lie down.
You have to lie down. You're a catfish.
- Am I really a catfish? - Yes.
(He keeps on having identity issues.)
- Your costume... - You can't see me.
wasn't ready.
Shouldn't the giraffe go in between those two?
- Where? - Next to the parrot.
(That's the spot.)
(They help him.)
(It requires a few people to move him.)
We can do this in five seconds?
Are there too many people on this side?
Yes, there are.
- Let's go back then. - Jae Seok.
Stop moving me around.
There are too many people here.
It's not an easy thing to do.
The beggar has cookies in his can.
(Goodness)
- Take it out. - Why?
Stop eating.
- Why do you want to take it out? - What are you doing?
- Hey. - Stop eating.
My trophy.
- Bring it back. - He put cookies in here.
- Hey. - It has to be realistic.
You have to be hungry. Why did you put cookies in there?
My gosh.
(Don't ruin the atmosphere. Stay still, homeless man.)
This is good. You two look so cute.
(Toshio and No-Face)
(Are we doing this right?)
You guys are so cute.
- What about me? - What?
- What about me? - Stay still.
(This is so sad.)
Jong Kook looks like Ahn Moon Suk.
He looks like her from the side.
(Who's Ahn Moon Suk from these two?)
Cat, come here please.
Where?
The beggar...
- is your owner. - I am his?
(The beggar is your owner.)
- Okay. - Lie down.
(I am...)
(the cute cat.)
- Good job. - You met a bad owner.
Seok Jin is pretending to pat Jong Kook's head.
He's not really touching him.
He's pretending.
(I can't touch this cat.)
Then I'll come in.
I'll stand here. It's here.
(He wants the camera on him.)
- Let's not move around. - Sorry?
Give us some lines.
- What lines? - Let us say the age 12 part.
Okay. I'll give you a line.
We can say, "12 years and older".
You can make a squawking sound.
Like this?
Say, "rated".
- Rated. - "Rated 12 years and older".
Rated. Okay?
I'll come to the middle.
Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
12 years and older.
Be louder.
- 12 years and older. - 12 years and older.
Stop it.
Do your job.
I was teaching her.
- 12 years and older. - 12 years and older.
12 years and older. Rated 12 years and older.
12 years and older.
(I can do it too.)
Stop it.
- Why are you holding the trophy? - Right?
Why is his trophy there?
It's honoring his past.
Okay?
Jong Kook, can you go on your knees?
- I can't see your face. Do this. - Okay.
Lick your hands.
(I'm an obedient cat.)
You two are great.
Toshio and No-Face are good.
- What about me? - The giraffe.
You have to make some noise. Do this with your tongue.
Right.
(Like this?)
- Do this. - Do I say something?
No, don't do that.
Stick your tongue out, and act.
(This is good acting.)
I won't come to the center.
I own this beggar.
- That looks so scary. - Wait.
I feel sorry for that beggar.
- What's wrong? - What?
Why can't a cat raise a person?
- Lie on his lap. - Me?
Yes.
Repeat after Jae Seok.
Say, "Running Man is".
I'll copy him.
While you guys are here,
I'll come in.
Do you have to look so gentle?
- Running Man is... - Running Man is...
No.
Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated 12 years and older.
12 years and older. Got it?
She's copying you because she's a parrot.
It's not funny.
Sir, you can do that when you're the director.
Let's do this again.
Let's do it again.
I'm so mad!
What if I win again?
My gosh.
Keep doing that, So Min.
Keep doing that.
Let's practice. This is the last time.
Ready.
- It's good. - Let's go.
(They've practiced.)
(They're absorbed in their roles.)
(Let's show our great acting skills.)
- Sorry. I need to use the bathroom. - Jae Seok.
(Excuse me.)
Jae Seok.
Why do you need to use the bathroom?
I'll be back.
Why all of a sudden?
Does he have a mission to complete?
Is this a mission or something?
I'm getting dizzy.
(Chuckling)
(She's satisfied with how she looks.)
- This looks good. - We can't get...
solo shots, right?
You have a good spot.
- We're in the background, right? - Yes.
- Running Man is... - Hey.
When Jae Seok says his line, let's jump in.
You can't do that.
It won't take long. Let's go in one try.
Let's do it twice and pick the better one.
Let's practice. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
12 years and older. Jae Seok is stupid.
(Jae Seok is stupid.)
Don't do that.
- Don't do that. - That was good.
Hey, don't do that.
You call that improvisation?
She's a drunk parrot.
Let's go twice.
Flap your wings as if you're flying.
You have a big role, So Min. I'm jealous.
- You get to flap your wings. - She's the main character.
I have a big role.
Jong Kook, lick your hand.
You're sticking your tongue out, right?
No-Face and Toshio.
- I'm doing it. - Good.
And... Hey.
(What?)
Why are you playing the lobster?
I have to do something.
This is a lonely spot.
- I don't know what you are. - Me neither.
- Are you a catfish or a mermaid? - I don't know.
You're an alien.
Let's go.
I should play this.
- Let's go. - You'll make noise.
Don't play that.
- You'll make noise. Stay still. - Let me do it.
- Stay still. - Goodness.
Do what I tell you to do.
Why do you have so many ambitions?
I thought I was supposed to hit this.
- I'm sorry. - Put it down.
Don't do it.
(While the three members argue,)
(they are forgotten.)
Seok Jin.
- Put it down. - Don't do it.
You scumbag of a beggar!
- Stop it. - I'm sorry.
- Finish it. - Stop it.
Hurry.
Why are you hitting me?
(Too much greed makes the other members mad.)
- Why do I have this then? - Don't be greedy.
- Fine. - Don't be greedy.
- This is a TV rating notice. - Put it down.
Viewers don't expect anything from you,
- so don't do it. - It's mine.
Don't do it. Put this inside.
This is symbolic. Leave it alone.
- Go. - Leave it inside.
It's mine!
- That stupid beggar. - Hurry up.
- Get out. Come here. - Hurry.
(They wrestle with each other.)
- Don't do it. - Kick him out.
Get out.
- Fine. - Do as you are told.
- Spray salt on him. - Gosh.
- What are you doing? - He's a tyrant.
Do as you are told, everybody.
That's the only way we will get done quickly.
- Let's do two takes. - Okay.
Here we go. Cue.
(They calm down.)
Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
12 years and older.
You blocked out the words.
His timing was off, too.
- You blocked out my voice. - He said the words a bit late.
This is a festival.
- Festival, my foot! - It's a festival.
The audio...
(Kicking)
You blocked out the audio.
No-Face is angry.
No-Face, are you okay?
Do it right.
All right.
You blocked out So Min's voice.
Don't beat the empty can. Take it from him.
Hey.
- Why are you coming this way? - He is exhausted.
(Kicking)
Hey.
What do you think you are doing?
- Seok Jin. - All right. All right.
I want to get off this thing.
All right. I won't beat the empty can.
I am feeling dizzy.
I need some anxiety-relieving pills.
It's a festival. I did it because it's a festival.
This will be our last take.
I am not the type to shoot for long. I work quickly.
- Okay. - We only need five seconds.
- It's shaped like a heart. - Stop it.
Let's go. Position your hands.
- Let's go. - Your hair is flying in the air.
I can't make you go flying in the air.
(What can I do?)
(I guess you are right.)
Focus. This is the last take.
(For the last time, action.)
Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
12 years and older. Jae Seok is an utter jerk!
- So Min! - What are you doing?
You utter jerk!
Can't you do it right?
Hey!
(There goes what was supposed to be our last take.)
- What are you doing? - I got so angry.
I was too angry.
This is a TV rating notice for 12 years and older.
What exactly is our problem?
Why can't we finish it?
Let me take off my shoes!
I feel nauseous.
Focus. This is the last take.
Let's focus. This isn't hard.
Your greed is making this hard.
Why do you keep messing it up...
when there is only one line?
Look at us siblings from Mapo-gu.
- You are doing well. - We don't try anything.
- Your greed is making this hard. - Stop being greedy.
Why are you so greedy?
Squash the greed that bubbles up in your heart.
All of us need to do our part.
Put it down.
- What? - Put the lobster down.
This is the last piece of my pride.
I need this for my pride.
All right.
It's okay to hold a lobster.
Let's go.
This is the last take. You need to do your parts well.
(With the hope that this'll be the last take, action.)
Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
12 years and older. 12 years and older.
Why does it sound like she's swearing?
(Did she just swear?)
Hold on. Don't repeat it like that.
- Don't do it. - Don't do it.
It really sounds a bit...
It sounds like a swear word.
Let's wrap it up. I think we are getting there.
- You are doing well, right? - Yes.
Let's go.
No matter how it goes, this will be our last take.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's go.
(The production crew is out of tape.)
It will air for a month.
(This time, it's the real one.)
No matter how it goes, this will be our last take.
Okay.
Cue.
(Let go of your greed.)
(For the very last time, action.)
Running Man is...
(We reveal the finished version of "Yu Jae Seok and the Animals".)
("Yu Jae Seok and the Animals")
(You will see this TV rating notice starting from next week.)
- Running Man is... - Rated...
12 years and older. Jae Seok is stupid.
My goodness.
(Embezzlers, Jae Seok and So Min)
(The lazy one,)
(Kwang Soo)
(Petty thieves,)
(Se Chan and Seok Jin)
(I am 203cm tall.)
(The swindlers,)
(Haha, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo)
(A place for sinners)
(Prison?)
(They will become new people after 8 years.)
(Welcome to Running Prison.)
(The eight petty criminals' prison live start.)
(Tofu is the only way they can escape.)
(If you want to leave, acquire tofu.)
(Tofu disappears.)
(Prison survival race for tofu)
Curse you! Three generations of your family will fall.
(Don't say such harsh words.)
(Running Prison)