(Last week)
(Which members served the penalty?)
(The members voted for Seok Jin and Kwang Soo to do the penalty.)
(These two members were resolute to take their revenge.)
(And unexpectedly, they are given a chance to take their revenge.)
(However, the staff has prepared conditions for them.)
(One of their identities as Furious Santa will be revealed.)
(Despite the unfavorable conditions,)
(they demonstrate a strong will to get their revenge.)
Today...
(And today's couple's race has begun at last.)
(In the center of today's secret stands Jee Seok Jin.)
(The members begin to suspect him after he has been singled out.)
(Will they be able to successfully take their revenge?)
(After choosing their partners...)
I saw "About Time" yesterday. It was really good.
It's good, isn't it?
- "About Time" is a great movie. - Hey.
Lately, I've been feeling really sentimental.
(Glancing)
- Right, right. - He travels back in time, right?
- That's the one. - That movie is so good.
(After the Santas exchange mysterious eye contact,)
(Kwang Soo starts off.)
(He avoids eye contact in a rush.)
(He's acting strange.)
(Kwang Soo heads to the back of the set.)
(Looking around)
I can't do anything.
Kwang Soo, what are you looking for?
(Startled)
Water. I'm looking for water.
(He gives a pathetic excuse.)
(Kwang Soo, what are you looking for?)
I'm looking for water.
- What are you looking for? - Water.
Why are you looking for it there? It's here. Come. Take this here.
Haha, Kwang Soo keeps doing strange stuff in the back.
Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
- I really went for some water. - It's on the floor.
Why would you go there to look?
(Several hours before the filming)
What can we do to win this race? That's the hard part.
- We have to win. Right? - That's right.
We're doing an important mission today, right?
Were there any personal belongings of the members that bothered you...
or that you didn't want to see?
Something that bothered me or I didn't want to see?
Write one item for each member.
(I'll write it down since you asked, but what is this all of a sudden?)
- "Jae Seok". Hold on. - Things I don't want to see?
- His tight pants. - Tight pants.
I hate seeing him in them.
He can wear loose pants like chino pants,
- but he never wears those. - When you look at his feet,
they are always purple because his blood doesn't circulate.
Those are leggings, not pants.
Besides, he has really skinny legs.
- Tight pants for Jae Seok. - Yes, let's go with tight pants.
Okay. Tight pants.
Jong Kook? Black clothes.
- Black outfits and... - Black outfits.
Jong Kook even wears a black bag to go with his outfit.
- He suddenly started wearing it. - What's in it anyway?
When he takes off that bag, I end up giving up on the game.
(They chose this because it's scary.)
The moment he takes it off, I know that I'm done for the day.
- Write down the black bag. - Yes, the bag.
What kind of a bag is that? What's that called?
He said it was a messenger bag.
For Haha, it's probably his cell phone.
What's up with his phone?
It's just that...
(I have this.)
(For now, I want you to blur out the photo.)
(Why is Kwang Soo obsessing over Haha's cell phone?)
(Haha stores records of Kwang Soo's private life...)
(and weaknesses in his phone.)
This is one of the wishes I pray for every week.
I want Haha to lose his phone.
Haha's cell phone is like a Pandora's box.
- Don't you remember your birthday? - I know, I know.
He took a photo when Seok Jin was peeing in an alien costume.
- Don't you think that was too mean? - He posted it on his social media.
He wrote, "Happy birthday".
Let's go with his cell phone.
He's infuriating.
At some point, she's always wearing hats.
I don't think she washes her hair.
(She's way too down-to-earth.)
I wasn't the only one thinking that.
I only thought about it in my head.
- Let's go with hats. - Hats.
- Let's write down hats. - Hats.
(Hats are chosen for Ji Hyo.)
I don't know when it happened,
but So Min started to get attached to her nickname, Frog.
Whenever she uploads posts on her social media account,
she uses a lot of frog emoticons.
She has a lot of frog-related stuff.
Frog-related items.
- Frog. - Yes, frog.
You know the plaid pattern?
- Yes, yes. - They're all checkered.
Sometimes, even his coat has the checkered pattern.
He likes checkered coats.
- Checkered clothes. - Checkered clothes.
Okay, checkered clothes.
We're done.
(Tight pants, hats, black messenger bag,)
(frog-related items, cell phone, and checkered clothes)
(But why are we writing these down?)
Today,
before the race ends,
you must steal all of the six items you have just written down.
(Steal all the annoying items before today's race ends.)
(They will win if they put all of these items in a producer's bag.)
If you bring these items to an assigned place, you will win.
If you can't steal all of the items before the race finishes,
for every item you fail to steal,
you will face the penalty.
Wait, how are we supposed to... After we steal it...
If we can't steal anything,
- we'll have six penalties. - Yes.
This is...
This is impossible.
Don't be disappointed yet.
- Why not? Is there more? - We have invited...
an assistant who will help you.
There's an assistant?
(An assistant will help the Furious Santas?)
Who is it?
(Who is the assistant?)
- Hey, hello. - Hey.
My goodness.
(Who is the assistant that will help these two members?)
(And will they be able to complete their revenge mission?)
Kwang Soo. Why...
- You're suddenly acting strange. - Rip off his name tag.
Why are you going off on your own?
I guess he must have gotten a hint.
- He's looking for hints now. - He is, right?
(Feeling nervous)
By the way,
why are you filming us if Seok Jin is in the center of this?
Did you choose me after getting a mission?
No, not at all.
- I'm serious. I really didn't. - This is strange.
Something is off. Sung Hoon chose Haha.
- Yes, your choice was very odd too. - Pardon?
No, Jae Seok. I'm really shy around people I first meet.
They're suspecting everything.
It's odd that Ha Na chose Kwang Soo too.
(Se Chan can't understand her choice.)
- Why is that odd? - That's just odd.
- Isn't that weird she chose you? - You're weirder!
- Seriously. Right. - Yes, it's odd that she chose him.
I don't think Ha Na likes Kwang Soo that much.
I don't think she likes him that much.
She said that she kept thinking about me after the filming.
I get it now. No one trusts each other on this show.
- This is odd. - It's very strange.
A hint about the secret is at stake on the first mission.
(The mission starts at last.)
(A hint about the secret is at stake on the first mission.)
It's Party Tree.
(Party Tree)
- What? - Party Tree?
- Party Tree? - If you look at that side,
- on top of seven gift boxes, - Yes, I see them.
envelopes with different keywords are placed.
After checking the keyword, you may try it out as a couple.
The couple that draws out the most sympathy from other couples...
- will acquire the hint. - Okay.
Please choose the first gift box.
(What is the first keyword?)
- Should we go with the big one? - Shall we?
- Let's be bold and get the big one. - What about you?
I want the apricot-colored box.
- I wanted that one too. - Because...
Stop lying.
- I bet that wasn't the one. - I wanted that one.
Kwang Soo, stop lying. What? Come on.
- Earlier, Seok Jin was... - Stop lying.
(Why did she pick the apricot one?)
wearing an outfit that had a similar color with the box.
- I see. With Seok Jin's outfit? - I was?
(The apricot outfit of Seok Jin, in the center of the secret...)
(and the apricot-colored gift box)
Oh, right. You're paying attention to that.
- You're paying attention to that. - She's right.
It's related to Seok Jin.
That was sharp.
(Will that box's keyword have a special meaning?)
I'll choose one of the boxes there.
Let me try this out.
- This one? - No.
That wasn't loud. How about this one?
(Booing)
- This one? - Yes!
(Let's go with the apricot-colored box!)
We will narrow down our choices to these three boxes.
- Okay. - We'll choose 1 of the 3.
(My gosh, that playful guy.)
- This one? - Yes!
(Jae Seok, the MC, is hooked on playing the MC of this game.)
- Yes! - Yes!
This one?
(Screaming furiously)
(He's out of energy.)
This one is out! This box is out.
I didn't hear anyone screaming.
- I didn't hear anything. - We're late.
This one is out. Should we pick this one?
- We'll go with this box. - Okay.
(What are his criteria?)
- What is this? - What is this?
- What is this? - What is it?
- What was that? - We wasted energy for no reason.
- We just wasted our energy. - What was that for?
I didn't... I didn't hear anyone cheering.
I didn't hear any cheer.
All right. I'll give you the topic.
"I have had a memorable date on Christmas."
No way.
- A date? - Everyone.
- Date? - On Christmas?
A date on Christmas?
Tell us about your memorable date. Which one of you will go first?
- I'll go first. - So Min.
(So Min confidently tries it first.)
- She's taking the lead. - I bet hers is a crazy story.
- Tell them a good one. - So Min.
It was when I was 24.
(What is the story about?)
It was that place in Yongin.
My boyfriend wanted to go there.
- I see. The amusement park? - Yes, yes.
- Okay. - So...
But the thing is that...
- tickets are pricey on Christmas. - Right, they are expensive.
You know the coupons?
Somehow, he managed to get those coupons,
so I went to the amusement park.
We took the bus together.
We were listening to Hajji and TJ's "Glittering Stars".
She likes Hajji and TJ.
She's a big fan of Hajji and TJ.
Right. The bus windows were really steamy...
because there were so many people.
We were sitting on the bus.
We shared the earphones on our way there.
- You were listening to their song? - Yes.
We were going there while listening to Hajji and TJ's songs.
We were about to go inside.
My ex-boyfriend went,
"Oh, no. This is bad."
- Why? - I asked him why.
He kept sighing. I asked him what was wrong.
Back then,
we had to print out the coupons ourselves.
- You had to print them out. - So...
he didn't know what to do, and I told him that...
we should forget about the coupons.
He said that he couldn't.
He told me to wait.
He said he would go to a PC cafe...
- and print them out. - He wanted to print them out?
- So... - My gosh.
Poor guy.
Back then, we were still in school.
(They weren't financially well-off.)
- Money was tight at that time. - That's right.
- When we were dating, we tried... - Right.
to save up money on our meals for our dates.
He took the bus to go to a PC cafe which was pretty far away.
- PC cafes weren't nearby. - Exactly. They weren't.
After his trip to the PC cafe, we finally went in.
He went somewhere to make a call again.
"Wait here. I'm going to make a call."
Where did he keep going to?
- Where did he go? - He kept disappearing.
- Seriously. - That's weird.
It seemed like he was going somewhere to check something.
(What did he check all of a sudden?)
To see how much money he had left?
(Nodding)
- I see. - Oh, no.
- He was checking that. - He checked how much he had left.
I can totally relate to her story.
Back in the days, I used to check how much...
I had in my wallet so many times under the table at cafes.
I saved up for two weeks when I had to take out my girlfriend.
Two weeks when I was in college.
So did you continue to date him?
(Her relationship with a man who made the long trip for her)
Since we were so young back then,
I drank too much.
We broke up because of that.
(I'm breaking up with you, you drunkard!)
You broke up with a lot of guys because of your drinking.
Did you break up with him because you drank too much?
Goodness, So Min.
(For now, she's in 1st place.)
- I can relate to her story. - Yes, I can.
- I didn't have money back then. - That's right.
I would go on a date with a limited budget.
- Actually, I've never heard of... - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo's dating stories. - Tell us one.
We've never heard of your dating stories over the past nine years.
We read about her dating life through the news articles.
(He's brutally honest.)
(Sinking her head)
Stop. Stop it!
Don't look it up! Don't look it up!
- Ji Hyo, I took care of it. - Okay. That's all right.
Okay. Tell us the truth.
Just tell us the important bits.
Make it brief, and tell us the juicy parts.
Well, I dated him...
- during one of my projects. - It's after you became an actress.
(Ji Hyo's love life has been kept hidden.)
(And her Pandora's box...)
(will open at last.)
Since we couldn't go on dates outdoors...
- She was famous by then. - Was he a celebrity too?
- Well... - Both of them were celebrities.
- You said to make it short. - Okay.
You asked her to make it brief.
- Come on, don't push her. - You said that.
- Make it short. - Don't try to make it long.
Please make it short.
- You couldn't go out for dates. - You'll hurt her.
- I think he was famous too. - That's too big.
- It was me. - I think both of you were famous.
- He was a celebrity too. - We'll make it short.
- You couldn't go out. - So...
We were going to spend Christmas together at home.
- That was the plan. - We were going to spend it at home.
- Great. - Right.
You should. That's a nice way to spend Christmas.
When we were hanging out,
I fell asleep.
- My gosh. - You fell asleep again.
- You fell asleep again? - You sure sleep a lot.
He brought me to another room when I was sleeping.
I saw balloons with strings...
- filling up the whole room. - Really? My goodness.
(I prepared this for you.)
There were candles in the room.
My goodness.
Then for how long did you sleep?
(For how long did you sleep?)
- Let her finish. - He lit all the candles.
Let her finish.
Ji Hyo is a heavy sleeper, you know.
Her boyfriend probably knew that nothing would wake her up too.
He knew that I wouldn't wake up.
He had been planning this surprise before Christmas.
- He ordered the balloons. - That's romantic.
- He ordered the candles too. - I'm jealous.
I was so touched. We had some wine together...
and had a good time.
(They had wine together.)
And...
And?
They had a good time.
They had a good time. And then?
- They had a good time. - And...
(And then...)
The next morning.
(She skips to the next morning.)
(Hold on.)
- What happened? - Why is it already morning?
(What happened in the meantime?)
Tell us what happened during that time.
She skipped a part of the story.
- I mean... - You can think what you want.
- Ji Hyo. - It was going well.
She skipped some part.
The staff will edit it out anyway.
Are you going to skip the part?
You did a good job.
My goodness.
- And? - I want to hear more.
- The next morning. - The next morning.
- I'm so curious. - When I woke up,
I felt something tingling on my face.
(She felt something on her face.)
(What is it?)
It's such a gripping story.
- What could it be? - What could it be?
I thought my boyfriend was touching my face.
- That's so romantic. - To wake you up?
I thought he was trying to wake me up.
When I opened my eyes, I saw...
(When I opened my eyes, I saw...)
(What did Ji Hyo see...)
(the next morning?)
The balloons had sunk,
and the strings were touching my face.
They sank?
All I saw was the strings.
- Seriously... - Ji Hyo goes to the top.
(Ji Hyo is in 1st place now.)
(My partner is the best!)
She completely got us hooked when she skipped a part.
The story really stimulated...
our imagination.
Let's go to dinner together after this.
(Who wants to hear the rest?)
(Pandora's box will be opened some other time.)
Ji Hyo, thank you for your Christmas date story.
I loved it.
Soo Young, do you have any story?
Of course, she does.
I have always spent Christmas...
with my family...
since I was little.
- With your family? - Yes.
You've never spent any Christmas with your boyfriend?
Well...
(A sudden attack)
(She becomes weak.)
Okay.
You gave in.
Why would you bring up your family? Tell us.
You must sometimes want to be with your boyfriend.
I mean,
I always wanted to be with my boyfriend.
But I didn't even dare to dream about it.
I always had to go to church...
and be with...
(She had to go to church.)
This is...
She is so determined.
Family and church?
What can we do?
- We always have dinner together. - We failed.
We failed.
We're very devout.
I pulled out my drill,
but it broke.
- You lost. - I lost.
I admit it. I lost.
(The drill loses.)
You lost.
- Okay. - It's 1 to 0.
Sung Hoon, what about you?
- I have a question for him. - What is it?
We used to go to the same gym for a while.
- We had the same trainer. - We had the same trainer.
Sung Hoon is very tough.
He is not very friendly to girls.
But I'm not like that with my girl.
Right. Anyway, there was another female celebrity in that gym.
And he was so nice to her.
(Ha Na says Sung Hoon was nice to a female celebrity.)
- Who is she? - Ha Na...
and another female celebrity were there.
- A female celebrity... - A female celebrity...
Hold on.
Who are you talking about?
(I mean that girl.)
(Absorbed)
(Whispering)
- It's not like that. - You heard it?
(Sung Hoon seems embarrassed.)
You're mistaken.
What exactly did you see?
He would give her a ride home.
(Shocked)
- He's only nice to his girl. - That's unbelievable.
(Who is this girl?)
It was on my way home anyway.
You're leaning too much towards us.
But you never gave me a ride.
You lived somewhere else.
(Sung Hoon explains Ha Na lived somewhere else.)
Where do you live?
Nonhyeon-dong.
I lived in Nonhyeon-dong too.
(I lived in Nonhyeon-dong too.)
Why would you live there?
(He is angry Ha Na lived in Nonhyeon-dong.)
What's wrong with her living there?
Can't Ha Na live in Nonhyeon-dong?
Why can't she live there?
- Why would you blame her? - Why can't she?
You had a boyfriend back then.
(Sung Hoon defends himself by revealing Ha Na had a boyfriend.)
- I didn't. - Are you revealing everything?
(Exciting)
Reveal everything.
- Ha Na. - Yes?
Did you have a boyfriend?
I have a boyfriend now.
(She suddenly confesses she has a boyfriend.)
Suddenly?
- That's not what I asked. - Just answer the question.
- There were articles. - Yes.
- There were? - Really?
She didn't answer the question.
- There were articles. - There were?
- What about Kwang Soo? - What about Kwang Soo?
- What's going on? - There were articles?
I didn't know.
(There were articles? Ha Na has a boyfriend?)
(You said you thought about me.)
(You said I looked like a nice person.)
- What is this? - This happens to him all the time.
You didn't know?
Kwang Soo.
This happens to him all the time.
Kwang Soo, she has a boyfriend.
She has a boyfriend.
I don't understand why she said she thought about me.
Why did she think about me? When she had a boyfriend?
I didn't at that time.
(After all that has happened...)
Shouldn't Kwang Soo win?
(Shouldn't Kwang Soo win?)
I approve.
- Let him win. - Let him win.
- Let him win. - That sounds good.
- He should win. - Let him win.
- Let him win. - No.
I don't want to win! It makes things more awkward.
I don't want to win.
- I'm okay. - Now.
Right now.
It's Christmas evening right now.
Kwang Soo wins.
(Kwang Soo and Ha Na win the Christmas date story contest.)
What shall we do next?
Which one did you say?
- The orange one. - The orange one.
- We're suspecting that. - You want this?
- Yes! - Yes!
- All of you? - Yes!
(Everyone wants the orange box.)
There is a letter for you.
- Please read it out loud. - Okay.
"I have..."
He's trying to sound cheerful. It breaks my heart.
(He is trying to sound cheerful.)
I'll read it.
I'll read it. You can sit down.
"I have shown off this extreme talent on a show."
Talent.
(I have shown off this extreme talent on a show.)
It can be any kind of talent.
- Chi Yeul is an amazing dancer. - Right.
He is incredible.
He used to be a B-boy.
(Ballad singer Chi Yeul used to be a B-boy in Gumi.)
(His powerful popping took Running Man by storm.)
(From powerful to weird and sexy, he can pull off any kind of dance.)
- He's amazing. - Windmill.
He can do the windmill too.
It's been a while.
- Please dance! - Let's see him dance.
- I mean... - Yes!
(He warms up.)
He is a great dancer.
He was the best dancer in Gumi.
He is so talented.
It's been too long.
(Hesitating)
Good.
(As soon as the music starts,)
(he starts taking steps.)
He used to be a B-boy.
(Way to go, my partner!)
The song is perfect for him.
(How did you know this is my kind of song?)
So light.
- Amazing! - So light.
His steps are so light.
It's amazing.
(He is incredible.)
Let's go!
(Let me spin now.)
What is this?
(His windmill was famous in Gumi.)
(He spins 4 times.)
(It's been a long time.)
- Oh, my. - Chi Yeul.
- That was amazing. - He is so talented.
He is incredible.
- My back. - That was fantastic.
That was amazing.
Great job.
While we're at it,
can any of you...
Jae Seok, we have 24-Hour Spinner.
- 24-Hour Spinner. - But...
24-Hour Spinner.
(Variety show legend, 24-Hour Spinner)
(The legendary dancer conquered the variety show with her spins.)
It's been too long. It's been more than 10 years.
I haven't seen it since "Love Letter".
Let's see it.
- Let's go! - But...
- Please. - It was a long time ago.
It's been...
Take off your parka.
(Hesitating)
Right. This song.
(Her theme song plays.)
Take off your parka.
This...
What?
(Her spin takes us back to the early 21st century.)
(It's an honor to see her spin in real life.)
(Her movements are still light as a feather.)
- 24-Hour Spinner! - She's so good!
She's still amazing.
24-Hour Spinner!
- She hasn't changed. - Here we go.
- Spin! - Let's go!
(Let me spin once more.)
There she goes.
(Perfect)
She's the best.
Stop!
It's embarrassing.
I'd never seen it before.
- Amazing. - It's even better in real life.
She's extraordinary.
She's special.
I'm overwhelmed.
She's an amazing dancer.
Ha Na must be a good dancer too.
- She used to be a singer. - She used to be a singer.
(Ha Na was a member of an idol group.)
(She made a refreshing debut as a member of Funny in 2003.)
(Ha Na is a surprisingly good dancer.)
She was a member of Funny.
Right. Funny.
I really don't remember it.
Can I dance to S.E.S. instead?
- Okay. - I'm still living...
in the 1990s and the early 2000s.
Then we'll play something from that period.
Soo Young, do you want to join her?
- Okay. - You can dance to S.E.S, right?
- Of course. - Of course, she can.
- All right. - So Min is taking off her jacket.
- So Min is taking off her jacket. - You can do this.
- So Min is getting ready. - Take off your jacket.
Let's do this.
We can do this.
Is Soo Young Bada?
A high ponytail.
(Soo Young wants to be Bada.)
(She even copies the hairstyle.)
That was her hairstyle.
- In the middle... - That hairstyle...
- Right. - Right.
- That hairstyle... - Some in the middle.
There you go.
(The trident hairstyle is recreated.)
(It looks exactly like the original.)
Is it okay to do this?
It looks amazing.
- It's perfect. - Oh, my.
It's the SM Entertainment hairstyle.
Let's play the song.
Right before that part...
By the way, who stands in the center during the refrain?
Who stands in the center during the refrain?
What?
She's the leader.
She sounds so professional.
- Bada... - You want to be in the center?
I never stood in the center in Girls' Generation.
- That's why? - Then you stand in the center.
- Can I do that? - Okay.
- We'll make way for you. - We'll make way for you.
- Then I'll lead the refrain. - Okay.
(Sunday, Sunday Loves Music)
(The debut song of the legendary fairies, S.E.S.)
(Bada sings the climax of this song in the center.)
(Will Soo Young manage to copy Bada?)
Now.
(It's your turn.)
(Perfect)
Look at that.
(She finally gets to stand in the center.)
- She stands out. - You stand out, Soo Young.
Let's go!
(Here comes the refrain with Soo Young in the center.)
(Harmony)
(Synchronized)
(They pull off the song even better than the original singers.)
(The fairy dance is copied perfectly.)
(But...)
(one of them is struggling.)
- It's the other direction. - It's the other direction.
- So Min, it's the other direction. - It's the other direction.
- So Min. - What is she doing?
- So Min. - So Min.
(Why can't I do it right?)
This doesn't look right.
(She's doing well.)
(But it's the opposite direction again.)
She stands out.
It's the other direction.
So Min looks happy.
(She dances in the opposite direction throughout the song.)
(The 2018 version of "I'm Your Girl" finishes successfully.)
(It brings back memories.)
- Good job. - Soo Young, you're amazing.
- It's different. - The thing is...
We thought So Min is an amazing dancer.
- But you guys are professional. - Right.
- It shows. - Chi Yeul knows...
why I dance in the opposite direction.
It's because I've only seen it on TV.
It's not like someone taught her the moves.
She just copied what she saw on TV.
That's why I dance in the opposite direction.
- But you're a genius. - Why do you say that?
- I mean it. - She's good, right?
She can copy what she sees.
- Your dance... - Aren't we doing Fin.K.L?
(After S.E.S, we should do Fin.K.L.)
- Do you want to do it? - Let's do it.
Which song do you want?
- "Eternal Love". - "Eternal Love".
- Let's see "Eternal Love". - Hye Bin.
- I don't know the dance. - Can you do it?
- Seon Hwa and I will try too. - Let's do it.
- Do it! - Then...
- You're the dancer among us. - We have four now.
- We have four now. - I'll be Oak Joo Hyun.
It's an honor. They're all former idol group members.
- Hye Bin... - I'm the oldest here,
so I'll be Lee Hyo Lee.
By the way, I'm Joo Hyun,
so when I sing, "Promise me", you should do this.
(Please do this.)
(She wants to stand out.)
What?
(She wants to be in the center this time too.)
Soo Young...
- We'll be standing in line, right? - Yes.
- She wants to be in the center. - Promise me
She wants to be in the center.
She's so enthusiastic.
Who will be Lee Jin﻿?
When you come out, your upper body should...
(Her upper body should lean forward.)
That's hard.
Like this.
(Her upper body should be straight.)
What about Sung Yu Ri?
Sung Yu Ri just needs to be pretty.
- I like it. - So Min likes it.
(It's the hardest thing.)
It's the hardest.
Let's see Fin.K.L. It's been so long.
- I can't wait. - It's a dance cover.
- It's a dance cover. - Right.
(The 2018 version of "Eternal Love" starts now.)
We should put our heads down.
It's been so long.
(Sunday, Sunday Loves Music)
("Eternal Love" by Fin.K.L)
(How will the 2018 fairies reinterpret this performance?)
(It's Hyo Lee's part.)
Let's go.
(But Soo Young sings it.)
(Center)
- She's in the center again. - She's good.
- She's in the center. - She's in the center.
- She's in the center. - It's perfect.
- She really looks like Joo Hyun. - Right.
She's amazing.
Oh, Joo Hyun's part starts now.
(Always)
Here we go.
(Your part is mine. My part is mine too.)
(Perfect)
Look at her face.
- This song makes my heart flutter. - Right.
- Here it comes. - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's go!
(Promise me)
(Harmony)
(The new generation fairies' show begins.)
Why do I feel moved?
(I feel moved too.)
(He falls.)
What is Jae Seok doing?
- Jae Seok... - "Saturday, Saturday is a Singer".
(Their synchronized dance pierces your heart.)
So Min!
(Choi Soo Young as Oak Joo Hyun, Black)
(24-hour Spinner as Lee Hyo Lee, Red, leader)
(Jeon So Min as Sung Yu Ri, pretty)
(Han Seon Hwa as Lee Jin, Blue)
Hye Bin!
(2018 is ours.)
- It gives me goosebumps. - I love it.
I love it.
(Everyone is overwhelmed.)
They're amazing.
(Suddenly)
(Soo Young stands in the center again.)
(Satisfied)
She looks exactly like Oak Joo Hyun.
She looks like Jin.
(They're in a competition, but they have fun together.)
(You're the only one)
That was amazing.
Fin.K.L, come back!
- We love you! - Fin.K.L forever!
- Fin.K.L! - Come back!
- Fin.K.L! - Fin.K.L!
Fin.K.L!
It's been so long.
(I danced in the same direction as the others this time.)
I mean...
Why do I feel moved?
- It moved me. - Right.
I feel moved too.
It was amazing. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
By the way, I got a little carried away...
and fell.
But no one seemed to notice it.
I couldn't go to you.
(Did no one pay attention?)
(Jae Seok gets carried away and falls from his chair.)
(Kwang Soo glances at him.)
(But he ignores it.)
(Jae Seok has to pretend like nothing happened.)
I saw you lying down on the floor.
I saw you, but I couldn't go to you.
(Why didn't you help me?)
- You saw me? - I didn't want to miss anything.
We were immersed in our memories.
- I was on the floor. - We couldn't pay attention to you.
While we're at it, can we see one more?
- What? - Seon Hwa's "Madonna".
"Madonna".
(Seon Hwa was a member of Secret.)
That sounds awesome!
("Madonna" is a hit song by Secret from the summer of 2010.)
(Seon Hwa, 21, was the youngest member.)
- "Madonna". - It's been so long.
- Can you do it? - So Min can do it.
- She can? - She can do it well.
- Can you do it? - Let's do it.
Ji Hyo. Seon Hwa, can you show Ji Hyo?
How do you do it?
- Hands like this. - How?
(Seon Hwa teaches the others.)
(It's easy.)
Ji Hyo will learn it fast.
- She's become so good. - You can do this!
Turn...
(And you shake hips.)
Good.
- That's good. - You can do it.
Good. So Min, you're doing great.
She's so cute.
(So Min's dance is always cute and funny.)
- So Min, you're doing great. - My goodness.
Let's start.
(The practice is over.)
(Just do as I showed you.)
Let's go!
- Here we go! - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(It's a perfect start.)
Let's go!
That's it!
(Ji Hyo is not a bad dancer anymore.)
(So Min is an amazing dancer as always.)
Way to go!
- Turn. - Amazing!
(My partner is so...)
(Shaking)
(So Min shakes her hips twice as fast as Seon Hwa.)
- She's so cute. - There you go!
(So Min is so good.)
She's so fast.
(So Min finishes up by shaking some more.)
(So Min did a great job.)
She was so fast.
- She's a lot faster. - She's so fast.
- So Min. - She's so fast.
You were even faster than Seon Hwa.
Can't we see that part again?
- Hye Bin wants to see it again. - Just that part.
- Let's see it again. - Try it again.
(Here she goes again.)
I'm confused.
Let's go.
2, 3.
(Powerful moves)
(She has the real moves.)
I think she's doing the twist.
- What's wrong with her body? - Isn't she good?
Her bottom protrudes too much.
(Here come the shakes.)
Your shoulders look weird.
She's so fast.
(My partner is so charming.)
You did so well.
She was terrific.
She's so cute.
She was.
That was hilarious.
Now, let's see Turbo's "Black Cat".
(The finale should be a Turbo's song.)
(He may look timid, but he's known for his shocking performances.)
("Black Cat" by Turbo)
(He is a living fossil who debuted 23 years ago under the name Turbo.)
(Today, we would like to see his performance once again.)
Turbo, Turbo.
- Turbo, Turbo. - Turbo, Turbo.
- Turbo, Turbo. - Come on.
- I can't do it! - Let's go!
("Black Cat" starts playing.)
(His backup dancers are all ready.)
- Here he comes. - Here he comes.
Darn it!
Gosh!
(The tiger has awoken.)
- Let's go! - Let's do it!
(Anticipating)
(It's been so long since he's danced to it.)
(Here comes the cat.)
(For a moment, everyone forgot...)
(that he was once a part of a legendary group called Turbo.)
(The kittens are also busy dancing.)
(An uninvited dancer appears.)
Do the popping dance. Great.
(Go away, Jae Seok. The real popping man is here.)
(He mimics Jung Nam perfectly.)
(Even Jong Kook approves.)
Chi Yeul is so good!
(This is the whining bit.)
- He's like Michael Jackson. - He is.
Let's go.
(It's Jong Kook's part again.)
(He acts unbelievably cute.)
(The kittens are all having fun.)
(Now comes the highlight.)
- To your right. - Let's go.
(Let's do this together.)
Let's go!
(We are all...)
(the black cat, Nero.)
(All of them dance as one.)
(It's exactly like back in 1995.)
(Back then, everyone was a black cat.)
(Acting cute)
(Reminiscing)
(We're all united under the name Turbo.)
(Jong Kook feels embarrassed.)
That was fun.
(They're still excited.)
- That's a great song. - It's been a while.
It feels like we're time traveling.
Excuse me. This isn't a club.
- You can't throw away bottles. - I'm sorry.
(There are piles of empty bottles.)
- I mean... - We'll pick them up.
- What are you doing? - I was having too much fun.
- I'm sorry. - You shouldn't do this.
- This isn't a club. - Sorry, I wasn't aware.
It's quite heartwarming today.
- It really is. - It is.
It's Christmas.
The winner should be...
If we're judging by the teams, it's Jong Kook and Soo Young.
- Me too. - Me too.
That's right.
- She did well. - Jong Kook and Soo Young win.
(Jong Kook and Soo Young win.)
To Kwang Soo's team...
and Jong Kook's team,
I'll give you each a hint.
(Each of them are given a hint.)
You're free to share the hints,
- but it's probably better not to. - Oh, really?
- Are we given the same hints? - Yes.
What does this secret have to do with Seok Jin?
- Do you really not know? - I don't.
- I have no idea. - He's suspicious.
(Kwang Soo receives a hint about himself.)
Do you get it?
Honestly, I have no idea...
- what this means. - Wait.
Is this what I think it is?
Share the hint.
(What is the hint?)
- We got the same hint, right? - Yes.
(Jee Seok Jin is a Furious Santa.)
Tell us.
(I think we're in danger, Seok Jin.)
Now, we'll be heading to the restaurants.
Let's go.
(Korean cuisine, Chinese cuisine)
What is the hint?
The thing is,
- we're lacking hints. - I know.
- So I'm lost about Seok Jin. - How am I related?
Does he really not know, or is he just pretending?
- I have no idea. - I think he's telling the truth.
- I'm serious. - Really?
- Aren't you blushing? - I'm not.
I have no idea.
It's the truth.
For another hint,
- we'll begin our second mission. - Good.
The second mission is called...
Random 5-minute Talk.
- 5-minute talk? - What is that?
You know this game.
The question will be related to your partner.
If you can give three answers...
- in five seconds, you pass. - Oh, no.
- It just needs to make sense. - Yes.
The answers aren't from our hearts.
- It doesn't matter. - It's just a game.
- Don't take it to heart. - Okay.
The first question is for Hye Bin.
- Is it about me? - Correct.
- I'll start. - Here we go.
What are some things you wish he wouldn't do?
(Things she wishes Seok Jin wouldn't do)
Picking his nose, looking at me pervertedly,
and being...
When did I look at you like a pervert?
Aren't you being too sincere?
- Hey. - No, I'm not.
I didn't mean any of them.
- I'm serious. - He was a pervert?
Back then...
Hey.
I only looked at you twice today.
(We're practically strangers.)
(When you were dancing as the 24-hour Spinner,)
(that was when I was looking at you.)
I've never looked at her like that.
I don't usually observe people.
She was being so detailed.
- Goodness. - They'll have a wrong impression.
Hye Bin...
- Seok Jin. - It's the second question.
- It's the second question. - Is it about her?
I know everything about her.
What were you thinking of when you saw her dancing?
(His thoughts when she was dancing)
Gosh, she's so sexy.
(She's so sexy.)
It's very sensual.
(She was sexy and sensual.)
What was the "gosh" for? You could've omitted that part out.
He thoroughly meant it which makes it...
- even more disgusting. - Goodness.
That was too much.
I had no idea he was like this.
It's been a while since I've heard such a disgusting remark.
Is it really that hard to answer this?
Striking, sexy, amazing.
Mind your own business.
Stay out of this.
(This game has only made him upset.)
- Mind your own business. - Moving on.
It's Chi Yeul's turn.
When do you fall in love with So Min?
(When do you fall in love with So Min?)
When I first saw her, when she changed her hat.
and when she smiled at me.
(Their first encounter, when switching hats, when she smiles)
What was that?
- It's only a game. - I'm so happy.
(Wake up. It's only a game.)
How did he notice that I switched hats?
Goodness.
She was wearing a red one before.
It's So Min's turn.
- You passed. - I did.
- We can get a hint. - All right.
Here's the question.
What are Chi Yeul's charms?
(Chi Yeul's charms)
Nose, eyes, and when he sings.
(Nose, eyes, and when he sings)
(Incorrect)
Why?
- Why? - Why?
Nose, eyes, and when I sing.
I didn't feel the sincerity.
- I couldn't feel it. - Honestly,
- I could see that. - Right?
(Haha is also a judge.)
So Min, you do admit to it, right?
It wasn't sincere.
It's such a disappointment.
(She plays along half-heartedly.)
(She's caught.)
See? I knew it.
- It's not true. - I caught her.
- I did. - No, no.
Right? You admitted to it.
This is great. Okay.
Kwang Soo's turn.
- You need to do well. - It'll be about Ha Na.
What was your first impression of her?
She's sexy, cute, and dainty.
(Is it the truth? He replies very easily.)
What are some things you wish she'd change in 2019?
Her boyfriend. No...
(He mentions about her boyfriend.)
I'm sorry.
- No, no. - Her boyfriend?
That was a mistake.
Why would she change her boyfriend?
Okay, okay.
All right, then. Next is Ji Hyo.
Be honest. We have nothing going on.
- You're right. - You can swear too.
What are some advantages of being a team with Se Chan?
I can eat, poop, and play well.
That's great.
- That was straightforward. - It was.
Some aspects where Se Chan is better off than Haha.
He is more handsome, cuter, and more dainty.
Okay! Come on!
What are some parts of him that you'd like to have?
Eyes, nose, and lips.
- She did well. - She did.
That was good.
Ji Hyo, that was nice and clean.
I'm far better off than Haha.
You're cute and dainty.
(He's cuter and more dainty.)
That's great. All right.
That was clean.
(Since you said you wanted to be like him...)
- Okay. - This is a good thing.
If they get a hint, then we'll all get two hints.
(If Se Chan and Ji Hyo share their hint, it'll be for the best.)
Goodness. This one's a pretty big one.
- What is it? - Tell us.
(What is the hint?)
(Two of the guests are assistants.)
Our hint is very straightforward.
(He tries to lure them.)
Let's switch.
I'll do it.
If you want, I'll do it.
- I'll show you ours. - What if...
- their hint isn't that great? - Last time...
(The three couples decide to share hints.)
What?
"Two of the guests are assistants."
(The guests are startled by this new hint.)
What's shocking is that the hint said "two of the guests".
The fact that it said that means...
that two of the members may be spies.
(Could there be two spies?)
(Is there another spy other than Seok Jin?)
"Two of the guests"...
could mean some of the members may be on their team.
This is just my guess.
(Kwang Soo is agitated.)
Some of the members may be on their team.
- This is just my guess. - I feel the same way.
Wouldn't there be too many spies then?
That's a huge hint.
(Stuttering)
Are you flustered?
(You must be since you're one of the assistants.)
I think my face is getting red.
If you deceive us again, I'll be so shocked.
- I think... - She wouldn't.
- Not again. - Come on.
But that hint is so weird.
Jong Kook, there's something you need to know.
We're cornering Soo Young as one of the assistants,
but we need to also think about Ha Na who's been quiet all along.
(Ha Na is suspicious.)
She hasn't said a word.
I'm not the talkative type to begin with.
- All of a sudden? - What do you mean?
- You were chatty with Sung Hoon. - You were.
I'm quite timid.
After hearing that hint, you've stopped talking.
I think some of the members are suspicious too.
- I think so. - Right?
- I'm positive. - Among the people here,
these two are worth our suspicions.
Oh, come on, now.
(Is one of them an assistant?)
I smell something delicious.
What is it?
It's Korean cuisine.
For this round, you'll be rewarded a hint and a meal.
The game is Three Syllable Game.
(Three Syllable Game)
(All right.)
Let's do it.
The director will say the first one, and you will finish it.
You succeed once you make a three-syllable word.
The category will be random.
Who will go first?
- I'd like Ji Hyo to go first. - Me too.
(Anyone but me.)
Go, Ji Hyo.
You did well during the last game.
- Right. - Okay.
I'll go.
- I'll start. - There's no category, right?
Correct.
- As long as it makes sense? - Right.
- Okay. - All right.
We'll each say a syllable.
(The game begins.)
- Jung. - Nan.
(What?)
- Gook? - Incorrect.
(Ji Hyo didn't give Se Chan much chance.)
Jung Nan?
Who is he?
- Who is Jung Nan? - Who is he?
- What were you talking about? - What was that?
- Was it pickled pollack tripe? - That's right.
- Pickled pollack tripe? - Jung...
Jung Nan Jung.
- What is that? - It's a person.
- Who is that? - Oh, I know.
She was a historical figure.
Hold on. Were you talking about a historical figure?
Did you expect me to actually get it right?
I'm sorry.
Do you know Jung Nan Jung well?
- Honestly? No. - Come on, Ji Hyo.
- I don't know that well. - She's more laidback now.
She changed.
We're talking about "Ladies of the Palace".
(She is from an older generation.)
The good, old days.
- I'll start now. - Okay.
Jung.
(It's the same syllable once again.)
Nan.
(He repeats the same syllable.)
(Jung Nan Jung appears once again.)
Goodness.
No one here knows who Jung Nan Jung is.
No one knows.
Jung Nan Jung.
- Who is she? - Who could she be?
- Jung Nan Jung. - I'd like to google her.
- I don't know her. - We can't get past her.
Ha Na will go.
- It's her turn? - I'll start.
Let's concentrate.
- It's easier than you think. - Okay.
Tell yourself that you can do it.
- I can do it. - Okay.
Do it in one go.
All right, then.
"Sah".
(What was that?)
Wait.
- Hey. - Come on.
So Hyun.
Hold on.
- What was that? - Come on.
Hey.
Hey, I'll talk to her.
Was that an apostrophe S?
(Calm down.)
(Was there an apostrophe?)
What was that?
Was that an S or an A?
- Which one was it? - I think it was an A.
- It was an A. - An A?
If you're going to be this cheap, I'll just give up and not eat.
(I'll give up.)
(Laughing)
She's not being fair.
- I'll start. - Go.
- We can do it. - All right.
- Stan. - Dard.
(Standard)
Language.
(Standard language)
They did it.
(What a surprise.)
You've succeeded.
(They finally succeed.)
I'll give the hint to Kwang Soo and Ha Na.
Justice will prevail.
(They receive a hint.)
Can we just eat?
Please.
As always, you won't be eating for free.
If you win, you'll be rewarded a hint and a meal.
Let's get a hint.
- Please, let's do that. - All right.
- Let's do this. - All right.
It's called Goldfish Game.
- What? - What is that?
Write what the opposing female member says and does the most...
on her headband.
If she says or does those things, she fails.
If she mentions the word or does the action,
we will draw on her partner's face.
Come on.
The team with the fewest punishments...
will receive a hint and a meal.
Okay.
- So I'll have to write about her? - This'll be fun.
- Right. - Like this?
- You can't read them aloud. - Of course.
- It's Seon Hwa for us. - All right.
What can we write?
The male member's face will get drawn on?
Let's see.
(Whispering)
(What did they write?)
That was good.
Are you done? Ladies, please close your eyes.
We'll put the headband on you.
(Chi Yeul and So Min)
("No" and touching Chi Yeul)
(Jae Seok and Seon Hwa)
("No" and touching her hair)
(Haha is the female member.)
("What?" and shaking his legs)
(Seok Jin and Hye Bin)
(Saying the male members' names and showing her gums when smiling)
What is it?
- What are they? - It's...
There's a mirror. Be careful.
(Sung Hoon looks at Haha's words.)
(Sighing)
(We made the right choice.)
Are mine difficult?
(Don't make me nervous.)
Are mine too easy?
Gosh, we're doomed.
We're doomed?
(Shaking)
- We're doomed? - You can't tell him.
You can't.
What is it?
(Everyone needs to talk.)
We'll start our 10-minute talk now.
How was this year?
Hye Bin?
(He asks Hye Bin.)
(Me?)
In the beginning, I wasn't that busy.
Now that it's the yearend...
and now that I've aged...
You're being too cautious.
(You're thinking a lot before speaking.)
(Smiling)
- You're being too cautious. - Well...
I felt like I should work hard.
- Please draw on Seok Jin. - Did I do something?
- Please draw on him. - Really?
- On Seok Jin. - Did I do something?
I like it.
(A fellow member draws on him.)
(Drawing)
(Lip botox)
- It's pretty. - It suits you.
It looks natural.
All right.
Anyway, 2018 was a nice year.
I look forward to next year.
Watching So Min,
I feel like she made quite an impact this year.
Is that true?
- Is that true? - It's not entirely true.
You made a lot of money, right?
(Well...)
(Please, So Min.)
(She stops herself.)
Why isn't she talking?
Please talk.
Perhaps, so.
(That was a successful defense.)
Seon Hwa, are you currently seeing anyone?
There are times when I am and also times when I'm not.
It comes and goes.
Do you have a boyfriend?
(Seok Jin attacks.)
(Standing upright, she just smiles.)
I think she's standing upright against something imaginary.
She didn't have to turn awkwardly like this.
(She's being very cautious.)
Do you have a younger brother?
A younger brother...
is existent.
(A younger brother...)
(is existent.)
- Are you a robot? - Are you, Seon Hwa?
(So Min's attack fails. Seon Hwa successfully defends.)
- "Younger brother". - Are you a robot?
By the way, Hye Bin.
I think you said something that you'll regret...
to Seok Jin.
You practically called him a pervert.
It must've hurt him.
You should send him a video message.
(Send him a video message.)
It'll be meaningful.
- I know he's next to you. - A video message?
I think you should draw your lips on an everyday basis.
How are my lips?
(Thanks to Jae Seok's sudden attack,)
(she shows her gums again.)
You have a strong look.
Please draw on Seok Jin's face.
Gosh, they're too good.
(Come on!)
(What did I do?)
They're all so good.
Hye Bin, please.
What? It was because of something I did?
I'm getting penalized because of you.
What did I do?
You're focusing on his lips.
The colors are pretty.
Is it getting bigger?
He contoured your lips.
Anyway, send him a video message.
He needs closure.
To Seok Jin.
(She said his name.)
I don't think we'll get another hint.
You've become disheartened.
He's sad.
(Laughing)
How do I look?
Seok Jin.
- We're filming right now. - Do I look sad?
You should be happy.
I am. I really am.
(He looks sad.)
I have a question.
How do you feel about Chi Yeul?
When we were playing that game earlier...
- Were you nervous? - You know, So Min is...
very honest.
Please draw on Jae Seok's face.
- On my face? - Correct.
Seon Hwa did something.
(While Hye Bin was talking to So Min,)
(Seon Hwa touched her hair.)
("No" and touching Chi Yeul)
(Jae Seok is being penalized.)
(Stamping and clapping)
(This melody and beat sounds familiar.)
("We Will Rock You" by Queen means...)
(Freddie Mercury is here.)
That was nice.
(All he needed was a simple mustache...)
(to look like him.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E432 Running Man
"Furious Santas’ Secret Mission"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(His charisma captivates the audience.)
(Jae Seok does a perfect impression of him.)
(Freddie Mercury)
Can you do this?
(Singing)
(Jae Seok becomes excited with a mustache.)
(He's not sad.)
Good. We're getting attacked.
I think we should get started.
- Go the opposite way. - Let's do that.
Okay, the opposite way.
Guys will put on the headbands, and ladies will get the punishment.
- All right. - It's this direction.
I'm doing Jae Seok's.
Are we doing Chi Yeul's?
Yes, Chi Yeul writes Seok Jin's.
(This is the aftereffect of impersonating Freddie Mercury.)
I think he really likes it.
I want to put this on him.
Me too.
We're the likely winners of this game. We're so good.
No, maybe not.
Maybe they'll feel bad.
This is driving me nuts.
Guys, close your eyes and please put it on them.
(The ladies put on the headbands for the guys.)
(Seok Jin can't impersonate Freddie Mercury and cannot touch his nose.)
(Seok Jin can't impersonate Freddie Mercury and cannot clap.)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok's forbidden words are the same.)
That's good.
(Chi Yeul's forbidden word is "I", and he cannot cross his legs.)
(Sung Hoon can't speak English and he cannot look at Haha.)
Can you go around...
You have to be careful.
- You can't be the same person. - Is that how I have to think?
- You have to become someone else. - Okay, got it.
I'm in trouble.
(He's also in trouble.)
- I'm in trouble. - What is it?
Don't do anything.
Okay, the topic is New Year's resolutions.
New Year's resolutions?
Start.
I think we concluded 2018 well.
2019 is about to begin.
Sure.
(He fixes his gaze on Haha.)
(Fail)
(They failed already.)
He was talking, and they failed.
(He gets the punishment as soon as they start.)
This will be tough.
It's not like I can stay silent. This is driving me nuts.
What is it? Why? I wasn't doing anything at all.
(Sung Hoon will be the center of this round.)
- Those are sunglasses. - It suits him.
Sunglasses.
- I'll continue. - Okay.
Great work in 2018.
(Great work in 2018!)
(Clapping)
(Clap, clap)
(Fail)
Jae Seok.
(Did I do something wrong?)
You guys will be matching.
- They're a couple. - You should both do this.
Do the Freddie Mercury thing once you're done.
All right.
Haha did something wrong again.
What?
It's you. What are you talking about?
- Did I do something wrong? Why? - It's you.
Why are you laughing?
Do it to Hye Bin. Do it to her.
(He claps like a seal.)
(He gets punished again.)
Who is it?
- What? - Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok did something wrong. - I got this for you.
It's a habit.
(Hye Bin is done with the face painting.)
She's so...
- You were being nice. - She's pretty.
- You were being too nice. - She's pretty.
You two look great.
(It's the Queen couple.)
Right.
(Celebrating)
(Fail)
Jae Seok.
(Seon Hwa gets the punishment again.)
- What's wrong? - Why?
(He tries to prevent Jae Seok from figuring out the forbidden word.)
(Am I doing good, Haha?)
- I've never seen her laugh so hard. - This is so funny.
More for Haha.
- You must like me. - This is good.
Chi Yeul is unbreakable.
How do we...
This is the first time I didn't get punished for face painting.
- Talk to us. - Okay.
Do you have something to say...
to 2018?
(Goodness)
(Haha gets punished again.)
I can't stay quiet. This is driving me nuts.
(He gets his face painted everywhere.)
This is incredible.
(What?)
I got it.
(Haha's face is already painted everywhere.)
There are no empty spaces on your face.
(It's a mess.)
Haha.
There's something here.
(She initiates an attack.)
(Shaking)
(What's on his face?)
(He stops turning his head.)
He knows one now.
There's no more space for you.
This is so funny.
I'm happy.
(Haha got all the face paintings.)
Everybody.
(I can't go down by myself.)
(What?)
(Seok Jin takes it.)
(Okay, he fell for it.)
(Seok Jin and Hye Bin get punished again.)
I'll count down 10 seconds.
Everybody, let's do a concert.
(This is the final attack.)
(Clapping)
(Jae Seok)
This is so obvious.
(Stomping)
(He controls his excitement.)
There's no time left.
Come on.
(It's irresistible.)
(Seok Jin can't help himself.)
That startled me.
Finally...
(Finally!)
So Min.
- Why? - Why?
(So Min gets the punishment right before the end of Round 2.)
Why?
(While So Min was attacking Seok Jin,)
(Chi Yeul crossed his legs.)
It suits So Min very well.
- Why does it suit you? - It suits you to do this.
Here's the result.
So Min and Chi Yeul are in first place.
- I'm envious. - Yes!
So Min and Chi Yeul get...
a hint, and they'll get food.
You're the best.
The losers don't get anything.
Why aren't you giving us anything?
There's nothing. Only the winners get it.
(What is the hint they received?)
The losers don't get anything.
Why aren't you giving us anything?
There's nothing. Only the winners get it.
(What is the hint they received?)
(Leave your shoes in the racket and valuables in the counter.)
(We're not responsible for lost items.)
- It's simple. - What's this?
What do we do?
Only 2 teams can eat. 1 team won't be able to.
Only one team?
It's simple. We'll give you water.
Open the lid and hit your water bottle.
If your water color changes, you win.
If there's no color, you won't be able to eat.
- Is this the luck of the draw? - Do we stay out of it?
Yes, you don't do it.
- Let's eat. - Go at the same time.
- In 1, 2, - Please.
- Please. - three.
Please!
(Haha's team is in last place.)
- All right! - All right.
Haha and Sung Hoon get...
plain rice, seaweed, and soy sauce.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Can we eat that?
(They're envious.)
We don't have food, so we'll drink this.
(Let's drink this instead of eating food.)
(Gulping)
This is good. It's vitamin.
We can drink this instead of soup.
(Let's replenish our vitamins and get the next hint.)
(Meanwhile,)
(Furious Santa Jee wasn't able to steal anything.)
(Is Kwang Soo doing okay?)
(The other group is eating in a Korean restaurant.)
(He sneaks out.)
(Kwang Soo sneaks out during lunch.)
(Is nobody coming?)
(Sprinting)
Where do I go?
(He looks around.)
Their cars should be here.
(He runs to the parking lot and finds the members' cars.)
Excuse me.
(Why is he looking for their cars?)
(This morning while receiving the hidden mission)
(They must steal items that belong to the members and put it in a bag.)
(They'll be punished according to the number of items they fail.)
Do you have Ji Hyo's hat?
- Her hat. - I'll give it to you.
The one she had on.
(He tries to steal Ji Hyo's hat at her car.)
Isn't this it? This is hers, right?
(He steals Ji Hyo's hat in no time.)
(Sprinting)
(On his way back to the restaurant)
The shirt Se Chan was wearing.
(He finds Se Chan's car.)
(Excuse me for a moment.)
Here it is!
The shirt.
(He steals Se Chan's shirt as well.)
(I just have to put it in the backpack.)
Wait!
(He finds the messenger bag.)
Right?
Se Chan's shirt.
(Se Chan's shirt is the first item he stole.)
And Ji Hyo's hat.
(I stole 2 items!)
(Furious Santa's Mission List)
This is the final mission to find the secret of today's race.
It's Catch Me If You Can.
(Final Mission: Catch Me If You Can)
- I loved that movie. - "Catch Me If You Can"?
Catch me if you can!
There are hints to solve the secret...
in different places around the building.
- There has to be. - Before the designated people...
complete their hidden mission,
you must rip their name tags...
- and eliminate them all to win. - All of them?
(They must eliminate Furious Santa and his assistants...)
(before they complete the secret mission.)
- We don't know how many there are? - You don't.
You don't know how many people are related to the secret.
However, if both of you are civilians in a couple,
you win if you eliminate the most number of people.
- That couple wins? - Yes.
You just keep eliminating people then.
But...
if you eliminate people other than those who know the secret,
the person who eliminated the other and the one who got eliminated...
are both out.
(If a civilian eliminates another civilian, they're both out.)
- Both of them are out? - Yes.
Okay, I like this.
- There's nothing to lose. - This is good.
Excuse me.
You know what you said about me in the beginning?
Can you tell them again? I don't want them to be mistaken.
Seok Jin, be careful.
Everybody, please move to different spots.
Hey, don't be fooled by that!
- We're going to run after you. - You know what?
If you rip my name tag, you'll get eliminated.
- I'm going to do this. - I'm nothing.
I'm nothing. It's fake.
- Come on. - It's fake.
I heard nothing.
I don't know anymore.
- Why are you doing this? - Please.
Why are you after me?
Did you get So Min's?
I didn't.
She holds on to her bag.
(The Furious Santas talk in disguise.)
(Se Chan is right after them.)
(Oh, my goodness!)
(He notices Se Chan.)
Where do I go?
(He changes the topic.)
This way?
(Did he hear what we said?)
What did you talk about?
(What did you two talk about?)
(Fortunately, he didn't hear it.)
(Kwang Soo leaves.)
See you, Kwang Soo. Be careful.
(The Furious Santas are uneasy from the beginning.)
(Will they be able to take revenge?)
The hints are...
too vague so far.
I'm certain about Seok Jin,
but the other parts are so vague.
I'm kind of confused.
(Who are the assistants?)
Maybe it's Hye Bin.
She's a couple with Seok Jin.
I'm suspicious of Hye Bin.
They're on the same team, so is she trying to protect him?
While we were in the car,
we thought Soo Young was the assistant,
and it looked like she was acting and denying it.
I think...
- it's Soo Young. - Soo Young?
(Chi Yeul is suspicious of Soo Young as well.)
Think about it. She kept on looking for something.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Do you know who was looking for something?
Kwang Soo was all day.
Do you know what he was looking for?
What is it? Do you know?
- I do. - Tell us what it is.
I can't.
- Hey. - Hold on.
(He knows, but he can't tell them?)
- Hey. - Did you receive instructions?
All this time...
I can't.
(Chi Yeul knows something. Is he the assistant?)
Chi Yeul?
I think it's one of the male guests.
Chi Yeul or Sung Hoon.
I suspect Soo Young and Sung Hoon as the assistants.
(Sung Hoon is the other male guest.)
(Who are the 2 assistants from the guests?)
The race will start.
(Will the Furious Santas and the assistants steal first?)
(Or will they get eliminated first?)
(The last race of 2018!)
This is such a difficult mission.
The race starts.
I have to look for hints.
I have to find the hints.
Quick. Let's find it.
(They must find the hints to track down the assistants.)
Where is it?
(Everybody is focused on finding the hints.)
How should I do this?
How do I steal this secretly?
It's impossible.
(It's Freddie Mercury again.)
(He was passing by.)
- What are you looking for? - Hints.
(Jae Seok strikes up a conversation.)
(He's obviously flustered.)
You look surprised.
- I was coming... - No way.
You were surprised when you saw me.
What are you today?
What are you talking about?
What are you?
Don't be suspicious of me.
I swear it's not me.
It's common sense.
If you're not related...
- What's he doing here? - You scared me.
(His lifesaver is here.)
I told you it's not me.
But I have all the hints.
Calm down!
- I can't help it. - You'll die.
I have three hints, and they're all about you.
What do you mean? Stop lying.
I didn't do anything.
You acted so strangely just now.
No, look.
This is a trick, Kwang Soo.
It can't be a trick. You're involved in it.
What's "involve"?
You're a part of it.
Have you heard about the assistants?
Yes, I did.
Two of the guests are the assistants.
Jae Seok.
Both of you will die if you rip my name tag.
Okay, I'll go for it.
(I'll rip your name tag!)
- Don't. - See?
You're being weak.
No, we just started.
I was going for it, and you...
- You have to find it. - This won't work.
Jae Seok, rip it.
(Jae Seok, rip Seok Jin's name tag.)
- You rip it. - Sure.
(He yields.)
- No. You can do it. - You rip it.
You know?
- Hey. - Jae Seok, rip it!
- Jae Seok! - Kwang Soo,
- it's not time yet. - Hey.
- I'm not certain. - Look, guys.
- I'm not certain. - This is a trick.
I'm not certain, so I can't rip it.
Hold on. I have no hints so far.
- I can't rip it yet. - Let's find a hint.
Oh, gosh.
(He was scared to death.)
(It's difficult being Furious Santa.)
I won't be able to live as a criminal.
(He's relieved now.)
What does this mean?
I don't get this hint.
The second hint.
"Valuables in the counter."
"We're not responsible for lost items."
(The Furious Santas might steal their valuables,)
(so it was a hint to warn them about losing items.)
"We're not responsible for lost items."
The counter?
There are many counters here.
The security guards are at a counter.
There's a counter on the first floor too.
Seok Jin was never interested in my clothes before.
We were talking on the bus.
(Seok Jin kept on talking about one thing.)
(Do you have a frog?)
(A frog all of a sudden?)
Hold on.
(She thinks about what Seok Jin said.)
(Jeon So Min)
It's on this.
(There's a frog sticker.)
Then I should leave this at the counter?
(Her valuable is the pouch.)
Where's the counter?
(Leave it at the counter?)
I'm in trouble.
Before coming here,
(He's looking for So Min everywhere.)
I should have done two more at least.
I have to look for So Min.
(How do I take the sticker without her knowing?)
(So Min heads for the counter.)
Hello.
(She leaves her valuable in the counter.)
Can I keep my pouch...
here?
Thank you.
(This is how the Top Excellence Award recipient interpreted it.)
(She left her valuable behind, so it's time to look for hints!)
(I'm a genius.)
I wish I had another hint. This is driving me nuts.
(He was watching everything!)
I have to look for hints.
(So Min doesn't notice, and she leaves the counter.)
This is so frustrating.
(What did So Min do here?)
Oh, goodness.
(He starts moving before Se Chan can find it.)
What's there?
I'm looking for hints.
(While Se Chan is looking elsewhere for hints,)
(he goes behind the counter...)
(and sees the pouch inside a trash can.)
(He has to avoid Se Chan's attention and take it out.)
Who's that?
- It's Lee Elijah. - Is it Lee Elijah?
Are you giving us hints?
What is it?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with her?
What is it? Are you giving us hints?
(He leaves while the attention is on Lee Elijah.)
Elijah.
You surprised me.
For a moment, I thought she was today's guest,
and I didn't recognize her.
- Hello. - Have you been well?
- You're filming a drama. - Your hairstyle changed a lot.
- Yes. I watch your drama. - Really?
- Elijah. - Hello.
Good luck filming.
Okay. Thank you.
There are too many people.
(What do I do?)
See you.
(She leaves after a short time.)
- Good luck. - Okay.
Elijah,
- can I ask you for a favor? - What is it?
I have a favor to ask of you. Come here.
(Is he asking her for a favor all of a sudden?)
I have a favor to ask of you.
(He hides behind a pillar.)
- Do you see the security office? - Yes.
In the trash can...
Okay. I'm getting nervous.
In the trash can, there's a pouch like this.
It's So Min's.
There's a frog sticker on it.
- Can you get it for me? - Are you sure?
- I'll try my best. - Please.
(In order to steal it without getting noticed,)
(he asks Elijah.)
(I will accomplish this important mission!)
(She approaches the counter.)
I hope she doesn't get caught.
(He worries a lot.)
(She's looking in the trash can.)
(She doesn't mind the dirty work.)
What are you doing?
- What are you doing there? - Nothing.
(They're both flustered.)
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
Why are you looking in the trash can?
This can't be on TV.
It's personal business.
Is it your personal business to look in the trash can?
(He doesn't understand.)
- What is it? - Please leave me alone.
(He finds So Min's pouch in the trash can.)
Why is this here?
What is it? Where did you get this from?
- Give it to me. - It was here.
- Whose is it? - So Min's.
- Give it to me. - Let me see.
(They fight over the pouch.)
- Let's see. - Hold on.
- Kwang Soo. - Let go.
- Let go. - Hold on.
(She casually walks away.)
Did you get it? Hurry up and give it to me.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. You completed an important task.
Thank you so much. Good luck.
- Thank you, Elijah. - You are set now, right?
(We thank Elijah, a family member of Running Man.)
I did it.
(He succeeds if he puts it in the newbie producer's bag.)
(He walks over without hesitation and puts it inside the bag.)
(He gets So Min's frog sticker thanks to Elijah.)
(Furious Santa's Mission List)
(Jeon So Min's frog item has been cleared.)
(The sun has set.)
(An assistant candidate, Soo Young, heads somewhere.)
Soo Young!
(You startled me.)
(Is Soo Young an assistant?)
Tell me you aren't an assistant. You aren't, are you?
I swear I am not an assistant. I have been wrongly accused.
Don't be that way.
You fooled me once.
There are two cameramen following you.
People are suspecting me because of you.
Did you find a hint?
What?
Don't open your eyes that way!
Stop!
I am not an assistant!
(Distrustful)
- What? - Soo Young drives me crazy.
- I didn't do anything. - All right.
- Search this area. - Okay.
- No ripping off the name tag. - Of course not.
- I promise. - I will have my guards down.
Okay. Me, too.
(As soon as he parts with Soo Young,)
(he finds a hint.)
Gosh, what is this?
(Assistant A is a woman with S in her name.)
(That means it's either Seon Hwa or Soo Young.)
(My goodness.)
Gosh, what is this?
Share it with me.
I don't want to do that. I found this.
- Share it with me. - Hold on, Soo Young.
You could be an assistant.
I am not an assistant. We should help each other.
I get that, but...
Hold on, Soo Young.
- I will be honest with you. - Okay.
- I am scared of you. - Why?
(He is too honest.)
I really want to go to the restroom right now.
After I become certain that you aren't an assistant,
I will share this hint with you. I promise.
I can't do it now.
- All right. - Okay. Don't rip off my name tag.
(He needs to be careful until he becomes certain.)
(People is suspicious of Hye Bin since she is Seok Jin's partner.)
(Walking down the hallway,)
(she finds a hint.)
(Assistant A is the same age as one of the guests.)
(Sung Hoon, Hye Bin, Kwang Soo, Soo Young, Seon Hwa)
The same age as one of the guests.
(Assistant A is a woman with S in her name.)
Then there are two candidates.
Two candidates.
Seon Hwa.
(She was strongly suspicious of Seon Hwa before the race.)
It's her first time on Running Man.
I get it now.
It's a bingo.
(She becomes sure after obtaining a hint.)
Where should I go?
(She spots Jong Kook and Soo Young, a strong assistant candidate.)
Should I go first?
- It's you, right? - It's me.
Rip off my name tag.
(It would be better to get my name tag ripped off.)
I should go first.
Did you find a hint?
Yes, I did.
- Really? - Yes.
What is the hint? Share it with us.
I only know what I know.
Tell us what you know.
(Does she want to remove suspicion by sharing the hint?)
Seok Jin is definitely innocent.
(Is that the hint?)
- What? - Really?
Was that the hint?
Seon Hwa told me this.
(Seon Hwa told me this.)
The hint we found said that Seok Jin is a Furious Santa.
(What are you talking about?)
- That's right. - Really?
Did it say that Seok Jin is a Furious Santa?
Seon Hwa said she got the information from you.
- Really? - I didn't say a word.
She said she heard you say that.
I didn't say a word.
(What exactly happened?)
You found a hint, right?
- I heard something. - What did you hear?
- What? - What did you hear?
(The hint Seon Hwa overheard is...)
Seok Jin is a civilian.
A civilian? Are you certain?
I am certain.
Who gave you this information?
Jong Kook said it as he was passing by.
Jong Kook?
(That means...)
Seon Hwa is an assistant.
I didn't say a word.
I haven't talked to her.
- She might be an assistant. - She might be an assistant.
That's right.
I need to find Seon Hwa,
who is most likely to be an assistant.
(Hye Bin's target is Seon Hwa.)
(She finds a woman with a secret,)
(Seon Hwa.)
I will remove Seok Jin's name tag.
(Seon Hwa said Seok Jin isn't a Furious Santa.)
I don't care. I don't mind...
getting eliminated.
(She has no reason to lie unless she is an assistant.)
Why did you show up again?
Excuse me?
What kind of a question is that?
Why did you show up again?
(When Seon Hwa is looking elsewhere...)
(Ripping)
What happened?
(She removes the name tag in an instant.)
(Is Seon Hwa an assistant?)
Are you not an assistant?
- What was that? - That startled me.
That happened so suddenly.
- Are you not an assistant? - Why did you rip off her name tag?
What was that?
I was just standing here!
That happened so suddenly.
Hye Bin, why did you do that?
(That means the assistant is...)
(Soo Young.)
The assistants who will help you are here.
Are there assistants?
Assistants, come in.
Who are they?
(The first assistant)
Soo Young!
It has been a while.
With Furious Santas, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo,
you will steal the members' items.
- We will work together, right? - Yes.
This is bad. We picked the items that are impossible to steal.
- I can get Jong Kook's bag. - How?
I was a couple with Jong Kook before, right?
He believes what I say.
That's right.
(A plan to steal Jong Kook's bag)
Jong Kook, may I please put this in your bag?
- Sure. - It's light.
(Become a couple with Jong Kook and put a pouch in his bag.)
Thank you.
I put my pouch in Jong Kook's bag.
(If you can't do it by force, use a thorough plan.)
(When people's suspicion falls on her,)
(she eyes the location of the newbie producer.)
I really want to go to the restroom.
(Why is she telling me that?)
What? You should go.
- Would you give me my pouch? - Sure.
(She put it in his bag earlier.)
Okay.
Just...
(He takes it out.)
It's okay.
(If you take it out, I won't be able to steal your bag.)
It's embarrassing.
- Do you want me to go with you? - Yes.
(He accompanies her to the restroom.)
(It's no wonder he is the winner of the Best Couple Award.)
(Soo Young calculates the distance to the newbie producer.)
(He is close enough.)
(Jong Kook walks ahead of her.)
(Reaching)
I can get Jong Kook's bag.
(Will she steal his bag when so many people are watching?)
This one?
I will take this.
(She unclasps the bag.)
- I will take this. - What?
Why are you taking that?
I will take this.
(While Jong Kook is flustered,)
(she goes to the newbie producer.)
To get Jong Kook's bag,
you should take the bag and run towards the newbie producer.
(It's the only way to steal Jong Kook's bag.)
(It's a suicide mission.)
- That's right. - That's the only way.
(Soo Young's behavior is unexpected.)
(What is going on?)
Why are you taking that? Soo Young.
Why are you taking that?
Soo Young, what are you doing in front of so many people?
Soo Young.
Soo Young, what are you doing?
What?
Come on.
(Is she revealing herself as an assistant?)
- What? - I really need to go...
- to the restroom. - What are you doing?
Why are you...
(Soo Young carries out a suicide mission...)
(and steals Jong Kook's bag successfully.)
Why did you take my bag?
Get her.
If you get her, I will remove her name tag.
- Get her. - You are an assistant.
- It's you. - You are wrong.
- I am not an assistant. - Be honest.
What about me?
- I am not an assistant. - I am 100 percent sure.
- I am not an assistant. - It's you.
I am serious. Jong Kook!
- You are wrong. - I will remove her name tag.
(Chi Yeul takes her out.)
(An assistant, Soo Young is out.)
Is there something? Let's see it.
I am not an assistant. You are making a grave mistake.
Is she not an assistant?
She is an assistant!
(Jong Kook got betrayed by Soo Young.)
My goodness.
I thought she was suspicious.
I can't believe you. You took advantage of me.
(Soo Young took advantage of him twice.)
(Furious Santa's Mission List)
(Kim Jong Kook's messenger bag has been cleared.)
We need to get a cell phone.
Gosh, we picked the most difficult items.
(Jae Seok follows him quietly.)
(He needs definite proof...)
(to assure his suspicion.)
(He trails Seok Jin instead of looking for hints.)
(Seok Jin looks around.)
Who are left?
- Who are left? - Turn off the light.
Haha, Jong Kook,
(He has no idea that Jae Seok is listening.)
and Jae Seok, right?
There are many people...
who don't believe I am a Furious Santa.
(He says things that reveal his identity.)
They won't be able to remove my name tag.
(Jae Seok hears everything.)
(His suspicion turns into conviction.)
I will rip it off right away.
(When Seok Jin shows his back,)
(Jae Seok runs towards him.)
What are you doing?
What did you talk about?
(His target is Seok Jin, a Furious Santa.)
(There is no reason to hesitate.)
Furious Santa.
Come here. Come here, Furious Santa.
You don't even know what Furious Santa is.
Come here, Furious Santa.
(He has no chance against Jae Seok.)
Come here.
(A Furious Santa, Seok Jin is out.)
- Is it over? - I was right.
- I am out. - You were a Furious Santa.
(Following Soo Young, Seok Jin is also out.)
He has a keen sense of smell and good hearing.
Did you tail me?
- I just followed you. - I had no idea he was behind me.
(This is how good Jae Seok's instincts are.)
Are you out?
- Gosh, he'll eliminate you too. - What were you?
- What? - What were you?
Stop trying to take a look.
Jae Seok didn't die because I'm the Furious Santa.
He's the Furious Santa.
(How can you get eliminated this quickly?)
Go, Seok Jin.
(He's heading to prison leaving behind his disappointment.)
He left the cameraman.
- Seok Jin! Get in the elevator. - Hold on.
- You can't just leave by yourself. - You should go with the cameraman.
Seok Jin, you should take the cameraman with you.
Go.
Jee Seok Jin is out. Jee Seok Jin is out.
My goodness.
(What should I do?)
- You're not the Santa, right? - I'm not.
Here they come.
(At that time, the three of them meet at a dead end.)
- Jae Seok. - I got rid of him.
- I eliminated the Furious Santa. - What?
Did you eliminate him?
- You eliminated him? - Yes.
I eliminated the Furious Santa.
Come on!
What's wrong with him?
- What is it? - I eliminated Seok Jin.
I eliminated Seok Jin!
What?
(He's at a loss for words.)
(There are no witnesses anyway.)
(He starts acting intensely.)
- What? - I just got goosebumps.
What's wrong with you?
- What's going on with you two? - I just got goosebumps.
(His acting confuses Haha.)
I eliminated the Furious Santa, and then you came.
What are you talking about?
- What's going on here? - Hold on.
- Both of them are suspects. - Hey, that's not it. Gosh.
- 1 of them has to be eliminated. - I'm 1 of the suspects?
I'm one of the suspects?
You are.
(You're the prime suspect.)
- Hey, you. You come here. - I can't believe you.
(You come here, Kwang Soo.)
(He grabs Kwang Soo's collar.)
Hey, you. Don't move.
You.
- Haha, get him. - Let go of me.
- Eliminate him. - Hey, listen to me.
Hold on. Let me show you this.
- Gosh, you... - I wasn't going to show you this.
- Gosh, I caught... - I'll just show you this.
(Will it be a crucial hint that will back up his argument?)
"The Furious Santas and assistants are shorter than 190cm."
Let me see.
(Actually, as for this hint,)
(Kwang Soo made it himself a while ago.)
(Is this a skill of his experience? How far will he go to cheat?)
- I'm taller than 190cm. - Is that so?
- Hey, mister. - Hold on a second.
- Hey, hey, hey! - I told you I wasn't.
- No, no. - Have you gone mad?
- What's this? - No, just eliminate him.
- Hey! - Hold on.
- What? - I got rid of Seok Jin.
- I eliminated Seok Jin. - Hey, hey. Let go.
- Get his name tag now! - Let go of me.
- Do it now! - What is this?
(Why are Sung Hoon's hands on Haha' bag?)
- I got him. - Hey!
(He pretends to help Haha get Jae Seok's name tag.)
- Get his name tag now! - Let go of me.
(He goes after Haha's bag.)
- Get it. Get it! - You come here.
(He took...)
(Haha's bag?)
- What just happened? - Get it. Get it!
(As soon as he gets the bag, Sung Hoon starts running.)
- I eliminated him. - Hey, Sung Hoon!
(What is wrong with him?)
(He runs into the darkness after taking Haha's bag.)
(He was the second assistant.)
(The reason for choosing Haha is finally revealed.)
(His target has been Haha from the start.)
(Forget about bromance. It was an act for this moment.)
What? What is this?
(Sung Hoon! Where are you going?)
Rip off his name tag. Rip it off.
- He... - I got his name tag.
(When Haha is in a daze,)
(Kwang Soo holds Haha's hand and eliminates Jae Seok's name tag.)
(It happened in a split second.)
- What was that? - What is this?
- He... - Why did you eliminate me?
He just took my bag.
- What he did threw me off. - Why did you eliminate me?
Why did you remove my name tag?
I didn't. He did that!
I ripped off his name tag while holding your hand.
(Kwang Soo removed Jae Seok's name tag with Haha's hand.)
- Why did you do that? - He did that!
Hey, you!
(Both Haha and Jae Seok are out.)
Go to prison. Get lost!
- Did you make this? - Get lost.
- You made this hint, didn't you? - Unbelievable.
- Hey. You... - You made this hint, didn't you?
I eliminated the Furious Santa.
You did that?
(Sung Hoon and Kwang Soo eliminated 2 members at once.)
(With Sung Hoon's help, they acquired...)
(Haha's cell phone too.)
We need Jae Seok's pants to finish the mission.
(Jae Seok, tight pants)
(The only item that remains is Jae Seok's pair of pants in prison.)
(The race will be over with Jae Seok's pants.)
What? No. I thought...
it'd be rude to take off his pants without anything to cover him with.
I'll get his pants after covering him.
You prepared a lot.
Jong Kook. Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
(Furious civilians gather around with Jong Kook as their head.)
(What should we do?)
I eliminated Seok Jin.
(He shares it voluntarily.)
- What did you say? - I eliminated Seok Jin.
- What? - I got Seok Jin.
(Sung Hoon backs off.)
Sung Hoon. Come here. Come with us.
- I'll go. - No, come with us. Why are you...
Why are you running away? Hold on.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo runs at full speed.)
- Kwang Soo. - I'm not the Santa! I'm really not!
(I see. You were the Santa.)
Gosh, I got caught.
(Sung Hoon didn't get far.)
Ji Hyo, get his name tag. Get it!
- I'm sorry, Sung Hoon. - Get his name tag!
(He's surrounded.)
We got it.
(In the end, Chi Yeul eliminates him.)
I got it!
I got it! Right?
(Sung Hoon, the assistant, is out.)
- He's so strong. - He really is strong.
(Now, only Kwang Soo remains.)
(Team Civilian will win if Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
Where's the prison?
Where is it?
(He manages to ditch Jong Kook after running at full speed.)
Kwang Soo.
(Where did Kwang Soo go?)
(Is no one in there?)
Where is the prison?
(Whispering)
(He finds out where the prison is located.)
(He advances into prison.)
What's going on? What is it?
(He just needs to steal Jae Seok's pants.)
- What's going on with him? - Behind you!
(Grabbing)
(Ripping it off)
(Jong Kook who was hiding under the desk removes his name tag.)
Behind you. Behind you!
(What? What just happened?)
Okay.
- He's the assistant. - Who eliminated him?
- I can't believe I'm doing this. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? Wait. - Hold him, Seok Jin. Hold him.
- This is what Kwang Soo is after. - Why did you...
I should hide under the table.
- He'll hide under there. - Okay.
(He'll probably come here.)
(Clueless of this, Kwang Soo walked toward Jong Kook on his own.)
- My gosh. - Okay.
- There's nothing we can do now. - What are you doing?
- It's Kwang Soo. - He's the Santa.
- Why are you taking off his pants? - What are you doing?
- He's the Furious Santa. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Answer me.
The couple who completed the final mission after uncovering...
the secret is So Min and Chi Yeul.
- What? - It's So Min and Chi Yeul.
(So Min and Chi Yeul eliminated 2 assistants.)
- Really? - You eliminated two assistants.
The present will go to Chi Yeul and So Min.
(Chi Yeul and So Min, the winners, will receive the present.)
Thank you.
(Health supplements for the New Year)
As for Seok Jin and Kwang Soo's penalty,
- we'll discuss it first. - Yes, let's do that.
- We shouldn't make this short. - Come on.
- It'd be a shame. - What are you planning to give us?
- By the way... - I'll be anxious for a week.
- Let's do it after the New Year. - Let us sleep without worries.
This is my point. Why were you furious?
Soo Young and Sung Hoon...
- will face the penalty. - Right.
This is your punishment for using me twice.
- I'll accept the punishment then. - Okay.
Thank you so much for your support throughout 2018.
We will see you in 2019.
- Happy New Year! - Happy New Year!
(Happy New Year!)
(May good fortune explode just like this whipped cream.)
(We thank the guests for the great finale.)
- Good work. - Soo Young, are you okay?
Happy New Year.
(2019 New Year Project on Running Man)
(Would you like to log in?)
(Welcome to the Running Man Canyon.)
(All 8 members enter.)
(Complete all the quests, hidden in the canyon.)
Shoot about five points.
(And the quest-keeper of the canyon is Apink.)
(Complete the quest-keepers' mission and level up.)
(You completed the quest. Your level goes up by 1.)
(However,)
(someone is keeping these level-ups all to her or himself.)
(A quest to level up goes beyond your imagination.)
(Which member will be in 1st place after reaching the highest level?)
(RPG: Episode 1, The Great Beginning)