(Asia Culture Center, Gwangju)
- Hello.
- Ji Hyo.
You are here, Ji Hyo.
Hello, Jong Kook.
Go away.
(Jong Kook is sulking.)
- Hello, Jong Kook.
- No, go away.
- She didn't relate to your story.
- It's not like that.
She had no reason to give me "Poor".
(The story goes back 2 weeks.)
(During the Christmas Special,
So Min rated his story "Poor".)
I couldn't relate to it.
(She couldn't relate to him then.)
It wasn't that bad.
Perhaps my explanation was
a bit lacking.
You are talking
about excellent, fair, and poor.
- If she had a justifiable reason...
- I had forgotten about it.
It's all in the past.
Do you understand her?
- I don't.
- He holds grudges.
It's possible that
she didn't relate to your story.
- That's funny.
- He is scary.
- I had forgotten about it.
- He holds grudges.
- So many days have passed.
- A week has passed.
So Min, take a fist to your face
and get it over with.
(So Min, take a punch
and get it over with.)
(It's better that way
since Jong Kook holds grudges.)
Take a fist to your face,
and get it over with.
Jong Kook catches a cold
and gets his feelings hurt easily.
(There is a soft heart
behind the muscles.)
He gets his feelings hurt
very easily.
I see that...
Kwang Soo only looks handsome
with a nice hairstyle.
(The comment comes out of nowhere.)
(Why is he bringing this up?)
That came out of nowhere.
- Seok Jin.
- I can't believe you.
You are talking nonsense.
Kwang Soo only looks handsome
with a nice hairstyle.
With that hairstyle,
he reminds me of Chil Deuk.
- Chil Deuk is back.
- What are you talking about?
Come on.
He has that hairstyle...
because he enrolled somewhere
in drama.
(His hairstyle has nothing to do
with his fashion sense.)
When I got out of the car,
every staff members said,
"What's wrong with your hair?"
"Are you trying to be funny?"
Everyone had a comment.
- He isn't handsome anymore.
- Your face is enough.
Kwang Soo,
you don't need to do more.
- You look funnier.
- What do you mean?
- You look funnier now.
- What do you mean by that?
- I mean...
- Look at Kwang Soo.
This is a cool hairstyle.
All right.
This is the first episode...
of the new year.
It's especially cold this winter.
- We came to Gwangju,
- Yes.
- the city of lights.
- The city of lights.
Gwangju, the city of lights.
It's the biggest cultural center
in Asia that is located in Gwangju,
Asia Culture Center.
Today, you will have a race here...
to welcome 2018,
the Year of the Golden Dog...
with the penalty
of bathing your body on the line.
This is the Gold Pouch Race,
the Mysterious Stone Pouch.
There are 4 Gold Pouches
and 4 Stone Pouches.
You will choose a pouch.
All members with the Stone Pouches
at the end of the race...
will have the penalty
of bathing your body.
The members who win
in each mission...
will receive advantages
for the race.
Okay.
However, among you are
two members with Hands of Stone...
who can change a Gold Pouch
into a Stone Pouch...
through the hidden mission.
(There are 2 members
with Hands of Stone.)
I told you.
If everyone's Gold Pouch...
turns into Stone Pouch,
Team Hands of Stone wins...
and the rest of the members
receive the penalty.
If there is a member
with a Gold Pouch,
those with Hands of Stone and
Stone Pouches receive the penalty.
However, while there are
two members with Hands of Stone,
they don't know each other.
They don't know each other.
If a member with Hands of Stone
performs...
the hidden mission on the other,
his or her Stone Pouch
will change into the Gold Pouch.
They need to spot each other.
- They need to spot each other.
- That's right.
What happens if the two members
are Jong Kook and So Min?
Will it be okay?
- My goodness.
- If they are Jong Kook and So Min,
will So Min be able to do
the mission?
They know, but they pretend
not to know.
- Even if they know,
- I got goosebumps.
they will feign ignorance.
So Min is hiding next to Kwang Soo.
(She is avoiding Jong Kook.)
- She stuck her head out.
- She is avoiding Jong Kook.
Thank goodness she is a woman.
If she was a guy,
he would've killed her.
When will Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
receive the penalty?
- It got postponed.
- They will receive it today.
- I see.
- We should receive it today.
- Today?
- We should.
Please pick a pouch.
- Okay.
- Pick the one in the front.
Okay. Move out of the way.
- I am choosing.
- Move out of the way.
(The member with a Stone Pouch
at the end,)
I will take the last one.
- I made a choice.
- I am not sure about my choice.
(They will be penalized.)
(The ace member, Ji Hyo, has...)
(a Gold Pouch.)
(So Min has a Gold Pouch.)
All right.
(Jong Kook and Haha)
(Both of them have Gold Pouches.)
I am not lucky.
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan have Stone Pouches.)
(So Min, Haha, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook
have Stone Pouches.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan have Stone Pouches.)
A Stone Pouch changes
into a Gold Pouch...
when the two members
with Hands of Stone change it.
- Yes.
- So Min.
(You are suspicious.)
This mission is for you.
Are Ji Hyo and So Min doing this?
(Are they the ones
with Hands of Stone?)
No, Jae Seok. I don't have them.
- You don't?
- No.
- I think...
- Ji Hyo and So Min...
(Seeing how you're naming us...)
I have a feeling Jae Seok might be
one of the Hands of Stone.
Yes, I do.
(Is he acting? Is he revealing
his identity from the start?)
(This morning,
30 minutes before the shoot)
Are you giving me another mission?
My last mission wasn't long ago.
You are 1 of the 2 members who have
Hands of Stone that can change...
the gold in members' pouches
into stone.
(Jae Seok is 1 of 2 members
with Hands of Stone.)
Jae Seok, your hidden mission is...
stepping on members' feet.
(This hidden mission can change
the gold into stone.)
I need to step on their feet?
(They catch on quickly. It won't be
easy to step on their feet.)
That's too difficult.
(They catch on quickly. It won't be
easy to step on their feet.)
(He has no time to waste.
He starts from the opening.)
No, the pouch changes from
what you have.
The Stone Pouch can change
to a Gold Pouch, right?
(He steps on Se Chan's foot.)
My gosh, these shoes.
- So that's...
- Goodness.
My gosh, these shoes.
(He steps hard on Se Chan's foot.)
What are you doing?
You need to get
your new shoes stepped on.
- They are new. I must step on them.
- Jae Seok.
(He accomplishes his mission,
but Se Chan has a Stone Pouch.)
(Jae Seok can't change
his pouch into a Gold Pouch.)
(Place for the Year
of the Golden Dog's first mission)
(Wait.
This indoor set looks like...)
- Wait.
- This set is quite intriguing.
I know what this is.
Fortune-telling.
For this mission,
your fortune for the new year
will be interpreted.
After having your fortune
for 2018 read,
you will be paired with a member
that's most compatible with you...
and proceed with the mission.
(The members will be matched with
those most compatible to them.)
So Min knows a lot
about fortune-telling.
- I like having mine read.
- She gets into this.
- Fortune-telling of five elements.
- Right, she has them read.
- What is that?
- Fire, gold, tree, water, and soil.
- I see, I see.
- People do get them read.
- Right.
My fortune is of the tree.
Seok Jin, I'm compatible
with someone of the tree.
- I thought you were of the gold.
- Yes, my fortune is of the gold.
- Why are you...
- So let me elaborate.
When gold meets water,
- it depends on the size of water.
- Is that why...
(For some reason...)
If gold meets a big puddle of water,
it will sink, but if water is...
Are you going to read
our fortune today?
- Are you going to read ours?
- Go sit over there. Go.
- What's gold not compatible with?
- It's fire.
I guess I'm fire.
(That means I must be of the fire.)
I must be quite a big fire.
I must be burning up.
Fiery Jong Kook.
Call me Fiery Jong Kook from now on.
(It could be true or not.)
All right. Then let us
introduce you...
a fortune-teller, Park Sung Jun
who will read your fortunes.
- Gosh.
- He's back again.
- I saw him on TV.
- Hello.
I don't like him.
- I saw him on TV.
- I don't like him.
My gosh, you're back again.
- Thank you for coming so far.
- I saw him on TV.
Didn't you collapse last year?
I'm going to...
I'm going to take off my shoes
and sit this year.
- Seok Jin must go first.
- He told you not to do anything.
- Last year...
- My goodness.
- He said not to do anything.
- This year...
- I'm looking forward to 2018.
- Stuck to the ground.
- Seok Jin's fortune must be good.
- I hope my fortune is great.
- It's about time.
- Yes, 2018 will be his year.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Long time no see.
This is...
from an analysis, right?
Yes, I look at yin and yang along
with the elements.
- You're not making this up, right?
- No.
These tell me
about the person's disposition...
and the environment
of his or her fortune.
- Birthdays determine the elements.
- They are all different?
Yes. So for you, Seok Jin,
you are a solid rock.
- A rock? Like a stone?
- Yes.
- Really?
- He's a speculum metal then.
I really hope his fortune is
better than last year's.
- Do you remember last year's?
- Yes.
- It can't be worse than that.
- Right.
You told me not to start anything.
You told him to do nothing.
(Seok Jin's last year's fortune
wounded him deeply.)
(His fortune said that Seok Jin
must not try to do anything.)
(What kind of fortune
will 2018 bring Seok Jin?)
- For the last two years,
- Yes?
you did a great job
of holding yourself back.
You did a great job
- 2 years? He waited for 2 years?
- My goodness.
(Lady Luck will be
on my side now at last!)
- 2 years? He waited for 2 years?
- What did he say? What?
- Goodness.
- Things are looking up for him.
Gosh, this sounds...
- quite hopeful.
- Things will go his way now.
It's finally here.
(Will he be successful now?)
- So now...
- Yes?
(So now...)
you can wait one more year.
(You can wait 1 more year.)
(We knew it!)
(Darn it!)
- How much more must he wait?
- I must wait more?
- He's the funniest.
- Seok Jin, you're almost there!
- You're almost there!
- You can do it.
- Seok Jin.
- It's almost over.
You waited for two years.
Waiting for one more year
isn't that hard.
Exactly.
You're almost there, Seok Jin.
- One more year.
- This will be over soon.
However,
good things will start happening
to you from 2020.
- He has a long way to go.
- That's so far away.
- That's too far in the future.
- He still has a lot left.
- I must wait for 2 years, not 1.
- Right.
- 2020?
- That's so far away.
2020?
Then you will be over 60 by then.
If you wait diligently
for one more year,
things will begin to move
in your favor.
- It'll be time for you to prepare.
- He can finally get moving.
- He can start crawling now.
- Right now,
he can crawl around.
Things are beginning
to look better for him.
By the way,
will I have some luck
in the offspring department?
(By the way, will I have some luck
in the offspring department?)
Why are you asking that, Seok Jin?
- What? Why?
- Why are you asking that, Seok Jin?
Are you guys trying?
- No.
- Last year...
I just find babies
insanely adorable these days.
Well,
- your luck regarding children...
- Okay.
If were to discuss this,
your luck will stay with you
until the first half of next year.
- So we may be able to conceive?
- Yes.
- What about after next year?
- We can't conceive after that?
After next year,
his luck will thin out.
- Is that so?
- He's going to get weaker.
How can he get weaker from this?
- He's going to get weaker? Really?
- Hold on.
I don't think you know me well.
In your fortune, you may get weaker
in the course of time.
(Whatever!)
He's going to lose energy
and get weaker.
- Come back to your spot.
- Seriously.
Seok Jin, come back to your spot.
(This year's fortune left him
scarred again.)
(Seok Jin's fortune for 2018)
(April showers bring May flowers,)
(but it will happen after 2 years.)
- My fortune was the best last year.
- Yes, Kwang Soo's was the best.
- Mine was the best last year.
- Really?
- Mine and Kwang Soo's was the best.
- Right.
- Kwang Soo had a haircut.
- Look forward to yours.
- Kwang Soo, are you sick?
- I'm curious about mine too.
What?
- It could've changed his fortune.
- You look sick.
No, no. Hello.
- He even acts strange.
- I don't think it will be good.
(They keep commenting on his hair.)
- I liked his back, long hair.
- Why did he cut his hair?
Kwang Soo, you should get
some extensions.
I will get mine read later.
(I will get mine read later.)
- I'll do it later.
- No, no.
- What?
- Okay, okay.
- We'll be quiet.
- You'll be fine.
(You'd better not speak a word.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
You only have an entrance,
but no exit.
(You only have an entrance,
but no exit.)
What does he mean?
(You only have an entrance,
but no exit.)
it means that things can go in,
but never come out, right?
What does that mean?
What did you mean by that?
You have a lot of thoughts,
and your mind is clustered,
but since you can't express them.
You feel frustrated and annoyed.
You aren't like an average person.
When these elements coincide
with loneliness,
you may show
some signs of a pervert.
He went out of the line.
My gosh!
Yes, he's a pervert.
(The revelation brings shock
to everyone.)
A pervert? A pervert.
Don't you think he's being too mean?
But he really surprised me.
His interpretation is spot on.
- How could he say this?
- Only we know that he's a pervert.
- What are you saying?
- This was our secret.
I'm sure some people may know,
but...
I'm not a pervert.
(Let's keep it a secret.)
You're not a complete pervert.
Your looks...
aren't of the typical pervert.
(Your looks aren't
of the typical pervert.)
He's not a typical pervert.
Should I be relieved?
His looks are average.
That's why...
I could say that
he's somewhat of a pervert.
- Somewhat of a pervert?
- Yes.
I just meant that you have
a unique way of thinking.
- It's not a bad thing.
- Okay. I see.
First off, your fortune for 2018...
is the brightest.
(2018 is the brightest year
for him.)
- His drama will be a hit then.
- His drama will be successful.
Is he going to be
as successful as Joong Ki?
(Can he be with Joong Ki now?)
- Is it a good year for me?
- Yes.
This year is the brightest
before the sunset.
In other words...
Before the sunset?
Wait.
The sun has been up only
for a short while.
Your last moment.
(It's his last moment
before the sunset.)
- "Last moment"?
- Is he trying to be funny?
- I had a feeling about this.
- No, no.
- He's the funniest.
- "Last moment".
Let me elaborate.
You will burn the last flame
you have left in you,
- Already?
- so it's the brightest for you.
I'm only 33.
(Is that good or bad?)
How could I have my last moment?
Later on, in your early 40s,
you will have great fortune.
The great fortune you had
for past 3 or 4 years...
will continue until early next year.
Then your flame will start
to dim a bit.
(He's shocked.)
I'll have my last moment? Already?
- Things will be better at 41.
- Right.
Things will be better for you at 41.
Hey, Seok Jin has to wait
this year again.
I keep waiting.
Among the members of Running Man,
there's someone who can give you...
affection and warmth.
- Okay. One member?
- Yes.
That member is...
(There's someone who can give me
affection and warmth?)
So Min.
What?
- So Min...
- It's me?
and Kwang Soo share similar traits.
So Min is affectionate
and warmhearted.
- That's how she is.
- Okay.
That's why when you and So Min meet,
- you are quite compatible.
- My gosh.
I'm like his lucky charm.
The Best Couple Award goes to...
Lee Kwang Soo and Jeon So Min.
(Is it because of the fortune?
We make a good couple.)
Hey, you guys should give it a try.
Only So Min can improve
your luck for the next six years.
Be nice to me.
He should read So Min's fortune too.
Okay.
But the problem is that only you
will benefit from the relationship.
It's not going to benefit So Min.
- See?
- It's not going to benefit you.
- Let's have dinner together.
- Forget it.
I mean it.
Is it not going to
benefit me at all?
If you two become a couple,
you'll have to look after
Kwang Soo as if he was your son.
You'll have to continue
giving in to him.
- You have to help him out.
- It seems so.
So Min has to keep helping
Kwang Soo out.
She has to look after him.
Kwang Soo doesn't have
good dating skills.
What do you know?
(My fortune talks
about my dating skills?)
Dating skills are...
- irrelevant. Aren't they?
- Does that come out?
- Psychological...
- Isn't this his personal opinion?
I'm talking about
psychological skills.
- They are weak.
- His psychological skills?
- He has poor skills.
- He's impatient.
You're his dating coach.
I'm his coach.
He has such poor skills.
My skills have become worse
because of you.
Without me, his skills would be
even worse.
Let me tell you a good thing.
This year and next year, you have
the highest chance of...
meeting the love of your life
in the coming 10 years.
(He has a high chance of
meeting the love of his life.)
- You're mine
He'll probably get married.
Why are you looking at So Min?
- While talking about love...
- That's not why I looked at her.
You might meet your future wife.
- My future wife?
- Yes.
He's now old enough to get married.
- It's about time he got married.
- Yes.
Joong Ki got married too.
Kwang Soo likes to copy him.
Exactly.
He has nothing to do with this.
(I won't get married
just to copy Joong Ki.)
This year,
- you might meet someone.
- I see.
- That's a good thing.
- Yes.
- You're lucky this year.
Thank you.
It's a lucky year for you.
That's what's important.
- Okay.
- It's your last year.
(Kwang Soo's fortune for 2018)
(It'll be a brilliant year.)
(Spend your last lucky year
with So Min.)
- Hello.
Your birthday has energy of...
- It's small gold, right?
- gold.
- Small gold.
- That's right.
You can compare it to...
jewels or a sharp metal.
You think too much and get
submerged in your thoughts.
- You worry a lot too.
- That's right.
I'd say you're...
half Jae Seok...
and half Kwang Soo.
(Half Jae Seok and half Kwang Soo)
That's the worst.
Should she sit between the two?
- You have both our strengths.
- Collaboration.
You're like a gift set.
You're not average.
You're creative, but
you can sometimes be a bit weird.
You think a lot and have a lot
going on in your head.
- You're also very conservative.
- I am.
If you hadn't become an actress,
- you would have enjoyed teaching.
- A teacher?
- That's true.
- A teacher would suit you too.
Someone told me I would have
become even more successful.
Teaching gives you...
a sense of superiority
and satisfaction.
That's why I'm not lucky with guys.
I tend to try to lecture guys,
and they don't like it.
You're lecturing him right now.
You're lecturing him.
You're talking more than him.
I'm sorry.
Guys tend to... How is my love life?
Your future husband will be
like a parent.
You want a man...
who can look after you...
- like a parent.
- That's right.
You'd make a nice couple...
- with Se Chan too.
- Really?
(She'd make a nice couple
with Se Chan.)
- I'm the one that got away.
- No matter how much you fight,
you will never break up.
If you get married,
you won't be able to get divorced.
That's bad.
- Because we can't get divorced?
- You can't get divorced.
- That's bad?
- That's bad.
You'll be inseparable.
(They'll be inseparable.)
You'll stick together like taffy.
That sounded weird.
They'll be inseparable.
- I was surprised.
- Like taffy.
- They'll stay together like taffy.
You'll be obsessed with each other.
I like that.
She's a pro at obsessing.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Thank you so much.
(So Min's fortune is not
entirely satisfying.)
(So Min's fortune for 2018)
(She could have become
a teacher too.)
(Don't try to lecture guys.)
- Se Chan.
- Is it my turn?
- Go.
- It's your turn.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
(I'm nervous.)
You're very different
from the other members.
You have the energy of fire.
- Fire?
- It's a huge fire.
- A huge fire?
- Yes.
I'd like to talk about
Haha and Jong Kook...
in relation to your fortune.
When you're with Jong Kook,
there's stress you can't avoid.
(When Se Chan is with Jong Kook,)
(there's stress he can't avoid.)
That's accurate.
- How can...
- Are you saying that on purpose?
How can you see through that?
- How...
Do you watch Running Man often?
- I understand what that means.
- Seriously.
Really?
You can never change it.
It's your destiny.
I'd say that.
Will it be like that all my life?
The unsatisfactory man.
- Stress is your destiny.
(Stress is your destiny.)
You have to accept it.
- Accept it.
(Is it really destiny?)
- I have to accept it?
- Accept it.
- We'll always be together.
- Of course.
Haha is the one who can
relieve your stress.
I knew it.
- Nevis.
- Nevis Swing.
Swing.
Haha is moist land.
- He has a lot of moisture.
- He's very emotional.
- I'm moist.
- He's emotional.
When a huge fire meets moist land,
it calms down.
When Jong Kook gives him stress,
he relieves it by talking to Haha.
I'm the one who connects the two.
- Yes.
- We're a good match.
- We are.
- Of course.
It seems like you'll be lucky
in the coming years.
Look ahead 4 to 5 years.
You'll become...
luckier and luckier.
That's great.
- That's great.
- I love it.
(Se Chan's fortune for 2018)
(Man of Fire)
(Accept your stress in 2018.)
- Hello.
- Ji Hyo.
- Why am I nervous?
Of the five elements,
you have the energy of wood.
Wood? I think you said that
last year too.
- Ji Hyo is wood?
- She's wood.
In the past two years,
you've been lucky with guys.
From now on,
you'll be lucky with money.
I'll be lucky with money?
You'll be even pickier this year.
No man can satisfy you.
(No man will satisfy her this year.)
This year too?
- This year too?
- That's a problem.
She should meet a man soon.
I see.
You become even pickier with guys.
When you look for a man,
you look for someone
you can look up to.
That's right.
There is a problem.
(The problem is...)
It's that there are very few men
you can look up to.
(There are very few men
she can look up to.)
Gosh.
You said that last year too.
Although you'll be luckier
with money than with guys...
this year,
you'll still have some luck
until March or April.
You might meet someone.
There's not much time left.
- March or April?
- Yes.
(If it's March or April...)
How is it between me and Jong Kook?
You said some good things
about him and me last year.
Suddenly...
Why...
Isn't this a confession of her love?
(Last year's fortune telling)
(Ji Hyo was dry wood last year too.)
(You're always thirsty
for something.)
(Jong Kook is a huge water.)
(Are Ji Hyo and Jong Kook
a perfect match?)
As a couple...
A tree born in the summer
needs water.
As Jong Kook is a huge water,
he can help you grow.
(I'm thirsty, Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook would feel burdened.)
He feels burdened.
I have to be careful
until March or April.
(Beware of Ji Hyo
in the first quarter of the year.)
Until the end of April...
I'd give your match...
85 to 95 points out of 100.
(That's great.)
- That's a lot.
- That's great.
(Shocked)
(Thank you for your nice words.)
(Ji Hyo's fortune for 2018)
(March will be a romantic month.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
would make a great couple.)
(It's Ji Hyo's huge water,
Jong Kook's turn.)
- Hello.
Jong Kook...
(What does the new year
have in store for Jong Kook?)
You are always dissatisfied
and make risky moves.
(Jong Kook will be dissatisfied
and make risky moves.)
- Me?
- Yes.
You'll be dissatisfied
and make risky moves.
You should try not to make
risky moves.
I'll try.
This year,
you'll go through many changes.
Your mindset changes,
and you want to change.
You might move to another place...
or change workplaces.
Jong Kook has been
talking about that...
for the last few years.
This year,
you're lucky with girls too.
(He's lucky with girls.)
- Finally.
- He's getting married.
- Please.
- That's the best thing.
Girls?
(Will I finally meet someone?)
You'll meet many women.
(He'll meet many women.)
- Many?
- Is it many?
- He waited for a long time.
You'll meet countless women.
- Countless women?
- Goodness.
You should meet women.
- Countless women?
It's okay for you to do that.
You should meet
so that you can find someone.
Based on your fortune in changes,
you could move to a new house
as you meet a new woman.
- What's this?
- It's marriage.
It sounds like marriage.
It's likely a marriage.
Really?
You have a lot of fortune
in moving and changes.
If I'm in a situation to move,
is it better to move?
- You should move this year.
- Really?
It's finally time, Jong Kook.
As your desire for
money and women get strong,
you may find stability and changes
as you meet someone.
If you move accordingly,
things will turn out well.
- Okay, sir.
- He'll have many changes.
- Goodness.
- That sounds good.
(Jong Kook's fortune for 2018)
(It is a year of changes and
luck with women.)
(Please get married this year.)
(How about Haha's fortune in 2018?)
In 2016 and 2017, compared to
the amount of work you did,
the results weren't as good.
That's right. It's true.
- He worked very hard.
- Right.
Why are you smiling?
However, in 2018...
(His career wasn't the best
during the past two years.)
(How about in 2018?)
The result of your work
will be worse.
Gosh, wait a minute.
Compared to 2016 and 2017,
will it be worse in 2018?
Will it be worse? I'm sorry, Haha.
(When will he be rewarded?)
- My goodness.
- Pardon me?
You have the worst fortune.
What I mean is...
(He's knocked down.)
(It must be painful for Haha.)
Help him get up. Haha.
He lost strength.
- Come on, Haha.
- Get up.
- Haha.
- It's only a start.
It's only the beginning, Haha.
- It's only the beginning.
- No way.
His bad fortune this year
doesn't make me laugh.
Do you mean my career
in TV broadcasting?
I mean in various fields...
- including TV broadcasting.
- Like what?
The moment before the sun rises
is the darkest.
Your fortune is like pitch darkness.
(His fortune is pitch dark.)
However, you start to see
the end of the dark, long tunnel.
Once you pass it,
you'll be able to breathe.
I think that...
you'll be very fortunate
in 3 to 4 years.
If you endure this year,
things will be great afterwards.
The only source of strength
to help you endure bad fortune...
- is your children.
- Right.
- Dream and Soul.
- He always thinks about family.
- They're Dream and Soul.
- That's right.
I'll take a look at
when you'll be fortunate.
- He feels bad for Haha.
- Right.
He wants to tell him
something positive.
(Let's see.)
In 2022...
(2022 is 4 years later.)
That's years later.
When you're 44, 45, or 46 years old,
you'll be very fortunate.
That's good.
That's a good thing.
It's better to be fortunate
when you're older.
- He's right.
- In 2022?
- Keep working hard.
- It's better this way.
He's right.
(Haha's fortune for 2018)
(Life starts when you're older.)
(Look forward to 2022.)
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Your fortune in money is
quite stable...
and well stocked.
Your fortune says that you adapt
well to various circumstances...
and make smart maneuvers
in earning money.
You also like to
dig deep into things,
so you hold money in both hands.
You try to protect what you have,
and you prefer
certainty and stability.
However, you'll want to
start something new this year.
- Really?
- How did he know?
We should open up
an organic bakery, Jae Seok.
- How about an organic bakery?
- Seok Jin...
- keeps insisting on that.
- It's time.
He suggested opening up
Grasshopper Bakery.
He's been saying that for years.
This year is the time to
open up an organic bakery.
As I said last year, Seok Jin
and bread don't go well together.
(If bakery doesn't work...)
He won't be lucky with bakeries.
How about
an organic food restaurant?
- Does it exist?
- Organic won't work for you.
If Seok Jin starts
a business like a bakery,
he should sell low-cost products
that aren't healthy but cheap.
- Like junk food?
- That's right.
You should keep to distribution.
- Distribution?
- Manufacturing won't work.
Don't manufacture.
Come on, don't say that.
You'll want to start new things
this year.
I suggest that you follow
such desires...
- this year.
- Okay.
It's similar to mine.
Right, it's similar to Jong Kook's.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
- You always have good fortune.
(Jae Seok's fortune for 2018)
(Everything is okay as long as
he avoids Seok Jin.)
(Don't open an organic bakery.)
(Couple selection result)
Here's the current status
of pouches.
Even though the Hands of Stone...
- completed their mission...
- Really?
(Gold gets changed to Stone.)
(Although Hands of Stone
were successful...)
the gold hasn't changed.
- They must have chosen incorrectly.
- Right.
(The number of stones
hasn't changed.)
- They did their mission?
- When did they do it?
Nothing happened.
When did they do it?
(He definitely stepped on
Se Chan's foot.)
(That means Se Chan was stone
from the beginning.)
Seok Jin came early
to the waiting room.
During the prior round,
Seok Jin and Jong Kook
massaged other members.
I'm not suspecting you.
Seok Jin had his elbow on me.
He moved it while
pretending to lean on me.
- Really?
- He's here.
Seok Jin made me feel
electricity on my hand.
- A massage?
- Electricity.
- Was it a massage?
- I was just playing.
I wouldn't be that obvious.
You haven't massaged us once
in eight years.
He's never done it
in the last eight years.
Let him do it.
It's certain that
Seok Jin received a mission,
but we don't know
what the mission is.
Where have you been?
Are you massaging me again?
It's because it's fun
to see your reaction.
You must be one of them.
- What's that?
- What is it?
What do we have here?
- My goodness.
(Is it a stepping-stone set
with a water puddle?)
It's a game of falling in the water.
There are jumping boards.
(There are four jumping boards.)
We have to fall in the water.
(Shall I change some gold
into stones?)
It's per couple.
- Is it an individual game?
- We won't win today, Haha.
(Hands of Stone Jae Seok succeeds.)
We won't win today, Haha.
- Kwang Soo.
- Jong Kook has advantage today.
- That's great.
- What did you say?
- What's your color?
- Mine is orange.
Why are you taking it?
I just took one.
Stop being obvious
in clearing your mission.
No, I wouldn't be this obvious.
I've worked with you over 20 years,
but you never massaged my shoulder.
- I know.
- Seriously.
- He's never touched me before.
- I do it because you enjoy it.
Why do you keep massaging us...
while looking in this direction?
- It's because...
- It's very strange.
Why do you look in this direction
while clearing the mission?
I'm doing it for fun.
(Just admit it.)
Let's start a couple's game called
Skipping Piggyback Ride.
Piggyback?
The four couples start together.
With one partner
on the other's back,
you skip the stepping stones.
The last couple to arrive at
the destination wins.
- The last couple?
- The last?
The one getting a piggyback ride
chooses a finger from 1 to 5.
If you pick a number that
coincides the most,
the couple skips
the stepping stones accordingly.
The couple to arrive at
the water puddle loses.
If you arrive at the jumping board,
half the number of members
must go in the water.
(Half the members
at the jumping board must go in.)
(1 of the 2 must go in the water.)
That means one of us
goes in the water.
It'll be me, won't it?
- Really? Okay.
- Gosh.
Please go to your places.
- It's the winning team last year.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
We can do it.
- Good fortune cross.
- We miss U Ie.
(We miss U Ie.)
- Good fortune, let's be happy.
(How about this?)
- What?
- What should we do?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Kook.
- That's enough.
Min, siblings.
- You should play along.
- He hates it.
Where did that come from?
- "Kook Min siblings"?
- What was that?
- It makes no sense.
- She took them from their names.
Kook Min siblings.
(She tries again.)
What is she doing?
(That couple will be funny today.)
One partner gets on
the other's back.
Choose who will get
a piggyback ride.
- Three.
- Ji Hyo is light.
(Se Chan gives a ride.)
(Seok Jin is older yet strong.)
Hold tight.
(They're weak.)
It's great to see
So Min and Jong Kook together.
Don't we look close?
(Goodness)
(Ji Hyo is way over here.)
All right. One.
(The last couple to arrive
at the puddle wins.)
Two.
(They must choose a number
that doesn't coincide.)
(They both choose 3.)
(Jong Kook and So Min, Seok Jin and
Haha must skip 3 stepping stones.)
How many stepping stones?
2 teams must skip 3 stepping stones.
- For goodness' sake.
- Okay! Okay! Okay!
- Okay! Okay!
- That's a lot.
Kwang Soo.
(Their reactions are as varied
as their fortunes.)
- This is crazy.
- It hurts a lot.
(The moment they move,
the suffering begins.)
(Round 2 arrives
when they are in pain.)
Let's go.
One.
Two.
Okay, okay.
We are safe.
Gosh, you are heavy.
Don't say that.
- My goodness.
- Don't say that.
(Is the acupressure mat painful,
or is Ji Hyo heavy?)
My goodness.
Stop pressing down on me.
I am not doing anything.
Let's go.
This is the beginning.
For goodness' sake.
- This is crazy.
- You must endure it.
You must endure it.
I know it's painful,
but you must endure it.
Hurry up.
It's okay.
- Step on it.
- For goodness' sake.
- A little bit more.
- Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
The last one.
Okay.
Hurry up.
(It hurts a lot.)
In 1, 2,
(These are how many steps
the teams have left.)
Did you pick?
It's over for them.
(Either Jong Kook or So Min
must dive.)
Okay. We are still in the game.
Let's go.
So Min and I should never be
on the same team.
- 4.
- 5.
- 5. Okay.
Let me down.
Step aside.
(Step aside, So Min.)
Is it okay if Se Chan let me down?
(Step aside so that I can dive.)
What are they doing this time?
Jong Kook cold act is a pretense.
He looks after So Min.
- Come on out.
- What are they doing?
Why are you trying to go
into the water?
- Let me.
- Come on out. I will go in.
His cold act is a pretense.
(He treats her warmly.)
- His cold act is a pretense.
- Come on out.
I will go into the water.
(He jumps into the cold water.)
- Jong Kook.
- Don't go into the water.
What is going on?
Don't say that.
I went in because I could.
I don't think
I will be able to sleep easily.
I am reminded of something.
I saw a couple fight viciously...
before they suddenly began to kiss.
Isn't that what they are doing?
What are you doing?
It feels like a party.
(It feels like a party.)
That came out of nowhere.
(He brings up a party
out of nowhere.)
That came out of nowhere.
It's a party.
- It's beautiful.
- I know.
Seok Jin's team is out...
if they pick a coinciding number.
Let's go.
Pick carefully.
One.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan
have 5 steps left.)
Two.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo
have 5 steps left.)
All right.
(Seok Jin and Haha pick 5.)
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan pick 4.)
For goodness' sake.
(Seok Jin and Haha
and Jae Seok and Kwang Soo pick 5.)
- What is it?
- We must advance five steps.
Did we win?
Yes, you did.
Okay. Let's play
rock-paper-scissors.
- What?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Let's have one team enter the water.
(Half of them must enter the water.)
- Yes.
- We need two people.
2 out of 4 people
must enter the water.
- Scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
- I dodged it.
- You should have played scissors.
You should have played scissors.
(Kwang Soo decides for them.)
Come here.
(Come here.)
(Running away)
Catch him.
Two people entered the water.
Jong Kook, would you call him?
Enter the water.
I don't have to do that.
- Hurry up.
- What?
- Hey!
Hold on.
Where is Jae Seok?
For goodness' sake.
Hey.
(He hides to apprehend
the rule breaker.)
Catch him.
Come here.
Two people entered the water!
- Hurry up.
- Two people entered the water!
Hold on.
(Splashing)
(It's cold.)
It's Gollum. It's Gollum.
(His hair reminds people of Gollum.)
- Look at his hair.
- He looks like Gollum.
(Kwang Soo isn't here.)
Kwang Soo, do something
about your hair.
Kwang Soo, fix your hair.
(I am angry.)
(I can put Jae Seok and Seok Jin
back into the water.)
(Slipping)
(He falls down.)
(Slapstick comedy makes the best
the New Year's greeting.)
Is he a fool?
Kwang Soo.
(He falls down again.)
Look at Kwang Soo's hair.
Please come to the middle.
(The winners can exchange
their pouches.)
Before the exchange, I will reveal
what everyone has.
There are five Gold Pouches...
and three Stone Pouches.
(Stepping on Kwang Soo's foot
results in one more Gold Pouch.)
Seok Jin did his mission.
(It may not be Seok Jin,)
(but it must be the work
of another Hands of Stone.)
Please open your pouches...
- and check.
- Let's check.
Seok Jin didn't touch me.
The contents must have changed.
- Jong Kook has Gold Pouch.
- Let's see.
(He had Stone Pouch.)
(He now has Gold Pouch.)
(The two Hands of Stone did
a mission on me.)
(So Min showed a lot of interest.
Is she one of the Hands of Stone?)
So Min.
This mission is for you.
(Seok Jin massaged everyone.)
(Is he one of the Hands of Stone?)
If a Hands of Stone does a mission,
does stone change into gold?
For stone to change into gold,
two Hands of Stone
must do a mission.
- They must do it on one person.
- I see.
(Who is the other Hands of Stone...)
(who did a mission on Kwang Soo?)
Either Ji Hyo or Se Chan
has a chance...
to change the pouch.
Play if you don't want to lose,
rock-paper-scissors
- Darn it.
- Okay. Okay.
- It's a good opportunity.
- He wants to change his pouch.
Is there a point in knowing
if someone has stone or gold?
That's the point of the race.
Seok Jin.
Stop talking nonsense.
That's the point of the race.
Is there a way I can change
my stone to gold?
You should try to change it.
You should touch your own shoulder.
(Why don't you do the mission
on yourself, Hands of Stone?)
That's a good idea.
Do it twice.
Can Hands of Stone
do a mission on himself?
- Is it possible?
- He can't do it on himself.
The two Hands of Stone
have different missions.
(The other one's mission isn't
stepping on feet.)
- I will exchange my pouch.
- With whom?
I will exchange it
with So Min's pouch.
If you want to do what's right
for the team,
don't be so sure
that I am the Hands of Stone.
- Seriously.
- Seok Jin.
(Se Chan had a Stone Pouch.)
(Is his exchange a success?)
(Gold)
(As a result, So Min gets stone.)
We will now move
to the next location.
(They ride a bus
to go and have a meal.)
I need your care.
Do we have water?
Please give me water.
(Drinking)
(Do you want some?)
I need some more.
Seok Jin gave me water...
- for the first time ever.
- Is it a mission?
Is it a mission?
- He gave me water earlier.
- Really?
He never gave me water before.
I took the water bottle from him
and drank.
Now that I think about it...
- He never does that.
- When I drink water, he goes,
- "Let me have some."
- That's right.
He gave me water earlier
for the first time ever.
- Seok Jin is the Hands of Stone.
- Seok Jin.
- It's not me.
- Come clean already.
This happened the last time, too.
You didn't believe me
no matter what I said.
This is driving me crazy.
(S Korean course restaurant,
Gwangju)
- It's a Korean course restaurant.
- Gwangju is well-known for it.
This is incredible.
- 1, 2, 3...
- This is a Korean course.
What is this?
It smells delicious.
(Delicious dishes fill the table.)
The samhap looks delicious.
(These are the tasty dishes
in the style of Jeolla Province.)
- My goodness.
- Look at this meal.
- This is incredible.
- This is no joke.
Do you want some water?
Give me some water.
This is driving me crazy.
Does he need to do it
in front of the camera?
What are you doing?
(She gets her foot stepped on.)
I don't know what she is doing.
For goodness' sake.
She got her foot stepped on.
(So Min makes Jae Seok
do a mission on her.)
For goodness' sake.
(Is So Min the second
Hands of Stone?)
We will have a mission
with a meal on the line.
Before that,
we will tell you what's inside
everyone's pouches.
It will give us some clues.
Inside the pouches are...
(I wonder if the other
Hands of Stone did a mission.)
Inside the pouches are...
4 golds and 4 stones.
It's the same as before.
(That means...)
We're back to square one.
It's the same.
(Is it Seok Jin
with his massage and water?)
(Is it So Min
who got her foot stepped on?)
(Is one of them the other
Hands of Stone?)
I will explain the mission.
We prepared a course with 30 dishes.
30 dishes?
The result of the mission
will decide...
the number of the dishes.
The name of the mission is...
Food Stone Flicking.
(A mission to win side dishes,
Food Stone Flicking)
- "Food Stone Flicking"?
- "Stone Flicking"?
(Is it similar to Stone Flicking?)
It's a 4-on-4 team match.
We have put 30 stickers...
of the side dishes on the stones
on the ends of the table.
(They will receive 30 stones
with names of side dishes.)
Each team will have
a strategy meeting...
and place the stones
however they want.
Each teammate will take
a turn to flick the stones.
- You must remove 20 stones to win.
- Okay.
You can only have a meal with the
side dishes of the remaining stones.
The team with more side dishes
will win.
How will we split the teams?
(Let's break into teams.)
Jong Kook!
Hey, don't come near me.
Don't get close to me.
(I know you have a big heart.
Be on my team.)
Should we split the teams like this?
(Se Chan, Haha, Seok Jin,
and Ji Hyo make a team.)
- Like this?
- Let's go with this team.
- I like this.
- Hold on.
- We will continue with these teams.
- Okay!
(Team Pink versus Team Blue)
Goodness, "pickled radish".
(Placement of stones is the key.)
- Goodness.
- We have to eat this.
Let's place really good dishes
in the center.
- Yes, yes.
- Should we put them in the back?
- First off, let's get them out.
- Put them where they'll be safe.
- Why don't we put this in front?
- Let's put bad dishes in front.
- Dishes like these...
- "Soy sauce". "Chojang".
Wasabi too.
Does anyone want fermented skate?
- Put that in front. Do you want it?
- I can't eat skate.
- We are not desperate for it.
- Hold on a second.
- We should place this here.
- That one.
Anchovy jeon.
- They don't want the skate.
- Really?
- I can't eat skate.
- Only some people can eat it.
(They are done
placing their stones.)
- Team Blue can go first.
- Try it.
I must get rid of one first.
Take the wasabi.
(What is Jae Seok's plan?)
(Pickled radish)
(He will break Team Pink's defense
with a dish they don't want.)
(Falling)
- There you go.
- Okay.
(He removes the stone for wasabi.)
Flip it.
(He successfully penetrates
into Team Pink's camp.)
It was wasabi.
- Should I go next?
- Yes.
(Seok Jin goes next.)
- This one...
- Radish water kimchi.
- If both fall, it'd be great.
- They might fall together.
Okay.
(Seok Jin is aiming at radish
water kimchi. What is his plan?)
(Radish water kimchi)
(He must control his power to remove
the stone for radish water kimchi.)
Okay!
(He eliminates both his team's stone
and Team Blue's stone.)
Are you all right?
- I did it gently. I had no choice.
- Okay.
(Both stones are out.)
- I could have made that work.
- Who's next?
- Should I go next?
- Let me go next.
Hey, go for chojang and salad.
No, go for the anchovy jeon.
We can't play offense then.
(We'll break your defense.)
Target the one in front.
(She's nervous
as Jong Kook is up next.)
Hold on a second.
Okay. Let's go with that.
Wait, should we use that instead?
(Can Jong Kook break their defense?)
Okay!
(He gets rid of the salad
and penetrates into their camp.)
- Great job, Jong Kook. Great!
- Gosh, that.
- That was a hard one.
- That was so cool.
Great, great. That was nice.
- That was a good one.
- Yes, it was great.
Things are going great for me today.
Since our stone penetrated,
we can use that to end the game.
- That will be difficult.
- Gosh, how cool.
I don't think we can eliminate that.
Should I use this to
get into their side?
- Yes, yes.
- Hold on, if we flick this stone...
But they won't be able to hit this.
It's harder than it looks.
- Or should we...
- If that goes into their side...
Hey, you should flick the stone
for cabbage wraps.
Haha, we should play
this game like this.
Since our stone is in their side,
we can use it to finish this.
(Team Pink decides to penetrate
into Team Blue's side.)
This game is over.
(Try to penetrate if you can.)
(Will Se Chan's attack
be successful?)
(Flicking)
- Gosh.
- That wasn't bad.
- Okay. Good job.
They can't touch that.
- Of course, we can get rid of it.
- How? With which one?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Use the chili pepper.
- Wait.
- What if I use that one?
- Chili pepper.
- Should I use that to remove that?
- If you use that,
it'd be terrible.
We have to discard cabbage wrap.
- Remove lettuce and cabbage wrap.
- Yes, use chili pepper for that.
Use chili pepper to get rid of them.
Hit the stone hard.
I don't think I can pull it off.
No, no. You can do it.
Just hit it hard.
Make sure the stone goes inside.
Make sure it goes
inside just slightly.
(My gosh, Jong Kook.
Let me flick this stone.)
- Don't let it fall off the table.
- Right.
- There!
- Yes!
(The cabbage wrap is out.)
You did it. This counts, right?
- Well done.
- Gosh, Jong Kook.
We can't let their stones stay
in our side.
- Okay, okay.
- This counts, right?
I'm going next.
(Kwang Soo gets rid
of Team Pink's stone in their side.)
- You did well.
- They won't get to eat a lot.
Okay. Good luck.
(Haha of Team Pink tries next.)
- My gosh! Okay! 2 stones.
- 2 stones.
(He removes two stones,
doenjang and kimchi, at once.)
- 2 stones at once!
- 2 stones.
(He discards salted anchovy
to remove doenjang and kimchi.)
- Move aside. Step aside.
- Move aside.
I'll use chojang.
- If only there was a bigger space.
- Don't push it.
- Don't push the stone.
- Flicking it that way is better.
- But it won't go far though.
- Let me...
- Haha did the same thing though.
- Yes, Haha did it.
- You can't do that.
- You can't push the stone.
- Flick only your stone.
- Don't use that one.
(He's nagging profusely.)
- You touched it.
- Don't touch the other stones.
- Go for those.
- Exactly. I'll get rid of two.
(He goes for the frontal attack
despite Jong Kook's disapproval.)
(With this one move,
I'll bring ruins to you.)
Okay!
(What? Did he lose his stone too?)
- Okay.
- My goodness.
(He wasted such a good chance.)
(It was so hard to put the stone
in their side.)
- That's all right.
- We don't need to eat that dish.
- That's okay.
- We only lost chojang.
- Chojang? Okay.
- Who's up next?
It's Haha. Wait, no.
It's you, Seok Jin.
What should we do? Should we use
this to finish the game?
Jong Kook is powerful.
Aim at the center to be safe.
Should I finish the game?
Or should I use this side dish?
- Let's try to finish it.
- Yes, go for it.
Hey, aim at the center to be safe.
- Aim at chojang and chili pepper.
- We won't have anything to eat.
(He plans to end it while trying
to remove several side dishes.)
(Jong Kook can drive the stone...)
(into the opponent's side and
is good at nagging their teammates.)
(What kind of move will he show?)
- No!
- Yes!
(What just happened?
It just slides off the table.)
(He said he was going to finish it,
but he makes a colossal mistake.)
(How fun! I enjoyed
watching your attempt to end it.)
(What just happened?
They are flustered.)
That was a strong flick.
- Is he on our team?
- Hey, this is...
Okay, okay. Let me do this. Wait.
But the upside is that
we have important side dishes.
(The important side dishes
are safe.)
Hold on.
- Who's up?
- Me.
Seok Jin.
Hey, just mess up
the cluster of side dishes.
(Okay. I got it.)
I bet he feels a lot of pressure.
(No, we can't go down like this.)
(Seok Jin is determined to
mess up the cluster...)
(and manages to destroy the zone
for the important side dishes.)
(Amazing!
What's gotten into you, Seok Jin?)
- Yes!
- Yes, Seok Jin!
(No way. This can't be
really happening.)
(They clustered their important side
dishes to avoid getting eliminated.)
(A flick from Seok Jin kicks
them off the table.)
I'm sorry,
but didn't he just push the stone?
Give me one more chance.
Let me redeem myself.
(I can't let this fly.)
- Jong Kook, just finish this game.
- Okay, go for it.
(Shake off your mistake,
and show them what you've got!)
Just don't get rid
of the potato dish.
(The fate of Team Blue depends
on Jong Kook's fingertip.)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(What? It just flew by.)
(Redeem himself? He ends up
losing their stone again.)
Why did the stone go that way?
- That was so funny.
- It was hilarious!
This is crazy!
Why did it go that way?
Is it because of the gloves?
- I can't believe it, Jong Kook.
- He's on our team!
Is it the gloves?
- Why does it keep going that way?
- The funny thing is that...
we all know that Jong Kook
messed up,
- but we can't say anything.
- No, no.
(They keep their silence.)
Now that I look at them
as a third party,
I understand how I might've looked.
I feel so proud of myself.
Gosh, I should...
I must take off my gloves.
Gosh, this...
If you lose four more stones,
the game will be over.
- It's over if you lose four more.
- Hey, what we should do is...
- We should hit this part.
- I see. Okay.
(Haha of Team Pink goes next.)
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(He will focus on attacking the zone
of important side dishes.)
Gosh, this is so frustrating.
I hit it really hard though.
(Haha, end this game!)
Okay!
(Sliding off)
- 4 stones dropped.
- 4 stones!
(Exactly 4 stones are eliminated.)
(Team Pink takes the win!)
What's up with the direction?
How could it go that way?
(He misses again.)
- I picked the wrong team.
- We had help from him.
We were so close. Seriously.
- What a bummer.
- Our team...
- My favorite dishes remain.
- Only the winning team can eat.
- Yes!
- The losing team will eat...
(They'll have rice and dried laver.)
(Side dishes they protected)
We managed to protect tteok galbi.
We did it.
Gosh, we have so many side dishes.
I understand the saying,
"the table legs might break."
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
(Feeling proud)
(Looking pitiful)
The dried laver is good.
It must be from the south.
(I'm glad the dried laver is tasty.
It must be from the south.)
It's delicious.
Gosh, give me tteok galbi.
(Team Pink is feasting
on tteok galbi.)
The tteok galbi is really juicy.
(This tteok galbi is the juiciest!)
(This tteok galbi is the best
in the world!)
It's really juicy.
(Amazed)
It tastes so good.
Please let me have a taste.
(Desperate)
I'll stop suspecting you, Seok Jin.
Even if you massage my shoulders,
I'll pretend I have no idea.
- What?
- Please.
(Ignoring)
Try tteok galbi with chili peppers.
It tastes amazing.
(Jae Seok steals fried eel.)
It tastes different.
(Let me have a taste.)
Jae Seok.
Why are you eating it?
- What?
- Why are you eating it?
(Kwang Soo attempts to
retrieve the fried eel.)
When did he take it?
(Choking)
(Kwang Soo retrieves fried eel...)
(and wraps it with dried seaweed.)
Look at that.
What?
Look at him.
(I give up.)
I thought you were pulling out
my uvula.
(Kwang Soo...)
- Jae Seok.
- How does it taste?
It tastes amazing. It's crispy.
Is it crispy
even after Jae Seok chewed it?
Yes. It's still crispy.
Who has the biggest eyes?
- Me.
- Why?
I'm giving this to the one
with the biggest eyes.
- It's me.
Seok Jin.
(I have bigger eyes.)
Mine are huge.
(They show off
the white of their eyes.)
- Look at my eyes.
- My eyes are bigger.
Look at me.
- Look at my eyes.
- My eyes are actually big.
- Look at me.
(Wide open)
- Come here.
- What about me?
- My eyes are bigger.
- Kwang Soo's were bigger.
I'm sorry. Kwang Soo's eyes were
the biggest.
The funny thing is that
Jong Kook isn't doing anything.
I have no chance.
(I can't do anything
with these eyes.)
There's no point.
Guys, I like big nostrils.
(Let me try.)
Me.
(My nostrils are big.)
Let me see.
- Let me see.
- Look.
- Mine are big.
- Let me see.
Look at me.
(Why are her nostrils so big?)
(So Min uses dried laver.)
- What are you doing?
- So Min, come here.
Good job.
This is so annoying.
(Let me have some food.)
- It tastes so good.
- This is annoying.
If you have thick eyebrows,
come to me.
(If you have thick eyebrows,
come to me.)
Mine are thick.
If you...
Okay.
Look.
(What do you think of my eyebrows?)
Who has...
- thick eyebrows?
- Me.
(He drops dried laver.)
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
(He wraps fried eel
with dried laver.)
I dropped it.
- It's my dried laver.
- It's just dried laver, right?
It's really...
Why are you eating it?
(I saw it.)
- What?
- Why are you eating eel?
- Why are you eating it?
- Eel...
(Kwang Soo attempts to
retrieve the eel again.)
(Jae Seok bites
Kwang Soo's fingers.)
(Screaming)
It's here.
(Is Kwang Soo giving up?)
So Min, take it out.
(He asks for help.)
- Take it out.
- Push his belly.
That's it.
Take it.
- Let's give them more.
- That's his tongue.
(The eel is intercepted.)
Hey.
(Eel tastes great with dried laver.)
(Give me my eel!)
Why were you eating eel?
I thought I was doing
an endoscopy on Jae Seok.
I felt something soft.
I thought you were pulling out
my tongue.
You might starve to death.
(You might starve to death,
Jong Kook.)
You shouldn't stay like that.
- I'm sorry.
- That's not how you do it.
- We don't do it like that.
- I was just being realistic.
What was I supposed to do?
I'm passing this fried eel over...
to Jong Kook.
Pass it to Jong Kook.
(Please pass it to Jong Kook.)
Here. Pass it to Jong Kook.
Why don't you give it to him
directly?
I'm giving it to Jong Kook.
Let's just take a little.
He didn't say how much of it
we should pass onto him.
(Let's take a little bit.)
Stop it.
Hold on. I'll take this.
(Whatever)
(The eel disappears.)
What happened to my eel?
- It's not here yet.
- There was an accident.
Please pass this tteok galbi
to Jong Kook.
(Please pass it onto Jong Kook.)
I ate some.
I just need this much.
(So Min takes everything.)
(I'm getting nothing again.)
Gosh, you're...
(Kwang Soo retrieves tteok galbi.)
Are you crazy?
(How will tteok galbi taste
wrapped in dried laver?)
I've eaten many different things,
but I don't know
their natural flavors.
(Let's move on.)
(Today's penalty is water bomb.)
It's war.
What's that?
(They'll be throwing shoes.)
(Barrel men)
It's the barrel man game.
This is your last chance to
avoid the water bomb.
It's Lucky Man Quiz.
(Lucky Man Quiz)
Lucky Man?
Lucky Man.
If you know the answer
to the question,
stick as many knives as you want
into the two barrels,
and say the answer.
If someone sticks more knives
than the previous person does,
that person will have priority
to say the answer.
The one who sticks the most knives
gets the chance to say the answer.
(That person has priority.)
- It was hard last time.
- You have to stick many knives.
We've done it before.
The rules are the same
except one thing.
(There's a new rule.)
Let's say one of the men popped up.
If you cause the other man
to pop up too,
you'll lose twice as many knives
as you've stuck.
(If you cause the other man
to pop up too,)
(you'll lose twice as many knives
as you stuck.)
- You'll lose them?
- Yes.
You should be careful.
(Who will win this game where you
have to be both bold and patient?)
As it's 2018, each member will
get 18 knives.
By throwing your shoes,
you can get additional knives.
(You can get additional knives.)
Let me tell you the numbers of
Gold Pouches and Stone Pouches.
- Yes.
- Right.
At the moment...
(The final update)
There are 2 Gold Pouches
and 6 Stone Pouches.
(2 Gold Pouches and 6 Stone Pouches)
(The number of Gold Pouches
decreased by 2 on the way.)
Six Stone Pouches?
There are six Stone Pouches?
- How many Stone Pouches?
- There are six.
(Jae Seok and
another Hands of Stone...)
(have started moving.)
When did it happen?
- I didn't do anything.
- It happened during lunch.
- It must be the other team.
- They were moving all the time.
- Right?
We were just trying to get food.
- Six Stone Pouches?
- It's the other team.
(It's time for two Hands of Stone
to work together.)
(Who is the other one?)
You can win additional knives
in this game.
Just do it like this.
- Right.
- There you go.
You have 23 knives now.
This side...
- Multiplied by two?
- Yes.
- I have the most knives.
Do you have your knives?
- Yes.
Here is...
the first question.
What is the name of the string...
attached to books such as the Bible?
One, bookmark string.
Two, middle string.
Three, notice string.
Four, dividing string.
It's hard.
Me.
Say how many knives
you're going to bet.
One.
(If she sticks it successfully,
she gets the chance.)
Please stick it into the barrel.
(Sticking)
(So Min succeeds.)
Me.
I'll bet five.
(Kwang Soo never lets
So Min succeed.)
- Five?
- Yes.
You get the chance
only if the man doesn't pop up.
- Pop up.
I'm sure it will.
Otherwise, it'd be weird.
Right.
Even more?
(It's the last knife.)
- It's there.
- If you stick so many...
Okay.
It's not like you.
(Kwang Soo gets the chance.)
- I have no idea.
- I can't even try.
If no one wants to try,
Kwang Soo will get the chance.
If he says the wrong answer,
So Min will get the chance.
(If Kwang Soo is wrong,
So Min will get the chance.)
Okay. I'll say the right answer.
- I'm sure.
- Kwang Soo.
- I know the answer.
- I'll give you three seconds.
Two, middle string.
- That's wrong.
- That sounded wrong.
I don't think it's middle string.
Is it?
(What's the name of the string?)
It's wrong. I knew it.
(Kwang Soo has to return 5 knives.)
So Min will get it right.
So Min.
Three, notice string.
- Please.
- Okay.
There are two left.
It's either 1 or 4 now.
You have to bet your knives.
You have to bet at least six.
(Se Chan was born as huge fire.)
I'll bet six.
- Do it.
- Let me try.
- I think he'll get it right.
- I bet six.
Six?
You can stick them
into the other barrel too.
- Can I?
- Yes.
- Really?
- That's why we have two.
- You should have told us.
(Why did I stick all of them
into one barrel?)
(Se Chan goes for the other barrel.)
One.
(I even won Excellence Award.
It's time to get moving.)
5 and 6. Okay.
The next person has to bet
at least seven.
The other barrel has
many empty slots.
I'll bet seven.
Then I have to bet eight.
(Seok Jin will finally
shake up the game.)
Was one bookmark string?
(Confused)
Was it?
(What was the question?)
Was one bookmark string?
He doesn't even remember
the choices.
Was number one bookmark string?
(He only memorizes number 1.)
- One is bookmark string.
- It's exactly...
- Two.
- like this year's fortune.
He acts before thinking.
Let's go.
Okay, one.
- He's amazing.
- What?
(He makes a bet with 7 knives.)
All right.
(He already stuck 6 knives.)
Please.
- It won't pop.
- Okay.
- Do I stick two more?
- Yes.
- I bet two more.
- Okay.
(Se Chan bets 2 more.)
- Here we go.
Come on. Okay.
(He successfully sticks in 2.)
I hope it pops for him.
If it pops, you lose.
This is incredible.
- It'll pop no matter what.
- Go on.
Will anyone invest two?
If I win, I'll give back four.
- I'll invest two.
- Okay.
Seok Jin.
- If I win, I'll give two more.
- Recite the choices.
What were the choices?
1 was bookmark string,
4 was...
- My answer is one anyway.
- Never mind.
- How can you invest in him?
- Come on.
Make your investment now.
- Will you give 4?
- If I win, I'll give back 4.
- I'll give you 2 more.
If this were a stock investment,
she's investing in an unknown stock.
Please don't pop. Please don't.
There aren't many here.
Please pop.
Okay.
(Double my investment?)
They're lasting for so long.
(This is as far as
Seok Jin will go.)
(Her dream of doubling
her investment is destroyed.)
(He gets back his 9 knives.)
This year's fortune
proves to be right.
(He's depressed.)
Don't take bold steps.
Do things slowly.
(Se Chan gets the chance to answer.)
- My answer is one.
- That's right.
- What's the answer?
- Number one?
He should say the answer.
My answer is one.
It's bookmark string.
One?
You're scaring me.
What did you say exactly?
One.
It's bookmark...
It's what marks pages.
- Could you repeat?
- Mark what?
(What is he saying?)
What I mean is,
the string marks pages.
Be more accurate. In 3, 2...
I'll choose four instead.
Four, dividing string.
(He changes his answer.)
(Incorrect)
- Number one was correct.
- That was correct.
- Was that it?
- Isn't number one correct?
- It's like a bookmark.
- The answer is bookmark string.
It's a string used as a bookmark.
(He returns his 8 knives.)
Bookmark?
(Se Chan and Seok Jin
shouldn't open a business together.)
(The two of them fail together.)
The next question is very easy.
- That's good.
- Everyone will make bets.
We should.
Everyone will make bets.
Which animal does year 2018...
- represent?
- Jae Seok.
- So Min.
- Ji Hyo.
We didn't see the choices yet.
There are only five choices.
I'll bet one for now.
I'll bet three.
(Jae Seok makes a bet of 1 knife.)
I know the answer.
We talked about it before.
Okay.
We'll be competing each other again.
- I bet five.
- Okay.
I knew Ji Hyo was competitive.
I haven't played in a while.
(Lucky Ji Hyo makes a bet
after a long time.)
Ji Hyo stuck five knives.
You must bet six
if you bet for the first time.
- Jae Seok must stick five more.
- Five more?
Can you guess which answer it is?
Come on.
We don't care because we're moths.
We just go for it.
- Isn't it...
- We go for it.
better to wait which answer remains?
No, we don't care.
(In that case...)
May I make a bet now?
- You must bet seven knives.
- I will.
I don't want to play this round.
If it pops for Kwang Soo,
do I get the chance?
I hope it pops for Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo bets 7 knives.)
Seven knives are a lot.
- Please pop.
- Is he betting them all?
I must win no matter what.
Which number do you think it is?
Answers to the last 2 questions
were number 1.
It's number three.
(He hopes that it will pop.)
I'll get it right.
(The others watch
Kwang Soo's bold action.)
It'll pop this time.
(Kwang Soo sticks 4 knives safely.)
This isn't like Kwang Soo.
(He sticks in 5 knives safely.)
- I have two left.
- Okay.
Kwang Soo.
This isn't like you.
Okay.
(He sticks in 6 knives
without a problem.)
(He's lucky in 2018.)
Please pop. It has to pop.
- It's the last spark.
- 5, 4...
It's not the last spark.
(Although it's the last fortune
for him,)
(Kwang Soo does get lucky
after all.)
- Two.
- This is it.
(Will he stick in 7 knives
successfully?)
Okay.
Jae Seok must stick in
two more knives.
- Two more?
- Yes.
- That's a total of 8.
- 2 will be worth it.
It's worth playing.
Okay.
Two is worth playing.
You should go for it, Jae Seok.
I'll just watch them play.
(Their competition
gets more intense.)
If Jae Seok fails this round,
we'll get four choices.
(Jae Seok only has 1 knife left.)
You lose if it pops.
Okay.
What will you do now?
- I'll bet more.
- This time...
Ji Hyo already made a bet of eight.
- You must stick 4 more.
- Is it 4?
My goodness.
I'm so glad that
I didn't play this round.
My goodness.
(What's up with everyone?)
She'll answer correctly
and win this round.
- Right.
- It'll be over.
That would be amazing.
There aren't many left.
(Will she be lucky again?)
She had the most fortune this year.
Okay!
(It pops.)
Goodness.
I only benefited others.
- You need to stick 1 more.
- Stick 1 more.
If it pops this time,
you'll lose double.
(If she fails,
she loses double the amount.)
Double the amount?
(She fails for the second time.)
Yes!
(Lucky Ji Hyo loses her luck.)
(The barrel man pops up every time
Ji Hyo sticks in a knife.)
What's going on?
- Ji Hyo.
- Goodness.
How could this happen?
(She returns 18 of her knives.)
I wanted to win.
Jae Seok bet eight knives so far.
It's time to answer the question.
What will you do, Kwang Soo?
If he's wrong, do I get the chance?
- Can I go after Kwang Soo?
- Okay.
- You're after Kwang Soo.
- Right?
- I forgot about So Min.
- I stuck three knives.
Gosh, that's right.
If So Min takes all,
that would be incredible.
All the bold ones made a bet.
Let's watch Jae Seok lose.
- Ji Hyo.
- Narrow down the answers.
Ji Hyo started the game for us.
- I didn't even get to play.
- Let's go.
(The real competition starts now.)
There's no way that
he'll answer correctly.
(Which number will Jae Seok guess?)
Number three, dog.
(Jae Seok chooses number 3.)
(Is number 3 the right answer?)
Three.
- Is it dog?
- Dog.
(If he gets it wrong,
the others get their chance.)
Number three, dog.
(Jae Seok chooses number 3.)
(Is number 3 the right answer?)
Three.
- Is it dog?
- Dog.
(If he gets it wrong,
the others get their chance.)
Is number three dog?
(Incorrect)
- My goodness.
- Jae Seok is eliminated.
(Passionate Jae Seok is eliminated.)
- Bye, you're eliminated
Kwang Soo made a bet of seven.
Answers to the last 2 questions
were 1.
- Don't win.
- It's either 2 or 4.
The question is easy.
That means the choices were...
one, spoon worms.
Two, dog meat.
- Four is most likely.
- In 5, 4...
Four, dog.
- No.
- Is number four dog?
(His choice is correct.)
Yes!
(The competition was fierce.
The final winner is Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo.
I was thinking that too.
The question was easy.
The choice would be the last.
(Number 4 is the answer.)
Here's the next question.
I'll win this time no matter what.
Don't joke around.
Among the choices,
which doesn't appear...
in a children's song called
"Butterfly"?
One, yellow butterfly.
Two, swallowtail butterfly.
Three, swallow.
Four, white butterfly.
I know the answer.
I bet three.
(She definitely knows the answer.)
Let me win once.
(So Min bets 3 knives.)
I bet four.
(Jae Seok bets 4 knives.)
Okay.
I compete against So Min again.
(Butterfly, butterfly,
fly over here)
(Here's the correct answer
for the viewers.)
(Number 2, swallowtail butterfly)
I bet five knives.
I'll stick five knives.
(Everyone gets competitive.)
If we aren't careful, I'll lose.
Isn't it white butterfly?
No.
Swallowtail butterfly,
white butterfly
- Come as you dance
- Come
- The spring breeze
The yellow butterfly is missing.
- The yellow butterfly?
- Yes.
The yellow butterfly.
Was it number one?
- I haven't heard it for so long.
- Right?
(Ji Hyo and So Min are stuck.)
Next person.
(Kwang Soo makes his bet.)
(There is only one left.)
The last one.
Oh, no. Goodbye.
(Goodbye, Kwang Soo.)
Goodbye. And...
No, I'm going to bet more.
We just got rid of a tiger moth.
(The whole place is
filled with tiger moths.)
- Wait.
- Please.
So Min.
(So Min is making a rash bet
with the wrong answer.)
Okay.
(The tiger moth war continues
until one drops out.)
Okay.
- Yes.
- Is she going to continue?
(Goodness, So Min knows.)
So Min knows.
You just bet six of them.
You're right.
- Tell me the answer.
- Two, swallowtail butterfly.
Two, swallowtail butterfly.
(That's the wrong answer.)
- Two, swallowtail butterfly.
- Yes.
That's it.
(They get six more knives
thanks to Jae Seok.)
"Yellow butterfly
and white butterfly"
- Yes.
- Right.
"Even sparrows tweet"
Swallowtail and white butterfly
- We thought it was the yellow.
- We both thought...
We went with swallowtail butterfly.
- Okay.
- It's not swallowtail butterfly.
Here's the current score.
The current number of knives.
(With two questions left, these are
the number of knives they have.)
(Jong Kook is the current winner.)
Is Jong Kook winning?
- He's leading with 26.
- I didn't do anything.
He just sat around.
- That's why he has 26.
- Wow, really?
I'll keep it going.
He's very cautious.
That's just my personality.
(I'll make my bet when I'm sure.)
Now, I have another picture quiz.
You can take a close look
and answer it correctly.
When you order pizza,
this thing sits in the middle.
What is this called?
I know this because
I've worked at a pizza place.
One, pizza holder.
Two, pizza guard.
Three, pizza saver.
Four, pizza stick.
I don't think he knows.
I bet three.
- I'm going.
- If he's sure, I won't jump in.
(Se Chan, the ex-pizza part timer,
attempts to save himself.)
I bet three.
I bet...
This will be the hardest year yet.
(I'll have to wait this year.)
- How many can I bet?
- You can join with four.
(No one wants to step in
because Se Chan is so sure.)
If he's perfectly sure, there's...
Are you completely sure?
I used to deliver pizza.
He's going to take this to the end.
So Min.
- Will you jump in?
- I'll bet five.
Okay, jump in.
- Fine.
- Okay.
There's no reason to save these.
- Oh, good.
- There's no reason to save these.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated at once
as always.)
That's the Kwang Soo we know.
Kwang Soo is back.
(The Kwang Soo we know is back.)
- There he is.
- Kwang Soo returns. Welcome back.
There he is.
No, you have to use that one.
You can't use that one anymore.
If it pops out again,
we're taking away twice as much.
- Wow.
- Wow, that's unbelievable.
(Kwang Soo of 2018
just got unluckier than ever.)
- This is insane.
- That's who you are.
Welcome back, Kwang Soo.
Welcome.
(Kwang Soo became the MVP again
with his unlucky hand.)
That's amazing.
How does he do that?
Do you know how sad I was...
- because you seemed normal now?
- Me too.
I was worried.
It was as if a superhero
lost his supernatural power.
My gosh.
Kwang Soo got eliminated,
so So Min gets the first chance
to give an answer.
I don't know this.
I have to take a guess.
I don't know the answer.
(What's this thing that holds
a pizza down in a box?)
One, pizza holder.
- One, pizza holder.
- No?
It's wrong?
Wait, it's not pizza holder?
What?
What do you mean?
Which pizza shop did you work at?
"Hey, go place
the pizza holder there."
Maybe the owner made it up
and called it...
- a pizza holder.
- "Put the holder in."
He said that before I went out.
"Bring the holders."
That's what he said.
It was a term that was only
used at that shop.
Pizza guard was number two, right?
Se Chan, if you get this right,
you'll be winning.
I choose number two, pizza guard.
You just chose
number two, pizza guard.
Yes, number two, pizza guard.
Why are you asking again?
Two, pizza guard.
What was that?
The question is over. The answer is
number three, pizza saver.
- It's number three.
- It's pizza saver.
Then why did my employer
tell me to bring the holders?
That's easier to say.
(Se Chan the ex-pizza delivery guy
loses 3 knives.)
- Here's the question.
- It's the last one.
Let's do this one.
How many do I have?
Am I in second place?
- How should I...
- Give me one moment.
I didn't do anything,
and I'm in second place.
- I'll jump in with this one.
- What if I double mine?
This question isn't too hard either.
- We have to get this one right.
- It's the last question.
You all know the Chinese dish,
ganjjajang, right?
- Yes.
- I used to work at a Chinese place.
- Ganjjajang from Chinese places.
- I really did.
- You worked at a Chinese place?
Yes, I was the delivery guy.
In the word "ganjjajang",
gan is a Chinese character.
What does this character mean?
Gan?
One, to see.
- Two, to become dry.
- To become dry.
- Three, between.
- Between.
Four, sincerity.
- I'll answer.
- Se Chan...
- So Min.
- I bet 10 knives.
Okay. Haha jumped in first
with 10 knives.
It's game over if it pops up, right?
If it pops up, it's game over,
and Jong Kook wins.
That's...
(If it pops up, Jong Kook will win.)
I'm going to jump in too.
- Here we go.
- Come on.
(Haha bets 10 knives.)
Here we go with 10 knives.
(Goodness)
(Did it pop out right away?)
Okay.
- Wow, it popped out.
- All right.
He went overboard with
betting 10 knives.
(He has to pluck in 9 more knives
into the 2nd barrel.)
(Wait, will I end up
winning like this?)
How did that pop out right away?
It's game over once it pops out.
Game over.
(Wait.)
(That means the winner is...)
Haha, 20 knives are
taken away from you.
The game is...
- over as of now.
- It's over.
- How can this be?
- How can it be?
How can...
- We solved one question.
- Great job, everyone.
- Jong Kook didn't do anything.
- Why does he get to win?
That's it.
- How can this be?
- He didn't do anything.
It's always the best idea
to play it safe.
Everyone, gambling
isn't good for you.
- What happened?
- Don't gamble.
Haha lost 20,
so he now has 1, not 21.
It feels as if I am stuck in
a pitch-black room.
(Was his fortune correct?)
- Can we play one more round?
- Don't gamble, everyone.
- Last round?
- Last one.
- Last one?
- Jong Kook, it's up to...
Do whatever you want. I don't care.
I didn't do anything to win.
It'll be weird if I stopped this.
Yes, thank you.
Then Haha can take a rest.
- Haha is bankrupt.
- Yes, he is.
- We'll keep the same question.
- Okay, thank you.
(The question remains the same.)
(The real, final round)
All right.
We're starting again from now.
I want to join too.
- It's too late. Go back.
- Why?
- How many?
- Seven.
- Then...
- Me too.
I'm going to begin at eight.
(Just take a rest.)
No, Jae Seok.
- How many do you have?
- Only six.
- You're out. It's just you and me.
- I'm going to bet eight.
I want to bet eight.
Gosh, I hate him.
Jae Seok bet eight.
- 8 knives?
- There's 1.
- Okay.
- Okay, you're done.
(He gets eliminated
at the second knife.)
- What was that?
- Wait, Jae Seok.
- You need to keep this going.
- How did he do that?
You need to push in
the rest of the knives.
I think I'm going to cry.
Come on, put them in.
You still have a chance.
My gosh.
What?
(Again?)
This has to be a prank.
How did he do that?
- Really?
- How does this make any sense?
- What is this?
- Really?
Jae Seok, we'll take away
16 knives. You have 3 left.
(Jae Seok gets 16 knives taken away,
leaving him with 3.)
- Jong Kook is still winning.
- I have eight.
That's amazing.
- Ji Hyo.
- My gosh.
My goodness.
To be honest,
the only two that has
a chance of winning are...
Seok Jin and Se Chan.
Then you two can
put an end to this game.
I'll give you one more chance.
(The truly, last, final round)
Rock, paper, scissors
- Okay.
- You can go first.
(Se Chan won, so he will go first.)
If this pops up again, something is
just telling us to stop.
To win against Jong Kook,
you have to bet more than six.
Six?
Let's start with six.
- 6 knives, okay.
- Let's start with 6.
- Let's do it.
- One.
(Feeling nervous)
What if Jong Kook wins
without lifting a finger...
(What if Jong Kook wins
without lifting a finger...)
(Jong Kook wins
without lifting a finger.)
Forget it.
We're done. I'm quitting.
(Forget it!)
- You have to put in the rest.
- Jong Kook didn't do anything.
That's unbelievable.
- Is someone playing a joke on us?
- No.
- Are you doing this?
- How could we?
Did you do something to this?
- Maybe you have a button.
- We don't.
- They might have a button.
- Then lift up both of your arms.
- I mean...
- We have to investigate.
Everyone, stop gambling.
Hey, go through their pockets.
- Who's doing this?
- Who has a hand in their pocket?
I'm not doing this.
Everyone, do you need
another chance?
We can't do that.
We don't have more players.
- Forget it.
- We lost.
Isn't the answer number two?
The answer is two, to become dry.
Exactly. That was
the only question I actually knew.
Wait, isn't it sincerity?
It's to become dry.
(He's sure it's sincerity.)
That's what I thought too.
Number four.
My employer told me...
Do you think regular jjajangmyeon is
made without...
- any sincerity?
- My employer said...
he makes ganjjajang
with more sincerity...
because it was
50 cents more expensive.
(50 cents worth of sincerity)
Oh, so that wasn't it.
The winner is Jong Kook
who has 26 knives left.
However...
(However...)
(Will it be stone or gold? The final
result is yet to be revealed.)
The current status is
0 Gold Pouches and 8 Stone Pouches.
(0 Gold Pouches, 8 Stone Pouches)
(Did everyone's pouch end up
becoming Stone Pouches?)
(Thanks to the Hands of Stone,)
(the 6 other members
will be water-bombed.)
The last chance you have is...
for you to figure out
the two Hands of Stone.
Let's get them.
You will each walk into
the voting booth...
and write the names of two people
you believe are the Hands of Stone.
So it's Seok Jin
and one more person.
It's Jae Seok.
Hey, I'm telling you. It's not me.
(Do most members think
it's Seok Jin and Jae Seok?)
- The two, old men.
- This is really frustrating.
I mean, I... I won't say it
because it'll only sound weird.
(Jae Seok puts on bad acting.)
(Is Jae Seok really
the Hands of Stone?)
So Min, it's odd that
you aren't investigating today.
- Me?
- You're usually curious.
First of all...
(So Min is usually talkative.
Why is she so silent today?)
Do you have an idea?
I don't think it's Seok Jin.
I thought it was him, but no.
I'm not it.
If it's not him, who is it?
- I'm really not it.
- Se Chan?
(Is Seok Jin desperate
because he really isn't it?)
- I think they're these two.
- Jae Seok and...
Jae Seok and So Min.
- The two of them.
- I thought so too.
Anyone that's not me.
(Hands of Stone remain in mystery.
What will happen to them?)
(Everyone except for Jong Kook
have begun to vote.)
I'm sure of one,
but I'm confused
about the other one.
It's either So Min or Jong Kook.
(Haha chooses Jae Seok and So Min.)
I'll go with my gut feeling.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
- I choose Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
- They were so obvious.
(Kwang Soo is contemplating.)
I really have no idea.
(Which two will he choose?)
(He votes for Jae Seok and Seok Jin
like Ji Hyo and Se Chan.)
I'll go with Jae Seok and Se Chan.
(So Min chooses
Jae Seok and Se Chan.)
(Another possible candidate,
Seok Jin)
(He chooses So Min and Se Chan.)
(Who's Jae Seok's partner,
the other Hands of Stone?)
I will announce the two
Hands of Stone now.
They successfully...
carried out their mission
so that you will all get wet.
And those of you
who guess them right...
will be excluded from
the water bombs.
Among the five members other than
Jong Kook and the Hands of Stone,
3 members guessed right
and 2 guessed wrong.
Three people got it right?
(The three will be
excluded from the penalty.)
The first Hands of Stone is...
(The first Hands of Stone is...)
Jae Seok.
- It was you?
- It had to be him.
(There were two Gold Pouches left
during the last mission.)
(He successfully...)
(carried out the mission
for Hands of Stone.)
(Nonetheless,
I carried out the mission.)
The second Hands of Stone is...
Who is it?
(Who's the mysterious
second Hands of Stone?)
This person put on great acting.
Gosh, please.
(Is she acting?
Or did she spot something?)
(This Hands of Stone will decide
the members who'll get wet today.)
Gosh, please.
- It's Seok Jin.
- See?
(The second Hands of Stone is
Seok Jin.)
Really?
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and
Kwang Soo answered correctly.)
(Haha and So Min were wrong.)
(Excited)
(Today morning
right before the shooting)
We met up so early.
You are one of
the two Hands of Stone.
Your hidden mission is...
to share your water
with other members.
(He got way too motivated and
offered Kwang Soo his water.)
The couples...
(Stepping on foot)
(But Jae Seok did his mission too,)
(so Kwang Soo ended up
with a Gold Pouch.)
(Ji Hyo, have some water.)
(Seok Jin never shares water,
but today, he was the water fairy.)
- I'm fine.
- Have some.
(He suspiciously kept on
doing his mission.)
(The water fairy successfully
changed everyone's pouches.)
(Seok Jin must be
the Hands of Stone.)
Did you two know?
To be honest, I thought
it was Haha at first.
I figured out later
that it was Jae Seok.
He's not a guy who's considerate
enough to offer us water.
He said something to me
which he never said before.
What did I say?
It was weird
that you offered me water.
Then I said, "I'm fine."
But you said, "Have some."
(He sounded so awkward
saying, "Have some.")
"Have some"?
My gosh, Seok Jin.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan are
excluded from the water bomb.
- Okay.
- That's awesome.
My gut feelings were right.
Kwang Soo, you guessed
the Hands of Stone correctly,
but you have to get the penalty
from last episode.
Right.
(Kwang Soo will receive the penalty
carried over from last episode.)
(Here are the people
who will get the water bomb.)
It's still a cold, winter day.
(The four members get to start
the new year with a water bomb.)
Thanks to Kwang Soo,
I also get to receive a water bomb.
I want to show him
how things will turn out...
when he gets water-bombed with me.
Kwang Soo, we have to
do this anyway.
Let's not keep this on.
- Okay, I'll do it.
- Yes, do it.
- I'm doing it. Really?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- I'm doing it.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'll do it.
- Let's take the jacket off.
- I'm doing it.
- Are you serious?
- Take off everything.
- Okay.
- Wait, are you going topless?
(They become competitive.)
Okay.
(Their passion is
headed to a wrong place.)
Take it off.
- Wait...
- Take them off.
What's he doing?
- What's with you?
- What's wrong?
- Take them off.
- Do it!
- What's with you two?
Take them off.
So Min, stop it.
Come on, stop it.
You don't have to do this.
- You don't have to join them.
- Stop it.
What's with you all?
Come on, take them off.
- What's with you all?
- Someone stop So Min.
- Okay, fine.
- Let's take them off.
(Kwang Soo has gone crazy already.)
My goodness.
What's with you?
So Min, what's wrong?
- Keep the shirt on.
- What's with you, So Min?
- Why is So Min jumping in?
- What's with her?
- Someone stop him.
- Stop it.
That's enough.
- Do it!
- That's enough.
I'm going to take them all off.
- Do it!
This isn't...
- My gosh.
- Do it.
I'm not in this insanity, okay?
- Of course.
- One.
- All right.
- Two.
- Let's go.
- Three.
(The four will begin the year
with a cold water bomb.)
(Splash)
(They come to their senses.)
(Kwang Soo!)
(Yes, Jong Kook!)
(She's having fun
not realizing how she looks.)
Hey.
(Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, So Min,
and Haha receive their penalties.)
- That was awesome.
- So awesome.
It's the year 2018,
the year of the dog.
- Happy New Year, everyone.
- Happy New Year.
(We will run hard this year too.
Happy New Year, everyone.)
(In the new year,)
(there is something
we really wish to do.)
(We'll wear spandex.)
(What?)
(Is Kwang Soo really
dressed in spandex?)
Se Chan becomes a catfish.
(Did Se Chan really
become a catfish?)
(Whatever they think
becomes a reality?)
(Help us, celebrities.)
Is this Yoon Kye Sang?
Are you all alone?
(Celebrities have joined in
to help out the members.)
(The more they contribute,
the less they will be humiliated.)
(Celebrities try their best
to keep them from wearing spandex.)
(The New Year Star Wars)