(Recap)
(Part 2 of the TV rating notice had finally returned!)
(It was time to change the current notice, Jae Seok and the Animals.)
(The notice, the poster, and the official photo were at stake.)
(The storyboards were more ruthless.)
(The disguises would be even more dreadful.)
(The race's winner's storyboard will be the TV rating notice.)
(The members' scenarios were more varied.)
(There was an ingenious scenario, Doppelganger TV Rating Notice.)
(Kwang Soo will be Han Gi Beom.)
(Jong Kook will be Pak Se Ri.)
(It's time to choose the scenario for the 2nd TV rating notice.)
(They carried out a mission with the guests.)
(Now, only the final mission remains.)
(The current score after the 1st mission)
(They enter the swimming pool for the last round.)
I am already scared. Is this what we are doing today?
We will fall into the water again.
(The final round involves the improved flying chairs.)
What should I do? I am so scared.
- You press the button. - Yes, from here.
- Running Man is rated... - Is that Pirate Roulette Game?
(Kwang Soo is surprised.)
We will play the Pirate Roulette Game with the flying chairs.
That's unbelievable.
All of you are here.
Before we move onto the last round,
let me tell you that your seat is very important.
Really?
(Their seats can change the result of the game.)
I will give you the last chance to choose your seats.
People who sit next to you are very important.
I won't sit next to Kwang Soo.
(No matter what it is, I don't want to sit next to him.)
Hold on.
We should avoid Kwang Soo and So Min.
We should avoid Jae Seok as well.
(The members become serious because of the flying chairs.)
Choose your seats.
Choose by the current ranks. Top one chooses first.
- Hurry up and choose. - You didn't tell us the reason.
Let's sit together.
- You came second. - All right.
- You should tell us the reason. - Will you sit there?
Okay.
Hold on. If you sit next to her...
- Ji Hyo, come here. - Do you want to sit next to her?
- Hold on. For goodness' sake! - Yes!
(I see that my seat is empty.)
- For goodness' sake! - Yes!
- Go away. - Yes!
- Go away. - We are saved.
Go away.
I am going to sit here.
- Do you have a problem? - It looks nice.
This side is better.
- It looks nice. - Seriously.
- What should I do? - It's your turn to choose.
- I am so nervous. - Jae Seok.
Poop should go to the poop field.
(Why are you hesitating?)
(It's clear that the seat is for Jae Seok.)
- Why would you say that? - Must you ask?
(Jae Seok is the last member of the trio.)
- Poop should go to the poop field. - Come here.
- Tiger moths should stay together. - That's right.
- Let's go. - All right.
Okay. That's good.
(The tiger moth trio is formed.)
I ended up sitting next to Jong Kook.
You ended up sitting next to me.
- Se Chan. - Let's go.
The last mission is...
The Flying Pirate Quiz.
(The Flying Pirate Quiz)
- How does it work? - Each member gets 20 swords...
and additional swords that match their scores from the last mission.
The member who knows the answer to the question...
can bet as many swords as he or she wants.
The member who bets the most swords will answer.
You know the rules, right?
(If your answer is wrong, you lose the swords and get a penalty.)
If someone gets a question right, the members on both sides...
get a penalty and lose five swords.
(The members on both sides get a penalty and lose 5 swords.)
(If the person next to you is good, you get penalties and lose swords.)
- That's too much. - For goodness' sake.
- My seat is bad. - The smart one gets everything.
- Your seat is good because... - Why?
If she gets a question right...
Oh, she can't get any right.
(Ji Hyo is hopeless when it comes to quizzes.)
She does horribly at guessing.
(So Min is nervous since Jae Seok is good.)
- Don't get it right. - Don't.
There are five questions in total.
The member with the most number of swords...
will win the three components of the TV rating notice.
I can do this.
(The Flying Pirate Quiz)
Here comes the question.
It's the first question.
The word, "bidet",
comes from a French word that means this.
- Really? - Choose from the following choices.
Number one, swan.
Number two, pony.
Number three, fountain.
Number four, valley.
- I have the answer. - How many swords will you bet?
(Swan, pony, fountain, valley)
I will bet five swords.
He gets the penalty if he is wrong, right?
I am glad I am not sitting next to Kwang Soo.
- I hope the pirate pops up. - I hope it pops up.
(Kwang Soo acts confidently as if he knows the answer.)
- Kwang Soo. - Pop up.
- Pop up. - He wants to get ahead.
Pop up.
(Careful)
Please.
(Please pop up, Pirate.)
- Pop up. - Okay.
(He succeeds in betting 3 swords.)
No way.
(They don't believe that Kwang Soo will succeed.)
- Come on out. - Please.
Okay!
(Only one remains.)
Your luck improved a lot.
(Inserting one more sword earns him the chance to answer the question.)
(Kwang Soo fails.)
- That was incredible. - What is this?
(Kwang Soo is the same.)
- I am so thankful. - That's amazing.
- My goodness. - I thought he might succeed.
When he sits down, we will launch him and move on.
He wants Kwang Soo to hurry up and sit down.
(He wants Kwang Soo to hurry up and sit down.)
I am scared. I am going to step aside.
I really don't want...
I really don't want to fall into the pool.
(Kwang Soo loses 5 swords and gets the flying chair penalty.)
- My goodness. - I can't bear to watch it.
(Even I am nervous.)
Here we go. 1, 2, 3.
(Even to Kwang Soo, the flying chair is nerve-wracking.)
(Flying)
(Tiger moth number 1 is launched.)
(High trajectory, long duration of flight,)
(and exceptional ugliness)
(It's a textbook example of the flying chair penalty.)
- It became stronger. - He doesn't look okay.
(He finishes testing the penalty.)
- It's a bit scary. - I know.
(The members become more nervous.)
- My goodness. - It's scary.
I can't help but focus.
- What are you doing, Ji Hyo? - Why are you fixing your clothes?
It might come off if I receive the penalty.
- I am nervous. - What is she doing?
(At that moment, So Min bets 5 swords.)
Five swords.
So Min will bet five swords.
Seeing Kwang Soo fly into the air made me less nervous.
(You should try it yourself.)
It's understandable that Kwang Soo is angry.
Still, it's scary.
It has been a while since I felt so angry.
- I am so annoyed. - My goodness.
- Do you know the answer? - We might fly into the air.
I think it's number one.
Is it because of the swan mark on the toilet?
- It's a trademark. - It's...
- It's for sinks. - Listen.
The bidet is white and shaped like this.
The round part looks like...
a swan's wings.
- I had the same thought. - That's why I chose number one.
Also, the word is French.
- It could be related to ballet. - Swan.
- Swan. - Are you thinking "Swan Lake"?
Will it be number one?
I have never been so scared.
I know for certain that the answer is "fountain".
(Screaming)
(The pirate pops out at the last sword.)
That was incredible.
- What should I do? - She doesn't disappoint.
1, 2, 3.
(Tiger moth number 2 is launched.)
(It looks like she is dancing.)
It doesn't look any weaker.
10 swords!
(10 swords!)
20 swords!
30 swords! I'll kill you all.
(As soon as she comes out of the water)
Are you serious?
I guess she gained confidence after the penalty.
Let's go.
(She tries the Pirate Roulette Game again.)
I have never felt so scared of the Pirate Roulette Game.
Stab him with swords.
(The game and the flying chair create synergy.)
- You have one more sword to go. - Bye.
(So Min successfully bets 5 swords.)
I don't know the answer.
I am sure the tiger moths will bet more swords.
(I am sure the tiger moths will bet more swords.)
- Let's see. - I will bet six swords.
(Kwang Soo decides to bet 6 swords.)
Kwang Soo got the hang of it.
Sit down, So Min.
(Peek-a-boo)
(He is the unluckiest tiger moth.)
What was that?
- My goodness. - What is wrong with you today?
Because of you, people think Running Man is scripted.
- How did this happen? - I am sick and tired of this.
(He has been the unluckiest of all time.)
(He gets launched with a resigned expression.)
(He loses 6 swords without having a chance to answer.)
If So Min gets it right, people on her sides will get thrown.
(So Min gets a chance to answer the question.)
- It's not swan. - It's not swan?
- It's not swan. - Answer the question.
So Min, what's your answer?
We get another chance if she gets it wrong, right?
We will need a bidet.
I don't want to fly into the air.
- What's your answer? - Number one, swan.
(She sticks to her answer.)
Number one, swan.
- It must be correct. - Sit down, So Min.
(If So Min's answer is correct,)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo lose 5 swords and get the penalty.)
Okay!
(Number 1, swan is incorrect.)
- She needs to get launched, right? - So Min.
(Number 1, swan, is incorrect.)
- You fool, it can't be swan. - Yes!
That makes no sense. How could it be a swan?
What was that? She went in well.
(She goes into the water in a stable way.)
- So Min is good at this now. - So Min, you did a good job.
Number one, pony.
- That's number 2. - That's number 2.
(That's number 2.)
My goodness.
It has to be pony.
(Haha gets involved with the war of bidet.)
(The pirate gives him the flying chair penalty.)
(Flying)
(Popping)
Thank goodness.
- Did you rig the game? - Thank goodness.
(Bye, kid.)
He went in well.
(The pirate's curse makes everyone suffer the penalty.)
I will bet 5 swords. 1.
(Seok Jin successfully bets 6 swords.)
I will stick in all the swords.
- Here comes Ji Hyo. - Here comes Ji Hyo.
Let's go!
What's wrong with you, Ji Hyo?
(Even Ji Hyo gets it.)
(The curse of Pirate Roulette Game)
- What's wrong with Ji Hyo? - It's her.
It's not Haha.
(Even lucky Ji Hyo is thrown.)
She went in.
- Are you okay? - What do you think it is?
(Seok Jin gets a chance to answer.)
What do you think it is? Is it pony?
You'll answer wrong.
I think it's pony.
- Napoleon rode horses. - Right.
French people like horses.
- Why... - Is it me if you're correct?
- It's you if I answer correctly. - No.
- You're telling me nonsense. - Fountain is the answer.
(He hopes that Seok Jin answers incorrectly.)
I know the answer.
(What's his answer?)
Pony.
(His answer is pony.)
- I hope he's wrong. - Is the answer pony?
(If it's correct, Haha and Ji Hyo are penalized.)
- I thought it was fountain. - He answered pony.
Let it be fountain.
(Is the answer number 2, pony?)
The answer is fountain.
(Pony is correct.)
- I told you. - Was it pony?
Everyone, please applaud.
Give him a round of applause.
(Bidet refers to a pet pony in French.)
(Haha and Ji Hyo lose 5 swords, and they're penalized.)
Both of them were thrown off.
(Seok Jin wins 6 swords.)
The makeup show is coming up soon.
Here's the last question.
- Do you know the current score? - Yes.
- Jae Seok is running first place. - It's Jae Seok.
Jae Seok is most likely to win.
(Jae Seok's "The Greatest Showman")
- Is it Jae Seok? - It's his TV rating notice.
It could be "The Greatest Showman".
We must stop him.
I'll be a giant joker.
(We must stop him. I'll be a giant joker.)
- It can't be his. - I should win.
"The Greatest Showman" doesn't fit.
I have to hang upside down.
- Who wants to be a giant? - We must do it. We have time.
I keep thinking of ideas.
(Here's the last question.)
Here's the question.
In Greek and Roman mythology,
what did the sphinx do...
when Oedipus answered the riddle correctly?
Number one, it turned into a rock.
Number two, it turned into dust.
Number three, it turned into an animal.
Number four, it jumped off of a cliff.
I bet five swords.
Five?
I'll go.
- Will you bet five? - Yes.
Please pop.
(He tries to jinx her.)
- Come on, Se Chan. - I'm sorry. I'll stop.
Empty your mind, So Min.
You've been in the water many times, so relax.
- I want to win. - Otherwise, you'll lose.
- Just stick the swords. - If you take time, you'll lose.
(The pirate pops.)
Come on, So Min.
(She really loses.)
I told you to be ready.
It popped at the third try. It startled me.
It's because you're sitting next to Kwang Soo.
(She gets penalized again.)
So Min, if you give them to me,
- I'll get penalized instead. - I have to win.
(Do we have a deal?)
- To you? - Give me 10 swords.
I'll go in the water if you give me nine.
I'll go in if you give me three.
- I accept 3. - 3?
(She accepts his offer.)
- Three. - Seriously?
Wait! I'll accept two.
- How about one? - Okay.
(Kwang Soo offers to take just one.)
(He feels like a loser.)
- Gosh. - One?
Is this how Kwang Soo will play?
(Currently, Kwang Soo has no swords.)
(He goes into the water instead.)
He can't control his body.
Kwang Soo is good at flying.
- It's strange. - So Min.
- Pardon? - Thank you.
- I only have two left. - Kwang Soo.
- You should bet one. - Okay.
If the pirate pops,
- What if it pops after one sword? - he deserves the Grand Prize.
I'd be really impressed.
(If the pirate pops, he deserves the Grand Prize.)
I'm getting teary-eyed.
- He looks so ugly. - Where are you looking?
He looks so ugly.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I got it.
- Let's start betting. - Wait.
What are you saying?
(Let's start to bet.)
- Why? - We should make bets.
- We should make bets. - Will you bet five?
Those next to him should bet.
- No way. I can't believe this. - What's going on?
I'll bet two.
(Se Chan bets 2.)
I bet two.
(He's safe.)
I'll bet three.
(He makes a bet of 3.)
Is it over for me after this round?
(Is it over for me?)
It's over once two people are ahead of me.
It's over.
I'll bet three.
(Haha is the third to play.)
That's amazing. He's bold.
(He becomes bold.)
(Haha makes a bet of 3.)
Is anyone betting more? It'll have to be four swords.
- You must bet four. - What about me?
We need two more.
- How about a bet of 4? - Will anyone bet 4?
Is there anyone? I'll bet two more.
- Can you take back your swords? - Don't be scared.
- Please pop. - Don't be scared.
I bet two more.
Please pop.
This is the last round.
- It went in safely. - Is this the last question?
(The competition gets fierce.)
Let's continue.
How many does the next person have to bet?
You must bet six swords.
- Six? - Make a bet.
I don't think he'll answer correctly.
After he's thrown in the water...
Can we try again after that?
Yes, that's what I'm waiting for.
- That's what I'm waiting for. - I'll do that too.
- I see. - You and I'll lose anyway.
- We'll lose anyway. - Anyway,
after those two get thrown in,
- I'll take my chances. - Let's do this.
- Let's bless each other. - Of course.
What's your answer?
- Mine is number 3. - Then I'll answer number 4.
Okay.
- Okay? Nevis. - Okay. Swing.
(The silly brothers return to the game.)
Okay, it's done.
(Se Chan makes additional bets.)
- It's done. - Go first.
(Go first.)
- Go and answer the question first. - Me?
- Okay. - Make more bets.
- I won't. - Why not?
You answer it.
Can't he make more bets?
- He doesn't have to. - I won't.
Haha also thinks that you'll answer incorrectly.
(Haha also thinks that you'll answer incorrectly.)
Other people can bet.
It's the last question.
- Se Chan won't be right. - It's too difficult.
The answer is number three.
(Se Chan's answer is number 3.)
Number 3, she turns into an animal.
- I think it's wrong. - Okay!
(Number 3 is wrong.)
Have a seat.
- Is it my turn next? - Go.
- I thought it was correct. - Okay!
- It's the last question. - I'm definitely correct.
Number four.
(If Haha is correct, he places first instead of Jae Seok.)
(If Haha is wrong, Jae Seok wins.)
Number four, it jumped off of a cliff.
(Will Haha answer and become the winner?)
All right!
(Haha answers correctly.)
- Is it correct? - How did you know?
(Haha wins the race.)
- How did you know? - How did you know the answer?
So now,
Haha gets additional 5 on top of his 26 swords.
He wins with a total of 31 swords.
- Haha, remember me. - Okay.
- Good job. Nevis. - I helped you. Swing!
I've never seen Han Gi Beom in person.
Doppelganger TV Rating Notice.
Hey.
I'll be the main person.
Hello, hello.
This wasn't necessary. Goodness.
I don't like the setup.
(It's a fancy banner for Haha.)
- Goodness. - What's that?
- What's that? - It's strange.
- Haha. - Welcome.
- Hello. - What's with your outfit?
- Welcome. - What's going on?
Haha has a script.
- Are you at the center? - Are you hosting the show today?
- Are you hosting the show today? - Yes, I am.
- He's the main person. - Stand around the center.
Haha is at the center.
Let's start. Are the cameras rolling?
- Where's the clapperboard? - What do you mean by that?
- Where's the clapperboard? - He looks amazing.
- Are the cameras on? - Is the sound okay?
- Audience, please get ready. - Where's the audience?
Please give us a round of applause.
(The audience claps.)
Here we go. Members.
Talk about what's going on these days.
(Talk about what's going on these days.)
- That's so unnatural. - It should be natural.
- What's this? - Jae Seok does it naturally.
- How did he do it? - This is frustrating.
- What do you mean? - Fix their outfits, please.
Fix their outfits, please.
- How about yours? - Let's go.
(He's so unnatural.)
- What's this? - What's going on?
Jae Seok, you run the show.
- This is the worst opening ever. - This is how it is.
- I have my own style. - It's horrible.
(Will things be okay today?)
What are we doing today?
Before we start the show,
- I'll introduce a beautiful host. - Really?
(I'll introduce a beautiful host who will join me today.)
- Today... - There were beautiful ones before.
That's right.
- She has quite a lot of experience. - Really?
Yes. She looks great in dresses.
(She looks great in dresses.)
- "In dresses"? - Her smiling face...
(Does he mean...)
Her smiling face is very lovely.
No way.
(Laughing)
That can't be.
I saw her not long ago.
I saw someone going up the stairs. Is it her?
- Did you see her clearly? - Yes.
She's full of positive energy.
She's cheerful.
She's the most beautiful woman. Here's today's host.
- "The most beautiful woman"? - "The most beautiful woman"?
Please come out!
(Who is the most beautiful host in the world?)
(Haha's mother, Ok Jeong, is here.)
- It's her. - I'm her fan.
(She wants to be known for a successful show.)
(Ok Jeong's entertaining skills are limitless.)
(His mother is adorable.)
My goodness.
(Her embarrassed son can't make eye contact.)
Hello, ma'am.
- How have you been? - I saw you a minute ago.
- Hello, Kwang Soo. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello, Seok Jin.
Let's greet later.
- Okay. - Oh, my.
- It's been a while. - "Let's greet later."
But we just greeted.
- We just greeted. - Seok Jin.
Ok Jeong said to Seok Jin,
"Let's greet later."
It seems like...
Ok Jeong feels a bit uncomfortable around you.
- Why? - I don't.
- No problem. - Seok Jin is a bit old.
Are we around the same age?
No.
(They're 20 years apart, but they have the same passion.)
- We're not. - She went too far.
- Nice to see you. - You're today's host.
(The mother and son will host the rating notice episode.)
- That's right. - Let's give her a big hand.
- Look at that. - There are even microphones.
"MC Haha".
(Special hosts need special microphones.)
It's like on a music show.
- Oh, my. - They look like music show hosts.
I'm so honored.
You're today's host.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello. I'm your beautiful host,
Kim Ok Jeong. Nice to see you all.
I wish you the best of luck.
By the way, Ok Jeong...
- enjoys being on TV very much. - She loves it.
She does.
I'm an ambitious woman.
(Haha's mom is ambitious.)
- Oh, my. - She's so jealous...
of the moms on "Mom's Diary".
"I should be one of them."
- "I should be right there." - That's right.
Anyone could tell right away that...
- you two are family. - Exactly.
- They look alike, right? - They really do.
Haha takes after me which is a good thing.
That's why he's so funny.
Is your husband...
Is your husband not as funny?
Not quite.
(He is not quite as funny.)
(I should be credited for Haha's wit.)
She's so good.
Today on Haha's Running Man...
for Doppelganger TV Rating Notice Special,
I invited the members' doppelgangers myself.
(Haha invited the members' doppelgangers.)
First, let's welcome Seok Jin's doppelganger.
- I think I know. - It must be Jo Woo Jong.
They look like brothers.
- They look so much alike. - I think I know.
Seok Jin's doppelganger.
Come on out!
It must be Woo Jong.
(Is it really Jo Woo Jong?)
(Seok Jin's clone is here.)
(They look alike from head to toe.)
(Seok Jin's twin brother, Jo Woo Jong)
(Amazed)
- He's even wearing the same shirt. - What is this?
They look exactly the same.
- Even the shirts are. - What is this?
(It's hard to tell them apart.)
- Nice to see you. - Hello.
- Woo Jong. - Woo Jong.
- Just the glasses... - Our glasses are different.
(Seok Jin's doppelganger, Jo Woo Jong)
- Hello. - Gosh.
I'm the young Jee Seok Jin, Jo Woo Jong.
- Hello. - Oh, my.
Even your noses look the same.
- This is incredible. - You're the same.
- They look so much alike. - Just the glasses look different.
- Do we look alike? - One of them is supposed to die.
(Are they real doppelgangers?)
- Well... - One of them should die.
- If doppelgangers meet... - Our glasses look different.
Our next guest is...
- Is that it? - Jae Seok's doppelganger.
Me?
There are many people who look like him.
- Including Bum Kyun... - There are many.
- Right? - Jae Seok's doppelganger,
please come out!
(Jae Seok's doppelganger, please come out!)
Seo Ji Suk!
Ji Suk.
(They look alike when they smile.)
There is a subtle resemblance.
Ji Suk looks a lot like me.
- He looks a lot better. - No.
- This doesn't count. - He looks like me.
Ji Suk looks a lot better.
Try Jae Seok's glasses on.
- These are prescription glasses. - Just for a moment.
I look pretty good without glasses.
1, 2, 3.
(Can the glasses turn the handsome actor into Jae Seok?)
They look alike.
(He's turned into a grasshopper.)
- They look alike. - Jae Seok!
- They do look alike. - Yes.
You look like me.
- They look alike. - They do.
- They do. - Jae Seok!
What is this?
- It gave me goosebumps. - You look like me.
That's how Jae Seok looks in his best condition.
Ji Suk's face is...
- the patted-down version of mine. - It's patted down.
That's why he looks better.
If you hit Ji Suk on the back of the head, he becomes Jae Seok.
(If you hit Ji Suk on the back of the head, he becomes Jae Seok.)
- What? - That's right.
- If his mouth pops out... - If his mouth pops out...
Jae Seok must have been hit on the back of the head.
You guys are mean.
Our next guest is...
- Jong Kook's doppelganger. - Me?
Is Pak Se Ri here?
- I'm curious. - Me too.
(Curious and excited)
No. I don't think so.
From the small eyes and the broad shoulders to the voice...
- You guys are like twins. - Really?
Jong Kook's doppelganger, please come out!
(Jong Kook's doppelganger, please come out!)
(K.Will)
K.Will.
(They look alike!)
Doesn't he look more like Dae Sung?
He looks more like Dae Sung.
You know what? Dae Sung,
K.Will, and Jong Kook all look the same.
(Jong Kook's doppelganger, K.Will)
It never occurred to me, but you do look alike.
- There is a resemblance. - Yes.
I look better.
That's just what you think.
(They even have similar characters.)
- He's very straightforward. - You're dressed in all black.
(You're dressed in all black.)
I wanted to match Jong Kook's outfit. This is my first appearance.
- Really? - Yes.
- We should be nice to him. - I wanted to be on this show,
but this is not how I imagined it to be.
(As Jong Kook's doppelganger?)
Dae Sung is supposed to be here,
- but he's in the military. - You're his substitute.
- I know. - He knows.
But I don't want to do this.
This is so fun.
- K.Will was my ideal man in 2013. - There is a resemblance.
(K.Will was So Min's ideal guy back in 2013.)
Gosh.
- I can't believe So Min. - Why?
- Again? - K.Will was her ideal guy in 2013.
- That's right. - Stop it.
- I know. - Back in 2013.
She was my fan for a long time.
- Really? - Yes.
She even asked for my autograph in the waiting room.
You remember that?
I didn't have many fans.
(Back in 2013, K.Will didn't have many fans.)
But So Min is so popular these days.
- I know, right? - Then she moved onto...
Gong Yoo right away.
Now, it's Jung Hae In.
She's changed.
K.Will, it's so obvious that you're trying to look like Kang Daniel.
It's usually not that obvious.
- Hey... - It's just so obvious.
- Stop it. - He looks like Daniel.
- Stop it. - Can I borrow your glasses?
- Try these on. - Will he look like someone?
- Why? - Daniel wears glasses like these.
(Daniel sometimes wears glasses like these.)
No, right?
(Amazed)
K.Will.
(Oh, it's K.Will.)
(You just look like yourself.)
- I mean... - That was honest.
And these glasses are a bit too small for K.Will.
They got stuck.
- The legs were pulled apart. - They left red marks on your face.
He's covering his face with his hair.
Our next guest is Ji Hyo's doppelganger.
- I think I know. - It's so easy.
- We know. - No one else looks more like her.
He'd look exactly like Ji Hyo with a wig on.
- Absolutely. - He's the male Song Ji Hyo.
- Come on out! - Come on out!
(I'm Ji Hyo's little brother, Seong Moon.)
(The actor looks just like his sister.)
You should hit your sister.
(They both have mischievous personalities.)
It looked like you were kicking a soccer ball.
They look exactly the same.
They look alike.
- They look exactly alike. - They're twins.
(The sister is shy.)
Hello.
They both have big foreheads.
They look the same when they smile.
Try smiling. You look exactly alike.
(Ji Hyo's doppelganger, Cheon Seong Moon)
Our next guest is...
- Se Chan's doppelganger. - Mine?
There are not many people who look like me.
Se Chan looks like Kim Kap Soo.
It'd be hilarious if Han Mu is here.
- Don't be surprised. - Kim Kap Soo.
- It's an actor. - Really?
Is Kap Soo here?
- Is he here? - It is indeed an actor.
Who is it?
(What?)
No way.
(Everyone is surprised by Se Chan's doppelganger.)
- Jong Hyuk? - Jong Hyuk?
(Lee Jong Hyuk?)
Jong Hyuk doesn't look like Se Chan.
This doesn't make sense.
He doesn't look like me.
Jong Hyuk, you don't look like Se Chan.
(Even Se Chan is not convinced.)
(Se Chan's supposed doppelganger, Lee Jong Hyuk)
- What happened? - Let me explain.
I was discussing with Haha.
No one wanted to appear as Se Chan's doppelganger.
What about Jong Hyuk?
- He looks angry. - I just had some free time.
(Nonchalant)
(He is so honest. He's given up on the theme.)
He was just randomly invited.
Next, let's meet Kwang Soo's doppelganger.
I've really wanted to meet him.
Is he here?
I put in so much effort. I did.
We've been talking about him for five years.
My goodness.
We've been...
You're starting to look a lot like Han Gi Beom.
(Just the mention of his name cracked everyone up.)
(Everyone except Kwang Soo believes the two are doppelgangers.)
Finally.
- Yes. - He's finally here.
I'm so nervous. What should I do?
Kwang Soo's doppelganger,
please come out!
(They are in awe...)
(and moved by his appearance.)
(No way. My legs are going weak now.)
(Hello?)
(You wanted to see me, didn't you?)
This is amazing.
(His appearance has the same effect of a dunk.)
- No way. He really came! Seriously! - My gosh, Gi Beom.
- My gosh. - It's nice to meet you.
No way.
- Hello. - It's nice to meet you.
- Does someone resemble me? - Seriously.
I can't believe this.
Hey, this is amazing.
Hey, lift your head up.
(He quickly gets a pen.)
What are you doing?
Hey, he can't wash that off.
They're the same.
- Do you really think we look alike? - Oh, no. He can't wash it off.
You two resemble each other. You two look really alike.
Kwang Soo.
- He looks like your father. - I'm so embarrassed.
- I'm so embarrassed. - You're the spitting image of him.
- Seriously. - I mean it.
- I wanted to see both of them. - I...
I didn't look at them yet,
but it'd drive me crazy if I glanced over.
Kwang Soo.
Now, I understand how you feel.
To be honest,
people pointed out the resemblance ever since elementary school.
(This is a historical day his dream of 20 years comes true.)
- I heard it ever since I was a kid. - My gosh, Kwang Soo will...
- look like him when he gets old. - Exactly.
- Let me introduce the last guest. - But who resembles So Min?
- But who resembles So Min? - So Min...
- I have many faces. - Who is it?
- She resembles Son Yeo Eun. - Son Yeo Eun.
She looks like Jung Yu Mi too.
- Is Yu Mi joining us today? - Really?
Jung Yu Mi. It's Yu Mi.
(I think it's Yu Mi.)
(When she smiles, she resembles So Min. Is she joining us today?)
Who is it?
(So Min's lookalike makes them laugh right away.)
It's Han Min Gwan. It's Min Gwan.
(Unbelievable. Who is that? Where is Yu Mi?)
- I see the resemblance. - He does resemble her. He does.
(The guests are invited according to the theme.)
- They do resemble each other. - They do look alike.
- I see the resemblance. - He does resemble her.
- Kwang Soo. - Hello.
- They do look alike. - My gosh.
(So Min's lookalike, Han Min Gwan)
- What is it? - It's been five years since...
I had tried to stay away from him.
I was the female version of Min Gwan.
- We got you today. - You two look alike.
- Why do they say you resemble him? - Well, the project I was on...
When I was starring in a drama, people wrote...
that I resembled Min Gwan online.
That's why for the related keywords, his name and my name...
- were paired together. - I see.
Ever since then, my nickname became Prince Aurora.
(Ever since then, my nickname became Prince Aurora.)
- People started calling me that. - Not Princess Aurora?
- It wasn't Princess Aurora? - No.
- Prince Aurora. - It's because...
back then, I weighed about 10kg less than I weigh now.
Since I was slimmer, I resembled him even more.
It's been a while since we had both Prince and Princess Aurora with us.
- They meet today. - Right.
- I see. But by the way, Jong Hyuk. - Yes?
You don't resemble him that much, but you're having fun today.
(As he blocks out the sun, he watches the show of lookalikes.)
- Jong Hyuk, enjoy yourself. - He's smiling.
All right, everyone.
- Be yourself during the interview. - Just be yourself.
He's the best at interviewing people about their current lives.
- Right. - To Jae Seok,
- I'll interview them? - I'll pass on the script.
And we'll rest for a bit.
(It was so hard.)
I can't do this.
- I'll take over? - Yes.
- This was Haha... - Yes, we will...
And Ok Jeong.
(They wrap up hurriedly.)
- I'll take over for a moment. - Okay, okay.
- Let's catch up for a while. - Should I stay here with you?
- First up is Woo Jong. - Yes.
- You're joining us today. - Yes.
Didn't people often tell you that you resembled Seok Jin?
- I heard that ever since my debut. - Okay.
- Whom else do you resemble? - Actually,
the improved version would be Park Shin Yang.
- I see the resemblance. - My gosh.
- You can do his impression. - Park Shin Yang.
- He can mimic his voice. - Yes, he can do that.
- Can you do that for us? - Park Shin Yang...
"I don't know how to act on this kind of a show."
"I don't know what I should do."
"I'm very nervous."
"Baby, I'll buy you ice cream, so hang out with me."
- This is it. - He does sound like Shin Yang.
- He sounds just like Shin Yang. - I'm sure Seok Jin can do this too.
- Try it. - No, I can't do that.
- You look like him. You can do it. - Try it. You can do it.
"Baby."
"I'm on this show today."
"I'm nervous that Woo Jong is joining us today."
Doesn't he just sound like an old man?
He sounds like an old lady.
- This was my first time. - "Hey."
- Hold on. Wait a second. - "Hey, the pot's boiling."
- Next up is Ji Suk. - Okay, okay.
You joined us today as my lookalike,
- but you don't seem to agree. - Why not?
Then why did you agree to join us?
- Pardon? - Why did you agree to come today?
I wanted to star on Running Man.
You had an agenda. You had an ulterior motive.
To be honest, yes.
To be honest, I didn't want to star for this special.
To clarify,
- K.Will feels the same way, right? - Right.
- Right now... - This can't be right.
Jong Hyuk feels the same way too.
I was invited to come. When I saw Gi Beom in the waiting room,
I thought, "This cannot be happening."
And his name sounds similar too.
- His name has Suk. I'm Yu Jae Seok. - Right.
- Seo Ji Suk. - Seo Ji Suk.
- I see. - What does Suk mean in your name?
- That's not my real name. - It's not?
What?
Why do you sound disappointed?
- Why does that disappoint you? - That's not your real name?
Haha isn't my real name either.
I know. Yours is Ha Dong Hoon.
- Ma'am. - Yes?
- Since we're on the subject... - Okay.
- Haha came up with his stage name. - Right.
- He chose it on his own. - Didn't that disappoint you?
No, it didn't disappoint me.
What upsets me the most is...
when my mom calls me Haha in crowded places.
(It's the other way around.)
"Haha".
That's really disappointing.
- I just call his stage name. - I see.
And as for her daughter-in-law,
"Byul". "Byul".
(She's the mother of celebrities.)
- It drives me crazy. - Next up are...
- K.Will and Jong Kook. - All right.
These two do look alike,
- but both are great singers. - I agree.
- They are great singers. - Right.
And both of them can sing "She's Gone" really well.
- "She's Gone"? - Yes, they are great.
- This is news to me. - I see.
Come here.
(I see. I was wrong.)
- Come here. - Did you not research?
- I only said one thing. - What do you know about me?
You're just good at fighting.
(You're just good at fighting.)
You're good at that.
- Go back to your spot. - Yes, sir.
(Since you know something, I'll let you slide.)
We don't need to explain the next guest. It's Seong Moon.
- The resemblance is uncanny. - The resemblance is striking.
Whenever Seong Moon stars on our show,
you always expose one thing about Ji Hyo.
Is there anything you'd like to add onto the list?
Since we're family, she's really comfortable around me.
When she uses the bathroom, she doesn't close...
She leaves the door open. Right?
They're family. That's understandable.
Ji Hyo, but still... That's...
- Shouldn't you close the door? - No, that's not it.
(I didn't know you'd share that.)
Come on. Tell them the truth.
Seong Moon, you're too mean. How could you share that?
- No, I was watching TV. - Okay.
- I had to use the bathroom. - So?
- But I was curious about the show. - Okay.
I walked back like this and left the door open.
And I came back out after that.
- That's why you didn't close it? - Ask So Min...
- Ask So Min how other siblings are. - That's why you didn't close it?
To be honest, I also...
- So Min, don't you do that too? - Yes, even if my brother is there.
- Exactly. - Seriously?
- Siblings are like that? No way. - Brothers and sisters...
When my brother goes to get his underwear after taking a shower,
he'd run across the room quickly.
He'd only cover his front. I'd see his bottom.
(Her description is very detailed with her hand gestures.)
Don't do the hand gestures. Stop using your hands.
My gosh, they are so free.
- No, they're not. - Hey, just get a pot for peeing.
(Brothers and sisters can be more at ease than same-gender siblings.)
- But... - Wait, to Se Chan...
To be honest, I feel so sorry.
Jong Hyuk and I don't look alike at all.
- We'll find something. - All right.
- What's your blood type? - Yes, blood type.
- 1, 2, 3. B. - A.
- Darn it. - Come on.
- B. - A.
(Even their blood types aren't the same.)
Darn it.
Should we check the blood types?
1, 2, 3.
- A. - A.
(Sighing)
- Even their blood type is the same. - Kwang Soo is more dejected now.
Welcome to Haha Land. This is the Doppelganger Race.
Since I'm a fashion enthusiast,
I prepared a race where you will obtain your outfits.
- Is that so? - It's a race.
- This is very important. - Tell us about the rules.
Members of Running Man and the guests...
will pair up to form a team.
They will buy an outfit with R Coins they earned throughout the show.
They will film the TV rating notice in that outfit.
All right. I will present you the outfits you will wear today.
- I bet they will look weird. - I'm curious.
- The outfits. - I bet they look weird.
(What are the outfits that will determine their looks for 4 weeks?)
- I knew it. I saw this coming. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - Look at that.
(What are those outfits?)
- We have to do the makeup too. - You'll do the makeup for Kaonashi.
(A fancy suit, Boy Frog, and Sailor Moon)
- I'd rather wear Kaonashi's outfit. - My gosh.
My gosh, Toshio is on the list too.
These are the outfits we'll wear for the TV rating notice.
We don't need a guest for Kaonashi, do we?
Their face might not be shown even if they came all the way here.
I knew this would happen.
- My gosh. - See?
- My gosh. - I want to wear the suit.
For the highest price,
the particular episode will be titled under the buyer's name.
- It won't be Haha? - We have a shot?
That's why you must try hard to acquire the money.
And if you don't have enough money to buy the outfit,
we'll provide elastic suits that...
- cover the whole body for free. - Elastic suits?
We'll paint your faces in the same color as the suit.
- I'm in trouble. - It'll be the same color.
That's the worst.
All right. After you change into your team uniforms,
we'll begin the race.
I bet people will be fighting over the outfits in the 10 R range.
First, we'll begin Money Signal so you can earn your Seed Money.
(Money Signal)
(We have to win a lot of money.)
What?
(Let's try to stay away from the makeup.)
Every couple will choose Signal Three Random cards randomly.
You will try to complete the mission stage by stage.
Every time you complete the mission, you will get 20 R...
(What? His pronunciation is a bit weird.)
- How can you say that? - My mother is here.
How can you say that?
- My mother is here. - It's okay. This is a variety show.
- Please be careful. - Say "20 seeds".
- 20 seeds. - Every step you pass,
you'll gain 20, 40, and 100 seeds.
You lose the chance to play if you fail.
- Do you understand? - We must win no matter what.
There are four types of games.
One is Song Ji Hyo Game.
Two members say a syllable each based on a given syllable.
For example, "make a bowl".
Another game is Say It in Reverse
When "Australia" is given, you say "Ailartsua".
It isn't easy today.
- Why is it so difficult? - That's a hard game.
Third is Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
If I say 3, you must say "giant chestnut bread" 3 times.
Fourth is Lee Kwang Soo Game.
When a word is given,
if you say the same syllable as your partner, you lose.
- We have an advantage. - That's right.
- We all have an advantage. - Woo Jong may be good too.
He's an announcer.
Which team would like to start first?
- How about Seong Moon and Ji Hyo? - Let's start.
For Lee Kwang Soo Game, the word is jjamppong.
Jjamppong. In 3, 2, 1.
(He should not say the same syllable.)
- Jjam. - Jjam.
(She hits me.)
- What's wrong with losing? - Aren't you on the same team?
- They're doppelgangers. - She hit him.
(Ji Hyo hits him well, and Seong Moon has a short temper.)
What's going on?
Don't hit him. It's difficult.
She said not to hit him.
(They fail the first step.)
You should speak your mind.
Unlike the sweet woman in "Something in the Rain",
- not all women are sweet. - She isn't warm and generous.
- Those only exists in dramas. - Seong Moon.
The female character is Son Ye Jin.
What type of woman is Ji Hyo?
(How does he think of Ji Hyo?)
She makes good sounds.
- She makes good sounds? - Yes.
What kind of sounds?
"She makes good sounds"?
(What does he mean?)
I mean in the bathroom.
(It's what he mentioned earlier.)
- Come on. - Hey.
You can't say that in public.
- She must make sounds. - Ji Hyo.
She's someone who makes good sounds.
That's hilarious.
Next up are K.Will and Jong Kook.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Okay. - Step one.
It's Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
Say "Symbols of Longevity" five times. Start.
Symbols of Longevity, Symbols of Longevity, Symbols of Longevity...
(They pass Step 1.)
That's easy.
This is Song Ji Hyo Game. C.
- Cro. - Crow.
It's Say It in Reverse. "Red dragonfly".
(The word is red dragonfly.)
Ylf... Goodness.
(Wrong)
They passed two steps.
- You still passed two times. - That was smart.
Their word was crow.
- You passed step two. - That was great.
(They win 40 R.)
"Symbols of Longevity" was easy.
That was too easy.
- Symbols of Longevity... - That's so easy.
It was too easy.
We aren't allowed to say "Symbols of Longevity" on TV.
- Why not? - No way.
- It sounds offensive. - What do you mean?
It's not allowed.
Shall I show you something that isn't allowed on TV?
(Is this how you'll play?)
Hit him.
- You should get him. - The screen can be blurred.
My goodness.
(I'll keep to myself.)
- Goodness. - It's your turn, ma'am.
You must make it, ma'am.
- Please, Mom. - It's Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
Say "counsel in charge" five times. Start.
(The word is "counsel in charge".)
Giant chestnut bread.
(She has no idea.)
(She says giant chestnut bread instead of "counsel in charge".)
- Haha. - Wait.
Don't make fun of my mom!
- That's right. - Don't.
- We aren't making fun of her. - She was so cute.
- It was because she was cute. - We weren't making fun.
- Don't make fun of her. - We weren't.
- Don't make fun of her. - We weren't making fun of her.
That's not what we meant.
- We weren't making fun of her. - Wait.
- We weren't. - Let me take a look.
- No. - Please don't do this.
- I can't look? - No.
It's over.
- This is hilarious. - Goodness.
Give us a chance to play Song Ji Hyo Game.
- Song Ji Hyo Game? - It's already over.
How do you play it?
- It's when they said, "crow". - That one?
- Let's start again. - Here we go.
This is Song Ji Hyo Game.
Spring.
Butterfly.
(It's incorrect.)
(She says butterfly instead of one syllable.)
Was it wrong? What was it?
- Say 1 syllable. - Just 1?
(Was it just one syllable?)
It's not easy.
- Say only one syllable. - This is impossible.
It won't work, Haha.
- Don't laugh! - She's so cute.
- Look at Kwang Soo. - You're cute.
- "Spring butterfly" is a good word. - I know.
We're laughing out of happiness.
She's so lovely.
It's okay. This is funnier.
It's our turn. Let's go, Ji Suk.
It's Say It in Reverse. The word is "omurice".
(The word is "omurice".)
Iricemo.
(Impressed)
- Is that right? - No.
(That's the wrong answer.)
(They're impressed by themselves.)
- That's wrong. - It's incorrect.
(Ji Suk's answer is wrong.)
Did you see that?
- He's a crook. - He's a crook.
- He was so confident. - You're a crook.
I thought he was right.
- They're the same. - Unbelievable.
- They almost tricked us. - They're similar.
- They're both crooks. - They were almost believable.
It's considered correct if you answer with confidence.
- How could you? - Confidence is important.
They almost tricked us.
When I applauded, he was quite flustered.
- Show that you're an announcer. - What?
- Who will start? - Woo Jong will start.
It's Lee Kwang Soo Game. The word is bag.
It's either ba or ag. In 3, 2, 1.
- Ba. - Ba.
(They say the same syllable.)
Wasn't I right?
(I said the same syllable.)
- You were wrong. - They should be different.
- Didn't I get it right? - You said the same syllabus.
Why is he on my team?
- He doesn't understand rules too. - They're similar.
- They're similar that way. - Right.
- He can't understand like me. - It was the sound.
As time passes by,
it becomes clear which teams are terrible.
(It becomes more obvious.)
That's strange.
It already started.
Next are Min Gwan and So Min.
- They're strangely similar. - Let's start.
(Why is he standing behind them?)
He's similar to Kwang Soo in his behavior.
(He acts like a trickster similar to Kwang Soo.)
What are you doing?
(Why are you over there?)
- He wants to practice. - I wanted to practice.
- He's just like Kwang Soo. - He's innocent.
- No. - Seriously.
They're similar.
(Gi Beom simply wants to practice.)
- It's because he's innocent. - He's similar to you.
(He wanted to practice.)
- I wanted to practice. - The way he acts...
I felt a breeze above my head.
- It's to practice. - He isn't bothering them.
- He's innocent. - I just want to practice.
They're somewhat similar.
Min Gwan will start first.
It's Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
Say "double muntin" five times. Start.
Double muntin, double muntin...
Come on.
(He fails to pronounce the word.)
My tongue is short.
- It's both of your faults. - My tongue is short.
It's because my tongue is short.
(So Min's team fails.)
That's hilarious.
(She gets angry.)
- My tongue is short. - So Min.
- You'll get a bodysuit. - He's so annoying.
Let's play Pirate Roulette Game.
- So Min will wear a bodysuit. - I'll do better.
- Are we the last team? - Yes.
He looks nervous.
All right.
First is Song Ji Hyo Game. Yang.
(The given syllable is yang.)
You can do it.
(Please make a word like cabbage.)
Gangster.
(Gangster)
(He says both syllables.)
"Gangster"?
I said, "gangster".
- No, you must say one syllable. - It's one syllable.
He said, "gangster". He's just like Kwang Soo.
- He's just like Kwang Soo. - He's Lee Kwang Soo!
He made the same mistake as Haha's mother.
- He did the same. - Now, I understand.
I understand now.
Why did you say that word?
- He's just like you. - No.
Their similar personalities become more obvious.
- Right. - It's becoming obvious.
He even thinks like Kwang Soo.
We gave you a chance to earn Seed Money.
- However, you didn't win any. - Let us play more.
- Give us one more chance. - Give us a chance.
- Play Giant Chestnut Bread Game. - How about Lee Kwang Soo Game?
- Play Giant Chestnut Bread Game. - Let's play Lee Kwang Soo Game.
- Lee Kwang Soo Game. - Let's keep it simple.
Lee Kwang Soo Game isn't fun.
(He's very opposed to it.)
Did you have to say that?
He selected the game, so don't say that.
- Play Giant Chestnut Bread Game. - Is that it?
Yes.
- My tongue is too short. - It's difficult.
- The pronunciation is hard. - I like that game.
Let's play Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
Say "Cheol Soo's desk" five times. Start.
Cheol Soo's desk, Cheol Soo's desk, Cheol Soo's desk, Cheol Soo's desk.
- Okay. - You mispronounced it.
(He fails.)
- He said "Cheol Shoo". - "Cheol Shoo".
- "Cheol Shoo". It's wrong. - He mispronounced the desk.
Is that how you'll play? Fine, just wait and see.
- Is that how you'll play? - It's wrong.
- Okay, bring it on. - Good job, Se Chan.
- It's okay, you did well. - It's Seong Moon's turn.
It's Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
Say "Doctor of law" five times. Start.
Doctor of law, doctor of law, doctor of law, doctor of law...
(It's a success.)
We got it.
"Cloud drawing".
Cloud drawing, cloud drawing, cloud drawing, cloud drawing.
- That's too easy. - It was...
- too easy for them. - He's good.
That team is good at everything.
- This is Giant Chestnut Bread Game. - It's hard.
The word is "red bean porridge".
Red bean porridge, red bean porridge, red bean porridge...
(The word is "red bean porridge".)
It's correct.
(Are you not going to give her a pass?)
- This is wrong. - What's going on?
She mispronounced it.
Parents' Day is coming up.
(How dare you say that she's wrong?)
Have you ever given her a present?
- 20 seeds are worthless outside. - Stop it.
- I'm sorry, Haha. - Stop it.
- Be good to parents. - It's a rule.
It's just a rule.
- Ma'am. - My belly button hurts.
(She finds it funny.)
Why does your belly button hurt?
(The producer says that it's wrong.)
- Does your belly button hurt? - It's so funny.
Here we go. Say, "counsel in charge" five times.
Counsel in charge, counsel in charge, counsel in charge...
Wrong!
Why?
Anyone could do that.
"Counsel in charge, counsel in charge, counsel in charge..."
"Counsel in charge..." Wrong.
"Probability distribution", start.
Probability distribution, probability distribution,
probability distribution, probability distribution...
Stop distracting him.
- It's even hard for an announcer. - It's even hard for an announcer.
- I'm not confident about this. - You can do this.
Giant Chestnut Bread Game. Say the word five times.
"Single layer..."
Hold on.
- He can't even say it himself. - He can't do it.
How are we going to do that?
(The members are furious.)
You can't even say it once.
We'll just give up.
It's too hard.
I'll give you an easy one then. Giant Chestnut Bread Game.
Say, "kim satgat satgat", five times.
Kim satgat satgat, kim satgat satgat...
That was too easy.
- That was too easy. - He said, "kim satga satga".
- He said, "satga". - "Satga" is not okay.
- You win 20 seeds. - Okay.
(He wins 20 seeds.)
I'm looking forward.
- He's been practicing all along. - I know.
(While the other teams were playing...)
(Counsel in charge...)
(Antibacterial effect...)
(Gi Beom never stopped practicing.)
Giant Chestnut Bread Game. Say the word five times.
"Choi Champan's house", start.
(Just do as you've been practicing.)
Choi Champan's house, Choi Champan's house...
(Choi Champan's house, Choi Champan's house...)
(Heavy rain watch)
Choi Champan's house...
(It's not over yet!)
He was spitting.
He got too worked up.
"Choi Champan's house..."
(Gi Beom's spitting makes everyone laugh.)
This is so funny.
It was difficult.
- It was difficult. - It was.
I like you so much.
The younger brother is never the equal of the older.
Kwang Soo is overshadowed by Gi Beom today.
You guys seem to be struggling at this.
Give another chance to the teams with no seeds.
Yes, please.
- Teams with no seeds... - Yes.
- No seeds... - How many teams are they?
Haha's, Jae Seok's, Seok Jin's, and Kwang Soo's.
I'll give another chance to one member of each team.
- Let's play Lee Kwang Soo Game. - Lee Kwang Soo Game?
- We'll start from Woo Jong. - Okay.
"Sparrow". Say either "spar" or "row".
- 1, 2, 3. - "Spar".
It's harder than I expected.
- We failed last time too. - You said the same one again.
"Big Bang". Say either "big" or "bang". 1, 2, 3.
- Bang. - Bang.
- Didn't you say, "big"? - No. He said, "bang".
- "Basketball". - "Basketball".
Say either "basket" or "ball". 1, 2, 3.
- Basket. - Ball.
Yes!
He sounded so confident.
He sure is a former basketball player.
- My goodness. - Gi Beom sounded so confident.
We'll do "ambition".
Okay. Say either "am" or "bition".
- 1, 2, 3. Am. - Bition.
There you go.
(She said it after the producer.)
(There clearly was an interval.)
I want to try "vision".
(You said it after hearing what the producer said.)
(My mom is the best, right?)
Let me try "vision".
- This is so funny. - No way.
- One more time. - Say the word he gives you.
Let's try "vision".
You have to say it at the same time with him.
- "Vision". - Say either "vi" or "sion".
"Vision". 1, 2, 3.
- Vi. - Sion.
(They succeed by a narrow margin.)
That's a relief.
What do you think?
- It counts. - I was so nervous.
- You won 20 seeds. - I was scared.
(R Coin Distribution)
The game will start soon.
We'll have 2 teams of 4.
Each team will share all the R coins within the team.
(Each team will share the R coins.)
- That's a relief. - The worst would be...
to become a team with Woo Jong and Seok Jin.
We have nothing.
Each team will then...
distribute the coins among four bags.
The winning team...
can choose one member on the other team...
and take the coins in the member's bag.
(The winning team can take the other team's coins.)
That might make a huge difference.
Let's decide the teams by drawing spoons.
You never know.
It'd be best to become a team with Jong Kook.
Right. The more coins, the better.
- Yes, we have the most coins. - We should...
- Here he comes. - Draw one.
You draw one.
We should avoid...
We should avoid teams that are broke.
- Don't say that. - What's wrong?
Is it a bad thing to say?
- Let's see Se Chan's spoon. - Okay. Jong Hyuk.
1, 2, 3.
- It's green. - Green. Okay.
Ours is green.
(Jong Kook and K.Will have a green spoon.)
Okay! Jong Kook!
I love him when this happens.
(I love him when this happens.)
- Come here. - I'm just happy.
- When do you not like me? - I always like you.
I like you especially a lot today.
- I did a good job. - You did.
(R Coin Distribution)
(Green, Yellow, Blue, Red)
Take your bags...
and write down the amount of coins each bag will have.
- Okay. - Within the total amount.
- We write it down? - Yes.
The other team can take away that much amount.
- Distribute the coins well. - Okay.
(The winning team can take away money from one bag.)
- What are we going to do? - Are we putting all coins in one?
- Or are we distributing them? - Should we distribute them?
Let's put a lot in one and nothing in another.
What about 30 and 10?
- Good. - 30 and 10?
- 30 and 10. - 30 and 10.
- 80 in one bag? - That might be better.
80 in one bag?
- Yes. - Yes.
But in whose bag?
Should we decide randomly?
- Let's put all in one. - That'd be better.
Let's do that.
- In which bag? - Rock-paper-scissors?
Okay.
- 20 R in the winner's bag. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Put everything in your bag.
(They put 20 in Woo Jong's bag.)
- Write it down. - Hold on.
The 20 belongs to us.
That's right. I completely forgot.
Think about it. It belongs to us.
We're a team.
- Rock-paper-scissors... - Whose idea was it?
What do you think about this?
I'm the one who won it.
(I'm the one who won it.)
Hold on. Aren't we a team?
We won it together.
That's right. That's right.
(They're done distributing the money.)
(With the members having become close, the first round starts.)
What's that?
(They haven't seen hop balls in a while.)
A banana?
(What game are they going to play?)
- Everyone. - Yes.
Haha Land TV Rating Notice Race. Round One.
Let's start the national survey quiz.
(National Survey Quiz)
Survey?
We surveyed 500 people in their 20s to 40s.
After hearing the question,
you'll move to the banana on the hop ball.
Take a bite of the banana, and you'll get to say your answer.
(The winning team will receive 30 R.)
We have to eat the banana?
Ji Seok, you and I should do this.
(Each team's ace steps up.)
We have to take our shoes off?
It's okay to cheat and attack others.
You can do anything.
Don't be surprised if someone pushes you.
Stay in your place. They'll try to push you away.
(Ji Seok seems relaxed.)
How...
- What happened? - Hey.
(He suddenly falls.)
We haven't even started yet.
- What are you doing? - Is this slapstick?
You said you were good at sports.
- What are you doing? - He's clumsy.
- Can we change the player? - Yes.
(Players for Round 1)
(Haha, Ji Suk, Gi Beom, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, So Min)
I'm next to Jong Kook. What should I do?
- This is... - I'm in trouble.
- Gi Beom, good luck. - Thanks.
Haha, good luck.
Call me Dong Hoon.
Dong Hoon, good luck. David, good luck.
- David. - David.
- I gave him that name. - You did?
- You call him David? - Yes. David is warm-hearted.
- David. - David.
I called him David when he was little.
When, Mom?
You never called me David once.
(You never called me David once.)
- David is warm-hearted. - David.
Isn't it nice?
(David is ready.)
You bought an expensive present for your boyfriend or girlfriend,
but your parents thought it was for them...
and bragged to everyone.
- Number one, you take it back. - That's hard.
Number two, you let your parents keep it.
- What would people have answered? - Parents should keep it.
Parents should keep it.
But we need to think about what most people...
- would have answered. Okay, Ji Suk? - Yes.
- Okay, Haha? - Yes.
Ready.
(The first round starts.)
(Jong Kook charges ahead while making weird sounds.)
(Shouting)
- Good! - Go!
Ji Suk.
My goodness.
(Jong Kook is highly likely to win.)
No. This is not okay.
(Ji Hyo catches up.)
(From the outermost lane, Ji Hyo gets to the banana first.)
(Proud)
(She has to take a bite of the banana.)
(From the outermost lane, Ji Hyo gets to the banana first.)
(Proud)
(She has to take a bite of the banana.)
(Punching)
(Se Chan blocks her.)
She didn't eat it.
(Kwang Soo opens his mouth.)
Kwang Soo.
(While they fight, the hyena Kwang Soo steals the banana.)
- What was that? - Oh, my.
I blocked Ji Hyo.
I had the banana here.
I brought it up to my mouth. Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo. - My gosh.
(Kwang Soo gets a chance to answer the question.)
I blocked her, and Kwang Soo came.
- What is the answer, Kwang Soo? - She didn't eat it.
Just give it to my parents.
Wrong.
- You have to get it back. - Wrong.
- It's expensive. - It's Parents' Day soon.
It's expensive.
(Kwang Soo is correct.)
Kwang Soo, you did it.
- Good job. - You did it.
She almost took a bite.
She took a longer route.
Se Chan is taking care of Ji Hyo,
not Seong Moon.
- Seong Moon. - Seong Moon.
Why do you have your arms crossed? She got her face dirty.
- It's okay. - That's realistic.
That's what real brothers and sisters do.
They're realistic.
Seong Moon, I have a question.
Ji Hyo doesn't usually talk about this.
She had boyfriends in the past, right?
- Yes. - Right?
She looks anxious. I'm just joking.
(Hold on.)
I'm just joking.
(Time out.)
- Ji Hyo. - It's not true.
(Stop it.)
(She tries to edit out the whole segment.)
(She tries to control the media since her brother is here.)
Stop it.
She looks anxious.
Jong Kook, you're not married. Did you give somebody a gift?
On birthdays...
or special days, I always write letters.
- Really? - I always do.
I write letters or cards.
Are you talking about chain letters?
Do you want one?
(This letter started in Britain and the first recipient got lucky.)
I see. May I get one?
What about you, K.Will? What have you given as gifts?
He's a lover.
I have hands to write letters.
My bank account is waiting for you.
(I have hands to write letters. My bank account is waiting for you.)
(They will fall for the money.)
He's happy about using money.
Salute.
(She salutes to K.Will's bank account.)
What will you do if So Min showed interest in you?
(What if So Min is being serious?)
Be honest. Don't joke around.
(Will K.Will say yes to her?)
To be honest, she's not my style.
(To be honest, she's not my style.)
Goodness.
Salute.
- You're not my type anymore either. - I know.
- So Min is hurt. - Salute.
(We're looking for somebody to accept So Min's salute.)
- What about you, Ms. Kim? - Okay.
It probably was a long time ago,
but do you remember what you got from Mr. Ha?
- I do. I still have them. - What are they?
There's a variety.
- She's absorbed in this. - There's a handbag and...
- She's absorbed. - Back then,
there was a handbag and more. Perfume...
and some others.
There's a variety, but you only mentioned the handbag.
(There's a variety, but you only mentioned the handbag.)
- It was the most memorable one. - What was the most recent gift?
I got some debt.
(That was the most recent one.)
That's the truth.
- Debt? - Yes, debt.
There must be a lot.
Did you get a lot?
Can we get 10 R Coins?
(We're poor.)
Let's go ahead with the next question.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
Yellow.
You have to pick between your lover and a phone for a year.
Number one, living with your phone for a year without your lover.
Number two, living with your lover without your phone for a year.
This one is tough.
It has to be a phone these days.
- It has to be your lover. - Ready.
Set...
Run. Go, Jong Hyuk. Pull yourself forward.
(This is their last chance.)
- Push yourself forward. - Good job.
(Gi Beom dashes forward.)
(Gi Beom is 205cm tall, and he charges out from the corner.)
(He advances with his long limbs.)
Gi Beom is fast. Gi Beom!
Gi Beom!
(Let's go, my hero.)
(Will Gi Beom relive the glory of his heyday?)
Gi Beom is fast. Gi Beom!
(He collapses at the very end.)
(Jae Seok takes the banana Gi Beom missed.)
(Who will take the banana?)
(Jae Seok takes it with his crunched-up face.)
What did you do?
(I ate it.)
Jae Seok, you first.
- I almost got it. - Gi Beom!
He's good.
- This... - I had some.
- Are you okay? - I almost had it.
- Jae Seok. - How many points do you have?
The banana smells like feet.
(This is a shocking report.)
(Jae Seok touched it with his hands, but it smells like feet?)
- This is a big accident. - Goodness.
How can the banana smell like feet?
- I'm serious. - Oh, gosh.
I shouldn't have had it.
- Jae Seok, get it right. - If you're wrong, you lose a point.
It has to be the phone.
For your reference, the percentages were...
55.6 percent and 44.4 percent.
- Right? - It's close.
(If you had to choose between your lover and a phone for a year?)
- It has to be the phone. - It's not the phone.
It's the first one.
I will probably choose...
Kwang Soo.
(You're Kwang Soo, right?)
What are you talking about? I'm here.
- Gosh. - I thought you were Kwang Soo.
(Gi Beom is a lookalike. Watch out.)
You can't live a day without a phone.
You can fight with your lover, but not your phone.
Still, you have a lover. You can't live a year just with your phone.
Phones are good for a short while.
I've lived a year with my phone when I didn't have a girlfriend.
(I did it.)
(I'm already doing it.)
- There's your testimony. - Look at him.
- That's true. - It's not bad.
- He says it's okay. - It's not bad.
If you put it that way, I don't know what to say.
I'm sure it's number 1, but you can choose 2.
- I choose two. - No, Jae Seok.
Two.
- Two? - That's sharp.
You think people chose to live with their lovers.
I think so?
(Jae Seok is correct.)
He was right.
(Lovers are better than phones.)
- That's right. - Really?
(Let's go, Jae Seok.)
- What was it? - That was unexpected.
I was trying to mislead him.
- He's right. - Right?
This is great.
Okay.
(This concludes the mission.)
Everybody,
Team Red and Blue are both in first place.
(They each got a question right, so they win.)
(But there's only one winner.)
We need just one team.
Do you want to do rock-paper-scissors?
(They'll do rock-paper-scissors to choose the winner.)
- Do it when he says, "scissors". - Rock-paper-scissors
(Gi Beom wins.)
- Okay. - What was that?
- Did I win? - Best out of three.
(Best out of 3.)
You didn't say that before.
- You didn't say that earlier. - It's Parents' Day.
- This is Parents' Day Special. - She wants best out of three now.
(I guess I take after my mom.)
- Best out of three. - Okay, do it.
You can't do just once.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I'm a pastor,
so the whole country is watching. I'm in trouble. I'll do something.
- Rock... - Wait.
Losing in rock-paper-scissors has nothing to do with being a pastor.
It has nothing to do with it.
- Okay. Rock-paper-scissors. - Don't lose.
Rock-paper-scissors
What's wrong?
Okay!
(She got another try, but Team Red wins.)
- Best out of three. - It was the same as before.
(They're going for Team Green who has 80 R Coins.)
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo choose to steal Jong Hyuk's bag.)
(But he has no coins.)
(They protected their 80 R Coins.)
(And the final mission followed.)
(It was Group Jump Rope Speed Quiz.)
(Team Blue showed great teamwork and can choose a bag.)
Team Blue, please make your decision.
Which bag from which team would you like to choose from?
This is driving me nuts. Who should it be?
(Team Green has 80 R Coins, Blue has 70, Red has 50, Yellow has 40.)
We only need 30 more R Coins.
We can choose any team.
Which team will be the funniest when they have no coins?
That's what we are thinking about.
What did you write, Gi Beom?
I wrote 10, 10, 10, and 20.
- 10, 10, 10, and 20? - 20 for Kwang Soo?
(20 for Kwang Soo?)
- There's not enough. - I'll be honest.
(When they were distributing Running Money)
(They gave 40 R Coins to Kwang Soo.)
40 for me, 10 for him.
- 10, 10, 10, and 20? - 20 for Kwang Soo?
Yes.
- Hey. - Hold on.
It's a trick.
Don't trust him. He's incredible.
So it's 20 for Kwang Soo?
I pick Kwang Soo.
- Wait. - That's what he said.
- Listen to me. - That's not it.
- That's what he said. - I know.
(Hello?)
He was just joking.
Think about it again.
(Let's take it easy.)
- What do you want me to do? - Just...
- give us another chance. - What did you do?
This is your last chance.
- Be honest. - You can tell the truth.
- Tell the truth. - The truth?
It's not 10, 10, and 10.
- We gave it to one person. - That's Kwang Soo.
(That's Kwang Soo.)
One more chance.
- I'll talk to him again. - Why?
- I have to explain. - I'm certain.
You can do whatever you want.
Okay.
- He's blushing. - No.
(He's blushing. It must be right.)
- I'm blushing? - You are.
(I'm blushing?)
(His face is obviously red.)
- Hold on. - He's blushing.
Don't anger him.
- He's angry now. - Hold on.
There will be an unexpected twist.
Let's go with Kwang Soo.
I think it'll be funny.
(Team Blue's instinct is to go for Kwang Soo.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo, we choose you.)
Let's open Kwang Soo's bag and check.
(Team Blue chooses Kwang Soo's.)
What is it?
Why is there an envelope?
Are you going to open it? Wait.
- Look. - 40 R Coins?
(Team Blue gets 40 R Coins.)
(We can wear suits now.)
(Team Red is poor, and Team Blue is in 1st place.)
- We were right. - This is insane.
- It was 40? - Gi Beom.
He was right.
- He was right. - What do we wear?
This is the final round.
This is an important time for TV Rating Notice.
- It's Loyal Shopping Time. - What's this?
(Final round: Loyal Shopping Time)
Loyal Shopping Time?
Starting from the team with the most coins, go into the shop.
You can each pick an outfit with the coins you have.
(R Coins must be divided within the team to be spent.)
If an outfit is purchased by another team, it's out of stock.
(If another team purchases an outfit, it gets out of stock.)
- We have to share the coins? - We do.
- This is not the end. - This team...
- has 10 R Coins. - They have to wear the tights.
- 1 person will be fine. - You can buy 1 outfit.
Only one person survives.
(Only one person can avoid the tights?)
(Current R Coin Distribution)
(Team Blue is in 1st place, Green in 2nd,)
(Yellow in 3rd, and Red in last place)
Team Blue has the most coins,
so you can choose who gets to go first.
The spoon with a sticker on it goes first.
Which one should I choose?
(Which pair will get to go first?)
- Is this normal? - You get to go first.
(Haha and Ok Jeong get to go first.)
Red sticker goes first.
You first.
- You picked a good one. - Really?
- You can go first. - Okay.
I believe you'll leave us 100 R Coins.
You are going to wear suits.
- That's right. - I want suits too.
Go ahead. Please be nice.
- Sure. - Please be nice.
(Haha and Ok Jeong will get suits. What will they buy?)
There they are.
Hold on.
(As soon as he comes in)
Whose name...
is Name Super under right now?
If I don't buy that, it's just Running Man. If I buy it,
is it Haha's Running Man?
(It's tempting.)
Jae Seok and Ji Suk can take it.
We'll just go.
- What do you think? - Oh, gosh.
(Will he take the honor of Name Super...)
(or be loyal and take the suit?)
This is driving me nuts.
(If they don't get Name Super, they can leave 110 R Coins.)
What should we do?
They're back.
We trust you two.
- Yes. - Goodness.
My mom is too soft-hearted.
- I'm too soft-hearted. - I know.
- You can go in. - I trust your mother.
No way.
(Did Haha and Ok Jeong choose Name Super?)
(Or did they leave some coins for Jae Seok and Ji Suk?)
All right. Haha and Ok Jeong...
- said they didn't need much. - Right.
There are 10 R Coins left.
(There are 10 R Coins left.)
(What? 10 R Coins?)
They left 10 R Coins?
They purchased Name Super.
(Haha backstabbed us.)
- This is our chance, Mom. - Really? That's right.
If you have the will, you can try it.
I saw you play the games today,
- and I take after you. - Really?
(They can't hide the selfish trait.)
This is too...
(Haha and Ok Jeong chose Name Super.)
- Ok Jeong is too... - They took it.
They were being too greedy.
You can choose from the remaining outfits.
(They got 100 R Coins taken away, so they only have 10 left.)
(They're all around the same.)
From these 3, eliminate 1.
Let's go with this one.
(This won't do.)
(Jae Seok chooses...)
(a Barrel Man?)
(It's a great choice.)
(Barrel Man was flexible and a great dancer.)
I'm sorry. We have to do this.
- I'm an actor. - It's okay.
These are all the same.
It's been a while since I've been casted for a drama.
It's okay. If you do this, you'll get some calls.
If you do this, they'll call you.
(They'll call me if I do this?)
Don't worry.
- No... - Let's go.
Is this okay?
(Jae Seok and Ji Suk choose Barrel Man.)
It's red. It's Barrel Man.
It's Barrel Man.
It was my mom's choice.
That's not the problem.
She really wanted to see Haha's Running Man.
So my son...
For four weeks, it'll be Haha's Running Man.
(Haha's Running Man for 4 weeks)
Really?
Who wouldn't pick this?
What's the whole point of dressing them in suits?
- I feel bad. - It's okay.
- You can choose. - It's us.
- Jong Kook, go ahead. - It's us.
- It's our team. - Pick one.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook and K.Will get to go first.)
Yes.
- This is important. - If we're going to do this,
I think Joker is better.
Frog is cute though, right?
Are you going to paint our faces as frogs?
- Will it be green? - Just a little bit.
- It's not too much? - No.
- It won't be too much. - These are tights.
- This one's cute. - Okay, let's do this.
We'll choose Boy Frog.
(We choose you, Boy Frog.)
Let's go.
Do you want to try this first?
You'll look cute anyhow.
It's cute for anybody.
(Really?)
This is cute for anybody.
(Boy Frog is a cute character that represents dream and hope.)
(It's a killer smile.)
- I'm so scared. - I'm cute.
(I'm just scared.)
- I'm scared. - I'm cute.
Shall we go? I'm cute.
(Jong Kook and K.Will choose Boy Frog.)
Let's choose this one.
- Annabelle? - Yes.
It'll be funny for female members to choose that.
Is this okay? The skirt too?
I like the color.
(He likes it.)
You don't care anymore. That's good.
This one. It's cuter.
It's cuter.
(They choose Toshio that Haha dressed up as with 10 R Coins.)
Toshio.
(Ji Hyo and Seong Moon choose Joker.)
Let's go.
We'll be back.
(The costumes will be revealed soon.)
Do rock-paper-scissors.
- Only 1 person gets to go. - Only 1 person.
- One pair? - You have to win.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin and Woo Jong win.)
They get to wear tights.
We at least get to choose.
(They can get Kaonashi.)
We have to wear tights.
I tried so hard to avoid it.
We did the dirty work for other people.
- Gi Beom, you're... - He looks upset.
He's penniless.
(It's time to transform.)
This is really bad.
(Complaining)
(Exclaiming)
That's new.
(That's new.)
- It's a new character. - It's okay.
(Welcome to Barrel Man.)
(You look so funny, Ji Suk.)
Oh, dear.
Jong Kook, you look so scary from the back.
(She's shocked.)
- You look so scary. - He's more scary from the front.
(The backside is better.)
He's almost like a toad. He's not a frog.
He's a bullfrog.
I'm Ranatan.
(Don't you see my skirt?)
(What happened to Ranatan?)
- He's so scary. - He is, right?
He's a frog.
(If you touch my pond, I'll punish you.)
How many weeks will this be for?
- For a month. - Oh, dear.
(I'll be Boy Frog for 4 weeks.)
- Look at him. - It's a dolphin.
Gosh, Gi Beom.
Gi Beom.
Please stop.
- This is legendary. - Please stop.
Please stop this.
I'm sorry.
(He turned from a basketball legend to a variety show legend.)
He's my hero.
I'm sorry.
(He gets up.)
(He's let loose.)
Don't get close!
(He's scary.)
Don't get close.
(He's as charismatic as he was on the basketball court in 1989.)
He's so tall.
Look at Kwang Soo.
(Joker Ji Hyo)
(Seong Moon is transforming into Joker too.)
- You look charismatic. - On Halloween,
- people would do that. - You'll be popular...
- if you do this on Halloween. - It'll be nice.
(What did I just see?)
- You're scary. - You look so scary.
(Watching him walk gives them chills.)
It's supposed to be cute.
It was cute when Haha did it.
(Toshio is in puberty now.)
- You scared me. - Oh, dear.
(Here's another Toshio.)
- It's the female version. - What?
Do I look scary? I look scary?
Why?
(Goodness)
I look so scary.
(She finally sees herself.)
You look more scary.
(You're scarier than me.)
How pretty! My goodness, Jong Hyuk.
Jong Hyuk looks so cute. I don't know what to do.
He looks so cute.
He looks like a cute and ugly doll.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
(It's nice to meet you, Seok Jin Kaonashi.)
(Do I look like I am in the mood for pleasantries?)
Was this the best choice?
- What? - Was this the best choice?
Look next to you.
It's better.
- At least we look human. - I know.
(Seok Jin gets attacked.)
(The winners, Haha and Ok Jeong)
(Barrel men, Jae Seok and Ji Suk)
(Gang Boy Frog and Ranatan, Jong Kook and K.Will)
(Kaonashis, Seok Jin and Woo Jong)
(Joker siblings, Ji Hyo and Seong Moon)
(Grown-up Annabelles, Se Chan and Jong Hyuk)
(Toshio siblings, So Min and Min Gwan)
(White towers in tights, Kwang Soo and Gi Beom)
(The shoot for the TV rating notice finally begins.)
(Gathering around)
(They are colorful.)
How should we do this?
Every one of them feels like my child.
I am so proud of myself.
The members and I can handle this,
but it's too much for the guests.
Jong Hyuk let go of himself.
I feel bad.
Jong Hyuk asked why we invited him for this.
Seong Moon and Ji Hyo look cool.
They look charismatic.
- I know. - It's hard to tell...
the two of us apart, right?
- The two of you look the same. - You resemble each other a lot.
K.Will looks like Cho Sae Ho.
- Excuse me? - Doesn't he look like Sae Ho?
He resembles Sae Ho. He really looks like Sae Ho.
(Honey, your face looks awful today.)
Firstly, I think those in tights...
will fill the screen.
Let's decide on our positions.
- Excuse me. - Hold on.
- Barrel Man. - Please move aside.
- Barrel Man. - Step back.
Kaonashis and Toshios...
should stand over here.
- Give us a nice spot. - We won't be seen.
It's not like that. You will be in the center.
- Why? - Stand over here.
Director Ha, where should the Annabelles go?
I think Annabelles should lie on their stomachs.
(I am sorry.)
- Lie on our stomachs? - Yes.
Jong Hyuk's expression tells me I shouldn't do that.
- I will think about it. - Annabelles...
- should sit in chairs. - We should sit in chairs.
Please give us two chairs.
Annabelles need to sit down.
- At least we will sit down. - I know.
- Annabelles, sit down. - Will they sit at the front?
- We need to sit at the front. - Should we sit together?
- Yes. - Please sit down.
As for Barrel Men,
please pass by as you dance when I say the line.
- Do you want us to pass by? - Yes.
You can exit that way.
- That's... - Pass by as you dance.
- Do what he says! - It will look nice.
(Let's finish up quickly and go home.)
Now... How cute.
- What? - You look cute.
- Stand over here. - Ranatan looks cute.
- What? - I think Ranatan looks scary.
You will look cute if you stand over here.
All right.
- Toshios and Kaonashis... - They should stick together.
should stay together.
The arrangement is perfect.
What should we do?
You are men in tights.
I will have to see how everything looks on the screen.
Aren't we too far in the back?
That position is perfect.
(Stay there.)
(Sad)
Since I feel bad, I will give you a part of the line.
I will give you "rated".
(It's a shocking offer.)
- The two of us? - Yes.
- Thank you. - That's a generous offer.
Yes, I will give you that. Mom, you and I will enter...
and say,
- "Running Man is..." - "Rated..."
- Say, "12". - Do we get to say that?
- "12..." - "12..."
This group gets "years". These two groups get "and".
- Will the 4 of us get "and"? - There are 4 of us!
- The 4 of you get "and". - Since there are 4 of us,
you should at least give us two words.
This is too much.
At least give us two words.
Some of us don't even get to show our faces.
Give us "years and".
We were here since the morning. At least give us two words.
- Give us "years and". - Gosh, I am so soft-hearted.
- Give us "years and". - Okay, you get "years and".
(I feel generous.)
- "Years and". - "Years and".
You get "old" and you get "er".
(Jokers get "old" and the frogs get "er".)
- "Er"? - "Older".
- "Er"? - After that,
- you will play your flute. - My flute.
Can you do that?
I can play that song.
- It will be a full shot anyway. - You're right.
Mom, let's go.
- "Running Man is..." - "Running Man is..."
- "Rated..." - "Rated..."
- "12..." - "12..."
- "Years and..." - What do Barrel Men do?
(What do Barrel Men do?)
- They get to pass by. - They get to pass by.
(Barrel Men get to pass by.)
We should still get to say something.
- Just pass by. - You have the action.
- Be satisfied with it. - You have the action.
- What is it? - Ji Suk is an actor...
who is in dramas.
Everyone is in dramas.
- Give us something to say. - In that case,
- we will pass by. - We will pass by.
If you won't show our faces, use two cotton swabs instead.
(He is unsatisfied.)
(Find the difference.)
In that case,
- I can do this. - Really?
- Give me some time. - How much time do we have?
- I can do this. - Five seconds.
Can you do it in five seconds?
(He is fascinated.)
Will you give him five seconds?
(The rating notice itself is 5 seconds long.)
(If he can do it in 5 seconds, he may be the main character.)
Let's try it. Get ready and go.
(Struggling)
He failed.
(Until when should I do the shoulder dance?)
What are you doing?
- This is driving me crazy. - He failed.
- What are you doing? - I wanted to do it in five seconds.
Don't try to get the spotlight. That's selfish.
- That's selfish. - Everyone is working hard.
Ji Suk is working hard.
Don't do that.
- It will hurt. - Don't do that.
- Just dance. - Okay.
- Don't ask for more. - Okay.
Mom and I need to find our positions.
- I found my position. - Excuse me.
- Excuse me, Haha. - A bit higher.
- Haha. - Yes?
I am not the type to work under someone.
Then you should have won.
You should tell Jae Seok...
- to move around. - Mom,
- stop being nice to Jae Seok only. - I mean...
(I doubt you will ever see him again.)
- You are showing your favoritism. - It's okay.
- He was supposed to pass by. - This is enough.
Let's finish this quickly.
Everyone is working hard.
All right. Let's go.
(It's finally time for the first take.)
All right.
Cue.
- Running Man is... - Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
- 12... - 12...
- Years and... - Years and...
- Older. - Older.
I love Yu Jae Seok!
- What was that? - Don't do that.
What is wrong with him? Anyone can do that.
It's not like we don't know how to do that.
Can't we improvise?
- We made a promise. - Are you drunk?
- Is that why your nose is red? - Jong Kook.
If Jae Seok improvises again...
- I will hit him if he does that. - Okay.
(Don't worry.)
- Hit him right away. - Okay.
Also, move that tennis racket to the side.
(Excuse me, middle-aged man.)
- It's distracting. - For goodness' sake.
Yours isn't like that.
(Running Man is rated 12 years and older.)
What do you think you are doing?
Don't put it like that.
He wants his to be like that.
My mom laughed loudly for the first time.
- Did you laugh? - It was very funny.
Say your allotted parts. Let's go after the count of three.
- Your dance skills are improving. - Thanks.
You are doing a good job.
Cue.
- Running Man is... - Running Man is...
- Rated... - Rated...
- 12... - 12...
- Years and years and years and... - Years and years and years and...
(Years and years and years and)
(They remix their part.)
We wanted to do it once.
- What was that? - Cut us some slack.
- Come on. - There are four of us.
- Come on. - You are so greedy.
"Years and years and years and"? That's longer than our part.
I must remove you if you improvise again.
(I must remove you if you improvise again.)
- What? - Who do you think you are?
Go away.
Are you drunk?
- Come on. - I am not drunk!
- Are you drunk? - I will remove you!
- Let's keep it clean. - Okay.
- Look how nice they are. - I am sorry.
When K.Will plays the flute,
Gi Beom can improvise.
- Say what you want to say. - You get to say something.
You can't say, "Han Gi Beom is the king of basketball."
Don't promote yourself.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
Gi Beom, put yourself at ease.
- Okay. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Running Man is... - Rated...
- 12... - Years and...
- Older. - Older.
Honey, I love you.
Me, too.
- Honey, I love you. - Me, too.
- I couldn't help but say it. - It's not true.
(It's not true that you love her.)
Don't say it's not true. Hold on.
Don't say that.
Stop him from improvising, but don't say it's not true.
- How would you know? - I am sorry. It just came out.
You don't know if it's untrue.
- I am so annoyed. - I am sorry. It just came out.
- I am sorry. - Let's keep it clean.
- Let's do this with seriousness. - Let's do that.
- This is the real round. - Let's go.
(The fourth take)
- Three. Running Man is... - Running Man is...
- Rated... - 12...
- Years and... - Older.
Honey, I love you.
(He even plays the flute perfectly.)
(Cut! It's over at last.)
Good job!
(Everyone, good job.)
(The shoot of the TV rating notice ends at last.)
Hey, now that we stopped being greedy...
Now that we stopped being selfish...
- That was nice. - It's done.
Good work.
- That was great. It was great. - We did it.
It worked because we stopped being greedy.
Let's take a group photo.
- It was great. - That sounds great.
(Thank you for joining us for the finale of the TV rating notice.)
Great job. 1, 2.
(The TV rating notice, the website, and poster will air next week.)
(Seol Hyun and Hye Jeong of AOA return to Running Man.)
(Kang Seung Yoon and Song Min Ho of Winner)
(Rising stars of variety shows, Da Young and Joo E)
Hey, buy me a meal.
(The best idol singers visit Running Man.)
(Uncontrollable excitement seizes the members.)
(However,)
(there's a sudden outbreak of the zombie virus.)
(There's a zombie among us.)
(In order not to turn into a zombie, they must run.)
(The list of the possible suspects gets narrowed down.)
(Will they be able to uncover the identity of the zombie?)
She and I...
- was somewhat of a love interest. - What love interest?
Don't you remember, Seol Hyun?
- No. - She doesn't remember.
(Zombie Couple Race)