(Last week's special was TV Rating Notice Part 2.)
(The first TV rating notice centered around Jae Seok.)
(After running it for 3 months, they will film a new notice.)
"The Boy Frog".
(8 members of Running Man presented their own storyboards.)
(To be in the limelight of the second TV rating notice, )
(dirty plays by the members were seen during missions with guests.)
(Members won points from missions by deceiving each other.)
(And with the accumulated points, )
(the last battle will unfold.)
(The member who wants the notice must endure the weight of the job.)
(Which member will get to direct the second TV rating notice?)
(The director of the 2nd notice will be revealed soon with the clip.)
(And it's a special day today.)
(It's spring in the popular place for retreats, Daeseong-ri.)
- Hello. Goodness.
- Hi. My gosh.
- What is that?
- Hey, there's a cake. I see a cake.
"Se Chan and So Min".
- Is it their birthdays?
- What is this?
- It's their 1-year anniversary.
- It's been a year already?
- Yes, it's been a year now.
(An abundance of food is served outdoors to celebrate the occasion.)
- So Min and Se Chan's Anniversary.
- It's been a year now.
- They will come down from there.
- My gosh.
(Everything is ready to celebrate their first-year anniversary.)
- Hey, hold on.
- This one is delicious too.
- Right?
- The sandwiches look delicious.
- What?
- The sandwiches look tasty.
(Screaming)
(What's going on?)
- What is that?
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
- You've got to be kidding me.
- You guys are hilarious.
- They didn't have to go that far.
- What are you doing?
- This is like a comedy skit.
You guys are ridiculous. My goodness.
- Look at So Min.
- Come on. Play along, guys.
They are so annoying.
(It's all thanks to your love and support.)
("Gapyeong", "Are They in Cannes?", "Dressing up Like Celebrities")
What is So Min doing? What's wrong with her?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, you two. What's the matter with you?
- So Min. Se Chan. come here.
- My gosh.
Look at the table.
- You prepared all this?
- Congratulations.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
- Running Man...
- It's been a year already?
- I know, right?
- It's already been a year.
- Yes, a year has already passed.
- We were in the container...
- That happened a year ago?
- A year ago. Yes.
- It's been a year.
- I can see that...
(April 3, 2017, at the filming of Running Man)
(Their first day was absurd and difficult.)
(The youngest members brought new chemistries and energy to the show.)
They joined the show when we were having the hardest time.
That's so true. You are our lucky charms.
- You two were of big help.
- Right, right.
(The driving force of the show's newfound popularity)
I like today's special.
It's their first-year anniversary. And the high-school rapper is here.
Jae Seok, it must be time to bring out the shorts now.
- Ji Hyo, my gosh.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Did something happen?
- You ripped the pants, didn't you?
- She ripped them herself.
- I must wear shorts by the river.
- Hey, look at Seok Jin.
- What?
- He wore a cardigan on a hot day.
- Hey.
- One of us isn't wearing...
- It's hot today.
Adventurous outfits now.
- People wear it at nursing homes.
- It's for spring. It's spring now.
(An outfit for nursing homes)
Hey, you! You'd better watch out.
- He didn't wear it to look young.
- Hey, you.
- Pigeon Gramps.
- "Pigeon Gramps"?
- Why?
- You know nothing about fashion.
- My gosh, Kwang Soo.
- What?
Don't you wear that in "Live"?
- No, no.
- Yeom Sang Soo.
- My gosh.
- Is the drama still on?
- I feel really bad though.
- Why?
- Jung Hae In has all the attention.
- He's the best!
- He's awesome.
- He's really getting popular now.
- I agree.
- My gosh, he's the best.
- I really like him.
- "Something in the Rain".
Hae In is so popular these days.
Kwang Soo could've gotten more attention too.
He doesn't have a love interest. Give him one.
- He needs kissing scenes too.
- He just has a crush on someone.
- He should have kissing scenes.
- Right.
Exactly. It's always unrequited love with him. It's frustrating.
Upload a video of your kissing someone on your social media.
(Upload a video of your kissing someone on your social media.)
(Do it on a "live" streaming show.)
What do you mean? Why would I do that?
- They didn't give you the scenes.
- Yes, do it.
Jung Hae In and I are on different paths.
Precisely. I'm happy that Kwang Soo realized that.
- I'm so relieved.
- Hae In will be like Joong Ki.
- He'll be categorized with Bo Gum.
- Right.
- That's right.
- They will take their own paths.
Kwang Soo will follow after me. He will star on "Reverse Drama".
- Why would I star on that?
- I was on that show.
- Why would I star on that show?
- I acted on that show.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
I did what you're doing now on that show.
No, I can't take that path.
- You make me very proud.
- That show isn't...
- Thank you.
- I'm happy that my fellow...
- comedian is a good actor.
- Wait.
He was a comedian?
- Did you not know?
- He was a comedian?
- Hey, pay your dues for the club.
- Yes, you should.
- Why? I'm not a comedian!
- You're a comedian.
Seriously.
- Why would I pay the dues?
- Pay your dues, man.
My gosh, he can be so frustrating.
Hey, So Min. You might get an offer for a farting commercial.
Jae Seok.
(That stupid farting.)
(So Min was in the midst of a scandal regarding her farting.)
I saw the keyword "So Min's farting" trending online.
I'm really sad that my related terms...
are "farting" and "gas".
As you can see on the table, it's So Min and Se Chan's...
- first-year anniversary.
- Okay.
To celebrate their anniversary,
- For our anniversary? - we prepared Running 365 Retreat.
(Running 365 Retreat)
"365"?
It's been 365 days.
That's why you can enjoy the retreat for 365 minutes here.
You can come up with your own schedule for the retreat.
- That's great.
- Really?
However, you cannot do anything...
that's not on the schedule.
(However, you cannot do anything that's not on the schedule.)
You must come up with a detailed schedule...
- that includes bathroom breaks.
- Seriously?
Can't we have a bathroom break unless it's on the schedule?
Everyone's bladder runs on a different schedule.
So Min and Se Chan will write a schedule each.
The rest will write 2 schedules as 2 groups of 3.
In total, there will be four schedules.
(So Min, Se Chan, and the two groups)
What should we write?
(They begin writing the schedules for Running 365 Retreat.)
What?
Jong Kook, I see what Se Chan wrote.
What did he write?
- "Jong Kook grills pork belly."
- Stop it.
(Jong Kook grills pork belly.)
(Is that so?)
Is that so?
I can grill both pork belly and Se Chan.
(I can grill both pork belly and Se Chan.)
- May I have a new board?
- Suit yourself.
(Se Chan is in trouble.)
Don't write Truth Game.
Truth Game is no fun.
- It's fun.
- Stop it.
- Why did you include Truth Game?
- It's no fun.
It's fun, Seok Jin.
- Erase it.
After me, Seok Jin became the MC of "Truth Game".
(The topic of "Truth Game" saddens Seok Jin every time.)
Stop it.
Seok Jin was in "Truth Game".
- Are we talking about the past?
- That's right.
The show got canceled because of me.
Let's play Mafia Game.
- That's a good idea.
- Find the Thief.
- Pass the Towel.
- Why would you play those games?
We can play in the water.
We will need a shower if we get wet. It's a hassle.
Treasure Hunt.
- We will need to hide the treasure.
- We played it for nine years.
Why are you complaining so much?
No matter what I suggest, you go, "I don't think it's a good idea."
"Let's do something else. I don't want to become sweaty."
You write it down!
We can write down "grill meat".
I don't suit this team.
(I don't suit this team.)
(He realizes it by watching Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
I realize that now.
(What do their schedules look like?)
If everyone is done,
each team will now present their schedule for the retreat.
Please put it up on the board after the presentation.
- Now...
- Let's begin with Se Chan.
Me?
- Kim Kap Soo, please proceed.
- Okay.
I have...
(Sincere rolling paper, Jong Kook grills pork belly, )
(couple dance time, shower and bathroom break)
(Jong Kook grills beef, Foot volleyball)
I want to have a sincere rolling paper time.
(The first period)
- Rolling paper.
- There must be things...
we weren't able to say to each other.
Wouldn't it dampen our mood from the start?
Aren't such sentimental moments more suitable during the nighttime?
You haven't done it, have you?
It's my schedule.
The next one is...
couple dance time with music.
(For goodness' sake.)
We will become couples.
(What is wrong with him?)
Why would we become couples?
Write it again.
We don't know what will happen.
We will have that for an hour.
Before we go home, we can play foot volleyball.
(Before we go home, we can play foot volleyball.)
When you go to a retreat,
don't you do those things in reverse?
(Don't you do those things in reverse?)
Hold on.
We should start with foot volleyball and end with rolling paper.
The schedule needs to go backwards. It's only right.
That's right.
(It goes askew.)
(Can't he do anything right?)
For goodness' sake.
(Flustered)
- Is that a difficult task?
- I am sorry.
- I am taking too much time.
- Is that a difficult task?
Se Chan, what are you doing?
(The briefing on Se Chan's schedule ends.)
- So Min.
I...
(Stay still without doing anything, bathroom break, )
(Jackstone Game, Random Game with beer, )
(speak casually to each other during a barbecue party, )
(bathroom break, say farewells)
We will begin by staying still...
without doing anything for two hours.
Doesn't that mean we will continue to hear you fart?
No, it's a misunderstanding.
Opening the door, you'll hear this.
The phone will go like this.
(So Min, sing for us.)
(She becomes confused.)
You should dance.
So Min, this is the perfect time.
Next comes drinking beer...
- while we play Random Game.
- 12-year-olds watch this show.
(Next comes drinking beer while we play Random Game.)
12-year-olds watch our show.
We can't drink beer while we are on the show!
- There is non-alcoholic beer.
- You're right.
Then I want us to have a barbecue party over a campfire...
and speak casually to each other for an hour and a half.
(Have a barbecue party and speak casually to each other.)
Is that so?
It doesn't matter.
I won't go easy on anyone just because he or she is older.
Hold on.
- That's not how you play this game.
- What?
- I will keep living the same way.
- It's Obedience Game.
(I can't win against him.)
We have the most typical schedule...
for the retreat.
We have over 20 years of experience.
(Play foot volleyball game against the production crew, )
(sauna time and snack time, eat Korean food, take a nap, )
(bathroom break, One Year Anniversary Party)
We are the veterans when it comes to the retreat.
In Daeseong-ri...
We are the legends when it comes to retreats.
Why does the most typical retreat include going to a sauna?
(Why does the most typical retreat include going to a sauna?)
What?
You said it's the most typical schedule.
- Don't you know?
- What?
- When you go to a retreat...
Why do you say...
(Let's high five for the retreat.)
He hit me!
- I didn't do that.
- Did you film it?
Did anyone see me hit him?
That was the slate.
- He hit me!
- What are you talking about?
Let's go again. In 1, 2, 3.
- That was the slate.
You're hearing things since you've been shooting until late.
I'm not hearing anything. I felt a slap on my cheek.
It's a tactile hallucination.
Does that even exist?
- Yes, it does.
- I see.
What's the point of going to the sauna here?
We can go to the sauna near home.
By your logic,
we should have stayed home instead of coming here.
Why don't you come at me as you did to Kwang Soo?
That's right. Why are you being so careful?
- Bring the board.
- What are you doing?
Bring the board.
- My goodness.
- Hurry up.
I can't believe him.
Let Jong Kook have that tactile hallucination.
Do you want me to make you tired?
(Slapping)
(He slapped his hand.)
Hold on.
- My goodness.
- That's not how you do it.
This is how you do it.
(This is how you do it.)
(You are bound to see children fight on a trip.)
(It's fun to watch them fight.)
(Is Jae Seok a veteran of retreats or a swindler?)
We kept the schedule simple.
The first thing...
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo's schedule)
(Hiking, fishing and lunch, rest and bathroom break, )
(Eat beef for dinner, game of yut, foot volleyball)
The first thing on our schedule is hiking.
- It's spring.
- That's a good idea.
The weather is nice,
so we will gather wild herbs.
- So...
- It sounds like a hassle.
Can we focus on hiking?
We don't know much about edible herbs.
We don't know which ones are edible or poisonous.
- All right. I will cross it out.
- Okay.
Let's just hike.
Why don't you take out a dot?
- A dot?
- Yes.
- Do you mean my mole?
- From the word "hike".
Then it becomes "fool".
(Then it becomes "fool".)
(Bingo)
Did I do it right?
Is it what I think it is?
- Yes, it is.
- Take out a dot elsewhere.
- Did I do it wrong?
There is no other character I can take it out of.
"Fool"...
- is the only possible answer.
- Come on.
You did it wrong.
- Then it becomes "copy".
- That's it.
- Each team presented the schedule.
- Yes.
Please bring in the schedule.
(Is there another schedule?)
Is there another schedule?
- What?
- Aren't these the schedules?
Maybe we can't do the things that are on our schedules.
- What is going on?
What's Misty Time?
- What are those balls?
- We are drawing lots.
It looks like we will pick numbers.
(The balls have the colors of the schedules.)
(The schedule is decided by drawing lots.)
We will tell you about the real race of the day.
The Running 365 Retreat...
involves an uncertain future...
in the form of 365 minutes of Misty Time.
What's Misty Time?
The retreat will follow the schedules you wrote down.
However, the order won't follow your schedules.
We will choose a schedule at random...
and follow the order it was chosen.
We will follow the time slots on the production crew's schedule.
(They follow the time slots on the production crew's schedule.)
What a bully!
Why did they tell us to decide on a schedule?
If we have 30 minutes for lunch, the time slot will end...
on our way to the restaurant.
What if we get an hour and a half of bathroom break?
What is this?
If a member deviates from the schedule,
he or she will receive a penalty and a penalty badge.
Is there a penalty?
After the retreat, the member with the most penalty badges...
receives the final penalty.
He or she will pick another member.
They will give autographs to 365 fans before they go home.
(The penalty is giving autographs to 365 fans before going home.)
- 365 fans?
- Yes.
Now, it's time to pick the first schedule of the retreat.
Who wants to pick?
- You should pick, So Min.
- Okay.
- Please do a good job.
- You can count on me.
Pick, So Min.
(With 4 schedules and 6 time slots, )
(there are 24 options available.)
(Which combination of color and number comes first?)
Please.
Pick the one next to it.
The one next to it?
- The one next to it?
- The one next to it.
- Did you pick?
- What's the number?
- It's yellow.
(It's a yellow ball.)
It's yellow.
(They must do one of these things for an hour.)
- It's yellow.
- Five.
(5 on the yellow schedule)
Yellow, five.
- That's my schedule.
- Restroom break.
(It's a restroom break.)
- That's my schedule.
- Restroom break.
We don't need an hour to use the restroom.
What will we do in the restroom?
Five on my schedule.
You will now change into the team uniform...
and take a restroom break.
How can we stay in the bathroom for an hour?
Let us pick...
- once more.
- Let's get started.
- Start with foot volleyball.
- Come to the front.
- Where's the bathroom?
- We'll start the timer.
Can eight people fit inside the bathroom?
(Fun 365 Retreat starts.)
(Welcome to the bathroom where we'll shoot for an hour.)
(60-Minute Bathroom)
- What?
- What is it?
It's time to start.
There are many things. Does it have to be the bathroom?
There's a lot on the set.
- There's a karaoke machine.
- It's a karaoke machine.
(This is amazing.)
We could even cook here.
This is amazing.
(There are spacious rooms.)
- Why did So Min pick that?
- What will we do in the bathroom?
- I'm sorry.
- What will we do for an hour?
How will we fit in here?
Seriously.
This is nonsense.
(The first activity seems impossible.)
It's too small.
What will we do in the bathroom?
Do we have to stay in there?
Go into the bathroom.
You'll do something inside for 60 minutes.
Do what?
Cameras are set up, so we can't use it.
If you need to go to the bathroom, there's another one next to it.
Is this it?
Are there cameras inside?
There are no cameras.
Let's say you want to do something.
If you come out to buy a drink,
- you'll be penalized?
- What's the penalty?
- Is there a penalty?
- You'll find out...
what it is once you come out.
- Goodness.
- That means...
- Kwang Soo should try it.
- Kwang Soo will try it.
Those who are reckless should go out.
- You'll be curious.
- I'm curious.
- Goodness.
- The reckless should try it.
I shouldn't be curious, but I can't help it.
Let's kick Kwang Soo out.
(Let's kick Kwang Soo out.)
Shouldn't you say that secretly?
You said it so loudly.
He talks as if he's in a sitcom.
I couldn't help but pretend not to hear him.
What's wrong with you?
"Let's kick Kwang Soo out, okay?"
(Kwang Soo looks around.)
Shall we get started?
(He fakes a laugh.)
We couldn't install a camera inside.
Please put a camera on your chest.
(They each film themselves with a camera.)
- Does everyone wear it?
- Yes.
- Could you help me?
- You seem so excited.
It doesn't work well.
Let it go. Hold it tightly, Kwang Soo.
(Screaming)
Hold it tightly.
(His private part is attacked.)
(What just happened?)
- What did you do?
- Hold it tightly.
- I couldn't hold it tightly.
- I didn't mean to do that.
- He isn't even married yet.
- I meant...
the top. It's okay if you push against me.
Keep yourself up.
- Wait.
- I wouldn't do that.
I'm not an amateur.
You didn't do that before.
I'm sorry. I'll forget what happened.
- Okay.
- What?
- I'll forget what happened.
- Let it go, Jae Seok.
Move on.
- You should stop too.
- All right.
You shouldn't do that at a shoot.
- I came for a shoot.
- Stop it.
- Let's enjoy the shoot.
- Go inside.
- Come on, go in.
- Wait.
- Get out.
- Go in.
- Why?
- It's my spot.
- There's no designated spot.
(Everyone complains.)
- Stop it.
- I don't want water falling.
I hate that.
Is the cameraman on vacation today?
- What's this?
- What are we doing here?
Why did you choose the bathroom?
- This is terrible.
- Seriously.
Why did you pick it?
I don't know.
The timer has started. For the next 60 minutes,
stay in the bathroom.
Do we get penalized if we go out?
Yes. You'll go back inside after getting penalized.
Kick him out.
(Go out.)
(Jae Seok gets a penalty after 10 seconds.)
- Okay.
- Go out.
- Jae Seok will be penalized.
- No way.
Go outside.
- Jae Seok will be penalized.
- Why?
- Why me?
- You're out.
Why would I be penalized?
- Seriously.
- Get your penalty.
There he goes.
(He gets dragged.)
- Tell me what it is.
- Hold on.
Haha.
- This is quite fun.
- It is.
- He went outside.
- This is fun.
- It's interesting.
- Will he come back?
- Yes.
- Kick him out when he returns.
- That's right.
Isn't that harsh?
(Surprised, is this the penalty?)
My goodness.
Look at him.
That's the penalty.
- This is it.
- Goodness.
We should never go outside.
- Gosh.
- It's simple but funny.
- We should never leave.
How about...
we play Musical Chairs?
- In here?
- We must do something.
- We can't stay still.
- We need chairs.
- We have to look forward.
We must look outside the door.
- We don't know what we'll do.
- When you turn,
don't turn inwards.
We must turn this way, okay?
- Okay.
- Please stand up.
- We're playing Musical Chairs.
- With these?
Take out a chair.
- We don't need all of them.
- Can we even turn?
We have to turn no matter what.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Round and round - Start moving.
- Dance while turning around - Dance while turning around
- Go fast.
- While clapping
- And singing - And singing
- Keep going.
- Let's dance
- Have fun - Turn the other way.
Turn the other way.
The whistle should blow from the outside.
Please blow the whistle.
(The whistle blows.)
(They start struggling as the whistle blows.)
(The members inside sit down successfully.)
There we go.
(Who will be eliminated?)
Okay, that's good.
(Kwang Soo fails to sit down.)
No.
(Go outside, Ji Hyo.)
- She already sat down.
- She sat down.
- I sat down.
(They end up fighting anyway.)
- Go outside.
- It's over.
- Is it over?
- Yes.
Do I have to go?
- Goodbye.
- Go outside. It's over.
(And so, the passionate tango started.)
- Goodness.
- Push him.
Push him out.
(The audience claps.)
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You were eliminated.
Lift Kwang Soo's feet.
I don't want to.
- What is this?
- Be careful.
(What? Is it Jae Seok?)
Goodness.
(While pushing out Kwang Soo, )
(Jae Seok pushes himself out.)
- He went outside.
- One of them went out.
He went out. We're safe.
Come on.
Hey.
Kwang Soo, you lost.
I lost this game.
I lost Musical Chairs, but you lost this game.
(He gets dragged out again.)
Wait a minute.
- Hey.
- That worked.
- It's exhausting.
- That was funny.
Why don't we play Musical Chairs outside where it's spacious?
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm tired.
I'm also tired.
- I have dark circles.
- This isn't an anniversary.
He's coming back.
- He got makeup.
- Is it?
- He looks cute.
- Jae Seok.
Hey.
- Why didn't you go out?
- I'm sorry.
What's the white thing?
Why didn't you go out?
The makeup is done carelessly.
- Let me see.
- The person isn't professional.
- It's done carelessly.
- He does it carelessly.
- What's on your face?
- It isn't makeup.
He should do it carefully,
but he put it on his thumb.
The penalty isn't the problem. You just look bad.
Who pushed me from behind?
- I didn't.
- I was sitting down.
- It was So Min.
- I just saw that...
you were doing a handstand.
You were already doing a handstand.
- So Min pushed you.
- Seok Jin was behind me.
- I didn't do it.
- Was it you?
- Did I do it?
- Was it Seok Jin?
No way.
- All right.
- Let's play the folding game.
- Okay, let's do that.
- The folding game.
The folding game.
- The loser goes out.
- He has to go out.
- You start, Jae Seok.
- Shall I?
Put down a finger if you're the oldest.
Okay.
- It can't be helped.
- It's just a game.
- Okay.
- I got it.
- It can't be helped.
Put down a finger if you're wearing glasses.
You never know with this one.
(Jae Seok takes off his glasses.)
- You can't take them off anymore.
- You can't.
- Really?
- From now on?
- Starting now.
- Before I take them off?
I took them off before.
It's my turn.
Seok Jin, put down a finger.
This is how you play.
- Can you call someone's name?
- It's allowed.
- Yes, you can.
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
(So Min is up next.)
Play it.
Put down a finger if you spray your hair black.
"Put down a finger if you spray your hair black."
(Seok Jin laughs.)
- Did you?
- Can you prove it?
- He's honest.
- What if we wipe it off?
- It's over.
- We got it.
- There it is.
(We see proof.)
Show it to him.
- We got it.
- Look.
- We did, didn't we?
- Okay.
- He has one finger left.
You have one left.
Put down a finger if you have one finger left.
(Put down a finger if you have one finger left.)
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
- Go out.
- Go.
- Goodbye.
- Stop it.
I'm not coming with you.
You should go.
Get out.
(He gets dragged.)
- Go out.
- Goodbye.
See you.
(Seok Jin screams.)
(He falls on the floor.)
(He gets penalized.)
You were going to leave anyway.
You wait and see.
- We work well as a team.
- That was great.
We have to stay here all day long.
(When will this be over?)
How many minutes passed so far?
20 minutes have passed.
How many more games do we have to play?
It's fun to be sitting here like this.
Goodness.
(Seok Jin comes back.)
He's not wearing makeup.
- How is the makeup artist?
- He looks cute.
How is the makeup artist?
He's in a yellow uniform.
Go outside if you're curious.
Kwang Soo looks so calm.
Let's play another game.
Staying in the bathroom...
for an hour is too harsh.
- Can it be 30 minutes?
- Can you give us jelly?
If we don't pick a game for food, we won't eat.
- We won't eat.
- You're right.
Can we use the bathroom?
- It's next door.
- Can we go there?
- Aren't you penalized if you do?
You're allowed to use the bathroom.
- It's a fake bathroom.
- You can go.
- Can I go?
- Of course.
You can use the bathroom next door.
- Is it really...
- Kwang Soo.
Do you want to use it here?
He stepped on it.
- You can't step on the floor.
- Okay.
I was going to the bathroom.
(He got caught.)
- I knew this would happen.
- You said I could.
Okay.
- You said I could use the bathroom.
- You can't step on the floor.
- Okay.
- You said I could use the bathroom.
- You should have used the wall.
- You can't step on the floor.
- I mean...
Isn't that common sense?
- It is.
- It's common sense.
How could he not know that?
You said I could use the bathroom.
Dong Geun, it's you.
(Chief referee)
Dong Geun.
Dong Geun, we're friends, right?
- Should we play kungkungdda?
- I wish I had a toothbrush.
Kungkungdda is boring.
What about 369?
- Kungkungdda...
- 369, 369
Playing 369 here would be the worst.
What are we supposed to do then?
Look at Kwang Soo.
- You look great.
- You look cute.
- It looks nice.
- It says, "poop".
- That's so boring.
It must have been done by someone with little experience.
You're not supposed to write letters.
Writing letters makes it boring.
How could he write "poop" on a person's face?
- This should go to the back?
- There's 30 minutes left.
Time is going by so slowly.
Guys, are you hungry?
- Yes!
One person can go out for 10 minutes.
You'll play a game loved by college students.
- Sounds good.
- Sure.
- We'll demonstrate.
- We needed this.
We were talking about 369 and kungkungdda.
It's called "Maggots in a Honey Bucket".
They play such a game?
- Let us demonstrate.
- Okay.
There's such a game?
- Maggots in a Honey Bucket?
- Yes.
I think I've heard of it.
Ready, start.
- Maggots in a honey bucket - Maggots in a honey bucket
- Mag - Gots
- Maggots - In
- A - In a
- Hon - Ey
- Honey - Buck
- Et - Bucket
- Maggots in a honey bucket - Maggots in a honey bucket
(What...)
(is that?)
- What's that?
- Can you pretend to be excited?
What's that?
What are they doing?
College students play this?
- It's so boring.
- When did you leave college?
- They really play this boring game?
- Are you sure?
Even Seok Jin doesn't know.
How old are the ones who play this game?
I don't know how old they are,
but if you lose, you'll have to go out.
Well... Who wants to start?
I want to start. Let's start.
- Maggots in a honey bucket - Maggots in a honey bucket
- Mag - Gots
- Maggots - In
- A - In a
- Hon - Ey
- Honey - Buck
- Et - Bucket
- No.
- It's wrong.
(They're supposed to say, "Maggots in a honey bucket, ha".)
Hold on. We were just practicing.
Go out.
Come on.
(Maggot Seok Jin is released.)
With Seok Jin out, it'll be different.
- All right.
- Let's try. Start.
- Maggots in a honey bucket - Maggots in a honey bucket
- Mag - Gots
- Maggots - In
- A - In a
- Hon - Ey
- Honey - Buck
- Et - Bucket
- Maggots in a honey bucket - Maggots in a honey bucket
(Haha is wrong.)
Oh, that's how you play?
Maggots in a honey bucket
(You can practice in the makeup room.)
(Annoyed)
College students these days play like this?
(1 in, 1 out)
It says, "stupid".
What's that?
- The game is difficult.
- It is.
- It's very hard.
Can't we play another game?
- 007 is fun.
- Let's do something fun.
Ji Hyo, 007 has been around since the 1980s.
- I mean...
- But the silent version is fun.
- Silent 007.
- You have to keep silent.
I don't know how to play it.
- I know nothing.
- You've never played it?
You start like this.
Let me explain the rules.
When the fourth person is pointed at,
the two people sitting next to that person raise their hands.
- You can't make any noise.
- That's right.
- You can't even make this sound?
- No.
- You can't even laugh.
- You can't.
- Don't laugh.
- Don't show your teeth.
- Let's start from Seok Jin.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Start.
(Zero)
(7)
(Bang! Screaming)
(Zero)
(0, 7)
(Bang! Screaming)
(The bathroom game is becoming intense.)
(Zero)
(Seven, Bang! Screaming)
(Flustered)
(Jong Kook makes a sound by mistake.)
(Jae Seok is supposed to raise his hands.)
You're out too.
You didn't raise your hands.
You said something. Come here.
I didn't say anything.
What are you talking about?
You punks!
Losers should come out.
Gosh.
- We should take Jong Kook with us.
- Jong Kook!
Can I stay in here?
(Happy)
At this rate, everyone will be out.
(You just said something.)
Are we still doing the silent thing?
(There's suddenly so much space.)
(The cruel 007 game continues.)
(Should I start?)
(In addition to the cameramen, the sound director gets a break.)
(Time out)
(No way.)
(The game continues in a serious atmosphere.)
(Harlequin)
Gosh, they sprayed my hair.
You're still playing?
(Zero, zero, seven)
(Ji Hyo loses.)
(She raises her hands at the wrong moment.)
(Why?)
Hey. I can't believe you guys.
You guys teamed up?
(You punks!)
Gosh, you two...
You two are together, aren't you? Hey!
You can't team up.
(With a new member, the game continues.)
(Are we playing 007?)
(Haha starts.)
(0, 0, 7)
(Bang! Screaming)
(So Min is late.)
(So Min is eliminated.)
We never teamed up!
(She wanted to say, )
("We didn't team up!")
We didn't team up.
We didn't.
I can go out, right? I'm the winner.
- Can I go out?
- But I said...
you needed to succeed the original game three times.
I never said the winner would be going out.
(What have we been doing?)
I don't have any space left on my face.
They definitely don't have much experience.
Are there any references?
Hey.
- Jong Kook looks scary.
- Jong Kook...
He looks so evil.
Is it Halloween today?
- He looks scary.
- Haha looked cute.
Guys, they're dating.
- What?
- I'm 100-percent sure.
They teamed up...
and tricked me.
- I'm not lying.
- Sit down and wait.
- I mean it.
- Take it easy.
I don't care if they're together.
Se Chan, you look good.
Jae Seok is drawing on his own face.
(Focused)
Look at him.
They're inexperienced. My scalp hurts.
They almost stuck the spray in his hair.
They sprayed my hair like this.
- Is it Halloween?
- I'm a robot every time.
- Why do you look so scary?
- They didn't make me look cute.
Let's play silent 007 again.
We need to earn the right to go out.
Let us play another game.
Not maggots in a honey bucket.
It was too difficult.
When everyone comes back,
let's just push each other out.
What are you talking about?
What did you say?
The one who is left in here will win.
- All right. Let's do it.
- You're selfish.
- Let's do it.
Let's do it.
(The girls are back?)
They're back.
- You're selfish.
- Let's do it.
Let's do it.
(The fart girl appears.)
(She is officially the fart girl.)
It says, "fart".
(The fart girl is here.)
- The fart girl.
- I love it.
Fart girl.
- Ji Hyo.
- Ma'am.
Are you on "Show Me the Money"?
- Ji Hyo looks cute.
- Look at her.
- Gosh.
- You look okay.
- Seriously...
- We've all been out.
We've all been out.
- That's what always happens.
- Everyone.
What's important is the number of penalty badges.
- Right.
- Jae Seok has three penalty badges.
- 3?
- 3.
- Seok Jin also has three.
- That's a lot.
The rest of you have one each.
I can't believe it.
Why was I out?
- Okay.
- Let's go out.
- It's over.
- Gosh.
- It was too much.
Finally.
Let's decide on the next activity.
Let's do it right this time.
We spent an hour in the bathroom.
What if it's the bathroom again?
We were in there for an hour.
Can we do the same thing again?
Of course.
- It's been an hour.
- Don't pick it again.
We shouldn't go back to the bathroom again.
But so many people wrote it.
It's not okay.
I hope we'll eat this time.
Let's eat some meat. I'm hungry.
- I want meat too.
- It's 30 minutes this time.
Let's decide on the next activity.
- Se Chan, try it.
- Se Chan should pick.
- Se Chan.
- It's his anniversary.
Yes. Those two should pick.
Be brave and pick.
It's only 30 minutes. Pick the right one.
(If they can't finish the activity, they'll receive penalty badges.)
- This one.
- Okay.
(What did he pick?)
- Let's eat.
- We have 30 minutes.
- It's a green ball.
- Let's eat.
(Green)
(Number 2)
- Green, two.
- Green.
Pork belly party. Yes!
(Jong Kook will grill pork belly for the members.)
- Jong Kook will grill the meat.
- I knew it.
- Guys!
- Great.
- Okay.
- We have only 30 minutes.
- We have 30 minutes.
- The timer will be on.
- We don't have much time.
- Right now, we...
Time will be up once we finish grilling.
- We don't have pork belly here.
- What?
Come on.
- You should've bought it.
- A team will go to the supermarket.
- The rest will prepare the meal.
- Are you serious?
- Listen.
- What do you want from us?
- Hey.
- That's not fair.
Are you serious right now?
We didn't think that you would have a barbecue.
The grocery store is a minute away by car.
- It might work. We'll have time.
- That's great.
Hold on. Everyone, calm down.
Let's split into teams. A team will go grocery shopping.
Another will start the fire.
- You two should go.
- The two of us?
- We'll be back.
- Run!
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan will go grocery shopping.)
- We're going like this?
- Yes, let's just hurry.
Let's get it. Hey, hurry.
Ji Hyo, it's a minute away. We have time.
(Eating pork belly grilled by Jong Kook for 30 minutes begins.)
Hurry, Ji Hyo.
(They can accomplish the mission only when no one messes up.)
First of all, when we get there,
- let's get thin pork belly...
- Thin pork belly.
And vegetables for wraps.
- And ssamjang.
- Ssamjang.
- We should get sausages too.
- Of course.
We should get some food for ourselves too.
Right. Even if the others came, they would've...
- Exactly.
- Done that too.
- If Kwang Soo and So Min came, - My gosh.
- We wouldn't have a chance.
- They would pretend to be running.
- Exactly.
- They would've done that for sure.
- Absolutely. That's for sure.
- Right.
Even if we come back quickly, the fire wouldn't have been ready.
- It takes time.
- It takes a long time to do that.
We should start the grill as quickly as we can.
(What do you mean? It blazes up straight away.)
(Oh, my gosh!)
- My gosh.
- What if this explodes?
Hey, hey, hey.
(With the torch, they have a camp fire too.)
Hey, this is a good torch.
- It makes strong flames. Hold on.
- That's good.
- Why do you get so scared easily?
- The gloves.
- My gosh.
- That's a flame thrower.
- Is that enough?
- It looks like the underworld.
(I will burn everything up.)
All right. Take a look. It's working.
My gosh.
We can eat as soon as they come back with the meat.
They should've been here already. What's taking them so long?
- They're taking too long.
- I had a bad feeling about this.
- My gosh.
- They are so slow.
Are they eating at the market?
- Where are you?
- We're on our way.
- Rush back.
- Hurry back. We don't have time.
- We're on our back way.
- You ate there,
- didn't you?
- You didn't eat there, right?
Why is your voice echoing?
- Did you get ramyeon?
- Why is it echoing in the car?
Something is fishy. He sounds like he's in the restroom.
Why is your voice echoing?
Hello? Hello?
- Something is going on.
- Something is up.
- Do they think I'm an idiot?
- No.
They are not in the car.
(Betrayal tastes sweet.)
- Do you think the grill is ready?
- Yes.
(We get that we don't have time, but we must feed ourselves first.)
Ji Hyo, should we just...
have a bowl of ox bone soup? Should we just do it?
- How many minutes do we have?
- You have about 15 minutes.
- No.
- 15 minutes? My gosh.
They should've come back a long time ago.
They need to be here by now.
- Did they run off?
Call Ji Hyo.
If we don't get to eat the meat after starting the grill,
- I would be so angry.
- Jae Seok.
Ji Hyo pressed the wrong button.
- What did she say?
- Thank you.
- They just bought the food.
- They just bought it.
- This is over.
I think they ate whatever they wanted to eat there.
Hurry, hurry. Come on, hurry.
- Run. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- They're just leaving the store.
- Why did they waste their time?
- The instant rice.
- Right.
(They are ringing up the food now.)
(Wait. Hold on.)
(What's going on?)
- I need to ring them up again.
- Why?
(He has to scan the barcodes again.)
- I need to ring them up again.
- Why?
Because of the previous customer,
the ones I scanned earlier got deleted.
- Hurry, hurry. Are you serious?
- No.
- Then please hurry.
- I'll cancel...
- everything and ring them up again.
- Okay.
- This is insane.
- My gosh.
(They face a crisis at the end.)
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't be.
- No, that's all right.
- It's over.
We wasted 2 or 3 minutes because we had to ring them up again.
It's over. We failed.
How many minutes do we have?
- About 8 minutes?
- You have 8 minutes.
- 8 minutes?
- It's over. It's done.
- We can't even eat ramyeon.
We should grill Se Chan's hands.
(We just need to grill something to succeed.)
- On the grill?
- Yes.
I'll grill his hands.
(We just need to grill something to succeed.)
(The blazing grill is empty. Will they fail to complete the mission?)
(They arrive with the meat with 5 minutes left.)
- Where are you?
- Hey!
- Is that you?
- What did you eat?
- We didn't eat anything.
- Grill the sausages.
- My gosh.
- Hey, this is the meat.
- Hurry, and grill the meat.
- Hey, we're running out of time.
- Here's the meat.
Throw the meat on the grill!
(Jong Kook has to grill the meat.)
You opened the bags of ramyeon in advance. Okay.
Jong Kook.
You have five minutes before the time is up.
- Hey!
- You guys!
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Do we have gochujang?
- Hey, hey.
- Is the rice ready?
No, it's not ready yet.
Forget about the rice.
- This is the ox bone soup.
- I put it in there. I already did.
- You have four minutes left.
- Darn it.
Hey, if we can't finish in time,
everyone can grab one of these and eat.
Got it?
- I got it.
- Grab one each, and start eating.
They're getting cooked.
This is insane.
They are almost done. They are almost all cooked.
Three minutes before your time is up.
My gosh! We 're almost done.
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(The undercooked meat frustrates them.)
I think ramyeon is ready.
No, not yet.
(Taking the noodles)
It's not ready yet.
- I like undercooked noodles.
- Wait.
(She eats undercooked noodles as she's desperate.)
- Let's eat the rice at least.
- You have two minutes.
Let's eat the rice.
Should we mix the rice with ssamjang?
- The meat isn't hot at all.
- Hey, we can eat this.
- We should eat now.
- Eat the ramyeon now.
- Let's eat.
- Eat up.
(They all eat ramyeon first.)
How many minutes do we have left?
Hey, the noodles aren't cooked.
- My gosh, it's all ready.
- You have one minute left.
- One minute.
- Eat the pork belly.
This is all cooked, right?
- They're cooked. Just eat it.
- I don't know. Just eat one.
- I ate one.
- Eat it.
(They finish their 2nd part of the schedule.)
Stop.
(Stop!)
Ji Hyo, stop eating. Everyone, stop.
- You'll draw for another mission.
- This doesn't qualify as a retreat.
What is this?
I didn't get to finish the ramyeon either.
You will proceed to draw for another mission.
We can pick the same one!
- We can pick the same mission.
- That's right.
(This time, the mission lasts for 1 hour and 30 minutes.)
Seok Jin, you should draw.
(We have set up everything for the meal.)
(Let us enjoy our meal for 1 hour and 30 minutes.)
Green, six.
- That's my schedule.
- Green, six.
- It's foot volleyball.
- Foot volleyball.
- We'll play on an empty stomach?
- Seriously? What about the food?
You can just play foot volleyball.
You will play foot volleyball for an hour and a half.
I don't want to. No!
I don't want to play it.
It's our retreat. Why must we?
- We'll starve to death then.
- Even if we do nothing...
You should at least give us some food if we play.
How can we play that for an hour and a half?
Let's try this then.
- Split into teams, and play it.
- We can eat ramyeon.
The winning team will have 10 minutes to go out.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay, okay.
- You can go out.
- Okay.
- I like that idea.
Split into 2 teams of 4 freely.
(Team White: Jong Kook, Se Chan, Seok Jin, and So Min)
(Team Black: Haha, Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo.)
(Play foot volleyball for 1 hour and 30 minutes.)
(Which team will win a chance to go out for 10 minutes?)
- Let's do the cheer.
- Let's do it.
- 1, 2, 3. We can do it!
- We can do it!
- Let's eat!
Hey, we are bound to win this match.
If we lose, we won't be able to eat.
- Let's have a break.
- You bet.
Which team will serve first?
We should play a game to decide that.
Let's play a game to decide.
- We should play a game for that.
- I'll start.
- I got it.
- We'll win anyway.
(Kwang Soo serves first.)
There you go. My gosh.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan make a play together.)
- Okay!
- We got it.
(Kicking)
- Okay!
- Let me explain what happened.
It happened because...
- Okay. We didn't start yet.
- Okay.
We did well. Yes!
- Take your time.
- Seok Jin.
We need to be careful of the ground.
- We can only kick it three times?
- Yes.
(She's new to foot volleyball.)
- Let's go!
- We're starting now.
I'll serve.
- How many points do we need to win?
- 10 points.
Seok Jin, move aside.
(He's in the way.)
You need to move away.
- You can't block the serve.
- I see.
The ball will hit your head then.
(The game starts.)
I see.
- Hurry, hurry.
- Nice.
- Wait.
- Just kick it over.
- That was strong.
- Nice!
(Jae Seok kicks it hard.)
- Okay.
- So Min. It's yours.
- Hit it with your head.
- So Min.
- There you go.
- It worked.
(Jumping)
- It's good.
- Well done.
(Did I do well?)
- Kick it smoothly. Se Chan.
- Well done.
Kick it smoothly. That's it.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo.
(Everyone stops. What happened?)
- You can't catch it.
- Let him kick next time.
- That's not how you play it.
- Nice.
- Yes!
- Was that a violation of the rules?
- Are we playing dodgeball or what?
- Is this dodgeball?
(Teasing)
(We got one point.)
- You're teasing us?
- Yes, we ought to.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- Really? Okay. Fine.
- We got a point.
- I see how it is.
- You weaklings
Let's kick the ball to Ji Hyo.
- Don't let it bother you, Ji Hyo.
- I got it.
- Kick it back.
- Okay.
Nice serve.
(Jong Kook from Team White serves the ball.)
- Nice serve.
- Great.
It's out!
- It's out. Okay!
- It's out.
(Is it really out?)
That's all right.
- Because it was over the line?
- Okay!
(Okay. The psychological warfare begins. I'm going to tease them.)
Okay.
(Pulling up)
(Se Chan gets back at Jae Seok.)
(Ji Hyo comes to aid.)
(She teases them by getting on the net.)
- Ji Hyo, stop it.
- Why?
- Why should I?
- Seriously.
- Ji Hyo, get off the net.
- She's crazy.
Why?
(She can't hold back her celebratory gesture.)
- Get off.
- She's crazy.
- Why can't I do that?
- What are you doing?
(The score is 1 to 1.)
- Let's go!
- Let's do this!
(Team Black serves.)
- I got it.
- It's over.
It's under control.
It's mine. So Min, you won't kick, right?
- No, I will.
- No, don't do it.
(She hesitates and rushes.)
I want to kick it.
So Min, it's yours.
(Se Chan kicks it over on So Min's behalf.)
Haha.
(Hitting lightly)
(Team Black loses a point due to the weak pass.)
- Okay.
- It took only one exchange.
(That's right. This is how it ought to be.)
(My gosh, they are getting on my nerves.)
(Team White leads 2 to 1.)
- I'll start.
- Okay.
There it goes.
Out.
(It goes out of the line.)
What's wrong with me?
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- Good job, Jong Kook.
(It's okay if it's Jong Kook.)
Wait, Jong Kook made mistakes twice while serving.
- Why doesn't someone else serve?
- It's okay.
You did well, Jong Kook.
- Is there anyone else?
- You lost two points because of...
- Don't worry about it.
- His bad serving.
- It's not your problem.
- Listen.
- Is this foot volleyball?
- What's wrong?
- We're having fun, so leave us.
(We're having fun. It's not your business.)
- We're having fun.
- That's right.
Isn't it harsh to tell us to leave?
- What do you mean?
- Come in.
- It's none of your business.
- Isn't he being too harsh?
- I've never heard that.
- It's not your business.
That was a good expression.
I made him confused.
We use that expression in my neighborhood.
"It's none of your business."
If the ball lands close, kick the ball, Se Chan.
It's mine.
- To the side.
- Person in the front should kick.
- It's mine.
- Get out of the way.
Shouldn't the person at the front kick?
That's good.
(Team White sends the ball over the net.)
- That's good.
- Kick it.
Jae Seok.
- Good job.
- It's mine.
(It's my ball.)
(He kicks.)
(It really hurts.)
He kicked himself.
Two touches!
I meant to...
I knew it.
(Look at how he moves.)
This is what's funny.
Only Jong Kook can kick the first ball.
(Only Jong Kook can kick the first ball.)
(He always kicks the first one.)
- It's how it is.
- Is it?
- No.
- Is that so?
Be quiet.
- I'm sorry but...
- Be quiet.
Shouldn't you kick if the ball lands closer?
- We did.
- When he ran forward,
- everyone got out of his way.
- This is so funny.
- I saw it.
- When Seok Jin tried to kick...
- They moved out of his way.
- Everyone's jaws dropped.
This is how you play.
- Don't be offended.
- You're right.
- Everyone has different skills.
- Of course.
(Team White gets ahead thanks to Jong Kook.)
- Let's play naturally.
- That was a great, short kick.
- Wait.
- It's Jong Kook's.
- There you go.
- I'll kick.
- You do it.
(She misses the ball.)
(Se Chan was prepared to kick it.)
All right, that's how it should go.
- This is good.
- We'll win.
Let's do it.
- So Min, say that it's yours.
- Good job.
- So Min.
- Say, "It's mine."
- There's Se Chan.
- Until the line...
- So Min, it's okay.
- There's Se Chan.
Go.
(Their scores are tied.)
I got it.
Get ready, So Min.
- It's yours.
- It's okay.
- Did it work?
- That's good.
Wait.
- Wait.
- Go, Ji Hyo.
- Come on, Seok Jin.
- It's done.
(He grits his teeth.)
- Seok Jin.
- I told you to leave it.
The ball landed here. How could I leave it?
In that case,
- if it landed there, - Goodness.
Just kick it lightly.
How much will you do when you're in the back?
- Seok Jin.
- What?
Why don't you make eye contact with Jong Kook after your mistake?
I'm looking at him right now.
(He looks at the empty space near him.)
(Team White falls behind by 1 point.)
- That's good.
- Good.
- It's late.
- Nice.
- Be careful. It'll be hard.
- Kick it.
That's right.
(He makes a strong kick.)
There you go.
(Seok Jin kicks the ball.)
(People are surprised by him.)
There you go.
(He saves the ball quickly.)
(It hits his face.)
(The ball hits the front of his face.)
- Oh, no.
- Poor Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
Are you okay?
I feel terrible for him.
- What's going on?
- Please take out the scene.
Did it scratch your face?
It really hurts.
- Are you okay?
- You're red.
I thought you took off the glasses to sleep.
I thought you were crying with your glasses off.
- They're upside down.
- Take them off. You have no lenses.
(Seok Jin with glasses can't kick the ball.)
You should put something on the nose.
I uploaded a photo of me and my father on social network.
Half of the people thought it's Seok Jin.
(They look similar.)
That's what I thought.
- Seriously?
- My dad was born in 1943.
Is that your father?
Is it your father in the photo?
- Yes.
- Isn't it Seok Jin?
- It's my dad.
- He's 23 years older than me.
(Team White: 3 points, Team Black: 5 points.)
That's funny.
It doesn't matter at all.
- Haha.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook serves.)
Go and kick it.
(Haha hits the ball.)
Go and kick it. Kick it over the net.
(Jae Seok sends it to Kwang Soo.)
- Let's go.
- It went over.
Come to me, So Min.
- It's okay. Good job.
- Go.
(Seok Jin hits the ball with the back of his head.)
That's good.
(Se Chan suddenly spikes the ball.)
You're doing well, Se Chan.
It's now.
(Haha hits it again.)
- Okay.
- Kick it.
(She misses.)
Don't do anything.
Just stay still.
- I told you to say, "It's mine."
- Give the signal.
I thought...
That was good.
I was ready to kick, but you changed its direction.
It fell on me.
- The ball fell on me.
- It's okay.
- Let's go.
(Haha serves the ball.)
All right.
(Jong Kook receives the ball safely.)
(Kicking)
Try it, So Min.
(The ball finally goes to So Min.)
(It's a golden opportunity.)
- It's mine.
- Try it.
(It's mine.)
(Team White: 3 points, Team Black: 7 points.)
- Hey.
- Say, "It's mine".
Say it before kicking.
What's the point of saying it after kicking?
(He shouts angrily.)
Why would you say it while kicking?
Say it before kicking.
That's how you get the ball.
It's not a shout.
"It's mine," isn't a shout.
- "It's mine."
- It means you'll kick.
- I thought you were shouting.
- Let's go.
- It's mine.
- It means that you'll kick it.
- Let's go.
When is foot volleyball over?
When is it over?
(She has trouble with the phrase.)
(Jong Kook serves.)
You did a very good job.
- There it goes.
- So Min.
That's right, Ji Hyo.
That's right.
(Ji Hyo's...)
(Ji Hyo's powerful spike)
- That was amazing.
- That was great.
- That's right.
- How did you do it?
- You play so well.
- Seriously.
- My heart is about to burst.
- Ji Hyo is good.
What's going on?
(The score gap gets wider.)
That was great.
(Jong Kook serves nicely.)
This looks pretty.
- Go.
- Can we do that?
- Hurry.
- This is difficult.
- It's hard for Kwang Soo.
- Ji Hyo.
(He sends it to Ji Hyo.)
- It'll be hard for Ji Hyo.
- Go.
(With her sharp smash, she sends the ball to Jong Kook.)
She plays well.
- It's out.
- It'll be hard for Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo's spear...)
(pierces into Jong Kook's shield.)
- You play well, Ji Hyo.
- You're the best.
(It's out.)
- You play well, Ji Hyo.
- It's my fault.
- I know it's my fault.
- Look at that.
(It's Jong Kook who made a mistake.)
(Everyone except Jong Kook feels guilty.)
(Let's do better since it's my fault.)
- You play well, Ji Hyo.
- No one says anything.
- What's going on?
- It's my fault.
No one says anything.
What's going on?
Why are you looking at me?
Why are you looking at me without saying anything?
- It's my fault.
- He admits that it's his mistake.
- Why are you looking at me?
- We can't get angry at him.
- He made a mistake.
- How can we say anything...
when he admits that he made a mistake?
How can we say anything?
I'm frustrated. I haven't looked at him in the eye for 20 minutes.
Be quiet, and let's play.
Let's go.
We got it.
Kick it over.
- That's right.
- Se Chan.
Kick it over.
Okay.
That's nice.
(Due to Jong Kook and Se Chan...)
My goodness.
Okay, it's out.
The scores are tied.
This is match point.
- Let's give it a try.
- I'm too excited.
- Okay.
- We can do it.
It's neck and neck.
Let's play.
(Kwang Soo serves.)
To this side. Nice.
(Kwang Soo serves well.)
Get closer, So Min.
(Jong Kook receives it with stability.)
Kick it over right away.
- Kick it over.
Just kick it over.
(They react to the attack.)
- That was good.
- Jae Seok, kick it.
Nice.
(Jae Seok's strong spike)
(Seok Jin plays defense.)
That's good. It's mine.
- Se Chan.
- Kick it over.
Okay.
(It's a strong spike.)
- That's good.
- Get ready.
- That's right.
- Send it.
(He tries to hit it, )
(but it is too far.)
- What do we do?
- Kwang Soo.
- Seriously.
I tried my best.
(The final score is 10 to 9.)
What did you think?
My spike was strong, wasn't it?
- You did it.
- We won.
- Okay.
- Did we win?
(Team White wins 10 minutes of free time.)
We're too good for them.
- We're too good for them.
- I agree.
- Okay.
- We were so close.
- I'm sorry.
Team White gets 10 minutes of free time.
You may eat.
(10-minute break starts.)
- What about us?
- Shouldn't...
only Jong Kook and Se Chan go?
Come here, So Min.
(Misty Time 1)
From now on,
- Misty Time.
- Misty Time will start.
- Okay.
- That's right.
The staff prepared Misty Time...
to give you a special chance.
(The staff prepared something special.)
Do we get exemptions?
What is it?
- What could it be?
- Many badges might depend on it.
My battery is already... I didn't mean battery.
- Seok Jin...
- My goodness.
Goodness.
(They're surprised.)
- What is it?
- They're here.
(What is this music?)
- It's Twice.
- It's a girl group.
- Who are they?
- All of them are here.
(In the shortest time, their music video is viewed by 50 million.)
(K-pop phenomenon, Twice)
(Twice is here.)
- Hey.
- Nice to see you.
Sana.
Momo.
Get out of the way. They have to perform.
- I love your song.
- They have to perform.
Twice is here again.
- I love you.
- Twice
Twice
(We love Twice.)
Here we go.
- Hey.
- Let's go!
(Cheerful)
(The nine girls want to know what love is.)
(What is love?)
I love it.
Yes!
(The whole team is here.)
(Yes!)
- Twice!
- Twice rocks!
(Welcome)
It's comforting.
By the way,
they're here to celebrate Se Chan and So Min's anniversary.
They even gave a performance.
Congratulations.
(Thank you, Twice.)
They came for you?
- Twice is very busy.
- Right.
Every time they make a comeback,
- they attract so much attention.
- It's incredible.
- It's their eighth hit.
- Really?
- 100 million views.
- It's amazing.
Their music video attracted 100 million views.
Last time, we met in Busan a year ago.
- Please introduce yourselves.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3.
- One in a million.
- Hello, we're Twice.
(They're so cute.)
- Can we hear...
- What?
Sana say, "cheese gimbap"?
- Please say it.
- Not now.
- I want to hear it.
- It's not the right time.
- Our viewers want to hear it too.
- Be quiet.
- Let's hear it.
- Right now...
- It's very cute.
Let's hear it.
- They need to introduce themselves.
- It's really cute.
Let them introduce themselves.
Why do you decide?
(Let them introduce themselves.)
(Why do you decide?)
Move!
- What are you doing?
- Calm down.
What are you doing?
- I mean...
- What is this?
- Everyone wants to hear it.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
Everyone is glaring at you.
- It's really cute.
- Hold on.
Are you all glaring at me because of cheese gimbap?
- You want to hear it, right?
- Yes.
- Make some noise!
- Yes!
Yes!
- See?
- Seriously.
Gosh, he never listens.
- Then Sana, can you say, "cheese gimbap"?
- Sure.
Please count down for me.
- 1, 2, 3, start.
- Then Sana, can you say, "cheese gimbap"?
- Sure.
Please count down for me.
- 1, 2, 3, start.
Cheese gimbap.
(Cheese gimbap)
I don't know what it is, but I like it.
(I don't know what it is, but I like it.)
"Cheese gimbap".
(Let me try.)
She's just being cute.
So Min, can you do it?
Say, "fart gimbap". "Fart gimbap".
Pretend you're farting. Try it. "Fart gimbap".
- What?
- Stop it.
- Try it.
"Fart gimbap".
- Fart gimbap.
- Fart.
(Fart gimbap)
- Fart too.
- Fart.
- Fart - Fart
(Cheese gimbap for Twice, fart gimbap for Running Man)
(Farting)
She's accepted it.
Anyway, "What is Love?" is...
their new song.
It has some unique dance moves.
Could one of you teach us?
Sure. Momo will teach you.
- Okay.
- Momo will teach us.
- Momo...
As you're wondering about love...
- A question mark.
- Okay.
"Where is my love?"
(What is love?)
- What is love?
- You need a dot.
We don't have much time. Let's speed up.
Start.
(What is love?)
All right. Next.
- Next?
- Yes.
You're wondering this time too.
We can do hard ones too.
- A more difficult one.
- We can do it.
They look down on us.
- I saw something like this.
- This is too...
This is not exactly a dance move.
- Please teach us something else.
- We can do it.
There's something like this.
- That's too difficult.
- It is?
- That's too...
- Not this?
We want something in the middle.
Between the 1st one and the 2nd one...
How about this?
- That's nice.
- That's perfect.
I like that kind of dance moves.
- I think we can do that.
- Okay.
We can do that.
Right after that, you make a question mark.
How?
(Flapping)
That's nice. Good job.
(What is love?)
He's so cute.
So Min used to be a singer.
- That's not true.
- She was a trainee.
- Try it.
- Start.
(Fart song)
(Farting)
(What is a fart?)
All right. We've...
heard from Twice briefly.
Now... Are they flies?
(You punks!)
(Get away!)
Are they crazy?
- How dare...
- Kwang Soo.
- What are they doing?
- Flies...
(He's so tough.)
Look at Kwang Soo.
(I'll kill you all.)
(Laughing)
We'll play a simple game...
- with Twice.
- Really?
Twice wrote down nine talents.
- We'll pick two of them.
- Sounds good.
Including a mission, there will be three rounds.
The winning team of each round can choose one member...
- who will get 2 penalty badges.
- 2?
(2 penalty badges)
Two?
1 person gets 2 badges?
The winning team decides who will get two badges.
It means you need to divide into teams.
We'll decide the partners...
- by drawing spoons.
- Okay.
There are different colors. Some teams will consist of...
- only girls.
- Only girls.
Also, one team will have three members.
Okay? Twice, please draw a spoon each.
(Twice starts drawing spoons.)
Blue.
- Purple.
- I like everyone.
(Teams)
The rest of you...
(It's Team Running Man's turn.)
- Please draw a spoon each.
- It's important.
Seok Jin's partner will be decided.
(Nervous)
- Don't draw a pink spoon.
- Seok Jin.
No pink spoon.
- Yellow-green.
(Seok Jin draws a yellow-green spoon.)
(Who has a yellow-green spoon?)
(She pops out.)
Chae Young.
Her smile looks sad.
Right now...
(Poor Chae Young.)
It's time to work.
- You should work hard.
- I'm happy.
Work hard, Chae Young.
- Haha.
- I'm friends with everyone.
- Blue.
(Haha draws a blue spoon.)
- Me.
- We were partners last time too.
(Jeong Yeon)
(Puzzled)
(We were partners last time too.)
(We were?)
(I don't remember well.)
It's so embarrassing.
- Maybe you weren't.
- Stop being so clingy.
- Gosh.
- I...
I hate this kind of thing.
What's with him?
- Are you doing well?
- Yes.
Nice to see you.
- Next.
- Okay.
(Kwang Soo)
- Purple.
(Me)
- Hello.
- They don't like each other.
- That's not true.
- It shows.
- You don't like me?
- It shows too much.
- I like you.
- She likes me.
- Are you okay? Mina.
- Yes?
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm good.
Whom did you want to be partners with?
- By the way...
- What's so wrong with me?
What?
(Teams)
Let's see what talents they wrote.
Twice members wrote them down, right?
- Things they're good at.
- Yes.
Let me pick one.
Okay.
Let's check this one.
(What is the first talent?)
Who wrote, "Cute Acrostic Poem"?
- Who wrote it?
The one who said, "cheese gimbap"?
- Sana?
- Did Sana write it?
- "Cheese gimbap"?
- I wrote it.
(Shy)
Na Yeon?
(Na Yeon's Cute Acrostic Poem)
Not everyone can pull it off.
It doesn't suit everyone.
You can't beat Sana.
- Na Yeon, will you start?
- Okay.
We'll try "Kim Jong Kook".
- Kim Jong Kook?
- "Kook" would be difficult.
- Okay.
Here we go. "Kim Jong Kook".
"Kim".
I want some kimchi fried rice.
(I want some kimchi fried rice.)
This is what she means.
She's good. She's very expressive.
Good. Continue.
"Jong".
I want to eat it with Jong Kook.
Oh, dear.
(This is driving me insane.)
- This is real.
- This is the last one.
She's getting ready for it.
"Kook".
("Kook")
(She makes cute, baby noises.)
How are you supposed to beat that?
(She's speechless.)
I've never seen her like that.
Remember I said...
I was an expert in retreats?
She's an expert in being cute.
- That's true.
- Goodness.
I think she should be selected as a living cultural asset.
She was incredible.
Let's continue.
Who would like to challenge her? If there's nobody, we win.
Ji Hyo can do it too.
- Ji Hyo can do this?
- She's ready.
- Can you do it, Ji Hyo?
- Yes.
All right.
What is the word?
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook's name.
Me again?
(This acrostic poem is dedicated to Jong Kook.)
Why am I not Lee Kwang Kook?
Too bad I'm not Lee Kwang Kook.
- "Kim".
- Go to him.
Please tell me you're going to make me kimchi fried rice.
(Please tell me you're going to make me kimchi fried rice.)
- What was that?
- She's good.
- What did she just do?
- Goodness. Look at her face.
I hate it.
Twice members hate it.
Why?
It's "Jong" next.
Jong Kook?
- Oh, gosh.
- "Kook".
(Promise me.)
(She's so cute.)
Oh, dear.
Oh, my.
I wasn't going to say this,
but when Na Yeon started,
Ji Hyo said, "What is wrong with her?"
(Ji Hyo transformed.)
Kimchi fried rice.
(He twists his body.)
(When it was Na Yeon's turn...)
What is wrong with her?
(What is wrong with her?)
Momo...
- got really mad too, - Gosh.
But she's practicing right now.
(This is more competitive than they thought.)
It's funny seeing her practice.
Did you see that? This is a very close match.
For ours,
Jong Kook will be talking to Momo on the phone.
- Really?
- Is that part of the acrostic poem?
- We'll use Momo's name.
- Momo's name?
This is a tough day for Jong Kook.
"Mo".
- Hello?
- Hello.
- "Mo".
- Momo would like kimchi fried rice.
(Momo would like kimchi fried rice.)
- Hold on.
- One kimchi fried rice, please.
Is this a kimchi fried rice special?
- Did you open a restaurant?
- Sorry?
Yes, I opened a restaurant.
- She ordered.
- It's for delivery.
Is it for delivery?
- It's a delivery application.
- One more, please.
We'll hurry.
Good job.
Who's next?
- Would you like to try?
- Do whatever you want.
- Would you like to?
- Yes.
- I'll use my partner's name.
- Really?
- Haha or Dong Hoon?
- Haha.
This one better be good.
- "Ha".
Ha Dong Hoon!
- Don't do it.
(Let's don't do it.)
(He takes her back.)
- That was cute.
- That was.
Let's focus.
That was cute.
Wasn't that cute?
Wasn't she good?
- Do you want to try, Sana?
- Okay.
- Jae Seok, Sana is ready.
- I'll do it.
- Jae Seok.
- Sana wants to try?
- Is it Jong Kook's name?
- Sana.
- Sana?
- Your own name?
You're going to use your own name?
- She has a partner.
- Or Se...
- It's possible.
- It's fine.
- She's advertising herself.
- Right.
Sana. "Sa".
What's love?
- I'm curious.
- "Na".
I think it's you.
(I think it's you.)
(This is driving me nuts.)
(What is wrong with her?)
They're going nuts.
What do I do? Is this even possible?
Is this possible?
(Sana is a strong candidate for 1st place with her acrostic poem.)
What about you, Tzuyu?
Jong Kook can do it too.
What would you like to use?
- I'll use my name.
- Tzuyu?
It won't be easy.
It's hard.
"Tzu".
Tzuyu is...
(She uses her nasal voice.)
This is so nice. What now?
"Yu".
- I have a stomachache.
- Oh, no.
(I have a stomachache.)
Give her some medicine. Where's the medicine?
(Nobody has tried to act cute by having a stomachache.)
Medicine for stomachache.
That wasn't bad.
- Tzuyu has a stomachache.
- I know.
That breaks my heart.
(Smiling)
You are all good at acrostic poems.
- They can all do it.
- It's so natural.
She'll finish it off.
(Na Yeon will finish it off.)
(This was supposed to be her talent, so she'll end it off.)
Then we'll accept the loss.
- What would you like to use?
- I'll use...
Kwang Soo's name.
(I'll use Kwang Soo's name.)
- Kwang Soo?
- This will drive him insane.
- Let's start with "Lee".
- Okay.
- "Lee".
- From now on...
(From now on!)
- "Kwang".
- Kwang Soo will fall for me.
(Kwang Soo will fall for me.)
He's in trouble. He already fell for her.
Kwang Soo, you're in trouble.
- "Soo".
- Abracadabra.
(Screaming)
(Abracadabra!)
(What do I do?)
That was awesome. Why is she so good?
- I approve.
- Me too.
Good job. That was good.
Kwang Soo is in trouble.
- He fell in love.
- What should he do?
You need to wake up from the spell.
Look at Mina.
He went somewhere else.
Kwang Soo, Mina is mad at you.
Don't be.
That was great.
You're so good. I'm not joking.
Both of hers...
- were good.
- This is too good.
Team Jae Seok wins...
in Cute Acrostic Poem.
He picked a good one.
I'll pick a team who'll take these two stickers.
I have four right now.
If I give this person 2, he'll end up with 5.
(He's a strong candidate with 3 stickers.)
Right.
It'll go to him.
There might be somebody who's right behind me.
That sounds good.
I like the three-way battle.
You want to avoid coming last.
- That's right.
- You can't be last.
If you don't want to be last, you have to give them to Seok Jin.
That's not true.
Should I give three to Kwang Soo?
- Should I give three to Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo?
(Should I give 3 to Kwang Soo?)
Me?
I'm on your side. Jae Seok.
It'll be weird if Kwang Soo doesn't join this party.
No, Jae Seok. I only have one.
Okay, I'll give two to Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo wasn't worried, but he gets 2 penalty badges.)
Really?
- Okay.
- You have to win.
I have a goal now.
They're getting started.
They're getting started again. I'm sick of this.
- Let's do this.
- Okay, let's get started.
Let's do this.
Ji Hyo, would you like to pick the next one?
- Me?
- Yes.
(This game will decide who'll get 2 penalty badges.)
- I'll pick.
- What is it?
- I'll pick this one.
- Okay.
(The second game is Dance.)
- Dance.
- Good.
Dance.
(This is what they were hoping for.)
- The time has come.
- Is it any dancing?
Who wrote that?
Twice is all good at dancing.
- Momo.
- Is it Momo?
Momo is unrivaled.
What's this about?
Dancing.
(What do you think it is?)
- Is it any dancing?
- I know that.
(What's wrong?)
- Do you think we don't know?
- What else could it be?
I know it's dancing, but it's not just any dancing.
It's freestyle.
- Is it freestyle?
- Yes.
- Freestyle.
- Momo will start off.
If there's another team that's better than Momo...
- Right.
- Right?
Momo is so good.
Momo started dancing since she was three.
(She's so good.)
- Isn't that too young?
- I'm serious.
- You'll get hurt at three.
Do you remember dancing at three?
Yes.
If we're to rate this,
who are the best dancers in Twice? What do you think?
Momo is in first place, and everybody else is the same.
- Everybody else?
- Everybody else is the same?
She's unrivaled.
- Completely?
- Yes.
- Are you that good?
- No.
- Jeong Yeon whispered to me.
- What did she say?
- She's going to crush Momo.
- When did I say that?
(Jeong Yeon said she's going to crush Momo.)
(She's going to crush her?)
- She's going to rip her apart.
- Will you?
- When did I say that?
- She'll spin her three times.
Spin her around.
Then...
- let's see Momo dance first.
- Let's see.
- All right, Momo.
- Good luck.
(Good luck, partner.)
(She starts off by taking off her jacket.)
(She's so confident.)
Goodness.
- I love these kinds of dances.
- The song is...
She's so sexy.
(This dance contrasts her cute face.)
She's so good.
(She's so relaxed.)
She's good.
What was that?
(She shows off a body wave.)
You've changed a lot.
- She's really good.
- What is this?
(She's so good! How can we beat her?)
We can't win this.
When we meant dancing, we didn't mean this.
- This is professional dancing.
- Gosh, how can we beat her?
How can the other contestants dance after you're done?
- This is...
- She's good.
- Gosh.
- She's coming.
- We can win.
- We can beat her.
We can win thanks to Ji Hyo.
We can win now. We can win!
- We can beat them now.
- We can do it.
- This isn't too bad.
- It's over. We can do it now.
- You failed.
- We can do this.
(Swaying)
This isn't too bad.
What should I do?
- It's over now.
- Oh, my.
It's over now. We can win thanks to Ji Hyo.
(Despite the mean comments, she showed off her dancing skills.)
- You're really cool, Momo.
- She's so cool.
She's really good with rhythm.
- It was great.
- She's really good.
We'll change it into a couple dance game...
because she's too good.
If you count Ji Hyo's dance, we can win them.
(We can win if you include Ji Hyo's dance.)
We can win thanks to Ji Hyo.
- Their performance wasn't great.
- It was great.
- Really?
- It was.
It was an eyesore.
- Eyesore? Gosh.
- No.
- Gosh.
- If you're that confident,
you should try too.
We'll dance again at the end.
In that case, does that mean we just need to...
dance better than Ji Hyo and Momo?
We'll turn the music on.
Each team should dance together.
What do you mean you don't know? Just do it.
- All right.
- Music start.
Gosh, "Havana".
- We can't dance to this.
- We need to dance to this?
- This is...
- This is impossible.
Jeon So Min.
(You can't dance to this? Then I will.)
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- She's coming out.
They're coming out to the stage.
(She throws her hat...)
(and shows off her wave.)
She just did her iconic dance move.
(Here goes So Min's pelvic dance!)
Gosh.
(Swaying)
It's exactly the same.
(I'm dancing just like Ji Hyo, aren't I?)
Ji Hyo, you should go out to the front.
- What's So Min doing?
- What?
It's "Havana".
How can you dance like that to "Havana"?
(It's a collaboration of her weird expressions and swaying body.)
What is that dance move?
- What is she doing?
- Gosh.
It's "Havana".
- It's better.
- Good.
Let's go. Let's have Mina next.
- Let's go.
- Mina.
Let's have Mina first.
It's Mina.
(Mina, )
(I'm going out too.)
(His long and useless body flaps wildly.)
What is that?
(Flapping)
(Visual shock)
- What is that?
- Gosh, what is that?
It's a human-faced bird.
(It's the last surviving human-faced bird.)
(It's a huge creature that measures 190cm. It represents peace.)
Gosh.
It's a human-faced bird.
It's a huge bird that has the face of a man.
(Flapping in joy and happiness while celebrating peace in Korea)
(You didn't need to come out to the stage, Kwang Soo.)
She's so pretty.
The Running Man members should come out after the Twice members.
If we come out from the start, it just becomes a huge mess.
(The Running Man members ruin the stage.)
All right.
- We want to see Twice first.
- Stay put, Kwang Soo.
I was just following her.
- We'll see Twice's dancing, - Yes!
And then we'll have you join them.
That's right.
You're good at emceeing.
And I don't think this dance fits "Havana".
(So Min, this dance doesn't fit the song.)
You should zoom in on her facial expression.
She was so into it.
What is that?
She usually...
- She usually dances like that.
- Gosh.
That's how she dances.
Why does she do that?
Play the music again.
(We'll start the music again.)
What is this song?
- First, - Da Hyun.
Da Hyun.
- She's going out.
- Da Hyun.
- She's really good at funny dances.
- Really?
- She's so brazen.
- Gosh.
You need to dance by yourself.
- She's good.
- She looks really cool.
She's good at dancing.
She's becoming one with the music.
- Gosh.
- She's good.
- What's that?
- Da Hyun's doing great.
- She's great.
It's so cool.
Good.
It's cool but also refined.
She wants you to join her.
- What are you looking at?
What's she looking at?
- Da Hyun.
(She's staring at the sky as if she's possessed.)
- It's coming!
- Let's go!
(Energetic)
(She rules the stage with her energetic dance moves.)
- What's that?
- This is really good.
This is the best.
- She has a weird facial expression!
- It's really good.
It's so cool.
- What is this?
- Da Hyun.
- Gosh.
- What are you?
(This is not the end.)
What is that?
What are you doing?
- What is that?
- Gosh.
- Look at her.
- Hey!
- Gosh.
- Gosh, it's so cool.
Look.
She's really good.
(She's like a dance machine.)
Gosh.
Da Hyun is really great.
- Gosh.
- She's like a squid.
- What's she looking at?
- What are you?
Da Hyun, what were you looking at?
- Do you see ghosts?
- Do you?
Da Hyun.
- What were you looking at?
- I've never seen a possessed dance.
I was really surprised.
(Her eyes look lost as if she's possessed.)
All right. You can go back, Da Hyun.
- That was cool.
- Did you see that?
- She's good.
- It was a difficult music too.
- It's difficult.
- It is.
Let's go to the next person. Music, please.
(The next music is...)
("Fire" by BTS.)
(I need to dance to this.)
It's not for couple dancing.
- It's not for couple dancing.
- Why do you keep coming out?
Wait.
- It's not for couple dancing.
- "Fire".
(I'm sorry for coming out again, but I need to dance to this.)
This is a song for Da Hyun.
(She imitates the exact dance moves by being possessed by BTS.)
- She memorized everything.
- Gosh.
She can do everything.
- She's so good.
- What is she?
Momo, you're in danger.
- I am.
- You are.
Wait.
Da Hyun.
I get that you like dancing, but stop coming out to the stage.
(I'm sorry, but please stop.)
- Others should get a chance too.
- I couldn't stop myself.
It was supposed to be a couple dance,
but she's trying to stand out by herself.
- She goes out by herself.
- But...
- this doesn't have to be.
- Really?
Momo is the one who said it was her specialty,
but Da Hyun was the best so far.
- Da Hyun was really good.
- No.
She's by far the best.
- Okay.
- The others should try too.
- Momo, get ready.
If you think you can do it, you can come out again, Da Hyun.
- Give us the music.
- This is so fun.
Momo, if you think you can do it, you should try.
(I can dance to this song.)
Oh, my.
"Gashina".
(Why do you leave pretty Momo here?)
(She's doing Sun Mi's dance moves perfectly to get first place.)
She looks so cool.
(It really is her specialty.)
Da Hyun came out too.
(Da Hyun is dancing again.)
She went down further.
- Gosh.
- Look at her back folding.
Gosh.
(Satisfied)
It's over. It's over now.
- She's doing great.
- Wait.
- She's great.
- Excuse me.
- It's over.
- Excuse me. Can you stop the music?
Wait.
(What was that?)
She shot the gun down here.
- Hey.
- She went all the way down.
After she went down, Momo shot Da Hyun.
- She shot Da Hyun.
- Momo became a little angry.
- She shot her.
- It's going wild.
(Da Hyun, how can you do this?)
(She shoots.)
- Gosh, she shot her.
- It was a weapon.
- Momo is angry too.
- She's the best.
Da Hyun and Momo are doing great.
But others like Na Yeon have their chances too.
Chae Young, you shouldn't stay still.
- You two should rest.
- All right.
(Momo and Da Hyun need to take a rest!)
Tie them up. They're so good.
- Mina can see ghosts too.
- What?
(My partner can be possessed too.)
- Mina can see ghosts too.
- All right.
Na Yeon is getting ready too.
Give us the music.
- It's "Nice".
- It's Seventeen's song.
"Nice".
Who's going to go first?
Jeong Yeon?
- Jeong Yeon.
- Go.
- Let's go, Jeong Yeon.
- She's going.
(She's starting to dance.)
What's this? What is this?
(Doggy dance?)
You don't need to be funny.
- I can't do this.
- You don't need to do that.
I can't win them.
- Do something cool.
- Jeong Yeon and Haha are out.
- No!
- You're out!
We were going to do something cool.
- Out!
- How can we beat them?
- We can't win.
- How can you do a doggy dance?
- How?
- It's really hard.
- Just wait a little.
- That was too much.
Give us the next music.
It's hard.
- What's this?
- It sounds cool.
(They're hesitating because of the cool music.)
Do you want to try? Do you want to go?
Chae Young is going.
(Chae Young goes out to the stage.)
- Gosh.
- That's good.
- It's hammer dance.
Hammer dance.
She's good.
(She's doing well too.)
Gosh.
That's right.
(Should I try too?)
(Powerful break dance)
That's great, Na Yeon.
That's it. Go on.
(She fights against Chae Young's hammer dance with her break dance.)
Use your arms.
Sana!
- That's right.
- Sana!
Sana!
(Right)
This is the newest dance move.
(That's the trendy dance.)
(I want to try too.)
(Dancing left and right)
(Speeding up)
Gosh.
(Going full speed)
They are giving it their all.
- Ji Hyo, go!
- My goodness.
- Mina, let's go!
- Ji Hyo!
Let's go!
(Ji Hyo and Mina shyly go out to dance.)
Mina!
(Mina dances shyly at first.)
(Then she suddenly transforms into a middle-aged man.)
What is that?
Mina, you don't have to do that!
What is Mina doing?
(Although she doesn't have to, Mina tries hard.)
- Thank you, Mina.
- She can dance well.
I was so surprised.
- She didn't have to do that.
- I was taken by surprise.
- She is tying her shoelaces.
(Momo ties her shoelaces.)
- No, no.
- Look at Momo.
She has never danced to this kind of music.
- I know.
- Yes, I have.
All right. Music, start.
They are really good.
(What is this song with a familiar intro?)
It's "Bboom Bboom".
- Na Yeon!
- What? Momo stepped forward again.
(It's "Bboom Bboom" by Momoland.)
(My goodness.)
(I should stop dancing.)
Let's go!
(Momo and Da Hyun are addicted to dancing.)
(Bboom bboom)
- Hold on.
- Did you see that?
They are like shamans.
(The shamans who can dance well perform an exorcism.)
All right.
(The audience channels the spirit as well.)
(Momo and Da Hyun's rendezvous)
Where are they looking at?
Da Hyun is leading.
Da Hyun has a good strategy.
Come back. Come back.
- Everyone.
- I need to stop.
- My goodness.
- I am sorry.
- I can tell that Momo...
- She can dance well.
Has danced for many years.
- However, Da Hyun...
- She grabs my attention.
Is getting a lot of points.
Da Hyun channeled a spirit.
You are right.
It's time to wrap up.
This round will determine the last winner.
Here comes Jeong Yeon.
- Music, please.
- It can be anything.
Just dance cheerfully.
- Let's go.
There goes Chae Young.
(I must dance.)
Da Hyun! Da Hyun! Hold on.
(Momo and Da Hyun, the dance addicts, step forward.)
- There goes Chae Young.
- Momo!
- Da Hyun! Da Hyun! Hold on.
- Hey.
(She becomes a human fan.)
Come on.
- I have to do this!
- Come on.
Let Chae Young dance!
They are unstoppable.
(They are in a trance.)
(I have to do this dance.)
(Momo takes over the stage.)
(The human fan moves her arms at 200km per second.)
Momo.
Hey.
(Da Hyun channels the spirit of a dancing ghost once more.)
Someone stop her!
(No one can stop Momo and Da Hyun.)
- In this round, - They are hilarious.
- Momo is the winner.
- They are incredible.
- Momo's arms moved quickly.
- Momo.
You should hold them back!
She ran out before I could do anything.
- Look at that.
- Where is the manager?
- Her arms move quickly.
- I had to dance.
I had to dance to that song.
How do your arms move so quickly? Do it again, Momo.
How do they move so quickly?
Do you spin your arms like that?
It looks like Momo can't stand to lose.
(It looks like Momo can't stand to lose.)
She's so serious.
Da Hyun and Momo,
you don't win by taking the stage.
I want to know if Tzuyu is having fun.
(I want to know if Tzuyu is having fun.)
- Tzuyu.
- Hold on.
Her stomach hurts.
Oh, is that why?
I couldn't help minding Tzuyu.
Tzuyu didn't dance, did she?
- She didn't dance.
Tzuyu, don't you regret it?
I am not confident about dancing.
- You are not confident.
- Her stomach hurts.
- Her stomach?
- Now, we will decide on...
the winning team.
The members of Running Man will vote.
This is hard.
I am tallying the votes.
- Now...
- What is that?
Jae Seok, what are you doing with your fingers?
(Hold on.)
- What do you mean?
- Your fingers!
Who has 2 votes, and who has 3 votes?
(You can tell the current score from his fingers.)
Jae Seok, what do you think you are doing?
- Jae Seok.
- This is...
The national MC shouldn't be like this.
The national MC should memorize the numbers.
My fingers tally the votes automatically.
Can't you memorize the numbers?
The national MC shouldn't be like this.
Must you use your fingers?
- My goodness.
- He can't memorize the numbers.
My fingers tally the votes automatically.
- What is this?
- Momo is the winner.
(Momo wins.)
You did well.
(The youngest member shows her cute acts.)
(I am cuter.)
(The 2nd war of cuteness breaks out.)
(Their greed...)
(knows no bounds.)
(They make an ordinary trip special.)
(1-year anniversary, my foot.)
(How will this retreat come to an end?)
(Finally)
(The Family Project faces its grand finale.)
(The package finally gets decided.)
(Secret doors are placed before them.)
(When the doors open, )
(they must leave to somewhere.)
Please.
(They bet their fates on the final mission.)
(If they don't stay alert, )
(their fates will change.)
(What lies at the end of this extraordinary trip?)
- 2.
- 3.
(Family Project Finale: Secret Doors)