(Last week)
(The members ended up at Incheon International Airport.)
(What? Global Random Tour?)
(No one can predict when and where they will go on their trip.)
You want us to call the guests we want to take on our trip?
(It gets worse. They must invite their own travel companions.)
(They boarded the fastest flights available with guests they invited.)
(Three teams head to Daema Island, Thailand, and Okinawa.)
(The rule with step counters makes the mission harder than it is.)
(The team with the highest, accumulated number will lose.)
(1 member from the losing team will pick 1 member to join the penalty.)
That means we shouldn't walk a lot.
(Okinawa)
Discuss among yourselves, and choose a dish you want to eat in Okinawa.
- Steak. - Steak.
(If a local recommends them steak, their mission is accomplished.)
(I'd like to recommend soba.)
(Thus began the curse of soba and ramen.)
(Every time they asked, locals recommended them soba or ramen.)
(They must eat the recommended dish to try again.)
(The fetters of noodles look like they can't be broken.)
(Their flight is at hand. Their last mission is to find a Higa.)
(They managed to find a Higa. What did she recommend?)
(She recommended ramen again.)
(They fail their mission, and 1,000 steps are added to their counters.)
(Daema Island)
We can just eat this?
(As soon as they arrived, they got to enjoy a feast of fresh seafood.)
(However,)
(they must catch every type of fish 1 of the members ate.)
(Per species they fail to catch, 1,000 steps will be added.)
(They set out in the morning to catch 8 types of fish Haha ate.)
(Team Love Triangle's morning fishing began at sunrise.)
(Kwang Soo caught a smallscale blackfish.)
You succeeded in catching a smallscale blackfish.
(It becomes a battle of pride between Kwang Soo and Haha.)
(Will they be able to catch the rest of 7 species?)
(Thailand)
(Team Between Friends will do Thailand's Specialty Tour.)
(They must spin the globe and accomplish 1 to 4 missions.)
(Every time they fail a mission, 1,000 steps will be added.)
(And they chose 3 missions to do.)
(For the first mission, they must beat Sunday in a painting contest.)
(The result is that Team Between Friends lost by a landslide.)
(Since they failed the mission, Shorry gets 1,000 steps.)
(Team Between Friends heads to Bangkok for the second mission.)
- All right. - Yes, Jong Kook.
- We ended up... - It was close.
losing by a close margin.
- That elephant did so well. - Sunday did an excellent job.
- So we lost. - We can't always win.
- That's right. - It's good as long as we had fun.
- That's right. - Missions aren't that important.
- That's right. - Let's complete the last two, okay?
- That's right. - We can complete those missions.
- Thanks to this show, we get to... - Are we in the army?
- Are we in the army? - spend time...
He's the drill sergeant, and we are the recruits.
- We... - The red cap means he's a sergeant.
- We can have similar... - Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir! - numbers on our step counters.
- Yes, sir! - We are in this together, you know.
- Yes, sir! - Let's prepare for that.
- Yes, sir. - We have two more missions left.
- We will finish the missions, sir. - We should start the missions.
- Let's have fun and finish strong. - Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, let's give this a shot.
- First of all, she's waiting. - Okay.
I had no idea that I would get to meet her in Thailand.
This is amazing.
(He shouts all of a sudden.)
- I think it was all meant to be. - It's all thanks to you, sir.
- Wait, that sounded too made up. - Hold on.
Hear me out. Who would shout like this when someone talks?
- He's right. He has a point. - "That's great!"
- Come on. Seriously, Shorry. - That was bad, Shorry.
- Honestly, it was terrible. - That was a valid point.
- We can do it again. - You did a good job.
Let's do another take.
Let's go and meet her.
- Yes! - Yes!
Let's have a jolly, good time!
(Let's have a jolly, good time!)
What was that?
(He is the king of forced reactions.)
How awkward!
That was too much.
"Let's have a jolly, good time!"
(They reminisce about the 90s with an outdated expression.)
(They drive for a long time...)
(and arrive in Bangkok.)
(The location of the second mission, Bangkok Night Market)
(It's the number 1 hot place with a view of Chao Phraya River.)
(You can find all kinds of Thai food here.)
(It's the center of the culture that includes fashion and rides.)
(Can they succeed the mission in the romantic night market?)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(They decide to do the mission after dinner.)
(There is an array of Thai dishes for Team Between Friends.)
The curry is tasty. Crab curry.
This dish tastes like chicken.
(Tom yum kung, crab curry, and chili Japanese sea bass)
Eating food reminds me that I am in Thailand.
We have a guest coming.
What's taking our guest so long?
(Food is very tasty,)
(but why isn't the guest coming?)
What's taking our guest so long?
Did you receive a text?
(It's about time.)
The guest is here.
(The guest...)
- The guest is here. - The guest is here.
(these four men eagerly waited for is...)
(Son Na Eun of Apink)
(Son Na Eun, the fairy, appears.)
(Na Eun was in Thailand for family vacation.)
(She promised to meet at the night market.)
(Who knew she would actually come to the night market?)
Na Eun!
(He tidies up his appearance.)
Come inside.
- Hello. - Na Eun.
Your outfit is similar to ours.
- She is so cute. - Thank you for coming.
- Thank you. - I can't believe this coincidence.
I know.
We ordered more dishes for you.
I am so touched she spared us time during family vacation.
I am so thankful.
She is so nice.
Na Eun, eat up. These dishes are delicious.
You will be surprised. These dishes are delicious.
I didn't use this fork.
- It's new. - Thank you for the food.
- Try this. - I think it's crab.
- That's right. - Crab curry.
- What is it? - I think it will work.
(He is talking about inviting a Thai celebrity.)
- Is she coming? - I think she is here.
- Where? - Here?
- I think she is nearby. - Really?
- Should I go and find her? - That's a good idea.
Would it be okay for me to go out?
I will be back.
- Do it right. - Okay, Jong Kook.
(It's amazing that their guests are Na Eun and a Thai celebrity.)
Where should I go?
I think she is nearby.
(He has to find a Thai celebrity in an unfamiliar night market.)
I will keep walking.
She has to be here somewhere.
(At Daema Island, Kwang Soo caught smallscale blackfish.)
Kwang Soo.
What else do we have to catch?
The rest of you should catch something like squid.
I will take care of the big ones.
I want to catch something.
(I really want to catch something.)
I really want to catch something.
This isn't an impossible task.
(Kwang Soo patronizes them for 30 minutes.)
I will try harder.
The thing is,
ships in Korea drops two anchors on the sides...
while ships in Japan drops one anchor at the front.
"Will I be able to succeed with this different system?"
I was worried at first.
Since I have people watching...
and cameras filming,
I wanted to show what I could do.
Thanks to that pressure,
I caught the fish.
That's right.
Please go back to fishing.
I am mad.
I must do this.
I keep wasting the bait.
- Relax your left shoulder. - My left shoulder?
- Then you will catch fish. - For goodness' sake.
(Kwang Soo doesn't stop spouting nonsense.)
What is going on?
- My goodness. - What is it?
- What is it? - What is it?
- That surprised me. - What is this?
My goodness, what's going on?
- It's a different species. - Really?
My goodness.
It's a species of fish in the rockfish family, false kelpfish.
- False kelpfish. - False kelpfish.
False kelpfish?
- We... - We ate it yesterday.
- We ate it yesterday. - We did.
- I ate it. - My goodness.
This is incredible.
I am sorry,
- but you didn't eat... - We ate it.
I think I ate false kelpfish yesterday.
Don't say that I didn't.
We really ate it.
Congratulations on catching fish,
but false kelpfish isn't one of the species.
(False kelpfish isn't one of the species.)
- It's a baby. - Let it go.
False kelpfish!
False kelpfish! False kelpfish!
- False kelpfish! - You caught a cute one.
Did you eat?
(He does a voice impression of Jung Woo Sung.)
(He shows his specialty to the false kelpfish.)
You can go, but don't tell your friends that we are here.
(Bye, false kelpfish.)
It's gone. It's gone.
I caught one.
(He does a voice impression of Lee Jung Jae.)
(Time passes.)
What is it?
Don't be surprised. Don't mind me.
(People gather around.)
I told you not to mind me.
Don't film me.
(He overreacts.)
It's nothing special.
(It's nothing special to a professional fisherman.)
Focus on fishing. It's nothing special.
- Kwang Soo. - No way.
It's really big.
No way! What is it?
(Look at the size.)
(What's the second fish Kwang Soo caught?)
It's yellowtail amberjack.
(Kwang Soo succeeds in catching yellowtail amberjack.)
This is incredible.
(Catching yellowtail amberjack adds fuel to Kwang Soo's bragging.)
- Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo! - It's so big.
- Everyone, - He is the best fisherman.
be quiet!
- Focus on fishing. - It's really big.
Kwang Soo is the best.
I caught yellowtail amberjack.
I caught yellowtail amberjack, the second species on the list!
No way.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, they catch 2 out of 8 species.)
Everyone,
what did I tell you?
I said...
I will show you what I can do.
Everyone,
it's yellowtail amberjack.
(Despite a job well-done, he is annoying.)
Everyone, it's yellowtail amberjack.
(It looks like he is asking for people's votes.)
(Haha is devastated.)
It's yellowtail amberjack.
(He gets slapped by yellowtail amberjack's tail.)
(It looks like yellowtail amberjack couldn't stand him.)
For goodness' sake.
- He got slapped by fish. - It's yellowtail amberjack.
Focus.
(They resume fishing.)
We have six more species to catch.
Haha, if you are going to continue fishing like that,
you should hand over the camcorder.
You are only filming the calm sea.
- My goodness. - If you aren't going to catch fish,
you should hand over the camcorder.
(Discouraged)
From the start, I couldn't understand it.
Why did Haha get the camcorder instead of me?
(That amateur doesn't need a camcorder.)
- Are you looking down on me? - We need a video of the sea.
Okay. I won't say more.
In that case,
I hope you get a good video of the sea.
(Discouraged)
How annoying!
In that case...
(Haha takes off the camcorder from his chest.)
Should I put it on?
(The camcorder goes to Kwang Soo.)
This is a bit embarrassing.
There wouldn't have been a hassle...
had you given it to me from the start.
I feel like it's my own item.
(He is satisfied.)
Please delete the saved video..
I am sure it only shows the sea.
What comes now is the real deal.
(I am okay. I am okay.)
Okay.
Such is life.
(He learns a lesson.)
When Mom goes to the island
(I catch life lessons, not fish.)
(Haha stops fishing.)
My goodness, I am sorry for being late.
Hello. Hello.
- Aren't you Haha? - Hello.
I am sorry for being late.
- Where is my spot? - It's here.
Hello, Ji Hyo.
- Did you just get here? - Yes.
My boat was delayed in Busan.
(That's why I am late.)
You look like the man who got his camcorder taken by me.
Oh, he is my father.
- Is he your father? - Yes.
- I am sorry. - Don't worry about it.
It's your father's camcorder.
Since he was bad at fishing, I took it from him.
I see. He is a man...
who catches life lessons.
(It looks like Haha left after catching life lessons.)
(Throwing)
(The son moves his hands in a fancy way.)
You must be an experienced fisherman.
(Shouting)
He caught something.
(Is Haha's son getting a bite?)
Are you serious?
(Judging by the fishing rod, it must be big.)
Put it against your stomach.
It's too big.
Are you serious?
(He is taken aback.)
(I am serious, you jerk.)
It's the curse of the camcorder.
Give me back the camcorder.
(Kwang Soo's camcorder films Haha's fishing rod.)
It's not like that.
Sir, please hold my fishing rod. It's too big.
It's trying to get away.
(He acts like his catch is incredibly big.)
- That's good. - There is fish.
Did I catch a shark?
It's so big.
- Stop, stop. - Hang in there.
I will hang in there.
All right.
(Haha's first catch emerges.)
You caught it!
What is it?
- Haha! - Yes, yes.
- You caught it. - Yes.
(Why did such a big fish get caught?)
Look at that.
It's huge. Isn't it tuna?
(Aren't I amazing? He's very satisfied.)
I fish to enjoy myself.
(Kwang Soo is very unhappy.)
Look at you.
(It's a cute yellowtail amberjack.)
We're fully loaded with fish.
(He celebrates all he ever wanted after catching only one fish.)
Come this way. Let's take a photo.
Come here.
Let's take a photo to commemorate.
Come and get in the photo.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Thank you. - Show the camcorder on Kwang Soo.
(He's very annoyed.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(The camcorder's bad luck continues.)
The captain...
is offering the fish that you caught.
- Have some. - Really?
(This is amazing.)
Wait, let's help him.
With the fish that you caught,
I made sashimi with it.
Everyone.
Okay, Kwang Soo.
It looks delicious. I was hungry.
(Taste of the sea is impressive.)
How is it?
Urban men?
Isn't it delicious?
Yes, I'm sure it is.
- Isn't it delicious? - It's so good.
Help yourself.
Actually, raw fish doesn't have any particular flavor.
However, this is different.
It's a little crunchy.
Right, it's crunchy.
Thank you, captain.
Thank you very much, captain.
(They restart to clear the mission.)
- Is this it? - No.
I'm sorry.
I'm hallucinating.
(She's so desperate that she hallucinates.)
We have to return the boat,
so you'll fish for the next 30 minutes.
Then we'll go back to the port.
The penalty is 1,000 steps.
We have to catch no matter what.
Pull it up.
I got it.
- Did something get caught? - Yes.
- Pull it up. - Ji Hyo.
She got it.
Is this correct?
You're doing well. Just turn it.
- Lower it. - Lower it a little and turn it.
Are you hurt?
What's that?
It's a new type of fish. What is it?
It's a chicken grunt.
Chicken grunt?
She got it.
- I caught one. - Great.
- Good job. - I caught one.
- Did we eat it yesterday? - Yes.
We got another type of fish.
That's impressive.
You did a good job.
I still caught one fish.
- Congratulations. - I caught one.
I got one.
Congratulations.
(She does what everyone else does.)
Good job.
(Ji Hyo's fancy debut)
We have to return the boat soon.
This was your last chance.
We'll go back to the port.
- No. - Good job, everyone.
- It's gone. - I can't catch any.
(They get additional 5,000 steps.)
(It's time to divide the steps.)
We have 5,000 steps left.
What will you do?
For everyone to survive, one person takes them all.
(Give them to one person.)
The rest will be happy.
- One person sacrifices? - Let's do that.
That sounds good.
We brought Pirate Roulette Game.
(They decide that 1 person will take 5,000 steps.)
Why don't we do this?
Each of us play the game.
How many does it take for the pirate to pop?
If the pirate pops after eight stabs, he wins.
If it pops after one time, he loses.
If you survive until the eighth, do you win?
- Yes. - I'll go first.
Go ahead.
(After suggesting the game, Haha plays first.)
Here's the first one.
(If it doesn't pop in the beginning, you're likely to win.)
Is that it?
(Haha succeeds 1.)
(Haha succeeds 2.)
Two.
(Please pop next.)
Three.
That's good.
Four.
He's good.
Five. Okay.
(Haha sticks 5 swords already.)
- It won't be me. - He's an expert.
Six.
(The loser won't be Haha.)
- Seven. Okay. - No way.
It'll be the eighth next.
Eight. That's crazy. I won't be it.
No way.
This is crazy.
I can't believe it.
No way.
(He doesn't feel lucky today.)
I can't believe it.
I got very lucky.
I'll go next.
This is incredible.
Gosh, I'm worried. I might lose again.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo. - I can do it.
One.
Two.
Everyone is good.
Three.
(And so...)
Four.
(She reaches 4.)
- Five. - What's going on?
Six.
(She successfully sticks 6.)
- Seven. - What's happening?
(Will Ji Hyo reach eight?)
(What's going on with the pirate?)
Eight. I'm done.
- I'm done. - What's going on?
(What kind of situation is this?)
(The game seems different.)
Ji Hyo.
We're Mapo Siblings.
Go ahead, Kwang Soo.
It's Sang Yeob versus Kwang Soo.
Hope that it pops on the first one.
I think it'll pop on his first one.
(Kwang Soo starts carefully.)
(Popping)
(What is this?)
This is insane.
(It becomes reality.)
Sang Yeob is a prophet.
(What's happening is 100-percent real.)
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo.
You're incredibly unlucky.
I can't believe it.
I even got goose bumps.
(It's very creepy.)
That's so harsh.
(How do you even live, Kwang Soo?)
Where did it go?
Does he win if he succeeds one?
That's right.
- He does. - Yes.
- Sang Yeob won't be that unlucky. - No way.
- No way. - Don't lie.
Please, please.
2, 3.
(The war between Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob ends.)
(Who will get the last laugh?)
There we go.
(He smiles.)
(Kwang Soo gets 5,000 steps.)
Shall I do one more?
- There we go. - That's right.
Here I go again.
- Did you think it'd pop? - That's right.
It's working so well.
- He has one left. - It's working.
- There we go. - Is it the last one?
It popped.
I'm still talented, aren't I?
(He considers himself talented.)
What have you done for the last two days?
Kwang Soo gets 5,000 additional steps.
That's amazing.
(Kwang Soo reaches 14,000 steps.)
It's over 10,000.
How did Kwang Soo...
- lose on the first one? - That's so unlucky.
- I couldn't believe it. - Me neither.
It's so stressful.
Let me say this.
I have nothing to fear. I know that I'll be last.
I'll steal yours and shake them.
You can take mine too.
I'll just steal one of yours...
and shake it.
Fine, shake it.
- I won't. - Shake it.
- Okay. - Shake it.
My goodness.
(Which place will Team Love Triangle be?)
Namcha, Namcha.
Namcha.
(Where are you?)
Where is she?
(There's someone.)
(The person he waited for...)
Namcha.
(The person he waited for is Namcha.)
Hello, I'm Namcha from Thailand.
(She worked with Shorry in Thailand.)
(Namcha is popular in Thailand.)
- Here's Namcha. - Here comes Namcha.
(A real Thai celebrity comes.)
- Welcome. - Hello.
- It's nice to meet you. - She's here.
- Our Thai celebrity is here. - She's here.
(She's really here this time.)
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Namcha. It's nice meeting you.
Welcome.
She's a famous actor in Thailand.
- It's actress. - Yes?
- You used to be a singer, right? - Yes.
She sings and acts.
She's done both.
I act, and I still sing.
I also work in cosmetics. I sell them.
- She also sells cosmetics. - Cosmetics.
- I do fashion shows... - Fashion shows?
in Asia.
- She does everything. - Usually in Asia.
- She's multi-talented. - She does everything.
You're a multi-talented entertainer.
- That's right. - Like Lim Chang Jung.
Lim Chang Jung?
Thank you.
- Lim Chang Jung? - Thank you.
Do you know Running Man?
Yes.
Do you know who he is?
(Do you know who I am?)
I... I never watched it before.
- Sorry. - That's okay.
(I've never seen him.)
- That's okay. - I've been on TV a lot.
That's okay.
He's a new member on Running Man.
- He's... - I'm part of YG.
YG?
YG Entertainment.
He's not important anymore.
- He's a lost card. - I'm the kitchen maid.
- He's a kitchen maid. - What are we doing?
As we mentioned before,
you'll give a present to the Thai celebrity.
- Right. - That's your mission.
At this night market,
buy five of these snacks.
Do we buy them?
We have to buy specific ones.
Will we eat them?
Why don't we...
(What? Taktaen?)
Taktaen.
How do you read it?
(There are five snacks written in Thai.)
- Do you understand? - There's kob.
What's kob?
- Do we buy them out there? - Yes.
I should be with Namcha.
The locals can't help you with the mission.
You should go.
I'll buy her a present.
Will you be staying here?
Yes.
That means...
your step counter won't move.
Mine is too high.
- Why don't you switch... - Why don't you switch...
- I'll take yours. - Switch yours.
(I'll take your step counter.)
- Switch. - I'll leave mine here.
Okay.
Let's do it.
- It doesn't matter. - Are you feeling all right?
I'm sorry, but how high is yours?
- 12,000. - 12,000?
You better not take more than a thousand steps.
(You better not take more than a thousand steps.)
What exactly does that mean?
- A thousand steps... - What do you think it means?
- Please explain. - He'll hit you.
With every additional step, he'll hit you once.
Let's hurry.
- Hurry. - We'll get going.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Na Eun, we're sorry. - We're sorry.
See you.
- Let's go. - Are you okay?
Where are they going?
These two guys are going to buy some stuff for you.
Why are you not going?
I should take care of you.
(Will the guys be able to complete their mission without Jong Kook?)
Where should we go?
First, let's find a place where they sell gifts.
But we don't speak Thai.
We'll just use gestures.
This way...
(Shaking)
(Constantly)
What gift should we get?
Let's find something a girl would like.
(Namcha is Thailand's fashion leader.)
(Where could they find something she would like?)
Namcha is in fashion business.
She must be picky.
All right.
Where should we go?
Thank you so much.
I'll...
definitely make it up to you.
How?
- I'll get you a gift or something. - I see.
- I have to. - I'm okay.
- I insist. - I came for Running Man.
Exactly. You're amazing.
I love Bangkok.
(I'm happy to be here with you.)
I love Bangkok too.
(I love Bangkok too.)
(We're in Bangkok, far away from home.)
Who would believe this?
(I can't believe I'm walking with you.)
I'm so happy.
I don't care if our mission fails.
(Forget about the mission.)
- It's fun! - It's fun!
It's very fun.
(They're raising Jong Kook's step count.)
(In the zone)
(Hold on.)
Kim Jong Kook.
(Is this real?)
Die, Jong Kook!
Bye, Jong Kook!
(While the two immature guys are shaking Jong Kook's step counter...)
I don't think it'll take that long. The night market...
(Se Chan and Na Eun are looking for snack stalls.)
It's there.
We have to complete our mission too.
That's right. Let's go to the night market.
Can you speak Thai?
- I can count. - Really?
(1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10)
- You're good. - Se Chan!
Se Chan!
- He can't hear us. - Na Eun!
Na Eun!
Let us join you.
- Did you buy something? - Did you buy something?
We're going to complete the mission now.
- You're not done yet? - You're starting now?
Can we join you?
Let's go together.
All right.
(They check the first stall.)
Let's check this place out.
What's that?
(Hold on.)
(What are these?)
(Thailand's specialties)
(Interesting food)
What's that?
(What are those?)
- What's that? - What's that?
(Scorpions?)
- Are they scorpions? - Should we ask them?
(Hopefully,)
(we won't find our mission snacks here.)
(Do you have...)
(kob?)
(Please say no.)
- Kob? - Kob.
Here.
- It's frog. - Frogs?
(It's frog.)
(Frogs?)
- It's frog? - It's frog?
(Screaming)
What was that?
(Gosh, you startled me.)
(I got you.)
Gosh.
- Come on. - You startled me.
Come on.
Gosh, you startled me.
"Kob" means frog?
Let's ask about other things too.
- Cinghrid. - Cinghrid.
(Do you have...)
(cinghrid too?)
(Here)
- Are they cockroaches? - Crickets.
- They're crickets. - Are they grasshoppers?
I'm starting to sweat.
- Do you have taktaen too? - Taktaen...
Here.
- They're grasshoppers. - They're grasshoppers.
- Ask about that one. - Nun turek?
(Do they have nun turek too?)
(Fried larvae)
- It's larvae. - Right.
- What is mengpong? - Mengpong?
(What is the last one, mengpong?)
Scorpion.
(The appearance makes them nervous.)
That's so big.
We have to eat them, right?
Are we going to eat them?
Each snack has to be tried by at least one member.
(Just one member?)
(It should be...)
How mad are you?
(The one guy who is not here.)
I really hate that kind of...
I think...
Should we give them to Jong Kook?
(Should we give them to Jong Kook?)
This is our chance.
Yes.
- Let's kill Jong Kook. - It doesn't taste good.
(Poison is removed.)
Of course.
- What is he doing? - He removed the poison.
He removed it now?
What if he forgot?
He just removed it before our eyes?
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye.
(Will they succeed in making Jong Kook eat them?)
- Let's go. - Bye.
We're back.
(Team Between Friends comes back after completing the mission.)
- Did everything go well? - Yes.
I see. What did you buy?
- It went well. - Did it go well?
Can I check my step counter?
Give it to me.
- I think... - I haven't checked it myself yet.
- Didn't you run around? - No.
- He didn't... - He was running around a lot.
Why did you run around?
I didn't.
(The video didn't freeze.)
- What's wrong? - What's wrong?
How high is it?
- It's over 13,000. - What?
The thing is, I met a pickpocket.
- I had to chase him. - That sounds so fake.
That sounds really fake.
- It went up a lot. - Give it.
- I'm sorry. - Give it to me.
- I'll take mine back now. - Give it back.
Give it to me.
(Give me your step counter.)
(Jong Kook is trying to switch the name stickers.)
This is not okay.
- He can't do this. - Why not?
Someone please tell him.
Look at this.
- He dug his own grave. - It's over 13,000.
Seriously...
He can't do this. Explain the rules to him.
It was too obvious.
It was too unnatural.
- It was. - It was unnatural.
Team Thailand,
let's check your mission result.
Seriously...
We couldn't only buy something for Namcha.
- We got something for Na Eun too. - Na Eun too.
Here you go.
What is it?
It's big.
- And... - It looks big.
- Namcha. - Is it a hat?
- Yes. - It's a hat.
It's pretty.
Look at Na Eun.
Isn't the color so pretty?
It's so pretty.
The colors suit them well.
You made the right choice.
- You look great. - You guys have a good eye.
Your second mission has been completed.
- Yes! - Yes!
We did it.
You went to the night market for the third mission.
You were supposed to buy snacks.
First...
(Frogs)
- It's a frog. - It's a frog.
- Did you eat it? - It's a whole frog.
We all tried it.
The legs are so far apart.
(We all tried it.)
(Only one member has to try it.)
(Jong Kook doesn't know this rule.)
(The others want to deceive him.)
- It's an appetizer. - It's an appetizer.
Can I just try the leg?
- No. - Eat the body too.
It tastes so good that you'll want to eat the body too.
It tasted like dried filefish.
- Cinghrid. - Cinghrid.
(Crickets)
I can eat it. It's no problem.
I ate them a lot when I was little.
Can you eat it now too?
- I ate it. - Okay.
- This one. - It's a grasshopper.
You have to eat it in a certain way.
I can't eat that.
(I can't eat that.)
You can't eat that?
- Did you eat it or not? - I did.
- Then why did you say that? - I mean, I can't eat anymore.
Look at this. I'll remove the legs.
Hold on.
- I'm removing the legs. - Remove the legs.
I know how to eat it.
You have to remove the legs.
The vendor taught us.
I might remove your legs.
I hope you're joking.
Jong Kook.
- Did you eat it or not? - I did.
- You did? - Yes.
- Do you know where Byung Jae lives? - Yes.
(Do you know where Byung Jae lives?)
I'll come to you.
I'm not joking.
I'll come to you. I'm not joking.
Give me one.
Eat it.
Put one in your mouth.
- The same one. - I can't let him come to my place.
Gosh, why is it so big?
It looks like a cicada.
Let's show our viewers.
- Hold it. - It's your punishment.
I can't.
- You have to eat it now. - Come on. Seriously.
This is why you should never lie.
My goodness, Jong Kook.
- He's good at eating these. - Hey.
(Jong Kook and Byung Jae both eat crickets.)
You must chew the innards and swallow.
- They eat all of it. - Isn't it good?
- This is delicious. - I told you it's good.
It's seasoned. It's really good.
- It's nutty. - And...
the last snack,
- the scorpion. - The scorpion. Okay.
(The fifth snack is the scorpion.)
Na Eun, you should give that to Jong Kook.
Why are you giving that to me?
- We got rid of the venom gland. - Did everyone eat this too?
We removed the venom gland.
- The venom gland is on its back. - Okay.
- The owner removed it. - So answer this.
We said that it was for you, and Byung Jae told him...
- to keep the venom gland. - Why did you say that?
(Se Chan is misleading again.)
- Fine. I said that. - This one has the venom gland.
Fine. I said that.
- I said that. So what? - He said, "So what?"
- I won't ever see you again now. - You...
- You won't ever see me again? - No, I didn't mean that.
I was joking. I lied.
Hey, you guys didn't eat this, right?
We should all share this then.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Only one of us will eat it.
Do we have anything we can play draw of luck?
(The last snack, the scorpion, will determine the result.)
- The last snack, the scorpion. - The scorpion.
(A roulette board with everyone's names is presented.)
Just remember. This is food.
- This is for the snack. - It's for the snack.
- Get ready. - You can spin it here like this.
(Namcha's spin will determine which member will taste the snack.)
- Good, good. - That was a good spin.
(Which one of them will get to taste the scorpion?)
- We'll decide with this. - This will determine the member.
(Byung Jae)
(Byung Jae is chosen.)
(Oh, no. I'm doomed.)
(Congratulations, Byung Jae.)
(Mom,)
(I miss you.)
How much of this can I eat?
I see its head. Didn't you remove the head?
- There was a way to remove it. - Where did it go?
The guy removed it and gave it to us.
- It's on the back. - My gosh.
(Hold on.)
How can I eat this if the local guide can't even remove it?
The local guide seems scared. How could we...
(He's terrified.)
- You can eat it now. - The guide was so surprised.
He was really surprised, wasn't he?
- How do I know if you did it? - I mean...
The local coordinator was scared too.
How could you tell us to eat this?
- Let's do it! - Let's do it!
1 bite. 1 bite.
(He takes a big bite.)
(He's chewing.)
(My gosh, Byung Jae is so brave.)
- Don't eat the tail. - It's edible. It's good.
- It's good. - I'm sure it's good.
Did we accomplish the mission then?
You accomplished the third mission.
(Team Between Friends completes the third mission too.)
(They finish all of their missions.)
- Hello. - Hello.
I feel like I haven't seen you in so long.
All right. Everyone returned safely after the mission,
Departure upon Arrival for Global Random Tour.
Well done, everyone.
(They will find out who will face the penalty now.)
You guys do work so hard.
- We'll tell you the final penalty. - Okay.
For the final penalty, you must fish in the indoor dome.
- It's fishing again? - What's an indoor dome?
We just came back from fishing.
For the penalty, you will go fishing at night...
and continue to fish until you catch one.
A member from the losing team will face the penalty.
The member will choose another member to join the penalty.
However, the member with the least number of steps in each team...
will be completely exempted from being chosen.
Now, we will reveal the accumulated steps from each team.
- I'll announce the losing team. - Okay.
First, Team Daema Island.
The total number of steps...
- My gosh. - How many did we have?
- It's 31,992 steps. - You were so nice to each other.
- 30,000? - Only 31,000?
- It was only 31,000? - Why do you say that?
- That's a lot. - Only 31,000?
- That's not that many. - Really?
I guess we didn't come last.
- We might be able to win. - We might not be last.
Team Thailand.
- Team Thailand. - Team Thailand.
The total number of steps is...
- 56,069. - That's a lot.
- That's our number? - We had that many steps?
- Seriously? - Hey, we're not last.
How is that even possible?
If Team Okinawa's total number of steps is less than Team Thailand,
- Team Thailand will do the penalty. - Okay.
But we walked a lot.
- My legs hurt so much. - A member in the team will face it.
Team Okinawa's total number of steps is...
(Team Between Friends will take last place if it's less than 56,069.)
- The total number of steps is 5... - 5.
- We walked that many steps? - Please don't let it be 56,000.
- Please say 7. 7. He will say 7. - 7. 7.
7. 7.
54,557.
(Team Okinawa's total number of steps is 54,557.)
- Yes! - Are we second?
(Team Between Friends comes last with the difference of 1,500.)
Hey, when you went out and shook my step counter,
didn't it increase about 2,000 steps?
- That was 3,000. He did that. - It was 3,000.
We lost because you added 3,000 steps.
Jong Kook, he's my friend. I invited him onto our show.
- I didn't mean to. - He took mine.
He shook my step counter.
I didn't know I had Little Kwang Soo in our team.
- He was shopping. - My goodness.
He held Jong Kook's and said, "What should I buy?"
How did you not know?
- It's because I had to stay inside. - He was inside.
I know where you live.
(He's terrified.)
- He knows the home address? - He might really visit you.
- He follows through on his words. - If Jong Kook knows his address,
they are best friends then.
A member from Team Thailand will be chosen for the penalty.
We will announce member who will be exempted from the penalty first.
- My goodness. - Team Okinawa.
So Min with 9,900 steps is exempted.
(So Min is exempted from the penalty.)
Team Daema Island.
- Ji Hyo with 3,686 is exempted. - Yes!
- 3,000? - Only 3,000 steps?
- Ji Hyo didn't walk at all. - Did you only lie down?
- Did she lie down the whole time? - My calf muscles are sore...
- from walking like this. Seriously. - Why do we have such a high number?
This is how I walked all day.
A member from Team Thailand will be exempted from the penalty.
(1st place from the team will be announced.)
With 11,755 steps,
- Se Chan will be exempted. - Okay!
Friends? Dream on, punks!
(He undergoes a sudden change.)
(Their friendship is shattered.)
How could someone with 12,000 steps win 1st place?
Se Chan, you only live for today.
Jong Kook. Oh, right. I'm so sorry.
- Is today your last day? - No, that's not it.
- Good work. Let's get dinner. - No, no.
- Are we having a farewell party? - Sure.
- I'll do it. - What kind of family are you?
- What kind of... - No, we are friends.
- You are friends? - We're old friends.
I will announce the member with the highest steps.
13,434 steps.
13,000 steps?
It's yours, Byung Jae.
Yours isn't the highest.
- My gosh. - Really?
- Yours wasn't the highest. - No way.
- You... - I thought it'd be me.
- I thought so too. - That wasn't the highest?
Remaining numbers are 15,201 and 15,679.
- 15,679... - Jong Kook, hold on.
The member with the highest number of steps, 15,679...
(Shorry lost to Sunday in the painting contest.)
(He volunteered to take 1,000 steps to take the responsibility.)
(Byung Jae took Jong Kook's step counter for a while.)
(3,000 steps were added thanks to Byung Jae.)
(Which one of them will have the highest number?)
Jong Kook? Is it Jong Kook?
- It's Shorry. - Yes!
(Shorry has the highest number.)
Shorry's number is the highest?
You must have done a lot of errands for Jong Kook.
- Errands? - He must've done a lot of them.
- You said we were in this together! - Hold on.
But isn't Shorry going to pick someone?
- I can't believe you guys. - Shorry, you will need to pick.
Shorry, you can choose a member who will join you...
to fish in the indoor dome.
Is that so?
- I can choose a member? - Yes, you can.
- Really? - We already discussed this.
Since we are very good friends,
we promised each other that we wouldn't choose each other.
- We did? - We made a promise.
- Yes, we did. - We made a promise?
- I made a promise like that? - Yes, we made a promise.
- I made a promise? - I have a shoot at 9am tomorrow.
- Get your hands out of the pockets. - What?
- Get your hands out of the pockets. - It was designed for that purpose.
- No, it's not. - You think so?
(Taking out his hands)
- You think so? - Yes.
(Looking humble)
- He took out his hands! He did it! - My gosh.
Se Chan, So Min, and Ji Hyo are exempted from the penalty.
- They can't be chosen. - Sorry?
Shorry, you can hug the member you want to...
- go fishing together from the back. - Okay.
- I can hug from behind? - This makes me nervous.
- I will act natural. - "Natural"?
- Just be yourself. - I'll choose a member.
- I will be myself. - He kept discussing made-up stuff.
- Be yourself. - That word comes up like 200 times.
- Don't sell your soul for laughter. - Okay.
- Let them laugh naturally. - I'll be myself.
Make them laugh naturally.
(Shorry promises to be himself when making his choice.)
- Here I go. - Byung Jae...
(Will he choose Byung Jae since he's been harboring ill feelings?)
What if he chooses Kyeong Hwan which makes no sense?
- Hey, don't mention my name. - He won't make it look forced.
(Will he choose Kyeong Hwan since he's easier to deal with?)
I'll make my decision now.
(Which member will Shorry choose?)
(Coming up)
(A new, grand project will be revealed.)
(A 4-week project of guided tours)
(Extreme ends of guided tours, luxury versus horror)
(Will they really go there? They are shocked.)
(Four sought-after stars whom Running Man fostered will join.)
(The beginning of these 4 weeks will decide their destinations.)
(Stay tuned. It's coming up!)
I'll make my decision now.
(They won't know when they will be done with the penalty.)
(Who is Shorry's most-logical partner for indoor fishing?)
Come with me, my friend!
(Buddy, join me!)
(Come with me, Jong Kook!)
My buddy!
(Shorry's decision was very logical.)
We won!
(This is a happy ending for us too.)
Okay, let me go. Okay.
- It's already decided. Let me go. - My gosh.
You made your decision, so let me go.
- I'm letting you go now. - Focus. Stand right here.
- "Focus"? - Stand right here.
Watch the show, and see for yourself how forced this looks.
You know what? Just watch the show. See if this is funny.
- It's funny. - It's funny.
Mark my words. I'll make sure all of your airtime...
comes from the penalty.
- How much more will he appear? - I made myself clear.
- You'll see. - This wraps up today's race.
Shorry and Jong Kook will carry out the penalty...
which was a very logical and natural turn of events.
We've never gone fishing together.
(Their trip continues.)
(They arrive at an indoor fishing site in Incheon at 12am.)
I can't believe this.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
(Silence)
We'd better finish in one hour.
- Okay, sir. - If we don't catch in an hour...
Then I'll go in the water.
(However,)
(the water is way too quiet.)
(He gets anxious.)
Just stay still.
- I'm getting anxious. - If you're loud,
the fish will run away.
Okay, Jong Kook.
Let me see.
- Is it a lobster? - They caught one.
(Other customers keep catching.)
I'm jealous of them.
- It moved. - Pull it.
I'll pull it.
(Shorry rushes as something bites.)
- Pull it fast. - We didn't catch anything.
It definitely got caught but ran away.
Right?
(Uncomfortable silence returns.)
(Does their friendship get better as time passes?)
I want to go home now.
(Their fishing continued.)
I really want to go home.
(Spring arrived soon.)
(It's a peaceful morning at Jinhae Station in Changwon.)
- Hello. - Hello.
It's such a beautiful day.
(Even Jong Kook is happy.)
Why did he dress up?
- I don't know. - How could you dress like that?
(Se Shan keeps dressing up with a black jacket.)
I have to wear something black for Jong Kook.
- Good job. - I have to wear something black.
That's how...
Jong Kook wears black often.
You wear more black after appearing on "Mom's Diary".
(Does he wear black after the show was aired?)
No, I always wore black.
It's for his character.
You used to wear gray at times.
Jae Seok, I hate being artificial the most.
(Jae Seok, I hate being artificial the most.)
- Jong Kook. - He starts again.
I don't dress according to the show that I'm on.
Is that why all your furniture is black?
I'm not artificial. It's because I like black.
Fine. Just don't get upset.
It's not something to get upset about.
You sound too artificial, don't you?
- Isn't this too artificial? - No.
- No. - Goodness.
Isn't it too early to wear shorts?
(He calls out Jong Kook.)
It's not early. It's too hot.
I see goose bumps.
It's hot.
It's perfect for shorts.
(She stares at him.)
- So Min. - Yes?
What is it, So Min?
What were you thinking?
I was too scared to ask if these were pajamas.
They are not.
I have about 10 pairs of them.
Most people...
don't layer their clothes of the same color.
- Black on black? - What's this?
- What's this? - My undershirt.
- What's this? - My middle shirt.
(It's his undershirt.)
(It's his middle shirt.)
- Is that your outer shirt? - Yes.
- Do you wear three layers? - Yes.
That means that you're cold.
He wears three layers of clothes.
- That's impressive. - I usually wear three layers.
Anyway, we'll be here today.
It's full of spring energy.
- It's great. - It's amazing.
It's warm.
- As you can see, - Flowers bloomed.
- flowers are blooming. - Are those cherry blossoms?
Jinhae Cherry Blossom Festival will start soon.
Isn't Haha the son of Changwon?
- Everyone. - Why is he the son of Changwon?
How's the weather in Changwon?
- Are you... - Didn't I tell you?
I told you that I lived in Changwon.
- How long did you live here? - For how long?
I graduated from elementary school.
How long did you live in Mapo-gu?
I'm the son of Changwon.
- Is that so? - Those from Changwon are...
Kang Dong Won and Lee Joon Gi.
You should be out.
- But... - They already exist.
- the mayor was so proud. - Stop joking.
My goodness.
(Come to Jinhae Cherry Blossom Festival.)
Anyway,
I think we have some guests today.
- Right. - Really?
- I read it on the news. - Right.
(Who will be coming?)
Everyone.
Spring, a new season arrived.
We have a new project for the spring.
Right.
It's called Family Package Project.
(It's full of fun Family Package Project)
For the next four weeks,
with your family-like members on Running Man,
you'll be on a new project.
- 4 weeks? - 4 weeks?
- For one month? - I heard that...
there's a guest whom Jong Kook fears.
- Who? - I read in an article.
- I heard Jin Young is coming. - Jin Young.
Jong Kook is scared of Jin Young.
- She's really coming. - Yes.
- Is Jin Young coming? - Yes.
His tone of voice became friendly.
(Have you been waiting for me?)
- He'll be a baby for four weeks. - I couldn't even talk.
He couldn't say anything to Jin Young.
First of all, we have...
four new guests...
- Four guests? - who will be on the project.
I'll introduce them.
- Really? - Is there a male guest?
- What's this? - Of course.
It can't be four females.
- I'm sure there is. - Why do you ask?
- What's this? - We gave you a phone.
Your family members sent the characters...
that look like them with a message.
(The guests send characters that look like them.)
I tried it before, and it works. Is it called Emoji?
- Really? - Yes.
- Wait, a message arrived. - It arrived.
Let's see.
(Who could it be?)
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
- Is it because of my face? - Your shadows block my view.
- Let me see it too. - I'm sorry.
- Can you stay back? - I'm curious.
Be calm.
Is Running Man yours?
You're being too harsh.
- My goodness. - That's childish.
It's so childish that I'm lost for words.
"Is Running Man yours?"
I want to see it too.
(You aren't in the center.)
(Whispering)
Jae Seok told me to tell you that it's his.
- He has a lot of shares. - No matter whose it is,
he has more shares than you.
- Hey. - If we had to determine it.
- You shouldn't say that. - Wait.
- What? - It arrived.
A face came up.
"Hello, it's been a while." She's been on the show before.
- She looks similar to Jin Young. - It looks like her.
Who is it?
Her hair is long.
She has a typo, so she must be older.
"Hello, it's been a while."
Based on the sound of her laughter,
it seems like...
It's Da Hee.
Is this Da Hee?
Wait.
- Who is it? - Her hair is short.
- Isn't it Da Hee? - It's Jin Young.
- It's Da Hee. - It's Jin Young.
Who's this?
It's Shin Bong Sun.
It's Kang Han Na.
Shin Bong Sun? No, it's Kang Han Na.
- Wait. - There's another one.
- It's a man. - It's a man.
He looks like someone.
- It's Lee Jee Hoon. - I'm so nervous.
- Who is it? - It looks like Lee Jee Hoon.
Isn't it Jae Seok?
No, it's not me.
Anyway, they're Kang Han Na.
- Hong Jin Young. - Hong Jin Young.
- Lee Da Hee. - Lee Da Hee.
Who's the man?
- Jee Hoon? - I don't know.
Who's the last guest?
(Which 4 family members will they be with?)
Let's see if your guesses are correct.
We'll invite the first family member.
Is it Han Na?
- I'm excited. - I don't think so.
First family member, please come out.
Let's invite her.
(It's an S.E.S song.)
- It's Da Hee. - Da Hee.
There she is.
The swindler character is back.
She's back.
(She annihilated the dance battle with a hair band.)
(She destroyed Kwang Soo by calling him a jerk.)
(She enters shyly after closing the door.)
"You're a thief."
Look at that.
- What's wrong with her? Da Hee. - She can't do anything at once.
What's wrong with her? Da Hee.
- She can't do anything at once. - Da Hee.
Come here now.
(She's busy saying hello.)
- Da Hee. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
I feel hurt.
- Why? - As soon as she saw me...
No way.
(She passes So Min.)
She held up her fists at me.
This is what she did to me.
- She doesn't like me. - Hey.
Do you know what she did to Se Chan?
(Flinching)
To me?
This is our first guest.
- She's our hero. - It's Lee Da Hee.
Hello.
The jerk's friend, Lee Da Hee.
As Da Hee knows,
as soon as she appeared on our show,
she made a popular phrase that's hard to make.
- "You're a jerk." - It's been a while.
- It was amazing. - Right.
She brought it too.
- What is it? - Kwang Soo.
- I brought it for you. - What is it?
(It's the bag that she used last time.)
- Did you bring something? - Yes.
- What is it? - Did you throw away yours?
I...
remember our past.
(What's this card?)
(Do you remember the nasty race that we had?)
(She said that her number was 6.)
(She kept her number 5 card until now.)
(She remembers that time.)
- What? - Did she keep that card?
(What's wrong with her?)
Take out money or something, Kwang Soo.
- What? - Take out something.
Did you throw away yours?
(Did you throw away our souvenir?)
- Of course, he did. - Did you throw yours away?
Stop forcing yourselves to be romantic.
(Haha acts like a sheriff.)
- It's too artificial. - I hate this the most.
- It's too artificial. - No, it's not.
- Come on. - It's not artificial.
Love ended between Ji Hyo and Gary.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
Now, I have a good friend.
- It's impressive that she has it. - Seriously.
Why did you keep it?
I just kept everything.
The staff was upset that the card disappeared.
Da Hee, you're supposed to return it.
Do you have kleptomania?
Don't say that.
- She can't take things. - That's too harsh.
I like it. It's a good size.
Really? What do you carry inside?
I carry...
- my cell phone and a pen. - Really?
- You kept the same things inside. - Scissors.
- Scissors? - Why do you carry them?
Wait, Da Hee.
You took scissors and a pen.
Your nickname is Thief Lee from now on.
(A beautiful entertainer is suspicious of being a thief.)
How could you call her that?
I'm just joking.
- Seok Jin, do you want this? - What is it?
I felt so bad about that day, so I brought some herbal medicine.
(Herbal medicine?)
Herbal medicine?
I wouldn't say no to this.
(Struggling)
He can't even open it.
Give me something that opens!
(Give me something that opens!)
- Let me try. - Gosh.
- Why can't you open it? - It won't open.
It's open.
You just have to pull the lid off.
I was going to give it to my partner...
at the last shooting...
That means it's very old.
(It was last January.)
- Check the expiration date. - Check it.
Isn't it expired? Will it give you a stomachache?
It'll be all right.
Check the expiration date.
What are you doing?
(What is with her?)
She wanted to give it to her partner.
- It smells okay. - Are you sure?
It's herbal medicine.
It's giving me energy.
Seok Jin really smells like an old man now.
It's the medicine.
It's the smell of the medicine.
Let's meet our next guest.
Okay.
(Ring)
(Jin Young is here.)
Look.
- Here she is! - Here she is!
(With her new song, "Goodbye", playing,)
(the intense girl appears.)
No one can stop her.
(Hong Jin Young)
This is strong.
(Hey, Jong Kook.)
(She can keep Jong Kook under control.)
(She can even make him do cute things.)
She's even wearing black pants and shoes.
- Black pants. - She's Jong Kook's partner.
Come stand here.
- Hi. - Stand here.
(Goodbye)
I love this song.
- I love it. - Seriously.
- Jin Young. - Yes?
- Well... - Hi.
Jin Young is here.
"Goodbye" is so popular these days.
(Goodbye)
(Forget everything)
(Forget me)
All right.
You haven't been on Running Man for a while.
Nice to see you. It's been a while.
Jong Kook already feels uncomfortable.
- You've lost a lot of weight. - Jong Kook feels uncomfortable.
You've lost a lot of weight.
There was a rumor that...
something was going on between Jin Young and Jong Kook.
- So... - What do you think about it?
About us?
(I shouldn't be standing here.)
Da Hee, where are you going?
- Da Hee, where are you going? - I don't want to be there.
I heard it gave you a bit of trouble.
- It gave you trouble? - Jin Young...
- experienced a bit of trouble. - You did?
When the article about my joining Running Man...
for four weeks came out,
a foreigner sent me a message on social media.
What did it say?
(She received a message from a foreigner.)
"If you hit on Jong Kook, I'll kill you."
- Really? - I mean...
When she entered,
she seemed to flinch when she saw me.
I wondered why.
- I mean... - Ji Hyo and Jong Kook's fans...
want to protect them.
Please translate this.
It's not like I'm going to stay here forever.
I can disappear like the wind at any moment.
Jin Young is scared.
- I'm like the wind. - You're like the wind.
I'm sure my fans were joking.
Even his fans make such jokes?
- They're just like me. - How could they say that though?
I haven't killed you although I joke about it.
But who knows?
(Who knows?)
- Wait and see. - You might not have noticed,
but he is slowly dying.
Look at him.
- Is it because of me? - He's under stress.
- He is slowly dying from stress. - I weigh only 38kg.
Jin Young and Da Hee have joined us.
Da Hee, why are you standing here?
I don't want to stand between those two.
- She wanted to escape. - Really?
Nothing is going on between them.
Stop pretending to be thoughtful.
(If you say so...)
(She goes back.)
- I know. - But you didn't have to come back.
Why would you stand there?
- She wants to stand in the middle. - No, no.
- They're both wearing green. - Make yourself comfortable.
- I don't want to stand there. - Stand next to Kwang Soo.
Hey, why are you wearing green?
- You look like a frog. - Exactly.
She's found her place.
This looks better.
Their height difference looks perfect.
- That's right. - That's right.
Your height difference looks good too.
- The colors of your outfits too. - Jong Kook.
Black?
(Black?)
Her hair is black too.
Jin Young is here with us.
Let's meet our next guest. Please come out!
(A girl with elegant bobbed hair)
(She surprises everyone.)
It's Han Na.
- It's been a while. - Han Na.
- Oh, My. - Hi, Han Na.
The emoticon looked just like her.
It looked elegant.
(Her crazy dance moves...)
(made her the scene-stealer.)
The funniest thing about Han Na is that...
she pretends to be normal.
During the opening, she pretends to be normal.
I am normal.
I don't know whom your partner will be today,
but is there...
(Laughing)
What is it?
(Why is she laughing?)
It's beginning.
- Stop pretending to be normal. - It's beginning.
- Come on. - It was so random.
No one else laughed.
It gave me goose bumps.
She suddenly laughed coldly.
Stop it. She didn't.
She suddenly stared into the air and...
(Laughing)
- Why did you do that? - I saw it too.
- I saw it. - What made you laugh?
Jae Seok seemed to be stumbling over his words.
She must have inhaled some helium.
"Jae Seok seemed to..."
"I mean..."
What are you doing?
I suddenly found it funny.
All right. I never finished my question,
but Han Na must have known what I was going to ask.
- What were you asking? - Her partner?
Yes. I was going to ask her...
if there was anyone she didn't want as her partner.
She probably knew what I was going to ask.
- She probably knows. - You probably guessed it right.
I guessed it right? Okay.
All right.
Seok Jin, stop pretending to be cool.
- Stop it. - Should I cry?
- Am I supposed to cry here? - Stop it.
What do you expect me to do?
- I have to smile. - Smile.
Do whatever you want.
(Let's see.)
(She has a feeling that she can't escape him.)
Han Na, will you be free on these days...
for the next few weeks?
Yes. I have no other plans than Running Man.
She'll be with us for the next month?
- She'll be with us for four weeks. - Han Na,
Da Hee and Jin Young will be with us for the next four weeks.
Aren't they busy?
- What? - Can they really do it?
- You don't like it? - That's not what I mean.
That's not it.
I love this.
Jin Young is busy.
- It's so funny. - She's busy.
Jin Young.
She's the best.
Han Na is with us.
(They've met 3 female guests.)
I love it.
Our last guest is a man, but I don't know who he is.
- A man with glasses. - Yes.
Please come out.
- Who is he? - I don't know.
- Is he a member of iKon? - Really?
(This song is "Love Scenario" by iKon.)
- It's Sang Yeob. - Sang Yeob.
Hey.
- I knew it. - You guys don't look so happy.
(Lee Sang Yeob)
(An actor with a thousand voices...)
(turned into a variety show ace.)
- Sang Yeob. - Hello.
Sang Yeob, we see you often these days.
Is he a regular member now?
Did you empty your Mondays and Tuesdays?
I don't think I've seen him looking this nice before.
- Who? - Sang Yeob.
He's like this every week. Don't say that.
No, I tried to look nice today.
- You did? - Yes.
- His voice changed. - The tone is different.
- That tone is for variety shows. - It's true.
- Hey. - He sounds silly.
- "I tried to look nice today." - Hold on.
- Don't say that. - I'm joking.
Have you all met Sang Yeob before?
- It's my first time seeing him. - You too, Da Hee?
I saw...
Jin Young...
- in a restaurant. - Yes, it was a pork belly place.
- I was asking you about Sang Yeob. - I see.
They're all weird.
What is she talking about?
- Jin Young is the most normal. - That's why...
we brought them back.
- They're all weird. - They are.
- We are weird too. - They're so weird.
I got goosebumps a few times today.
I asked her about Sang Yeob, but she was talking about a restaurant.
Everybody's here including Sang Yeob.
(All the weird people are here including Sang Yeob.)
They're the best.
We'll be conducting a Family Package Project...
with the new family for four weeks.
You'll race every week, and if you win,
you'll receive the luxury package filled with luck and happiness.
If you lose,
you'll get the Shuddering Package...
and go on a global trip.
Global? I guess we're going overseas again.
Why do we have to go somewhere that makes us shudder?
- Let's go somewhere nice. - That's what I mean.
The destinations...
were recommended by the four members of the new family.
Really?
(They were recommended by the 4 members of the new family.)
- It must be somewhere nice. - Right.
(I recommended some places?)
They probably don't know that they recommended some places.
Let's watch a clip...
and find out what they chose.
Hey, what should we do now?
- Let's go somewhere nice. - We should.
I really want to go somewhere nice.
(A few days ago, at an office in Yeouido)
(Why is Sang Yeob here?)
What? When did they meet up?
(You had no idea, right?)
You'll be participating...
in the Running Man family project for four weeks.
We don't know what kind of traveling you like.
We have a questionnaire...
about your traveling styles.
Please fill it out so that we can refer to it.
Name is Hong Jin Young.
I've never done this before.
I don't have anything I need to take.
I have to have instant noodles. I need food.
I can last a few days with instant noodles, so I need it.
Good job.
- We need instant noodles. - It's a must.
There is something I don't want to take.
The step counter.
(He doesn't want to take the step counter.)
(He doesn't even want to look at it again.)
It's going to give me neurosis.
- I don't want to take... - No step counter?
the step counter.
For the necessities,
can I write "Lee Kwang Soo"?
(Me?)
- Why? - Really?
Kwang Soo...
has this irresistible charm.
- He moves your heart. - I'm touched.
I'll write Kwang Soo.
(His heart races.)
Kwang Soo.
I've never been a couple with a guy.
(I'm nervous. I've never been a couple with a guy.)
"Which member do you want to go on a trip with?"
(She's shy.)
Kwang Soo.
You want to go on a trip with Kwang Soo?
We became friends after filming last time.
I think I'll feel comfortable,
and I can order him around.
She's going to make you do stuff.
- She'll order you around. - I think it'll be fun.
I'm comfortable with him.
Which member I don't want to go with?
(Whom does she not want to go with?)
(Se Chan)
- Why did you pick him? - She doesn't like you.
Why doesn't she like me? Did I do something wrong?
(You didn't.)
- Let's hear it. - Se Chan?
It's Se Chan.
When I came on the show last time, he wasn't too happy.
Let me change this.
I think I like Seok Jin less than Se Chan.
I feel like I have to take care of him.
(This is an intense battle now.)
Why did she change her mind?
- This is intense. - He got two votes.
(Why don't you like me?)
I think I like Seok Jin less.
I feel like I have to take care of him.
That's tiring.
I think he'll keep nagging.
I pick Seok Jin.
"If you have a chance, which tour package would you go on?"
(What's all this?)
- Really? - Yes?
Is it exactly like the picture?
Yes, that's what we found.
"If you have a chance, which tour package would you go on?"
Where is that?
It's New Zealand.
- That's Canada. - That's amazing.
(8 destinations of Luxury Package were selected carefully.)
There are so many nice places.
- This is great. - I would love to go.
(We really want to go on the trip.)
(What did the new family choose?)
I want to go to Spain.
There's a hotel package...
you have to go on before you die, selected by BBC.
You have to go before you die,
so it feels like...
you have to go right at this moment.
(FC Barcelona)
(It's a famous Spanish soccer club everybody knows.)
(We have to see that.)
Messi.
(Real Madrid)
Barcelona.
(Real Madrid is Barcelona's eternal rival.)
Do we get to watch El Clasico?
- Do we get to watch that? - That would be awesome.
(The oldest restaurant in the world is in Spain?)
(This traditional Spanish restaurant was Ernest Hemingway's favorite.)
I feel motivated now. I want to go there.
It's so nice.
(The suckling pig dish is cooked in the fire pot.)
We have to go there.
(A romantic night in the 19th century fortress?)
You get to spend time in the fortress.
Look at the swimming pool.
Isn't it so nice?
It's so nice. I mean it.
- Jin Young is great. - I know.
(Spain, luxury passion package)
I really want to go to Mexico.
"Bullring hotel package"?
(Take a bath in the hot spring?)
They have the hot spring in a cave?
Mexico is great.
That's awesome.
(Mexico City's fine dining is 12th best in the world.)
It looks so good. It's Mexican food.
(Q restaurant has Mexican fusion food.)
(They have the only hotel remodeled from a bullring.)
- It's so nice. - We're going there?
It's so nice.
(Mexico, luxury paradise on earth package)
Mexico is so beautiful.
(I chose a good one, right?)
Canada?
(This river in the Rocky Mountains is a must-see in 2018.)
I really want to go to Canada.
(The Bow River is the place for fly fishing.)
- That's what I wanted to do. - Fly fishing.
- You know it, right? - I've seen that in movies.
I wanted to do that.
(I picked it.)
It has a great scenery.
You don't have to look for it.
It's just there.
(Niagara Falls is 1 of the top 3 waterfalls in the world.)
(That comes after eating. They have a big, delicious steak.)
(This steak weighs 1.35kg.)
It looks so good.
We have to go there.
- Do you think we can? - Of course.
It looks amazing.
(You get to spend a night in a hotel that's 130 years old.)
(Canada, luxury nature package)
Da Hee.
This is great.
I know I won't be able to go everywhere,
but I really want to go to Switzerland.
I want to experience the pure Mother Nature.
Switzerland.
I really want to go there.
Me too.
I hope we can go.
(You can look at the Alps in the train.)
Look at the mountain.
(You can ski here in the middle of the summer?)
(You get to ski in real snow in the Alps during the summer.)
- It looks so much fun. - Right?
(You get to have something soft to fill your stomach.)
It looks so good.
That's it.
(There's an environment-friendly hotel in the middle of the Alps.)
(Switzerland, luxury snow kingdom package)
Are we really going there?
Are you tricking us again?
- I think you are. - We have to go there.
It doesn't matter if it's Australia or Canada.
It can even be Thailand because it's close.
The fact that you're on a plane to somewhere is nice.
(The fact that you're on a plane to somewhere is nice.)
(There was one last question in this questionnaire.)
What's this?
They got tricked.
(There's something else.)
"What is a destination you would like to recommend..."
"but not go yourself?"
See?
These are the bad ones.
See? That's the swing.
Do we have to go on scary rides?
(Which Shuddering Packages did they choose?)
For somebody else?
Wing walking in the UK.
I don't want to do it myself. I'm scared.
(The plane flies at 217km per hour.)
What's this?
(You have to stand on it without any harness?)
He's standing on a flying airplane.
That's crazy.
You must be crazy.
You're hanging from an airplane.
(Wing walking gives you the thrill of walking in the sky.)
What's that?
(You can't spin it around.)
They must be crazy.
(This plane leads you to...)
(a hotel where the sleepless souls visit every night.)
What's this now?
You'll get possessed.
Goodness. Don't do this.
Oh, gosh.
- No... - Turn it off, So Min.
- The ghost... - Turn it off. Kick it.
Hey.
Thanks. You did it for me.
- Casper is a ghost. - Goodness.
Casper is cute.
Giant Canyon Swing.
Wasn't Haha supposed to do this?
- But he couldn't go, right? - Right.
He can do this then.
America.
(Did you think you were safe? The terrifying swing is back.)
That's the swing.
We were supposed to go there.
You can go there. You were supposed to do it.
(I almost forgot about it.)
Look.
(The designer was too scared and only went on it once.)
This is unbelievable.
It's insane.
(Giant Canyon Swing throws you 400m above the ground.)
(After that, you get to sleep 6m below the ground.)
Why is there a hotel 6m below the ground?
We have to sleep there?
You have to swim to it.
It's an underwater hotel?
You have to swim to your room.
(In the underwater hotel in Florida, you can spend a breathless night.)
Switzerland.
There's so much. Do you get to do everything?
It won't be me anyways.
What's this?
A suspension bridge.
- I can't do that. - You have to risk your life.
My goodness.
(Canyoning involves swimming, rock climbing, and hiking.)
You have to jump down?
(You get to free jump from a gondola that's 134m tall...)
(in a cable car bungee jumping.)
You must be insane.
(There's a single bed in the middle of the Alps?)
Why would you sleep there?
(There's an Alps outdoor hotel with no walls, roof, or bathroom.)
It looks different on the screen.
Does this mean...
you have to climb the cliff?
That's right.
Peru.
(Why are there capsules on the cliff?)
- Oh, my. - Do you have to rock climb?
(The hotel is suspended 122m. You have to rock climb to check in.)
Why is that necessary?
(You can spend a cozy night in the cliff-side hotel.)
Are you ready?
What's this?
(What just happened?)
(It only takes 5 seconds to be launched 125m in the air.)
- How high is that? - That's Superman.
(The deadly Cusco slingshot allows you to dangle from a cord.)
(They're speechless.)
We thought we were done after the Nevis Swing.
Where do you get all the information from?
You won't know when you are there, but once you get up,
the ghost will be stuck to your luggage.
(That's if you go to the haunted hotel in the UK.)
It'll turn Korea into chaos.
Really?
- Why would you say that? - It really happened.
What's this?
Why would you bring this?
This? No way.
(It's the roulette again.)
(There are actually 2.)
That's how they went to the Nevis Swing last time.
- This is not right. - Did you see it?
Did you see the Nevis Swing?
- I really don't want to do this. - I can't go on the plane.
Why?
We're going to be serious...
and pick the luxury one.
- I want to go to Switzerland. - We have to go to these places.
- Me too. - Anyway,
the new family members filled out questionnaires...
and picked the destinations they wouldn't go to.
- We have all the packages here. - Okay.
These are the four destinations...
you chose.
You can't say that they chose these places.
Do you really think...
they picked these places?
This is really bad.
They picked 4 out of 8.
(He's adamant.)
(They didn't feel the pressure because it was for somebody else.)
(These choices became the proposed sites.)
(It won't be me anyways.)
They said it's for somebody else, not us.
- Is that why? - I wanted to see it.
- You'll end up doing it. - It'll be you.
That's why I chose it.
There are so many nice places.
We can win and go there.
- Do you think it's possible? - We'll make it possible.
- We have to. - Of course.
The family project...
that involves 12 members...
will run for four weeks.
The winning team each week...
can stick their name tags on the Luxury Package roulette.
The losing team will have their name tags...
on the Shuddering Package roulette.
(6 losers each week will have their name tags on the roulette.)
During the last week, we'll spin the roulette...
decide the destination and the members.
You'll be going on package tours to the different countries.
(Shuddering Package vs Luxury Package)
So half...
of us are going.
- Half of us are going? - I can already see...
- whose names will be on here. - Right?
Me too.
As soon as I heard "six people", I looked at Jae Seok.
I know who's going.
You know what's funny?
We looked at each other when this roulette came out.
We made eye contact.
I don't know why.
(Kwang Soo)
(Jae Seok)
(Are we all thinking the same?)
I don't know why,
but my eyes turned to you like magnets.
If Sang Yeob and Da Hee come here...
and Seok Jin and I go there,
- we're the favorites to lose. - That's true.
- You are the losers. - That's so true.
We have bad luck,
but we have these four,
- so you never know. - You don't.
According to probability, 2 of them will join us.
That's true. That's for sure.
What do you think, Jin Young?
I like the Giant Canyon Swing the least.
This?
(She chose it without thinking much.)
But I heard Haha was supposed to go there,
so I think he should go.
- You should go. - That's at least better.
- I've been... - It's better.
- on the Nevis Swing. - You've done it before.
- You've been on the Nevis Swing. - Number 26.
Number 27.
- Hey. - Crocodile.
- Crocodile. - Crocodile.
That's nice.
There's a high chance...
Sang Yeob will go here.
- Me? - Yes.
I think Sang Yeob...
might go because of Kwang Soo, not himself.
I'm here today...
because I want to send Kwang Soo here and go on the luxury tour.
- Really? - I think you're in the same team.
You'll both get step counters.
You'll do the wing walking with the step counters on.
I'll be shaking the step counter the whole time.
(They'll fight and both end up in the Shuddering Package.)
I can't say I won't be going there,
but I swear if I do go, I'll take you with me.
Exactly. He'll do that.
You might go because of Kwang Soo.
And Jae Seok.
(Why are you playing dumb, Jae Seok?)
I finished speaking...
and turned away.
- Why are you bringing me into this? - I was hurt.
I thought you would do that,
so I turned away.
(They have strong ties. They never die alone.)
The first part of the project is...
Romance Goes Away.
(Family Package Project: Romance Goes Away)
Romance?
It goes away?
You are in Jinhae that's known for the cherry blossoms,
so we prepared a couples' race.
Unfortunately, we have five female members...
and seven male members.
Five teams will be female and male couples,
and one team will be a bromance couple for the races.
- We have to win. - It's a male couple.
I'll have to try so hard for four weeks.
So this is the important part.
The couple selection mission is called...
As Long As It's Not You.
(Couple selection mission: As Long As It's Not You)
"As Long As It's Not You".
The female members will choose one male member they don't like...
and compete in a game they choose.
If she wins,
she can become a couple with the member she wants.
If she loses, she becomes a couple with the male member she chooses.
(If she wins, she can pick her partner.)
You have to be smart about whom you choose.
- That's right. - This is insane.
If you object to the couple selection process,
you can bring it up and play the game.
If you win, you can steal the loser's partner.
(If you win, you can steal somebody else's partner.)
You can steal a partner? Oh, dear.
- The teams are really important. - This depends...
on the teams.
- The results will depend on this. - Everything depends on this.
The teams are important, but it's all fate.
(Winning and losing depend on fate.)
He's ruining this for us.
- You might try hard. - I am disappointed already.
There's fortune for each day.
That was so sensible of you.
(My Jong Kook)
(Smiling)
- That was sensible? - Of course.
He looks happy. He got complimented.
He's flaring his nostrils.
If you keep doing that, you'll tire him out.
Keep doing it.
First of all, let's pick...
one person to play.
- Let's start with So Min. - So Min.
Let's go, So Min.
- Doesn't she usually win? - She's intense.
What did she choose?
Pinching with my toes.
(Pinching with toes)
- What do you do? - Pinching?
(What's that?)
Do you lose if your skin rips?
(Do you pinch somebody and lose if their skin rips?)
Do you lose if you bleed out?
I know she can move her toes freely.
- My toes are long, - She's good at pinching things.
so they're pretty strong.
If you don't make any sound, you win.
- If you make any sound, I win. - For 10 seconds.
For 10 seconds?
Hold on.
That's simple. I think anybody can hold it.
But I'll pinch your face.
With your toes?
(That's something she would do.)
I'm sorry, but you'll be doing this?
Like this?
It's 10 seconds.
So Min, whom will you pick?
(Who does So Min not want to be a couple with?)
(So Min's As Long As It's Not You)
Se Chan, as long as it's not you.
Why all of a sudden?
If I don't make any sound, you'll become a couple with me.
You can't hold it.
- Really? - Really?
(Se Chan vs So Min)
I'm really good at this.
- You are? - Should I take my jacket off?
It doesn't matter.
(She beats her foot like a middle-aged man.)
Please give me wet tissue.
- She has good manners. - Will she wipe her foot?
She might wipe Se Chan's face.
(She might wipe Se Chan's face with wet tissue.)
It will be a surprise if she wipes Se Chan's face.
That will be a twist.
My face is cleaner than your foot!
She might leave her foot be and wipe Se Chan's face.
(Fortunately, she wipes her toes.)
So Min, your toes are so long.
She will be able to pinch freely.
- I am self-conscious of them. - I see.
I can pull up my big toe.
(She can pull up her big toe.)
I bet she can play piano with her toes.
She picked up her item at doljabi with her toes.
I can shake your hand with them.
(Isn't it amazing?)
Is this really a game?
She can shake my hand with her toes.
Her foot is like her hand.
What will she do if I hold out?
If you hold out,
someone will say, "So Min is mine."
What?
I think you watched too many dramas.
- I am sorry, - She looked at Sang Yeob.
but we are only playing this game for a day.
(Sang Yeob, come to my aid.)
Get ready. Where will you pinch him?
- Where should I pinch you? - You can pinch hard.
- Where will you pinch me? - I will pinch your ear.
- I think it's a nice choice. - Ears don't hurt.
- Ears don't hurt. - They don't?
- No. - Ears don't hurt.
- There? - Try it.
(She reaches for his ear as if she is ready to rip it out.)
(Screaming)
- What was that? - I have a cramp.
- Are you okay? - What was that?
(She complains about the pain due to a cramp in her toes.)
What's wrong?
- Just now, - Are you okay?
she pushed me with her foot when she couldn't punch my ear.
- So Min, don't do that. - I have a cramp.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I will massage your toes.
All right.
- So Min, are you toes okay? - Yes.
They are dangling.
They are dangling too much. Are your toes okay?
Yes. Se Chan's makeup was slippery.
Are your toes okay?
- Pinch his neck. - There isn't much to grab.
- It's a nice choice. - Pinch his neck.
It will hurt. He is bound to make a sound.
It will hurt.
(I never make the same mistake twice.)
(I am determined to end this with a single shot.)
My goodness.
(She gets a cramp again.)
- If this keeps going on... - For goodness' sake.
This player isn't ready, Jae Seok.
This player isn't ready.
What are we supposed to do if she continues having cramps?
- Are you putting on a show? - What are we supposed to do?
Gosh, my toes became twisted.
- Do you have a certificate? - When I learned ballet...
(You are good at this.)
- I got a lot of cramps. - Doesn't she look like a nurse?
She looks like a nurse.
Han Na learned ballet.
When you have a cramp. you need to push your toes back.
Your toes might be stronger, big sister.
Am I older than you? You called me big sister.
- She does that to everyone. - I don't know how old you are.
She says that to people who are five years younger than her.
In which year were you born? I was born in 1989.
- 1988? - 1989.
1989? I am sorry.
They don't hurt anymore, right?
Thank you.
I think feeling nervous...
- is putting a strain on her body. - It's because she didn't warm up.
Please be understanding if she pinches with her fingers.
(Come on, Se Chan.)
Why?
- She can't pinch with her toes. - Excuse me.
- Her fingers? - That's right.
He is bound to feel pain if he gets pinched by her fingers.
- Why doesn't she punch him instead? - Seriously.
Why doesn't she hit him with a bat?
You shouldn't change a rule so suddenly.
- Please calm down. - Kick him in the calves.
Come on.
- I will get started. - The skin is thin here.
- It turned red. - It's okay.
(Se Chan's neck)
It's okay. His skin turns red when you rub on it.
Of course, it turns red...
when you rub so forcibly.
What is wrong with you?
You rubbed so forcibly.
Back off. For goodness' sake.
- Are your toes okay? - Yes.
- Se Chan. - It's okay.
You won't get a cramp this way.
(I feel bad for Se Chan.)
This way...
Pull his sideburns.
Don't you think you made yourself too comfortable?
(She uses him as a foot stool.)
I am sorry,
but you have a lot of dead skin on your foot.
(He notices it.)
It's because I used a pack.
You have a lot of dead skin.
Why do you have so much dead skin?
Take proper care of yourself.
Back off. Back off.
- She is the worst. - It's because I used a pack.
I can't believe what I am seeing.
I used a pack...
that removes dead skin.
Can I scream after looking at her foot?
- I can scream. - Stop it.
Stop it. We need to play the game.
It's not that I have dead skin.
The pack makes dead skin fall off a week after you use it.
- That's why my skin is flaky. - Are you live-streaming?
Yes. It's not dead skin.
I thought it was the tangerine pith.
(A witness says it looks like the tangerine pith.)
We saw it.
The white part of a tangerine.
So Min, you don't have to worry since we will blur your foot.
Do you want to pinch the inside of my arm?
It will hurt a lot.
- It will hurt a lot. - He is pulling his skin.
- Your skin is the softest there. - That's right.
- It will hurt a lot. - It will hurt a lot.
Let's go.
- All right. - Set.
(If Se Chan endures for 10 seconds, he becomes So Min's partner.)
(Can So Min avoid having Se Chan as her partner?)
(Screaming)
- My goodness. - Did it hurt?
It hurt here. Gosh, it hurt.
Did it hurt? Se Chan's lips turned white.
- Her toes are strong. - Her toes are strong.
(His arm turns red after a single pinch.)
Let's get a shot of you getting pinched on the face.
Let's have So Min pinch you on the cheek.
(The first one may be too violent to air.)
We want to use a good shot.
Why don't you let So Min pinch you on the face?
Did the rules change?
- Did they? - We never know.
- All right. - We never know.
We never know.
Let's go.
- I guess the rules changed. - That's right.
Set.
Go.
(So Min begins pinching.)
- I guess it's endurable. - Yes, she can't pinch with force.
I see. That's enough, So Min. Let's use the one with the arm.
Is that it?
To make it more interesting,
why don't I pinch So Min's face with my toes?
(This isn't very interesting.)
- You can edit it later. - No.
Shall we give it a go?
You can edit it later.
(The editing techniques must be advanced.)
- That won't do. - You can edit it later.
So Min succeeded.
(She can choose her partner.)
She succeeded.
So Min.
It's hard to choose.
For your information, male couples can be at a disadvantage.
- Really? - That's what I thought.
- They are at a disadvantage? - We must avoid it.
I...
(So Min chooses the lucky partner.)
(I need a female partner as soon as possible.)
(What is So Min's choice?)
I want to partner up with a new face.
Sang Yeob.
(Sang Yeob, do you want to be my partner?)
(Can So Min partner up with Sang Yeob?)
(Next week)
(Are they flirting with each other?)
(However)
(Colorful diamonds tempt the lovers.)
(I really want them.)
(The game starts as soon as they touch the diamonds.)
(The Curse of the Diamond)
(The greedier they become, the deeper they fall.)
(Greed makes them lose love and friendship.)
It's too dangerous.
(Diamonds bring about...)
(the wild chase of stealing and getting stolen.)
(Can you withstand the curse?)
(The Curse of the Diamond)