(Bleak atmosphere surrounds a party room in Incheon.)
(There are jack-o'-lanterns and various Halloween decorations.)
(Despite the bleak atmosphere, there is upbeat music at the party.)
Don't dance like that. It's scary.
Stop it.
(I bet you haven't seen costumes like these in a while.)
(His movements are on a different level.)
(Everyone enters under the hip clown's lead.)
(Frankenstein's Monster is having fun.)
(Giggling)
That's scary. That's scary.
Seok Jin, why didn't you wear makeup?
I am wearing a lot of makeup. It took an hour and a half.
- Really? - I am wearing a lot of makeup.
I got more wrinkles.
Isn't that how you normally look?
(Hong Kong Grandma looks younger than the usual.)
What's your costume?
- "It's the end." - Park Joong Heon.
- "Goblin." - "Goblin."
You need to watch dramas.
- "You..." - "You..."
(Park Joong Heon has a silver tongue that scares a goblin.)
Se Chan looks cool today.
People told me that I am handsome when my face is covered.
- Se Chan is handsome. - The costume brings out his face.
I see that I have to cover everything up.
I didn't know that Kwang Soo's shoulders were so broad.
(Broad shoulders)
(It should be one-meter-wide at least.)
The best part of your costume is your back hair.
- It's not a part of my costume! - Is it your hair?
- Yes. - You grew out your hair for this.
No, I didn't.
- It wasn't for this. - It looks good.
The costume wouldn't have worked without the back hair.
(Frankenstein's Monster has back hair instead of screws.)
(Mummy looks handsome thanks to the costume.)
I don't know her costume is.
Corpse Bride.
- It's well-known. - I haven't watched it.
It's from an animated movie, "Corpse Bride."
An animated movie? Gosh, you have big eyes.
You look like you got Botox under your eyes.
- You became younger. - You became younger.
People tell me that I look younger...
- because my wrinkles are gone. - You look younger.
That must be why people get Botox under their eyes.
I want this costume.
(Corpse Bride can swear until people turn blue.)
(She looks really pretty.)
(Jealous)
So Min's outfit suits her.
- So Min. - She became prettier.
You look prettier than the usual.
- Is this a good look on me? - You look prettier.
You really look pretty.
Jong Kook, are you a dog or Wolverine?
- I think he is a dog. - He is a mutant.
- He is a mutant. - I am a werewolf.
He dressed better than he usually does.
- You know, - It's like a stage costume.
this is better than what I usually wear.
- You look good. - You look fashionable.
His hair looks cool.
You shouldn't have tried to look cool.
I didn't try!
You look like a muscular fool.
- Really? - Your outfit looks cool.
Haha is the one with the best costume.
Haha.
(He is on a different level.)
Why wasn't I notified ahead of time? This is a penalty.
He put a lot of effort...
- into this one episode. - Here is what I think.
If you make a comeback as RGP like this, it will be a hit.
- That's right. - It's a nice costume.
You will be NORAZO's rival.
If she and I team up,
(Do you know this?)
you will get the Big Mac set.
You are right. You are right.
Let's unite!
(So Min's costume and Haha's face make a McDonald's character.)
- You are right. - You are right.
Don't eat Burger King today.
- My goodness. - You will be the talk of the town.
I am Ronald McDonald.
Is this product placement?
Yes.
(Werewolf bites if you touch him.)
(Chucky is a mix of a tiger moth and a crazy woman.)
(Clown isn't a product placement for McDonald's.)
This is a Halloween party.
To be honest, Jae Seok and Seok Jin belong in a comedy skit.
The rest of us...
- belong in Itaewon. - We are dressed for Halloween.
- Hey. - Hey.
Make sure you go.
Make sure you go in that state.
People will take pictures of me.
This costume is stylish. I suddenly feel confident.
For the Halloween party, you will be joined...
by the three guests.
- Really? - We have guests today.
- We are in this state. - Did they dress up as well?
- You will know when you see them. - They must have dressed up.
I will be angry if they haven't dressed up like us.
- They had better not be pretty. - Seriously.
I will be angry.
- What? - "Sugar"?
"Sugar."
- My goodness. - What is that?
Hello.
(He looks fresh.)
(Ahn Hyo Seop, Dracula, has looks that make hearts flutter.)
(Ahn Hyo Seop is a popular actor who captivated older women.)
(He visits Running Man with the burning enthusiasm alone.)
Hello.
- What? - Hello.
You didn't wear any makeup!
- I did wear a lot of makeup. - What is this?
He is handsome! He is handsome!
- What is this? - Why didn't he wear makeup?
Oh, you wore a lot of makeup.
Why didn't Hyo Seop wear any makeup?
Putting wax on hair doesn't count.
I want a costume like that!
- Hyo Seop. - You didn't wear makeup.
What is this?
This is my first time to be rude to a guest.
- You can't tell, but he is Haha. - Go and get your makeup done.
- Get your makeup done. - Hyo Seop.
You didn't wear eyeshadow like Dracula,
- but an idol singer. - It's not like that.
It wasn't my intention.
He has the desire to look good.
You have more desire to look good.
He is handsome.
- He is handsome. - I am in your care.
(Good-looking New Face Ghost)
- Who is next? - Here comes the second guest.
(The second guest)
- I will be angry. - Seriously.
The guests should wear makeup.
(Let's see if this guest is wearing proper makeup.)
- "Havana." - Who is that?
It's the virgin ghost.
(Dancing)
- Hold on. - This virgin ghost is sexy.
- She can dance well. - She can dance well.
Who is she?
(Who could she be?)
- What? - She can dance well.
It's Na Eun! Na Eun!
(Na Eun, Virgin Ghost, makes men's hearts flutter.)
(It's Na Eun!)
- It's Na Eun. - Why didn't you wear makeup?
- It's Na Eun. - Let go of me.
Na Eun didn't wear makeup.
Why didn't you wear much makeup?
- She looks pretty. - She is the virgin ghost.
Our costumes are excessive!
- This is ridiculous. - Gosh, this is embarrassing.
- The guests look pretty. - Put blood on her face at least!
She still would have looked pretty with blood on her face.
- Our costumes are too much! - The guests look pretty.
- Why did we dress up? - This is ridiculous.
That's the proper way of dressing up for Halloween.
- Look at us. - I won't stand still.
- Jae Seok. - What?
You look exactly like your mother.
I became so startled for a second. I'm so sorry, ma'am.
I will put an end to this.
Jae Seok looks like a woman...
- with makeup. - That's right.
Really?
Why are you happy about it?
- He has a middle-aged woman's face. - For goodness' sake.
I am so annoyed.
- The last guest had better be good. - Seriously.
If the last guest is fresh-faced, we won't stand still.
We will go home.
Who is that?
(With a broom,)
(the last guest appears.)
- My goodness. - Come on!
What is that?
She didn't wear makeup.
(Seo Young Hee, Witch, is a rare guest at a variety show.)
(It's impossible to gauge how dangerous she is.)
(Seo Young Hee is an actress with 1,000 faces.)
(She is genius who pulls off both comedy and horror.)
She didn't wear makeup.
- Hello. - I refuse to work today.
- This is too much. - Seriously.
- This is hilarious. - She is so pretty.
Her face is practically bare.
The guests are here, but everyone is angry.
I am happy to see you. I am sorry.
- I am sorry, we just... - I am just too angry.
We are happy to see you,
but we thought the guests would wear heavy makeup...
to celebrate Halloween.
That's the proper way of dressing up for Halloween.
We have three guests today.
Let's start with Seo Young Hee.
Hello. Hello.
- Young Hee is an actress... - I am a big fan.
- who played a ghost many times. - That's right.
- A ghost. - She played a villain many times.
She played a character who kills old ladies in an island.
- That's right. - That's right.
This is the first time Young Hee is joining us on Running Man.
Yes, this is my first time here.
As for this kind of variety show where we stand and move around,
I've been only on "Love Letter."
- "Love Letter"? - "Love Letter"?
- That's ages ago. - She was on "Love Letter"?
- She was on "Love Letter"? - You were on "Love Letter"?
(During the 2000s, "Love Letter" was popular among young adults.)
(Back then, Jong Min and Young Hee were a popular couple.)
(She's a master at variety shows. Or is she not?)
- She's quite old. - She starred on it with Young Eun,
- Chun Myung Hoon, and Jong Min. - That's right.
My goodness, no way.
Is this your first variety show after "Love Letter"?
- Yes, it is. - What?
This kind of system is all new to me.
- Hyo Seop, why did you laugh? - I was told to laugh a lot.
(My agency told me to laugh a lot.)
Even so, how can he laugh at nothing?
- That laugh was unnatural. - I'm sorry.
- He has a handsome smile. - Exactly.
It's been a while since I saw someone taller than Kwang Soo.
- Seriously. - How tall are you? I'm curious.
I'm 187cm tall.
- Kwang Soo is taller. - Right.
- But your body proportion... - Why does he not look taller?
- What do you mean? - It's the body proportion.
- Why don't I look taller? - Something is completely different.
It's the makeup.
I always tell you this.
If you want to be tall, you should have his physique.
No, it's the makeup.
I understand why it'd seem so. It has to be the makeup.
By the way, Kwang Soo is...
- very tall among comedians. - That's right.
- You haven't paid your club dues. - You're in a comedian association.
- Why would I pay the club dues? - You're behind a lot of dues.
No, I'm not in it.
Pay up your dues.
- Visit the meeting room too. - Yes, come visit us.
Whenever we put on makeup,
they put a lot of paint in front of me.
Last time, it was blue. And green, today. They use a lot of paint.
You're frustrating. This just shows...
you have two jobs now.
- Your main career is the comedian. - That's right.
- You're acting on the side too. - Exactly.
We won't stop you from acting.
- However, pay your dues. - Why would I?
My goodness, he's so weird.
He won't pay the dues.
Let's interview Hyo Seop.
You mentioned earlier. Did your agency give you tips?
- He's sweating a lot. - He must be nervous.
- His costume is thick too. - He's just nervous.
Let me wipe that for you.
(Talking kindly)
- Thank you. - Let me wipe that for you.
(What are you doing?)
Please get a close-up of this.
You should wipe your drool instead.
You should just wipe off your booger.
People have been badmouthing me a lot.
Okay, let me wipe this.
- Wipe your snout instead. - Did your agency give you any tips?
Like the one you said earlier. They told you to laugh a lot.
(Did his agency give him any special advice?)
They just...
- told me to sweat less. - Okay.
- You sweat a lot. - Yes, I do sweat a lot by nature.
Here's my observation.
- Because he's nervous, - That's right.
- he's exploding with sweat. - I see.
- When you're new to the industry... - He's sweating more and more.
or when you star on variety shows, usually...
Why are you laughing?
(He laughs as soon as he looks at Haha.)
You look so funny.
Unbelievable.
- Hey, sorry to interrupt. - Look at the mirror.
Here's my advice. Don't talk about serious stuff today.
Usually...
(He suddenly speaks in a high-pitched voice.)
(Do you want me to lose all my seriousness?)
People predict what will happen on the show.
Don't discuss serious stuff.
(His costume is pushing him to the edge.)
Don't mention serious topics.
- Gosh, the CG was amazing. - Seriously.
Tell us about today's race.
Today's race is Dangerous Invitation for the Halloween party...
that will unite ghosts from the East and West.
"Dangerous Invitation."
Among 11 guests who are invited to the party,
there are real ghosts who have grudges...
against the humankind and have penetrated...
to turn humans into ghosts.
- I saw this coming today. - My goodness.
- Who is it? - How did you know?
- Who is it? - How did you know that?
(Striding)
It's not me.
What are you doing? It's not me.
- It's you, isn't it? - I'm just Frankenstein's Monster.
- I'm just Frankenstein's Monster. - Isn't it you?
Wait, it's not me.
Whenever there's a spy...
We have to suspect him first.
All right. After going through three missions,
winning members will receive a hint about the ghost.
If humans work together and get rid of all the ghosts,
Team Humans will win.
However, if the ghosts eliminate all of the humans,
Team Humans will lose.
Goodness, I must catch those ghosts today.
All right. After you change into your team's uniform,
- you'll start the first mission. - We dressed up for this?
We'll remove our makeup now?
- Hold on. We'll remove the makeup? - We're going to remove it now?
- Hey. - Already?
Let's keep the makeup to the end.
- It took me two hours to do this. - Are you kidding me?
- Are you joking right now? - Hold on.
I thought we were going to keep it the whole day.
- This is it? - It's over?
- The first game... - What is this?
(They set out for the first mission.)
It took longer to put on and remove the makeup...
than to film with the makeup on.
(They finish washing their faces.)
I can't believe we wasted that makeup.
(The members are brought to the next place for the party.)
Kwang Soo, now that you're not wearing that makeup,
I think you looked better before.
- You had an excuse before at least. - No, no.
I didn't completely remove the makeup.
I left a bit of makeup.
(I didn't completely remove the green paint.)
So Min, did you put on the Egg Ghost's makeup?
- She looks cute. - I removed all of my makeup.
The 1st clue about the ghosts is at stake on the 1st mission.
It's Dancing with the Ghosts.
(Dancing with the Ghosts)
- Hey, let's get the hint. - Great.
- We must catch the ghosts. - Let's get them.
I'm sure there is only one ghost,
but the ghost must have a helper.
- There's a helper. - Of course.
It can't be just one.
- It has to be more than 2. - I think it's one of you.
- Then are there 3 ghosts? Or 4? - What?
(Hyo Seop makes a mysterious remark.)
- Are there 4? - There are 3 ghosts?
- How do you know there are three? - How do you know that?
- Who told you that? - What's going on?
- I don't know how many there are. - Are you sure?
You didn't tell us how many yet?
- He started to sweat now. - He's sweating.
- This is it. - No.
- You're sweating again. - No, I'm just...
Let me retract what I said.
Fine. I'll pretend I didn't hear you.
They said there were three ghosts?
I don't remember hearing such a thing.
Is he acting or what?
(Is Hyo Seop the ghost among us?)
You'll form Team A and Team B with five people in each team.
For 100 seconds, you'll pass on the dance moves in a relay.
If the last member on the line correctly guesses...
the title and singer, it's a success.
If you answer more than 8 songs, you'll get 3 hints.
If you answer more than 5, you'll get 2 hints.
If you answer more than 3, you'll get 1 hint.
Team A is already formed with five members.
- How? - Is that so?
From me to So Min, it makes a team of five.
(Jae Seok, three guests, and So Min make up a team.)
- Come on, Jae Seok. - You'll form Team B.
- Why? - You took all the good ones.
- What? I just have Na Eun. - We're doomed then.
I want to play with the guest too.
- I want to play with the guest. - Why do you mean?
Play what?
- You're unbelievable. - They can be on the same team.
- My goodness. - Why don't the female guests pick?
- They are the female guests. - Why don't you two choose members?
- You should each pick a member. - Okay.
They can play rock-paper-scissors.
Is there another game than rock-paper-scissors?
- Stop it! - That's enough!
(Don't even bring up about the Race of Wits.)
- That game isn't suitable here. - Hasn't it...
- been a while since we played? - Stop it.
I hate having to observe other people's wits.
- It's been long since we played. - It's only been a week.
My goodness.
Does anyone have the blood type B?
- Blood type B? - Should we use our blood types?
- I like that idea. - I have blood type B.
- Blood type B. - Blood type B.
- It's Na Eun. Okay. - Blood type B. Okay.
- Okay. - Great. This is great.
(Na Eun has blood type B?)
(Mine is blood type B too.)
- Stop lying. - I know you don't have it.
Why would you lie about your blood?
- I don't know mine. - Don't lie about your blood.
Hey, you don't have blood type B.
Hey, this isn't good. That's not a good way to form teams.
Is any of you Leo?
- Me! - Me!
(Haha is full of ideas. He suggests using zodiac signs.)
- You're a Leo? - What about Sheep?
- I'm Sheep. - I'm Deer.
My sign is Mat!
(What?)
- Me. - You're Mat?
I'm Grave Site.
(This is a fun pun game.)
Grave Site? You're a Grave Site?
- Grave Site? - You're a Grave Site?
(Jee Seok Jin, Hong Kong Grandma, and Grave Site)
Grave Site. Seok Jin is a Grave Site.
All right, everyone. Let's be fair.
Okay. How about this?
- You'll play rock-paper-scissors. - Come on!
- Hey, we said that earlier. - We should've done that earlier!
- You're just wasting time. - Look how many minutes passed.
We ought to think and brainstorm.
I will accept your opinions...
and follow them.
You two should play rock-paper-scissors.
- We'll choose our members? - Yes.
You two will pick.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Na Eun wins.)
Na Eun won.
Na Eun has an upper hand at this mission.
- That's right. - I want to be in Na Eun's team.
We have to dance, right?
- That's right. - She has an advantage.
(Silently pleading)
What should I do?
(Pick me.)
(Gazing)
(She turns away when their eyes meet.)
You have completely wiped out memories of Se Chan.
(Is he that bad?)
- Na Eun, look over here too. - She forgot about me.
- She completely forgot about him. - Wait.
(You were shy when I nicknamed you Beautiful Deer.)
(And you said that you wanted to become a close friend.)
- She didn't even look at him. - Hey, Jae Seok.
She never once looked at me.
For a while, Se Chan couldn't forget about Na Eun.
Na Eun, choose one member.
It's just a team game for a day.
- Don't let that pressure you. - That's right.
- It's just for one game. - Me?
Okay.
(He tries to force his way into Team Na Eun.)
- What? She didn't pick anyone yet. - She just picked me.
- She just chose me. - Jae Seok.
She looked at me.
- Seriously? - Really?
- You chose So Min? - She wants to stand out.
(Vicious slandering)
(He slanders Na Eun out of jealousy.)
- My goodness. - Hey.
- You're so mean. - This is unbelievable.
Na Eun, you're so mean.
- That's not true. - You guys are cruel.
- You're so mean. - You're so mean.
Na Eun just gave me goosebumps.
We haven't seen her for a while. She changed a lot.
- She's so cruel. - How cruel.
- That's not true. - The Queen of Leggings.
Young Hee will choose next.
Me? All right.
She wants to stand out.
Seriously. She wants to look pretty.
I won't wait for long.
(He's bluffing.)
- Haha. - That's it.
- My goodness. - This is the best combination.
(Na Eun chose Haha.)
- I'll choose Hyo Seop. - Hyo Seop.
Team Good-looking!
Let's go! Let's go!
If you don't pick Se Chan, you'll look mean.
Se Chan.
Okay!
You're trying to look nice.
(She turns down his handshake.)
Good job.
(That's... That's all right.)
(Team A: Na Eun, So Min, Haha, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, and Se Chan)
(Team B: Young Hee, Hyo Seop, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Jae Seok)
Which team will go first?
- Should we go 1st? - Yes, let's go 1st.
- We have six people in our team. - Okay. Let's watch carefully.
As we watch them play, we have to single out the ghosts.
- The ghosts will look obvious. - Don't mess up in the middle.
(Someone among them might be a ghost, sabotaging the mission.)
(They play songs unrelated to the mission.)
Great.
(Na Eun will present, and Se Chan will answer.)
I like the song.
Tell you what.
Even if he's listening to recent songs,
the way he dances is different...
compared to the old people.
(Unlike young members who are dancing trendy moves...)
Seok Jin is doing the traditional mask dance.
(This guy from the old times is engrossed with an old dance move.)
Get ready.
- Start. - We should observe.
She's starting now.
(Okay, I got this.)
(So Min, you know these moves, right?)
(Na Eun puts her hands on her face...)
(and gestures shooting a gun. What song is this?)
("Gashina" by SUNMI, 2017)
(Na Eun perfectly copied the key moves.)
(I know this one.)
It's so easy.
They'll definitely get it right.
(So Min's moves are perfect too.)
They can definitely get it right.
(Good job, So Min.)
- If they get it wrong... - They would be the ghosts.
(Only ghosts don't know what song this is.)
(Oh, I know this one.)
(Jong Kook, look at this. I'm scratching my face.)
(The attractive move turns into having itchy cheeks.)
That's wrong.
(It looks weird, but I think I got it.)
Okay.
Many of them are good dancers.
(Jong Kook managed to understand Seok Jin's moves.)
(Se Chan doesn't seem to be sure.)
(You don't know this song?)
Let me answer.
"Gashina" by SUNMI.
Okay!
(Correct)
(Let's continue this way!)
- Come on! - What was this?
He did it a bit wrong.
You should have done this instead.
(Is Seok Jin just old or is he a ghost?)
(They move onto the next question.)
(Okay, I got this.)
(She moves her arms vigorously.)
(What is that?)
(You don't know what song it is?)
("Fire" by BTS, 2016)
(Na Eun perfectly copied the moves from the intro.)
(You're supposed to move arms like that?)
(I got it.)
(So Min got it perfectly.)
(It's so easy.)
(Haha pulls it off 200 percent.)
- That's perfect. - It's impossible to get it wrong.
- You have to get it wrong. - It's so easy.
(I know this one.)
(What?)
(An old man's mask dance)
He's a ghost.
- Isn't it too obvious? - He's 100 percent a ghost.
I'm sure.
(He seems to be hoping the mission would fail.)
You know this one, right?
(It's not sure if Seok Jin is a ghost or just a bad dancer.)
(Jong Kook copies Seok Jin's moves without understanding them.)
(Will Se Chan be able to say the correct answer?)
"Fire" by BTS.
(It's the correct answer.)
He's so good.
Okay!
(Jong Kook and Se Chan's amazing teamwork)
Wasn't that good enough?
Don't go overboard.
Seok Jin is a ghost.
(Seok Jin is suspicious again. Is he really a ghost?)
(There are only 40 seconds left now.)
(I can do these moves perfectly.)
(Confused)
Oh, that one.
(It's my song. "Mr. Chu" by Apink.)
("Mr. Chu" by Apink, 2014)
(These are Apink's most famous dance moves.)
(Na Eun repeats the dance moves.)
(What is that?)
Oh, that one.
(Let me just try.)
Seok Jin is good at this one.
(Na Eun did this.)
(She moved her arms like this...)
(and did this with her fingers.)
(You have to kiss, not poke.)
(Na Eun...)
(made a V sign.)
(Haha is not sure.)
It's too difficult. What should I do?
(Haha points at Na Eun.)
(A square face?)
(What's that?)
(Seok Jin starts dancing a little irritated.)
(Square face)
- Park Nam Jung. - Park Nam Jung.
(The cute kissing gesture...)
(turned into the alphabet dance.)
(I'm a bit confused.)
(It's something like this.)
That's wrong.
That's not the right move.
"With My Dad."
It's "Mr. Chu."
(There are only 20 seconds left.)
The ghosts must be in action now.
(She shoots a gun and does a body wave.)
- I got it. - What is it?
"Ddu-du Ddu-du."
(It's obviously "Ddu-du Ddu-du.")
("Ddu-du Ddu-du" by BLACKPINK, 2018)
(These gun-shooting moves became a hit last summer.)
(So Min gets it right away.)
Okay.
(But...)
(her moves look a little different.)
(I have no idea.)
(That's not quite right.)
(Ddu-du ddu-du)
(Like this?)
(It's too hard for a bad dancer like Seok Jin.)
I'm not sure. It's too hard.
- You know what it is? - No.
(I'm sorry. I don't know what it is.)
It's too hard.
(How is the suspect going to dance?)
He's a ghost.
(He definitely acts like a ghost again.)
He's a ghost. I'm 100 percent sure.
What's that?
(They got 2 questions right in 100 seconds.)
- Isn't it "Ddu-du Ddu-du"? - Yes.
- Who did it wrong? - You should have done this.
You should have done this. Who did it wrong?
So Min is a little suspicious.
She...
- Is she a ghost? - I can't dance to new songs.
(She gives an excuse.)
(But So Min is known to be good at dancing to new songs.)
She says she can't dance to new songs.
I don't know the moves.
She's acting a little strangely.
I just copied Na Eun.
Na Eun must have known the moves,
but she did them a little wrong.
(It's impossible for Na Eun not to know the moves.)
(It's strange that she seemed unsure and did the moves a bit wrong.)
- How did Na Eun do it? - She didn't make it clear.
- Look at that. - You should have done this.
Her dance is a bit pretentious.
(Criticizing)
- She's a little pretentious. - She's pretentious.
- She's pretentious. - When she dances,
she doesn't do this. She's like this instead.
She is a good dancer, but she's a little pretentious.
- You're right. - Seriously?
Just because she failed once?
So Min started it.
Is that why?
(Is Na Eun just pretentious or is she a ghost?)
Should I say the answer?
You should do something because you know many songs.
Well... Na Eun is the most suspicious.
Na Eun, try it. Do you want to be the last person?
So Min and Seok Jin are seriously suspicious.
Seok Jin is definitely a ghost.
I just didn't know the moves.
Okay. Seok Jin, come here.
- He either didn't know or... - He's too suspicious.
I seriously didn't know.
But remember, Seok Jin loves attention.
I realized it last week.
He loves close-ups.
Young Hee, you can do this!
- You can do this! - I'm a terrible dancer.
We have to get many right to win a hint.
If you just copy the moves,
we can get it right.
- I'll do my best. - You can do this!
All right.
Ready.
Hyo Seop.
(He is facing the first player.)
Please turn around.
(Variety shows are so hard.)
He's cute.
Ready.
(They're given 100 seconds. They start from the first question.)
(What is this?)
What should I do?
I don't remember anything.
(She forgets everything when she turns around.)
(She tries to memorize the moves again.)
What should I do?
(Clumsy)
That's Ppak Gu.
(It brings back memories.)
- "Gag Concert." - That's Ppak Gu.
What should I do?
(Young Hee shows the Ppak Gu dance to Hyo Seop.)
What is this?
(He copies the dance perfectly.)
(This is what Young Hee did.)
What's this?
- That's Ppak Gu. - That's Ppak Gu.
(The handsome Ppak Gu)
What is it? Is it taekkyeon﻿?
(Ji Hyo becomes confused.)
(She is infected by the Ppak Gu virus too.)
(Am I doing it right?)
What should we do with those three?
- What's that? - What should I do?
That's just a fool.
(The Ppak Gu brother and sisters)
What is this?
(This is how it should look.)
("Fantastic Baby" by BigBang, 2012)
(The key moves make you look somehow like Ppak Gu.)
What is this?
They're in trouble.
(Seok Jin turns the moves into...)
(the "Swallowtail" dance.)
Like this.
(Kwang Soo takes it seriously.)
What is this? Hey!
(Flapping)
Are you kidding me?
What is this?
(That's not quite right.)
- What is this? - What should we do?
"Idol" by BTS?
(Wrong)
What is this?
Young Hee can't possibly be this bad at dancing.
- She even saw the video clip. - Let's see what it was.
(They start to suspect Young Hee.)
("Dance in the Rhythm" by Kim Wan Sun)
- What should I do? - Hurry up.
(Young Hee is in trouble.)
(The first question made the members suspect Young Hee.)
(Will she able to clear up that suspicion?)
What's that?
(She seems to know the moves.)
(But she makes them look completely different.)
Young Hee is a terrible dancer. What's that?
(Is she a bad dancer or a ghost?)
What's that?
- What's that? - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Hyo Seop copies Young Hee's moves again.)
He's a bad dancer, but he's cute.
(He is handsome and bad at dancing.)
(What is this?)
(Ji Hyo is infected by the bad dancer virus.)
(I have no idea.)
What should we do with those three?
- They're suspicious. - What's that?
You three should all go to a club together.
(It's Seok Jin to turn to show the moves to Kwang Soo.)
(He does the "Swallowtail" dance again.)
- We're suddenly at a marketplace. - I don't know what this is.
What is that?
- Isn't that "Macarena"? - That's "Macarena."
- Isn't that "Macarena"? - What's that?
(Isn't that "Macarena" from 1992?)
What's that?
(It went from Kim Wan Sun to "Swallowtail" to "Macarena.)
- It's "Macarena." - It's "Macarena."
Isn't it "Macarena"?
"Macarena"?
(Jae Seok's answer "Macarena" is incorrect.)
- Isn't it "Macarena"? - What are you doing?
- Wait a minute. - You have 15 seconds left.
Hurry, we don't have time.
She's terrible at dancing. We're in trouble.
(I know this for certain.)
- She got it. - We're in trouble.
Here it is.
- I know what it is. - I know this.
Did you see it?
("Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND)
(Young Hee does this dance well.)
I know this for certain.
Do exactly what she did.
That's not it.
(Moving about)
- Oh, no. - Hyo Seop is in trouble.
Take a look.
(Hyo Seop's dance is too weak.)
- Hurry up. - I know what it is.
That's right.
(It goes back to the correct moves of "Bboom Bboom.")
- She's got it. - Is that it?
(Is that it? Okay.)
- I bet Seok Jin will do his dance. - Right.
Seok Jin will do it.
("Bboom Bboom"?)
(But it turns into...)
(It turns into his left and right movement.)
- Right? - You were right.
There he goes again.
- Goodness. He always does it. - There he goes again.
He moves like a ghost, right?
- What's this? - What is it?
Take a look.
(Apparently, this is it.)
It's "Bboom Bboom."
It's "Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND.
(Surprisingly Jae Seok answers correctly.)
- Did he get it right? - It's "Bboom Bboom."
He answered it.
- He was right. - He was correct.
(The dance turns back into "Bboom Bboom" miraculously.)
- What was the first one? - That's surprising.
The first one was "Fantastic Baby."
- "Fantastic Baby"? - That was it?
- This is what to do. - How did you do it, Young Hee?
How could you not know?
- She danced like Ppak Gu. - What was it?
What's certain is that there are five ghosts.
Hyo Seop could dance a little,
but he made no effort.
I can't dance.
(He scratches his head.)
What? Is that your acting voice?
While scratching his head,
he says, "Gosh, I can't dance at all."
(While scratching his head, he says, "I can't dance at all.")
(Is that some kind of drama?)
I've never seen anyone scratch his head outside of dramas.
- It was like acting. - That's because I'm nervous.
Let's have 6 of us play 1 more time.
It should be six suspicious people.
Let's find who they are. Pick those who aren't good.
(They pick six candidates for being a ghost.)
Get ready, set...
(So Min, Na Eun, Young Hee, Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Haha)
("Growl" by EXO)
(She copies the dance perfectly.)
This is it. It's obvious.
This is it.
It's EXO.
(I know, it's EXO.)
(But he doesn't know the song title?)
- Hey, come on. - Don't you know it?
Haha, you're a ghost.
There's no way.
- It's EXO's what? - You can't remember it?
They dance in school uniform.
- Haha. - "Growl."
("Growl" is correct.)
- Okay. - He almost missed it.
That's right.
- It's definitely Haha. - He was buying time.
He's suspicious.
("Gee" by Girls' Generation is famous for its dance.)
- It's easy. - That's right.
- Na Eun is good. - That's it.
That's all you need to do.
(Next is Seok Jin's turn.)
(Knock, knock, is anyone home?)
How do I do it?
What's wrong with him?
- He's knocking. - Why is he knocking?
(The ghost continues to knock.)
- It's "Gee" by Girls' Generation. - Yes.
(Haha answers correctly despite Seok Jin's knocking.)
It's confusing.
Isn't he strange?
He's definitely a ghost.
Everyone should know that.
- Everyone must know. - Everyone should know it.
- Right? - I know.
Okay.
(Both Young Hee and Jae Seok succeed.)
I know.
(He's very confident.)
(Hey, Haha.)
(Wait a minute.)
He's very suspicious.
(He kicks Seok Jin.)
(Go away, you ghost.)
(Seok Jin is a ghost who's stuck awkwardly.)
"Dim Memories of You" by Hyun Jin Young.
- Okay. - He got it correct.
(I'm sorry for kicking you.)
Okay.
You answered a total of six questions.
You get two hints.
- That's a lot. - Someone from the last group,
please come out.
(I'll go.)
Is it just one person?
The last group?
- This goes to the last group. - We're the last group.
They decide whether to share it or not.
- Why? - No.
- Jae Seok. - Let us see it.
- Wait, those who are suspicious... - We're on the same team.
- Jae Seok. - We're the last group.
We helped the last group.
I said that we're the last group.
We picked you.
Joseph, block him.
(He should learn a lesson.)
We should look at it together.
Who are you calling Joseph?
Joseph is someone from the Bible.
He's Hyo Seop.
Who's Joseph?
- Wait a minute. - Wait.
(Jae Seok touches his chest.)
What are you doing?
Why did you touch me?
(He's very volatile.)
- I was just... - Why did you touch me?
- I can't share the hint. - Apologize to me now.
- Apologize to his chest. - Hurry.
- I'm sorry. - Okay.
That's cute. He's cute.
Hey, kiss right here.
- I'm sorry. - Apologize.
Okay.
(He apologizes directly to his chest.)
(Jong Kook is satisfied.)
- It didn't hurt your pride, did it? - No.
It's better to apologize to his chest.
You seemed cute too.
It didn't hurt my pride.
If you did something wrong, it's good to apologize.
Let's not do that.
We don't know who the ghost is.
Right, and the hint would be very vague.
- It's a woman. - The first...
- What did it say? - It's a woman.
It means that it's a man.
- There's a younger female ghost. - Yes, the first is a female ghost.
It's you.
(One of these four is a ghost.)
- It's Jae Seok. - That's not it.
One of the three ghosts is a man.
- Are there three ghosts? - No.
Three ghosts?
We got him.
It's over. Seok Jin is one of them.
Are there three ghosts?
- It's over for Seok Jin. - Three ghosts?
- They're Hyo Seop... - It's over.
- and Seok Jin. - It's over.
- They're Hyo Seop and Seok Jin. - It's definitely him.
It's obvious.
- He's denying it. - He said it.
Stop it.
- Look at him. - Let us think.
(They've found another hint in their suspicion.)
"The ghosts are 2 men and 1 woman."
"2 men and 1 woman."
Three ghosts is correct.
(There are 3 ghosts.)
- Joseph said it a moment ago. - They're here.
- Joseph said it. - No way.
- No, he didn't. - He's Hyo Seop, not Joseph.
- Hyo Seop? - Seok Jin is...
- more like a grandfather. - I know.
That's why it's a hint.
- Is that why? - If he's called a grandfather...
- It's to confuse us. - Right.
2 men and 1 woman.
We've found out the two of them.
(Is either Seok Jin or Hyo Seop a ghost?)
- I'm hungry. - Abalone galbitang sounds good.
Next mission is a chance to win lunch and additional hints.
It's called Your Name has Three Syllables.
(Your Name has Three Syllables)
Divide into a group of two.
Listen to the first syllable.
You and your partner answer one after the other.
Complete the three-syllable word.
In six dishes prepared for today's lunch,
a sentence about ghosts is distributed.
- We have to put them together. - We do.
This won't be easy.
- There are many twists. - Okay, everybody.
- I'm uncomfortable. - Why?
A ghost is sitting next to the person next to me.
- What? - It's Seok Jin.
- Don't be fooled again. - Seriously.
I'm never it in the end. It's the same today.
- Everyone. - Goodness.
Four female members will pick male members.
(Picking one's partner determines their success.)
Okay, I got it.
- Ji Hyo, pick your partner first. - Yes?
- Do I go first? - Pick one.
Ji Hyo has to eat no matter what.
She has to win.
Is she looking at you?
Won't she pick Haha?
Don't I exist? She doesn't look at me.
You aren't human, so I won't look at you.
- He's a ghost. - You're a ghost.
- My goodness. - You aren't human.
I'm not a ghost.
I know which member Ji Hyo won't choose.
Kwang Soo is out.
- Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo is out.
- What about you? - I'm out too.
Jae Seok and Se Chan are out.
- Seok Jin is out. - I have potential.
Are you over with Haha?
- Are you over with Haha? - She needs to find someone new.
(She might need to find a new business partner.)
- She just glared at him. - She's a ghost.
She's a ghost.
- She's ghost indeed. - She's the original ghost.
She's from "Whispering Corridors."
(Do you want me to make it scary?)
It's from that movie.
You aren't over with Haha.
It isn't over yet.
- It's Ji Hyo and Haha. - Okay.
Please tell me today. What makes me attractive?
- Everything about you. - Goodness.
Tell him today.
I want to play with someone else.
I pick...
someone easy.
- Seok Jin? - Yes.
(What?)
Is that easy?
(Wouldn't a ghost pick another ghost?)
- They're both ghosts. - I bet he's good.
I'm great.
I'm also Young Hee's fan.
Didn't she watch him play all day?
- How can she think he'd be good? - Seriously.
Wait, are they ghosts?
(Are Seok Jin and Young Hee a team of ghosts?)
What about Na Eun?
(Na Eun is another candidate for a ghost.)
Na Eun could be a ghost.
I don't think she is. She played well.
(It's okay even if you're a ghost.)
- I don't think she's a ghost. - She played well.
(She approaches slowly.)
(She comes towards me.)
(Please, please)
(Tell me that it's Se Chan.)
- I pick Jae Seok. - Me?
(I'm sorry, Se Chan.)
- Okay. - Me?
Why did you look at the staff and the director?
Why did you do that?
- I didn't. - Why did you look at the director?
Na Eun could have picked Se Chan.
She works hard.
- I was uncomfortable. - Why?
Na Eun picked me when I'm sitting next to Se Chan.
- I was uncomfortable. - It's okay.
(I'll wait until the day when we become closer.)
It's too difficult.
Whom should I pick?
I don't know either. Pick Jong Kook.
- Just pick Hyo Seop. - Pick Hyo Seop.
Isn't it your first time picking a male guest?
- By the way, - Pick Hyo Seop.
if Hyo Seop doesn't get chosen...
So Min.
Why are you blushing?
You're not choosing someone to go out with.
- It's just a game. - Choose someone.
Me?
Why are you not looking at Hyo Seop?
It's not like that.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Why?
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Why? - Why?
- We don't want to. - Why do we have to compete for you?
You choose someone.
- You're being ridiculous. - What are you doing?
Why would we do that? We don't want to.
- Just play rock-paper-scissors. - We don't want to.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - You four.
The winner becomes her partner?
- The winner. - Hold on.
I hate the fact that we're doing this.
If you don't show anything, you lose.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Win, win, lose, lose)
Okay.
(The losers are happier.)
- Why are you so happy? - I mean...
I really hope Jong Kook will win.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- The winner becomes her partner. - You have to win me.
She says we have to win her.
(You have to win me.)
(We'd rather lose.)
I hate it.
Rock-paper-scissors
(I'll lose so that I don't have to win you.)
(Who will win So Min?)
Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min becomes Jong Kook's.)
(You're happy?)
Jong Kook looked happy.
(Jong Kook looks happy.)
(Jong Kook wins So Min in the end.)
My goodness.
- I like it. - Okay.
- I love it. - It's so funny.
I love the result.
It's so funny.
The competition was so fierce.
- It was. - By the way,
Hyo Seop needs to think about this matter.
This has never happened before.
He is the first male guest who didn't get chosen.
He should...
- He shouldn't be sitting here. - His agency should think...
After the shooting,
- his agency should have a meeting. - He shouldn't be sitting here.
- He... - This is what I thought.
"Wait."
"You're the first girl who didn't choose me."
That's why.
Was that your intention?
Seriously...
Focus on the show.
(Male lead Ahn Hyo Seop)
"I'm glad it's you."
(Female lead Jeon So Min)
All right.
Stay on alert, Ji Hyo. It's a group game.
You have to say a celebrity's name.
- A celebrity's name? - A celebrity's name.
It's a celebrity's name.
The ghosts will try to fail.
They definitely will.
It's easy to fail.
That's right.
Start. Yu.
- Jae. - Seok.
That was easy.
- Park. - Jae.
Beom.
- Is this how you do it? - Choi.
- Chang. - Min.
But celebrity names are easy.
It's easy.
Good job.
- Bravo. - Good job.
(Haha and Ji Hyo win a dish.)
All right. It's celebrity names again.
- What should I do? - It's easy.
Ready.
- Start. - Ko.
- So. - Young.
Yoon.
- Je. - Pil.
(Yoon Je Pil?)
Hold on.
Who is Yoon Je Pil?
- She meant Yoon Je Moon. - Yoon Je Moon.
He's definitely a ghost.
That's not it.
He's 100 percent a ghost.
Which celebrity's name starts with "Yoon Je"?
- There are many. - All right.
You failed, so you lose a dish.
- What should we take away? - Dried seaweed.
- Dried seaweed. - I'm sick of it.
But it's too predictable.
- It might have a good hint. - Take away the dried seaweed.
It's hard.
- Let's move on. - Is it our turn?
- The dried seaweed was taken away. - It's me and Na Eun's turn.
It's food names this time.
- Food. - Okay.
I'm confident.
- Here we go. - Food.
- Start. - Gim.
I thought Na Eun was going first.
(I thought Na Eun was going first.)
- Hold on. - Let us try again.
- Is Jae Seok a ghost? - Is Jae Seok a ghost?
He gave me the chills.
- You gave me goosebumps. - That's not it.
What should we do?
- That's not it. - It was Jae Seok?
I'm not a ghost.
I just froze. I thought Na Eun was going first.
- It's food names. - It's easy with categories.
- Right. - Okay.
Start. Gim.
Bap.
(Only two syllables?)
You could have said, "gimmari."
- He just ended it. - Gosh.
He only cares about himself.
This is not okay.
He's so selfish.
- He's suspicious. - Hold on.
- Are you a ghost? - No.
- Let me try again. - He just ended it.
What are you talking about?
Another dish will be taken away.
- I'm sorry. - Gosh.
Hold on. Na Eun didn't get to say anything.
- He said, "gimbap." - Let us try again.
- It just happened. - "Gimbap."
- Period. - Period.
- He just ended it. - He ended it.
- He put a period. - It's so funny.
One dish will be taken away.
Hyo Seop, choose one dish.
- Please take away anchovies. - Okay.
(Hyo Seop is squeezed to half.)
- He's scared. - He feels uncomfortable.
- Do you want to switch? - His shoulders were squeezed.
You like it, right?
- You like sitting next to me? - Yes, I do.
Hyo Seop is sweating again.
He's covered in sweat.
It's nice to rest on his shoulders.
They're so broad.
I hope we'll have Lee Soon Jae as a guest someday.
I want to see if Jong Kook will put his arm on his shoulder.
Me too.
I shouldn't do that.
So Min.
Okay. Focus.
So Min, let's do this.
Let's show them.
This time, it's animals.
- That's good. - I like it.
- It's good. - It's too easy.
Start. Song.
- A. - Ji.
- Oh. - Ri.
Bal.
(Duck feet?)
- That's not an animal. - Duck feet?
What are you doing?
- What's wrong with it? - What's that?
- You could have said, "osori." - It has to be an animal.
Duck feet.
Jong Kook is supposed to be angry with So Min,
but he knows it's his fault,
so he didn't say anything.
What's wrong with "duck feet"?
Why didn't you think of "ojingeo"?
I get it. Stop now.
- Mr. Gimbap. - Please stop now.
- What are you doing? - You've said it many times.
- Mr. Gimbap. - Once is enough.
- How could they not think of it? - My goodness.
It's not like you did well.
We're the same.
Please choose a dish to be taken away.
Let's choose japchae.
Let's take away kimchi.
I think kimchi has an important hint.
It's possible.
- They'd think we'd take it away. - Okay.
- Japchae. - We'll make sure to get it.
- Let's do celebrity names. - Okay.
- Celebrity names? - Celebrity names.
- Think of idol groups. - Okay.
- It might be harder. - Probably.
- Right. - Let's go.
Seon.
- So it's a celebrity? - Seon.
(It's the same with Jae Seok's strategy.)
It's just a question.
Okay.
Hyo Seop, you're busted.
- No. - He's definitely a ghost.
He came back to Korea only recently.
He did?
That's why he can't...
- do this game well. - We should give him an advantage.
Now I understand.
We should have let him say English words.
Something like "maple syrup."
You should have given him "ma."
- What? - "Maple syrup."
That's five syllables.
- Okay. - Gosh.
What's with him?
- It's celebrity names. - Celebrity names.
- I'm sorry. - Group names are okay too.
- Okay. - It might be a group.
If you can't think of a person's name, think of a group's name.
Here we go.
Go.
Doo.
(A celebrity whose name starts with "Go Doo" and has 4 syllables?)
(Even someone who's lived in Korea all his life is not sure.)
Are you thinking of Go Doo Shim?
- Hey! - Go Doo Shim.
- Go Doo Shim. - Go Doo Shim.
- Go Doo Shim. - Gosh.
Oh, I get it.
- Hyo Seop, focus. - Kwang Soo.
It's not your fault.
- Go Doo Shim. - It's not your fault.
- What's with you guys? - Four syllables are hard.
It's really hard.
- What are you talking about? - I can do three syllables.
Four syllables are easier.
- Easier? - Yes.
- Mr. Gimbap. - What?
- Aren't you Mr. Gimbap? - Please sit down.
- You can't say that. - Gosh.
He's Mr. Gimbap.
Another dish will be taken away.
- I'd take away grilled pork. - Young Hee.
It's better to keep it.
- Young Hee should choose. - Grilled pork goes well with rice.
We should let Young Hee choose.
Hold on.
Why do you keep hitting me?
What are you doing?
I don't want to sit between these two.
- Can't we just talk? - I didn't hit you.
- I didn't hit you. - You did.
You didn't?
Apologize to his arm.
(Humiliating)
I didn't hit him.
- Apologize. - Kiss his arm.
- Kiss his arm. - Do it.
(I'm sorry, arm.)
I'm sorry.
What should we take away?
- As the others have been saying, - Kimchi.
I want kimchi to be taken away, not the main dishes.
- Okay. - Okay.
That's a wise choice.
Kimchi has to go.
We started with six dishes,
and we've played five rounds so far.
Would you just eat one dish...
or play another round to win two dishes?
- Let's play another round. - Should we do that?
- Should we bet 2 dishes? - 2 dishes...
Who feels confident?
I'm really confident.
(Go Doo Shim, Mr. Gimbap, Yoon Je Pil)
I'm really good at it.
I'm really good at this game.
Since he feels so confident...
What's with your face?
I feel really confident.
- You look so serious. - Let me try.
But...
if Jae Seok fails this time,
- it means he's a ghost. - That's right.
Whether he plays or not,
he is a ghost.
- He doesn't get another chance. - How could you say, "gimbap"?
Jae Seok shouldn't play.
Okay. Kwang Soo, Young Hee, and Na Eun. What do you think?
- Kwang Soo? - Yes.
- I'm really good at this game. - Why?
I feel burdened.
Kwang Soo. Okay.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
- We've bet our dishes. Do well. - I'll be serious.
- There's no category. - No.
- Just say any four-syllable word. - Let's do this.
I can help them.
He wants to help, but I don't think it's a good idea.
I'll help you, so don't worry.
(Trust me.)
Here we go. Start.
S.
(Glancing)
(Will Kwang Soo overcome his crisis...)
(with Jae Seok's help?)
(Glancing)
S.
(Jae Seok... Help Me....)
(Kwang Soo...)
(Kwang Soo... I'm sorry.)
You said you'd help me.
Why did you avoid my eyes?
- He said that he'd help me. - There's Sri Lanka.
You didn't help me.
- You said that you'd do well. - That's not it.
- It was "S." - Why did you look at me?
How could you?
Listen. I was embarrassed.
Kwang Soo looked at me.
He avoided my eyes.
I reached for him.
He ignored me.
You lost all the dishes.
By the way...
(They fail to win food and hints.)
- Gosh. - We have to eat soy sauce.
I got a feeling of who the ghosts are.
I know who they are.
The big brother is Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok.
Come on, So Min.
(Is Jae Seok really a ghost?)
What's this?
(There are four rooms with holes on the doors.)
Here's your second mission.
It's Get Out, It's Overcrowded.
(Get Out, It's Overcrowded)
Listen to the question. Choose among four choices.
Enter the room of the number that you think is the answer.
Only four people can be in each room.
Within a limited time,
you must claim your spot by pushing out extra members.
Can we push?
We have to push.
Goodness.
Jong Kook is getting ready.
(Intimidating)
He's getting ready by taking off his bag.
Why are you getting ready?
Why are you taking off your bag?
I have to.
He took off his bag.
(Be gentle, Jong Kook.)
Wait, So Min. Did you drink during the day?
(Laughing)
What's wrong with So Min?
It's because...
So Min got a lot of sea breeze during her drama shoot.
- She got tanned. - I was on an island.
When you concentrate on acting,
only your mind changes, not your looks.
She got completely into it.
Is that so?
Sea breeze got on her face.
Get ready.
Here's your first question.
When is Halloween...
in the US?
Okay, I know this one.
One, last Saturday of every October.
Two, last Sunday of every October.
Three, every October 30th.
Four, every October 31st.
- This is confusing. - What is it?
We haven't started yet.
This is confusing.
- It's October 31st. - October 31st.
- We have to get it. - 31st.
Is it number three?
- It's 31st. - Is it 31st?
(We think it's number 4, October 31st.)
We need to push someone out.
(Let's push out Na Eun.)
(Bye, Na Eun. This is how far we've come.)
(He was happy to see her when she came.)
(You ignored me completely.)
(You only focus on work.)
(I'll work too.)
How dare you come here?
(I'm going to wake up now.)
(It's your turn, Se Chan.)
You don't belong here.
You don't belong.
(They thrust him out.)
(Where should I go now?)
I have nowhere to go.
(I can't go where Na Eun is.)
(He goes to number 1.)
The answer is number four.
It's October 31st.
- Is 31st right? - It's 31st.
It's 31st.
The answer is...
(What is the answer?)
- Number four, October 31st. - Okay.
(It's a day before All Saint's Day, November 1st.)
- What? - What?
(Their faces are smashed with flour.)
(Seok Jin gets some.)
(Some foundation is applied on So Min's red face.)
(What's this?)
(Is this what variety shows are about?)
Your approach is frightening.
(He gets a slap for being a traitor.)
Everyone in room number four gets one point.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Na Eun.
(I'm sorry, Na Eun.)
Next question is very easy. Here it is.
- Okay. - Let's fight.
To prevent misfortune,
our ancestors ate this...
which has a similar color to Cheoyong's face.
Right.
What is this?
Yes, I know.
- "Cheoyong"? - Sister-in-law?
One, ginkgo fruit.
(Peeking)
Two, walnut.
Three, red bean porridge.
(I'm ready too.)
(Jae Seok knows the answer. Let's follow him.)
(Everyone follows Jae Seok.)
Is it red bean porridge?
(Everyone runs to red bean porridge.)
Don't come in here.
What did you say?
- Sister-in-law? - It's Cheoyong.
- "Cheoyong"? - Cheoyong.
- Why did everyone come here? - Please.
Why did everyone come here?
Leave.
(It's a chaos in room number 3.)
I'll survive.
Is it walnut or peanut?
- Peanut wasn't a choice. - Is it walnut?
(My answer when I'm confused...)
I'll stay with Hyo Seop.
(Smiling)
(My answer is you.)
- I think it's number three. - I'll close the door to keep him.
(How dare you?)
(I caught you.)
I'll close it to keep you.
(This is a real Halloween date.)
Push him out.
(They're still fighting for their spot.)
That hurts.
Hey.
(He's thrown out again.)
(And the man who always fails...)
(He gets eliminated as always.)
(Red bean porridge is the answer.)
Red bean porridge is against misfortune.
It could be peanuts too.
Whom should I help?
Who?
- Who is it? - It could be peanuts too.
Who shall it be? 2, 4.
- Six. - Whose face is clean?
- Three of you should leave. - Whose face is clean?
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - No way.
Come here.
(Did you push me out a moment ago?)
(Dragging)
Come here. Who else?
- Who else? Ji Hyo? - Ji Hyo.
- Who else? Ji Hyo? - No way.
(Next target is Ji Hyo.)
- Come here. - Come on, Ji Hyo.
(She helped Kwang Soo and pushed me out.)
(Why did Jae Seok step out?)
We got it.
(He went to see Ji Hyo.)
(He got pushed out.)
(I want to go back in.)
- We got it. - Hey.
I said the answer.
- It was me. - It can't be walnuts.
- I said it. - It's walnuts.
- Close the door. - It's red bean porridge.
My goodness.
- That's so funny. - It's red bean porridge.
- What's Cheoyong? - It isn't walnuts.
- What is sister-in-law? - It's Cheoyong.
What does it mean?
- Let me tell you the answer. - Red bean porridge.
It's number three, red bean porridge.
(Red bean porridge is the answer.)
(Cheoyong's face is red.)
We got it.
I want some red bean porridge.
(That's why our ancestors ate red bean porridge.)
It's water.
(Splashing)
(Water will cleanse off their misfortune.)
What's this?
I'm so glad that I didn't get water on my face after the flour.
(Jong Kook, Haha, Young Hee, and Na Eun win 1 point.)
Here's the third question.
Which actress did not play the nine-tailed fox?
One, Ko So Young.
Two, Kim Tae Hee.
Three, Shin Min A.
Four, Min Hyo Rin.
- Four, Min Hyo Rin. - Wait.
What is it?
What?
What was number three?
Isn't number three Shin Min A?
Wait a minute.
I'll use force. Who will it be?
Okay.
Who didn't get water?
It's 1 of the 2, right?
It's you.
I'm sorry, Young Hee.
(The target is Young Hee this time.)
(She hops away.)
She's going somewhere.
(Who will be at the next door?)
Next is So Min. Come here.
(Get out, So Min.)
- Get out. - Okay.
- Good job. - Get out.
- All right. - My beloved.
- Let's go, Hyo Seop. - Okay.
(Let's go, Hyo Seop.)
Let's go.
Let's go. What was number one?
- I can't remember. - Who was number one?
Both number 1 and 2 are incorrect.
What were the choices?
1, Ko So Young. 2, Kim Tae Hee. 3, Shin Min A. 4, Min Hyo Rin.
Everyone played it.
- All of them are answers. - This is clear.
(She doesn't want to be penalized.)
(She runs away.)
(Where I go is the way.)
Where are you going?
(Where is she going?)
- So Min, come back. - Where is she going?
(She runs away from penalty.)
What is she doing?
(She is one of a kind.)
I'm running away.
I want to run away.
I'll announce the answer.
The answer is...
(Is it Kim Tae Hee or Min Hyo Rin?)
- Number four, Min Hyo Rin. - Okay.
(Min Hyo Rin is the answer.)
Okay, that was good.
Do it on my cheek.
- On my cheek. - Wait a minute.
(They get nine-tailed fox makeup with flour.)
(So Min comes back late.)
Give it to me. Give it.
I got it wrong too.
(She confesses to get a lighter punishment.)
(Dabbing)
(The biter gets bitten.)
(Her face is white as snow.)
That was mean.
That was too much.
Here's the next question.
(This is the third question on horror movies.)
Why is it so long?
- I think it's number two. - Right?
- It's "A Tale of Two Sisters." - I was right.
(Jong Kook, Na Eun, Young Hee, and Kwang Soo earn 1 point each.)
- Okay! - This is awesome.
I knew it'd be "A Tale of Two Sisters."
Jong Kook and Na Eun are currently in first place.
(Both of them have earned three points.)
I'm going to throw her out next time.
We have to keep watching.
You know one of them is the ghost, right?
It's true. They're trying so hard.
(Are they trying to get all the hints?)
- Does that mean we're ghosts? - Yes, it does.
- Why? - You don't want us to get hints.
- That's not true. This is a chance. - You two...
(Jong Kook and Na Eun are suspicious.)
(Current Ranks)
Here's the final question.
This is a difficult question, but it's worth two points.
- Good. - Okay.
I'm going to turn the table around. Let's go.
Male ghosts who died without getting married...
are called Bachelor Ghosts.
I knew this.
What's another word for Bachelor Ghosts?
- Okay. - Number one, Egg Ghost.
Number two, Bride Ghost.
Number three, Solo Ghost.
Number four, Triplets Ghost.
(What's another name for Bachelor Ghosts?)
(Their answers differ.)
What are you doing, Se Chan?
It's over once the door is closed.
- I have to go in. - Pull.
- Come this way. - We have to go in.
- It's closed. - Let me go in.
- Give me one spot. - It's closed.
(He takes the last spot.)
Are you coming in?
- Where do I go? - Give me one spot.
(He's desperate and sticks his head in first.)
He's in.
(He's actually in.)
- No! - Come in.
(Give me my spot back!)
No!
Move over.
- I'll move. - Move.
(What's another name for Bachelor Ghosts?)
(Kwang Soo stays, and time is over.)
(What's the answer to the question that's worth 2 points?)
It's number four, Triplets Ghost.
- Really? - I knew it.
- All right! - I remembered this.
Those are clothespins.
I was so close.
(Clothespins are the last penalty.)
You can't do it there.
You can't clip it there.
(Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Haha, and Kwang Soo earn 2 points each.)
- See? - I told you.
(What's that?)
I remembered Triplets Ghost.
See? I told you it was right.
(Kwang Soo can't come out.)
- How did you get in? - I don't know.
Hold on to me.
- How did he get in? - He's in trouble.
How did he get in?
How did you get in?
- Help me. - Go forward.
- He can't get out. - Go forward.
Come here.
- Points your arms forward. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Point your arms forward. - It worked.
(Kwang Soo is rescued.)
How did you get in?
I don't know.
(He almost became a ghost himself.)
Jong Kook is in first place.
I got a hint.
If he's a ghost, this game is over.
- Kwang Soo is in second place. - Okay!
You got the final question because of me,
so you have to share the hint.
- What? - You got it because of me.
It was because of me. You were going for Egg Ghost...
That was my spot.
I told you to go there.
(Stop taking the credit.)
- How's this... - Well...
Did you think I was going to show you?
But it's true.
Did you think I was a fool?
It's true though.
(He's looking at the hint by himself.)
(Let me be the only one to know for now.)
What's this?
(Hint for the second place)
What...
(The second ghost is a daughter.)
- What is it? - Never mind.
(There are 2 boys and 1 girl. The 2nd one is a daughter?)
- What is it? Share. - Was there a name?
Let's move to the final location.
All right!
(It's boy, girl, and boy. Who's the daughter?)
The last mission to conquer the ghosts...
is Find the Hidden Ghosts.
(Final mission, Find the Hidden Ghosts)
"Find the Hidden Ghosts"?
Humans must find the ghosts and ways to conquer them.
They win when all the ghosts are eliminated.
Ghosts must rip the name tags of humans,
and they win when all humans are eliminated.
It's more complicated for humans.
We have to find the ways while we're running away.
Hints about the ghosts...
and the weapons are hidden throughout.
- They are? - There are weapons.
(They must find the weapons.)
I see.
The ghosts don't know how they'll be eliminated either.
Is that so?
(They don't know who the ghosts are.)
It could be Seok Jin or Jae Seok.
This is too difficult. I don't know who the ghosts are.
I wonder what will happen.
The race starts soon.
(Will the ghosts rip name tags and win...)
(or will humans find the weapons and win?)
- Race starts. - Okay.
(Find the Hidden Ghosts race starts.)
Let me look at the hints.
(In order for humans to win,)
(they must find out the identities of the ghosts fast.)
What boxes are there?
(They must find out the identities of the ghosts fast.)
Se Chan.
(That sounds too sweet.)
(He hears a sweet voice...)
(from far away as soon as the race starts.)
What is it? Why?
What's going on?
(She walks lightly towards me.)
Go with me.
(Go with me.)
(He's so happy.)
Okay, let's go together.
(It's okay if she's a ghost.)
Go. Take the lead.
(It's okay if she rips my name tag.)
(It's fine as long as I can walk with you.)
Na Eun, are you a ghost?
What's with you?
(It makes him smile to look at her.)
This is driving me nuts.
Don't worry, Na Eun. I'll protect you.
- He likes her. - What are they doing?
What's going on?
- This is strange. - It is.
She's not like that.
Maybe Na Eun is trying to rip his name tag.
She's Virgin Ghost.
She's setting the atmosphere.
That could be true. She's setting the atmosphere.
She won't be doing that otherwise.
That has to be it.
(Is Na Eun luring him so that she can rip his name tag?)
(What's this?)
Okay.
(Is this the power of love? He's found a hint.)
(It's been over 20 years since the 1st ghost made his debut.)
- Why? - "It's been over 20 years..."
"since the first ghost made his debut."
(It's been over 20 years since the 1st ghost made his debut.)
(That's Jong Kook, Jae Seok or Seok Jin.)
This is so obvious.
- What is it? - This has to be Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin is the most likely candidate.)
This is too obvious.
- This is Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
What? What is it? Share it.
How long has it been since your debut?
25 years.
What about you?
What's this?
"It's been over 20 years since the 1st ghost made his debut."
(He looks at the hint,)
(and he gets anxious.)
This has to be Seok Jin.
(Can 25 years of experience not disguise the panic?)
Gosh, it's not me.
I'm warning you. It's not me.
(He even gives a warning.)
Kwang Soo, I found a hint.
- Ji Hyo. - What is it?
(The third ghost is an actor.)
They said the third ghost is a man.
It says he's an actor.
(The ghosts are 2 men and 1 woman.)
(The second one is a daughter.)
(The third ghost is a male.)
It says he's an actor.
(If he's an actor...)
You...
(Hold on. You're an actor too.)
Wait.
(She's terrified all of a sudden.)
- It's not me. - Kwang Soo.
It must be Hyo Seop.
(Don't get any closer.)
I swear it's not me.
(Is Kwang Soo the third ghost?)
Kwang Soo, how tall are you?
191cm.
(Another hint says the third ghost is over 180cm tall.)
Se Chan.
(It was just the two of them moments ago.)
- Did you figure out anything? - You scared me.
(He came out of nowhere.)
Wait. Why are you guys surrounding me?
- It's not me. - Guys.
Did you figure out anything?
You're talking better all of a sudden.
I feel like I need to do something.
- I didn't do anything so far. - Why in front of me?
I'm sure it's Hyo Seop.
Why? What makes you think so?
I'm sure. All the hints point to him.
Who's taller than 180cm?
- How tall are you? - Around 179.1cm?
- 179cm? - It's not me.
- I'm sure. - Are you 179cm?
You're sweating. Are you all right?
I'm okay. It's hot all of a sudden.
(Hyo Seop starts to sweat,)
(and they start to question him.)
(Haha leaves quietly.)
I'm going to do something important.
Look. Look at Hyo Seop.
He's looking for people. He's watching for movements.
He's not looking for hints.
All right. As a human,
I'll uncover the ghosts and die.
I'm going to follow Hyo Seop.
(He's certain Hyo Seop is a ghost.)
I'll let him rip my name tag.
(He carefully walks towards Hyo Seop.)
How do I get to the first floor?
(Hyo Seop doesn't know anything.)
It's Hyo Seop.
(Haha prepares something in hiding.)
(They run into each other.)
(He hides a cell phone behind him and gets closer.)
(They start running.)
(Why are they running?)
Hold on.
(What's going on?)
What is this? Haha... Who's that?
(Everyone is confused as a race starts all of a sudden.)
What?
Why?
(What's going on?)
Hold on.
(He runs away without knowing why.)
(They chase him without knowing why.)
(Let's catch him first.)
Wait.
(Kwang Soo catches him.)
Hold on.
I found him.
- Do you have a weapon? - Haha does.
What is it?
- Haha. - Where is he?
Hurry. Eliminate him fast.
(Did he find a weapon to eliminate Hyo Seop?)
Hold on. If we're wrong...
If we're wrong...
Hey.
- Look. - Do you have to take a picture?
(Is Hyo Seop out when you take a picture with him?)
Is it a selfie?
- Really? - A selfie?
(He took a selfie.)
(Will Hyo Seop be eliminated?)
I just wanted to take a selfie with him, but he ran away.
(He just wanted to take a selfie.)
(He tricked everybody.)
Really?
(It was Haha's way of judging who the ghosts are.)
This is nothing.
I wanted to take a selfie with him, but he ran away.
(Haha is a genius.)
There must be a reason he ran away.
(There has to be a reason.)
(That means...)
(Is Hyo Seop a ghost?)
(Hyo Seop is...)
(a ghost!)
This is so difficult.
(He's a ghost.)
You're sweating a lot.
(He was sweating profusely.)
It's getting worse.
Then are there 3 ghosts? Or 4?
(He's confused from the beginning.)
- How do you know there are three? - How do you know that?
(He's bad at lying.)
(He made staff anxious.)
(The third ghost is Hyo Seop.)
Where are you going?
(I have to get away.)
It has to be Hyo Seop.
I know. I agree.
- He's the youngest. - I agree.
It's Hyo Seop.
(They have to find the weapons fast.)
Can I rip the name tags any time?
(He reveals his true colors.)
There's no way.
We have to run away.
(Will they find the weapons first or get their name tags ripped?)
There's Seok Jin.
(He finds Seok Jin on the other side.)
(Hyo Seop is a ghost, and he's happy to see Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin was a strong candidate for a ghost from the start.)
He's done.
(The more hints got discovered, the more they become certain.)
(There's something going on between them.)
Did you find anything?
- I didn't. - Really?
Not yet.
Let's share information.
- I'll share it. - Okay.
(They share the hints in order to eradicate the ghosts.)
- He's in his 40s. - The 1st ghost is in his 40s.
(This is a crucial hint Jong Kook earned earlier.)
(Among those who debuted over 20 years ago...)
- It has to be you or Jae Seok. - I know.
He's a ghost. I think he's a ghost.
Earlier...
(Ghost and human meets.)
How do I explain this?
At this point,
I'll just rip your name tag.
(His attitude has changed.)
I'll rip your name tag.
(The ghost starts hunting for humans.)
At this point, I'll just rip your name tag.
- Me? - Yes.
(He sprints like a flash of lightning.)
Hey.
(Human Jee Seok Jin is out.)
(He was helpless.)
See?
Human Jee Seok Jin is out.
Already?
(That was faster than expected.)
He was with me a few moments ago.
(Hyo Seop is showing his true colors.)
Did Hyo Seop get him out?
- He did. - Was it him?
(It's me. Which humans should I eliminate now?)
[VIU Ver] SBS E424 Running Man
"The Nightmare of Halloween"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
It's Hyo Seop.
(Hyo Seop was looking for a prey. Haha spots him.)
I need an item to eliminate the ghosts.
(They must find these items to eliminate the ghosts.)
(At that moment!)
I found it.
"Ghosts are not allowed to have this."
(She's found a weapon box.)
What's this?
What's this? Is it a garlic necklace?
(She finds a garlic necklace.)
"This is a weapon to eliminate the vampire."
"The vampire is out once you put the necklace around their neck."
(Is the vampire...)
(Hyo Seop?)
- Haha, I found it. - Did you?
- What is it? - Where's Hyo Seop?
- Hyo Seop's head? - I have to put this around him.
- He's there. - Where?
There.
- Hyo Seop. - Come.
(They start chasing him.)
(They arrive on the 3rd floor where Hyo Seop was earlier.)
He's gone, Ji Hyo.
He's gone, Haha.
I think he's in hiding.
(He couldn't have gone far. Let's look nearby.)
(Vampire Hyo Seop is here!)
(Let's rip Haha's name tag.)
Hey, get him.
(Take this garlic necklace!)
- Get him. - What's this?
(They start chasing him with the garlic necklace.)
What's this?
Get him!
Be careful.
You scared me.
- Catch him. - Catch him.
(Jong Kook was going up the stairs and joins the chase.)
- Hey, here he is. - Catch him.
Hyo Seop is here. He's here.
He's here. Come in.
Hold on.
- He's here. - Catch him.
Let me go once.
- Catch him. - We got you.
You're too guilty, so I can't help you.
- Let's go. - Take him.
- I was shocked. - Go, Hyo Seop.
(He got Seok Jin out and went away in vain.)
Ghost Ahn Hyo Seop is out.
(Third ghost Hyo Seop is out.)
(Hyo Seop is out,)
(but the candidates for the first ghost are both here.)
Goodness.
Look at him.
Oh, gosh.
One of them is a ghost.
- It's one of them. - This is driving me nuts.
Jae Seok was at the entrance.
He could have caught him.
He could have easily caught him.
But he let go,
and then he went in.
- Be truthful. - He didn't touch him.
(Stop setting me up.)
I was going to catch Hyo Seop, but Jong Kook was behind me.
You know how he looks at you?
I didn't know you guys were behind him.
I thought I was going to get eliminated.
You guys came, so he got eliminated.
(Who's telling the truth?)
It's a tie...
because it's gimbap versus duck.
(Duck, gimbap)
- It's him. Look. - It's gimbap versus duck.
I usually eat gimbap.
(They were both bad at the previous race.)
I'll leave it for now.
I'm going to find it. You just wait.
Come back for a second, Jae Seok.
I'll find it and come back.
It's not me. I'm really nothing today.
This is so unfair. I got covered in flour...
and got soaked.
They even made fun of me because my face was blushing.
Nothing is working out.
(Sighing)
I found a weapon!
I found a weapon. This is awesome.
This is it.
(What weapon did she find dramatically?)
(What? A tray?)
(She was running away earlier, and she creates her own weapon now.)
I have to escape somehow.
Is there nothing else?
Is this a weapon?
(Who was behind her?)
Hey!
Kwang Soo!
Come here! There's a ghost!
The ghost...
What is it?
(Ripping)
Are you out?
(Did she get eliminated by a mysterious ghost?)
Who ripped your name tag?
Hold on. Hold on!
(This ghost attacked Kwang Soo before he had a chance to breathe.)
Se Chan!
What's going on?
(What's going on with Kwang Soo?)
(Kwang Soo is terrified. What happened?)
(Is Kwang Soo also out?)
Are you out?
(Did something happen? He can't speak.)
Why?
(So Min and Kwang Soo are out in an instant.)
(Ghost status, third ghost is out.)
(Human Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and So Min are out.)
"Human Jeon So Min is out?"
Human Jeon So Min is out.
(There are fewer humans remaining, and they don't have a clue.)
- Who? - I'm more confused now.
(Why is Na Eun so relaxed in this situation?)
Na Eun...
(Why is she so relaxed?)
Na Eun is a little bit strange too.
(Jong Kook, candidate for the first ghost, appears.)
Look at Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
Look at him.
You're just unbelieveable. What did you say?
- Are you playing dumb? - Goodness.
Are you pretending like you're not a ghost?
- I'm frightened. - Oh, gosh.
- Hey. - Look at him.
For goodness' sake.
No wonder...
you teased me so much today.
"No wonder"?
- You were. - Hey.
- Fine. - You shouldn't play that way.
I'm going to eliminate you.
Give me a second.
This is insane. We're the only ones left.
(You should watch it, Jae Seok.)
I... Gosh.
I really want to eliminate him,
but I can't right now.
(Why is Na Eun here?)
Na Eun...
(She's very awkward.)
I was looking for a hint.
(Really? Were you looking for a hint?)
A hint?
(Where did Young Hee come from?)
Were you looking for a hint?
(This is spooky.)
Why? I'm scared.
(Who are these two people?)
(They leave together.)
Where are you heading?
I think the two of them are ghosts.
Aren't they ghosts?
(Are Jae Seok and Young Hee the 1st and 2nd ghosts?)
Look at that.
They are talking as they walk.
(They enter an empty room.)
- Gosh, it smells good. - What a nice place!
- Doesn't it smell nice? - It smells good.
Let's enjoy the fragrance.
(Are they having a secret meeting between the ghosts?)
It smells good in this room.
(Jae Seok's name tag...)
(gets ripped off by Young Hee.)
(She collects the name tag quietly like a real ghost.)
I thought Na Eun was a ghost!
(Human Yu Jae Seok is out.)
(That means...)
(Yeong Hee is the second ghost.)
(Humans, just you wait.)
Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo!
It's Seo Young Hee! Seo Young Hee!
(She collects name tags with a serene facial expression.)
My goodness.
Hello.
(If Young Hee is the second ghost,)
(that means the first ghost is...)
Hello. Gosh, it's nice to meet you.
(Kim Jong Kook.)
(That's how the 3 ghost siblings came to be.)
(When Kwang Soo was surprised to see Young Hee take So Min out,)
Hold on! Hold on!
(Jong Kook attacked him.)
Let's hurry up and go.
(The perfect collaboration of the 1st and 2nd ghosts.)
Hurry up.
(When he met Jae Seok,)
(he stuck his tongue out.)
Gosh, is anyone else seeing this?
You are unbelievable.
Is anyone else seeing this? Hey!
- You are unbelievable. - Am I the only one?
Jae Seok, you drive me crazy.
Human Yu Jae Seok is out.
Is Jae Seok out?
Hold on. Is Jae Seok out?
Who ripped off his name tag?
Now, everyone will know that I am a ghost.
(Then they must rip off everyone's name tag with speed.)
- Se Chan. - Gosh, you startled me.
What's going on?
Is it you? Hold on.
Hold on. I got it.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to rip off my name tag?
Stay still.
- Se Chan. - Is he a ghost?
(Human Yang Se Chan is out.)
(Young Hee eliminates Ji Hyo.)
(I see that it was her.)
I am sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
(With Young Hee's bright smile, Ji Hyo is out.)
You are the worst!
Human Song Ji Hyo is out.
- What? - My goodness.
(Is Ji Hyo out as well?)
(I don't know who ripped off Ji Hyo's name tag.)
Earlier, I saw Young Hee with Jae Seok.
(That means Young Hee eliminated both Jae Seok and Ji Hyo.)
Then the remaining humans are me and...
You and I are the only ones left.
Really?
(Are we the only humans left?)
I got goosebumps.
(Does that mean we have to face Jong Kook and Young Hee?)
I want to pee.
(Thinking about it makes him want to pee.)
I got goosebumps.
I can't believe this.
We have to do this.
Do the two of us need to take out those ghosts?
(Young Hee searches for the humans.)
(She's finally found them.)
(The two humans)
- What should we do? - It has to be here somewhere.
There is...
no weapon here.
- I searched this place before. - It's a good place to hide it.
I know.
(We must find a weapon before the ghosts come.)
(Young Hee enters the hallway of the 2nd floor.)
(They focus on the search without knowing that.)
(Gasping)
Is a ghost here?
(He freezes for a second.)
It's... It's a ghost.
(It's... It's a ghost.)
You scared me!
You scared me, Young Hee.
Why are you so scary?
(Calm down, my heart.)
(Shall I begin the hunt?)
Did you find a weapon?
- This is driving me crazy. - What should we do?
Run away while I hold Young Hee back.
You will hold me back?
(Don't you dare.)
Young Hee.
Are you a ghost?
I am sorry. I am a bad woman.
You are really scary.
Don't say that.
(She approaches them with a serene facial expression.)
She is so scary.
When you say, "Don't say that," you are really scary.
Where are you going?
I mean...
(I can't fight against two humans.)
(Wait for me. I promise I will find them soon.)
Na Eun, I will do what I can do.
Go and find a weapon.
- Go. - Please survive...
- so that we can meet again. - My name tag will get ripped off.
Go and find a weapon. Hurry up and go.
Hurry up and go.
(Hurry up and go before Jong Kook comes.)
Na Eun, find a weapon quickly.
Go easy on me.
(Young Hee, go easy on me.)
- Don't say that. - I am really weak.
I have no strength.
(While Haha stalls for time,)
(Na Eun searches for a weapon.)
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is searching for the humans.)
(Na Eun is searching for a weapon.)
(Where is the second ghost?)
(A human that looks for a weapon...)
(versus a ghost that looks for the group)
Stay alive!
(The one who ends the search first is bound to have an upper hand.)
(I really need a weapon box.)
(She's finally found it.)
"This is a weapon that can eliminate a witch."
"The witch is out once you put the angel's headband on her hair."
(Okay, I got it!)
(She must put the headband on her before Haha gets eliminated.)
I need to rip off the name tag.
Come on.
Did you find it?
- What? - She found it!
- No way! - She found it!
(I can't believe it.)
(They turn the tables.)
- No! - Come on.
(Na Eun needs to put the headband on her head.)
(The weapon is activated.)
We did it!
For goodness' sake.
(The scary ghost, Seo Young Hee is out.)
Gosh, Na Eun.
For goodness' sake.
A ghost!
Seo Young Hee is out. Seo Young Hee is out.
(Is Young Hee out?)
(Ghost Jong Kook versus Humans Haha and Na Eun)
This is driving me crazy.
- Na Eun. - We need to find a weapon.
Let's find a weapon.
(Finding the weapon for Jong Kook is the only way they can live.)
(Where are the humans hiding?)
(They must find a weapon before Jong Kook catches them.)
Haha!
(Where are you hiding?)
(Is that Jong Kook's voice?)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
What are you doing?
What?
Who's left?
(Does he not know that I am a ghost?)
You, I...
Are you a ghost?
What?
I am not a ghost, Haha.
How could you say that...
when we are the only men left?
(Don't lie to me.)
(He knows everything.)
Haha.
Since I am not a ghost,
you must be a ghost.
Stay right there.
Okay, Haha?
(Stay right there.)
(I will go to you.)
No! Please!
(Don't let your guards down.)
(Ghost Jong Kook is coming to get a human.)
(Haha hides in a room.)
(I see that I got you.)
(Haha is trapped.)
Haha.
Hold on, Jong Kook. I am sorry.
Why are you acting this way?
- For how long do you plan to stay? - I am sorry.
(For how long do you plan to stay?)
Don't do this. Why are you acting this way?
I trusted you.
I trusted you. I swear.
- Haha. - How could you do this to me?
Are you a ghost?
(Is that Na Eun behind Jong Kook?)
(A weapon is activated.)
What is this?
(She got me.)
(I am glad I didn't pee my pants.)
(This is how it happened.)
What does a weapon box look like? I haven't seen one.
(Haha and Na Eun search here and there.)
Isn't this a weapon?
(She's found a weapon.)
What is that?
A full moon is related to the werewolf.
- Right? That's Jong Kook. - That's Jong Kook.
(Let's hide.)
Go inside.
I will pretend...
to hide in this room.
- You should stay here. - Here.
Come inside.
Hurry up and come inside.
(When he ran into Jong Kook,)
(he lured him with his acting skills.)
(This is my chance.)
(Ghost Kim Jong Kook is out.)
(The race ends.)
Let me announce the result of the race.
Team Humans won!
Yes!
You are the best.
My goodness.
It was so close.
The gold badge is back after a long while.
Gosh, this is my first time I've received it.
(Shiny)
What is this?
It lights up. Look, it lights up.
My goodness.
(Good for you, humans.)
It happened so quickly.
(Getting jealous)
By the way...
- My goodness. - You should take it.
- Thank you. - Take it as a souvenir.
- Generous members share prizes. - Right.
- I'll give this to Hyo Seop. - Okay.
- This is for Hyo Seop. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It's for Hyo Seop.
Thank you.
Some will share, but some will take theirs.
(Do whatever you want.)
(When it comes to gold, Seok Jin sticks to the principles.)
- That was scary. - I got goosebumps.
- I thought it was Na Eun. - Goodness.
I really thought it was Na Eun too.
I felt so wronged.
Why did you try to stay with me?
I was a human. I wanted to be with another human.
- You chose him since he's a human. - I see.
By the way, the frustrating part was that...
- Se Chan was just getting over her, - It's so frustrating.
but here's Na Eun again.
- This is driving me crazy. - Goodness.
- Get over her quickly. - Yes, that's not easy though.
- It was hard. I'm out of energy. - Forget about her now.
- Hyo Seop, it's all right. - Okay.
Yes, it's all right. You had a lot to carry on your own today.
Don't pretend you're nice. Remember how you were when you eliminated me?
You glared at me.
It wasn't a big deal anyway. I was just playing with him.
I was just teasing that he might be the ghost.
I told him that I was just kidding.
"At this point, I'll just rip your name tag."
("At this point, I'll just rip your name tag.")
Come on. What was that?
Seriously? That really happened?
Hyo Seop came to me to remove my name tag.
I told him not to do it. What?
Go back to your spot.
- Sorry? - Go back to your spot.
(Go back to my spot?)
Move back.
(The rules of conversations are strict only to Kwang Soo.)
- What are you doing to me? - Right now,
we're talking here. Give us some space.
Let me say something too. I have a funny story, is all.
Do you have a funny story? Go ahead.
- Go on. - It won't be funny now.
- No. - Can you tell us next week?
(The race ends without hearing the funny story.)
(A mysterious video letter from their father arrives.)
(They have to find the food their father wants to have?)
(Pardon?)
(Food?)
(Thus began the Search Party of Autumn Delicacy.)
(They will gnaw,)
(chew,)
(taste, and enjoy the food.)
(Of course,)
(everyone can't eat the food.)
(To find the food for their father,)
(they hold a battle of food.)
(This is quite a funny show.)
(However,)
(someone among them knows what the food they're looking for is?)
(Slowly, the secret of the family is unraveling.)
(Some are trying to conceal the secret.)
(Some are trying to find out.)
(What's the secret of the food their father is looking for?)
(Mom!)
(Is my mom alive?)
(I'm sorry, Mom.)
(I love you.)
(Dangerous Family)