- Hello. - Hello.
- It's the rainy season. - Hello.
- It's raining too heavily. - Do we go this way?
It's nice. It's pink.
- The mood is pink today. - Okay, come on!
I found out through an article that we will have a couple race.
- Many articles have been released. - Yes.
It's impressive. The cast is impressive.
- I didn't read the articles. - The curtains are colorful.
- Okay. - It's a rainbow.
- The curtains are rainbow-colored. - This place smells like perfume.
(The legendary couple race begins now.)
Kwang Soo became the actor with 3,000,000 views.
- What do you mean? - His movie had 3,000,000 views.
- Congratulations, Kwang Soo. - Congratulations.
Congratulations, Sang Woo.
Why would you congratulate him when I am right here?
The success of the movie is all thanks to Dong Il and Sang Woo.
- That's not true. - Congratulations, Sang Woo.
- I knew the movie would be a hit. - I am sick and tired of this.
- I knew the movie would be a hit. - That's right.
I will watch it when it's on IPTV.
- Haven't you watched it yet? - You should watch it.
- You should watch it. - I will watch it.
It's time to meet the guests who will join you for the race.
- That's right. - Please come on out.
- Will they come out at once? - Let's see.
- Hello. - What is up with this appearance?
- Hello. - When did you get here?
Chi Yul.
(With his explosive singing skills and a charming voice,)
(Hwang Chi Yul is making a name for himself all over Asia.)
It's Hwang Chi Yul! It's Hwang Chi Yul!
I will team up with him today.
- Did you decide to pick him? - Yes.
- She decided to pick him. - I call dibs on him.
(I call dibs on Chi Yul.)
That's too bad. You have to comply if she calls dibs on you.
- Really? - I call dibs on him.
Hearing her call dibs made me think, "Ji Hyo is pretty old."
- Speak for yourself! - "I call dibs on him."
It means the same thing as taking a pick.
- That's right. - The expression is really old.
Hwang Chi Yul isn't the only guest of the day.
Ji Hyo and So Min, please move behind the curtain.
- Ji Hyo and So Min, go ahead. - Okay.
Go to red and orange.
You know which color to go to, right?
- Blue. - Okay.
(See you at the blue curtain.)
- I will go to the yellow curtain. - Blue.
She told him that she will be behind the blue curtain.
- The blue curtain. - Is Black Pink here?
I had no idea. Is Black Pink here?
- Haha loves Jennie of Black Pink. - Really?
She is so stylish.
(He is a big fan.)
- Haha is excited. - She is a city girl.
- Step back. - Jennie!
(Behind which curtain is Jennie, the stylish city girl?)
What is this?
- What is this? - Those are the childhood pictures.
Okay. A black and white picture belongs to Ji Hyo.
There is no black and white picture.
- Orange is So Min. - Is it orange?
- Orange is So Min. - That's So Min.
- The one on the red is familiar. - Hold on.
- The one on the red looks old. - Even though it's colored,
- the background is too empty. - It must be Ji Hyo.
Isn't that Pohang?
- Imjin River. - Is it from the Joseon dynasty?
It looks like a picture from the Korean War.
- She was born in the 80s. - I am 100-percent sure.
- Let's see the second picture. - It's So Min.
- So Min. - I see Han Min Gwan.
(The baby who resembles Han Min Gwan is...)
- Jong Kook. - It's So Min.
- I see Han Min Gwan. - He says he sees Han Min Gwan.
This picture has So Min's characteristics.
She looks to the side.
- She still does that. - She doesn't do as she is told.
- She really doesn't. - I am sorry,
but we aren't curious about these two pictures.
(We aren't curious about these two pictures.)
- Hurry up. - Move on. Move on already.
(We just want Hwang Chi Yul.)
- This is driving me crazy. - Let's see the next picture.
- Her limbs are long. - She is stylish.
- This picture is old as well. - That's not true.
Is she Kim Mi Hwa?
- I think she is Kim Mi Hwa. - Everyone,
the 1st 3 pictures look like they were taken in the 80s.
- They do. - The swimming pool has that vibe.
Yes, it does.
- This was taken in the 90s. - That's the S.E.S. hairstyle.
That's right. The clothes...
- and the hairpins... - Maybe she is Jisoo.
She looks like she has a temper.
- Don't say that. - She looks feisty.
Why would you say that...
- upon seeing a child's picture? - I bet...
she was a stubborn child.
- She has distinct facial features. - Let's see the next picture.
I think this picture was taken...
- in the late 90s. - Her parents must've been rich.
- I have no idea. - I have no idea.
- She is... - Jennie! She is Jennie!
Her clothes are stylish even by today's standards.
She is Jennie.
- Her face has style. - Is she Jennie?
- She hasn't changed a lot. - This is like a work of art.
(The last picture)
- A professional took that picture. - Who is this?
- Who took this picture? - A professional took that picture.
I think she was a child actress.
It's time to decide the order in which you choose the picture.
- Okay. - Please, please.
- I don't want to be last. - Please.
As long as I am in the top five, I will be fine.
- Let's be in the top five. - Everyone.
- Your facial expressions... - Listen.
- I am really serious right now. - I won't place 6th or 7th.
Like I always say,
- the guests will leave after today. - That's right.
- It's still good to have guests. - That's right.
- Can I go first? - Pick a spoon.
- Don't look at the number. - The entire day depends on this.
- We are serious. - I have no idea.
Please!
- 1, 2, 3. - Please let it be 7.
- Three. - It's a good number.
- 5. - 5. That's good.
- Okay! - What is this?
(I can't believe I picked 6.)
Jennie! Jennie!
- I am sorry. - Which one is Jennie?
- Jennie. - Why would you be sorry?
- Your wife, Byul, is watching. - Oh, right.
- You are on TV. - That's right.
This episode will air.
First, Suk Jin...
- will choose his partner. - Partner up with So Min.
- I don't want to. - Your wife is watching.
She is a stranger when I leave the house.
"She is a stranger when I leave the house."
- Why would you say that? - Why would you say that?
- A stranger? - Why would you say that?
- That's how it is. - Right.
- Once I go home, we're a family. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Come on, Suk Jin.
It will be nice to partner up with So Min.
(The choice is complete when you stand before the curtain.)
Number one.
- My goodness. - Okay.
(He goes toward the stubborn girl behind the green curtain.)
He made a choice.
Who is behind the green curtain?
- Did you hear that? - I heard that.
(Screaming)
Who is behind the green curtain?
- I am curious. - I am curious.
- The one behind the green curtain. - You are Suk Jin's partner.
- I will make you a star. - "I will make you a star."
(Suk Jin promises to make the guest a star.)
I am so nervous.
(A girl in twin buns)
- She has years of experiences. - The curtain is shaking.
- Hello. - Bora!
Bora.
- Bora. - Bora.
- It's Bora. - Give her an umbrella.
- What's wrong? - What is it?
- What's wrong? - It's okay.
I don't like you either. For goodness' sake.
I don't want you as my partner either.
What's wrong, Bora?
- It's Bora. - Bora is the first guest.
- Who is number two? - It's me.
- Kwang Soo. - Why is he so lucky these days?
- Don't go there. - Kwang Soo, don't pick Jisoo.
- Okay. - The blue curtain.
- Let's see who is behind it. - He's anticipating.
- Please come on out. - I can't believe you.
(Who is the girl?)
- It's Jennie. - Jennie.
(She shyly sticks out her head.)
- Se Chan, what's wrong? - Yes?
I am so jealous of him.
Gosh, I didn't know you would be behind the curtain.
Jennie!
(Jennie is the stylish member of Black Pink.)
Please come this way.
- Kwang Soo, stop smiling. - I am not smiling.
- I didn't choose her on purpose. - It's Jennie.
She is incredibly stylish.
I feel like I am in New York.
- Stop it. - It happened this way.
- She is so stylish. She is great. - Stop it already.
Okay.
- Se Chan. - It's only the beginning.
- Se Chan, what are you doing? - Jisoo.
Jisoo.
- Jisoo. - Stop it already.
No. I will pick Jisoo.
- Jisoo? - Yes.
- Okay. Let's go. - Be good to Jisoo.
Be good to Jisoo.
Se Chan. You don't know where Jisoo is.
- It's confusing. - It's confusing.
(Either the blue curtain or the purple curtain is Jisoo.)
- Where is Jisoo? - It's a dilemma.
- It's confusing. - It's really confusing.
The girl at the stream is...
I don't think Jisoo is the girl at the stream.
- Jisoo. - Jisoo.
Jisoo. Let's take a look. 1, 2, 3.
(Is Se Chan's choice correct?)
- The light blue curtain. - The light blue curtain.
(Jisoo, it's me, Se Chan.)
- Hello. - What?
- Pyo Ye Jin. - Hello.
(A rising star with a unique charm, Pyo Ye Jin)
(She is a scene stealer who starred in popular dramas.)
(A talented actress who is making a name for herself, Pyo Ye Jin)
- "What's Wrong with Secretary Kim". - Ye Jin.
- Aren't you busy these days? - Pyo Ye Jin.
- I am not busy. - Really?
You know...
- Hold on. I am sorry. - Why do you look so unhappy?
Why did you ask her, "Who are you?"
- Seriously. - Hey. I mean, Ye Jin.
- It's an honest reaction. - Shall we go?
Why did you ask her, "Who are you?"
"What's Wrong with Secretary Kim".
- She is busy with the drama. - "What's Wrong with Secretary Kim".
This is incredible.
I am number four.
- Who is number five? - It's me.
- Jong Kook. - Jae Suk.
- Go to the orange curtain. - Go to the orange curtain.
- The thing is... - Come on.
You shine the most when you are with So Min.
My goodness. Listen.
- He's right though. - Why would I partner up with her?
- It's true. - She brings out the best in you.
Jae Suk, let's work. Come on, let's work.
- They're a funny couple. - This is...
Everyone can see that this is So Min's photo.
Then just keep running. When we tell you to stop, stop.
Just keep running.
- I like this idea. I like it. - Hold on a second.
- That didn't exist until now. - Just run.
- Just run back and forth. - Fine, I'll do it.
- That sounds like fun. - We'll close our eyes then.
- I'll do this for fun. - That's the spirit.
- I'll make it more interesting. - That's right.
- Keep running. - Okay.
- I'll just keep running. - Haha, you should say, "stop".
- Haha will stop him. - Then I'll close my eyes.
- Okay. - Close your eyes, and stop him.
- The lady I stop at is my partner. - Okay.
Start.
Hold on a second.
Wait.
- If... - Stop!
(Stop!)
(Rushing)
No, what are you doing?
(When Haha stops him at the orange curtain,)
(he pretends not to have heard him and runs at full speed.)
- Why did you keep going? - What?
- We all saw what you did. - What?
- Haha said, "stop". - That defeats the purpose of this.
- Who said, "stop"? - Haha did.
- Why did we play this then? - Jae Suk.
- Haha had his back on you. - Okay.
- Let's do it again. Do it right. - Okay, okay.
- Turn around. Don't look. - I didn't tell him anything.
- Goodness. - Hey, let's do this instead.
Why don't you stand here and jump from side to side?
I'll say, "stop", when you're jumping.
- I'll team up with 1 of the 2 here. - Yes, it's 1 of those 2.
Start.
Right foot, left foot...
(Moving side to side)
Right, left.
- Right, left. - Hey.
- Right, left. - You can't...
(Haha and Jae Suk become one body and mind.)
- You can't jump with me. - Right, left.
(What is this?)
- You can't jump with me. - Wait.
- Why not? - You can't do that.
He was just jumping on his own.
- You didn't tip him off? - No, I didn't. It was all him.
You should choose whomever you want.
- I'll choose 1 of these 2. - Okay, okay.
- I'll follow that rule, at least. - That's right.
(Jae Suk will choose his partner at last.)
I don't know whose photo this is.
(His final decision is the yellow door.)
I chose yellow. I chose the yellow door.
Is that her?
(Who is the girl at the waterpark?)
- It's Eun Jung. - It's Han Eun Jung.
- Hello. Hi. - It's Eun Jung.
- My goodness. - It's Eun Jung.
I heard what you said behind the door.
- Someone said I resembled Mi Wha. - It was him.
- Who said that? - It was Suk Jin.
- I heard everything. - Suk Jin said that.
To be honest, I almost came out.
- Please calm down. - Okay.
- Jong Kook, you're next. - Okay.
- Is it my turn? Okay. - Yes.
Gosh, he doesn't need to think at all.
Goodness, look at him.
Congratulations.
- It must be Jisoo. - Come on out.
Goodness, Jisoo.
- My gosh, Jisoo. - It's Jisoo.
- Hello. - Hi.
- It's Jisoo. - Let's go.
(Feeling sad)
Jennie told me that Jisoo wanted to team up with Jong Kook.
- Really? - I'm glad to hear that. Hold on.
We have Ji Hyo and So Min left now.
1, 2, 3.
Come on out.
It's Ji Hyo.
(Chi Yul is mine!)
There are only a few couples that are happy to be paired up.
(Suk Jin and Bora, Kwang Soo and Jennie, Jong Kook and Jisoo,)
(Jae Suk and Eun Jung, Se Chan and Ye Jin, Ji Hyo and Chi Yul,)
(and Haha and So Min)
So Min, the Frog.
- Ye Jin. - Gosh, today is...
We're going to have short interviews...
- with today's guests. - Short interviews?
- Eun Jung is joining us today. - Gosh, long time no see.
Here's the thing.
Eun Jung said that she wanted to star on Running Man before.
I could've joined...
- when it first started. - Really?
I was about to star on this show to promote my movie,
but I couldn't do that because the schedule didn't work out.
Strangely, I didn't get to star on this show before.
Then did you join us today just to experience this show?
- Yes, yes. - Are you sure?
From what I heard, you're appearing in an SBS drama.
- Eun Jung. - What's wrong with you?
You have to be honest on variety shows these days.
- You must be honest. - Let me explain.
That's not the reason.
I just happened to be in that drama.
Seriously.
Gosh, she's so thick-skinned.
- So... - Tell us the truth.
- My agent clearly told me this. - What did he say?
"Eun Jung, you're not here to promote the drama."
"I just want you..."
Aren't you in the new weekend drama, "Let Me Introduce Her"?
Yes, that's the one.
That's the drama, but I'm not here to promote that.
- That's not why? - Not at all.
- We should... - But by the time this episode airs,
the drama would have started airing. It would be after it must've aired.
- You weren't supposed to promote. - Why do you keep bringing that up?
(You said you weren't here to promote the drama.)
- You mentioned it so many times. - You keep mentioning it.
- You already mentioned it a lot. - She's not promoting the drama.
- I'm not promoting the drama. - She's merely sharing the news.
All right. Next.
Goodness, these two singers are causing quite a stir.
It's Black Pink.
(Black Pink is the most sought-after girl group.)
What's your ranking in the Billboard Chart?
Goodness, we helped you succeed. I'm serious.
(Black Pink was on Running Man in December, 2016.)
My gosh.
- We have to see "Ddu-Du Ddu-Du". - We ought to.
(They want to see "Ddu-Du Ddu-Du" that swept the charts.)
The song heated up the US.
- I love this song. I really do. - My goodness.
- The song is playing now. - Here it is.
(Black Pink)
(The whole world is hooked on "Ddu-Du Ddu-Du" for a month now.)
(This middle-aged fan's heart pounds.)
Here it comes.
- Let's go. - Hit you, hit you, hit you
- 1, 2. - Hit you with that
(Jennie's bullet hits this guy right in his heart.)
(Their thousands of charms are turning everyone into their fans.)
(What's up with his face? He's firing the gun with his face.)
(Let me do that too.)
Let's give it up for them!
(Black Pink has united everyone at the shoot.)
(Gosh, this is why I'm their fan.)
- Goodness. - Good work. Well done.
- How have you two been? - I'm curious too.
We were on a break for a year.
You were on a break?
- When did you take a break? - You didn't do anything?
- I thought you were busy. - Weren't you performing abroad?
- We had a one-year hiatus. - Yes, we were on a hiatus.
- Really? - We returned after a year.
- Really? Usually... - Why did you take a year off?
- Did you just rest, Jennie? - You did nothing?
- Yes, we were preparing the album. - Really?
- We just took a year off. - You didn't perform at all?
Since you're on a show, say something to Mr. Yang.
- A video message? - You two should stand together.
- Stand together. - A video message?
- Say that the hiatus wasn't fair. - That's right.
- Tell that to your CEO. - That's not right.
Which camera do I look at?
(To Mr. Yang)
- Start. - Start.
Hello, Mr. Yang. It's Jisoo and Jennie.
- "Okay." - What was that?
(They're the cutest.)
(Shouldn't you make a complaint?)
- What was that? - "Okay."
- He must be really scary. - You have to sound firm.
- Jennie was ventriloquizing. - Try to sound firm.
- She was using ventriloquism. - Jennie.
- That was her way out later. - You should try to move your lips.
- She wasn't going to be part of it. - Please do that.
- She was going to pull out later. - You must tell him your opinions.
- Tell him. - Okay.
- Go ahead. - Say something.
Mr. Yang.
Help us release two songs a year.
That's right. We ought to do that now.
- That was good. That was nice. - What was that all of a sudden?
- Is she trying to start a fight? - Yes, she's trying to fight him.
You sounded firm. It was nice.
- Great. - You were firm. Great.
- I'm sure he watched it, right? - Twice a year. That's good.
- Yes. - They're cute.
- They'll comeback twice a year. - Right.
There are fans waiting.
- We want them to return too. - That's right.
- Do you want them to return? - Yes, I do.
- Tell that to Mr. Yang. - Pardon?
- You have the same last name. - You are a Yang too.
- You share the same last name. - Hi, my family is from Namwon.
I don't know where you're from, but this is from a Yang to another.
- Let them continue to be on TV. - That's right. Yes.
- Thank you. - That was nice.
(He uses his last name to petition for Black Pink's yearly comebacks.)
- That's great. - I'm a Yang too.
You can see...
- the next guest in a drama now. - She's really popular.
- Pyo Ye Jin. - It's Pyo Ye Jin.
Before she became an actress,
- she used to be a flight attendant. - That's right. Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
- You became an actress after that? - Yes.
- She seems to smile a lot. - She's likable.
Kwang Soo has a long face.
- He always... - I do?
- Long face? I'm always smiling. - Be quiet.
- I'm always smiling. - Stay out of it.
- I was smiling. What do you mean? - He looks like he's about to cry.
How should I describe his face? He's always nervous like this.
Horrible face.
(Horrible face)
- That qualifies as a horrible face? - Come on.
- Hey. - That was good.
Stop it.
Black Pink's watching.
And Haha.
Kwang Soo doesn't put on expressions like that anymore.
- Why not? Yes, he does. - Why not?
- He's changing his image. - It sold three million tickets.
In his movies and dramas,
he's pushing forward to become the male lead.
- He was the lead actor in "Live". - He was the lead actor a while ago.
Staring now, he'll try to beat Joong Ki now.
- Why would you say that? - What?
- Why would I beat Joong Ki? - It was just an example.
- Do this pose. Do the pose. - Yes, do it.
- Do it. - Yeom Sang Soo.
- Do the pose from the drama. - Do the Yeom Sang Soo pose.
- Do it. - How?
That's it.
- Great, great. - Take a screenshot of this.
"Freeze, Joong Ki."
(An exclusive interview with Kwang Soo)
- What do you mean? - "I'll catch him."
Well done. We got the scoop.
Why would I try to catch him?
- We got it. We got the exclusive. - I have nothing to do with him.
"Joong Ki can't beat me." That was great.
- What are you talking about? - "Joong Ki can't beat me."
- I'm saying that you have it wrong. - Great. Great.
- "Joong Ki, you can't beat me." - That's not right.
- That's not what I meant. - They'll print a lot of articles.
Why did you bring Joong Ki into this?
All right. I'll explain the rules.
Today's race is a couple race called Catch My Heart.
Among 14 briefcases, you will each choose 1.
2 bomb cards and 2 heart cards are randomly put into these briefcases.
The rest of the briefcases have empty cards.
After every round, winning couples can switch their briefcases.
After the final mission, the couple with both of the bomb cards...
will face a penalty.
- There's a penalty today. - We won't be last. We won't be.
In the order of acquiring the heart cards,
the presents will be awarded respectively.
Which present do you want?
The couple rings. Red ginseng? The red ginseng set.
Each couple will come forward and choose a briefcase.
Let's all choose one.
- Haha... - Thank you.
- and So Min will go first. - Thank you.
Yes, that was a great choice.
- Next up are... - Okay.
- Kwang Soo and Jennie. - Jennie.
(She strides toward one without any hesitation.)
Jennie, pick one more. Kwang Soo has the worst luck.
That's right. Let me choose it for you.
Jennie was shooing him away.
(Go away.)
Kwang Soo, she wanted you to back off.
- Okay. - Here.
I bet Disney will make...
- a film about them. - "Beauty and the Fish".
What? "Beauty and the Fish"?
- How does that relate to this? - Fish.
He doesn't have to wear a mask.
- He already looks like a fish. - Right?
What did you say?
(Don't say that in front of Jennie.)
(They pick a total of 14 briefcase.)
- Does everyone have a briefcase? - Yes.
Spread out...
and check the inside of your briefcase with the cameramen.
We have to go to the corner and check.
It's by couples.
- I don't even hope for a heart. - I bet mine is empty.
I just don't want bombs.
Most of them are empty.
(He checks his briefcase.)
(Jae Suk finds a heart.)
(That's amazing.)
Jong Kook saw us.
What's this? What is it, Jong Kook?
I saw them. I did.
(Jong Kook saw Eun Jung's reaction.)
- Jong Kook saw us. - Goodness.
How do we know that we have a heart?
Take a look inside and control your facial expression.
They're watching us.
(It's Kwang Soo's briefcase that Jennie picked.)
(They find a bomb inside.)
My goodness.
I picked another briefcase,
but you handed me this one.
You'll have a chance to exchange it.
Isn't it advantageous to have it in the beginning?
- No? - What do you mean?
You may have a chance to change the briefcase.
(Where's the other heart and bomb?)
(What do the others have?)
(Kwang Soo has a bomb, and Jae Suk has a heart.)
It's the first mission where you may exchange your briefcase.
- It's That Talent is Mine. - Okay.
- "That Talent is Mine" - Talent.
Do we select and steal it?
Select 2 out of 7 talents written by female partners.
If you win the competition of your talent...
or beat the competition of someone else's talent,
you may exchange the briefcase with a member of your choice.
(The winning couple may exchange one of their briefcases.)
This is difficult.
Ye Jin, pick a talent.
Okay.
(Ye Jin selects the first category.)
(The winner is determined by the talent category.)
(What's the first category that Ye Jin picks?)
- What is it? - Is it dancing?
"Matching Dance"?
(It's Matching Dance.)
Jennie wrote it.
Jennie?
(Matching Dance is my talent.)
(Jennie's Matching Dance)
I can't win.
- Goodness. - What's Matching Dance?
It's dancing to match the music.
No matter what kind of music plays,
your dancing must match the concept given.
There are a total of six concepts.
Cute, sexy, bizarre, dreamy, powerful, and innocent.
There are six concepts.
There's bizarre.
We'll score points when it's the concept, "bizarre".
Do the leg dance.
- This is Jennie's talent. - You can do it, Jennie.
- Let's start with Jennie. - Okay.
- Okay. - She dances very well.
She's good.
- It's "Havana". - This is the song.
- "Havana". - This is the song.
(She moves lightly to the music.)
(She dances with confidence.)
Gosh, it's "Havana".
- She's good even from the start. - She is.
She dances well.
(Her shoulders and pelvis move freely.)
Look at her shoulders.
(Moving lightly)
Look at her shoulders. They're amazing.
Her shoulders.
(Her dancing is aggressive.)
- I'll select a mood. - Here he goes.
Let's go.
(Pick one that Jennie is good at.)
Please pick one.
- Power. - It's power. Make it powerful.
(The mood is powerful.)
(She dances very powerfully.)
Make it powerful.
(She stomps the ground.)
- Power. - It's powerful.
(Did you see my partner?)
- She should dance more. - You must dance more, Jennie.
- Make it more powerful. - It has to be powerful.
Stop.
- You can't win at this rate. - It won't work.
No, go back in.
It's Ye Jin's turn.
Jennie was disappointing even though she's an amazing dancer.
- It's difficult. - She's never done it before.
- Jennie isn't good at this game. - I'm not.
Which team wants to go first?
(So Min will go.)
- Goodness. - Do it.
What have you done today?
- Hey. - Bring me some Korean beef, okay?
Bring it.
(They only care about the prizes.)
He told me to bring the Korean beef set.
Haha told me to bring the Korean beef set.
"Bring the Korean beef set"?
(Please win the Korean beef set.)
Do you know what Eun Jung said?
After seeing Haha and So Min,
she said, "they aren't close, are they?"
(Haha and So Min only care about the business.)
(Even a guest member senses they focus only on business.)
She said that they don't seem close.
They don't seem close.
(Be friendly to each other.)
- I'm not confident. - So Min caught a cold.
- I caught a cold. - She took a lot of cold medicine.
I have a cold.
The effects of the medicine will make her dance.
She'll be perfect for a dreamy dance.
- Here's So Min. - Let's go.
- Gosh. - So Min.
Please start.
(She starts to move.)
- This is good. - What is she doing?
So Min is good at dancing.
- This is good. - Move your arms too.
(She warms up with a traditional techno move.)
- So Min. - Sexy.
- Sexy. - So Min.
(The mood is sexy.)
It's sexy. The mood is sexy.
(Is it sexy?)
(She takes off her cap.)
This is good.
(She appeals to the audience with her hair.)
That's sexy.
- What's that? - What are you doing?
That looks very terrible.
- What's that? - That's not sexy.
It's not sexy at all.
- It looks terrible. - Thank you.
- That's good. - What's next?
- That's good. - Power.
(Next mood is power.)
Here's So Min's powerful dance.
(Shaking)
(She moves powerfully like a dryer.)
What kind of dance is that?
(She shakes her bottom powerfully.)
That's awesome.
(Haha is content.)
(I'm embarrassed for her.)
She's a good dancer.
(It's an old powerful dance from the 90s.)
What's next? It's the last.
That's good.
(I'll take the Korean beef set.)
How about bizarre?
What's next? That was great.
- Bizarre. - Bizarre.
(The mood is bizarre.)
- It's bizarre. - It's bizarre, So Min.
- It's bizarre, So Min. - It's bizarre.
The mood is bizarre.
(Is this how to do it?)
(I'll bring something to help you.)
(He brings out a spoon.)
(Where did you get it?)
It's been a long time.
(Come out, Magnet Human.)
- It's a magnet. - Stick to it.
So Min, act like Magnet Human.
(Welcome back, Magnet Human.)
(Look, she's back.)
(You've waited a long time.)
Show us.
You should approve of her.
(Everyone bursts out laughing at Magnet Human.)
That's good enough.
Go back in. You did well.
That's hilarious.
(Come back in.)
- Hey. - That's enough.
(I'm still hungry. I'm not done yet.)
(Her bizarre dance is a success when she attaches the spoon.)
- You're the best. - That's great.
It was definitely bizarre.
- It's been a long time. - It's been a while.
- That was cool. - Magnet Human.
- Jennie. - Yes?
Did you see her?
- I approve of her talent. - Jennie.
- So Min... - It's very competitive.
- can't dance well as Jennie. - Jennie.
She went against Girls' Generation alone.
(She has a winning record.)
- It's true. - It's really true.
- As you can see, - It's true.
So Min is a street dancer.
She just dances.
No one can defeat her bizarre dance.
- Who's next? - It's Chi Yeul.
- It's Chi Yeul. - Will Chi Yeul dance?
Here's Hwang Chi Yeul.
- It's Chi Yeul. - Chi Yeul.
G-Dragon from Gumi.
- We'll see him b-boying. - It's G-Dragon from Gumi.
His dancing is amazing.
I haven't done bizarre dances.
I thought...
Chi Yeul was on "Happy Together" today.
(What's wrong with his outfit?)
- I have a water gun. - He's in a sauna outfit.
- Happy Together. - Together.
(They advertise another show.)
(At that time,)
(music starts.)
(Oh, I know this song.)
(He dances to the rhythm.)
(It's a nice shot.)
(How far will my charms go?)
(He dances so well.)
He dances very well.
(He warms up his body with an amazing movement.)
Innocent.
(He does a side moonwalk.)
Chi Yeul, it's innocent.
Innocent.
(They scream at Chi Yeul's innocent dance.)
(Winking is perfect for innocence.)
You're doing well.
He's moving backwards.
- It looks more powerful. - What is he doing?
- His dancing is more powerful. - Right?
Isn't it cute?
What's next?
- Bizarre. - Bizarre.
(The mood is bizarre.)
(Moving about)
What is he doing?
(Why is he taking off his shirt?)
Goodness.
(He moves about.)
What's that?
(It's a bizarre dance where his arm shoots out.)
(My partner does a good bizarre dance.)
What's that?
(That's amazing.)
- What's next? - Powerful.
(The mood is powerful.)
- It's powerful. - Here it comes.
(G-Dragon of Gumi starts.)
(His power is explosive.)
(He dances perfectly to the concept just like G-Dragon of Gumi.)
(Shall I lie down?)
(He goes back up.)
(Is there something above?)
(Chi Yeul also known as G-Dragon of Gumi)
(I'm G-Dragon of Mapo.)
- Hey, kid. - Haha.
Go back in.
Go back in, kid.
- Haha. - Go back in, kid.
You're making it dusty.
You're the best in my eyes.
I knew that Chi Yeul was good at dancing.
- He was excellent. - That was amazing.
He dances really well.
I've never seen such a powerful dance.
His arm shot up.
I didn't turn that much.
(He speaks with an accent.)
(Unlike his fancy dance, he speaks like an old man.)
I want to see him spin.
- What? - I want to see him spin.
- Next up is... - Bora.
- No. Let's see Eun Jung first. - Okay.
- No. Let's see Eun Jung first. - Why?
(Cold)
- Bora has been getting ready. - It's okay.
Eun Jung, please come forward. Come on.
- She might be a good dancer. - You never know.
She appeared in one of SG Wannabe's music videos.
She danced.
- When was that? - It was a long time ago.
I watched it over a thousand times in the army.
She's a great dancer.
- I can't do this. - Give us some music.
I'm here to promote my drama.
(Confession)
(As soon as the music plays, she starts dancing.)
- Here we go. - I knew it. I love it.
She is warming up.
She is a bit hesitant.
I can see that she's never taken any dance classes.
- No basic skills. - It's club dance.
Let's go. It's been great so far.
Here we go. Eun Jung.
- "Cute". - "Cute".
(Cute?)
(That's very cute.)
That's cute.
(It's a bit too cute.)
Don't get her wrong. She's not promoting her drama.
(Please watch my drama.)
Let's move on.
- Next. - Next.
Next.
- "Powerful". - "Powerful".
- Powerful? - Yes.
- Why are you taking your shirt off? - What are you doing?
(She gets stopped.)
What are you doing?
Why... What are you doing?
(Her unexpected behavior leaves the audience in shock.)
- Hold on. - What are you doing?
How is this powerful dance?
(Powerful)
- What is this? - What are you doing?
- What's that? - What's with her?
- What's with her? - Stop her.
Pick something else.
(Don't pick the next one yet.)
Eun Jung.
- "Sexy". - "Sexy".
(They hurriedly pick the next one to stop her powerful dance.)
Eun Jung is so funny.
(What?)
- What's that? - What's that?
(If you want sexy dance,)
(here it is.)
(It gets worse.)
(Please stop right now.)
(She throws her t-shirt.)
- Why did you throw it? - This isn't a club.
Why did you throw your shirt?
Eun Jung, you can stop now.
- She said she didn't want to dance. - Please stop.
Someone drag her out!
- You didn't want to dance. - Please stop the music!
- She knows no shame. - What?
- What was that? - When she threw her shirt,
the cameraman got hit by it, and...
(The cameraman hated it.)
(She starts to feel embarrassed.)
- It was amazing. - You're a great dancer.
It was very unrefined.
- It was the ultimate raw dance. - Right.
- It was old-fashioned. - She's clearly never taken classes.
- Respect. - Respect!
Big respect.
- Next up is... - Bora.
- She's the real one. - Our final contestant.
- I feel pressured. - She's an amazing dancer.
- Yes. - Bora is...
- a fantastic dancer. - She's incredible.
What is this?
(To this song,)
(you should dance like this.)
(Her waves are so sophisticated.)
- That's a recent dance. - She's amazing.
- She's really good. - She is.
- She is an amazing dancer. - I can't believe it.
You're beautiful.
(It's so sophisticated.)
(My partner is amazing.)
She's a really good dancer.
(Her sophisticated dance is completed by leg-shaking moves.)
(Feminine)
"Feminine".
(Like this?)
(She completes her task 200 percent.)
- I'll admit it, she's really good. - Seriously.
- She's amazing. - She changed her style right away.
She's really good. Doesn't she deserve to win?
- She's amazing. - She's fantastic.
She's really good.
She's so expressive.
- "Dreamy". - "Dreamy".
"Dreamy".
That sounds hard.
(Let me be dreamy and sexy.)
- It's incredible. - It's amazing.
(She looks like she'll fall asleep.)
She even closed her eyes.
- She's really good. - She's fantastic.
- Lastly... - "Powerful".
(Powerful)
(She conquers the stage with a completely different style.)
She's amazing.
(That's a whole difference class.)
I can't believe it.
(Have you've liked it so far?)
- This is amazing. - I can't believe it.
(I'm not done yet.)
(She completes her powerful dance with a popular move.)
Her sense of rhythm is impeccable.
Give her a big hand.
- She's an amazing dancer. - It was fantastic.
I don't know what I just did.
- She's a fantastic dancer. - Everyone is shocked.
Bora was amazing especially after we saw Eun Jung.
It was completely different. It was fantastic.
Wasn't it amazing?
(After Eun Jung, Bora's dance looks even more amazing.)
(Elite dancer versus unrefined dancer)
- But... - She's the best dancer.
this talent was chosen by Jennie.
- It's hard. - It is.
But Bora deserves to win.
We admit it.
Bora wins!
(Bora and Suk Jin get to switch their briefcase with another.)
- This will be the last talent. - Okay.
So Min, please pick one.
Me? Okay.
- "Cute acrostic poem". - "Cute acrostic poem".
- "Cute acrostic poem". - Whose talent is it?
- Okay. - Ye Jin?
("Cute acrostic poem" is Ye Jin's talent.)
Ye Jin, please start.
You could use Se Chan's name or your name.
Recently, Twice tried it on Running Man,
and it became a hit.
(Twice's Na Yeon's cute acrostic poem became a sensation.)
(I want to eat it with Jong Kook.)
(Kookookaka)
(Her cute poem left the whole Gapyeong County in shock.)
Our standards have become higher.
A lot.
- It's all over the Internet now. - Right.
Ye Jin, which word do you want to use?
- I'll try with my name. - Okay.
(Okay)
Se Chan was looking forward to it.
I was looking forward to it so much, I almost stepped forward.
I can see that this is an individual game.
Ye Jin, I understand you.
Like I said before, Ye Jin is on her own today.
- She's on her own. Okay. - It happens to you all the time.
"Se Chan and I are..."
"just wearing the same color."
- Yes. It's a coincidence. - It's a coincidence.
All right. "Yang Se Chan".
She wants to go with "Pyo Ye Jin".
But she'll do it while looking at me.
- Isn't it interesting? - That's unusual.
- While looking at me. "Pyo". - Okay.
Let's try.
- Should we go to the center? - Okay.
- The normal way is boring. - Yes. Go with "Pyo Ye Jin".
This is an unusual experience.
- I've never experienced it before. - She's using her own name.
We'll pay attention.
"Pyo".
- What's with your face? - Okay.
I knew you were in a bad mood.
- Is this a cute acrostic poem? - Is this a cute acrostic poem?
- It's supposed to be cute. - It's supposed to be cute.
- Let's hear the whole thing. - "What's with your face?"
"Ye".
- Do I look pretty today? - Of course.
(Of course.)
Why do you look away? Keep looking at her.
- He's shy. He likes it. - Lastly, "Jin".
Lastly, "Jin".
Gosh, I don't know.
- What? - Please go back.
(Hitting)
- Please go back. - Hold on.
- I really don't know. - Hey.
- You don't know what? - I don't know either.
You don't know what? What do you mean?
- Hold on. - Like I said before,
stay in your spot.
- If we had known... - Stay in your spot.
- I thought it'd be better. - She made us expect more.
If it's nothing special, stay in your spot.
We're supposed to show off our talents,
but the owners of the talents have been awful so far.
- It's awful. - Jennie tried her best.
Everyone has been disappointing.
If no one wants to try, she'll win.
- Really? - We'll win?
- Ye Jin will win? - That's not okay.
This is not okay!
- If no one wants to try. - It's absurd.
- Jennie wants to try. - Good.
Jennie is cute the way she is.
Do you want to use someone's name?
You can use "seagull", for example.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
Why "seagull"?
Usually, it's the partner's name. Why did you say "seagull"?
Kwang Soo was looking forward.
- "Seagull"? - "Seagull"?
She could use "fish" too.
- "Seagull"? - What's wrong with it?
- Kwang Soo was looking forward. - Which word do you want to use?
I'll try "Lee Kwang Soo".
(Jennie is the best.)
- Kwang Soo is dreaming again. - This is unfair.
- Wake up! - This will...
- linger for a while. - Exactly.
- Kwang Soo will... - He'll get the wrong idea.
It'll give Kwang Soo the wrong idea.
Jennie will try "Lee Kwang Soo".
"Lee".
I think it's time for President Yang Hyun Suk to give me permission.
- What is this? - Is this a public announcement?
No. Not yet.
- On TV? - "Kwang".
Kwang Soo, do you want to...
What's going on?
"Soo".
Have a drink with me?
(Do you want to have a drink with me?)
(I love it.)
(Kneeling down)
You're just going to pay for drinks.
- Hey. - Do you know that?
(You're going just to pay for the drinks. Nothing else.)
- Just give her your credit card. - When they're done...
We're not drinking together?
- Just give her your credit card. - You're just her wallet.
- We're not drinking together? - You're her wallet.
- "Will you pay for my drink?" - Just my credit card?
If you buy all of them drinks it will cost 2,000 dollars.
That was good.
- It made my heart flutter. - That was good.
Listen.
More than anything,
the content was referred to Kwang Soo.
I'm in.
(I'm in.)
- I'd love to have a drink. - You don't have to answer.
- Don't answer it. - I'd love to.
- We could go out. - Don't answer.
Listen, Kwang Soo.
Hyun Suk will send someone for you.
- Why? - All of a sudden.
- We're co-workers. - Men in black suits...
- will take Kwang Soo away. - We can drink as co-workers.
Why would men in suits take me away?
Why would they?
- Kwang Soo. - For now,
do it only if you want to try it.
We're currently the winner.
(If there's no competitor, they're like to win.)
Otherwise, Jennie will win.
Jennie is currently the winner.
Who could do better than that?
I'd like to start.
- Eun Jung? - She finally plays.
Tell her to keep quiet.
Here comes a powerful dancer.
Here's Eun Jung.
Tell her to take a break for a bit.
I didn't think that Eun Jung would do it.
Will you do it?
You have to make it cute. Can you do it?
- Yes, I can. - Eun Jung.
Which name would you like?
Kim Jong Kook.
Me?
(Not me?)
(He laughs at him.)
(That serves you right.)
That's great.
That's good.
Okay.
It serves him right.
Jae Suk asked about which name she'll use.
She said, "Kim Jong Kook".
(Jae Suk backs away in disappointment.)
- That's great. - Hey, you punk.
You punk.
(It serves you right.)
- Okay. - All right.
- Let's start with Kim. - Okay.
"Kim".
(Kim)
During my career on TV,
I saw Jong Kook for the first time in 20 years.
- For the first time? - Is it the first time?
Is it the first time?
I don't think so.
- It's our first time. - Is it?
- It's our first time. - It is.
"Jong".
I'll do it again.
Is she filming a drama?
- Did you hear that? - Is she filming a drama?
She does whatever she wants.
- She wants to start over. - Hey.
- She can't do it again. - Be quiet.
- She can't do it again. - That's not fair.
Be quiet. I'm going to kick you.
It can't be interrupted.
- Right. - Let's keep going.
- There must be a flow. - Did you hear her?
- Don't interrupt her. - Okay.
Who interrupted you?
I think she interrupted herself.
(Who interrupted and said that she'll do it again?)
- "I'll do it again." - I said, "Jong".
She didn't keep going.
- Let's do it again. - Please start again.
"Kim".
During my career on TV, I saw Jong Kook...
for the first time in 20 years.
- It's the same as last time. - But...
- I said but. - I see.
Don't interrupt her and keep going. "But"?
"But"?
"Jong".
He's very amazing.
"He's very amazing".
- "Kook". - Wait.
Wait, it's a cute acrostic poem, right?
She told you not to interrupt.
Don't interrupt her.
- Don't do that, Kwang Soo. - That's not what I meant.
- Leave. - This isn't a love poem.
- She has to start over again. - I'm sorry.
- Do you have to start over? - I'm sorry.
I have to start over. It has to flow.
Don't you dare interrupt her!
I'm sorry.
Stop interrupting. Don't say anything.
Let her do it.
- We'll do it again. - Pardon?
We'll do it again.
Here we go again.
"Kim".
During my career on TV...
You saw him.
- It's our first time in 20 years. - Don't interrupt her.
Kim Jong Kook...
I saw Jong Kook for the first time in 20 years, but...
"Jong".
He's really amazing.
"He's really amazing."
"Kook".
"His muscle that I want to press".
Was that your poem? Eun Jung.
- "His muscle that I want to press"? - His muscle that you want to press?
Go away.
You just wanted to touch it.
- Go away. - What's wrong with her?
- You did a good job. - It's because...
It's because the flow was interrupted.
(It's difficult to be cute.)
- Wasn't it okay? - It was good.
- What's wrong, Kwang Soo? - What's going on?
Se Chan said,
"As Eun Jung pressed down his muscle,"
"I thought she would kiss Jong Kook on his cheek."
That's what I said.
- That's what he thought. - To be cute.
- Then Jennie said, - No way.
"Oh, that would have been better."
(That would have been better.)
No.
That's what Jennie said.
She did a good job.
She's free to think however she wants.
It seemed like a good idea.
Eun Jung tried hard.
She did the best that she could.
- It was a good poem. - Right.
I don't want to be the first woman to get hit.
- You wouldn't be the first. - She wouldn't?
She wouldn't be the first?
I warn you.
So Min is at risk.
- I was the first candidate. - Right.
Who's next?
- It's Bora. - All right, Bora.
Bora can be quite cute.
Which name will you use?
I'll use Kim Jong Kook.
What? Me?
Why me all of a sudden?
Why is he so popular?
Let's go with Kim Jong Kook. "Kim".
- Kim Jong Kook. - What?
Do you...
"Jong".
Do you hear bells ringing?
(Kim Jong Kook, do you hear bells ringing?)
"Kook".
Poke, here it is.
(Poke, here it is.)
(Here is what?)
How dare she?
(Do you know what it is?)
- Hey! - Bora, Bora.
These girls keep touching me!
- Good job. - Hey.
- How could she do that? - This isn't "Dining Together".
Why did you ring the bell?
What are you doing?
She hit the right spot.
She poked it in one try.
"Kook" is a good word.
- Push hard. - Goodness.
- Poke, poke - Stop it.
(Stop it.)
Goodness.
Poke, poke, poke
(He keeps poking.)
(I told you to stop.)
(He pokes him back.)
That's not it. It's right here.
- No. - It's here.
It's here for Jae Suk.
(He points at his knees.)
(How low are you going?)
That brat.
It's unclear who the winner is,
but she has a chance.
(Bora threatens Jennie.)
You did a good job.
No one can defeat them.
- She's cute. - She was very cute.
- All right. - I'll try.
- Okay. - Which name do you choose?
- Kim Jong Kook. - Kim Jong Kook.
- His name is best for cute poems. - He got so lucky.
I wish my name were Lee Jong Kook.
Jisoo...
already has a cute voice.
Let's start. "Kim".
Why are you playing with other women and make me angry?
"Why are you playing with other women"?
- Why am I playing with others? - She's angry.
"Jong".
Jong Kook, you'll be mine.
No way.
(She says that he'll be hers.)
I'm in trouble.
No way.
"Kook".
Poke.
- That was cute. - It was cute.
- Good job. - It was cute.
Her act was cute.
Kook is great.
Mother, thank you for giving me this name.
Kook should be the last word in acrostic poems.
I saw Jong Kook.
He held his hands together, and when you said, "Kook",
he tensed up his chest in case she touches it.
Watch the recording.
I definitely saw him.
His chest got tense.
(He gets ready for the poke.)
(Tensing up)
- He thought it'd be his chest. - Stop it.
As a man, I understand.
(His chest muscle gets ready for Jisoo's fingers.)
(You didn't have to do that.)
For this round of acrostic poems,
- we have a winner. - We do.
- Jennie. - She's the winner.
(Jennie wins.)
That was amazing.
- She did a great job. - She did.
(She knows how to be cute.)
We should accept the truth.
The winning couples...
get to exchange a briefcase with another couple.
A few minutes ago...
- I know with whom I want. - Who?
May I exchange it?
(With who will Bora exchange her briefcase?)
Me?
(Bora exchanges with Jae Suk, who has a heart.)
- We'll exchange with Jae Suk's. - Okay.
(Bora gets a heart. What will Jae Suk get?)
(It's time for Kwang Soo and Jennie to exchange.)
It's our turn.
We'll exchange...
this bag with Jisoo's.
(We'll exchange the briefcase with Jisoo.)
(Kwang Soo has a bomb in his.)
It's because...
I saw the look on her face when she opened it.
She's been holding onto her bag.
Check the inside with cameramen.
Let's take a look.
Suk Jin, don't make any face, okay?
- Everyone is watching you. - Keep a straight face.
I'll keep a poker face.
Shall I show it to you?
(She finds a heart in Jae Suk's bag.)
- Are we done? - Keep a poker face.
- Everyone is watching you. - They're watching me.
(What did Bora give to Jae Suk?)
(It's empty.)
(Our heart card was stolen.)
(Kwang Soo gave away a bomb card.)
(He gets an empty card from Jisoo.)
(At least we got rid of the bomb.)
I knew it.
(Will they get rid of it during the next mission?)
I could tell by his expression.
Okay.
(Current card status)
(Bora has the heart card, Jisoo has the bomb card.)
(They enter a refreshing outdoor water park.)
- Which will we ride? - The red one is really fun.
Here's your second mission.
It's a chance to exchange bags and win snacks.
Snacks?
- Chi Yul, let's eat snacks. - I'm hungry.
- I'm hungry. - I'm hungry.
- There are snacks. - I'm hungry.
- Are you hungry? - I'm hungry.
The mission with snacks on the line is Route of Your Choice.
Two couples will make a team.
You'll pick between Horror Room and Mirror Room.
(You'll choose between Horror Room and Mirror Room.)
Horror and Mirror?
- Horror Room must be scary. - Mirror...
When you go in, you'll see two rooms.
(Horror Room, Mirror Room)
(Horror Room will startle you,)
(and Mirror Room is a maze of mirrors.)
Each of you will hold...
a glass full of water over your head.
The team with more water left...
at the end will win.
The team that finishes last will lose half of their water.
You have to be quick and keep as much water as you can.
Wouldn't Mirror Room be better?
It'd be better.
- We choose Horror Room. - Let's do it.
- You'll startle the ghosts. - Let's be quick.
There are seven couples,
so one couple will compete...
against a couple of staff members...
who already know exactly how the rooms look.
That'd be hard.
- That'd be bad. - That'd be bad.
Let's decide which team will compete against the staff.
Only one of these guns is filled with ink instead of water.
Shoot your partner with a gun, and if it's filled with ink,
- you'll compete against the staff. - Oh, my gosh.
- Should we pick one? - Pick a gun.
Let's pick a gun.
Eun Jung, pick one.
- Jennie, pick one. - No.
- You can shoot me with it. - Chi Yul.
- Chi Yul. - Let's pick one.
(They have to avoid the gun with ink.)
Competing against the staff is a bad idea.
- It's a bad idea. - It has ink on it.
(It has ink on it.)
- I hope it's not. - Jisoo picked one,
and why does it look darker?
- No. - It looks dark inside.
Let's start from Haha.
(Haha and So Min)
(So Min is usually unlucky. Which gun did she choose?)
Okay.
(Water)
It's water.
- It's water. - It is?
- Okay. - It's pretty strong.
- It shoots pretty strong. - Okay.
(Jae Suk and Eun Jung)
If it's ink, it's over.
I hope it's ink.
It'll be over.
Eun Jung, please.
(What will happen to the unlucky Jae Suk?)
- It's water. - Okay.
Hey, stop.
(She keeps shooting even after seeing that it's water.)
What are you doing?
You saw it was water.
(It was too fun to stop.)
Okay. Good.
Good.
Okay.
It must be us.
(We must have the ink gun.)
Jisoo.
(Jisoo's gun had ink on it. Is it filled with ink?)
(Yes! It's water.)
- Only three teams are left. - It's one of three now.
It's one of three now.
- You'll shoot Ji Hyo? - Here we go.
Okay.
If it's not ink, there will be two teams left.
- Here we go. - Okay.
It's ink.
(With Chi Yul's good manners, they pass.)
He has good manners.
(He's so sweet.)
They must have ink.
It's ink.
(It smells like ink around here.)
- It must be Kwang Soo. - It's ink.
- No. - It's Kwang Soo.
It's 1 of the 2 Ddu-du Ddu-du
(There are two teams left. Who will be shot with ink?)
Start.
(Ink)
(Even if the tool changes, Kwang Soo is always unlucky.)
Who is it?
It's incredible.
Who is it? Is it me?
(Jennie, is it me?)
How can this be possible?
- What's incredible is, - It's unbelievable.
Jennie picked the gun.
Jennie picked it.
Jennie, you're one of us.
- Let me do it next time. - You're one of us.
Let me do it.
I'm fine.
- Let us wash it off. - Let us wash it off.
We'll wash it off for you.
There you go.
- You're clean now. - You're clean now.
It's done.
You're clean now. You look good.
Jennie picked it, but he still ends up unlucky.
How is this possible?
Kwang Soo's soul... I mean, impact...
My soul? What are you talking about?
What's wrong with my soul?
You seem to make a lot of slips of the tongue.
Why would she bring up my soul?
It's what she really thinks.
(Kwang Soo and Jennie will compete against the staff.)
(Game Plan)
Let's beat Jong Kook.
It's going to be scary.
Let's just look at the floor.
If you just look at the floor...
It looks hard.
They're all people.
(Suk Jin and Bora choose Horror Room.)
Okay.
- What should I do? - Let's do this. They're all people!
1, 2, 3.
- They're all humans. - I'm spilling so much water.
(Suk Jin walks behind.)
- Gosh. - I was startled.
(Ladies first.)
What is that?
- What's that? - Suk Jin.
(Follow me.)
- We're spilling a lot of water. - What should I do?
We're spilling so much water.
(I've been waiting for you.)
(Screaming)
(They spill a lot of water.)
This is so scary.
Go away!
(I was so startled.)
My heart almost burst.
Almost half of my water is gone.
Hurry up! Why am I ahead of you?
Why are you ahead of me?
Let's go. Be careful.
Be careful.
Both hands.
Wait.
All right.
(With mirrors everywhere, it's hard to find a way out.)
This way.
- I think I got this. - You're amazing.
Jisoo, you're so good.
This way. And...
(She is going through the maze so fast.)
You said you're bad with directions.
- But I somehow see the way. - I start to see it too.
I'm doing so good.
You are.
(Jong Kook and Jisoo are moving fast.)
Why am I ahead of you?
(Suk Jin and Bora are bickering.)
Why are you...
(Screaming)
(Scared)
No.
- Go away! - My side hurts.
Let's hurry up.
(Screaming)
(As former singers, both of them have loud voices.)
I was so startled.
(Screaming)
- Who just screamed? - Me.
It was me.
Are we done?
(They finally escape Horror Room.)
- Did we win or lose? - Let's hurry.
- Can we put the glass down? - No.
You can put it down.
(Were they faster than Jong Kook and Jisoo?)
Let's beat Jong Kook.
(Hi, we're already here.)
Gosh, we lost.
(Why couldn't we be faster?)
Jisoo was amazing.
She was so good at finding the way.
(The maze queen)
- Gosh. - Look at this.
As you came last,
you'll lose half of your water.
What should we do?
Jong Kook and Jisoo win.
- Good work. - How...
The winners can...
go on the slide and have fun.
- Gosh! - It's so cold.
(It's extremely fast.)
It's so cold.
(At the end of every long tunnel...)
(lies a turning point.)
(Excited)
What will happen now?
(Suk Jin and Bora are waiting at the end.)
Please have a seat and wait.
(We're jealous.)
- Jisoo, was it fun? - Yes.
- You can rely on me. - Okay.
Let's win.
(They put the glass over their heads.)
Over our heads?
(Eun Jung's camera is dipped in the water.)
- Hold on. - Eun Jung.
- Hey. - Please fill my glass again.
- Please fill it again. - Eun Jung.
Why did you spill the water?
It bumped into my camera.
You have to keep your hands on your glass.
- Gosh. - We better hurry.
(Jae Suk is scared as usual.)
- I'm not scared at all. - Eun Jung.
I'm not scared.
Hey, I'm confused.
- Follow me. - You're so good at this.
We're done!
Were we late?
(Thanks to Eun Jung, Jae Suk's team wins.)
(Round 2 ends with the winners going on the slide.)
- Hey. - This is fun.
- Mirror Room. - Mirror Room.
We want Mirror Room.
We're cowards.
1, 2, 3.
Okay. Mirror Room.
- It'll be scary for you. - What should we do?
Where should we go? It's blocked here.
It's blocked here.
- Let's hurry. - Let's hurry.
- We should hurry. - We're done.
I didn't scream once.
(Haha plugged his ears with tissues.)
Hurry up, cowards!
It worked really well.
This is fun.
(They slide down as fast as they went through Horror Room.)
It was so fun.
Kwang Soo, you can choose between Horror Room and Mirror Room.
- What do you want? - Horror Room is faster.
If you keep going forward, it won't take long.
We want Horror Room.
(Jennie confidently chooses Horror Room.)
You can go to Horror Room.
Hold on.
- Then... - 1, 2, 3.
We choose Horror Room.
You have chosen your room.
Horror Room?
Good luck.
What should we do?
Jennie, you should lead Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo... - Do you want to lead or follow?
Are you confident?
If you're not, I can lead.
(I have an iron heart.)
I think I can do this.
To win, you should let me lead.
All right. I respect your opinion.
(Thank you.)
- Follow me. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
(Yelling)
(She advances boldly while yelling.)
Why is she... Wait for me, Jennie. Jennie!
- Jennie, wait for me! - Oh, my gosh!
(Haunted house is nothing.)
(Hi, Jennie.)
- Oh, my gosh! - Wait for me, Jennie!
(She was full of confidence, but she goes back the way she came.)
Wait for me!
(Screaming)
- What's wrong? - I'm scared.
What is it? What's wrong, Jennie?
I was in a hurry, and I got scared.
- Where? - There's a person here.
- Where? - There's a person in the corner.
(Shouting)
(This is a wailing duet.)
(Jennie said she wasn't scared.)
Hold on. Jennie.
- I'm so scared. I can't keep going. - Jennie.
I'll go first.
Please. Let's go.
- I'm so scared. - There's nothing, Jennie.
- I'm so scared. I can't keep going. - Jennie.
I'll go first.
Please. Let's go.
- I'm so scared. - There's nothing, Jennie.
(You're a woman with unexpected charms.)
What do I do? Do I go first?
- You go first. - Okay.
Jennie, are you okay?
Jennie. All right.
She's crying. Jennie's crying!
It's okay, Jennie. Look at my back.
Don't cry. Look at my back.
Can I go first? I think it'll scare me.
- Who will? It won't. - This one.
- It won't scare you. - I think it will.
No, it won't. You can go first. I'll be here.
(Move over, softie. I'll take the lead.)
- Go first. - I'm so scared.
Stay there. I'll go first.
(Screaming)
- Jennie! - Goodness.
(What is that laughter?)
Jennie, get up.
- Get up. I'll go first. - Goodness.
I'll go first.
Jennie!
(She flings the water glass.)
Stay still, Jennie. I'll go first.
Don't move, Jennie.
(Why did you say you'd go first?)
- Who said this wasn't scary. - It's okay.
It's fine.
- Don't do it. - Okay. They won't.
It's over.
- I'm scared too. - I think this will scare me.
- It won't. - It will.
(Look out.)
(They collapse.)
(Kwang Soo's glass is almost empty too.)
Stop it!
- They will. - Stop it.
It's already over.
- It's looking at me. - Who's looking at you?
- Okay, I'll stay here. - What now?
Get up. Okay.
You won't die. Walk along the wall.
- It's looking at me. - Okay, come here.
Come here.
- Okay. - What do I do?
- You said it won't scare me. - It won't anymore.
I'll go first.
- This is going to shake. - It won't.
- I think it will. - It's a normal bridge.
- I think there will be a hand. - No, there won't be.
Stop, who is this? What do I do?
- I'm going to go. - Should I go first?
I think there will be a person here.
- I'll go first. Hold on. - Let's go together.
- Okay. - Let's go together. Hurry.
- Hurry up. - Okay.
- I'm scared. - All right.
That startled...
(Shouting)
(Kwang Soo is so tall that his glass touches the ghost.)
That startled me. Something hit me.
I hit something.
It's okay. It's over.
- I'm scared. - It's over, Jennie.
Jennie, it's okay.
(She looks like a female soldier exiting the CBR training.)
It's okay.
They said nothing pops out.
Who said that?
Bora did.
- Bora said that? - Yes, she said nothing pops out.
- It's okay. It's over. - I thought it'd be okay,
- but it was so scary. - I know.
- What do I do? - Good job. It's over.
It's over. You can stop crying.
Hey!
(Hey! You staff members!)
Look at her.
- They said nothing pops out... - I know!
from the bottom.
We're really sorry,
- but you lost. - We know.
- We know. - I gave up from the beginning.
I didn't know Jennie would...
She bawled as soon as we went in.
Jennie.
I was so scared. I'm sorry.
She started speaking casually to me.
(She started speaking casually to me.)
The cowards are coming down.
- They're coming. - Jennie.
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
You lied.
- I think... - There were people scaring me.
she's the biggest coward I've seen in my life.
In my life.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What's wrong?
She bawled as soon as we went in.
"I'll go first. Follow me."
She screamed, and she continued to cry.
She kept on crying.
You said it wasn't scary.
- I did. - Why did you lie?
Why did you say that? Why did you lie to her?
- Apologize to her. - But...
isn't she so cute?
(Jennie is so cute when she cries.)
- Don't go there. - She is. I made this happen.
You should treat me to lunch.
She started speaking casually to me.
- What did she say? - "Hurry!"
"Hurry up!" "Go before somebody pops out. Hurry!"
Jennie was probably scared,
but that was the best scene.
- That was. - Since Choi Ji Woo.
This will get five million views online.
- Goodness. - I made something incredible.
Decide if you're going to keep the bag or switch.
We'll switch. We have something ready.
- We already have a plan. - We do.
- Who would you like to switch with? - Bora's pouch.
- Me? - Bora?
Bora's pouch.
(Are they certain about switching with Suk Jin and Bora?)
(When they were selecting briefcases)
(This is awesome, Jae Suk.)
(Jong Kook saw us.)
(Eun Jung's reaction was too big.)
(We caught them. Jae Suk has a heart card.)
We'll take Jae Suk's.
All right.
(Jae Suk had a heart card, and he switched with Bora.)
- Switch. - What's this? Is this a dud?
- This. - Please check separately.
- Can we check now? - Yes, you can.
- It's a bomb card. I'm 100 percent. - Right?
(As predicted, it's a bomb card.)
Oh, gosh. It's for sure.
I knew it.
- Where is it? Here it is. - Open it.
(Yes, we got a heart card.)
(Who has the remaining heart and bomb cards then?)
Here are the rules.
This is the last chance to earn a heart card...
or get rid of your bomb card.
It's Ready to Burst.
(Last mission of Catch My Heart: Ready to Burst)
You have 30 minutes in this race.
With the conclusion of the race, the couple with two bomb cards...
will get the water bomb as a penalty.
Really?
Both of them?
If two couples have a bomb card each,
they'll face off to decide on one couple.
You have a chance to earn a heart card...
when you go on rides with R flags.
Once you reach the bottom of the ride, there will be three bags.
1 bag contains the heart card, and the other 2 are empty.
If there's a team with a heart card,
you can get lucky and pick another heart card to escape.
(If you get lucky, you can go on one ride and go home.)
- That's good. - Okay!
Does Jong Kook have two heart cards?
It's so obvious, Jong Kook. Do you have two?
- I guess you have one. - Okay!
The couple that earns two heart cards win.
You get prizes according to how fast you complete the mission.
If you have a bomb card, you cannot go on any rides.
Oh, my gosh.
(If you have a bomb card, you cannot go on any rides.)
If you have a bomb card,
you have to rip somebody's name tag and pass on your bomb card.
Rip their name tags off?
You pass on your bomb card by ripping name tags off.
Can we rip off one person's name tag from the couple?
(You can choose who you want to trade with.)
I'm getting goosebumps.
- Really? - I am.
(That didn't sound true at all.)
Stop acting, Jisoo.
That was bad acting.
What? Say it. What is it?
If you're not going on a ride, it means you have a bomb card.
(Couples with bomb cards will be after people's name tags.)
They'll be going around to rip people's name tags.
All right. You can move to your designated spots.
(Which couple will end up getting the penalty?)
(Final race is ready to begin.)
People who know what we have are Kwang Soo...
- Four people know what we have. - That's right.
- They know you have the bomb card. - That's right.
Let's go on the rides the whole time, okay?
- We have to get rid of the bomb. - Yes, let's get rid of it first.
- Let's get rid of it fast. - Okay.
We can't go on any rides with the bomb card.
People I have to watch out are...
- Bora. Her team. - Yes, Bora for sure.
What do we do?
We have to go on the rides.
Let's go on as many rides as possible.
Let's not get on the scary ones.
Let's get on the scary ones. I like those types of rides.
- Stop lying. - I'm serious.
I really like them.
You said you'd go first.
I was scared of people popping out.
I think you are...
all bluff.
- I'm not. - I think so.
Let's go on a ride. I'll show you.
I'll prove it to you.
Protect me, Ji Hyo.
What?
I'm joking.
Do you think Ye Jin has a heart card?
- Ye Jin? - I think...
she has a heart card.
You've been on rides before, right?
- Yes. I'm scared. - You're just nervous.
I'm nervous.
(5 seconds before the start of the race)
(4 seconds before the start of the race)
2, 1.
- One. Race starts. - Let's go.
(The final race starts.)
- Watch your back. - Okay.
- We have to look around. - Look around.
Let's get two heart cards fast and finish this.
We have to go on it. We have to hurry.
(Kwang Soo and Jennie run to a ride.)
- Kwang Soo. - We're okay.
I have no energy.
(Wait for me.)
(She runs out of energy 30 seconds into the race.)
Stairs...
- Hold on. - I'm bad with stairs.
Hang in there. We're almost there.
I'll slow down.
You're bad in everything, not just stairs.
Let's hurry. We have to hurry.
- Jennie. - Stairs.
Hang in there.
- I'm bad with stairs. - We're almost there.
You're bad with scary things too.
Jennie.
(She has a soft heart, and she's unfit too.)
Oh, dear.
We're almost there. We're here.
Stairs.
It's high.
(What's waiting for Jennie?)
(It's a very tall water slide.)
It looks fun.
Yes.
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
What are you saying?
Don't say that.
- It looks fun. - What's that?
I can't do this.
I don't think I can do this.
- The mic. - We have to take it out.
Take yours out.
I didn't know it was like this.
Let's go right away.
I can't.
Kwang Soo, let's go.
I don't think I can, Jennie.
I...
(I don't think I can go on this.)
Is this scary?
I don't think it is.
You're okay.
I can't go on rides like these.
You're going.
Bye.
(Kwang Soo is frightened.)
(Sliding)
[VIU Ver] SBS E409 Running Man
"Catch My Heart"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(This is so much fun.)
(This is too exciting. Help me.)
Please.
Please stop.
(Giggling)
(Kwang Soo screams at the top of his lungs.)
Please stop.
(The ride is over.)
(You can see from his face how spectacular this ride was.)
That was fun.
Kwang Soo, let's do this again.
We can't.
(I've had enough thrill with this one ride.)
I don't think I can do this.
- Let's go again, Kwang Soo. - I want to stop.
I'd rather face a penalty.
I can't do this.
- Let's do this. - I can't.
(There are 3 suitcases in front of them...)
(on the bottom of the ride.)
- One suitcase has a heart card. - Yes.
It's in 1 of 3 bags.
You can pick now.
Which one would you like?
I pick the first one.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
This was a bomb card earlier. I brought the first briefcase.
Should we go with this?
Let's go with this and go on another ride.
Wait.
- I think this is a heart card. - If it is, I'll go on another ride.
If this is a heart card, I'll go on a ride you want.
If it's not, this is over.
- It can't be over. - We'll see.
- Okay. - Okay.
- If it's a heart card, I'll go. - We'll head for the stairs.
In 1, 2, 3.
(It's a heart card.)
(Joy and sorrow)
We can go on again.
You can put it in your pouch.
Do you want to take it?
Should I?
(They put it in Jennie's bag.)
Are you going on a ride again?
Yes, let's go. Let's get another heart card and take a break.
They'll know where we are because of the camera light.
(Looking around)
What's this?
(Grabbing)
(It's Suk Jin and Bora's surprise attack.)
(Ji Hyo is an ace member. She defends herself by turning around.)
That startled me.
Hold on.
I almost got it.
Wait.
Hold on.
- Why are you here? - Why are you here?
You must have a bomb card.
- We have a bomb card too. - That's true.
- We're on the same side. - That's why...
I asked you over there...
- what you had. - You have a bomb card?
We have the bomb cards.
- We have the bombs. - Right.
We have a bomb card too. I told you what I had.
- See you later then. - I was looking for other people.
Okay.
Where do we go?
It's good we didn't rip theirs.
If we did, it would have been worse.
They could have died.
- We would get two or they would. - That's right.
- There's somebody there. - I think it's a ride.
Who's that?
Did you get on a ride?
Did you...
(They were looking for a target. They find Se Chan and Ye Jin.)
Did you get on a ride?
This one's good.
- It's fun. - Is it good?
I want to go on a ride. Do you want to go on it?
- Okay. - Do you have a bomb card?
No!
(They start hunting.)
Stop it!
(Give us your name tag and take our bomb card.)
No!
I have a bomb card.
We do too.
(Goodness)
Stop lying.
(Ji Hyo has the bomb card.)
I ripped hers.
(Se Chan rips Bora's name tag.)
(He has to switch with Suk Jin or Bora.)
(Se Chan and Ye Jin has the other bomb card.)
We have to act.
Ji Hyo said she had the bomb card.
I don't think she does.
(She tricked us.)
She tricked us?
You fool. You can't get flustered like that.
- I was so flustered. - You fool.
- Ji Hyo, you are the best. - You fool.
You can't do that.
Check, Se Chan.
- Is that yours? - Yes.
Check.
We have to go on a ride.
It's the same thing.
(They switched a bomb card for another one.)
- We're back to square one. - Square one?
Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin! - What is this?
- We're back to square one. - That's not it.
Hold on. Listen.
- That's not why. - Listen to us.
You can't keep talking. Please go your separate ways.
- That's not why. We got tricked. - You can't keep talking.
- Let's go on a ride. - This is scarier.
Sit here.
- Move in more. - It's cold.
Let's go.
You're going down.
It's so fast.
Why is this so fast?
Oh, shoot.
Rainy days are perfect for going to waterparks.
No. Hey.
It's going up too much.
(Yelling)
(It goes up.)
(This is the highlight of this ride.)
(There's a whirlwind.)
(It reaches the top then splashes again.)
(He's having fun.)
I almost died.
This is fun.
- This is? - It's fun.
Hurry. Pick this one.
We came here first.
Pick this one.
(Will they pick a heart card in a game of chance?)
(What did Haha and So Min pick?)
Should I open it?
It's empty.
I'm sorry.
(If they want to pick again, they have to go on another ride.)
Let's go on rides for two people.
We have to start over again.
(Trudging)
Let's go again.
Which one do you want to pick?
This one?
- I was thinking of this one too. - Really?
- Yes. - Shall I open it?
(Jong Kook and Jisoo have one heart card currently.)
(What will they pick?)
(There's no heart card.)
No?
- Oh, gosh. - What do we do?
- What do we do then? - What?
- We go on another ride. - Should I open the next one?
I can't, right?
That was good.
- That was natural. - That was.
- I think this is it. - What?
- It's too long. - This one's really scary.
- We can't. - Is this really scary, Eun Jung?
(You go down on a mat.)
How long is the slide?
- 120m. - 150m?
I don't think I can ride this one.
(I can't believe we picked such a hardcore slide.)
What should I do?
Jae Suk, save me.
- Eun Jung. - Save me.
Eun Jung, I am scared too.
I can do everything but this.
What should I do?
Eun Jung, I hate this too.
- Eun Jung. - Jae Suk, save me.
I hate this too.
Hold on.
(Eun Jung, we still need a heart card.)
(Don't leave me behind, Jae Suk.)
- Shall we go? - Yes.
Okay. Thank you, Eun Jung.
- I will give you a signal. - Okay.
Go when I tell you to go.
Eun Jung, let's pick the right briefcase.
- For goodness' sake. - Okay.
- Get ready. - Let's get a heart card each.
- Go. - Eun Jung, let's go.
(Eun Jung, let's go.)
(Screaming)
(Splash)
(The water hits his face as he slides down.)
(Groaning)
Eun Jung!
Didn't she go down the slide?
(Right before riding the slide)
(Halting)
(Jae Suk's scream put the brakes on her.)
I am sorry.
(Jae Suk, I can't do this. Go ahead.)
(Eun Jung, I am coming to get you.)
(Kwang Soo and Jennie move in order to avoid the bombs.)
I think they are hiding.
(Se Chan and Ye Jin are looking for preys.)
I am nervous.
Let's go where we came from.
Okay. Let's go that way.
Hold on.
(Hold on.)
- Hold on. - No, no.
- Come here. - Hold on.
It's about Se Chan.
- Se Chan? - It's about Se Chan.
(They pretend to share information and begin to attack.)
(Ripping)
I ripped it.
(She rips his name tag.)
(Suk Jin and Bora get a chance to exchange their bag.)
- What was that? - I got my name tag ripped.
Kwang Soo!
(Whose bag do they want?)
We want Jennie's bag.
Jennie's bag.
- Whose bag will you give her? - I will give her my bag.
Make an exchange.
Shall we check what's inside?
- Please spread out first. - Okay.
Let's go.
(Thanks to their surprise hunt,)
A heart card.
(they get a heart card.)
(We can escape if we get one more heart card.)
I showed it to them.
Hello, you are a familiar card.
In the beginning,
- we brought it into the world. - It has been a while. That's right.
It's our baby.
It came home.
- Welcome home. - Our baby came home.
It grew up...
and came back as an adult.
You have to rip another team member's name tag...
- and give away the bomb card. - Okay.
(They have to give away the bomb card.)
(Haha and So Min enjoy the ride to get a heart card.)
- What is this? - What is this?
(Screaming)
(Heart cards, here we come.)
That was fun.
- That was incredible. - That was fun.
I can't believe I went on this ride.
(The coward, Haha go on an adventure for heart cards.)
I believe in you.
You should pick this time.
However, I think it's this one.
(One of the three briefcases has a heart card.)
- Here we go. - Please.
(Let's see if Haha gets a heart card.)
You picked this one earlier, right? It can't be this one.
- It's this one. - Okay.
(He chooses a briefcase that is without So Min's bad luck.)
Please. Please.
Please let it be inside.
(They get a heart card.)
- We have two heart cards now. - This is insane.
We have two heart cards now.
(Do Haha and So Min have two heart cards?)
Let's take a look.
This is incredible.
(Haha and So Min's first briefcase contained a heart card.)
Not too bad.
(She kept a poker face.)
- In 2, 3. - In 2, 3.
(Here are the two heart cards.)
- You succeeded. - Yes!
Yes!
(We are on the 1st place.)
(They celebrate their placing 1st by splashing in the water.)
(Haha and So Min escape the race.)
Yes!
(after collecting two heart cards.)
This isn't a scary ride.
This isn't a scary ride. Get on.
Let's go.
(Chi Yul and Ji Hyo get on the ride.)
This isn't a scary ride, right?
I don't think it is.
What should I do?
(This is scary!)
This is scary.
It isn't scary.
(He holds on to Ji Hyo.)
Why did you hold on to me if it isn't scary?
I wanted to keep you safe.
I will choose.
(Ji Hyo chooses the briefcase.)
Okay.
(Only one briefcase has a heart.)
(Chi Yul and Ji Hyo obtain 1 heart card.)
We did it.
(Eun Jung, you have to go down this time.)
Okay. Let's go.
(This time, Jae Suk and Eun Jung go down the slide together.)
(Speeding)
(It's pretty fun.)
It was okay, right?
- It was nice. - What?
I think it's this one.
I don't know.
It's a heart card.
(Jae Suk and Eun Jung obtain 1 heart card.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Suk Jin and Bora obtain 2 heart cards.)
We are done. This is incredible.
We are done. Do I take these with me?
- Pick the one in the middle. - The one in the middle?
- Pick it up. - The one in the middle?
In 1, 2, 3.
(The briefcase in the middle contains a heart card.)
We have two heart cards.
You have two heart cards.
(Jong Kook and Jisoo finish in 3rd place.)
(There are 4 couples remaining.)
- You have 1 minute left. - 1 minute? Let's go.
(Let's get rid of our bomb card.)
No!
- 1 minute? - We have 1 minute left.
Let's run.
- Hold on. - Let's run.
We have to remove Jae Suk's name tag.
(They are in a hurry.)
If we go on this ride and get a heart card,
we will be done.
We have to remove a name tag no matter what.
Come on.
- We can't end the race like this. - No! Let's catch them.
Come here.
No, come here.
(Why does it have to be this couple?)
(The bomb card war resumes.)
(They must remove a name tag first...)
No!
(to give away the bomb and obtain a blank card.)
(Kwang Soo's hand grabs Ye Jin's name tag.)
(Se Chan protects her.)
Did you get his name tag?
(Jennie has Se Chan's name tag.)
(While Se Chan was busy protecting Ye Jin,)
(Jennie removed his name tag.)
(Jennie is the best.)
Did you get his name tag?
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo and Jennie can exchange a card.)
We get to choose, right?
- Kwang Soo. - This ends here.
- It's Ye Jin. - Here,
one of you will go down.
- It's Ye Jin. - We can escape.
Let's escape from this pit of bombs.
Okay. This is our last chance.
- It's her. - That's right.
- It's her. - Until the end,
go with your style.
- Ye Jin. - Jennie.
(Jennie exchanges her card with Ye Jin's.)
- Shall we exchange it? - Shall we exchange it?
- But... - Okay, Ye Jin.
Okay.
It's over.
It's over for us.
(What is Ye Jin's card?)
- This is... - Please.
- This is... - This is our last chance.
(If Ye Jin has a blank card, Kwang Soo and Jennie can escape.)
We are ruined.
(What does that mean?)
- This is our last chance. - This is...
(Let's escape from this pit of bombs.)
(She gets a bomb card for a bomb card.)
Why is it here, Kwang Soo?
They saw it.
We sent it away in the morning.
We have one bomb card.
I can't believe them.
(They end up exchanging bomb cards.)
We removed the name tag.
- The race is over. - Okay.
The ones who obtained two heart cards first are...
- Haha and So Min. - Are you serious?
- No way. - Are you serious?
Did So Min place first?
- Are you serious? - Will they get the matching rings?
(The winners get matching gold rings.)
The second ones to obtain two heart cards receive...
a Korean beef set.
That's our card.
One of those cards is ours.
(The Korean beef set is ours.)
- You can take it. - Korean beef!
The third ones to obtain two heart cards receive...
(Jong Kook and Jisoo place 3rd.)
red ginseng set.
Red ginseng.
(We promise to eat red ginseng and become healthier.)
- Now, - Okay.
- the two problematic teams. - Problematic teams?
- Don't say that. - Problematic teams?
Two teams currently carry bombs.
- Problematic teams? - We haven't caused trouble.
We worked hard all day.
Se Chan and Ye Jin couple...
and Kwang Soo and Jennie couple each have a bomb.
We will now have the final deathmatch.
(The final deathmatch)
You will sit at a table and mix the briefcases well.
Then you will exchange the briefcases.
The team that gets two bombs will lose...
and receive a penalty.
Are you ready?
(The deathmatch requires luck and intelligence.)
It's a psychological game. Who should go first?
- Shall we play rock-paper-scissors? - Play rock-paper-scissors.
The winning team will have a chance to choose.
- The winning team gets to choose. - Yes.
- Okay. Let's go. - Rock-paper-scissors
Jennie.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Between Jennie and Ye Jin, who is fated to choose?)
(Ye Jin wins.)
- Okay. Good job. - Oh, yes!
(I am sorry, Kwang Soo.)
- Jennie. - We have to choose carefully.
Seriously.
- This is driving me crazy. - You know,
Jennie is really unlucky.
- You know, - Jennie is...
she is the unluckiest guest I have ever met.
She is really unlucky.
Despite that, she keeps trying to do things.
- Unlucky people are like that. - You are right.
They like to take the lead.
My goodness.
And for some reason, we feel like we'll strike gold this time.
- That's right. - It won't happen at the end.
- We won't be last. I promise. - Unlucky ones always try to lead.
- That's right. - Let's get started.
- Pick one. - Good luck.
- Choose one for me. - What if...
(A butterfly lands on his glasses.)
(Screaming)
Hey, you coward!
(No, save me!)
- It's just a butterfly! - It's over.
Jennie, you're okay. It's all right.
- You're okay, Jennie. - The butterfly landed on you.
It was just a small butterfly.
- It startled me. It hit my face. - It was a butterfly.
- No, no. - Hey, right now...
By the way, Jennie is a new...
- addition to the unlucky ones. - That's right.
She does fit in with you guys.
- She easily gets scared too. - No pretty women were this unlucky.
- It's my first time seeing one. - It's a rare mix. It is rare.
- Seriously. - Exactly.
- Can we choose ours? - Yes.
Will you choose, Se Chan? Or will you let the other team pick?
- It's your decision. - Make them choose.
- We'll make them choose. - Yes, that's better.
They have the worst luck.
- You should choose, Jennie. - Do I need one without the bombs?
Yes, of course.
This one.
- Okay. - Then which one do we get?
(She chooses Ye Jin's without any hesitation.)
- All right. - Which one will you switch with?
- Is it done? - No.
We'll choose Se Chan's.
(The winning strategy is to pick the one she didn't pick.)
- Kwang Soo. - Jennie already chose.
- It's because she chose it. - Trust me on this.
- Yes, trust her. - I don't think we'll be last.
Let's just go with Se Chan's this time. What do you think? No?
(Shaking her head)
- I think this is the one. - Gosh, she's stubborn too.
- I have no control over this game. - By the way,
- She's unlucky and stubborn. - That's how unlucky people are.
She chose the briefcase with the bomb card to begin with.
- All right. - I'll open it.
- What could this be? - I can just...
(Is there a bomb card in Ye Jin's bag which Jennie was certain of?)
- Hey, darn it! - Okay!
(Hey, what is this?)
- Okay! - Yes!
- Let me see. - Did she really pick that one?
(You have my respect, Jennie.)
- Jennie. You're truly... - No way.
- You should join our club. - This is unbelievable.
- No, don't shake my hands! - We hold regular meetings.
- We have regular meetings. - Come to our meetings.
- This is incredible. - You'll be a regular member.
- That's not it. - Kwang Soo and Jennie lost.
(The unlucky couple, Kwang Soo and Jennie, will face the penalty.)
Tell you what. It rained today.
I was concerned that we were filming at a waterpark.
- But it's better on rainy days. - It was quite nice.
- It was fun. - It was nice.
- We should come on rainy days. - Right.
Kwang Soo and Jennie will face the last penalty.
- Get ready. Start. - Be careful.
(All the water bombs are thrown to Kwang Soo.)
(It hits his face.)
Wait. Time-out.
- That must hurt. - Wait, hold on!
- I can't throw it. - That must hurt a lot.
(Who could be the cause of this disaster?)
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
- Good work. - Good job, everyone.
(The best spy troupe on variety shows, Running Man)
(And)
(The ultimate spy who will stand against them)
(Tom)
(Tom C...)
(Tom Cru...)
(Tom Cruise)
(Running Man versus Team Mission Impossible)
(Henry Cavill)
(Simon Pegg)
(Running Man: Mission Impossible)