(A day before the shoot, at a movie theater in Seoul)
(The members are entering the rented, empty theater.)
Jae Suk, how much money did you spend?
(What? Only Jae Suk, So Min, and Se Chan are coming in?)
- Jae Suk, is this a surprise? - Did you rent the whole place?
- This must be a surprise event. - My gosh.
Even if I had to rent a place, I wouldn't rent this big place.
This place is huge.
(Why did only these three members come to the theater?)
This is nice.
- Se Chan, is this a surprise? - Yes?
Yes, it is. You'll see a video message soon.
Kwang Soo will pop up and say, "So Min".
- "Have you been well?" - Then I'm going to leave.
- I'm really going to leave. Yes. - If Kwang Soo shows up?
(Kwang Soo's surprise event makes him cringe.)
- He might suddenly start singing. - Right, he'll sing too.
You all know who's joining Running Man, right?
- Yes. - Of course.
Is he going to come out in the middle of the movie?
- No, he wouldn't. - Right, no. Gosh, you surprised me.
(The door opens)
- "Hey, So Min." - What are you talking about?
(Is this Tom's surprise for her?)
- "Hey, So Min." - Tom can't be here right now.
- Right? - Tom doesn't even know who you are.
- He probably doesn't know us. - That's right.
Obviously.
Everyone, we've asked you to come in for a reason.
This week's race is called Catch the Spy.
- Catch who? - It's Catch the Spy.
You've been instructed by M Agency, the best intelligence agency.
You have infiltrated into R Agency...
and will be secretly carrying out missions.
- We're spies. - In a nutshell, you're the spies.
- This is so cool. - Gosh, it's definitely doomed.
(It's definitely doomed.)
Whenever So Min is the spy, that episode gets ruined.
She has never succeeded when she was a spy.
She's already trembling.
- Se Chan barely succeeded once. - Right. I got the last one.
- That's right. - Right.
You need to show us a success case.
The writer said that I'm the female version of Suk Jin.
- The producer said the same thing. - Female version of Suk Jin.
- Gosh. - We're in trouble.
But you gave me the dumb members.
(Dumb members)
- My gosh. Seriously? - Hey. That's not true.
- What are you babbling about? - We can make this work.
- Or they're the ugly members. - No.
(Let me introduce my ugly friends.)
That's not true.
We'll hand over the mission your superior in M Agency sent.
Dear proud members of M Agency. Have you been well?
What's going on?
(Who's our superior that's giving us this mission?)
- It's Tom. - Gosh.
(It's Tom.)
(The superior that they will have a rendezvous with tomorrow is Tom.)
It's been a while since you guys infiltrated our rivalry, R Agency.
How is your mission coming along?
A while ago, we received a tip that...
the head of R Agency is making moves to target M Agency.
Eliminate this mysterious leader of R Agency and keep M Agency safe.
In order to support you guys, we'll be heading over to Korea.
(Tom and his friends will be coming to Running Man to help.)
Your mission is to conceal your identities until the final mission,
fish out the leader of R Agency, and eliminate the individual.
(Their mission is to conceal their identities and remove the leader.)
You must stop members from getting clues about the spies.
And you must acquire hints about the leader of R Agency.
At the end of the voting, if two of you survive or eliminate the leader,
it will be your victory.
- They're going to vote. - This is bad.
But I get the feeling Jong Kook might be the leader.
- No, no. It won't be him. - Really?
If they choose Jong Kook, they'll be uncomfortable too.
The moment he becomes the leader, it'd be suffocating.
It will be a lot of pressure, so it won't be Jong Kook.
(That's why he won't be the leader.)
- You know what I mean, right? - I know what you mean.
- It's suffocating. - His subordinates will suffocate.
Gosh, he's no joke. Let's catch the leader of R Agency.
(The next day at 4am, at a cafe in Seoul)
Hello. Hi.
- Hello. - Nice to see you again.
- Hello. - Nice to see you.
Where is Tom?
- Where is Tom? - Where's Tom?
Where is Tom Cruise?
- Hey, do you think Mr. Cruise... - We came to a coffee shop.
- would be here at this time? - Hey, look at the time.
The fact that we're here...
means that we are working around his schedule.
(It means that we're accommodating to Tom's schedule.)
- We'll be filming to meet him. - That's right.
- We'll meet when he's feeling good. - Of course.
(Thank you for being so considerate.)
- It's hectic on cable networks. - Yes, indeed.
- All of his movies are being aired. - Right.
- All of his movies were on it. - His movies were released again.
- He hasn't changed at all. - Tom Cruise from "Top Gun".
- Gosh. - We'll get to see him in person.
- Have you seen "Top Gun"? - Yes, I have.
- I saw it when I was young. - Really?
- Really? - Kwang Soo...
(A nostalgic melody)
(Humming)
Tom Cruise
(Tom Cruise)
(He knows only half of the melody.)
- You did watch it. - I did.
(Humming)
Right. My gosh.
- Suk Jin, he made it funny. Stop. - Tom Cruise
- He already did that. - He...
- I was just adding a few spices. - He already made it funny.
- I was just adding... - Why would you take that from him?
- I was just improving it. - You're standing far from him.
- Let Kwang Soo take the glory. - Exactly.
(You little...)
- What are you doing? - Do you want to get beat up?
(Boiling with anger)
- Suk Jin is really angry. He's mad. - Goodness, come on.
- I can't believe you. - That's no way to speak on TV.
Hey, you. Actually, I don't even know how powerful my punch is.
(Actually, I don't even know how powerful my punch is.)
- I've never had to use it. - He doesn't know.
- He's never punched someone. - Suk Jin.
Suk Jin. Don't be shocked if I lick your punch when you punch me.
(Because it will be sweet.)
- It will be really sweet. - It will be sweet.
- Oh, sweet. Gosh, it's so sweet. - Hey.
- Give me a punch. - It's so sweet.
- Suyu-ri's Honey Punch. - Give me one more.
- His punch is as sweet as honey. - Suyu-ri's Honey Punch.
- That will be sweet. - Spread it on bread and eat.
I heard that Henry Cavill is joining too.
- Superman. - Superman.
- That's right. - Did he play Superman?
- Superman. - Simon Pegg?
Simon's character helps him...
- from the headquarters in secret. - Right. He worked with computers.
As you already know,
today's race will be Catch the Spy with these famous stars.
- Catch the Spy? - Spy?
You're agents from the best intelligence agency, R Agency.
- It's been a while. - We haven't done this for a while.
- I'm getting into the role. - R Agency?
However, among the eight of you,
there are three double agents who secretly infiltrated from M Agency,
- rival agency for their missions. - Three double agents?
- And there is... - Three?
a leader of R Agency.
After three missions, the winners will be given clues...
about the spies or the leader of R Agency.
R Agency wins if 2 of the 3 spies are chosen by votes at the end.
However, if R Agency's leader is voted among the three,
M Agency wins.
The winning team will be given the gold badges.
Does it mean that all of us belong to R Agency?
- Three of you are from M Agency. - M Agency.
One of us is R Agency's leader.
Does the individual know he or she is the leader?
- M Agency... - Do they know their identities?
- Did you tell them? - They know their identities.
Goodness, everyone is acting now.
Hold on. I came 30 minutes before the shoot,
but Se Chan was completely ready for the shoot.
- Me? - Yes.
- We should share information. - I always come in my outfit.
- Se Chan... - I always come in my outfit.
- From where? From home? - Yes.
- Is that so? Turn around. - Okay.
Your suit doesn't have creases.
- I didn't have my jacket on. - Did you take it off then?
Come on. Why are you doing this? We just started.
- Come on. - This isn't how you play it.
- You don't play it like this. - Do it later. Later.
- What are you doing? - We just had the opening segment.
- No, it's not that. - He already started.
He's trying to finish the race in the opening segment.
Jong Kook, the sun didn't even rise yet.
- We need to get hints too. - I couldn't sleep.
No, it's not that. I couldn't sleep.
I went to bed after watching "Sherlock Holmes".
- I went to sleep after watching it. - All of a sudden,
I broke out in a cold sweat.
(The race could've been over even before meeting Tom.)
At the final mission, M Agency's senior agents,
Tom Cruise, Henry Cavill, and Simon Pegg...
- are waiting to help their agents. - Is that so?
I can't believe this.
For your information, the senior agents...
know who the three double agents are among you.
(They know the identities of 3 double agents from M Agency.)
- They already know? - They saw the photos in advance.
- They know our names? - They know our faces.
- Do they really know our names? - My gosh.
Please do your best to win this mission.
At the end of show, I hope...
it ends with Tom getting a stick slap from Jong Kook.
(I hope it ends with Tom getting a stick slap from Jong Kook.)
He's one of us now.
- We'll be close friends. - My gosh.
- I wish I could give him a slap. - We should make good memories.
He would be so shocked.
You must be hungry since you came in early in the morning.
- Yes. - Yes.
The mission where the first hint is at stake...
is called Sounds of Breakfast.
- Sounds of Breakfast? - We have to guess by the sounds.
(Do we need to whisper?)
Break into 4 teams of 2 freely.
Each team will choose a dish for their breakfast...
and quietly eat their breakfast for five minutes.
You must eat at least one bite of every dish on the tray.
If you make sounds louder than 60dB,
you will be punished with the squeaky hammer.
(Sounds over 60dB mean the squeaky hammer.)
(In other words, they must eat without making any sounds.)
The team with the lowest number of hits will win.
Only a member of the winning team will get the hint he or she wants.
- All right. Let's choose. - Should we start?
(They'll choose teams with the spoons.)
Gosh, this is important. It's important.
Kwang Soo will go first.
- I... - Okay.
We're breaking into two teams, right?
- I got yellow. - I see.
You'll team up with Suk Jin.
- Gosh. - You'll team up with Suk Jin.
(He lets out a deep and sincere sigh.)
- You're happy, right? - Kwang Soo, don't make it obvious.
- I'm sorry. - Why did you...
- Next up is Se Chan. - I...
- chose blue. - Gosh.
Okay.
- Who has red? - What?
- Hey, Jong Kook. - Wait.
(Only two people remain. That means...)
(Jae Suk and So Min make a team.)
- What's going on? - How is this possible?
- They always partner up. - They're like magnets.
- Gosh, the frog. - You're meant to be.
- They meet again like fate. - This is so meant to be.
There are four dishes you can choose from for breakfast.
A cutlet set, a snack set, a snack bar food set, and a clattering set.
- The cutlet set is the best. - The cutlet is the best.
- We have to slice it. It's noisy. - The cutlet set.
(A cutlet set, a snack set, a snack bar food set, and a clattering set)
Jong Kook, let's win this.
(The breakfast dishes and the order)
The clattering set comes with bibimbap, whole radish kimchi,
- and the coffee with an egg. - The kimchi will end them.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but why are there five people behind Jong Kook?
Ji Hyo is playing it too.
- Is this a festival for you? - Why?
No, it just happened. It just happened this way.
- I love these kinds of games. - We can hit him legally.
Gosh, I should exercise my neck.
- Bring it in. - Should I cover Ji Hyo then?
Besides, they have to mix the rice.
- That looks good. - It looks delicious.
- They added the sesame oil. - What's that?
- That's coffee. - They have to drink coffee too?
You have five minutes.
- The young radish kimchi is big. - Get ready.
We have five minutes?
- We'll give you five minutes. - Get ready.
Start.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo start.)
(Because of the air conditioner, it's louder on the right side.)
(She carefully adds the vegetables into the bowl.)
(Good job, Ji Hyo. We had a good start.)
(Getting their hammers ready)
(Ji Hyo: Let me lift the spoon.)
(They're utterly nervous. She carefully lifts it.)
(Please go over 60dB.)
(Clattering)
(Hammering)
(It went over 60dB. It's a shower of squeaky hammers.)
(I hit Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook: The spoons are stuck together.)
(He struggles while making a face.)
(It's so hard to eat a meal.)
(It's time to mix it after adding gochujang.)
(It will go over 60dB. They're going to mix it.)
(They're mixing it.)
(They manage to add gochujang quietly for now.)
(Please make a noise. They're fully ready.)
(He adds it quietly.)
(They manage to mix it quietly just like the best members.)
(They're good. How disappointing.)
(The only thing left for them to do is eat.)
(He quietly finishes the egg in one bite.)
He's only eating the whites of the egg even during this game.
(He's unbelievable.)
I got the goosebumps.
(Jong Kook's love for protein is unyielding.)
(He finishes absorbing his protein.)
Eat the kimchi. Eat the young radish kimchi.
It will definitely go over 60dB at once.
It's impossible not to.
(It's hard to eat it without making a sound. Can he succeed?)
(As they get ready, they're getting their hopes up.)
(He tries to eat the kimchi. Well, let me see.)
(Everyone is having a blast. What are you looking at?)
(Flinching)
(So Min: I didn't look at you.)
(He finally takes a bite.)
(Even if he bites into it, it's lower than 60dB.)
(He bit the radish. How is this possible?)
He didn't make any sounds.
(Who on earth is this man?)
(Who could he possibly be?)
He's good at eating without making sounds.
He's not making any sounds.
- This is annoying. - Look at that.
(He made a sound.)
(He was eating without making any sounds.)
(He suddenly chokes on the food.)
(It's time! It's a festival of squeaky hammers.)
(Everyone is excited at the chance to hit him under a proper reason.)
(A series of hammering)
(Kwang Soo is especially doing his best.)
Stop. That's enough.
- Just hit him once. - That was Kwang Soo.
- It was 100dB. - He has a lot pent up inside.
The number skyrocketed.
- You hit him too many times. - It was all Kwang Soo.
- You beat him up. - No, the number was too high.
- It was 100dB. - Kwang Soo, you're in trouble.
Ji Hyo, drink the coffee.
(This time, they try making the instant coffee.)
(She pours the water first.)
(Hammering)
(He chokes again after getting a hit.)
(As soon as he chokes,)
(they keep hitting him with the hammers.)
(Jong Kook: Is it you again, Kwang Soo?)
It's because...
it went over 100dB.
(He's brazen.)
(I'm going to move over there.)
(I'm going to go too.)
- I think Jong Kook is really angry. - It wasn't me. It really wasn't.
You've gone mad.
- Kwang Soo, just hit him once. - Hit him once.
No, it wasn't me. He kept...
(In the midst of this, he keeps coughing.)
(What's wrong with my throat?)
I didn't do it. I didn't.
(Ji Hyo: Have some water.)
(Jong Kook: You're the best.)
(You have to pour the coffee mix.)
(Ji Hyo: 1 coffee mix, 1 spoon of cream, and 1 spoon of sugar?)
(Again? He coughs again.)
(What a surprise! He hammers Jong Kook like a mad man.)
(Gosh, am I allergic to the young radish kimchi?)
(Jong Kook, here you go.)
(You might need this. So Min hands the hammer over.)
(Use it well.)
(Thank you, So Min.)
(You're not going to use it on me, right?)
(She tries having a sip of the coffee at last.)
(It didn't go over 60dB.)
(Amazing. It was so close!)
It was 59.7dB.
(Gosh, Ji Hyo is incredible.)
(Their 5 minutes to have breakfast finally are over.)
(It's already over?)
If Jong Kook didn't cough, he probably didn't get any hits.
- If he didn't cough... - It went down the wrong pipe.
If he didn't cough, he wouldn't have gotten any.
When he was chewing, he didn't make any sounds.
- Kwang Soo went over the line. - Right. You hit him a lot.
- Aren't we supposed to hit once? - He kept hitting Jong Kook.
By the way, you went too far.
- Pardon? - I thought we weren't on TV.
- Seriously. - You can hit only once.
- Anyway, let's continue. - When did you move there?
- It's us. - Next up are...
- Kwang Soo and Suk Jin. - Yes.
- You got the snack bar food set. - Gosh, it will be delicious.
We chose a good one.
Jong Kook has already found his spot.
(The spot next to Kwang Soo is mine.)
I'm sure it's a coincidence. I'm sure it is.
Yes, probably.
(Is it a coincidence?)
(He cleans the squeaky hammer for Kwang Soo.)
(Turning ghastly pale)
Gosh, it's going to hurt. It will hurt.
- Gosh, that. - That ramyeon is spicy.
(The stir-fried noodles are spicy.)
- That looks good. - I can't eat spicy ramyeon.
- They have the spicy ramyeon. - Gosh, that ramyeon.
- When they unwrap the gimbap... - Suk Jin, let's do well.
- I won't let them hit me. - Get ready.
- Start. - Start.
(Seok Jin: Should I get the spoon first?)
(Clattering)
(Hammering)
(He smashes down with the edge of the hammer.)
(He's confused.)
I heard a sound.
(My ear is ringing.)
(You're not allowed to talk.)
(Be quiet. Let's eat.)
(Go ahead and eat.)
(He takes a bite of udon.)
(Slurping)
(He barely makes it.)
(Suk Jin is doing quite well.)
(Kwang Soo takes a bite of udon.)
(Slurping)
(He gets hit.)
(He gets hit hard.)
Is someone hitting with something harder than a squeaky hammer?
I don't know.
(It sounds as hard as a hammer.)
(He keeps being too loud.)
(Punching)
(He's loud again.)
It's the sound of the squeaky hammer.
(That's what's going over 60dB.)
- It sounds very loud. - Wait a minute.
When he hits...
Will I get hit forever?
- Listen. - It detects whenever he hits me.
I look at this only.
I don't look at anything else.
It's the echo of the sound when he hits with his squeaky hammer.
The number goes up because of the echo.
- That's right. - Really?
After I hit him, it's 60 again.
- After I hit him, it's 60 again. - What's that?
It keeps going.
- It's the echo. - I'm sorry.
I didn't understand how the machine worked. I'm sorry.
(Fine, I'll hold my anger.)
(Suk Jin tries some spicy stir-fried noodles.)
(It's coming.)
(Squeaking)
(It's more painful in his mouth.)
(Have some juice if it's too spicy.)
(It's so spicy.)
(He breathes out heavily.)
(He breathes out again.)
(It's so spicy.)
What's going on?
- He keeps being loud. - Hey.
You misunderstood.
(What are you doing?)
He keeps breathing heavily because it's so spicy.
You just wait and see.
I'm serious.
It's because it's too spicy for him.
It's the echo of the squeaky hammer.
No it isn't.
I'll hit you while I'm yelling.
No, it's the rule.
- No, I heard it clearly. - Ji Hyo.
I do it accurately.
Start.
(He removes the foil from the gimbap.)
(Crackling)
(Squeaking)
(We got hit so much, it doesn't even hurt anymore.)
(Shall I take out some gimbap?)
(Hey, Kwang Soo.)
(This gimbap is strange.)
(Kwang Soo says...)
Why isn't it cut?
(Why isn't the gimbap cut?)
(Why are you talking?)
(It's a whole gimbap.)
(You still have to eat it.)
(He decides to cut it with his teeth.)
(He takes a huge bite.)
(He pulls out the spinach.)
(Laughing)
(Kwang Soo gets hit.)
(Poor Kwang Soo.)
(Both of them succeed in eating gimbap.)
(Words that someone used...)
(A staff member's cell phone rings by mistake.)
(We didn't make the sound.)
That's just your luck.
(They're unlucky as always.)
(After many controversies, Suk Jin and Kwang Soo's time is up.)
It was a lot.
They ate a lot.
One of my ears is numb because of Jong Kook's hammer sound.
- I was being accurate. - He hit too hard.
I only looked at the number.
By the way,
this hasn't happened in 30 years.
Udon broth is coming out of my nose.
It happened when I was in elementary school while drinking milk.
It's leaking.
Next up are me and So Min.
How will we eat the apple?
(Pork cutlet, apple, Sprite with ice)
Goodness.
Get ready, set, go.
(Their meal starts.)
(Let's eat the pork cutlet first.)
(That sounds good.)
(Where is the music coming from?)
(There's a sound.)
(He's dumbfounded.)
(Did you play it, Kwang Soo?)
(Where is it?)
(Squeak)
(He pretends not to know.)
(He leans forward to stop him from searching.)
(The sound is coming from here.)
(He finds a cell phone.)
(It was my alarm.)
He set an alarm.
(He set an alarm to create a sound.)
You said that it's luck.
(You said the staff's phone ringing was my luck.)
(They resume their eating.)
(I'll cut the pork cutlet.)
(She's about to cut it.)
(Crunch)
(A loud crunch)
(Squeak)
(Cut it quietly.)
(She tries it again carefully.)
(Crunch)
(My goodness.)
(She cuts it quickly.)
(She gives up.)
(It's hard to take a bite of pork cutlet.)
(I should eat the whole piece.)
(You should cut it.)
(Can't I just eat it?)
(You have to cut it.)
Don Spike tore it with his teeth.
(Don Spike tore it with his teeth.)
(Your talking is loud.)
(Why do I have to cut mine?)
(Just cut it how I did.)
(He cuts it carefully.)
(I got it.)
(People attack at different times.)
(He's getting annoyed.)
(This is for Jae Suk.)
(He puts the detector close to him.)
(He puts the detector close just for Jae Suk.)
(Move it away.)
(The crunchy sounds should be aired.)
(Good job, Kwang Soo.)
(So Min tries to eat the apple.)
(She'll make a sound no matter what.)
(She puts it close to her teeth.)
(You're doing well.)
(She takes a bite.)
(The sound isn't over 60db.)
(It's unbelievable how quietly she eats.)
(They approve of So Min.)
(It's your turn to take a bite, Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk will make a sound no matter what.)
(He starts off quite well.)
(Crunch)
(Hitting)
(His glasses fall off.)
(I'm sorry, Jae Suk.)
(We have Sprite left.)
(Opening the can is expected to be loud.)
(She does it carefully.)
(Squeak)
(She gets hit.)
(He also gets hit. It's okay, keep going.)
(She's more careful on her second try.)
(It makes a sound.)
(What kind of breakfast is this?)
(Have some, Jae Suk.)
(He accepts it nervously.)
(He pulls out his lips and drinks.)
His lips are dirty.
(Look, his lips are dirty.)
(He chokes.)
(He burps.)
(Squeaking)
(The bubbles explode because he drank too fast.)
(The sound of his burp is funny.)
(You drink it this time.)
(She swallows it.)
(It's very close.)
(It'll go over 60db soon.)
(She drinks almost all of it.)
(Ice cubes make a sound.)
(Squeaking)
(Burping)
(An actress burp is aired.)
(Sounds from So Min's body get extensive.)
(Jae Suk and So Min finish eating.)
- We're done. - Goodness.
- You did well. - Seriously.
- You did well. - I thought the apple would be bad.
They didn't fail.
I thought my teeth were coming off.
My teeth almost came off.
That was great. Okay.
Next up are Se Chan and Haha.
- Have a seat. - I'll sit here.
These will be hard.
All of them will be noisy.
What's this?
- It's to break this. - You have to break it to eat.
Come on.
This will be hard.
(They'll get hit a lot.)
Get ready, set.
- This is terrible. - Start.
(He takes it carefully.)
(Crunch)
(He gets hit.)
(Jong Kook acts as a police officer.)
(We have to tear the bag and break it.)
(He can't believe it.)
(Your laughter is too loud.)
(I only looked at the number.)
(The problem is opening the Schneeballen.)
(Crunch)
(Squeak)
(I tore it opened, but what's going on?)
He didn't tear it properly.
(He only tore open the outside.)
(Poor Se Chan.)
(Haha.)
(It's not coming out.)
(He laughs.)
(You have to open the inside bag too.)
(I'll open it again.)
(Come on...)
(Why did you take that part off.)
(His head is numb from getting hit so much.)
(If the Schneeballen has no way out,)
(then this is the only way.)
(He opens it while shouting.)
(He hits it with the hammer.)
(The squeaky hammer festival begins.)
(Just eat everything you can!)
(Eating frantically)
(Drink the cola too!)
(Opening)
(It's impossible to count how many times they got hit.)
(There are still rice crackers left even after all of this.)
(You take care of this.)
Aren't they set for last place?
(My real game starts when they begin to tease me for being last.)
(Mission Impossible, "Rice Crackers")
Can you open it?
(Carefully finish the rice crackers under 60dB)
It's so funny how he pretends to be careful.
(What is he doing?)
(That's right.)
What more do you want when you guys are already in the last place?
Just eat it.
(Let's just eat it all!)
(Game ends after they chew everything down angrily.)
We were given the most difficult snacks to eat.
- Snacks are difficult. - They're really hard.
The air from the AC is flowing this way.
- Yes, it's because of the wind - Is that right?
It's constantly at around 60dB.
Well, we can't do anything about nature changes.
(It's unfortunate.)
It's "natural disasters".
What on earth does he mean by "natural changes". My goodness.
- "Natural change". - You are the real "nature change".
Don't use phrases you are uncertain about.
How embarrassing.
The final result of the mission is a victory for Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
(They win with 14 accumulated squeaky hammer hits.)
- They chose a good meal. - Please choose...
who will receive the hint out of the two.
For the hint, you can choose between the R Leader or spies A, B, C,
and the hint will disappear after five seconds.
(Five seconds is so short.)
(A symbol of "Mission Impossible", disappearance after five seconds)
That's really cool.
I forgot Tom Cruise is going to be on the show today.
Don't forget that.
He's the main guest.
Please choose who will get the hint.
Between the two of us? Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do it. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo wins right away.)
You can choose between the leader of R Agency,
or M Agency's spies A, B, C.
(Since Ji Hyo is an R Agent, her choice will naturally be...)
I want the hint on M Agent A.
(Out of M Agents Jae Suk, So Min, and Se Chan)
(A hint on one of the M Agents will be revealed!)
(M agent A is over 40 years old.)
(It applies to Haha, Suk Jin, Jae Suk, and Jong Kook.)
(Which means that the hint was on Jae Suk.)
Now we move on to the next mission.
Let's go!
Okay.
You guys are aware that there are three spies...
- and the R Leader among you. - Who's the spy?
R Leader should let us know as soon as possible.
He should let us know somehow.
I'm not the Leader.
- I'm the Leader. - I already told you it's me.
The scale of today's show...
is too big for Suk Jin to be the Leader.
(That's so rude...)
I'll fit that scale.
It might be possible...
if Tom Cruise wasn't coming today.
A battle between Tom Cruise and Suk Jin is just weird.
It'd be so awkward.
I'm the one only person whose around the same age as Tom Cruise.
"One only person"?
"One only person"? He's leaving some wise words today.
Please, get some sleep while we get there.
- We gathered too early. - Being a radio DJ didn't help him.
- I need to have lines to speak. - Suk Jin!
Anyhow, if all members successfully complete the next mission...
a common hint that applies to all three spies...
(Success in the mission will lead to a common hint on the spies)
It will be given to everyone.
We can make an educated guess with that.
But have we ever won a group mission like this?
- Very rarely. - It's so difficult.
- This mission is... - Please give us something easy.
called "3 Characters in 1 Second".
What is that?
("3 Characters in 1 Second")
It's a mission in which a person tells a story with three letters.
If all eight members successfully finishes a sentence...
using 3 characters in 1 second for each member...
according to the subject that we give you.
(The mission cleared when 8 members complete a full sentence.)
This is hard. Making sentences is not that easy.
Whoever messes up here is a spy.
He's right, if they mess up here...
This is the perfect mission to find out who's the spy.
- This should be easy. - Hey, Mr. Suk Jin...
- why are you... - What do you mean, Mr. Suk Jin?
Hey, sir...
why are you acting this way.
You're making me mad.
When should I punish him?
It wouldn't be too late if I do it within this year, right?
Show us at least once.
To be honest, it's a difficult thing to say in our relationship,
but you can come at me from behind if you'd like.
(You can come at me from any angle.)
He's almost saying he can take you on with his hands tied.
Yes, you can come at me from behind.
So sweet.
(Anyone volunteer for his "honey punch?)
Sweet, sweet, Mr. Sweet.
I don't even know how much power I'm packing here.
Okay, Mr. Sweet.
Lend me those hands when we drink coffee, I can use some honey in it.
To sweeten your coffee?
It'll be like putting sugar in your coffee.
"Suyu-ri's Honey Punch".
We'll begin now, and the subject is "farewell".
- Farewell. - It's a sad topic.
- Who starts? - We'll start with Jong Kook.
- Ready, set... - I start first.
say "3 Characters in 1 Second".
"3 Characters in 1 Second, start!"
Ji Hyo...
Yesterday...
To Suk Jin...
(Incorrect)
("To Suk Jin" in a game that is limited to three letters?)
- That was four characters. - Come on, Suk Jin.
- Let's extend it to four letters. - Listen.
- It just has to go with the rhythm. - Is he a spy?
Why do you play so dirty?
"To Suk Jin" is just stupid.
I'm not taking this out only because it's so dangerous.
He hid his honey punch in the honey pot.
Let's have some honey.
Remember, I'm not taking this out only because it's dangerous.
It's all over when I take this out.
The game's stopped because of you.
Suk Jin, stop getting scolded.
- We're just having a conversation. - That's not true.
It's just a conversation.
It's such a one-sided conversation.
(Have some honey when you get scolded.)
As soon as I take my fist out, you guys are all finished.
- It's a honey pot. - It is.
We will give you one more chance, the next subject is...
- "Ennui". - That's a hard subject.
This will be the last game before we arrive.
Ennui.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(Will they succeed this time and get the hint?)
"3 Characters in 1 Second", start!
Is Jae Suk...
Having Ennui...
Right now?
I don't think so.
I'm not sure about that.
(Incorrect)
- He just didn't want to answer. - What was that?
- It's three characters. - I was trying to end the game.
- I was trying to end the game. - What was that?
Jong Kook's face just now...
had the loveliest expression I've seen of him so far.
Why?
"What was that?"
(What was that?)
- I did? - Yes, you did.
- Am I the only one who saw? - I missed it.
- He really said it like that. - Really?
- Yes. - Me? I didn't do that.
(Just a moment ago)
(Cute laughs)
(What was that?)
(Sweet nasally voice)
(One more serving of sweetness, please)
I did that? How did you even see that?
Recently, you've been staring at Jong Kook a lot.
What is up with you?
You're acting weird.
Now you've moved onto Jong Kook?
- Mission failed. - Give us one more chance.
Let's try to succeed at least once.
Can you give us something easier, those two were too hard.
For those of you who wanted one more opportunity...
only four of you will need to get it right on the next mission.
That's good news.
The next mission is, "Same Beds, Different Body".
What?
The question will be on the four fundamental arithmetic operations.
Say the correct answer and indicate the wrong answer with your fingers.
- If you do it right, you win. - It's like the Idiot Game.
Okay.
We can pass this no matter what.
Only the four of us needs to get it right.
We have a good chance of winning.
Each person needs to get it right three times.
(Each person needs three correct answer to win.)
In the order of addition, multiplication, and subtraction.
That's difficult.
The first person is very important.
First up is Jong Kook.
Then we move to Jae Suk.
- Hands and words separate, start! - Hands and words separate, start!
- 2 plus 1 is? - 3?
Hey.
(His fingers and mouth did say different things, but...)
Jong Kook, stop acting cute.
Why did you do it like that?
And what is up with the rhythm?
Your mouth was in a weird shape.
I'm sorry.
2 plus 2 is...
Okay, I got it.
But I saw that you were trying to be cute at the end.
You did something like this.
Did you get a girlfriend or something?
People usually do this to indicate the number two.
- You did it like this. - He even opened his mouth.
- Did you chance your concept? - That's enough now.
- Seok Jin, that's enough. - That's enough.
- Okay. - Hey!
(Seok Jin, that's enough.)
- Hey. - That's enough.
- You're embarrassing Jong Kook. - That's enough already.
- We have a chemistry together. - Worry about yourself.
He's a shy guy.
Seok Jin, stop getting scolded!
It's a conversation.
We're only having a conversation with each other.
Do you want me to take this out?
- Gosh. Let's start with Suk Jin. - I'll start us off.
- The beat is harder than I thought. - Look at me.
We begin now. Start.
- Hands and words separate, start! - Hands and words separate, start!
- 7 plus 2 is? - 9.
- 6 minus 3 is? - 2.
(Incorrect)
You already got it wrong.
(Super confident)
(Wrong mouth, correct fingers)
- You did 2 with your fingers? - You're trying to act cute, too.
- Why are you trying to act cute? - This is difficult.
- Why are you so bad at it? - You try it, it's hard.
How can you be so bad.
- It's not easy. - As a result,
you failed to get the hint.
(They fail to win a hint about the spies.)
I agree with it.
- Seriously. - Who's the spy?
- The spy won so easily. - That's right.
We can't ask each other about it.
We can't say anything.
Everyone got it wrong.
- I have an idea. - Me too.
(What mission awaits them?)
- Olympic Park is very nice. - It's beautiful here.
I haven't seen sunlight in the morning in a while.
This is great. It is sunlight in the morning.
- It's a roulette. - What?
(There's a colorful roulette in the middle of the park.)
Are we spinning it?
Why is there a roulette?
What is it?
It's set up well.
What are we doing?
- There's a roulette. - What are we doing?
Next mission is called...
Time-out Shooting.
What is it?
(3rd mission is called Time-out Shooting.)
"Shooting"?
It's a four-person team game.
The first half is water gun fight.
The second half is Target Name Tag Elimination.
(Target Name Tag Elimination?)
Everyone.
(Everyone picks Jong Kook.)
Come on, everyone.
- Don't fight. - That's right.
- It's not necessary. - Haha is right next to him.
Stop it.
For the water gun fight,
find guns filled with paint of five colors all over the park.
- It'll be messy. - We have to find them.
That's why we're wearing this outfit.
Within 10 minutes,
hit the opponents with as many colors as possible.
With different colors?
We should change the colors quickly.
The last half is Target Name Tag Elimination.
Spin the colored roulette.
Whoever has the selected color on his outfit becomes the target.
Are we playing Name Tag Elimination as well?
Mom's.
- Mom's... - Diary.
Let's go.
(What?)
- Not you. - I want to join.
The four of us will make a team.
- When did So Min join the team? - Why are you joining them?
Join us.
The team to eliminate a name tag within five minutes wins a point.
Once the target is out, we'll select a new target.
The hint is given to 1 of the 4 members...
- from the winning team. - Let's go, my team.
- We can do it. - You can do it, Jong Kook.
You'll divide into two teams.
So Min and Ji Hyo will play rock-paper-scissors to pick members.
(Ji Hyo and So Min get to select the team.)
It's So Min.
The first and the last member to be selected...
are obvious.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min wins.)
Kim Jong Kook.
Okay, that sounds good.
We must join So Min's team.
- It has to be So Min's team. - Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
(Round 2 of rock-paper-scissors)
(Ji Hyo wins.)
(She ponders.)
Can I take him away?
No.
If it's possible, you have to play it forever.
(They'll take Jong Kook back and forth all day.)
We won't finish by today.
You have to play rock-paper-scissors until tomorrow.
Take Jong Kook back and forth.
- I pick Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo picks Kwang Soo.)
(Sighing)
(Goodbye, Kwang Soo.)
- It's done. - It's done.
(Is it a fight with the tiger?)
Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min wins.)
(Okay!)
(Our team will win.)
Wait, no, it's not him.
(Haha invites himself to her team.)
- So Min. - Wait.
No.
- No, I pick Se Chan. - Okay.
You're not close with her. Get away.
Okay, okay.
You're not close with her. Move out of the way.
Things are getting strange here.
(He's disappointed.)
- You're making her uncomfortable. - We must win.
We must win.
- This round is important. - Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min wins again.)
Who plays it like that?
(Ji Hyo isn't lucky today.)
What's going on?
Whom you pick now is important.
(Let's go, "Mom's Diary" members.)
Pick Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk. - Okay.
(Jae Suk joins So Min's team.)
- Seriously? - We're doomed.
- Why did you pick me? - Is this our team?
- You're the best on our team. - Why did she pick me?
- You're the best. - Is this it?
I'm not the best.
- You're the best. - What?
Game is over.
Are you okay?
Seriously,
they're the weakest.
We've never been a team before.
- Okay. - It's over.
- Thank you. It's over. - It's over.
Let's get ready.
- Okay, let's do it. - Should we wear a hat?
Let's be serious.
- That's right. - Let's try it.
Will we use water guns?
I'm not sure.
Jae Suk and Jong Kook's team...
- should go over there. - Okay.
The other team will near the sculpture.
This is my first time.
- We're the stronger team. - Aren't you happy?
I'm going to play seriously. I'm annoyed.
(Let me show the power of the eldest.)
You just wait and see.
You'll see how fast... How fast...
Come on, Suk Jin.
- Can you talk? - He can't talk.
Our team can't even talk.
If the paint gets on the clothes, the person...
- Let's not cheer. - She doesn't know the rules.
She doesn't even know the rules.
- Hey, the best member. - Try to avoid them.
- Don't be like that. - Why am I the best?
- You're the best one. - Why am I the best?
- Let's go. - I'll be the best.
Let's go.
(Their cheer is weak.)
- Let's go. - We can do it.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - All right.
(Let's go and play.)
- In 3, 2, 1, let's go. - Let's go.
It's a water gun fight. We don't need strength for this.
- Search well, So Min. - Okay.
Go.
They're within the boundary, right?
- Are they hidden over there? - Let's see.
- We must find them. - Find them quickly.
(Kwang Soo runs as soon as they start.)
- What? - Here it is.
(He finds a water gun.)
- Attack right away. - Shall I go?
(I'll destroy all of you.)
- He found a water gun. - Really?
- I mean the other team. - Go now.
(They're surprised by how quick the others are.)
He already found one.
He found a water gun.
- What color is it, Suk Jin? - What?
- What color is it? - I think it's yellow.
What color is yours?
Don't shoot at me.
(He shoots at him while trying to show the color.)
(Shooting)
I'm sorry. Why did you shoot at me?
Did I get shot?
- This doesn't count. - It doesn't?
You shot me too.
- How could you shoot at me? - Goodness.
How could you?
(They start off by shooting the same team.)
We must shoot them quickly.
Is it big?
(Here it is.)
(Things are working out for her today.)
Come on.
(Come on.)
(Here's an attack.)
(The one with the selected color becomes the name tag target.)
I got you.
I can't find any water gun.
(Getting the least number of colors is the best.)
It's orange.
(The 10-minute water gun fight is over.)
Everyone, stand with your team.
I knew I'd get hit with most of the colors.
I got all the colors on me.
(No blue on Jae Suk, all for Se Chan and Jong Kook, no green on So Min)
We don't have blue.
There's no blue.
(None of them have blue on them.)
Look at him.
(What's this?)
Look.
Chul Min.
Shouldn't Kwang Soo change his pants?
Look at where it's stained.
- Kwang Soo. - It's okay. Leave it.
(Does it look that bad?)
Let's see if it's better on the front or the back.
(He shows his care.)
(It wasn't care at all.)
(He runs away with his shorts.)
Wait.
Stop it.
Look at his buttocks.
Where are Kwang Soo's buttocks?
Jae Suk, you also took Kwang Soo's buttocks.
Stop it.
(People in Jamsil saw a skinny marathon runner in leggings.)
Don't film me.
(Don't film me.)
We have no hope if it isn't blue.
Let's do it.
- It's over once eliminated. - We don't have to run away.
- We have to fight. - Let's fight.
We just have to avoid blue.
- Do we have all colors? - Yes.
I have all colors.
We'll spin the roulette.
(It's time to select the color.)
I hope it's blue.
Please don't be blue.
Please.
Please spin it.
(Once the target is out, a color is selected again.)
Let it be blue. Please let it be blue.
I have a bad feeling about this.
(It's the rule of Target Name Tag Elimination.)
It's orange.
(The target color is orange.)
We lost.
Gosh.
Stay out of it.
- It's a children's play. - What?
It's a children's play.
Stay out of it, Jong Kook.
(Once one person is out, the round is over.)
Seriously. Jong Kook should stay out of this.
We know that there's no use of running away.
He's here.
(He runs forward.)
- He's here. - Catch anyone.
Go.
No, no way.
(They run backwards.)
(Here's our chance.)
(Suk Jin is quite experienced with playing.)
We got it.
- Goodness. - Got it.
- I got it. - It's done.
- Oh, no. - We got him.
Okay.
Suk Jin is eliminated.
Let's go.
Take him to jail.
(I want to go home.)
It's been a long time since we played this game.
We haven't played Name Tag Elimination in a long time.
The race starts.
- Who eliminated the name tag? - I did.
Great job, Jong Kook.
I wish we could throw the name tag somewhere.
- I've never done it. - That's right.
- You're amazing. - It's okay.
We need blue.
(It's over if we lose again.)
If it's blue, let's eliminate Jong Kook.
- Okay. - Good.
They're nothing without Jong Kook.
You're right.
If it's blue, let's eliminate Jong Kook.
Spin it, please.
(Color roulette start!)
It's spinning now.
Forget everyone else, get Jong Kook.
(If it isn't blue, Sparta Kook will go after them.)
(If it is blue, the other team's one-sided counterattack begins.)
(The target color is blue.)
- Blue! - Okay.
(It's blue!)
(It's blue, we're done for.)
Here they come.
What should we do?
So Min, let's have you in the front.
Stop there.
Please don't abandon me.
So Min.
It's blue!
(Let's go get Jong Kook!)
Here we come.
(Hysteric laughs)
(I'm the bait, come and get me.)
Get me.
Why is no one getting me?
Why is everyone ignoring me?
Come here.
So Min, come here.
So Min.
(We only have to wait five minutes until the roulette spins again.)
Let's help her.
Hey So Min, get them!
Get them!
(Great teamwork from M Agents, they're only protecting Jong Kook!)
Get me please!
(Jong Kook runs away to plain fields.)
(While other members create distractions.)
Get So Min!
Hey, Ji Hyo!
Get me.
Get away from me!
(Go away, I'm busy.)
(Get me before you go.)
Take it off! Rip it off of me!
(He's getting in the way.)
Let go of me!
(Bites)
(Painful teeth)
You're not the one I want.
(Ace Kook on the run from his fanatic fans.)
(His tag must be removed before the target color changes.)
(Get me before you go.)
Come out here.
Hurry.
(Jong Kook hides while Jae Seok distracts.)
- You're not going anywhere. - Haha.
- We have to get him. - You can't go anywhere.
Two minutes before the roulette change!
I'll do something.
We have to get him.
(I get the tiger today.)
Try me. Try ripping it off.
(There's no one I can't beat.)
Rip it off.
(Screams in pain)
Hold on.
Ji Hyo!
(Screams in pain)
Haha, you're the only one left.
You're alone now.
Rip off my name tag first.
(He tried to catch the tiger.)
(Now he's about to face the consequences.)
Hey, Ji Hyo!
- Hey, this is our last chance! - This is our last chance, Haha.
We won't get blue again.
One minute before the roulette change!
Hurry up and get the tag.
(With a minute left, Ace Ji Hyo goes on the hunt.)
Get him.
Get him right now!
Try it.
Hurry up.
(Mapo-gu duo versus Jong Kook and So Min)
We have to stop her.
Stop Ji Hyo.
(Mapo-gu duo versus Jong Kook and So Min)
Get So Min instead!
If you can't get him, at least get So Min.
- Move. - At least get So Min!
- Isn't time up yet? - Take anyone's name tag off!
(When the color changes, they lose the chance to get at least a point.)
Get So Min instead?
No, wait!
Time is up, the roulette spins now.
(The 5 minutes are up, the roulette will spin now.)
- Wait it out. - Get the tag!
(The roulette is spinning, we have to get something!)
(Lies down on the ground)
- Wait it out! - Get So Min's name tag!
(So Min chooses the strategy of laying down.)
The time is up, the roulette will spin now.
(The roulette begins to spin.)
(If they wait this out, a new target will be set.)
Please, let me go.
- Should I rip her name tag off? - Let me go please.
- We have to get her! - Ji Hyo.
Please, let me go.
We have five seconds left, get the tag!
- Get the tag! - Hang in there!
Get the tag now!
- Take it off! - Hang on!
(With her tag halfway off, will they get the point?)
Try to wait it out.
Rip it off!
Roulette change! Green!
- We got it! - Hang on!
So Min is out!
No, she's not out!
(Just before So Min's tag was ripped off...)
(the target changed to green, which So Min doesn't have.)
Roulette change! Green!
(The target changed to green, which So Min doesn't have.)
No!
(Situation turned in an instant.)
- Let's get them! - Kwang Soo, no!
I'm out!
(Kwang Soo is out of the game from So Min's counterattack.)
Kwang Soo is out!
He's out.
(The roulette changed, so you're out.)
You got her after the roulette was spun.
I didn't hear it changed to orange.
(Even with the perfect chance, they blew it and lost 2:0)
It changed to orange?
- It really changed to orange? - You're out.
The result of "Time-out Shooting",
Jae Suk, Jong Kook, So Min,
and Se Chan win with the score of 2:0.
(The M Agents and Jong Kook win and get a hint!)
Let's hear the hint.
The winning team will vote to choose who will take a look at the hint.
We need to vote?
What if we all get one vote each?
Don't vote for someone who's been acting like a spy.
I think Jae Suk would've been given...
a special role for a special episode.
It'd be weird if they left him alone without an assignment.
Jong Kook also speaks English well.
It'd be Tom and Yu.
He can't get to Tom Cruise either.
What I can say for sure is that Se Chan is a regular R Agent.
Se Chan is just an R Agent.
(There's no way they gave a special role to someone so insignificant.)
You write down who'll receive the hint, right?
(M Agents have finished voting.)
The person with the most vote...
is So Min.
(Acting surprised)
I knew it. There are two M agents there, and they voted for her.
Really?
They gave her the votes.
(How did they know?)
You can choose between a hint on one of the...
M Agents A, B, C and the R Leader.
Choose which one you want to see out of the four options.
R Leader!
(She chooses R Leader, of course.)
M.
(What is the hint regarding their target, R Leader?)
(The leader was born on an even numbered month.)
This is difficult.
(The potential Leaders are Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Haha, and Jong Kook.)
Now we will move to the location of the final mission.
You will divide up into three cars to get to your destination...
to figure out whether or not the others are spies.
- Three different cars? - Three different cars?
They want us to look into each other.
You can choose whom you'll ride with.
(It's their final chance before meeting a senior agent of M Agency.)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan get in one car.)
Who do you suspect the most?
- I want to know your opinion. - In my opinion,
- So Min is suspicious. - I see.
- While I suspect So Min... - Yes.
I suspect Jae Suk at the same time.
If Jae Suk wasn't an M Agent,
he wouldn't have voted for So Min.
- If he wasn't an M Agent, right? - Right.
I don't think he would've voted for So Min.
So let's leave out Jae Suk for now.
Let's think about Kwang Soo.
(I suspect Kwang Soo...)
- You suspect Kwang Soo? - Yes.
Why do you think that?
I think it'd be weird for him to be out of the picture...
on a stage as big as this. It's not like Running Man to do that.
That's right.
Haha is weird today, too.
When Haha receives directions,
he acts like it's too difficult for him.
On that day? You're right.
He says, "I'm having a really bad day today."
He's said that a lot today.
When I saw him saying things like that so often today,
it made me suspect him a bit.
Or I think that he may be...
the R Leader, too.
- Haha? - Yes.
Since Tom Cruise is coming today...
(Vehicle of the people from R Agency)
- I'd like to show some teamwork. - Me too.
Be honest, what are you?
I'm just an R Agent.
I really got nothing else today.
How can I trust him?
It's because...
Put something on collateral before you talk.
I'll give everything I have.
If you lie today,
I'll tell people who your celebrity ex-girlfriends were...
on social media.
(You're seriously bringing that up?)
You want to do that?
I'm serious. If it isn't a lie, you should be able to do that.
- Seriously, what are you doing? - What?
- Are you a spy? - Okay, post it if you want.
- Fine. - I'll really do it.
Do it if I'm lying.
- Okay, I'll really do it. - What are you?
I'm the R Leader.
(I'll be honest with you since you were honest with me.)
- Really? - I'm telling you because...
you told me that you were an R Agent.
If you're not the R Leader,
I'll post the same on you.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Who?
Your...
(Way back then...)
I'm married.
I'll just post the initials.
It wouldn't matter if you're not lying.
If you're lying, I'm posting pictures too.
Okay.
When this episode is over,
I'll just post a picture...
instead of a name.
Dear viewers, if Kwang Soo is lying...
I will post a picture of the person...
you are unaware of.
If he's lying.
Then I will...
his is not a celebrity.
(She's not a celebrity.)
But Dong Hoon...
Although his wife...
is his first love...
I don't know what I'm saying.
I don't know!
I'll do it! I'll post it too!
(This car is filled with disclosures.)
Okay.
If this guy is not an R Agent...
Stop it!
Please stop it!
(The car goes to the final destination.)
It'd be fine if you're an R Agent.
- I am. - You are, right?
Now you are at the final destination.
- Yes. - We are.
You are only given one hour.
I'll explain the rules of the final round with three hints on the line.
The game is "Mission Impossible: Three Battles".
(Final mission of Catch the Spy, "Mission Impossible")
The three guests who are senior agents of M Agency are...
(Henry Cavill with fatally good looks.)
(Simon Pegg with a crazy mouth)
(Tom Cruise, world's number one)
(It's an unbelievable lineup of 3 senior agents from M Agency.)
The three guests, who are senior agents of the M Agency...
are aware of who the spies are.
(The guests know who they are.)
If the senior agents win,
the hint regarding the R Leader will be given to the spies.
(If the three senior agents win, the spies will receive a hint.)
On the other hand, if the senior agents lose...
a hint on the M Agency spies...
will be given to the R Agents.
(If the senior agents lose, the R Agents will receive a hint.)
We don't even know who the Leader is yet.
We were so distracted by meeting Tom Cruise...
we all forgot the rules today.
It's making me nervous for no reason.
Honestly, Tom Cruise is...
someone whose movies have...
- been with me since my childhood. - It's true.
- Starting from "Cocktail"... - That's right, "Cocktail".
- to "Top Gun"! - "Top Gun"!
("Top Gun" made Tom Cruise into an action star.)
From "Mission impossible" to...
- He was in "A Few Good Men", right? - That's right.
You guys are absolutely right.
I watched many of his films.
He's our enemy today.
He's an enemy to R Agents, right?
- No, he's a guest. - Is he a guest?
We're getting instructions, so put your earphones on.
They just criticized you. There was an instruction.
- I'm glad I didn't hear it. - You need to watch your mouth.
- That's what they said. - All right.
Henry Cavill will be here as well.
- "Man of Steel". - Right.
- He's Superman. - He is.
Henry was born in the Year of the Pig in 1983.
- The Year of the Pig? - Yes, 1983.
I'm the most worried about So Min right now.
She's very interested in Henry.
Don't be interested in him.
What will you do if he looks at you?
He makes eye contact with you. What will you do?
- He makes eye contact with you. - Hi.
(Winking)
(Hi, Henry. I'm Jeon.)
I hate that.
He'll think you're cute though.
That's fine,
but the securities might use the taser on her.
There's a small chance.
- Tom Cruise is also very nice. - That's the general impression.
He shakes everybody's hands.
I'll shake his hand as the representative.
(He's too kind, so it might take too long.)
- What? - What are you talking about?
- What do you mean? - You're not funny.
- He'll shake everybody's hands. - When will I get another chance?
We can make a line here.
And as you know,
when we invite superstars on our show,
- some people try to take pictures. - Let's not do that.
- Let's not do that. - Who brought their phone?
(Me)
I have mine.
- Don't take it from us. - We won't take pictures with him.
- We won't do it. - Give it to me.
Is this the reserve forces? Why would you take it from us?
Who are you? What's your role?
I'm rearranging the situation.
- What do you mean? - Who are you to do that?
- Fine. - Give it to me.
- He's the homeroom teacher. - Are you the manager?
Everybody, they're waiting for us.
- Do we finally get to see them? - Are they really here?
All right.
Are they coming?
Finally, it's time to welcome them.
- Senior agents, come on out. - I'm excited.
I'm excited to see Tom Cruise...
Henry Cavill, and Simon Pegg.
I spent my school years watching Tom Cruise's films,
- and I still watch them. - Exactly.
- What's that? - He's there.
(Cheering)
(Simon Pegg is indispensable in the film.)
(Tom Cruise is an action film genius.)
(Henry Cavill is every woman's heartthrob.)
(The real ones are here.)
(What's up, Running Man?)
(Tom Cruise from M Agency is in Korea to catch the R Leader.)
(The real ones are here.)
(What's up, Running Man?)
(Tom Cruise from M Agency is in Korea to catch the R Leader.)
Henry.
(They can't stop gaping. Is this for real?)
(They forget about their dignity in 3 seconds.)
- Nice to meet you. - Henry.
- It's very nice to meet you. - Hi.
Nice to meet you.
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - How are you?
- Hi, Simon. - Hello.
- That's me. - How are you?
(Did I just shake their hands?)
(I'm not going to wash my hands.)
We shook hands.
- Brother Tom. - Hello. How are you? Ready?
- Yes, I'm ready. - Let's do it.
Cavill.
(It looks like a reunion of a separated family.)
(This is unbelievable.)
- Hello. - My heart is pounding.
Hello.
- Hello. - Thank you.
(They're world-class sweet guys.)
Shall we sit?
I don't want to show bad manners, so I can't even express how I feel.
He just stood up and sat back down.
(M Agency and R Agency are in the same room.)
He's our boss, Tom Cruise.
Tom Cruise!
Thank you very much. Thank you.
(Thank you so much.)
- Thank you. - He's my brother.
- He's our brother. - My brother.
Next is Henry Cavill.
(Henry Cavill is the youngest agent in M Agency.)
Superman.
We respect you.
My gosh. He's so handsome.
- He's the oldest agent. - He's my style.
Simon Pegg.
Nice.
I feel good.
Simon said, "I feel good."
- Yes. - "I feel good."
These three actors have joined us today.
Please say hi to the Korean viewers.
First of all, congratulations on your show.
We're very, very happy to be here. It's a great show.
We're very excited to be here, so thank you.
This is my ninth time being in Korea.
I'm very excited to be here as always.
- That's right. - Thank you. We love it here.
This is my first time here in Korea.
- It's his first time. - His first time.
- Yes. - I'm incredibly excited to be here.
Thank you so much for having us on the show.
This is my second time in Korea.
- This is his second time. - I'm enjoying it this time.
I learned the love hearts.
Yes, yes.
(Everybody knows the love hearts, right?)
They know this.
- There you go. - They know this.
- You got to do this. - I can't believe they know this.
They know this.
- This is a new one. - There you go.
- That's good. - This.
That's good.
They know this too.
Like that?
(He makes an elbow heart too.)
This.
- He looks so cool. - His arms touch.
Let me see. Wait.
There it is.
(He searches...)
(and takes a heart out of his back pocket.)
What's that? Watch.
(It's a heart of course.)
- Hold on. - What's that?
They're awesome.
They know it all.
- He did this too. - They're funny.
This is great.
This is season six...
- of "Mission Impossible". - Six.
Why do you think it was able to last this long?
- Tom. - Him.
I don't question it. I'm just happy...
that people want to see us and allow us to make it.
It's a very extreme and a very challenging film to produce.
The 1st "Mission Impossible" was the 1st film I ever produced.
Really? I see.
Tom's probably too modest to say this, but I think one of...
the things that makes these films really quite amazing...
is the fact that he genuinely risks his life...
in order to make it so thrilling.
- That's right. - He put his life on the line...
- hanging from helicopters. - That's right.
This one has a helicopter.
- It has a helicopter. - Right.
I learned how to fly a helicopter for the film.
- You drove by yourself? - Sure, everything.
Everything you see in the movie, I do it all.
I trained for a year and a half...
to fly and learn how to do aerobatics in helicopters.
That sounds scary.
- Motorcycles too? - Motorcycles.
All of it.
Free driving the whole time.
Sometimes over 100 miles per hour.
(The highlight of this film is the chasing scene on the road.)
(Tom Cruise drove the motorcycle himself.)
Computer graphics is really advanced now,
so that's what we thought you'd use. Why do you do it yourself?
You can see when it's computer graphics.
There's a difference. You see the difference when you see...
films with computer graphic images. They're cartoons. They're not real.
What I'm interested in is how can I engage an audience? How can I...
get them not to just watch the film, but experience the movie,
and to feel the movie.
Henry, did you shoot the gun...
in the helicopter yourself?
I do. Oh, yes.
He brings his own machine gun.
You brought your own gun?
No, I didn't.
(Apparently he even brought his own machine gun.)
Me? I do as much as I can, but...
I mostly just... My life is put in enough danger by him,
so anything else beyond that, I just stop.
"Okay, I'll take it."
(Safety first.)
Do we have any questions for them?
So Min, do you have a question? Anything for Cavill?
(He stares at her.)
You ask.
(She's shy.)
(What is wrong with her?)
I can't think. I'm so shy.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
I want to know if you three are good friends.
(Good friends?)
We're just too nervous.
- I'm so nervous. - Yes.
Yes, we're great friends.
It's... We worked together for 12 months,
and especially when you do stunts... I mean,
my life was in Tom's hands for 12 months,
and you...
I don't like these guys.
(I don't like Henry.)
He's right though. I'm making that up about him.
Tom I like. Simon not so much.
(They must be great friends.)
(We're close.)
I have a question.
How do you get in shape?
- And... - I'm curious.
- Cavill... - For the film.
Did you work out this time in Korea?
It's...
- Only Henry? - Yes.
Hush, you.
He's talking about people in shape.
They're like us.
- They're similar to us. - "Stop it."
We're similar.
(Shall we start the mission between Team R and M?)
We don't have that much time...
- with these three. We have an hour. - Right.
We feel sad about it.
Here's the mission we prepared.
Here are the rules.
Let's start Mission Impossible: Three Battles...
- right now. - All right.
The first mission is Metal Box Quiz.
With them?
(We'll be playing Metal Box Quiz with them?)
(You have to guess the item in the metal box.)
(MC Yu's dramatic style is the point of this game.)
Do you want us to play the game with these three?
Is this the game we're thinking about?
The game I lead?
Do you want us to play that with Tom Cruise?
With these guys?
The team that gets 2 out of 3 questions right wins.
For your information, the senior agents...
know who the double agents are.
If you pay attention to the results, it'll help you figure it out.
- Okay. - We'll know.
Let's get 3 out of 3.
Let's go. Let's get 3 out of 3.
Simon Pegg is first one up.
Please pick your opponent.
Simon is up.
Okay, I think I'm going to choose...
(This will be their only chance to play this game with Simon.)
(Which opponent will he choose?)
Lee.
Me?
Okay.
(Let's do this.)
I like working with tall people.
Let's do this.
Good luck.
(Tom steps up.)
Me too.
You are similar to him.
You're Asian Prince.
All right. Let's go.
Who are all these people suddenly?
Simon and Kwang Soo...
have to guess what's in this.
(It's a game between the Korean and British princes.)
- Ready. - Yes.
(They're serious.)
- Ready? - Yes, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
He sounds nervous.
- I can hear his heartbeat. - I can't...
believe we're playing this with them.
It's funny seeing you two next to each other.
- Ready. - Here we go.
(In the first metal box...)
(is a broccoli.)
(Who will recognize it first?)
It'll be fast, so you have to watch carefully.
(They're focused.)
I see something.
Can we do this to Simon?
Hurry up.
(He talks about something else.)
(Here he goes again.)
- Hurry. - We can't do this to Simon.
- They're world stars. - I got my super hero pose.
Hurry up.
(This is Korean humor. They start again.)
It's nothing. It's a...
(He can barely see it.)
- It's nothing. - There's nothing in there. Hang on.
It's in a shelf that's above...
(The metal box show time begins.)
(Flinching)
What is this madness?
- Don't come forward. - I saw it.
(Simon's eyes move back and forth.)
It's a box.
You came too close.
(He inches forward.)
Sorry. Sorry.
You came up too much.
(That's not how you play this game.)
(Laughing)
He likes it too.
Tom likes it.
- People like it worldwide. - Let's go. Yes.
(Tom is focused on the game.)
I'm going to take this out.
(Turning)
(I saw something.)
It's a wasabi.
What?
- Answer. - Answer?
(Kwang Soo sounds confident.)
(This is his only chance to beat the heroes of "Mission Impossible".)
Chewed gum.
(He's confident.)
- Watch your pronunciation. - Be careful.
- The gum. - Wrong.
You're incorrect.
- It's green... - Watch carefully.
- Yes, it's green. - Yes.
(They know it's green.)
Okay.
What's that?
(They're annoyed.)
(They crawl to it.)
(Simon is mad at MC Yu's tricks. He crawls on all fours.)
(At that moment)
It's a broccoli! It's broccoli!
(He finds out.)
(It's a broccoli!)
Correct.
Broccoli is correct!
- It's correct? - Yes.
- It's really broccoli? - Yes.
- Really? - It's broccoli.
(Great job.)
It came out of the thing.
- It's broccoli. - It's my favorite food.
Thank you.
(It's my favorite food.)
(Thank you.)
Broccoli.
Why did you eat that?
Did you see Simon?
He just ate the broccoli.
He was so happy to get the question right.
That's good Korean broccoli. It is.
Have you played this game before?
Are there games like this in America?
That's the first time I've seen that game.
No, I've never seen this before.
There's nothing like this in the world.
There's nothing like this in the world, okay?
That's right. This is only in Korea.
We only play the game here.
(It became a Korean traditional game on variety shows.)
- Henry is next. - Yes.
Go, Henry. Go, buddy.
You're going to win. Come on.
Let's go, Henry.
You have to choose an opponent.
(My opponent is...)
(They're nervous.)
Is it Jun?
(He considered it carefully.)
You? It's So Min.
(Henry said, "Jun".)
Thank you.
(She smiles with her eyes.)
(That shook her heart.)
- Thank you. - So Min.
We're playing a game.
- This is competition. - It's a game.
(It looks like they already won.)
Please shake hands.
She's smiling strangely.
Why are you doing that with your eyes?
(Her eyes have a problem.)
It's different from when you say hi to us.
She looks so happy. She crinkled her nose.
You never smile like that.
I've...
- never seen you making that face. - Why are you smiling like that?
- What's wrong with her? - Focus on the game.
Good luck.
(Good luck, Henry.)
- What do you mean? - You're playing against him.
Good luck.
- You're not on the same team. - She looks so happy.
- He's an opponent. - Ready.
(They get suspicious of So Min.)
(The second item...)
(is a whistle.)
Here we go.
(The second game starts.)
Henry is doing this.
(He's focused.)
Good job.
It's fancy.
(Jae Suk moves fast from the beginning.)
Superman can't see everything.
Use your X-ray vision.
Yes, use the x-ray vision. Come on.
It was yellow.
It's yellow.
Is it a bottle opener?
A bottle opener?
Incorrect.
I'll throw off the lid.
All right. He gave it to you.
(What just passed by?)
- This is an incredible game. - You have to focus.
(The master gets excited by the attention he's getting.)
Is it a key chain?
(He starts teasing.)
(He stands up.)
(Henry can't stand the teasing and gets up.)
- That's fancy. - Good job.
- You're a human cultural asset. - He's Korea's best MC.
(Peeking)
Henry is trying so hard.
- Look, Henry. - What's Superman doing?
Oh, dear.
(He couldn't see it,)
(so he uses force.)
(What are you doing?)
(This is an easy way.)
What are you doing?
It's a whistle.
- He said it first. - He said it first. Sorry.
- Sorry. - Sorry.
Henry is correct.
(Henry Cavill wins.)
(So Min wasn't interested in getting it right.)
Let's go again.
Henry can't do that.
What's the whole point of the game?
- Isn't this cheating? - It's cheating.
It's cheating.
(Quiet)
He's too strong.
(He takes Jae Suk away from the cameras.)
What are you doing?
- What's going on? - He's Jong Kook.
- He's the American Jong Kook. - Is he Jong Kook?
He's much stronger than Jong Kook.
That was cheating, but he made it natural.
I didn't know that was the rule. You just said...
- You didn't say that. - I was just being in character.
I was being in character. August Walker.
(Look at these guys.)
- They look innocent. - We approve.
It's the last person to go.
It's Tom.
- It's Tom. - Tom.
(It's finally Tom's turn to choose an opponent.)
Okay, Kim.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Jong Kook is a good opponent for Tom Cruise.)
- Show him your body. - Let's go.
He won't lose.
I won't.
Jong Kook...
- looks happy. - Of course.
I'm next to him.
(I'm next to Tom.)
(They lost twice in a row, but this might be good.)
Let's go.
(Will Jong Kook win with 20 years of experience on variety shows?)
(Or will it be Tom, who can accomplish any mission?)
(This game has their pride on the line.)
(He's serious.)
- This one's kind of hard. - Is it?
It's empty.
- It's on the second shelf. - It's the second shelf.
It's second from...
(The item is on the 2nd shelf.)
What's this?
(Simon comes forward.)
(What are you doing?)
Isn't that cheating?
You can't do that.
You're good at this.
Simon is really good at this.
(Tom and Jong Kook's game continues.)
Wait a minute. What's this?
You have to show us more.
(They're having a difficult time.)
(They hear the familiar background music.)
(Singing)
(We still don't have a clue.)
(What should we do?)
(Everyone focuses on the metal box.)
Simon! Simon!
(Hurried)
(He moves to the back of the metal box...)
(and gets caught.)
(The newbie of the variety show gets apprehended.)
I just wanted to see.
I don't know what it is.
(He is the British Lee Kwang Soo.)
(The match continues on.)
(Jae Suk suddenly takes off his jacket.)
(Tom suddenly moves as well.)
(Singing)
- He is tying his shoes! - Why is he tying his shoes?
(This is the Metal Box Quiz.)
(Tom goes along with what Jae Suk does.)
(It's time to give a full view of what's in the metal box.)
Turn it over.
(Both of them are frustrated.)
What is it? Match?
Match! I said it!
Correct!
(Tom Cruise is correct.)
- Correct! - Match.
(Tom Cruise gets the answer, which is a match.)
All right.
Is match "Magic" in English?
Why would it be "Magic"?
"Magic" means something entirely different.
- Didn't he say "Magic"? - He said "Match".
- How did he get it right? - How did you see that?
How did you see that? Your eyes are like...
(I can't believe you got the match right.)
My goodness.
How did he see it?
I didn't recognize it from here.
Give them a round of applause.
(The senior agents of M Agency wins the first mission.)
- Great job. - It was hard.
They are good.
(I can't believe we lost three rounds.)
- They are good. Respect! - Okay.
Since Team M won the first mission,
you won't receive a hint on the spies.
(It's good news for Jae Suk, Se Chan, and So Min.)
We won't receive a hint.
We will now move on...
to the second mission.
(What's the second mission?)
Now, we will have a match...
against the three of them.
The second mission is the mystery box.
The one who feels and guesses the object right first wins a point.
Please pick your opponent.
(The 3 senior agent pick their opponents.)
I will pick Ji.
Suk Jin.
(It looks like Henry will have an easy match for the 2nd time.)
I will pick Song.
Ji Hyo.
(Simon chooses Ji Hyo.)
Tom.
Who is left here? Who is playing...
(Se Chan, the spy, gives him a sign.)
Yes. Yang.
(Tom chooses Se Chan after reading his signal.)
Thank you.
You will compete against Tom Cruise.
He called me Yang. Yang.
- Thank you. It will be fun. - Yang.
Simon and Ji Hyo will go first.
(Song Ji Hyo versus Simon Pegg)
- It won't be easy. - It's a bit scary.
Let's get started.
(Nervous)
It's a bit scary.
(Do you remember how Ji Hyo did with this scary game?)
(Screaming)
(Ji Hyo screamed every time she put her hand inside.)
(The Mystery Box is a screen time maker.)
(She is already nervous.)
- What is that? - What is that?
What...
(The content of the first box is revealed.)
(Pasta)
What will they do? This is scary.
What will they do?
Are you serious?
Don't you think you went too far?
(He pretends to be relaxed,)
(but Simon is a bit nervous.)
Guess what's inside the box.
This is scary.
This is... Go.
(Can Simon overcome fear?)
Go.
Be careful.
(Screaming)
(They show big reactions.)
- Be careful. - Oh, my goodness.
(What is that?)
What is that?
- Be careful. - Seriously.
It's wet.
Pasta.
(He blurts out the answer.)
(Pasta)
Pasta.
(Simon is correct.)
Correct!
(He is relaxed.)
What was that?
He isn't scared.
He is the master of variety shows.
How was I supposed to get this right?
Don't eat it!
Weren't you scared?
Yes, I was. It felt organic.
(Simon, the master of variety shows)
But then it was the unmistakable shape of fusilli.
How did he know?
You know,
- had we done this, - We wouldn't have known.
we would have spent 20 minutes.
Simon won a point.
Next up is Henry.
(Next up is Henry Cavill.)
We need to receive a hint.
We need to receive a hint on the spies.
Something scary will be inside.
Please tell him that. Something scary will be inside.
- Yes. - Something terrible.
- Okay. - In 1, 2.
- No! - My goodness.
(Their reactions are bigger.)
What will they do?
(What's inside the second Mystery Box?)
(A human hand?)
(Let's talk about this hand.)
(A single touch is enough to make a member nearly faint.)
(It's unpleasant enough to stop the shoot.)
(It's ready to surprise Superman.)
It's alive.
No!
(I didn't expect a human hand to come out.)
(With everyone's expectations,)
(the match between Suk Jin and Henry starts.)
(Henry is takes the aggressive approach.)
(He makes a fuss.)
(Henry is relaxed.)
- What is it? It's moving. - Wait a second.
(Henry grabs the human hand.)
It's a human hand.
Come on!
He is Jong Kook!
I can't believe it.
(This isn't how you play this game.)
He is Jong Kook.
- How... - Is it over?
- It's over. - What's the answer?
What's the answer?
How did he know?
(It's more like Speed Quiz, not Mystery Box.)
(Good job.)
- We would have put... - Who is in there?
our hands in there...
- and taken 20 minutes. - Seriously.
Aren't you scared? You don't know what's inside.
No, I have been in a helicopter while I was being chased by Tom.
(That's his secret.)
The last round is between Yang Se Chan and Tom Cruise.
- Okay. - Okay. Great. Let's go.
- The last one. - Tom, this is a bit...
You have to be careful.
- You have to be careful. - Yes, I will be careful.
Oh, my goodness.
(Even Simon is surprised.)
- Don't tell him. - All right.
(What is it?)
What is it?
(Inside the third box is...)
(a moving toy snake.)
(What is this unpleasant sound?)
- What is that sound? - My goodness.
What is that sound?
This is happening for real.
It's alive.
- Ready? - Yes, I am ready.
- It's dangerous. - Go slowly.
(They grab each other's hand.)
Let go!
(They have a passionate handshake inside the box.)
(This is interesting.)
(Tom grabs the toy snake.)
- My goodness. - Hold on.
(Don't tell me...)
Snake toy. Toy snake.
(He gets it right in 12 seconds.)
Come on!
(It looks like we won again.)
(He is cheerful.)
- Is it over? - It's over.
Wasn't it above?
- Wasn't he scared? - We can't win once.
- They are really good. - He said, "Snake toy".
His answer was precise, too.
He touched it.
- Maybe he knew the answer. - He...
This is frustrating.
(Even a real snake can't scare them.)
We can't win against them.
They are really good at games.
(The last mission is revealed.)
The last mission is Pirate Roulette Game.
(Pirate Roulette Game)
- Okay. - That's good.
The two teams will take turns...
inserting a sword.
The team that makes the pirate pop out loses.
We might win this time.
This is pure luck.
I can't believe we are playing this game...
- with Tom Cruise. - Have you played...
this game before?
- Never? - Never. I have never.
(It's his first time seeing it.)
This is the last mission.
This is our last chance to receive a hint.
- That's right. - We need to receive a hint.
Please insert a sword anywhere.
(Tom Cruise looks out of place before the Pirate Roulette Game.)
(Which slot should I choose?)
- Tom... - Tom is also...
(What's the result?)
(Inserting)
Tom is also...
(He succeeds in inserting one sword.)
- Safe. - Safe.
It's over if the pirate pops out.
- Is it over if the pirate pops out? - Yes.
You only have one chance.
(I think it will pop out this time.)
(It's their last chance to receive a hint.)
It's our last chance to receive a hint.
(Shouting)
(Simon gets used to Korean variety shows.)
(Simon is hilarious.)
(Inserting)
Henry, you are up.
- Go, Henry. Come on, Henry. - Come on.
Henry.
(Childish)
(Henry is nervous for the first time.)
(Is he fated to succeed?)
Oh, he changed his mind.
(Please)
(Inserting)
(Pirate Roulette Game makes the three of them happy.)
Let's make this interesting.
(Jong Kook goes next.)
(Inserting)
(Is it my turn?)
Okay, Simon. Let's go, Simon. Come on.
- Simon. - Simon.
(We have a good feeling about this, Simon.)
Please. Please.
(The British Lee Kwang Soo is bound to make the pirate pop out.)
- Simon. - Simon.
He is funny.
(Let's see if Simon will make the game interesting.)
(Inserting)
(He exits in a cool way.)
So Min.
(Singing)
(Tom goes along with it.)
Please.
(So Min succeeds.)
(It's Tom's turn again.)
(Tom gets caught.)
(Tom is human after all.)
I won!
I won, right?
(If it pops out, I win, right?)
Good job. Good job.
That was incredible.
We won.
The Unlucky Club should celebrate.
Jennie and Tom are the new additions.
- We won, right? - Yes.
- No, no. - We won.
We won.
(R Agency wins for the first time.)
This time, M Agency lost.
We won.
That's their spot.
The three of them are hilarious.
- They go to their spot... - They are so nice.
- no matter what happens. - They are so nice.
They are so nice.
- We are actors. - We are actors.
- We know to stay on our marks. - We know to stay on our marks.
It's time to say goodbye.
This was so much fun.
Thank you. You guys are wonderful. You are absolutely wonderful.
Thank you all so much. It's been a lot of fun playing.
You guys are absolutely fantastic. It was amazing being on the show.
- Lovely. - It's a great show.
Also, who is in that box?
Yes. Get that person out of the box.
- Who is in that box? - Who is in that box?
(They are cheerful until the end.)
This was really fun. You guys are amazing.
- You guys are amazing. - Thank you.
I think I am happy because we won a lot,
- but... - You won a lot.
(It's fun to win a lot.)
- That makes sense. - We prepared...
small gifts. Please wait.
Is it broccoli? It's not broccoli, is it?
(The master of variety shows makes them laugh until the end.)
Thank you very much.
(The first gift is the golden R Badge.)
Thank you, Running Man.
- Excellent. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - That's the name tag.
- It's a name tag. - Tom Cruise.
- That's so cool. - Thank you so much!
- Thank you. - Excellent.
- Nice. - Thank you so much.
- Would you put it on my back? - Yes.
(They are touched.)
- My goodness. - Come on.
Tom Cruise.
Take a picture of us.
Stop it. What are you doing?
- Get lost! - What are you doing?
Take a picture of us.
(The 3 senior agents finish their mission.)
(What are the fates of the two agencies?)
Following the result of the missions,
the spies of M Agency will receive two hints on the leader of R Agency.
The spies of R Agency will receive...
one hints on the leader of M Agency. If you go to your position and wait,
you will receive the hints via texts.
The three people who receive the most number of votes...
will go up the platform and get their identities checked.
If more than two people are the spies of M Agency,
R Agency will win. If the leader of R Agency is...
one of the chosen ones, M Agency will win.
The winning team will receive a golden badge.
(So Min receives 2 hints on the leader of R Agency.)
(The leader has gone on a Luxury Package tour...)
(and uses a stage name.)
(Among the members who have gone to Luxury Package tour,)
(Haha and Ji Hyo use stage names.)
It's either Haha or Ji Hyo.
(Jae Suk, here are the hints.)
This is...
(The leader of R Agency is either Haha or Ji Hyo.)
Who could it be?
(The 2 candidates are unexpected.)
This is too hard.
(Between Haha and Ji Hyo, who is the leader of R Agency?)
(Among the agents of M Agency, A has a younger sister.)
It's Jae Suk, right?
- Yes. - Okay. I knew it.
It's exactly as we said.
- We have 1 agent. - 1 agent.
(We have one agent.)
- There are more. - There are B and C.
(Who are the rest?)
- The person they pointed to... - That's right.
(They have So Min as well.)
- I am 100 percent sure. - Me?
- Me? - The other one is...
What are you doing?
(We must get the leader of R Agency on the platform.)
The results are in.
The three people with the most votes will go up the platform.
- Yu Jae Suk. - Okay.
(Yu Jae Suk)
(This is bad.)
- Jun So Min. - It's obvious.
(She always gets caught when she is a spy.)
The last one is...
(It's obvious the agents of M Agency...)
(voted for either Haha or Ji Hyo.)
- Haha. - What?
What? Me?
- Haha? - Haha?
(Right before the final vote)
It's Haha. Haha.
- It's Haha, right? - Yes.
(The 3 agents of M Agency voted for Haha.)
That came out of nowhere.
- M Agency... - That came out of nowhere.
(Ji Hyo avoids the platform.)
Let's check Jae Suk's name tag.
- Okay. - It's under the name tag.
- He has a name tag. - When did he get one?
Let's go. In 1, 2, 3.
(Spy)
- That's good. - I knew you were a spy.
So Min.
I knew...
(Spy)
- So Min. - We won.
- We did it. - We caught two spies.
- Haha shouldn't be the leader. - Haha shouldn't be the leader.
If Haha is the leader, we win.
- If Haha is the leader of R Agency, - That's right.
- M Agency wins. - This is so confusing.
The hints narrowed it down to two people.
(Is their hunch correct?)
An agent of R Agency.
(He isn't the leader of R Agency.)
- We did it. - Our secret is safe.
(The agents' past is safe.)
- We did it. - Is Ji Hyo the leader?
- Ji Hyo is the leader. - Is Ji Hyo the leader?
(I am the leader of R Agency.)
(Leader)
Ji Hyo.
The leader.
- We got you. - Se Chan.
I can't believe it's Ji Hyo.
- You spy! - Se Chan must have been startled.
You were certain Haha is the leader.
I didn't trust Se Chan until the end.
Thus, the victory goes...
to R Agency.
(The victory goes to R Agency.)
(Where are my shoes?)
(Jong Kook's shoes disappear.)
Are Jong Kook's shoes missing?
(Where are my shoes?)
(Jong Kook's shoes disappeared without a trace.)
(Who is the culprit?)
(Strange behaviors are spotted.)
(One of us is the culprit.)
(They narrow down the suspects.)
(It's unwise to touch things that belong to Jong Kook.)
(They close in on the culprit.)
(Running Man desperately tries to escape suspicion.)
(You either get caught...)
(or hide.)
(Let's see how the suspenseful detective game ends.)
(The 3rd part of the Catch Project, Missing Shoes)