- Hello. Hi. Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - My gosh, long time no see.
- Se Chan is all dressed up. - He looks so cool today.
Se Chan's outfit is so cool. Seriously.
- I'm a fashion leader. Hello. - Look at Se Chan.
- Hello, Ji Hyo. - Hi, Ji Hyo.
He doesn't look like himself. He's making me uneasy.
Doesn't he look great? He buttoned up all the way up.
Did someone break up with you? What's wrong with you today?
All right. Have a go at me.
This is how you felt.
(This is what you were feeling.)
You tease me whenever I wear oversized clothes.
Se Chan, you prepared a lot for today's shoot.
Jae Seok, we started on Se Chan.
You look great.
(He doesn't know what to do after wearing the wrong outfit.)
- It started already. - Se Chan, your outfit looks cool.
No, no.
- It's Jong Kook from "Mom's Diary". - It's cold today.
- What? - My gosh, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook is here! - I got here a while ago.
I didn't see you there. You are wearing black.
Someone called me her prince.
She wrote that I'm her prince.
Who called you that?
(His old endearment showed up in an old love letter.)
- Prince! Prince! - Prince! Prince!
- Are you a prince on "Mom's Diary"? - Yes.
- His ex-girlfriend called him that. - He read it in an old letter.
- Really? - I...
Kwang Soo, did you not watch the show?
- I didn't get to watch it. - Shut it.
- I was going to give you a recap. - I didn't get to watch it.
(I see. Kwang Soo didn't watch the show.)
My gosh, Se Chan.
- Yes, Jong Kook? - Prince Jong Kook.
You must've been tired, but thank you for watching the show.
- No, we ought to support the show. - I didn't have time.
- Gosh, I really didn't have time! - Seriously.
- Thank you so much. - Why are you doing this?
- Cut it out. - Thank you.
- You're making me feel bad. - Thank you so much.
- Thank you. - I saw it in the car.
- Thank you. - I watched the show too.
- Right. - I thought that part was funny.
The clip in the attic.
- You didn't watch it. You didn't. - I laughed so much my stomach hurt.
(My gosh, why didn't I watch that show?)
Oh, right. I was on my way here.
I saw a sign, Random Tour, on the bus.
- What? - That was written on the bus.
- Come again? - I saw that.
- "Random Tour"? - Are you sure it was ours?
- Was it our bus? - Out of the blue, at 4am,
my agent called me in a hurry.
- He said I must bring my passport. - That's right. The passport.
- What are we doing? - What is this all about?
- Why did you want us to bring it? - What's this all about?
- Are we going somewhere today? - Are we done with missions?
Am I the only one who didn't bring it?
- You didn't bring it? - You didn't?
I'm not sure.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
Please get yourself together!
- Seok Jin. - No one told me about that.
I'm sure they told you. You just forgot.
No, they didn't. They didn't.
Think carefully.
You already found out.
Today's race is Random Tour Race.
You will divide into three teams and complete the missions.
Someone from the losing team will face the penalty.
- Penalty? - There's a penalty?
I brought two pairs of underpants.
- I prepared myself. - Really?
- You never know what will happen. - To prepare myself, I had to...
bring two pairs of underpants.
- Actually... - I wasn't going to share this,
but I'm always wearing my swimming pants.
(He's always ready.)
Always.
- I need two pairs of underwear. - Just in case.
- Should I wear them too? - Yes.
- You should. - The penalty isn't a water bomb.
- What? - Is it something else?
You will hate this.
You might be the only one going home late today.
(You might go home late today.)
That's the penalty we prepared.
That's the worst.
I'd rather get the water bomb.
Please.
Since the name is Random Tour,
- you'll randomly choose teams. - Okay.
You'll split into three teams.
- Choose one blindfold. - The blindfolds.
- Do we put this on now? - Yes, please.
Why are we wearing blindfolds?
(They'll play a game and divide into teams.)
- At least my eyes are warm. - I can't see anything.
- This is fun. - What should we do now?
With the blindfolds on,
- you will sit down, stand up, - Sit or stand up?
- or lie down on your backs. - In case, we try to peek...
- What? Lie down on our backs? - Lie down?
Who would lie down on this cold ground even if it's for the team?
- Who would lie down? - Do you think so?
- Lying down on our back is weird. - Why would we lie down?
- Who would lie down here? - That'd be so weird.
(Slowly lying down)
The camera crew asked you guys to slightly move back.
- Someone will do that. - My gosh.
Kwang Soo, please move back a bit.
(Rolling)
- I'm sure of it. - I'm going to lie down.
(Bumping)
- I'm going to lie down. - What's this?
- Wait. - What's this?
(Stepping hard)
- There's someone here. - What? What is it?
Hey!
- Kwang Soo is already lying down. - Already?
You can sit down, stand up, or lie down to choose your teams.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(Should I sit? Stand up? No, let's just lie down.)
(I'm going to stay up.)
Three.
(The teams aren't decided as it's 4 to 3 to 1.)
- It's cold. - I didn't choose to lie down.
(He struggles in pain.)
I didn't lie down.
Don't sit down. I'm sitting down.
I'm lying down. Gosh, it's cold.
Choose whether you'll keep your positions or change.
(Should I sit down?)
- It's cold! - Make your final decisions.
1, 2, 3.
(What kind of teams will they form?)
All right.
(The members are divided into 3 to 3 to 2.)
Take off your blindfolds.
(So Min, Jae Seok, and Seok Jin, who stood up, make a team.)
There are people who got down?
- Se Chan. - Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan, who sat down, make a team.)
My gosh, I like this.
- I knew it. - Me too.
- It knew it'd be you. - Jong Kook.
- All right. - All right.
- Did you lie down? - Today won't be pretty.
I wasn't lying down.
Seriously. I didn't choose to lie down.
I was going to sit, but I felt that Jong Kook was sitting down.
Be on my team. You should've sat down.
I was trying my best to avoid teaming up with Jong Kook too.
- My gosh. Seriously. - How is this possible?
- My gosh. - Goodness.
You have divided into three teams randomly.
- You haven't teamed up for a while. - 3 to 3 to 2.
- It's been a while. - It's been so long.
I should give my swimming pants to Seok Jin later.
What would you say that? You should just keep them on.
- I think I'd be okay. - Hey, our team will probably lose.
- You're one to talk. - My teammates...
You know they like to drag each other down, right?
- Of course. - You know?
- I'm already feeling tired. - I'd never go down alone.
You're already acting like this servant.
- I'm carrying out my penalty. - You know...
You shouldn't be biased.
- What do you mean? - Let's travel like we're friends.
Okay. Jong Kook, I'll treat you like my friend.
I'm sorry.
(When you said we could be friends, I went over the line.)
- Let me tell you this. - This is great.
- Se Chan, what's wrong with you? - That's the way to go, Se Chan.
- Keep that up. - We can travel "like" friends.
We won't actually be friends.
Seok Jin, why don't we treat each other like friends?
You jerk.
What?
(Random Tour Race with a group of friends starts.)
Ji Hyo, you...
- You sent me a photo. - What kind of photo?
She sent me a photo of a poster recruiting players for gateball.
Seriously.
- Hey. - It's the sport old people play.
I'm too young to be playing gateball.
I was told that there are a lot of people around your age.
(Ji Hyo is rooting for Seok Jin's new hobby.)
- Random Tour has begun. - Okay.
We're heading to our destination.
First, pick a team name, write it, and submit the paper to us.
I'll write it.
The name of our team will be The Old Man and the Sea.
- "The Old Man and the Sea"? - How about Between Friends?
Hey, who is the old man?
- Who do you think? - This is annoying.
- Take a wild guess. - Seriously.
The Old Man and the Sea.
- My goodness. - The team name...
Yu-So-Body.
"Yu-So-Body"?
- What about my name? - Yu-So-Body.
- You're the Body. - I'm the Body?
- Hey, - Yu-So-Body.
we're going to go with Yu-So-Body.
- Yu-So-Body. - That's a nice name.
- What's your team's name? - Between Friends.
- Between Friends. - Between Friends.
(Between... Between Friends?)
- Are you guys friends? - Of course, we are.
What is this?
Off-the-wall Love Triangle.
(Haha, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo's team is Off-the-wall Love Triangle.)
How does that sound?
Where are we going?
I can't see anything.
It's dark outside.
I can't wait.
Hold on.
Okay.
- What? - What is it?
We are at Incheon International Airport.
(Are we at Incheon International Airport?)
(Random Tour Bus enters Incheon International Airport.)
- For goodness' sake. - We must be going abroad.
- Are we at the airport? - We must be going abroad.
- Did you bring our passports? - Hey.
You should have told us if we were going abroad.
- Where are we going? - Don't suddenly drag us somewhere.
What is going on?
Are we really going abroad?
(Where are the members going?)
Are we really going abroad? I don't have luggage.
If we are going abroad...
Where are we going? Don't we need luggage?
- What is going on? - Are we really going abroad?
What is this?
What is this? Look at this.
- What is that? - "Global Random Tour".
Are we really going abroad?
Jakarta? Are we going to Jakarta?
Wait a minute. Are you out of your mind?
(There are names of cities...)
(and flight numbers written on the board.)
Is this really happening?
- Is this an overnight trip? - What is going on?
I don't have luggage. I have two underwear.
What is going on?
- Are we really going abroad? - Do you have our passports?
I will explain the real mission...
- of today's Random Tour. - What is going on?
This is unbelievable.
The real mission...
is the Global Random Tour with a big penalty on the line,
Departure upon Arrival.
- What? - Departure upon Arrival?
Global Random Tour requires a group of four people.
You must recruit travel mates who will join Random Tour.
As soon as the recruited travel mates arrive,
you can get on the next plane that is boarding.
(Get on the next plane that is boarding.)
- Finish your mission, and return. - Who'd go with us?
- Who would go? - You mean we must recruit people...
who will go on a trip abroad with us?
- That's ridiculous. - At this hour?
Who will suddenly go on a trip abroad?
You have a shoot for Running Man tomorrow as well anyway.
Wait for your guests to arrive,
and get on the next available flight.
Production crew, you are utter jerks.
This is insane.
We excluded flights that are headed to Europe and the States.
Do you see the "unavailable" stickers?
If there are no seats or time for the boarding procedures,
we will put a sticker next to the flight information.
(There are missions available wherever they go.)
(Global Random Tour)
There is a flight to Daegu.
- There is a flight to Daegu. - There is a flight to Busan.
There are domestic flights.
- There are domestic flights. - Busan.
Busan.
- Where is Khabarovsk? - I have no clue.
- Where is Khabarovsk? - Isn't it in Russia?
We don't necessary want our travel mates to arrive quickly.
If the next flight is for Singapore, we will have to fly for six hours.
Whom should I call?
So Min, do you have anyone to call?
- My dad. - Your dad?
Why would you call your dad?
They don't have to be famous, right?
It doesn't matter.
I will call someone who will be easy to travel with.
I will call a younger member.
Please split up and begin.
- Whom should we call? - Whom should we call?
Whom should we call? Hold on.
What can we say at this hour...
- to recruit someone? - What should I do?
What should I do? Hold on.
Call Keun Sik.
- Keun Sik will be available. - Keun Sik?
He would be asleep.
He isn't picking up. He would be asleep at this hour.
I am sure he is asleep.
(He isn't picking up.)
I received a text from Won Yun Jong just now.
- Who is that? - The bobsledder.
(Haha, thank you for narrating the documentary.)
(A bobsledder in the national team, Won Yun Jong)
Tell him to come.
Should I give him a call?
- Is he in Pyeongchang? - He must be in Pyeongchang.
He should rest after the games.
He can rest during the trip.
It will be impossible to rest.
Hold on. Who is available?
I have no one to call.
Hold on. Jong Kook, can I call someone younger?
Do that.
You and I are friends.
That's right.
Call someone younger so that we can be comfortable.
Call someone you can boss around.
How about Byung Jae? Do you know him?
- Who? - Yoo Byung Jae.
I know who he is. He has been on Running Man.
- Really? - Yes.
I will try calling him.
He wouldn't pick up at this hour.
- Hello? - Hello.
Byung Jae, what are you doing?
- I was asleep. - Were you asleep?
- Yes. - You are awake now.
Yes. You called me.
That's right. Hey, listen.
(How can I make him come?)
Have you done something wrong to Jong Kook?
- Who? - Jong Kook.
What do you mean?
Jong Kook talked about you.
Have you worked with Jong Kook?
I have only worked with him on an episode of Running Man.
Did you do something wrong then? Jong Kook talked about you.
I received his number, but...
You never contacted him, right?
No, but I received his number.
Jong Kook hates things like that.
You should come here...
and talk it out with Jong Kook.
We are at Incheon International Airport.
You should bring your passport...
and get rid of bad blood between you and Jong Kook.
You want me to bring my passport?
Yes. Jong Kook...
You want me to bring my passport to make up with Jong Kook.
It's necessary...
because he is worried that you will run away.
He wants to get a hold of your passport.
He has a weird personality.
(My goodness.)
He doesn't have a weird personality,
but he can be hot-headed.
I don't know if he will pick up.
I don't think he will.
Hold on. Hello?
Hello, Jae Seok.
Hey, hey, hey, jerk.
(Is he Heo Kyeong Hwan?)
(Groaning)
- Are you sleeping? - Kyeong Hwan.
- Yes? - What are you doing right now?
(It's 6am.)
What? I should wake up now.
Kyeong Hwan, I am sorry...
for calling so suddenly.
(He suddenly says Kyeong Hwan's popular phrase.)
(He goes along with it.)
- Kyeong Hwan. - Yes?
Don't be surprised. Do you have...
any plans for today?
I will make plans now.
- What did he say? - "I will make plans now."
(We are glad to hear that.)
- That's great. You are free. - Kyeong Hwan.
Kyeong Hwan.
(She suddenly talks to him.)
(Kyeong Hwan.)
Kyeong Hwan. Hello, I am Jeon So Min.
(Kyeong Hwan. Hello, I am Jeon So Min.)
- Hello, So Min. - Hello.
- We have never met. - You have never met.
I should let you meet me.
What?
I should let her meet me.
I am glad to hear that.
- Kyeong Hwan. - Yes?
You said exactly what I wanted to say.
Kyeong Hwan, I am sorry,
but please don't be taken aback.
Can you come to Incheon International Airport?
Where do you live?
- Geumho-dong. - It's close.
It's not too far.
- Kyeong Hwan. - Yes?
I am putting on my pants.
- What are you doing? - He is putting on his pants.
(He is putting on my pants.)
Would it be okay?
- I will go and see. - Okay. Come.
Please bring cup noodles.
Kyeong Hwan, we didn't bring anything.
- Bring snacks. - And cup noodles.
Bring something to munch on.
Something to munch on?
- Something to munch on? - That's right.
Kyeong Hwan, I am sorry to call so suddenly.
Please come quickly.
- I will do that. - I am sorry.
- Is he coming? - We recruited Kyeong Hwan.
I will call...
- Do you know who Shorry is? - Yes, I do.
Shorry is older than me.
(Jong Kook attempts to recruit Shorry of Mighty Mouth.)
Don't worry.
He tells me not to worry.
- All right. - We will get to leave soon.
- Who is coming? - Hello.
Hello.
- Jong Kook. - Shorry.
- Shorry? - It's me, Shorry.
- Where are you? - He is ready.
I am home.
- Are you home? Shorry. - Yes?
Do you have work?
Do I look like I have work?
You don't have any plans for today and tomorrow, right?
Then pick up your passport, and come to Incheon International Airport.
(It's settled.)
Passport?
Yes. Pick up your passport, and come...
- to Incheon International Airport. - You sound like a gangster.
- You sound like a gangster. - Right now?
Yes, right now. Hurry up.
It's so sudden. Okay, Jong Kook.
Throw on whatever, and come.
Just bring your passport.
It will take two days. Just bring your passport.
- Come quickly. - Shouldn't you ask nicely?
- I am hanging up. - Shouldn't you ask nicely?
I don't need to ask nicely.
- Will he come? - Yes.
My friends are like that.
You took a direct approach.
I called someone I could use a direct approach on.
That's Shorry.
Do you want me to make another call?
(You only have to ask.)
They will come right away.
- There will be a group. - They will come right away.
Then we can make them play a game...
and take the winner.
We can do that. Seriously.
What do we do?
(What do we do?)
(Glancing)
Whom should I call?
What do I say?
- How about Sang Yeob? - Let's call someone.
You are so mean.
- Why do you say that? - You are so mean.
"Hello, this is Running Man."
"You were chosen as the number one celebrity..."
- "people want to travel with." - Stop harassing Sang Yeob.
(About 2 months ago,)
(these two tricksters pulled a prank on him.)
(Lee Sang Yeob was directly invited as the best teenage star in 2017.)
(Do you remember him?)
- I can't call him now. - Haha.
These days, he is...
Whom else should I call?
Let's just invite Sang Yeob.
Wait a minute.
I feel bad for Sang Yeob.
Why?
He ranked first as someone whom you'd want to travel with.
- Who else? - But...
I just feel bad.
- Sang Yeob. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, Sang Yeob.
- Hello. - Congratulations.
(They shout.)
- You're on Running Man. - Sang Yeob.
You placed first...
As the most wanted celebrity to travel with...
- in 2018. - In 2018.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, Sang Yeob.
- This is Haha. - This is Kwang Soo.
I'm Ji Hyo.
(Congratulations.)
(He simply laughs.)
- Sang Yeob. - Were you asleep?
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I don't have plans.
- Sang Yeob. - Yes?
You're selected as the most wanted celebrity to travel with.
- We're serious. - It's true this time.
(He keeps laughing.)
It's true, Sang Yeob.
- Sang Yeob. - Are you shooting right now?
- Yes. - Sang Yeob.
We're shooting Running Man.
It's Monday.
- You're selected as the top. - Sang Yeob.
(Sighing)
We can invite...
the second in place, but we wanted to go with the top.
You placed first.
Brad Pitt placed second.
(What did you say?)
No, you placed first.
Gong Yoo placed second.
Wouldn't the broadcasting company prefer Gong Yoo?
No way.
- Sang Yeob. - Yes?
Can you go on a trip with us...
for a day?
When is it?
- Come right now. - Right now.
(Come right now.)
(He bursts out laughing.)
This is what's going on.
You must travel light.
Bring one pair of boxers.
- Okay. - Can you come now?
Where should I go?
- Incheon International Airport. - Incheon International Airport.
Really?
I'll call you when I'm there.
- Okay. - You're amazing.
That's insane.
You know that we're shooting, right?
We're shooting.
- Okay. - All right.
You'll also get paid.
Why would you say that?
It's better to work.
Hurry up, okay?
Okay.
Come quickly.
Then we have more choices.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Sang Yeob is great. - He's...
ambitious about this.
He's ambitious.
(They invite Lee Sang Yeob.)
I want to join this team.
- Who did you invite? - Is Sang Yeob coming?
What are you doing?
- He's coming to meet you. - Who is it?
- It's Kyeong Hwan. - Kyeong Hwan.
Kyung Hwan?
We invited the most special guest.
- Who? - Jong Kook...
- has amazing connections. - Of course.
- Whom did you invite? - This is why I dressed up.
- Who is it? - Is it a woman?
- Really? - Is it a woman?
- Who is coming? - Your belt is loose.
Can you tie it up?
Someone is thinking of you.
- Why? - That's what a loose belt means.
- Really? - I'm glad that you brought it.
If you do something wrong during the trip...
You wink at junk cars.
Why do loose belts mean someone is thinking of you?
- Is it true? - Yes.
A pimple on the forehead means someone likes you.
That's due to hormones.
That's what I heard.
Did what So Min say...
almost make you angry?
Did you see me look at her from head to toe?
I did.
Take a look at the flight times on your right.
- Can you take it off, Kwang Soo? - Yes.
I'm taking off the first column.
(Departure time)
- Is it 7am now? - Yes.
Some already departed.
- These already departed. - Right.
(Some flights are unavailable.)
They departed.
They did.
- The second column is possible. - The second.
It's possible from 9am.
- From 9am... - It's possible from here.
It starts from here.
For your information,
the flight to Kalibo...
that departs at 8am is unavailable. I'll put on the sticker.
That's not possible.
- By the way... - Wait.
This is the problem.
- What is it? - We should tell the staff...
that we aren't going.
Instead, you look at the flight times...
- and discuss where to go. - What else can we do?
- The staff told us to go. - Are you willing not to go?
Let's work together as a team and say,
"How could you do this?"
"How can we go on a trip today?"
You should take initiative...
so that the staff doesn't abuse us.
Can your team take initiative first?
- Right. - Go ahead.
- Say it first. - I already invited Kyeong Hwan.
- What? - You should do it.
We invited people too.
- Do it. - We invited people too.
My goodness.
Since you keep being...
- We'll go anyway. - obedient,
- I'll work hard. - they keep forcing us.
What did you say, So Min?
- You're terrible. - It's best to go somewhere...
as close as possible.
(Where will the three teams go?)
- Shouldn't they invite 1 more? - They're only 2.
Whom did you invite?
They invited Shorry.
Hyo Ri?
Shorry.
(Hyo Ri?)
(No, Shorry.)
I thought it was Hyo Ri.
- I misheard. - It's Shorry.
(Hyo Ri is in Jeju Island.)
- We couldn't have invited Hyo Ri. - It's Shorry.
- I hope he comes soon. - It'll take long to arrive.
I'm worried.
(Nervous)
(The first column is closed.)
(There aren't many places that we can go.)
Will we be able to go?
(Time keeps passing.)
Why isn't he here yet?
Osaka at 8:05am and Tokyo at 8am,
please cross them out.
We're in trouble.
(Their mates can't be reached.)
(No one comes through the entrance.)
How old is she?
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors and the loser buys sandwiches?
The youngest member...
- represents each team. - Let's play.
(So Min volunteers.)
Wait.
- The youngest is Seok Jin. - Really?
(Seok Jin is the youngest.)
- You didn't know. - I'll consider myself...
the youngest today.
Then what's the point of the youngest members playing?
- I'll be younger than Se Chan. - Let's play.
Okay, let's play.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jong Kook wins.)
Okay.
Goodness.
- I knew it. - Of course.
(Did I do well, Se Chan?)
I knew it. Good luck.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo loses.)
Okay.
(I knew it.)
- I expected it. - That's Kwang Soo.
- Let's go. - Go.
- "Let's go"? - Your team suggested it.
Please buy us sandwiches.
I want an egg sandwich.
Didn't I tell you? It would've been better if you went when...
- I told you. - A hot Americano.
- We don't have money. - I can't drink coffee, okay?
- Do you have money? - No.
I don't have money.
How could you?
- The loser pays. - Okay.
We'll go get it.
No, you have to go and buy...
- All right. - as well.
It's understandable.
Is it understandable?
They didn't mention about buying.
- They're right. - Let's determine who pays.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- The loser pays. - Okay.
(Se Chan plays this time.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay. - Good job.
Friends are alike.
Birds of a feather flock together.
- Between Friends. - We're alike.
(We'll definitely win this time.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
(Team Love Triangle loses.)
(What have we done?)
Okay.
You were to lose anyway.
See? If you just went...
- If you just went... - We suggested the game,
but we have to buy and get everything.
Choose one to do it.
- Okay. - That's crazy.
Let's choose one to do it.
Haha, you should just go. You're the oldest.
- Come on, Haha. - Let's play.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha wins.)
Okay!
Kwang Soo will win next.
The oldest member won.
- He won. - He's the oldest.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo loses.)
- Yes! - He lost.
- Go, Kwang Soo. - Did she win?
- Just go, Kwang Soo. - Go.
- Isn't it incredible? - Go, Kwang Soo.
It wasn't even planned.
Kwang Soo is always unlucky.
(He goes reluctantly.)
Shall I come with you?
- Yes. - Just go.
- Go with him. - We'll go with you.
- I want one Americano. - Go.
- I want coffee too. - Kwang Soo.
I want warm milk.
Hey, hurry up and run.
(Jong Kook yells angrily.)
Jong Kook, we're shooting.
Don't use that language.
That's a little rude.
Isn't that an official phrase?
Of course not.
- You should say, "Hurry up." - Don't people say it?
- "Hurry up." - Say it gently.
- Aren't you my friend? - Say, "Hurry up."
I'm pointing it out as a friend.
Shouldn't friends sympathize with each other?
Say please.
(Friends are supposed to sympathize.)
He'll grit his teeth when he asks.
He's already here.
(Someone arrives.)
(Who's the first mate to arrive after a long wait?)
(Which team's partner is it?)
- He's already here. - Come here, you.
- I can't believe it. - Come here.
- You came so late. - Byung Jae.
Hello.
I told you to dress up well.
- Byung Jae. - Yes?
How did you get here?
- He called me. - Put on a microphone.
- Where's the microphone? - Hey.
- How did you get here? - He came so quickly.
(She's jealous of their team.)
- Did Byung Jae arrive? - Yes.
Another mate must arrive...
before you can take a flight.
(Many cities are being eliminated. Shorry must come quickly.)
Do you know that you may have to travel abroad?
No, Se Chan called me.
He said that Jong Kook was angry at me.
(He doesn't know why Jong Kook is angry.)
He said that he'll hurt me.
- I didn't know what was going on. - I was really angry.
I didn't do anything wrong.
- Give me your passport. - What did you do?
Why are you angry at me?
Give me your passport.
You're in trouble, Byung Jae.
In case you flee out of the country, I'll take your passport.
- What is this? - It's almost over.
I'm not close to Se Chan either.
I'm serious.
- Byung Jae. - I saw him twice.
Did you meet Se Chan through Sae Ho?
- Yes. - I knew it.
He's close to Se Hyeong and Sae Ho.
- Goodness. - We're like family.
That's right.
- We're family. - Explain to Byung Jae.
Please. What's going on?
Look over there.
Let me explain briefly. We found out only today too.
As soon as we form a team of four, we can leave.
We're going abroad.
- We have a mission. - Are you free tomorrow too?
- Luckily, yes. - We're taking you on a trip.
Shouldn't you be happy about it?
I am, but you look so scary.
(You look so scary.)
- You look scary. - You should be happy.
"Shouldn't you be happy?"
- Don't you feel bad? - He should.
He should thank us.
- Thank you. - There you go.
- We're going to shoot abroad. - Exactly.
(They're going abroad.)
Do you think he turned the boiler off?
- Did you turn off the boiler? - Did you turn it off?
The boiler? Why would you ask that?
- I turned it off. - "Why would you ask that?"
- I turned it off. - Byung Jae.
You're wearing new shoes.
They can't go to Hanoi, Manila, or Nagoya now.
This is not okay.
There are fewer and fewer places we can go to.
(The earliest flight is for Busan.)
If Shorry shows up soon,
you'll go to Busan.
- We can go to Busan? - That'd be nice.
- Busan would be nice. - It'd be great.
I want to go to Busan.
Try calling Kyeong Hwan. I want to take the 9am flight to Fukuoka.
- He just woke up. - What about this one?
- Fukuoka at 9am. - We could go to Osaka.
We really shouldn't, but we're starting to pressure them.
- We should. - He won't pick up his phone.
- He wasn't supposed to come. - We shouldn't feel bad.
I told him to hurry.
I thought he'd be here soon.
(Soon, they won't be able to go to Busan.)
I want to go to Busan.
That's Byung Jae.
- He's already here? - Hi.
- Byung Jae. - Hi.
He really came.
- You came so fast. - I did.
You didn't get any coffee?
- Thank you. - You didn't?
- Look. - Yes?
- Didn't I ask for a sandwich? - There were no sandwiches.
It'd take too long.
Didn't you get any drinks?
- Milk. - Banana-flavored milk.
(If it's Shorry, Between Friends can leave.)
(If it's Kyeong Hwan, Yu-So-Body can leave.)
(If it's Sang Yeob, Love Triangle can leave.)
We bought one for each person.
Before... Sang Yeob!
- Sang Yeob! - You're here!
(Sang Yeob is here.)
- Sang Yeob! - Sang Yeob!
(Thank you, Sang Yeob!)
- He came! - Sang Yeob.
Sang Yeob.
Kyeong Hwan will come last.
- We're leaving second. - Sang Yeob.
- I can't believe this. - Hi.
(Love Triangle can leave for Busan now.)
Sang Yeob is here.
- You're leaving for Busan, right? - Yes.
Please explain to Sang Yeob on your way.
We don't have much time. Please leave now.
We have to say goodbye to Sang Yeob already?
Should I shout, "Eon Nyeon"? It's been a while.
Eon Nyeon!
What are you doing now?
- You just arrived. - Did you drink last night?
We didn't ask you to do it.
Hyuk didn't seem to like it.
(Hyuk didn't seem to like it.)
- He felt a bit offended. - I saw it.
Please talk to him.
- I'll talk to him personally. - You should.
Arrange something.
- I'll arrange something. - Settle it.
- I'll do something about it. - Do it.
We'll do what we can so that you can keep doing it.
- Don't worry. - What are you talking about?
- What do you mean? - I was overzealous.
Okay.
Let's go. Are we really going?
- Let's go. - What should I do?
- Bye. - See you.
See you.
Bye.
We're already leaving?
This happens all the time. They told us about it...
only this morning.
Really?
Are they going to Busan?
- Yes. - They're so lucky.
Where is Shorry, by the way?
I'm jealous.
- Why? - They're going to Busan.
We're so lucky to go to Busan.
I'll pay for everything.
Are you going to take us to your restaurant?
Yes.
(There are many other things to do than visiting Haha's restaurant.)
Unbelievable.
I love it. It'd be so easy.
It'd be so easy. I'm so happy.
Random Tour starts now.
But as I told you, the losing team will face a severe penalty.
Let me explain how we'll determine the losing team.
During the tour,
each of you will carry a step counter.
(Each of you will carry a step counter.)
The team with the highest combined count...
will lose.
The member with the highest count in that team...
will choose one person...
and be penalized together.
The member with the lowest count in each team will be...
exempted from the penalty.
You'll put on the step counters now.
(They put on the step counters.)
- That's the rule. - Why...
- Why... - This...
So you should try not to walk a lot?
That's right. We have to compete within the team too.
We have to compete.
Guests can be penalized too.
Penalty...
- It can be very bad. - You're a team.
(You're not exempted just because you're a guest.)
Really?
Where is your step counter?
- What? - Where is your step counter?
- Where is your step counter? - Here.
(Pushing)
Gosh.
(I better stay alert.)
We should try not to move.
- We should. - Is that how step counters work?
All domestic flights that leave from this airport are transit flights.
You can't get on a flight for Busan here.
(You can't get on a flight for Busan here.)
You have two options.
Either take a flight from Gimpo International Airport instead,
or take a ferry or KTX from here.
Which would you like to choose?
Well...
(We have to choose between the two options?)
Please make a decision.
My goodness.
- Why don't we... - Busan...
take a bus from here?
You want to sleep on the bus, right?
(Ji Hyo likes to sleep.)
- I mean... - It'll take too long.
- The fastest way is by plane. - Right.
- We should do that. - We're in Incheon now.
- Do you want to go to Gimpo? - Yes.
Then please leave for Gimpo International Airport.
- Okay. - Okay.
(They take a bus to Gimpo International Airport.)
Our steps must be getting counted even on our way to the airport.
I'll try to walk slowly.
Don't try to shake another person's hand like this.
(Haha is playing with the innocent guest.)
The number is going up.
- Exactly. Don't do it. - It is going up.
Sang Yeob, thank you.
- Stop it. The number is going up. - Thank you.
(It keeps going up.)
- Sang Yeob. - Hold on.
In 2018,
- Sang Yeob will... - The number is going up.
The number-one star...
- to go on a trip with. - Number-one!
The number went up by 10 because of you.
It's 224 now.
I feel so relaxed.
Looking at you makes me relaxed.
What should I do?
Should we play a game?
We have nothing to do anyway.
The winner can take the loser's step counter for 10 seconds.
- 10 seconds? - The loser's step counter?
The winner can just hold it.
Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Okay.
The loser gives his step counter to the winner, right?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Hey.
(Kwang Soo takes Sang Yeob's step counter.)
- 10 seconds. - Please be nice.
There's no reason to shake it hard.
It'd make the team's count go up as well.
- That's right. - Exactly. That'd be stupid.
The result will be bad.
Let me count 10 seconds.
Ready.
(Will Kwang Soo just hold still for his team to win?)
Start.
(Shaking)
Hey.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me for 10 seconds.
We're a team.
Stop.
Why did you shake it?
- What? - Why did you shake it?
Because then, I can relax.
- Still... - I won't be the loser.
We're a team.
If I do this...
I think this game is fun.
What's your count?
332.
332?
It went up by 40 because of you.
You're so mean. Why did you do that?
Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob should play it again.
I'm scared of Kwang Soo.
- I can't believe you. - What?
Don't fall for Haha's trick.
What are you talking about?
Don't fall for it.
I'm already so behind.
- Why don't the three of us play it? - Sure.
- Guys only. - The three of us.
- The three of us? - Yes.
- Okay. - Okay.
- The winner... - For 10 seconds.
- 10 seconds. - If you shake it, it's war.
- I want to play too. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins again.)
- Okay. - It's Kwang Soo again.
Let's not do it.
- Let's not do it. - Just don't lose.
If you don't lose, you can get ahead.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Sang Yeob loses again.)
- I lost again. - Sang Yeob.
- Sang Yeob. - It's 335 now.
10 seconds.
- Are you going to... - Ready.
- Seriously. - Start.
(Are you going to shake it again?)
Of course.
I can't believe him.
(It must be his instinct.)
Think about the team.
- 3, 2, 1. - Stop.
It was 332.
It's up by 30 now.
- Let's compare. - My goodness.
(They compare their counts.)
Show us.
(Haha 40, Sang Yeob 395, Ji Hyo 47, Kwang Soo 119)
Mine is 40... It's going up.
It's going up even right now.
There must be a weight inside.
- Show it to this camera. - It goes up so fast.
- Show it to this camera. - That camera?
(Show it to this camera.)
Wait, no, no!
(Never lower your guard.)
Sang Yeob.
Now, I get how it is.
(This team is full of enemies.)
I get it now. I get it.
You were supposed to show it to this camera.
I got it. I got it.
I think I completely get what kind of team this is on the bus.
It's like I'm in the Serengeti with this team.
(Can Sang Yeob survive in this team?)
We're done with our friendship game.
They said to hurry.
(Domestic Terminal at Gimpo Airport)
Really?
Everyone looks silly.
(Waddling)
(Everyone walks like there's a bucket of water on their heads.)
(They glide through to the gate, bound to Gimhae Airport.)
(Flight bound for Gimhae Airport)
Let's not sabotage each other.
We should get some sleep now.
(Stealing a glance)
(Sleeping)
(Where is his step counter?)
(I caught you acting suspiciously.)
(It's embarrassing to watch him.)
I saw your eyes.
(I saw your eyes.)
Sang Yeob, you get it now, right?
(This was another chance for him to learn more about the team.)
Walk carefully. You must walk carefully.
- It's cold. - The weather is perfect.
Seriously. The weather is great.
(Midwinter sunshine welcomes Team Love Triangle.)
I'm sure we are the first ones to arrive at the destination.
- That's right. - Right?
That's for certain.
But we are so loyal.
For an hour on the flight here,
no one tried to pull any tricks.
There wasn't a single incident.
With this flight,
we proved to the public that we are a family.
Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- Thank you, Sang Yeob. - Seriously.
Thank you, Haha.
I didn't even think about doing that.
But I didn't feel comfortable,
so I hid mine and slept.
You...
- That's why Sang Yeob... - He hid it in the pillow.
- On our way here... - You hurt my feelings.
- He couldn't trust me. - That was funny.
(Sang Yeob is getting to know them.)
I guess we're doing something here.
What? What is it? Do you see something?
- What is that? A globe? - Is that a globe?
- No way. Could it be... - What is this?
"Island, fishing, apartment in Busan, sea, and boat".
- What's that? - All right.
(Five mysterious keywords which seem relevant to Busan)
(What is the mission Team Love Triangle will try?)
Everyone, on the globe,
keywords related to your mission are written.
- We'll go to an apartment in Busan. - That's the best one.
One of your teammates will spin the globe,
and the keyword, chosen within three seconds,
will be the mission you will have to accomplish today.
(The keyword will be picked randomly.)
(They must spin the globe to choose a keyword for their mission.)
(Fishing, sea, boat, island, and apartment in Busan)
Hold on, if there's an island,
- Where would we go? - it must be Jeju Island.
(I have a hunch.)
- We can go to Jeju from Busan. - That's a possibility.
(You want us to go to Jeju Island again?)
- Let's get the apartment in Busan. - Yes, let's go with that.
- Where is that keyword? - We must pick that one.
Practice. Let's practice.
(They'll practice first.)
- My gosh. - No.
(Welcome to Jeju!)
- No, no. No island. - Hey.
You will never pick the destination.
Ji Hyo, we should do a practice run.
It's a practice round.
"Fishing".
(Even Ji Hyo picks fishing.)
- "Fishing". - Why did you use that finger?
You should try too.
Hey, don't criticize me for using my finger.
All right. Everyone,
please pick the member who will pick the keyword.
- All of us should try. - Right now,
Sang Yeob's number is the highest.
- Right. - He's the last among us.
I think he's probably the last in this world.
- Given his number... - That's true.
- Why don't you spin it? Yes. - Me?
- I don't get lucky often. - Hey.
Sang Yeob should do it.
- Yes, he should do it. - I'm really bad at this.
- Say, "Start," when ready. - We won't blame you.
- You should do it. - Okay.
- We're going to do it now, right? - 1, 2, 3.
- Start. - Start.
I'll spin it first. Then you can spin it.
I'll spin it.
What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
(Did Kwang Soo point at boat?)
(When he sneakily gives it a try and picks boat,)
(he pretends to give a spin.)
Hold on. I was supposed to do it. I had to pick the place. Wait.
- Sang Yeob was supposed to do it. - Right.
- That's right. - I was spinning it too.
Is that so? Were you spinning it well?
- Okay. - I did it.
- Apartment in Busan. - We got it.
(I have chosen the apartment in Busan.)
- We said start before we did it. - Okay.
- We did it by the book. - This was perfect.
- You can't find fault here. - Right.
Say start,
- and do it again. - Pick the member.
- Who's going to do it? - Is Kwang Soo going to do it?
- Who's going to do it? - Sang Yeob should do it.
- Okay. I'll do it. - Sang Yeob will try then.
- He will point at the keyword. - Okay.
Say, "start," before you begin.
1, 2, 3.
- Start. - Start.
Here he goes.
- You're trying it now. - Yes.
(Which mission will Sang Yeob choose for the team?)
(No way! It's the apartment in Busan.)
- Apartment in Busan! - Yes!
- Apartment in Busan! - We did it.
- We got it! - Apartment!
- All right. - This is great.
Let me tell you today's mission.
- You chose the apartment in Busan. - Yes.
You can head to an observatory in Daema Island from where...
you can see an apartment in Busan.
(Head to an observatory from where you can see an apartment in Busan.)
You can head to Daema Island.
(Excuse me?)
What... What did you say?
- Explain it again. - Again.
Let me repeat your mission for today.
You can head to an observatory in Daema Island from where...
you can see an apartment in Busan.
Will we really be able to see it from the observatory?
What was the mission for the keyword, sea?
- The sea? - Go to the sea in Daema Island.
You can cross the sea and go to Daema Island which is the closest...
foreign country from Busan.
- What about the boat? - My gosh.
There are a lot of boats in Busan as it's a harbor city.
You can take a ferry and go...
to Daema Island which has the closest foreign harbor from Busan.
So right now,
we did everything we could to choose the apartment in Busan.
(Feeling dejected)
I mean...
- Our fate was already decided. - Didn't I tell you?
I didn't even think about Daema Island.
- Right? - I mean...
If you put Daema Island from the start instead of Busan,
we wouldn't have felt annoyed like we are now.
It's Random Tour.
Random, my foot.
Okay. Then tell me this.
Is Daema Island our final destination?
Or is there more?
That's our final destination.
It is, right? If you change your word, you're dead meat.
- Otherwise, tell me now. - Daema Island is our destination.
Everyone is on edge because of the step counter.
See? I knew this would happen.
It was just too easy. Busan would've been too easy.
(He shakes Sang Yeob's step counter.)
That's not the right pocket.
(My step counter isn't there.)
Where is it? Where did it go?
- Where did it go? - I don't have it there.
(When did you hide your step counter?)
- Where is it? - I don't have it there.
It's right here.
- He fooled me. - My gosh, he's good at this.
- He got me. - You are one of us now.
You got that down on the flight from Seoul to Busan.
After seeing Kwang Soo's eyes earlier,
the sense of warning surged through me.
I'm getting irritated.
- Let's get going then. - Let's go.
I've never been to Daema Island.
Hey, give Kyeong Hwan a call.
Seok Jin.
Kyeong Hwan only woke up an hour ago. Stop nagging.
He lives far from here too.
- Thank you, Byung Jae. - Don't mention it.
We'll go with Jong Kook and Shorry.
- We'll have fun, Byung Jae. - We'll put stickers...
We'll put stickers...
from Busan to Hong Kong.
Gosh, we're in trouble.
Shorry is causing us trouble. Are you sure?
Kyeong Hwan isn't coming either.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
If Shorry comes now,
you'll go to Bangkok.
Please. What happened to Shorry?
Can't we give him a call?
(He has to come at the right timing.)
Seriously.
- Osaka is better. - I'd like to visit there.
- Osaka or Hong Kong. - I've never been there.
Yes, Jong Kook?
Hey, you. What time is it now?
I'm almost there, Jong Kook.
- Hurry, Shorry. - Okay. I'm almost there.
- You'd better come... - I can see you now.
(No way. You can see us?)
- You can see us? - He said he can see us.
Then he can't come in yet.
If he comes now, it's Bangkok.
(Bangkok)
(If he comes now,)
Jong Kook, Shorry is here.
(If he comes now, they must go to Bangkok, and Shorry shows up.)
How could you come now?
- Shorry is here. - There's Shorry.
- It's Bangkok. - You'll go to Bangkok.
- Put on the microphone first. - It's Bangkok.
- My gosh, Shorry. - It's Bangkok.
(Team Between Friends is set to leave for Bangkok.)
(Why am I putting on this microphone? I'm confused.)
First off, put on the microphone, and get over here.
Yes, sir.
(He sounds disciplined.)
Is he in the military?
Are we in the military now?
My gosh, he's so disciplined.
Hey, what's your relationship with him?
He's like my family.
- He sounds like a soldier. - Come here, Shorry.
- Welcome. Come this way. - Hello.
- What is that? - Hello.
- Shorry. - I'm sorry, sir.
(He kneels down right away.)
- What are you doing? - What is this?
- What's going on? - What's going on between you two?
- Why are you kneeling down? - You...
Do you know how fast Byung Jae got here?
- I'm sorry. - You embarrassed me.
- The traffic was bad. - I called you here.
- You're making me look bad. - I can understand that. Why...
- Shorry. - Please get up.
Why are you sorry? Jong Kook is the one who should be sorry.
I'm always a sinner.
(In the eyes of Jong Kook, I am.)
Why are you a sinner?
We have to go to Bangkok because he just came in?
Since we don't have much time,
Team Between Friends will leave for Bangkok now.
My goodness. They're going to go to Bangkok?
- I'm going to Bangkok? - It's because of you.
Shorry is still dazed. How can he leave now?
Had you come a bit earlier,
we could've gone somewhere close like Sendai or Hong Kong.
- Byung Jae came in the morning. - You're going to Bangkok.
But could you go to Bangkok in that outfit?
I'm still half-asleep, but I'm going to Bangkok?
You'll be so hot there.
- Have a good trip. - Bye.
(Bye)
- Byung Jae. - Yes?
Tell you what.
The theme of our trip is a trip with friends.
- But you don't look friendly. - Hey.
- Be comfortable. - You can relax.
- Let's get going first. - Jong Kook, let's be simple.
Keep it simple. Let's go.
- We're leaving now? - Yes. Let's go.
Look at him walking. He looks like a thug.
Let's go.
That team is hilarious.
- Tell him to hurry. Seriously. - It's driving me crazy.
Everyone else is gone.
(We miss you, Kyeong Hwan.)
He's driving me crazy.
What's left?
They're being eliminated.
Each of you get a step counter.
The team with the highest sum of steps loses.
In the losing team,
the member with the most steps...
is the ultimate loser.
That member chooses another member to be penalized with.
The member with the least number of steps...
from each team will be excluded from the penalty.
The least number of steps?
It's best not to move.
We're going to Bangkok.
Let's go, Shorry.
- Okay. - Move as carefully as possible.
Right, let's go slowly.
Take wide steps, okay?
Is that better?
- Yes. - We can reduce the steps.
Right.
Let's take the escalator.
(They get lucky.)
Come on, guys.
To reduce the number of steps,
we must use moving walkways.
It may be frustrating,
but let's reduce our walking as much as possible.
Why don't you film yourself?
(They don't listen to Jong Kook's nagging.)
(He smiles big.)
I was at home, and I was...
startled by your call.
- Then go back home. - No, it's okay.
We'll have a great time. We'll make memories.
Take wide steps.
Okay, I am.
We'd like to go to Bangkok.
Do you have tickets for four?
Yes.
- Great. - There are available seats.
Are there?
Please give us good seats.
There are two separate pairs of seats.
(There are only two separate pairs.)
(Two separate pairs means...)
Do you mean two each?
(Someone has to sit with Jong Kook.)
Mr. Kim Jong Kook and...
(Who will sit next to Jong Kook and listen to him nag?)
Shorry.
(Shorry is selected.)
Can I sit separately?
May I switch seats?
I want to sit next to Jong Kook.
- Are you traveling together? - Me too.
- Move, Shorry. - Why?
- What are you doing? - I'll sit next to him.
Let me sit next to Jong Kook.
I want to sit with him. What are you doing?
- The tickets are... - We can't change, can we?
(Come here, my brother.)
What you did was very natural.
- I was being honest. - Seriously.
Byung Jae doesn't talk much.
- Be comfortable, Byung Jae. - Okay.
How do you feel when you travel with friends?
Traveling with friends is exciting.
Right?
You should be excited now.
- Right, I'm excited. - Show us.
- I'm very excited, Jong Kook. - Good.
Talk more, okay?
- Promise me. - Okay.
- Okay. - Promise.
- I'll keep watching you. - Okay.
All right.
Let's go on a tour with friends.
- Shall we say, "Between Friends"? - Okay.
Between Friends.
- Team... - Between Friends.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
- That's great. - Start.
- Team... - Between Friends.
- Did you say anything? - I did.
- Say it louder. - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Stand next to Jong Kook.
- No, I'll stay here. - Come.
We don't have time.
- Get closer to him. - We're trying to have fun.
Don't act like you're being forced. Otherwise, we can't air it.
We should do well...
- in one go. - Make it clear.
Okay.
- Team Between Friends. - All right.
- Let's do it. - Get ready.
- Team... - Between Friends.
Byung Jae.
It's Team Between Friends.
- That's right. - I did that.
Your words overlapped mine.
- I'm sorry. - Ready, set, go.
- Team... - Between Friends.
- That wasn't bad. - Good job.
That wasn't bad.
It was good enough to go.
Give me a hug too.
Let's go.
- We're friends - It's this way.
(Se Chan and Byung Jae get on the flight together.)
(He doesn't look happy.)
(He acts cautiously.)
(Byung Jae was quite nervous,)
(but he falls asleep immediately.)
Byung Jae.
(Is Byung Jae sleeping?)
(What's this?)
(It's Byung Jae's step counter.)
Byung Jae fell asleep.
(He prepares a surprise for his sleeping friend.)
It's Byung Jae's.
(He'll be surprised when he wakes up.)
Wake up, Byung Jae.
(After Byung Jae's, he goes after the other members'.)
Where are their step counters?
(He's flustered.)
I couldn't find them.
(He gives up finding them.)
Byung Jae disappeared.
(In that case,)
(he shakes his step counter again.)
Shake it when Byung Jae isn't here.
(He gets caught.)
There you are.
Take good care of it.
(He's surprised by the count.)
Why did you leave it here?
(He learns the new meaning of friends.)
Always keep it on you.
(They finally arrive in Thailand.)
(It's where modernity and traditions coexist.)
(People live with nature.)
(It's a rich place.)
(Welcome to Thailand.)
I can't believe that we're in Bangkok.
I'm so happy right now.
Can I brag to my friends that I have new friends?
We're friends because we were...
- born in the Year of Dragon. - Right.
Really?
- Se Chan. - You're friends.
It's good to see you.
(He pinches him.)
Come here.
(He pinches Jong Kook.)
What are you doing to Jong Kook?
Even I haven't touched his cheeks.
I detest it when someone grabs my cheeks.
(The gang leader and his friends)
Didn't I tell you?
We shouldn't do what each other doesn't like.
He's getting to know you, so forgive him.
(The others are simply happy.)
We're friends.
(They're still friends.)
- Are you excited? - Yes.
(They're excited anyway.)
It's been a long time since I went on a trip with friends.
There's a crowd.
- Where? - They came to see Byung Jae.
- Where? - Seriously.
Special effects make them wave.
They were probably notified.
Is it possible that no one is here?
It's my first time here.
- Really? - It's my first time in Bangkok.
- It's your first time? - Yes.
Guys.
Look at the weather.
We're in Bangkok.
It's hot.
Isn't it hot? Let's turn around.
(Let's turn, everybody.)
(Mom, I'm in Bangkok.)
(I'm with great friends.)
(I'm so happy.)
Hey, friends
I will never forget you
Let's go. It's hot.
(The current temperature is 35°C.)
This is great!
(They're dressed up for 5°C below zero.)
(They're sweating.)
It's been a long time.
The weather is beautiful.
(What mission will be given in Thailand?)
- Are you hot? - Yes.
Welcome to Random Tour in Thailand.
The random mission in Thailand is called...
Thailand's Specialty Tour.
Each of you will spin the globe...
and choose a mission.
A drawing competition with an elephant.
Meet a Thai celebrity...
and give them a small gift.
Another mission is taking a group photo by the sunset.
Another is eating snacks at a night market.
After clearing all missions,
you may return to Korea.
(The number of missions may be 1 to 4.)
- And... - Do we spin it first?
If you fail to clear a mission,
1,000 steps will be added to your step counter.
- 1,000 steps? - That's a lot.
Divide the number amongst yourselves.
"Meet a Thai Celebrity".
"Eat Snacks at a Night Market".
(Overlapping missions reduces the number of missions.)
- Let's spin it first. - Okay.
I'll spin it first.
Here we go.
(What will be their first mission in Thailand?)
"Eat Snacks at a Night Market".
- That's good. - We get snacks.
Did I do well? Compliment me.
Good job.
Good job, Jong Kook.
- Good job. - Great job, Jong Kook.
I'll spin it next.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
1, 2, 3.
(It's best to overlap.)
(He gets "Drawing Competition with an Elephant".)
- With an elephant? - It's not bad.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Next is Byung Jae. - Okay.
I can't believe how it's working out perfectly.
(Byung Jae selects...)
"Meet a Thai Celebrity".
- Let's go. - Okay.
We have Shorry left.
(His has to overlap.)
Do it.
(The globe drops.)
(He drops the globe.)
(He even steps on Jong Kook's foot.)
- Hey. - It's okay. Let's laugh.
Let's laugh.
It's nothing to cry about.
- Let's laugh. - I'm sorry.
Let him go. Friends must fight sometimes.
Why didn't you spin it more gently?
Go back home.
It's my first time on Running Man.
(It's my first time on the show.)
Spin it slowly.
(Shorry tries again.)
Select well.
(They may have to do all 4 missions.)
- We'll do this. - Okay.
None of them sound difficult.
Is it okay if we finish too early?
- It's okay? - Let's hurry.
- Let's go. - Let's hurry.
- Shall we? - Let's go.
(However,)
(they had no idea about the secret behind the mission.)
We're the only ones left.
- Everyone else has left. - Let's sit down.
We reached Kyeong Hwan first.
He got the call first.
My goodness. Where could he be?
What is taking him so long?
For Hong Kong,
Taipei, Sapporo, and Fukuoka, there are no seats left.
Tickets are being sold out.
- We can't go anywhere. - What should we do?
All flights on this board are fully booked.
- What should we do? - What are we doing...
Please bring the next board.
(Please bring the next board.)
There's another board?
They keep changing the board.
- My goodness. - They're scary.
- Running Man is scary. - Our staff is scary.
(The afternoon schedule is ready too.)
(Worried)
Many of the flights are already fully booked.
Flights that leave around noon. What time is it now?
- They're afternoon flights. - We can go to Hong Kong.
(The earliest flight leaves for Hong Kong at 1:45pm.)
Why did you tell us to come here by 5am?
(They're spending hours at the airport.)
They're putting more stickers on the board.
There are not many flights we can take.
- Busan... - We've lost Busan.
- It's fully booked. - We've lost it.
- Osaka... - It's Okinawa again.
- It's Okinawa again. At 2:35pm. - It's Okinawa again.
(Restless and anxious)
We've been waiting for so long.
I'll teach Kyeong Hwan a lesson when he comes.
If we fail to go to Okinawa, it'll be Kagoshima?
I've never been there.
He's here.
- Kyeong Hwan is here. - Is he here?
It's not him? It is. He's wearing sunglasses.
Look at him. My goodness.
Why is he running?
I'm sorry.
- You brat. - You brat.
(Why are you so late?)
- Kyeong Hwan. - Hi.
Where are the others?
They've already left. You took so long.
- They've already left. - Seok Jin.
- What? - Kyeong Hwan got the call...
and came here. We should thank him.
- Still... - I came like this.
There's a flight at 2:35pm.
- It's for Okinawa. - It's for Okinawa.
Team Yu-So-Body will take the 2:35pm flight...
for Okinawa.
- What should we do until then? - 2:35pm?
- You should have come early. - I'm sorry.
- I didn't know. - Gosh.
Our team should win.
- Of course. - So we shouldn't...
- Guys. - Let me check if yours is working.
Hey.
(Seok Jin steals So Min's step counter.)
- Seok Jin. - Gosh.
- Come on. - Let me check...
(Let me check yours too.)
Hold him, So Min.
(Jae Seok runs away with Seok Jin's step counter.)
Stop.
- Your count is going up too. - Right.
I forgot about mine.
Yours is going up too.
(There is no point.)
Give it back!
(The team count is going up.)
(They're leaving for Okinawa.)
We're moving too much.
There's some time left until the flight.
It's about 20°C in Okinawa.
Get something to eat, or buy some summer clothes.
- You can do whatever you want. - Hold on.
We have to buy clothes?
I don't have my wallet.
From the morning...
We could go home and come back.
(The flight doesn't take off until 2:35pm.)
- Go home then. - We could do that.
We could even open a bank account while waiting.
Be quiet.
Be quiet, Kyeong Hwan.
- Let's get something to eat. - Let's eat first.
- Let's eat. - We shouldn't walk a lot.
We shouldn't walk.
The count goes up every time I breathe.
We can walk like this.
(Careful)
Like a sloth.
We're going on a trip, and we can't even walk?
This is too much.
We have to wait for two hours. It's your fault for coming late.
I didn't know.
(8 hours later)
(They arrive in Okinawa 13 hours after they started shooting.)
(The weather is nice.)
It's not as hot as I expected.
- It's cool. - It is.
It's very cool.
I love it.
(Warm weather all year around)
(Okinawa is the Hawaii of Asia.)
It's already 6pm...
here in Okinawa.
Hold on. We haven't done anything yet.
Kyeong Hwan hasn't done anything yet.
We haven't done anything yet.
- We haven't filmed anything yet. - My step counter says...
3,610.
- We haven't done anything yet. - Mine says...
Wait. Mine is weird.
It says 4,666.
Have you been somewhere?
(He has already taken more than 4,000 steps.)
We sat in massage chairs at the airport.
- Right. - We didn't think about it.
The count went up by 1,000.
It reached 1,000 while I was sitting in the massage chair.
I didn't sit in the massage chair, so mine is around 2,000.
- Mine has doubled. - 4,690...
Now that you're in Okinawa, let me announce your mission.
Japan is famous for delicious food.
Please come to an agreement...
on what food you want to eat here.
You can search on the internet about some food in Okinawa.
- Okinawa... - Could it be...
- Guys. - What would you like to eat?
- Me? - Yes.
I want meat.
- Meat? - Wagyu.
Either Wagyu or sushi.
Here it says steak.
- What? - It says steak.
- Steak? - Steak.
- We should eat it. - Should we eat that?
Soba.
- Soba. - Let's eat that.
- What do you think? - Soba?
We should have meat.
- We just arrived. - Let's come to an agreement.
This looks tasty.
These cookies are made with a special kind of salt.
- Don't they look tasty? - Look at that.
Why would you have cookies instead of a meal?
- Gosh, we're such a bad match. - Hold on.
Let's have a meal.
- He thinks we're a bad match. - We are.
I'm hungry. It's 6pm.
Hold on. Producer Jung.
- Yes? - Each of us wants different things.
- It's 6:10pm. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
It's 6:10pm. It's time for dinner.
Why would you eat cookies?
It's just that...
we're craving something sweet.
Okinawa is famous for steak.
(Let's just have meat.)
Like I said,
why don't we have steak?
I've been saying that the whole time.
You said you wanted seafood.
I said I wanted steak this morning.
(I can't believe these guys.)
Let's go.
- What do you say? - Sounds good.
Let's have steak then. 1, 2, 3.
- Steak. - Steak.
Then you can...
- go have steak now. - Can we go?
Once you complete the mission, you can go home.
- Really? - Then...
our step count won't be that high.
- If we finish early. - Okay.
(Once they complete the mission, the step counter will stop.)
- Okay. - But you can't leave right away.
Here.
- What's that? - What are we supposed to do?
(Globe)
"Someone over 90", "a taxi driver",
- "someone called Suzuki"... - "Someone called Suzuki".
(What is this?)
- What are we supposed to do? - You have to go to...
a restaurant a local recommends.
(A restaurant recommended by a local)
You have to find a local...
who recommends a steak place.
You have to succeed before going back to Korea.
You have a little time.
If you fail, your step count will go up by 1,000.
(1,000 steps as a penalty)
1,000 steps? A taxi driver would be easy to find.
A convenience store clerk is okay too.
Let's say a local you found...
recommends a sushi place.
Then you have to eat sushi before trying again.
(They have to eat that dish before trying again.)
I'm full.
If they don't recommend a steak place?
Keep trying until someone recommends steak.
- Steak is a hard one. - People don't usually...
That's why he didn't stop us when we were eating.
Why didn't you stop us?
Why didn't you tell us that we were going to eat later?
Why...
I'm going to start farting.
(I'm too full.)
We're in trouble.
The only things So Min have been doing all day were...
(Sleeping)
And then...
(Eating)
(Having a snack)
(Taking a nap)
(Having a meal)
(Taking another nap)
(I'm about to fart.)
I visited Okinawa...
- three years ago... - We get it.
- with my family. - I know that.
But you were stuck in the hotel the whole time.
What?
- I was stuck in the hotel? - You were.
My family was stuck in the hotel?
I just feel sorry.
- Have you been here before? - It's my first.
I've been here,
- so follow me. - Okay.
He's been...
everywhere.
- He knows nothing. - Can you speak Japanese?
(A little)
- I mean... - A little?
(Seok Jin can speak a little.)
(I can speak a little too.)
She sounds Japanese.
It's a line from a drama, right?
- Is it a line from a drama? - What does it mean?
"Thank you for introducing a delicious dish to me."
That might be useful.
I can't believe this.
Last time, all she could say was,
"Excuse me,"
and "thank you."
(She could only say those two.)
(Excuse me.)
(Thank you.)
She's like that.
She can't speak Japanese.
We have to choose one person.
- Let's turn it. - For us...
Decide who will do it.
- Kyeong Hwan. - Me?
Let me try first.
- Don't. - Why not?
- Try it. - This is just practice.
- It's practice. - It's practice.
A convenience store clerk...
(Seok Jin picked "Someone called Suzuki".)
- See? - It's hard.
We should avoid "someone called Suzuki".
- It'd be the hardest. - We'll have to...
- try many times. - Why did I pick that?
Let me practice.
Do you know what's the best?
- A convenience store clerk... - Or a taxi driver.
- Let me practice. - Okay.
- Suzuki. - Suzuki.
(So Min picked "Someone called Suzuki" too.)
You and I are unlucky.
This doesn't feel right.
(So Min picked "Someone called Suzuki" too.)
- I'm getting worried. - From the beginning...
(The thing they're afraid of happens again and again.)
(They keep picking "someone called Suzuki".)
It's Suzuki.
Why do we keep getting Suzuki?
- At this rate, it'll be Suzuki. - Exactly.
Wasn't it difficult to find a Suzuki in Osaka?
- It was. - It was really hard to find one.
It was hard.
I see.
- Please say, "Start." - Let's do it.
- In 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
- Start. - Start.
(Practice is over. It's time for the real challenge.)
I hope it's not Suzuki.
(He's aiming for a taxi driver or a convenience store clerk.)
- It's a taxi driver. - Taxi driver.
- It's a taxi driver. - It's a taxi driver.
(He picks a taxi driver.)
(He overcomes the curse of Suzuki and picks a taxi driver.)
- Then... - Okay.
get on a taxi and ask the driver.
- I gave it to you, right? - Okay.
If the taxi driver suggests steak,
- we'll go home right away. - We're going home.
We're serious.
- Where? - The driver at the front.
- The driver at the front. - Let's ask him outside...
and get on later.
There's a taxi like that.
You can't close it.
(Sir, let me ask you something.)
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
(What is she asking for?)
(What will he recommend?)
(If it's steak, they'll go home.)
(If it's something else, they have to eat it and try again.)
(Will the driver recommend Okinawa steak?)
- What do you... - Buckwheat noodles.
(Okinawa has great soba noodles.)
- Soba? - Soba?
- Soba noodles? - Okinawa soba noodles.
- Okinawa soba noodles? - Everybody.
(It was on the list too.)
(Seok Jin was against it, so they picked steak.)
- Soba? - Yes.
Go to the restaurant he recommends, and please eat.
(They're full, but they're forced to eat soba.)
(They go in two separate cars.)
We have to do this...
until we get steak.
This mission is difficult. It's hard to get steak.
It's hard. This is not possible. It's so hard.
If we go to the convenience store,
let's pick somebody who seems to like meat.
We have to pick somebody with that kind of look.
If I knew Japanese, I would have asked him many questions.
This is driving me nuts.
This is hard. We don't know the accents,
- I know. - so they don't understand.
Try it.
(Did I do it wrong?)
Isn't that a female tone?
A man sounds like this.
- Isn't this how you do it? - Who does that?
Who does that?
Men are like that.
There are advertisements at the end of Japanese dramas.
That's the female voice I heard.
- Oh, dear. - They say, "Toyota".
You know what I mean? "Asahi".
Language is not like that.
I don't think you understand.
(This is an actual Japanese advertisement.)
(It sounds the same.)
Hold on. Let me ask him something in Japanese.
- It's a translator. - I'm going to use it.
What is the most delicious food in Okinawa?
(What is the most delicious food in Okinawa?)
Steak.
This was it.
- Gosh... - He should have told us earlier.
- So Min. - Does this mean something else?
(He says steaks are good too.)
He said steak.
- What? What soba? - "What soba?"
(She's mad.)
What are you doing?
- What are you saying? - What soba?
(She means, "Why did you say soba earlier?")
What?
Why did you recommend soba earlier?
(They ask the driver for an explanation.)
(Why is it in Korean?)
I'm sorry. This is driving me nuts.
Excuse me. Gosh, this is not it.
(Didn't you just recommend steak?)
(Why did you recommend soba?)
There are many delicious food.
Soba and steak are both delicious.
- They're all delicious. - I see.
- They're all delicious. - They're delicious.
Because they're all delicious.
You keep translating with this, so that's why...
you use that female tone.
- Goodness. - You used a female tone.
That's not true, So Min.
- This one. - We're here.
- This is the place. - Thank you. Here.
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
Okinawa soba.
See? People usually say it normally.
You just used a soft voice.
Come on.
(They arrive at the soba place.)
Thank you.
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
Have a nice day.
Okinawa soba.
(How will Okinawa soba taste?)
I like soba.
There's pork cutlet as well.
- They must be famous. - They sell noodles.
The tofu looks good too.
(This place has a variety of Japanese food including fish.)
(Locals love Okinawa soba.)
This is great. It feels nice.
- It's our first one, so I'm happy. - Me too.
- This is easy. - Me too.
Let's have a light one.
- I'll eat happily. - Seriously.
- This looks so good. - Are you Korean?
The pork cutlet looked good.
It was this size.
We can't eat too much.
- Let's order two... - Okay.
- and share. - We'll save money too.
Hi.
Excuse me.
(He takes out his translator again.)
Take a cup.
Which soba noodles taste the best?
(She goes away.)
She left.
(It's too late.)
- She left. - This is late.
(The translator has problems during important moments.)
Why is it a female's voice?
- That's why he has that tone. - Switch it to a man.
Stop it. It didn't work properly,
so it said, "Which sofa tastes the best?"
Leather sofa.
(They didn't start it off right. Will they be able to order?)
We're going somewhere.
We shouldn't have been happy about it.
Is Daema Island a vacation spot?
Like Okinawa?
- I don't think so. - It's good for fishing.
- Fishing? Right. - Daema Island?
People go there to fish.
- Sang Yeob. - Yes?
If you get last place, don't pick anyone from our team.
Of course not.
- He's loyal. - That much, yes.
- Okay, this is my mistake. - It is.
Yes, I'm loyal.
You're really good at hurting people.
We invited him...
as the number one celebrity we want to go on a trip with.
Haha, that's not helping.
- Then what? - Haha.
- What? - Sang Yeob is not stupid.
Why?
- How? - Do you think he's really stupid?
- What do you mean? - That's not good.
Why? He's not in 1st place? Is he 2nd?
- Did we make this up? - I heard you.
Who's in first place then?
This makes me feel bad.
- That's not what I meant. - Ji Hyo.
Who was the number one celebrity you wanted to go on a trip with?
Me?
Park Bo Gum.
(He loses.)
She's so weird.
I'm just saying that's just me.
I know what you mean.
- Sang Yeob. - Yes.
I'll be on your side today.
It's okay if I get last place.
I hope you don't change until the end.
Hey, I'm a fool who only knows one thing.
- Haha, let's do this then. - What?
You guys can do rock-paper-scissors,
and the winner gets the loser's step counter for five seconds.
I'm serious. Then I'll accept this friendship.
I won't try to come between you two again.
Should we try it?
I trust you.
- I gave it to Kwang Soo too. - All right.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Sang Yeob loses.)
- Okay. - Okay.
- How does this work? - Give yours to Haha.
It's 769 right now.
- That's insane. 5 seconds? - 5 seconds.
- I won't do anything. - Okay.
- Start. - Let's start.
- One... - Kwang Soo, you idiot.
(He pretends like Kwang Soo is shaking it.)
You idiot.
- Hey. - It was you.
- Goodness. - Oh, my.
- Goodness. - That was so mean.
That was so mean.
Kwang Soo, you are so bad.
- You're so mean. - You think it's me?
- You're such a jerk. - You're such a jerk.
You're such a jerk.
I won't say much.
- Did you see that? - You saw him, right?
You saw him. I give up.
- This is Haha. - Hey.
- You win. - This is Haha.
- I give up. I won't say anything. - You know...
when you tell a puppy to wait,
it waits, right?
He can't wait.
As soon as he has it in his hand,
he shakes it without knowing. He can't resist.
This is driving me nuts.
You two should try.
- Kwang Soo and me? - Yes.
- I won't do it. I'll show you. - Trust each other.
Kwang Soo, let's recover our trust for each other.
- Okay, let's do that. - Let's do it.
I don't mind giving you mine now.
I know. Give it to me then.
But there are rules.
- I'll do rock-paper-scissors. - Tell him.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Sang Yeob loses again.)
Kwang Soo, I...
might not talk to you again.
- Sang Yeob. - Today is the day.
It's 793 right now.
- Haha, you can count until five. - Okay.
- Five, - Hey.
4, 3... Remember what I said?
- You're such a bad dude. - I'm not even touching it.
- That's enough. - Two...
Stop it.
One.
I understand...
- why you swore at him. - What's more important...
- Goodness. - Hey.
What's more important than me shaking it...
is that Haha counted 5 seconds in 10 seconds.
(Haha is the really bad one.)
- What? - I was innocent.
- I was innocent. - Hey.
- When he counted to 3, - He thinks I did that.
10 seconds have passed.
- There were two seconds left. - You're a traitor.
I asked him to count to five.
I was going to shake it once per second.
I'm serious.
I had to shake it.
- He said... - You're totally trash.
- five seconds, but... - He's trash.
You're the biggest trash in the universe.
- He counted for 20 seconds. - No way.
- He's the biggest trash. - He is.
He belongs to a space station.
- He took too long. - He's making me the bad guy.
- Goodness. - I...
- I want to stay out of this. - Haha.
I mean...
I lost. I don't want to do it.
Da Hee was on the show before, right?
She called him sneaky. He's so sneaky.
That's a cute way of putting it.
- It's too cute for him. - That's right.
When you think it's too unfair, you get dazed.
- Every word you say... - I don't know what to say.
- makes me so mad. - I'm being honest.
It was the truth.
Is this what the world is like?
- Sang Yeob. - Is that it?
You can watch it later.
The society is not like this, right?
- Of course not. - Goodness.
There are people like me and people like him.
It's the bad guy's golden age.
I'm going to be bad today.
(You're trash.)
(He learns...)
(little by little.)
(Sang Yeob will be transformed the wrong way.)
I can't...
look into Kwang Soo's eyes anymore.
How can he look at me like that?
- It's scary, right? - Kwang Soo.
- He's so... - He has the innocent eyes.
(Thinking)
Okay.
- Okay what? - That was scary.
He said "okay".
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
What if it gets higher when we are on the boat?
(Daema Island is so far.)
- Hello. - Welcome.
(She's slow.)
I give up. I'm past 1,000.
We might not be first place, but let's not be last.
(They're finally off to Daema Island 6 hours after leaving the airport.)
I'm going to try not to be last for Sang Yeob.
I have many games in mind. Let me make suggestions.
Take a sock...
and put a step counter inside.
We'll have 4 socks and pick 1 randomly.
Then...
(That sounds fun.)
That sounds fun.
Why does he think of games like that?
- You won't know whose it is. - I brought some socks.
(You pick a step counter randomly and spin it in a sock.)
- Let's try it. - I don't know if I should do it...
- or leave it. - Then...
can I borrow your cap?
Put your step counters in here.
Don't look,
and put one in a sock.
(A staff member will pick one randomly and put it in a sock.)
- This is fair, right? - I think it'll be me.
Don't look.
You can do it.
Put it in here.
I'll leave the rest here.
We don't know whose it is.
(If you get picked, you'll lose a few hundred steps here.)
Give it to me.
All right. We'll spin it five seconds each.
You can do whatever you want in five seconds.
(You can spin it for 5 seconds.)
(He's worried.)
It could be yours.
(He finally gets to shake it as much as he wants.)
1, 2.
- 3, 4. - Shake it harder.
- I don't even know. - Five.
Okay.
(He probably raised it by more than 100 steps.)
- I wonder whose it is. - I hope it's not mine.
1, 2, 3...
(He's next, and he starts to get nervous.)
(He shakes it insanely.)
- 1, 2, - I hope it's not mine.
3, 4, 5.
You're done.
- Hey. - It could be yours.
(10 steps, 100 steps, 1,000 steps)
It could be yours.
(He's satisfied.)
- Goodness. - One...
(He tries his best not to be last.)
- This doesn't work. - Five.
- You're done. - I don't think it worked.
(The step counter was shaken for over 20 seconds.)
I'll put this on top.
If it's yours, you can take it from the cap.
(It's time to give the step counters back to the lucky 3.)
- I'm worried. - Give one back at a time.
- One at a time. - Okay.
(The first lucky step counter)
- Give it to them yourself. - Please.
Don't shake it.
Sang Yeob.
I'm not in last place anymore. I'm not in first place.
I don't know what I'm saying.
(The second lucky step counter)
Haha.
(Then...)
(The step counter that was shaken madly...)
(was either Ji Hyo's or Kwang Soo's.)
(Who's the last lucky person?)
Ji Hyo.
(The step counter inside the sock is Kwang Soo's.)
- We didn't plot this. - We really didn't.
Kwang Soo shook it the hardest.
We didn't plot it.
(Kwang Soo always gets picked.)
(It serves you right.)
- Kwang Soo shook it the hardest. - Show it.
(How many steps does he have?)
(His step counter reads...)
(2,169 steps.)
I feel better now.
It's because of that game.
How did he get picked?
(While they were playing...)
It's so interesting.
(Meanwhile, they arrived after an hour and 10 minutes.)
We're in Japan.
I know.
I can't believe it.
(Daema Island is a Japanese island between Korea and Kyushu.)
(It's 49km from the Korean Peninsula and its population is 30,000.)
(Its nature has not been destroyed, so fishing industry is developed.)
- Let's go. - Where do we go?
Let's...
Right. I keep forgetting.
I thought it was an isolated island,
- but there are things. - Right.
Let's wear our team uniforms first.
Yes, we have to wear team uniforms...
to feel like one.
That's right.
(They argue often, so they need a team uniform.)
What about a very cute hat...
and a hoodie?
It looks good.
- What is it? - It's a burger.
You're easily surprised, Sang Yeob.
Are you slightly tired?
- Are you? - No.
He's easily surprised.
- Is that a bookstore? - There are socks.
It's incredible.
- "Welcome". - They sell things.
It's an automatic door.
- Let's go. - Go.
- They have clothes. - Let's go.
Let's be like the locals.
(Hello)
(I'm Korean.)
I've seen this a lot in Japanese animations.
- They have school uniforms too. - They have suits.
(There are jackets from Japanese animations and school uniforms.)
(There are clothes from different generations.)
- This. - Haha, this is so nice.
It looks warm.
- It's thick. - This is the top.
- It's good. - Let's wear this.
(It's hanten, a Japanese indoor jacket.)
- It's popular. - It's 45 dollars.
- Try it. - You should try it.
- Can I try it? - Okay.
- Thank you very much. - You're amazing.
(He speaks 3 languages fluently.)
I feel like we're a team.
I wondered why we had no unity.
(Can they get over the past and become one with the uniforms?)
(They look chic.)
Make a pose.
(We conquer fashion in Daema Island.)
(They are unfashionable people...)
(who wear whatever they want.)
(Staring)
(We look so cool.)
- I'm tired. - We're one now.
- We look cool. - Let's go.
Let's go. Right foot.
1, 2...
(Their limbs don't move together.)
(It's the Beatles of Daema Island.)
(They're worried about their step counters.)
Our feet are not moving together.
It's okay.
- Let's just go. - We did it.
(They're very satisfied.)
Let's go eat.
(They're finally united. They go to eat.)
I'm happy we bought the jackets.
What's this? What do they have here?
Is this it?
(They are too hungry.)
Let's go in.
(They step into the restaurant.)
It's so clean.
- He looks like a great chef. - I'll sit in the middle.
Okay.
(He looks like a master.)
Look at how he's making the sushi.
(They're excited.)
- He looks like a master. - He's using his hands.
Were you hungry?
- Yes. - Yes.
Enjoy the food.
Can we just eat?
Yes.
- Why? - There's the menu.
You can just eat.
- Let's get sushi. - What's this?
You sent us here.
(They're suspicious because the staff is being too nice.)
We didn't do any missions.
We just shot the intro.
(This is the first proper shooting since the intro.)
- You're just going to feed us? - Yes.
- That makes me feel uncomfortable. - Tell us now.
Let's just eat then.
- What's the best in the menu? - The best?
(They can't wait any longer, so they order.)
(They order assorted sashimi first.)
Sushi too.
- Sushi. - Sushi please.
(They have to order the sushi.)
(They are worried after ordering it.)
I think their sea eels are good.
I think so too.
We'll share...
seafood rice. One seafood rice.
This feels like a dream. There's something.
That was so fast.
They cut it fresh.
(Assorted sashimi is the first menu.)
- Sashimi? - Yes.
This must be for one person.
(These are fresh fish from Daema Island...)
(cut with a master's hands.)
(Daema Island Assorted Sashimi)
Can we eat?
(It looks so good.)
It's sushi.
(Sushi is next.)
(It's a fresh-looking master piece.)
What's this?
(It's good.)
- It's good. - Thank you.
(He takes two pieces at a time.)
It's good.
(It's so good.)
We had this before too.
- It's the Japanese apricot. - It's so good, sir.
- It's so good. - It's fresh.
(It makes them forget how tired they are.)
This is high-quality.
- Why did I put the sauce far away? - The sushi is good.
The sushi is good.
But I don't understand.
Isn't there a game to play?
- Isn't there a game to play? - What are you writing?
Are we getting food without any conditions?
I had two.
I had two pieces of sashimi.
Why do you feel so uncomfortable about having a meal during a trip?
(Laughing)
- Why do you make us uncomfortable? - Suddenly,
I feel unsure.
(Is there something under the plate?)
I picked it up.
(She makes a sudden remark.)
- This is supposed to be fun. - I will feed him.
Kwang Soo, eat it.
(The mission is a success, right?)
They are writing something down.
I am sorry, but please go outside...
so that we can eat in peace.
(Everyone freezes.)
- Let's eat, Haha. - Okay.
Let's eat.
I don't know anymore.
It's really tasty.
I know. It's so fresh.
(The taste makes them forget about their suspicions.)
The sashimi is sweet.
It really is sweet.
(Lastly, seafood rice is served.)
- Seafood rice. - Seafood rice.
(Seafood rice of Daema Island contains four kinds of fish.)
Thank you.
Try the rice.
I want to recommend this dish.
It's so tasty.
Unlike the Korean counterpart, this soy sauce is sweet.
There is squid, too.
- Is there squid? - Yes.
I have one.
(I have squid.)
Being with good members...
fills me with happiness.
There hasn't been an unfortunate event.
- No. - Things are going smoothly.
Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes. It was very delicious. - Thank you.
- Now, - It was very delicious.
I will tell you the Daema Island mission.
The Daema Island mission is Fishing Comes after Eating.
You succeed when you acquire...
every kind of seafood you have eaten.
(Acquire every kind of seafood you have eaten.)
You succeed when you acquire...
(Do you want us to catch...)
(the seafood we have eaten?)
(They inhaled all kinds of seafood from Daema Island.)
You have eaten a variety of seafood.
(Do you really want us to catch them?)
You will spin the globe with the members' names.
If you acquire the seafood the chosen member has eaten,
the team mission for Daema Island is a success.
You piece of garbage.
Each kind of seafood you fail to acquire...
adds 1,000 steps to the step counter.
(It adds 1,000 steps to the step counter.)
We wrote down...
the kinds of seafood each member has eaten.
- We will tell you. - I didn't eat a lot.
- Ji Hyo didn't eat a lot. - I didn't eat a lot.
Ji Hyo doesn't usually eat sushi.
I don't usually eat sushi.
I ate everything.
She didn't eat.
Kwang Soo, you ate...
chicken grunt, filefish, red seabream,
yellowtail amberjack, smallscale blackfish, striped beakfish,
- and squid. - That's seven kinds of seafood.
Did he eat seven kinds of seafood?
- It's over if I get picked. - Ji Hyo, you ate...
yellowtail amberjack and smallscale blackfish.
- I ate two kinds of seafood. - That's amazing.
Sang Yeob ate filefish, smallscale blackfish, yellowtail amberjack,
striped beakfish, and squid.
I thought I had eaten everything.
- I ate a lot. - Which two did I miss?
- Haha, you ate... - I ate everything.
filefish, yellowtail amberjack, red seabream, smallscale blackfish,
chicken grunt, conger eel, striped beakfish, and squid.
- Oh, my goodness. - I think you ate everything.
Gosh, that makes me upset.
You ate everything by yourself.
When did you eat conger eel?
It's fortunate that I didn't eat seaweed.
I almost ate seaweed.
Like I explained earlier, you only need to acquire seafood...
- one person ate. - I need to be picked.
- Ji Hyo needs to be picked. - Please bring in the globe.
- Think about it. - It should be Ji Hyo or me.
This is too much.
- I hope Ji Hyo gets chosen. - If we choose you...
and fail to catch anything, we will have 8,000 steps added.
With Kwang Soo, it will be 7,000 steps.
- That's right. - 7,000 steps.
We will have 7,000 or 8,000 steps added.
Before you begin, say, "Start."
When you are ready, please say it.
(What lies ahead for Team Love Triangle?)
(The war of step counter begins in earnest.)
(Does discord surface among them?)
(Their friendship gets ruined thanks to the step counter...)
(and recovers thank to fishing.)
All right.
(They get lucky at the sea.)
(Do they succeed in catching a full load of fish?)
(We are happy to be on the boat together.)
(These people are also on the same boat.)
(They can do anything to be in Jong Kook's good graces.)
(I like you guys.)
(They have the most intense mission with the scary Jong Kook.)
(They must succeed to avoid getting scolded.)
(Try your best to win against me.)
(A dinner with the most delicious Thai dishes)
(They are wary of Jong Kook even when they eat.)
(We can't live like this.)
(Take good care of my step counter.)
(Shaking)
(These dangerous members dream of a coup.)
(Chew, gnaw, taste, and enjoy food...)
(during the Okinawa trip that satisfies all five senses.)
(Why are there so many tasty dishes?)
(It's tasty.)
(They are unaware...)
(of the effect saying, "It's tasty," will bring.)
(What do they need to eat until the end?)
(Please let us stop eating.)
I can't do this anymore. Also,
I need to poop.
(Global Random Tour Part 2, Mission Impossible)