(Last week)
(The final race of the Family Package Project)
(It's You Take the Shuddering Package.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Jong Kook became the team leaders.)
(Global, package, family)
(Hong Kong, land, and island)
Our destinations depend on our choices?
(They met the team leaders through the door of the fate.)
(Ridiculous missions ensued.)
(They must complete the missions to avoid the penalty by today.)
(This is so annoying! This should count as a penalty.)
(Team Jae Seok must stand in line whenever they see a queue.)
(Team Jong Kook must play yut with three brothers on Shinshimo Island.)
(Team Seok Jin must ride the longest zip line in Korea.)
(And today...)
(Avoid getting the Shuddering Package.)
(The war abroad, on land, and on an island unfolds.)
(Will it be a Luxury Package or a Shuddering Package?)
(Their 4 weeks' worth of effort will come to an end today.)
(It's the grand finale of the Family Package Project.)
(Which 6 members will depart for the Shuddering Tours?)
My gosh, I hate this.
It's fine as long as it's not me.
Then on our way there,
we should come up with a fair game.
Just to be clear, no one wants to ride it, right?
No.
We should get someone.
The one with the latest birthday will be chosen.
- I like that. - It's about the birthday.
- I'm game. - Are you?
We should switch.
- Later birthdays will win? - The latest birthday will win.
- The later birthdays are better? - The latest birthday will win.
- The highest number will win? - The higher, the better.
We should just pick a group of four people.
- We should pick a group. - Okay.
(They will choose 2 members with the roulette.)
- My gosh, I'm nervous. - Time matters if it's the same day.
- Time will be a deciding factor. - Right, right.
(The earliest birthday gets 4 slots. The next 2 members get 1 slot each.)
My gosh, I'm really nervous. It's double.
(I must win since four slots are at stake on this game.)
(Whoever doesn't win has a higher chance in riding the zip line.)
Can you come here for a second?
Please.
- Please come this way. - They are coming.
- Come this way, please. - This way, please.
We have four people here.
- Why don't you stand over here? - Come this way, please.
Please move along.
We have four people here. Okay.
(4 employees who will determine Team Land's fate are invited.)
I choose him.
(He picks the youngest-looking cashier.)
Please come this way. You and I are partners.
I'll choose the chef.
My gosh, you chose the chef.
I pick Mr. Lee Jin Ho, the chief of the Product Department.
I'll stand next to Im Young Min, the sales' chief.
We'll start from here.
- I'll go first? - Yes.
What's the date of your birthday?
(Sang Yeob chose the chef. When is his birthday?)
- Just the date. - It's on the 24th.
(It's on the 24th.)
(Sang Yeob is happy while Seok Jin is disappointed.)
I got goosebumps.
- Is today his lucky day? - My gosh, what's going on?
- What's up with him today? - He is...
All right.
(Seok Jin changed the rules at the last minute.)
What's the date of your birthday?
(Did Seok Jin make the right move?)
- It's on the 31st. - My gosh!
It's on the 31st.
(Seok Jin's decision has brought upon a miracle.)
- That's the highest it can get. - Yes!
- It's the winning number. - It's the highest.
(I must avoid being last.)
- This is incredible. - My gosh.
I just got goosebumps. I got goosebumps.
I didn't think it would be the 31st.
I'm on the 19th.
- That's not bad. - That's not bad.
- Thank you. - My goodness.
Will Haha place last?
(Haha's fate depends on the 19th.)
(Was he born later than the 19th?)
- It's double. - Your name will be written twice.
Mr. Lee Jin Ho,
what day of the month were you born?
(If it's earlier than the 19th, Haha loses.)
(If it's later than the 19th, Ji Hyo loses.)
It's on the 19th.
(My answer is 19th as well.)
- The number is the same. - 19th?
- What time were you born? - What time?
- Do you know? - The time of birth.
- 12:35am. - Yes!
(Yes!)
- If it's 12:35am... - It's bad, isn't it?
- The later the time, the better. - My goodness.
- The later the time, the better. - What time were you born?
(How about Haha's partner?)
- 11pm. - Yes!
- I am not last. - 11pm.
(Thanks to his partner, Haha doesn't finish last.)
- Ji Hyo. - Thank goodness.
(I can't believe I will get 4 slots.)
Ji Hyo will get the most number of slots.
Thank you so much for being born at 11pm.
Seriously.
(Ji Hyo gets 4 slots. Haha and Sang Yeob get 1 slot each.)
I keep going to the restroom.
(Haha gets 3 slots, Seok Jin gets 2 slots, and Ji Hyo gets 1 slot.)
- I became sensitive. - Already?
How many slots does Haha have?
- He has three slots, right? - Haha has...
- 3 slots. - 3 slots.
(It can't be like this.)
3 slots. I have 3 slots, too.
Sang Yeob, what is your opinion on variety shows?
(Why is he suddenly asking about his opinion on variety shows?)
- What do you mean? - What is your opinion on them?
A variety show has different characters.
That's right.
I recommend that you become a character who says,
- "I will do it." - That's right.
I was going to say the same thing.
You are a veteran. Let me tell you.
You should be Yes Man.
(Yes Man?)
- Yes Man? - You will be rich and popular.
You will land a pizza commercial.
"We don't have anyone to deliver pizza."
(Take the bait.)
- "What should I do?" - "I will deliver it!"
(Here comes Yes Man.)
(He takes the bait.)
All right. I will write my name down.
(He is naive.)
Let's light up the fireworks!
- My goodness. - I will do it.
(The innocent sheep wants to have a unique character.)
Yes Man did it.
Yes Man!
(Yes Man fills the remaining slots with his name.)
(Sang Yeob, congratulations on your new character...)
(and the higher probability of riding the zip line.)
(The festive car runs on the highway.)
It's a good day to go on the zip line.
(They arrive at the zip line spot in Hadong.)
- I suddenly feel carsick. - Hold on. I feel nauseous.
It's okay. I can do this.
Only the people who are chosen will ride the zip line.
Oxygen is scarce up here. I am serious.
I bet oxygen is scarce up here.
Yes Man, I love you.
(Please do this for us.)
Yes Man went home.
- Yes Man clocked out. - Yes Man clocked out.
We are here. This is it.
This is ridiculous.
(Is this the zip line? This is ridiculous.)
(Is this your first time at this kind of a zip line?)
I feel like I am going to puke.
This is crazy.
Let's stop this.
We can't go down this slope.
How will we go down?
One. Let's go.
(An actual video of the ride)
(The land is nowhere in sight.)
(After traveling down 732m on a steep slope,)
(you go down another 1,487m.)
(The adventure ends after you travel 967m over the archipelago.)
- The slope is... - Look at this.
Look at the slope of the zip line.
This is ridiculous.
- This is too much. - This is crazy.
- This is... - Does it go down to there?
- It seems so. - It's so far way.
(Haha heads to the restroom.)
(Retching)
(He retches in extreme nervousness.)
(I remember Se Chan did this for the Nevis Swing.)
(It's time to choose 2 people who will ride the zip line.)
We have to spin the wheel.
Let's ask the director to spin the wheel.
- There will be no practice rounds. - Okay.
There will be no take backs or practice rounds?
There will be no practice rounds. Don't make excuses.
Please spin the wheel. Who will ride the zip line first?
Get your fingers off the wheel.
(Ji Hyo has 7 slots, Haha has 3 slots,)
(Seok Jin has 3 slots, and Sang Yeob has 3 slots.)
Who will it be?
(Which member is fated to ride the zip line first?)
(Meanwhile, Team Island)
- We arrived at the island. - Okay.
(They arrive at Shinshimo Island, the three brothers' island.)
This is Shin Island.
You are right.
- Is this Shin Island? - Shin Island.
This is Shin Island, not Shi Island or Mo Island.
Before you get started with the mission,
I will share additional rules regarding the Running Balls.
Depending on the outcome of the mission,
the team will get either 4 or 40 Running Balls.
The distribution of these Running Balls...
will be decided by the team members' votes.
If every member gets one vote, they will be distributed evenly.
If one member gets more votes than the others,
he or she will receive all of them.
However,
if a member is voted unanimously,
the member he or she chooses...
will receive all the Running Balls.
Please cast your votes carefully.
- This is the war of nerves. - We will have to play smart.
If you receive 40 Running Balls, you will get a Shuddering Sticker.
The producer is carrying a ballot box.
It's the moving ballot box.
You can change your decision, right?
You can revise your ballots until the end of the mission.
(You can revise your ballots until the end of the mission.)
Should I write down Kwang Soo's name ahead of time?
(Should I write down Kwang Soo's name ahead of time?)
My name?
Let's base our decisions on how we do on the mission.
Don't make up your mind from the start.
I didn't make up my mind.
- Okay. - Also,
if all of us write our own names, we will have a happy ending.
- Our own names? - Our own names?
Then the Running Balls will be divided evenly.
- Let's write our own names. - Let's do that.
- Let's do that. - Kwang Soo won't write his name.
- I will. - He can't be trusted.
Let's write our own names.
- Let's do it now. - Will you change it?
Tell me before you do that.
It has begun.
(Tell me before you do that.)
That's great. Da Hee, you are doing great.
Pressure him. I like it when you do that.
You became annoyed so early on today.
- I am sorry. - He is an utter jerk.
- Write it on the left corner. - Oh, here?
The voter.
- Write down the name of the voter. - Okay.
- Did you write it down already? - Yes.
Did you make your vote?
- Yes. - Already?
- Oh, you want me to do it now. - No, write down your name.
(The producer is flustered.)
Write down the name of the voter.
You should pull her aside and explain the rules.
- I mean... - What is wrong with her?
He said I could change my decision later.
- Did you write down a name? - Yes.
What?
Why did you write my name? Write your own.
I wrote my own name right here.
Then why did you write my name and cross it out?
(My goodness.)
- Write your own name. - She voted.
- Write yours. - She's done.
She made a decision in her mind.
- She already voted. - Did you vote already?
- Yes, she did. - Gosh, my nose is runny.
Don't get mad at her for her vote.
It's time to find the three brothers.
Please ask around to find them.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's finish the mission quickly.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
(Team Island bickers from the start.)
- It's nice. - I feel like I am on a picnic.
I know.
Da Hee, I am going to get a Luxury Sticker.
You should get a Shuddering Sticker at least once.
Jong Kook has a Shuddering Sticker.
(Jong Kook has a Shuddering Sticker.)
Don't you care more about being with Jong Kook?
He will go on the Luxury Package.
Who? Me?
- Luxury Package? - Trust me.
He has a Shuddering Sticker.
- Trust me, Jong Kook. - Okay.
How about you?
Between Luxury Package and Jin Young, what would you choose?
This is what Jong Kook is like.
If Jin Young really wants it, he will go with her.
- Of course. - Well...
- I am not desperate about a man. - No?
(I am not desperate about a man.)
That's why you should be desperate, okay?
(That's why you should be desperate, okay?)
Why are you asking him to be desperate?
(Jin Young tries to tame a tiger.)
When a woman isn't desperate, I ask her to leave.
- I am like that. - I am like that, too.
I think Jin Young likes him,
but it's not enough to go on the Shuddering Package.
Really?
That's what I gathered.
If she gets a chance to go on the Luxury Package,
she will go.
When I was on Running Man last time...
- Was it Kwang Soo who said it? - What?
Someone said that I called Jong Kook in a drunken state...
only to have him screen my call.
Someone said that.
- I keep seeing in the comments. - What?
"Even though Jong Kook rejected her, she keeps making advances."
Really?
- Firstly... - Say it. Say it.
Have I ever called you in a drunken state?
I have never done that.
(Say that I have never called you in a drunken state.)
I think you did call me.
(I don't know about drinking though.)
- What? - At night.
I did call you but...
- I don't know if you were drunk. - Stop it.
- I mean... - Stop it.
- Stop it. - I don't know if you were drunk.
(She hits him in embarrassment.)
- My goodness. - What is that?
There is a township office.
- Look. - You are right.
- There are a lot of buildings. - I know.
- Let's go. - There is...
- a township office. - That's right. Let's get off.
- We should ask here. - I see a sign.
We should ask here.
We don't have a clue right now.
We will get useful information at the township office.
- Are we allowed to do this? - Can we...
- Can we ask at the township office? - Are we allowed to do this?
We don't have a clue on how to find the three brothers.
It's game over.
- We will get our answer right away. - Then it's a matter of going there.
Can the production crew go in?
Can they?
- Hello. - Hello.
Is it okay if we shoot here?
- I'm not sure. - We weren't sure about that either.
- I was wondering... - Just do it.
Okay, thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you for being kind. - He has a good personality.
We were wondering if there's a family of...
three brothers living in this region.
- Three brothers? - Pardon?
(Are there three brothers in this region?)
That's not common.
- It's not common. - Why?
- It's not common, right? - It's because...
in this region,
there aren't many people who work around here.
- Don't they move out? - They work elsewhere.
- Right, that's what I said. - There aren't many people...
- who work here. - Right.
Are there any elderly people...
who live with their brothers?
- Are there anyone like that? - No.
It's okay if they make baby noises.
- They can be infants. - Right.
How about this?
I was there during lunch.
It's for planting rice seedlings.
- Some people are planting them. - Right now?
- It's a group of 20 people. - Really?
Is it nearby?
It takes 20 to 30 minutes by car.
- We should go there. - I see.
Thank you so much.
- Will we go where they're planting? - Let's go.
- Will there be people? - I think so.
The colors in this neighborhood are pretty.
- You're right. - It's so colorful here.
- It's because it's sunny. - It's because of the good weather.
Isn't the bus stop nice too?
This would make a great background for photos.
- Shall we take a photo? - What?
Look over here.
1, 2.
(On a warm, spring day,)
(they make a souvenir.)
It's done.
Shall we take one while looking at the sky?
Let's look at the sky.
- She seems so excited. - Let's do that.
- Look directly at the sky? - Yes.
(Just stare aimlessly at the sky.)
- How about we do this? - Can we please stop?
Let's pose like models.
- Andre Kim's trademark pose? - Yes.
- Okay. - Like Andre Kim?
- In 3, 2, 1. - 3, 2.
(Are you really making that pose?)
(What else can I do?)
(She successfully trains Jong Kook.)
(Is this a wedding photoshoot?)
What are they doing?
(Laughing)
- Do it, Kwang Soo. - Do what?
Take a photo in this pose.
Why should I?
(They put their heads together.)
(They look like enemies.)
(Let's smile, Kwang Soo.)
Let's go now.
- Let's go. - We don't have time.
- Let's go. - We don't have time for this.
(They move while blaming the lack of time.)
It must be here.
- All of them are here. - Where?
It's a sight I've only seen in dramas.
We'll definitely get information from them.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Hello, sir. You're working hard.
- They'll like her. - He likes Jin Young.
They'll like Jin Young.
Keep showing your teeth. You must show your teeth.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello, ma'am.
- Hello, ma'am. - Hello.
- You're working hard. - Hello.
- Hello. - You're working so hard.
We'd like to ask a question.
We should give this to each of them.
- You're the best. - I agree.
Hello, ma'am.
- Have one each. - Please drink this.
(She's very cute and polite.)
- Please drink it. - That's right.
- Have a drink. - Thank you.
Please have a drink. Hello.
Why didn't you come with Song Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo went somewhere else.
He's her biggest fan.
Do you like Ji Hyo?
When you appeared on "Law of the Jungle",
I saw you many times.
Do you mean me? Thank you.
I saw you running in bushes.
- You're number one. - Thank you.
The work must be difficult.
- Don't let others be mean to you. - I'll work harder.
Are there any families of three brothers...
- in this neighborhood? - Three brothers?
Is there a family of three brothers in this neighborhood?
(He has one.)
You too.
- Wait. - Do you have two brothers?
The three brothers must live here.
Do they live near here?
- No, they aren't here. - You must cross the sea.
We should have made three brothers.
- Three brothers? - That's not your fault.
Not making three brothers isn't your fault.
We're just asking.
I'd make three sons if you had called ahead.
In that short period of time?
How long in advance should we have called?
How could you make three sons in the meantime?
I'd have one more child if you had called yesterday.
Yesterday?
(No way.)
Is it possible in a day?
(His eyes quaver.)
Medical practice is advanced these days.
(He speaks without changing expressions.)
Pardon me? Is it true?
- No way. - You seem so naive.
- Go and see. - Okay, thank you.
There's a family of three children.
They're somewhere. They have three children.
- Listen, Jong Kook. - Hello.
- Let's shake hands. - Hello, sir.
(They get acquainted.)
Is there a family of three...
Why do you only like black?
How did you know that?
- Black? - You should also like white.
Black doesn't get dirty easily. Thank you for noticing.
Instead of getting married, you want others to have children.
I'm sorry, sir.
I promise to have three children, sir.
- You'd better keep your promise. - I will.
I'll have three children.
Your mother expected so much from you on "Mom's Diary".
You're right.
This is how I get scolded.
I'm impressed that all of them know all this.
- They know everything about here. - They all know.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you so much.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Good luck on your work. - Thank you.
- We haven't seen it in a long time. - Goodbye.
- Good luck. - Thank you, goodbye.
I think...
- it'll get more difficult. - It's getting harder.
It makes me concentrate on the voting.
What are you talking about?
- Look how pretty it is. - What is?
When would we walk on a street like this again? Look at this.
- The yellow paint is coming off. - You're right.
- There's a house here. - Hello, sir.
- Hello. - Hello.
May we ask you a question?
- We're from Running Man on Sunday. - Hello.
Hello.
On this island, is there a family of three brothers?
Is there a family of three brothers?
- Three brothers? - Yes.
- Who are living together? - Yes.
I have a family of three brothers.
My older brother lives in Uijeongbu.
- He moved away. - Really?
- Jong Kook, talk to them. - For now...
- Listen. - This is great.
We searched very hard,
- but we couldn't find any. - Listen, sir.
- Please, sir. - Listen.
Let's make a deal.
- He has a family of three brothers. - Right.
Instead of meeting his older brother,
can we meet another member of his family?
I have a daughter-in-law.
- Okay. - That sounds good.
Will you substitute his brother with his daughter-in-law?
Yes, is it possible?
- We can't clear this mission. - He's right.
It was supposed to be three brothers.
As a penalty,
if you accept 10 Running Balls, we'll let you continue.
- 10? - 10?
- Accept 10 balls? - Yes.
Will you accept 10 Running Balls and continue?
- Will you accept 10? - Let's do it.
- Let's do it. - His brothers aren't here.
- It's hard to find. - Right.
- Okay. - They said there aren't any.
- They don't live here. - Accept 10 as a penalty.
- In 3, 2, 1. - 2, 1.
- Start. - Start.
Let's play a game.
I'm disappointed.
(Will they finish the next mission safely?)
Let's go in.
- Hello. - Hello.
These are three brothers of the family.
It's the daughter-in-law instead of the eldest brother.
- That's right. - She'll join the game.
So we're here to play yut.
- Do you play it often... - Yes.
- during the holidays? - You won't defeat us.
Really?
I see.
- Some people have old talents. - Right.
We have...
- What is it? - Do you have the game board?
- We need to spread it out. - Of course.
- You must play it often. - Right.
- Is it already prepared? - He has it prepared at home.
We need one more layer to see better.
Spread it out. You lose your turn...
- if one stick goes out. - You're right, sir.
That should be hard to do.
- That will be hard. - It'll be unless you throw it hard.
All right, let's win in one go.
That sounds good.
I thought you were only good at sports. Are you good at yut?
Me? I don't know if I'm that good.
We need to tie up a string.
(We need to tie up a string to play it properly.)
- A string? - A string?
- A string? - Why do we need a string?
It's to measure the height.
(I'm a professional.)
- We don't need to. - He's right.
- The height should be measured. - I didn't know that.
He's a professional yut player on the national team.
You must throw 1.5m high.
- Do we tie up a string? - One of the sticks...
must be higher than the string.
(It's a special method.)
Did he just make up that rule?
- It's an original rule. - Really?
- Look at that. - Here it is.
- Here it is. - What is it?
Are you tying up a string like that?
He's setting them up for the string.
(He sets it up naturally.)
- Sir. - Wait, sir.
Why...
(He does it with bare hands.)
- Sir. - Wait, sir.
- Yes? - Why...
It doesn't work well.
- Sir. - Help him.
- That's right. - What's going on?
This is impressive.
- She brought a hammer. - Where did you find it?
The game became more serious.
- What's this? - I've never played it like this.
We should invite a professional judge.
Sir, isn't this too high?
- Shall we lower it? - No, no.
- It's high enough to hang laundry. - They're very determined.
- They seem determined to win. - We're...
We're not that serious about this.
- Look at that. - They have that.
- What's that? - Let me fix it.
Sir, what do you do for a living?
Sir.
What is going on here?
- It's a broken hoe. - It's a hoe?
- We could fix the rope with that. - It's broken.
This is fun.
(Another strange item appears.)
It feels nice that they're so enthusiastic about this.
They play yut like this?
If the sticks go up just this high,
- It's a fail, right? - it's a fail.
It's a fail.
Sir, can you demonstrate?
Your daughter-in-law...
(Of course, I can demonstrate.)
(Here we go.)
(Here, I'm demonstrating.)
- It's a geol. - One stick went above the string.
There must be a technique to get one stick go higher.
There is another version.
Like this.
- It's a fail. - It's a fail.
- It's a fail. - It's okay when one stick is out.
(He takes a chance.)
Sir. Hold on.
- It's okay when one stick is out? - That's a fail.
That's a fail.
- Is it okay? - It's a fail when one is out.
It's a fail.
So at least one stick has to go above the string.
If even one stick gets out, it's a fail.
If none of the sticks touches the string, it's a fail.
Your last try was a fail, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
You denied it earlier.
It's a fail.
We should decide which team will be which color.
- Which color do you want? - Which color do you want?
We want the passionate red.
You want red.
(The color of Team Running Man will be blue.)
Let me see.
What if we get a mo from the beginning?
(Nervous)
You have to move your stones wisely.
Well...
(These old men seem to know a lot about yut.)
(How good are they?)
We should look closely.
(One stick gets out.)
- It's a fail, right? - It's a fail.
(Is it a fail?)
- It's a fail, right? - Yes.
- Okay. - You look annoyed.
- Are you okay? - It's better this way.
It's not good to start first.
- It's better to fail? - What? Of course.
If you start later, you can catch the other team.
That was your plan?
- No. It happened to be a fail. - All right.
I don't think this is the Shishimo rules.
They're just making everything up.
- I'm confused. - They're making it up.
No, we're not.
(Will Team Island complete their mission?)
(Team Hong Kong is attempting to accumulate 100 in queue numbers.)
There was a restaurant only a few steps away.
That was close.
What if we don't get to eat?
What if we only take buses before we go back to Korea?
No way.
How long do I have to be on the same team with Jae Seok?
(How long do I have to be on the same team with Jae Seok?)
Hey.
Let's get this straight.
Today, you chose me.
You guys attract each other like magnets.
I shouldn't be on the same team as So Min's.
It makes me shudder.
The air conditioner is off.
- Of course. - Se Chan, take your shirt off.
- It's cool in here. - Right?
You can keep your shirt on. It's okay.
I'm hot. Why do you say that?
- What's with you? - Calm down.
You're too worked up right now.
(Jae Seok checks Se Chan's eye.)
You're so worked up.
- Can you tell? - You're worked up.
- Are you a doctor? - Calm down.
- Calm down? - Trust me and calm down.
This is strange.
On the bright side, 11 people were in line.
- There were 11 people. - It counts.
Of course. Let's get off.
Let's go. We're finally here. It looks better here.
There are many restaurants here.
There are more places on the left side.
There are so many people.
It's crowded.
- It's so crowded. - I like it.
It looks like Hong Kong now.
- It's nice. - It looks like a Hong Kong street.
Listen carefully.
There are many lines here. We should choose wisely.
I'm too scared to say anything.
- So am I. - I'm scared.
I see a line over there.
(Jae Seok sees a line again.)
- It's a line. - 1, 2, 3, 4...
There are five people.
You have to get in line.
- What is this line for? - Let's get in the line.
What's this place?
It's a restaurant.
(They're lucky.)
- It's a restaurant. - It's a restaurant?
It's a restaurant.
(They're lucky because they're hungry.)
How many people are in line?
When we first saw the line, there were five people.
- Okay. - So we'll count five.
(5 will count.)
- We have to choose what to eat. - What's that?
Isn't that Japanese ramen?
(Isn't that Japanese ramen?)
Well...
- Isn't that Japanese ramen? - Isn't that Japanese ramen?
It's Japanese ramen.
Why did you say you saw a line? Watch your mouth.
- Ramen? - It's a ramen place.
Is this a follow-up to our Okinawa trip?
(Is this a follow-up to our Okinawa trip?)
(Is the noodle torture starting again?)
When you're in Hong Kong...
You should try dim sum or xiaolongbao.
You have to eat here. At least one dish.
- Ramen... - Let's order ramen.
This one.
- We might be able to eat. - Just one?
- 2? - Yes, 2.
Let's order this one too. What's that?
(They have to obey the rules.)
Thank you.
- Is this the place? - Yes.
(They're not allowed to shoot here.)
We can't?
We can't shoot here?
- Luckily, - Right.
we can't shoot here.
Then it doesn't count?
The five people don't count.
- No? - It's not our fault.
The owner said no.
You have to experience the place for it to count.
We don't have much time. Let's go.
This is why you should look carefully.
I thought it counts...
You're the one who should look more carefully.
- Hey. - Watch your mouth.
Sushi. There's a sushi place.
(They look for another line.)
There's another line.
No. Don't look at it.
(Jae Seok is too careless.)
- Don't look at it. - Let me count.
Wait. We didn't see it.
- We didn't see the line. - 1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. There are 10 people.
Let's get in the line.
- There are 10 people. - Let's get in the line first.
- What's this place? - It's a restaurant.
(Let's see what they have.)
- It's noodles again. - It's noodles again.
(It's a noodle restaurant again.)
(There are only noodles on the menu.)
It's a soba restaurant.
- What do they have? - Only noodles.
- Yakisoba. - Hold on.
- It's a soba place again. - It's a soba place again.
- Isn't that soba? - It is.
This is a problem.
(It looks like a cafe, but they have only noodles on the menu.)
- This is not what we should eat. - We should eat xiaolongbao.
Should we ask if we can take out the food?
Should we get sandwiches?
Chul Min, I don't think we can shoot here.
They've given us permission.
But my fans are going crazy.
(But my fans are going crazy.)
What are you talking about? Come on.
- I think we can go in. - I don't want to...
cause too much trouble. Would it really be okay?
They say it's okay.
(Now, they have no choice but to go in.)
Oh, this place is...
(Yu Jae Seok is here!)
It's very big.
(An enthusiastic welcome)
(They stop eating and welcome Jae Seok.)
(Hello, Hong Kong.)
(Jae Seok just waved at me.)
Hi.
You're a huge star here.
All right.
(We'd like to thank everyone for their cooperation.)
Oh, my.
Excuse me.
(Se Chan takes off his shirt.)
Okay.
Take out the lint roller.
(Take out the lint roller.)
Why did you bring it?
(It's a must for a fashionista.)
- Roll it. - It's...
(Let me roll it on your face.)
- Is it for your face? - Is this too unnatural?
- It's for his face. - There's nothing.
Your t-shirt is so cute.
- Do you want to try? - I'm okay.
- I'm okay. - We don't need it.
- How about your back? - It's okay.
Okay.
Cameras like this...
(Extreme close-up)
- This angle is... - It's very flattering.
This angle is flattering?
No angle is flattering for Jae Seok.
(Let me film you at this flattering angle.)
You only see her forehead.
(Her face fills up the frame.)
(Let me try.)
Han Na.
Your eyes are very far apart.
(Now that I see your face...)
(Hurt)
Do you get that a lot?
- Her eyes are far apart. - So Min.
This angle works best for you.
(The best angle for So Min)
- You look like Kim Kwang Kyu. - She looks cute.
You look just like Kwang Kyu.
Let me see.
(Upside down)
(Hello, teeth.)
- This is not okay. - Is that an alien?
You're so ugly.
(An alien from another star)
We're having so much fun with one selfie stick.
Isn't Hong Kong amazing?
You look so excited.
If I did this to Jong Kook, he'd say,
"This is too unnatural. What are you doing?"
"Stop it. There are other cameras." I'm having so much fun.
- Yes. - It makes me happy.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm so happy.
(Jong Kook, are you watching?)
- Our food is here. - Our food is here.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - What's that?
- We'll gobble it up. - It looks tasty.
(They enjoy the food.)
It has a curry flavor.
(The 10 people in the line are counted now.)
- It tastes good. - Right?
It has a charm.
- Let's do this. - Let's do well.
- We can do this. - We have to try xiaolongbao.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
(Let's try some Hong Kong food next time.)
- We don't have much time. - Now,
- we don't have much time. - We don't.
Let's go to the place you know.
- Let's go. - Let's have some dumplings.
Se Chan, how do we get there?
- Do we turn right? - Yes, we have to cross.
We need to follow the people.
No, no. They're just talking over there.
Hey, there's a line here.
(Wait a second.)
- Hey, there's a line here. - Hold on a second.
(What kind of line is it this time?)
- Hold on a second. - Oh, no.
(Jae Seok spots a line across the dim sum restaurant.)
We have to get on the bus again.
(Unbelievable. It's a line for the bus again.)
All right. The line.
- There are five people here. - Come on, Jae Seok.
I told you we were going that way.
- Why did you mention the line? - Hold on.
He definitely said that there was a line.
(Thanks to his mouth, the team finds a line again.)
Okay. We'll ride the bus again.
(Thanks to Jae Seok, they ride the bus again.)
Why do you keep mentioning lines?
- Stop mentioning it. - Okay.
- Tsim Sha Tsui is right there. - I got it.
We can ride the bus there.
(They ride the bus right in front of Tsim Sha Tsui.)
- Let's ride it there. - I should ask them.
- "Ma'am". - A photo...
(What?)
- What did you say? - "Ma'am".
(Don't people say that in a gangster film?)
What was that?
- What did you say? Hold on. - I said, "ma'am".
- I was shocked. I thought... - Wait. You should've said this.
- Jae Seok. - I saw a lot of Hong Kong films.
- People understand this phrase. - This... It...
- Isn't that a Busan dialect? - Hey.
- "Hey, I'll show you." - "Hey, listen up."
"Your father lives in Yeomchang-dong, right?"
- "Hey". Just like this. - "Hey".
My gosh, these two are like flies.
They're coming at me.
They keep gnawing and bothering me.
(They annoy him.)
- Hey, you. You can't... - What?
- say anything to Jong Kook. - Jae Seok.
Jong Kook always says this is unnatural.
This is so much fun. This isn't unnatural at all.
You're thriving today. You are.
- Right. This is great. - Se Chan is thriving.
Here it is. Here it comes.
(They are forced to ride the bus again.)
- 4 people to Tsim Sha Tsui. - 4.
(After adding 5 more people, the accumulated number is 26.)
(Thank you.)
They startled me.
(Jae Seok is a top star.)
- With his mouth? - What did you mouth to them?
He mouthed, "Thank you."
- "Thank you." - "Thank you."
- I thought he cursed at them. - I thought so too for a second.
- To them, you know. - Hey.
This is what Jae Seok did.
(Mouthing)
- They are giving us a big welcome. - Jae Seok looks...
- like a real man in Hong Kong. - I thought they wouldn't know.
- He was very ladylike in Japan. - Stop it.
(He was very ladylike in Japan.)
(He learned Japanese from a female voice actor in a translating app.)
(His Japanese was overly gentle.)
- My gosh, this punk. - He's a man here.
(He's so manly in Hong Kong.)
- Let's get off. - Let's get off.
Okay. Let's go eat dim sum. Let's get it.
(They get off while hoping to find a dim sum restaurant with a line.)
Where are we?
- I think this is the harbor. - Really?
(The beautiful waterfront is seen at a glance.)
I can smell it already.
My gosh, look at that.
- Look at the boat. It's a boat. - Are we at the right place?
(Ferries that connect Hong Kong islands come and go at the harbor.)
My gosh, look at the ferry. That looks so interesting.
It looks very vintage.
I just remembered something.
It happened a long time ago, so I can't remember clearly.
- 20 or 30 people waited in line. - Let's go there.
- We must think about our mission. - Let's go there.
- Let's go. Let's go. - Let's go.
- What about the dim sum? Please. - We can eat it on the other side.
- I hope there are 90 people, right? - Exactly.
- It's because... - We should complete our mission.
We should cross over straight away...
- And we'll have dim sum. - and end it after eating dim sum.
- Isn't this the line? Is this it? - 1, 2, 3, 4...
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. - We will count 5 people.
(Unlike Jae Seok's memory, there are only 5 passengers.)
- All right. 5 people. - 6 people. Wait, wait.
- Let's wait a while. - We should wait for a bit more.
It became packed all of a sudden.
(The dock is swarming with people.)
- This is great. - I don't know how many there are.
There are many kids here too. They dropped the baggage.
There are 15 people. 15 people.
- There are 15 people. - We counted the heads earlier.
(The producer can't accept it since he already counted before.)
- Okay, okay. We understand that. - So Min.
So Min, let's not play dirty.
We should just go. We should just forget about it.
So Min. Forget about it.
(My gosh, that producer gets on my nerves!)
Come here.
I'm sorry. She's a bit riled up.
Let me vote.
"Jung Chul Min".
(She votes for the producer.)
- Let's go. Give us the money. - So Min, come here.
(They set out to ride the ferry after angrily casting her vote.)
- Let's set out - Jae Seok, it's so pretty.
My gosh, I feel like I'm on a trip.
(They get to admire the real side of Hong Kong for the first time.)
My gosh, this is nice.
- Do you know where you're going? - No.
- You're going to Hong Kong Island. - Island?
(I asked around and found out you're going to Hong Kong Island.)
- You're going to Hong Kong Island. - Hong Kong Island?
Where is Hong Kong Island?
We are already in Hong Kong. What do you mean by Hong Kong Island?
(Where is this island that everyone is worried about?)
(Hong Kong Island is the heart of politics and commerce.)
(It's where all the popular places are clustered together.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
This is equivalent to Gangnam in Seoul.
- That's great. - That's great.
- The buildings we saw from there... - It's all over there.
- We arrived. - We are here.
- Great. - This is excellent.
(What will happened to Team Hong Kong?)
(The members decide on who will zip line first.)
(The director will spin it.)
(Ji Hyo has 7 slots. Haha, Seok Jin, and Sang Yeob have 3 slots each.)
(Ji Hyo takes up 50 percent of the roulette, but you never know.)
(Everyone is desperate to let the others ride the zip line.)
The first one to ride it is...
(Everyone wants to avoid the ride. Which member will be chosen first?)
(Haha is chosen!)
(He used up his luck for the day during the birthday game.)
(Now, only 1 of the 3 members needs to be picked.)
(The thought of it makes them retch.)
I knew it. Today is Haha's day.
(This guy who rode the Nevis Swing goes pale.)
You should spin it. No practices. This is it.
1, 2, 3.
- Start. - Start.
- Spin it. - Start.
(The roulette is spun to pick the last member.)
(She has 7 slots.)
(They each have 3 slots.)
(Which member will join Haha?)
(It's Sang Yeob.)
(Yes Man is here to comfort me.)
(He seems different from the time when he earned his nickname.)
I knew it. I am the lucky one!
Lady Luck is on my side.
Seok Jin, my luck hasn't run out yet. It hasn't.
Haha will ride it first, and then Sang Yeob will go.
I'll ride it for our team's sake.
(Haha gets ready for the zip line.)
It looks quite windy.
- The weather... - I'm sorry. I'm easily scared.
(He's nervous as if he's in space.)
I want to brave it out.
My gosh. Goodness.
Haha. Daddy is going to...
Take a seat.
- My goodness. - Your left foot.
So Wool. Dream. Honey.
I rode the Nevis Swing. I can handle this.
(I can ride this zip line.)
(Just like that time, I can ride this fabulously.)
(I thought it would end there. Why am I hanging here?)
I'm going.
(Why am I hanging here?)
He's removing the safety pin.
1, 2.
- My gosh. - Darn it!
(Darn it. My gosh!)
(It scares him too.)
That's all right. That's all right. You can do this.
- I love you. I love you. - You can do this.
You can do it!
- I love you! - Let's do this. This is nothing.
Get ready.
- 3. - 3.
- 2, 1. - 2, 1.
(Haha is 1 second away from his 1st flight at 894m in Hadong.)
Go!
(Go!)
(Haha, the 1st rider, makes a great leap forward.)
Go!
(My gosh! Darn it. Goodness. Shoot!)
(For how much longer will I go down?)
No, no. I see a cliff.
(The legend of Mount Geumo, the golden stork.)
(He's losing it.)
No!
So Wool. Dream.
(Stuttering)
Go Eun. Hey, hey.
(His facial expression is the same as that on the Nevis Swing.)
Sang Yeob.
(Laughing)
(What's happening down there?)
Sang Yeob, it's your turn.
(Why am I here?)
(Why was I so rash earlier?)
(He wants to take back his generosity now.)
Don't cry.
The wind... The wind is biting.
My life up to this point...
just flashed by.
Dream. So Wool.
Daddy...
(Retching)
Daddy loves you very much.
(He's a bit shy to share his feelings.)
I love you so much too, honey.
And...
I'd like to thank the viewers too.
Let me open up now. I love you, Sung Yong.
Sung Yong. Sung Yong.
You must answer me when I'm talking to you!
(Please stay by my side, my beloved ones.)
Hurry. Stay next to me.
I want to sing now.
Life is full of opportunities
I believe I can
Darn it. I didn't curse. I didn't.
10, 9, 8, 7...
(This is what I meant.)
I wish this could go faster.
I'm almost there.
Oh, no. What will I do? What will I do?
(I can see the landing point at last.)
(Haha lands safely.)
I'm about to pass out.
(Now that it's over, the self-pity he held back gets unleashed.)
(This is Haha's first message after successfully landing.)
What have I done wrong? Why do you always make me do this?
Jae Seok.
Wait and see.
I can't do this kind of activity.
I have to ride another one?
(If you make me do this again, I'll hate you.)
You can do this!
(Sang Yeob gets ready.)
- My gosh. Goodness. My gosh! - A bit more.
Sang Yeob, go for it.
(He tries a new activity on this lucky day.)
- 4, 3... - 3...
- 3, 2, 1. - 3, 2, 1.
- Go! - Let's go!
My gosh, it's fast. It's faster than I thought.
(Screaming)
Look at him with his arms wide open.
(I will spread my wings and fly freely all over Hadong.)
(Unlike Haha, Yes Man admires the nature and enjoys the ride.)
(He flies in the sky over Hallyeosudo.)
(He passes through the wind as if he's sliding.)
(He arrives at the destination in an instant.)
(The first flight is a success.)
(He's moved.)
Watch your feet.
Watch the feet.
(The spectacular view is hard to forget.)
Put your feet.
- It wasn't a big deal, right? - Good job.
- Sang Yeob. - That was amazing.
That was amazing.
(Haha and Sang Yeob finish zip lining.)
Let's give them a round of applause.
Yes Man.
Betraying Man.
Cross.
(Yes Man and Betraying Man unite.)
This makes me feel accomplished.
Are you Yes Man, and is he Betraying Man?
(They head to Incheon after clearing the mission.)
You have succeeded the mission.
- Good job. - Let's go.
- We're here. - We're here.
We're here.
We arrived.
(Team Hong Kong arrives on the island.)
The weather is cooler here.
- Really? - Hong Kong is better.
I got it now.
We have to go to the main street.
It isn't so crowded here.
(That's strange.)
It's almost empty.
It must be here somewhere.
We just can't find it.
Will there be a waiting line for the Ferris wheel?
No, the seats are empty.
They're empty.
Why isn't there a waiting line...
- by the electronics store? - I don't think there are any.
- It's completely empty. - Even the buses are empty.
- There isn't anyone. - There's no one.
Why isn't there a line?
Let's go back.
- Why aren't people waiting? - We shouldn't have taken the ferry.
I know.
- We shouldn't have taken the ferry. - Was that a mistake?
(They trusted Jae Seok.)
Did we make a mistake?
- What happened? - Listen.
I wanted to give you a ferry ride in Hong Kong.
I got motion sickness.
I'm about to throw up the noodles.
The ride was good for the first three minutes.
- What happened? - Wait, we still have three hours.
I know what's here.
People wait in line to get on the escalator.
- Are they from "Chungking Express"? - Right.
The movie "Chungking Express".
(It's the world's longest escalator from "Chungking Express".)
- That's it. - I know what it is.
We should go there. It appeared on "Chungking Express".
I played a game there on Running Man.
That's where we should go.
Will there be many people waiting to get on the elevator?
- It's an escalator. - Right.
- I hope there will be 50 people. - That would be amazing.
- It's crowded here. - It's crowded.
It's over here.
- Aren't you happy that we're here? - Let's go farther.
I agree with you for now.
- Move out of the way. - Why?
- Follow me. - He wants us to follow him.
So Min, let's follow him.
- I think it's near here. - I think this is it.
(They arrive at the entrance.)
(Will it be crowded like Jae Seok said?)
(There are many people on the escalator.)
(How many people are waiting in line?)
Is this the waiting line?
- I think it's here. - What's this?
(There's no waiting line.)
This is the site from the movie.
- Is this it? - It's where the line starts.
You may get on it when there are five waiting in line.
Wait a minute. They keep getting on it.
How will there be a waiting line?
- Is there a waiting line? - Wait.
Is this where you meant?
Is this where I was talking about?
- Yes. - There should be a waiting line.
(You said that there's a line.)
Tell us.
Is a waiting line possible for an escalator?
- Wait a minute. - What is this?
I'm not here to take you around.
(I'm not your tour guide.)
It's a misunderstanding. We're on Running Man.
I'm not...
your tour guide right now.
I'm here to clear a mission with you.
- There's no waiting line. - Right.
- There is no line. - How is this possible?
There is...
(That's strange.)
- There's a famous egg tart place. - Where is that?
After you take three sets of these escalators,
- it's on the right. - That's right.
- I saw it. - Let's go up.
(It's a famous egg tart shop with a long, waiting line.)
(I know it too.)
- There's a famous place. - He didn't see it.
- He's lying again. - Jae Seok.
Don't agree with her. We'll just listen to her.
- I'm sure of it. - He'll jinx it again.
There's definitely a waiting line. Let's go.
- Then the escalator doesn't count. - Okay.
- It doesn't count? - No.
The egg tarts at that shop are very delicious.
I've heard about it too.
People still go even if they have to wait in line.
We looked it up.
A British governor couldn't forget the taste of this egg tart.
- I know. - When he returned to the UK...
He missed the egg tarts.
- Right. - So he came back.
- How could it be so great? - This is good.
(Their success rate is high.)
It's on the right. I can smell it. Right?
Just wait and see. There will be 20 people waiting.
Wait and see. There will be a line.
(They must find up to 100.)
Isn't this it?
Is it here?
(How many people are waiting in line for this popular shop?)
- Is it here? - There's no waiting line.
(What's going on?)
(It's completely empty.)
- Isn't this the place? - Wait.
This is it.
Is it here?
(It's usually so crowded.)
(However, it's completely empty.)
- There's no waiting line. - What happened, Han Na?
It's a famous, tasty restaurant.
It's under construction.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Travel guidebooks always say that there's a long line.
- There's a long, waiting line. - That's right.
Then why is it so empty?
(Hong Kong is full of waiting lines.)
(However, it's so empty today.)
Nothing is going well today.
(Let's think.)
- What's going on? - I think it's because of So Min.
(He avoids taking responsibility.)
I thought I was unlucky,
but every time I was unlucky, she was with me.
Whenever I felt unlucky, Producer Jung was always around.
I think he's the one.
When I came here last time...
(Let's go somewhere else.)
There was a square.
(Stop talking.)
Don't ever come back to Hong Kong. Don't come back to Hong Kong.
(They cover Jae Seok's mouth.)
Instead of this shop,
- how about this one? - Where?
- There's a temple in Hong Kong. - Will there be people?
(They search a temple.)
- Wouldn't this be a good place? - It looks empty.
I bet it's empty.
Let me explain.
To go back to Seoul, we must pass Tsim Sha Tsui anyway.
- I recommend we go there. - Let's go to Tsim Sha Tsui.
What will you do? Make a decision, Jae Seok.
- It only takes five minutes. - On foot?
Let's go.
(Let's go to the temple.)
If temple doesn't work, let's go to Tsim Sha Tsui.
- Okay? - To the temple?
Let's go to the temple.
(They go to the temple.)
We don't get to eat the tart.
I'm thirsty. Do we have to wait in line to get water?
I can't believe that this is happening.
Let's find at least 20 people at the temple.
- I bet it's empty. - I think so too.
We're almost there.
- Where is it? - I think it's here.
Is there... I think people are waiting in line.
- Where? - I see some people.
- I think there are some people. - They keep going in.
There's a waiting line.
(Many people are standing inside the temple.)
- This is the temple. - Okay.
Is this the entrance?
It starts from here.
(This place, which is empty, is the starting place.)
The line starts here.
When you look inside,
- people are waiting to get in. - No.
- There's no waiting line. - There's no line.
Who suggested this place?
- Who suggested this place? - Jae Seok.
Did Jae Seok suggest it?
- We suggested Tsim Sha Tsui. - We suggested Tsim Sha Tsui.
Jae Seok suggested the temple first.
(The three strongly recommended Tsim Sha Tsui.)
(Jae Seok drags them to the temple.)
How about this?
Let's go to Tsim Sha Tsui.
(Now, he suggests Tsim Sha Tsui.)
- Tsim Sha Tsui. - Goodness.
What did he say?
To get to Tsim Sha Tsui from here,
you must go back and take the ferry.
Why did we take the ferry in the first place?
- That's where we made the mistake. - It was the ferry.
You have 1.5 hours until you have to go back.
(They must go to the airport in 1.5 hours.)
- 1.5 hours? - Is that all we have?
(They must take the 5:30pm flight to return home.)
We must go to Disneyland now.
We came all the way to Hong Kong.
This is what I think.
I'm terribly unlucky.
I really am.
- You should accept it. - Right.
I think Jae Seok is cursed in Hong Kong.
(He's definitely cursed in Hong Kong at this rate.)
- In Hong Kong? - Yes.
You must be cursed.
I don't think I can go back to Korea.
People will criticize me if I go back like this.
We didn't get to enjoy Okinawa when we went there.
We didn't even see the ocean.
Listen, So Min. If I repeat this 2 to 3 times,
people will think that I take horribly boring trips.
(Jae Seok's horribly boring trips)
- Jae Seok's trips? - Yes.
Whatever place I suggest is horribly boring.
It's not fun at all.
(It's not fun at all after experiencing it.)
- Seriously. - You only traveled with him once.
- We couldn't eat egg tarts. - Han Na.
- You're so talkative. - We couldn't eat xiaolongbao.
What should I do?
(Team Hong Kong's mission is over.)
- Go. - Do well, Kwang Soo.
- One of them must go higher. - It must go higher.
- Remember the string. - Okay.
- Good luck. - Throw them.
- He got it. - Gae!
(Is it gae?)
- It's gae. - Wait a minute!
- It's gae! - Isn't it geol?
It's gae!
(She interferes with the board.)
- It's gae. - It's gae.
Isn't this considered flipped?
It's on the bottom. It's gae.
- It's gae. - It's gae.
- Gae! - Gae.
- It feels... - Gae!
- I know it's gae, but... - It's gae.
(Even his team members say it's gae.)
- Wait... - It's gae!
The daughter-in-law was like, "Gae!"
- Here, sir. - I was surprised.
- "Gae!" - Sir.
We'll go this way.
- Catch them! - My goodness.
Catch them!
(He throws the sticks with a shout.)
- Geol! - Gosh.
If ours had been geol, we would have been caught.
Okay.
- Above the string? - Yes.
- Above the string. - Above.
- Above the string. - Do it.
Don't cheat.
Everyone is so sensitive right now.
If they don't go above the string, it's a fail.
(It's too low.)
- It's too low. - It's too low.
It didn't go above the string.
It didn't.
(Laughing)
He's too happy.
He's really happy.
Don't think they'll go easy on us. It's not like that.
Throw them up high.
- If it's a fail... - Fail.
Fail!
(Glaring)
Why did you say that?
I said it very quietly.
- I'm sorry. - Don't worry.
- I said it quietly. - Geol.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn, and they need geol.)
- Look closely. - Geol.
- Fail! - Hey.
(Fail)
(Yelling)
Come on.
Focus.
Did you hear her voice? "Focus."
Gosh. It's driving me crazy.
Okay. You better not make any mistakes.
Her voice changed.
(The second oldest brother goes.)
It must be a fail.
- Fail! - It's a fail.
It's touching.
(His daughter-in-law steps up.)
- Hold on. - It's a fail.
Hold on.
- Hold on. - Look.
Look at this. It's not touching.
- It's obviously... - It's touching.
(Take a look.)
- It's touching. - It's not.
Hold on. She just pushed me.
Is it okay?
It's not touching.
- It's a fail. - Yes, it is.
- Okay. - He brought a camera right away.
Good job.
- You were insisting. - Good job.
Da Hee, we have to catch them.
- Yes. - What do you want?
- What do you want? - Yut would be the best.
Yut.
Either yut or mo.
- Can I throw them like this? - Yes.
- It's okay. - Right?
Hold on.
You're being too generous with Da Hee.
- Can I throw them like this? - Yes.
It doesn't matter.
Ta-da.
- If it's... - It's touching!
- It's touching! - It's gae.
- It's gae. - Should we run away?
We should listen to Da Hee.
If we get geol and then gae, we can go there.
All right.
(It's the daughter-in-law's turn.)
It's a fail.
- Gae. - Gae.
- Let's catch them! - Let's catch them!
Let's catch them.
(Laughing)
- You should run away. - Throw them up high.
(Thanks to the daughter-in-law, the brothers are ahead.)
- Geol. - Geol.
Catch them with gae and make a turn with geol.
(What?)
- Make a turn? - Yes. That's what we say.
- Make a turn? - You make turns at the corners.
- Here too. - Ma'am.
(You can make turns at the corners.)
He's using professional terms.
(He hasn't shown off all his skills yet.)
That's not okay. We'll get a back do.
(It's neck and neck.)
We'll get a back do.
- Yut! - Yut!
- He can throw them again. - It's yut.
(Amazed)
How can he get only one stick above the string?
I'm finally showing off my skills.
- I tried to copy him. - There you go.
- Gae. - Gae.
He throws one first.
- Try it. - He's stubborn.
- Throw one first? - Yes, do it.
- Just try it. - Try it.
(The old men have fabulous skills.)
(Will Kwang Soo...)
(be able to copy him?)
Wait.
(What?)
(He throws one...)
(and puts the other three down gently.)
(What is that?)
He threw only one.
He shouldn't just put the others down.
You're confusing it with another game.
You throw 1, and drop the other 3.
Let him try again. He didn't know.
Kwang Soo didn't know. You can try again.
- Drop the other three? - Just throw them.
You have only one chance.
Do it well.
Good. You threw them well.
- Geol. - Geol.
- We should catch them. - Let's catch them!
Do, gae, geol.
- We've been caught. - One more time.
Kwang Soo, good job.
I'm sorry, sir.
We caught you once too.
- You have to... - This feels nice.
catch the other team.
- Good. That was nice. - Nice.
(Kwang Soo throws a mo.)
- It's mo. - It's mo.
Throw them again first. We'll decide later.
Sir.
Good.
If it's do...
(The man makes monkey sounds.)
Hold on. Can he do that?
(It's allowed on this island.)
It's allowed.
- It's okay? - It's okay.
- Is it really okay? - It is.
- Sabotage. - Sabotage is allowed.
Of course. As long as you don't touch them.
(I have to focus.)
(Attack)
(He's so cute.)
- We shouldn't lose. - We won't.
It's a fail.
This works best.
We have to win. Otherwise, we can't leave.
It's too late to leave.
You have to win to leave.
Can I use earphones?
(The men's strategy even surprises the cheaters.)
We need earplugs.
My opponent makes sounds, and my team members rush me.
- You have only 30 seconds. - 30 seconds?
(Hurry up.)
A time limit has been added. You have only 30 seconds.
- Is there such a thing? - This is not baduk.
- Why 30 seconds? - Hold on.
There's no way we can beat them.
(The more you learn, the harder it becomes.)
Your chance is gone after 30 seconds.
Hurry up. I told you.
- I'm stressed out. - It's like baduk.
I just want to escape.
- Hurry. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo throws the sticks under stress.)
It's a fail.
- It could have been yut. - Hey.
Focus.
(Laughing)
(My strategy worked.)
He gets on people's nerves.
He's so happy. He's laughing.
(That's how we play around here.)
We need do to catch them.
(Let me show you my skills.)
(Show them.)
Here we go.
- Don't get them out. - It's a fail!
You get them out every time!
(The youngest is the least skilled.)
- He got scolded. - Okay.
Da Hee should throw yut, right?
I'm usually not that lucky.
You can do this.
It's yut!
- Throw them one more time. - It's yut!
(I'm not supposed to be good at this game.)
Throw them one more time.
- Da Hee. Pull yourself together. - Da Hee.
- Hold on. - We need geol.
- Geol. - Let's do this.
- Yut! - It's yut.
(Another yut)
- Throw them one more time. - Yut.
- One more time. - Good.
- Is it good? - Yes. Good job.
We need geol.
Yut!
(Three yuts in a row)
Da Hee!
- Da Hee, let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Three yuts. Now, we need geol.
Geol and something else.
(She can throw whatever and still be the MVP.)
Geol.
(Da Hee casually throws the sticks again.)
It's the fourth yut!
- Yut! - What's going on?
(What is going on?)
I'm getting scared now.
Da Hee.
- Da Hee. - What's going on?
- Good. - Da Hee.
Look at the men's faces.
We need geol.
- Geol. - Geol.
- Geol. - Geol!
- Hold on. - Good.
Catch them, and throw the sticks again.
What did you do?
- Da Hee. - What is this?
- How did you do that? - I don't know.
- Anything is fine. - Yes.
(Da Hee's final try)
- Do. - Do.
- Okay. - Okay.
- The tables have turned. - You did an amazing job.
- It was fantastic. - You did it.
- Now, we just have to... - Da Hee.
- We just have to finish. - It was amazing.
We just have to finish well.
- Unbelievable. - Hold on.
Ma'am, why are you glaring at me?
I didn't...
- Stop annoying her. - I mean...
- Even the way you look is annoying. - I didn't throw them.
All right. Let's go.
(The daughter-in-law throws.)
- Gae. - Gae.
We're in trouble. We need something big.
- Hold on. - Is it my turn?
- You have 30 seconds. - This is our last try.
What? It's our last try.
- Then... - A situation like this...
doesn't happen often.
Kwang Soo, please.
Kwang Soo, everything depends on you.
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, please.
Let's go home. We might not be able to leave.
(Focused)
Anything except a back do would be fine.
It's a fail!
(It works best right before throwing.)
You seem to only disturb me.
He must think I'm his rival.
- Only me... - You two...
- look alike. - That's right.
When he was young...
You two look like each other.
- You do. - Yes, you do.
- Don't they look like each other? - Even their smiles are similar.
Kwang Soo, those from up above...
- will help us. - This depends on you.
(Kwang Soo, let's go back home.)
This depends on you.
- You just need a good one. - Hurry up.
- Fail. - It can be anything...
- as long as it's not a back do. - Kwang Soo.
This depends on you!
Please, Kwang Soo.
We're being helped by those from up above.
(The mission is over if he gets mo or do. It's up to Kwang Soo.)
- as long as it's not a back do. - Kwang Soo.
This depends on you!
Please, Kwang Soo.
We're being helped by those from up above.
(The mission is over if he gets mo or do. It's up to Kwang Soo.)
Hey!
(He got mo, but it went outside.)
- Hey! - Hey.
(It's like making a dish and knocking it over.)
- Hey! - It's over.
- Are you a spy? - It's mo, but it's out.
(His distraction worked.)
(Are you sure you don't have a secret mission?)
You must be so unlucky.
(They're speechless.)
You were trying to be funny.
I can't continue. My heart...
Hey, you. What are you doing?
- It went out. - It was almost over.
- Back do, okay? - All right.
(Please get do or mo, Jong Kook.)
It's back do.
(If he gets do or mo, they can go to Incheon Airport right away.)
- It's geol. - He got geol.
Why are you doing this too?
(The guys feel really guilty now.)
- It's geol. - He got geol.
Why are you doing this too?
(The guys feel really guilty now.)
Good job. Congratulations.
Why does this keep happening?
First of all,
you won in the game of yut,
but you failed the mission.
(They won the game but couldn't win with mo or do.)
Can we play another game?
(He looks miserable.)
- We couldn't focus. - We'll try...
We'll try to tone it down.
We won't be too happy or anything.
- Sir. - We're okay.
- One more game? - In this game,
it's best 2 out of 3.
(What are you talking about?)
That's the rule.
- This is Shinshimo Island! - It can't be just one game.
- Great. - Good point.
- You're the master of this game. - That's right.
Let's select him as a human cultural asset.
Let's select this village as the village of yut.
- To get on the cruise... - His wife is here.
- Oh, dear. - Hello, ma'am.
Are you playing a game here?
- Yes, we are. - Did you hear our rules?
You have to throw it above this line.
I'm bad. Just play.
(She's jolly.)
Kwang Soo.
(Da Hee is the first to go.)
(Geol)
- Geol. - Geol.
It's okay, ma'am.
(First player on the other team is the wife.)
Here you go.
- I hope she doesn't get geol. - Please throw it above the string.
(She throws it indifferently.)
- What is it? - It's geol.
Catch her. That changes the lead.
In the beginning, you said, "I'm bad."
I'm bad.
- I'm bad. - She's good at catching up.
It's mo!
(She said that she's bad, but she gets mo.)
(Let's go, honey.)
- Sir, it's mo. - It's mo.
It's mo
- She gets another try. - One more time.
(She gets to play 3 times during her 1st turn.)
- Geol. - That changes the flow of the game.
She's really good at this.
We were going soft.
(Did you see that?)
(His wife is actually the best player.)
I keep getting geol. I hope I get yut.
(You should have ended it earlier.)
It doesn't feel right.
(Running Man doesn't have many chances left.)
- Gae. - Gae? It's gae.
Is that good? Just go around.
- You're going around anyway. - Like this?
I have a question. I'm not clear about this.
Can you move your piece after you put it down?
It's supposed to be final once you put it down.
That's how it is for us.
- We're not sure. - We don't know.
In those situations,
- you have to say, "pudong". - Sorry?
Say, "pudong".
(Pudong?)
What's that?
That means you can't move. That makes it final.
You have to say it then.
- Do we have to say it? - You can't move then.
- If we say it? - Yes.
(If you say it, the other team can't move their piece again.)
I think you made it up.
- Does that rule exist? - Just listen to him.
- Are you supposed to say that? - Just do it.
- Okay. - That's the rule.
We can do this.
- I'm starting to get dazed. - Hold on.
I'm most curious about this.
Do these people truly live on Shinshimo Island?
Didn't you recruit them?
Let's go for geol.
(He tries to focus and throws the yut.)
- This is... - It's back do.
(Back Do)
Back do.
(Laughing)
(I want to escape this island.)
Geol?
- Do I catch up to them with geol? - No, but you'll get close to them.
- I need geol then. - Geol.
- Is it geol? - It's gae.
- Okay. - It's gae.
Use this other piece.
Use the other piece.
- The one at the front. - Is it my turn?
Pudong!
- Pudong! - Pudong!
(Nice one.)
Nice. Good job.
- That's how you do it, right? - That's it, right?
- Right? - Good job.
I learned it.
- Good job. - I said it.
- You remembered. - Good job.
- Yes, sir. - Good one.
We almost got into trouble.
(With Kwang Soo's "pudong", they reclaim the flow.)
- It's yut. - It's yut.
Good job.
- It's do. - Do.
(Running Man is close behind the other team.)
I guess you play this game all the time.
Do you know what our problem is?
- The end. - I know.
- The process is good. - Where is it?
(They only have two spaces to go.)
Like this?
We're good leading up to this.
- It's do. - Do.
(They move a space.)
You need another one.
(Kwang Soo gets the last chance again.)
It's do. Kwang Soo, I gave you a turn.
- Mo or do. - It's mo or do.
I can't do this.
Kwang Soo, I gave you a chance.
- Why did you do that for? - Do it.
(You should have finished it off.)
- This is our only chance. - Oh, my.
Throw it.
(While Kwang Soo is resenting, the other team plays.)
This is up to you. Hurry up.
We can't do this.
Please say, "start" with me!
(It's finally my turn.)
1, 2, 3.
- Start! - Start!
I can feel how desperate you are.
- Mo or do. - Please, Kwang Soo.
(The team's fate depends on Kwang Soo's throw.)
(If he gets mo or do, the mission is a success.)
It's mo. It's do.
(What?)
- It's do! - But it's out.
You're going out.
(It's do, but it's outside again.)
- It's do! - But it's out.
It touched!
- It touched. - It's a fail.
What is wrong with you?
It's difficult doing that all the time.
(Wait, I've seen this situation before.)
(Don't be so hard on me. After me...)
(is you.)
- Jong Kook. - Why is it me again?
- Jong Kook. - This?
Gather your energy.
You should have ended it.
No, you'll be fine. You have the energy.
- Let's do this. It's possible. - 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3. Start! - Start!
Let's go!
(If he gets mo or do, the mission is a success.)
(If they fail the mission, they get 40 Running Balls.)
(What's the result?)
(Do)
It's do!
(They finally did it.)
(She's losing it.)
It's do!
We got do, sir.
This is seriously...
- Jong Kook. - That was so difficult.
What did I say?
Hey, we did it.
- That was the best game of my life. - That was so hard.
It's the 1st time in 33 years that I felt so thrilled.
- I sweated so much. - Goodness.
- That was the best. - Thank you, ma'am.
Thank you for your time.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
Thank you for entertaining us.
- It was so much fun. - I agree.
- We felt like a family. - That's true.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Please be well. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
(All three teams have completed their missions.)
(The conclusion of Family Package Project.)
This is bad.
Did they fail?
Se Chan, it's going to be you.
I know it's going to be me. I already think that way.
Lastly, Han Na...
picked Se Chan. So...
Hey, look.
So what does that mean?
Se Chan got the most votes...
(He got 70 more Running Balls as a penalty.)
- You'll get 20 Running Balls. - Poor you.
What did I do so wrong?
Haha's...
love, Seok Jin.
- I love you. - Hey, you...
You two talked about this, right?
I'll say it one at a time.
Jin Young...
- voted for Kwang Soo. - Really?
Jong Kook voted for Kwang Soo.
(Jong Kook voted for Kwang Soo too.)
- Da Hee... - Yes.
I won't leave you alone.
Kwang Soo.
(She also voted for him.)
- You never know. - We were thinking the same.
Kwang Soo...
picked Kwang Soo.
Really?
- Hey. - Really?
- Stop lying. - Really?
He erased it and wrote his name down.
(He's so sly.)
My gosh, I knew it.
Did you write your name instead?
(Se Chan has 71, Jae Seok has 16, Da Hee has 15, and Seok Jin has 5.)
Da Hee has 14.
(All balls are put together, and 6 are picked for Shuddering Package.)
(Once the spaces are filled, they will turn the roulettes for...)
(Luxury Package, Shuddering Package,)
(and then the people going on those trips.)
This is the end.
(Today, the destinations and the people will be decided.)
Will it be decided today?
Yes, it will be.
All right. We'll pick out the balls now...
to put people's names down for Shuddering Package.
Before we start, there's one additional rule.
Once the Running Balls are selected,
if somebody has been picked already...
For example, if Se Chan gets picked first...
and he gets picked again,
then he can pick another person...
- to join the Shuddering Package. - Pardon?
(If a name gets repeated, they can choose a person to join the list.)
Do I get to pick?
- If it gets repeated? - He'll be choosing the whole time.
(Se Chan has many Running Balls, so it's good news for him.)
You should try to avoid it.
- Get ready. - You should try to avoid it.
Everybody, get ready. You better be nervous.
All of you, got it?
He should try to avoid getting picked.
Why didn't you point at Jong Kook?
At that instant,
I felt like my finger would break.
I was going down and thought my finger would break.
(He was pointing at everybody...)
(and skipped Jong Kook.)
(His finger wanted to survive.)
Hey.
Why aren't you acting like earlier?
- I couldn't do it. - Se Chan.
He sent many messages to Jong Kook in Hong Kong.
Wasn't that edited out?
- No. - No, it'll be aired.
Did you say something to me?
You punk. I'll make sure I watch it.
(I'm so happy Jong Kook is not here.)
(Are you watching, Jong Kook?)
(He went with the flow and warned Jong Kook many times.)
(Jong Kook took the message.)
So Min too. Han Na said something too.
- Really? - I think I did something wrong.
Okay. Okay!
(Can you edit it out? Please.)
He said, "okay".
(For everybody's peace, the originals were put away.)
- Should we put them in? - Yes.
- Let's go. - All of them?
Se Chan has so many.
- Okay, I'm the lead today. - He has the attention.
Let's just enjoy this.
(Se Chan has 60 percent of the balls, so he has given up.)
(Running Balls are picked for the Shuddering Package roulette.)
(If there's a repeat, they can pick a different person.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
What now?
(Se Chan, Jae Seok, Da Hee, and Seok Jin have the highest chances.)
You have...
one Running Ball each, and imagine if you get picked.
- That's not possible. - It's up to chance.
I hope it's not me.
You never know about this.
All right.
- Why are there so many? - Catch it.
- Just pick one. - Let's go!
It's just one.
- Just one. I'll put these back. - No.
The second ball was Da Hee's.
I'll put the rest back in.
How do we do this?
(She only has 15, but she almost got picked.)
1st ball. 1st...
It must be Se Chan.
This is the first person.
(Is it Se Chan with over 60 percent chance...)
(or somebody else?)
It's Da Hee.
(What?)
(Sighing)
- Why? - I beat her.
This is unbelievable.
It's Da Hee.
- Why? - I beat her.
- This is unbelievable. - Hold on.
Se Chan has 70.
It's 70 versus 14.
- This is insane. - Get her sticker.
- It's Da Hee. - Hold on.
Stick it on the pink area.
- Next. - Please.
There's a good chance.
Spin it.
She had 14 and got picked.
Please be me.
Please be me. Please pick me, Jae Seok.
- You got it. - There it is.
If it's not me, I'm really lucky.
(Who's the second one?)
It's Se Chan.
(Of course.)
- Of course. - That was obvious.
Of course.
- Se Chan is here. - It's a formula.
- Put it on the pink. - Da Hee and Se Chan are confirmed.
If they get picked again,
- They get to choose, right? - they get to choose.
Please let it be me.
(Whose Running Ball will it be next?)
Who is it?
(Please... Please...)
- Da Hee. - Goodness.
(It's Da Hee again.)
(She gets to choose.)
Are you happy?
- Look at Kwang Soo's face. - Don't do it.
Is that all you can show me?
"Is that all you can show me?"
(He kneels down.)
You're so desperate.
"You're so desperate."
(Begging)
- "You're so desperate." - He's so desperate.
Da Hee, 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo pleaded. Who will it be?)
Kwang Soo.
(It's Kwang Soo.)
You're going on the Shuddering Package.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Things go around. - Congratulations.
I remember you picking her.
Best of luck.
Congratulations.
- Let's continue. - This is so much fun.
Da Hee?
(The fourth ball comes down.)
My gosh. What now?
The next ball was Se Chan's.
- I hope I get picked. - It squeezed out.
Let's go.
(Whose ball is the fourth one?)
- Jin Young. - What?
(What? Jin Young only had 1 Running Ball.)
- Jin Young? - You?
What do you mean?
- Didn't she have 1? - She only had 1.
Congratulations.
- You were too lucky today. - Congratulations
You have to choose.
- Jae Seok. - Is this even possible?
It's her first time getting picked for the Shuddering Package.
What's going on?
- Hey. - What is this?
- Nothing lasts. - There are two left.
(There are 2 spaces left. The 5th Running Ball comes down.)
I hope Jae Seok gets picked.
- I think I can avoid this. - Please.
- Se Chan. - Okay.
(Se Chan gets to pick somebody else.)
(Laughing)
(He's anxious.)
- Jae Seok is so cheeky. - Don't give him a peck.
- He keeps on saying, "Seok Jin". - What are you talking about?
I'm going to hit your mouth.
(They're fighting for Se Chan's love.)
- Se Chan. - Yes.
You know, right?
Don't hold his hands. Se Chan.
(He gives a politician smile.)
- Why are your hands so warm? - He's like a politician.
- I have a warm heart. - His hands are warm.
- It looks like you're campaigning. - I'll decide.
Wait.
(He wants to recommend Sang Yeob.)
- What? What did you do? - What did you just do?
It's Seok Jin.
What was that?
(He provoked Se Chan...)
(then hit his cap.)
(What did you just do?)
- Hold on. - Look at him.
Wait. Why did you hit me?
- He hit me. - Hey!
- I choose Seok Jin. - I couldn't understand that.
Why did you manipulate this?
- What did I do? - Okay.
- Seok Jin. - He tried to drag me in.
(It's Da Hee, Se Chan, Kwang Soo, Jin Young, and Seok Jin.)
- I must have been crazy. - Why did you do that?
- You never know. - I can avoid this.
Last space.
(This person will fill in the last space.)
Please. I don't want to get picked.
- Just one. - How will I live?
Please. I'm lucky.
Last space. Rest are all Luxury Packages.
(The last ball comes down.)
It's Se Chan again.
- Second ball is mine? - It's all probability.
(According to probability, Se Chan has the highest chance.)
(Even if you have one Running Ball, you can't be sure.)
(Who's the last person to go on the Shuddering Package list?)
It's Se Chan.
Okay!
(It's Se Chan again.)
What did you say to me in Hong Kong again?
(Are you talking about me?)
Oh, dear. You should have kept your mouth shut.
You should have kept your mouth shut.
You should have stayed quiet.
- Se Chan is so cool. - Why did you do that to me?
So Min. So Min and Han Na.
- Them? - Han Na keeps looking away.
Wait. Han Na and...
I've never heard Jae Seok being so polite.
- I know. - Don't say anything.
- Don't say anything. - Oh, gosh. Hold on.
This is a dilemma.
- Han Na and So Min. - Why me?
What is the problem, Se Chan?
(She's polite.)
- Why? Earlier, you were... - What is the problem?
You were happy when you were giving me 70.
What is the problem? I wanted to go to Tsim Sha Tsui.
What about Jong Kook?
Jong Kook, come here for a second.
(He's confident.)
Jong Kook?
You can put my sticker down.
(He doesn't care.)
- What's wrong? - That's not how you do this.
What's wrong?
- Are you mad? - Hey.
- Stick it on. - That's not what I meant.
Hold on.
(Put me on the Shuddering Package.)
- Hold on. - Move.
- Let go! - Don't do it.
- Resist. - Stop it.
- Stop him. - This isn't necessary.
(Kwang Soo kicks Se Chan.)
- Stick it on. - This isn't necessary.
- Calm down. - For goodness' sake.
I don't care either way. Stick it on.
It won't hurt me.
- Calm down. - Stick it on.
I am envious of him.
- How is he so confident? - Hey!
- Stick it on. - What?
- Put my sticker on it. - Okay! I will do that.
Hey.
(Is that so?)
(He attempts to imitate Jong Kook and gets chosen instead.)
Come on!
(That's not how you do it.)
- For goodness' sake. - Okay!
- It's done, right? We passed. - It's done.
- Yes! - Yes!
- I got the Luxury Package! - We did it!
- We did it. - I got the Luxury Package.
I did it once.
Where does it go?
- This is the beginning. - This is the real deal.
- Seriously. - This is the real deal.
This is the real deal.
(The Final Roulette Time determines the destinations.)
- Jin Young, you should spin it. - Shall I do that?
- Jin Young will spin it. - It doesn't matter where you go.
- All the options are nice. - Seriously.
- Any one of them will be nice. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Luxury Package, come on! - All right.
- Any one of them will be nice. - Spain. Spain.
Spain. Spain.
(Spain, the Luxury Passion Package)
(Watching La Liga, the best soccer league...)
(that stars Real Madrid and FC Barcelona.)
(Dine at Hemingway's favorite restaurant...)
(which is the oldest restaurant in the world.)
(Mexico, the Luxury Paradise Package)
(A natural hot spring cave is a healing place in the mountain.)
(Q Restaurant offers world-class fusion cuisine.)
(Canada, the Luxury Mother Nature Package)
(Bow River in Banff is a place you must visit in 2018.)
(Niagara Falls...)
(is a wonder of nature that makes you speechless.)
(A 1.35kg tomahawk steak surprises with its size and taste.)
(Switzerland, the Luxury Healing Leisure Package)
(The mountain train that runs across the Alps offers great views.)
(Enjoy summer skiing on the show of the Alps.)
(Fondue is a collaboration between soft cheese and nutty bread.)
(A luxurious and nature-friendly hotel near the Alps)
(One of them is the destination for the Luxury Package.)
(They don't know who will go,)
(but they are happy to imagine going to one of these places.)
Spain. Spain.
(What is the destination for Luxury Package?)
Switzerland.
Switzerland. Switzerland!
(Switzerland gets chosen.)
Yes! It's Switzerland!
- Switzerland. - It's a good choice.
- That's incredible. - They'll go to Switzerland?
I really want to go to Switzerland.
The travel destination for Luxury Package...
is Switzerland.
- I got goosebumps. - Switzerland.
I should take out my winter clothes.
You are right.
- Switzerland. - This is incredible.
- For Shuddering Package... - Da Hee, spin the roulette.
Let's go, Da Hee.
It will be fun if all of us go to Switzerland.
- Let's get it. - In 1, 2, 3.
The UK would be the worst because it involves wing walking.
Please don't let it be the UK.
Please.
- Please don't let it be the UK. - Please don't let it be.
(The UK, the Shuddering Extreme Package)
(Stand on the wing of an airplane that is flying at 217km per hour.)
(Wing walking offers the thrill of walking in the air.)
(What comes after this thrilling flight...)
(is a hotel that is visited by the spirits.)
(There have been many sightings of ghosts here.)
(The US, the Shuddering Thrill Package)
(It's so scary that its designer only rode it once.)
(Giant Canyon Swing throws people 400m above sea level.)
(After having fun in the air, sleep 6m below water.)
(You must swim to check into the underwater hotel in Florida.)
We have to swim.
(Switzerland, the Shuddering Mother Nature Package)
(Walk across the Alps on Charles Kuonen Suspension Bridge.)
(Enjoy a real hiking experience through canyoning.)
(Jump toward the lake from 134m above the ground...)
(by bungee jumping from a cable car.)
(The outdoor hotel at the Alps has no walls, roof, or a restroom.)
(Peru, the Shuddering Height Package)
(The cliff hotel that hangs at an altitude of 122m...)
(requires its guests to check in by rock climbing.)
(A shocking flight beyond your imagination)
(With the slingshot at Cusco, you go up 125m in 5 seconds.)
(US, Switzerland, Peru, UK)
(Which one will it be?)
- We don't want the UK. - Other options are fine.
We don't want the UK or Switzerland.
The US. The US.
- We can't wing walk. - Please.
- This is bad. - This isn't good.
(Where will they go?)
What is the destination? The UK?
The UK!
(The UK)
We can't go there. We can't wing walk.
It will be impossible.
How are we supposed to sleep in the haunted hotel?
That will be the worst.
We will sleep at the haunted hotel.
(A place that makes you shudder)
(Shuddering Package involves...)
(wing walking and the ghost hotel at the UK.)
Thus, Luxury Package will be in Switzerland.
Shuddering Package will be in the UK.
- This is bad. - It's fine if you don't get chosen.
Get chosen for the Luxury Package.
It's fine if you don't get chosen. There is still hope.
- Everyone, - Please.
the most important roulette is...
- It's that one. - That's right.
(It's time to choose the members of the two packages.)
It doesn't matter where I go.
I can't wing walk!
Let's take a look at the roulette.
I can't wing walk.
I can't watch it.
I will work harder.
I will work harder from now on.
Please give me the Luxury Package.
(The members in the chosen week will be chosen as the final.)
2, 3.
(Week 1)
(Luxury: Haha, Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Se Chan, Han Na, and Jin Young)
(Shuddering: Jae Seok, Seok Jin,)
(So Min, Kwang Soo, Da Hee, and Sang Yeob)
Three.
(Week 2)
(Luxury: Jae Seok, Jong Kook,)
(Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Da Hee, and Jin Young)
(Shuddering: Haha, Ji Hyo, So Min, Se Chan, Sang Yeob, and Han Na)
Please.
(Week 3)
(Luxury: Jae Seok, Seok Jin,)
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, So Min, and Jin Young)
(Shuddering: Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, Haha, Sang Yeob, Han Na, and Da Hee)
(Week 4)
(Luxury: Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, So Min, Han Na, and Sang Yeob)
(Shuddering: Jae Seok, Seok Jin,)
(Kwang Soo, Se Chan, Da Hee, and Jin Young)
(What is the final combination of the two packages?)
The red section is the Shuddering Package.
- Here I go. - My goodness.
- Hold on. - This is really happening.
We will have one go.
- This is happening! - We will start.
- One. - My goodness.
- Let's go. - Please.
- Please. - Hold on.
- I am about to shed tears. - Please.
- In 1, 2. - 3.
- Let's go. - Spin it with force.
(The final roulette begins to spin.)
I can't bear to watch it.
(Through this roulette, some will enjoy their time in Switzerland...)
(while the others will cry of terror in the UK.)
Here it goes.
I am here.
I won't get it.
(They show the highest level of concentration.)
- Don't go further. - No.
I got it. Maybe I didn't.
(He makes a fuss.)
(The two packages the arrow points to are final.)
(Which list...)
(does the roulette...)
(choose as...)
(the final list?)
I won't get it.
(Is it Week 1 or Week 2?)
I got it! I got it!
(Week 1 is chosen.)
(Shuddering Package versus Luxury Package)
I won't get it. I got it! I got it!
(Luxury Package: Haha, Jong Kook,)
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Han Na, and Jin Young)
(Shuddering Package: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo,)
(So Min, Sang Yeob, and Da Hee)
I got it!
I am going to Switzerland!
My goodness.
(A slot's difference on the roulette changes the members' fate)
(We love Switzerland.)
That was incredible.
- I can't believe it. - My heart is pounding.
- This is crazy. - Isn't this Week One?
- This is Week One, right? - Come here.
You jerk!
This is your fault.
Gather around if you went to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
- Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear. - Raise your hand.
- How about the crocodiles? - Raise your hand.
- I went to Osaka, too. - Osaka.
How is this possible?
That group has the best members.
- This is... - Jae Seok.
You know,
you should have sent us after the first week.
Why did you make us struggle for four weeks?
You made us harbor false hope.
We will leave as soon as your visas and the preparation for the shoot...
are in order.
This is crazy.
May I bring my children with me?
(May I bring my children with me?)
(I am sure my son, Dream, will like Switzerland.)
- Who? - Your children?
Don't do that.
Look at Jae Seok's facial expression.
If you want to bring your family with you...
To the ghost hotel?
Can my wife go on this trip instead?
- What? - She will like it.
How will she wing walk?
Can my wife go on this trip instead?
- He is ridiculous. - My wife will go in my place.
Yes Man.
My dad likes these kinds of trips.
- I think my dad will like it, too. - It's a good opportunity.
(The members for the two packages are decided.)
(Next week)
(The end of the war of TV rating notice)
(Only one scenario is chosen.)
(Who is the winner of this war?)
(However)
(It's not over until it is.)
(What in the world is this?)
(There is an array of strange outfits.)
(Stay alert until the end to avoid becoming the sacrifice.)
(The most intense and the worst shoot for TV rating notice)
(Become either the sacrifice or the hero.)
(Who is the final winner of the TV rating notice war?)
(TV Rating Notice Final, Game of Thrones)