(The 1st global project of Running Man in 2018)
(To celebrate the dawn of spring, Family Package Project is prepared.)
(6 winning members will put stickers on the Luxury Package roulette.)
(The losing team will put stickers on the Shuddering Package roulette.)
(After four races, they will decide the final destination by roulettes.)
(4 perfect guests will join Running Man for the new project.)
(They recommended destinations of Luxury and Shuddering Packages.)
(It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance. Say that you can go on these trips.)
Which trip would you like to go on?
(Spain, passion package with sports, tradition, and rest)
(The best soccer clubs, FC Barcelona and Real Madrid)
(They will watch El Clasico, Barcelona versus Madrid.)
(The oldest restaurant in the world and Hemingway's regular restaurant)
(They use a 300-year-old oven to cook the suckling pig.)
(Members will get to stay at a hotel which used to be a fort.)
(Mexico, paradise package with great food, beauty, and a chance to relax)
(A relaxing spot in the mountain, a hot spring in a cave)
(A world-class restaurant which is Mexico's pride)
(It's the one and only hotel which used to be a bullring.)
(Switzerland, snow kingdom package with a chance to experience winter)
(A snowy train that runs along the picturesque Alps)
(Skiing on the Alps at 3,800m altitude during summer)
(The perfect mix of soft cheese and various ingredients, fondue)
(The most luxurious and organic hotel in the center of the Alps)
(Canada, Mother Nature package)
(The mecca of fly fishing and the most peaceful river, Bow River)
(Niagara Falls is on everyone's list and 1 of top 3 waterfalls.)
(The Mother Nature gives them no choice but to be amazed by it.)
(An ax-steak that weighs 1.35kg)
(A night in the Rockies, 130-year-old hotel in the mountains)
(These are the luxurious trips everyone dreams of going on.)
(However, not everyone is lucky enough to enjoy these luxuries.)
(4 shuddering destinations that you only want to watch people enjoying)
(They will stand on...)
(a plane that flies at 217 kilometers per hour?)
(Wing walking gives you the thrill of walking in the sky.)
(The destination of this flight ends...)
(at the resting place of those souls that can't leave this world.)
(A ghost hotel in England where many visitors saw ghosts)
(Giant Canyon Swing which Haha and Se Chan couldn't go before)
(The creator of the swing only rode it once as it's too scary.)
(After enjoying the air, you can sleep 6m below the ground.)
(It's an underwater hotel in Florida you must swim to get in.)
We have to swim to get into the hotel.
(Is it a simple hanging bridge that connects dizzy ravines?)
(They will cross the longest hanging bridge that measures up to 494m.)
(The valley triathlon, canyoning)
(Free falling into the lake from a 134m-high gondola cart)
(Cable car bungee jumping)
(There's only a bed in the middle of the Alps?)
(An Alps outdoor hotel without walls, roof, or bathrooms)
(To check into this hotel at 122m altitude, you must rock climb.)
We will split.
- Why must we go such lengths? - Are you...
(It only takes 5 seconds to be launched as high as 125m.)
Ready?
(The deadly Cusco slingshot allows you to dangle from a cord.)
(These are everyone's nightmares, Shuddering Packages.)
Where do you get all this information?
I must do my best for the next four weeks.
(The first race is Romance Goes Away.)
(A female member will battle a male member she doesn't want.)
(If she wins, she can pair up with the member she wants.)
(If she loses, she will pair up with the member competed against.)
(Somin was the first one to try.)
(Her talent was pinching with her toes.)
(I'm okay as long as it's not you, Se Chan.)
(If Se Chan can endure her pinching, they will pair up.)
(He screamed within 0.1 second.)
(Somin gets a chance to pick the member she wants.)
(Which member will she choose?)
All right, Somin.
It's hard to choose.
Male couples will be at a disadvantage today.
- I knew it. - Really?
- Guys might pair up together? - We must avoid pairing with guys.
I will...
(The first lucky guy depends on Somin's choice.)
(To avoid pairing up with couples, they must pair up with ladies fast.)
(Which member will Somin choose?)
I want to pair up with a new face.
It's Sang Yeob.
(Do you want to be my partner?)
How about becoming the Crazy Couple?
Crazy Couple. Crazy Somin. Crazy Sang Yeob.
- Crazy Couple. - I'll protect you!
(I will protect you, Somin!)
No one has said that to me. He's the first.
(No one made my heart flutter.)
Hey, don't you think we should stop this union?
- I don't want to pair up with her, - Hanna.
but I just want to stop her from pairing up with him.
It's not that I like Somin. I just don't want you two to pair up.
- He wants to film a drama here. - That line didn't sound right.
- That line made me challenge this. - Hey.
- I know, right? - That was the worst.
- "I'll protect you." - She likes it.
- Forget about that. - This has never happened before.
This has never happened.
Somin really likes it.
- Hey. - Are you going to do this?
- Will you do it, Jae Seok? - Do you want to do it?
I would like you to challenge it.
- He has strong toes. - No.
- Why don't you try that, Haha? - Mine?
- She's really strong. - Haha, don't get involved.
(You're my partner.)
Why don't you two try it?
Are you Ji Hyo's partner?
- He's Ji Hyo's. - He's mine.
I'm really curious. What do you like about me?
(What's my charm, Ji Hyo?)
- Later. - Why do you like me so much?
- I'll tell you later. - Why is that?
I'm really curious. Aren't you curious?
All right. Sang Yeob and Somin are about to pair up,
- but let me challenge that. - Okay.
(Jae Seok will challenge the pairing.)
(Don't mess up my love interest.)
It's been ages since you did something nice for the team.
- I will... - I'm very happy about that.
- It's been so long. - I don't care who my partner is,
- but I hate this union. - That's so true.
- Somin is... - This is great.
- Let me try this. - Okay.
But Jae Seok isn't good at enduring pain.
Sang Yeob might be worse than me.
- He follows through though. - You bet.
Jae Seok can deliver when he's determined.
He might win, you know.
- By the way, Somin. - Yes?
Go back to your spot. We're not fighting over you.
(Let me emphasize one more time.)
I'm sorry, but I think you got the wrong idea here.
Don't stay in the middle. Get out of the way.
- This isn't for you. - They're not fighting over you.
This has never happened to me.
- It's not because of her charms. - It's my first time.
- She loves this kind of thing. - She does.
She likes to be pursued. I really hate this.
Hey, we're not doing this to win you.
- You have gotten the wrong idea. - Jae Seok, lean your face forward.
- Lean forward. - This isn't to win you over.
- Let's get started. - Pinch this part.
- Okay. - Pinch his cheek first.
I can't move my toes well.
- They're ready. - No, Sang Yeob.
- Get ready. - Get ready.
(Sang Yeob, don't make a sound. You must win by all means.)
(Crazy Sang Yeob promised to protect me.)
(He's my first love interest. I can't lose him.)
Start.
- Hey. - It's over.
(Screaming)
(He screams within 0.1 second and couldn't protect her.)
- Okay! Great. - It's over.
- Okay. - Hey, it's not that.
- Yes! - We did it.
- Let's do it over. - I thought...
- That was a clean game. - No, no.
- We did it. - Listen.
I screamed because I was trying to get ready.
- You lose when you scream. - Hold on a second.
- You screamed. You lost. - You lost.
Does it mean you and Jae Seok will pair up?
- I have done my job. - Okay.
- All right. - Somin said she's going home.
I did it.
(Somin and Jae Seok will be partners.)
- 1, 2, 3. - It's Da Hee.
I'm okay as long as it's not you, Seok Jin.
(Da Hee goes next.)
- There were no surprises. - There weren't any surprises.
- I knew this would happen. - I will beat you.
Da Hee wins!
I will choose Kwang Soo since no one will challenge to take him.
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee are partners.)
- You make a cute couple. - Cunning Couple.
Next up is Jin Young's challenge of putting on pants quickly.
- Putting on pants quickly. - Let's try it.
(Jong Kook is mine.)
- Jin Young. - Hey, you, Jin Young.
- Hey. - Jin Young only wants Jong Kook.
These two will be partners.
Next up is Ji Hyo.
- Well, Ji Hyo... - All right.
- My talent is... - Okay.
- saying a series of compliments. - I see.
(Ji Hyo's talent is complimenting.)
- Complimenting? - A series of compliments?
You're going to compliment someone?
I found out for the first time today that I had this talent.
- You'll give compliments? - Yes, I'll give compliments.
- You never give compliments. - You don't compliment people.
- Right. - I have never seen you...
- compliment someone. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo... - First off,
- I will pick... - Which member is it?
(Which member does she not want?)
- Anyone, but you, Haha. - Me? Me?
Really?
(She was pursuing him. What is this sudden change?)
I'll pick anyone, but you, Haha.
- Wait, no. - But you just said that...
- She will lose on purpose. - She's...
- Right? - No, Seok Jin.
- I'm wrong? - I must do my best.
- If I win, this... - What's going on?
- What's happening now? - For Ji Hyo's talent,
- you will exchange compliments. - You must take the first shot.
If you get stuck or get angry at the compliments, you will lose.
You will lose if you can't handle the compliments,
get stuck, or can't say a compliment during your turn.
- Okay. - Start.
(If Haha wins, they will be partners.)
You parted your hair nicely today.
Thank you. You look great in hats.
- You look just like your brother. - You have full lips.
The resemblance scares me sometimes.
- You look just like your son. - You're hot-tempered.
- And you are good at cursing. - Haha wins. They will be partners.
I won? I won?
(Hold on. What?)
- I'm so confused. Really? - She couldn't speak.
- She couldn't compliment you. - I'm hot-tempered?
- Right now, there aren't... - Okay.
- many ladies left. - Hold on.
(He interrupts.)
- Will you challenge it? - I will challenge this.
- All right. - He's going for it.
- I will challenge it too. - Ji Hyo, I will...
(It's been a while since someone pursued Ji Hyo.)
(Sang Yeob delivers his punch line.)
Go on.
I will protect you.
(He continues to say, "I will protect you.")
- I will protect you. - What?
He is strange.
- Go to Jae Seok! - He is strange.
He is too old-fashioned.
How about me?
- "I will protect you"? - You are too old-fashioned.
What does that even mean?
Why would you protect her?
He is too old-fashioned.
- Each to their own. - He should have been on "X-Man".
- I know. - He has the same repertoire.
This is the repertoire from the 90s.
He would have done well on "X-Man".
Now, this game may not be suitable...
for deciding on the winner.
We need a game with a clear outcome.
Let's play a game with a clear outcome.
Which game could it be?
Should I bring chairs?
- Should I bring chairs? - A game of toe-pinching.
- That's a good idea. - Let's not play that game.
- I will bring the chairs. - Okay. Bring them.
Let's not play that game.
- The thing is, - It's a good game to play.
Sang Yeob is familiar with the game.
(He reveals his toes for the second time today.)
I came up with this game.
- Somin. - I lost, but...
Partnering up with a woman puts you at an advantage, right?
- That's right. - In that case,
I have no reason not to choose Ji Hyo.
It will be harder to partner up with Hanna.
I have to win this game.
Ji Hyo will be my partner if I win,
- right? - Good luck.
I will bet my life to win.
(Somin prepares wet wipes so that they can wipe their feet.)
I won't wipe my feet.
Okay. It's individual freedom.
That's right. It's a matter of personal taste.
Gosh, my feet are sweaty from wearing the boots.
- However, - My goodness.
we need to maintain...
- a modicum of cleanliness. - What will he do?
I, the referee, will wipe his foot lightly.
Okay. Okay.
- Get ready to pinch. - In 1, 2, 3.
Get ready.
- Haha has firm cheeks. - He is ready.
(They have a toe-pinching match to partner up with Ji Hyo.)
His cheek can be grabbed easily.
There we go.
- Get ready. - Hold on. Hold my hand.
Set. Set.
(Their toes are on standby.)
Are male couples at a disadvantage?
(They have a match to avoid becoming a male couple.)
Set. Set, go.
(The match starts.)
Set, go.
(They are desperate from the start.)
- He is enduring pain. - Really?
(My goodness.)
(Their pinching turns intense.)
Let's try a different area.
I can't believe I am trying so hard.
I can't believe this.
(They end up holding out for 20 seconds for Ji Hyo.)
I can't believe I am doing this for Ji Hyo.
I am so upset.
(It looks like Sang Yeob is capable of enduring pain.)
He wants to partner up with Ji Hyo.
Earlier, he made a sound right away.
Earlier,
I didn't mean to groan.
You had better be careful.
What did I do?
I will torment you for four weeks.
Show him what you can do!
- Get ready. - I will pinch you here.
Where will you pinch him?
Set, go.
(Haha aims for the belly while Sang Yeob aims for the thigh.)
(Who has what it takes to protect Ji Hyo?)
Set, go.
He is pinching Haha's thigh.
(It's a neck-and-neck match.)
(Is Ji Hyo worth this kind of effort?)
My goodness.
(Screaming)
(Sang Yeob loses again after enduring a lot of pain.)
Ji Hyo, I will be good.
You are the best.
(Ji Hyo and Haha become a couple.)
Now...
(Sang Yeob walks away.)
Sang Yeob lost all matches.
He had a lot of chances, but...
(He planned to show his manly side...)
(and protect his image as an actor.)
- I will protect you. - He is too old-fashioned.
(His character becomes similar to Seok Jin's.)
- He lost all matches. - I know.
I lost on purpose to turn the tables.
Hanna, please come forward.
- All right. - Sang Yeob, come here.
- Sang Yeob will compete. - The three of us will compete.
Who knew you would be alone until the last round?
Sang Yeob lost all matches today.
Hanna, which game do you choose?
I choose...
the balance game.
(The balance game)
It involves palm-pushing to force your opponent off balance.
Yes.
Please say, "Anyone else but you".
My mind is set.
(Hanna has to choose from the three weakest members.)
(Which member is her least-preferred partner?)
- Jee Seok Jin, anyone else but you. - I just need to win.
I just need to win.
- Yes. He just needs to win. - He just needs to win.
You will have a chance if you win.
I will have a chance if I win. Thank you.
I will win.
This is my chance.
- We have no reason to be happy. - This is my chance.
It will be either one of us.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- She can balance herself well. - I know.
Hold on.
- All right. - Seok Jin can't stand up.
- Seok Jin. - I need to stand up.
- There you go. - I bet he will lose right away.
- Get ready. Set. - How do I...
Set, go.
(The balance game starts.)
(The fear of losing wipes a smile off her face.)
Hanna is good.
Come on.
(Sang Yeob is desperate.)
(At that moment,)
(Seok Jin loses his balance.)
(Screaming)
Hanna wins!
(She smiles once again.)
I won.
Seok Jin lost all matches today.
- Hanna. - Yes.
(Seok Jin loses as everyone expected.)
It has been decided...
that Seok Jin will partner up...
- with a male. - No, no.
- No. - It's true.
It's true.
It's over. It has been decided.
Seok Jin.
Your partner will be decided now.
Either Se Chan or Sang Yeob will be Hanna's partner.
Hanna, please pick your partner.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Whom does Hanna want as her partner?)
Sang Yeob.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
(They become a good-looking couple.)
They look good together.
(They look good together.)
I won't allow it. Come on out.
Come on out. I won't allow it.
(Se Chan seeks to defeat Sang Yeob.)
Sang Yeob lost all matches so far.
He was chosen many times, but...
He is really bad at games.
Sang Yeob lost all matches so far.
Sang Yeob.
He isn't really good at anything.
Sang Yeob, I think you will partner up with me.
Sang Yeob was chosen many times,
but he lost all matches.
If Se Chan wins,
Se Chan and Hanna will be a couple.
Hanna, I will protect you!
(He makes the same promise.)
- I will protect her! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go.
His style suits the variety shows in the early 2000s.
- "X-Man". - Sang Yeob is bad...
- at games. - "X-Man".
Get ready. Set, go.
(The match starts.)
(His face turns serious.)
- Will Sang Yeob win this time? - He looks cool when he is focused.
(If you win, you become a couple with Hanna.)
(If you lose,)
(you become a couple with Seok Jin.)
(Neither of them wants to lose.)
It will end in an instant.
(He falls into Se Chan's embrace.)
Se Chan won!
For goodness' sake.
(Se Chan and Hanna become a couple.)
Se Chan did it!
(Sang Yeob, I can't believe you.)
Se Chan!
- Se Chan! - Good job!
- I love it! - Se Chan!
You did a good job.
- You did well. - Let's play three rounds.
Let's play three rounds.
No! This can't be happening.
This is...
He definitely lost.
Why is he...
Why is he on top of me again?
Why?
Se Chan!
I waited a long time.
This is great.
Please say, "Seok Jin, I will protect you."
"Seok Jin, I will protect you."
Seok Jin and Sang Yeob become a couple.
How did this happen?
(The couples)
Let's make an emoji. Look at the camera.
(Shall we make an emoji?)
Earlier...
There you go.
(Laughing)
It's a frog.
- Does it look like me? - It's a frog.
Let's choose the skin tone.
- Make it lighter. - Let's make it lighter.
Is it wearing glasses or not?
You can change the glasses.
Oh, my goodness.
I will text it to you.
To me? Okay.
This is fascinating.
- There it is. - There it is.
Seok Jin.
(I envy you for your partner.)
Why would you be envious?
- Don't be envious. - I am envious.
Don't be envious.
All right. All right.
- We make a good couple. - I have you.
Don't they look like they are at a company athletics meeting?
I know.
I brought the head of the department to the company athletics meeting.
The principle and the P.E. teacher.
- Manager Lee. - Yes, sir.
- You're good. - Thank you, sir.
He isn't the head of the department but the founder of the company.
He is old enough to be the founder.
The founder of the company!
I am the president.
Since the couples have been decided,
it's time for the most important part of the race.
You will choose your diamonds in What Are These Diamonds?
What Are These Diamonds?
(What Are These Diamonds)
You will choose your diamonds in What Are These Diamonds?
- Da Hee, it sounds like your name. - You are the heroine,
Da Hee.
She is the heroine of the game.
Each couple will go...
into the diamond room...
and put 1 to 10 diamonds...
in the couple's briefcase.
Decide on the number with your partner,
and keep it a secret afterwards.
It's up to us to decide...
how many diamonds we take.
Having a lot of diamonds might be a bad thing.
You are right.
Let's take turns going into the room.
Jae Seok's couple can go first.
- Us? - Yes.
- Is this the briefcase? - Yes.
Go in and get as many diamonds as you want...
- from 1 to 10. - We need to decide well.
I think Jae Seok and Somin will get five.
Jae Seok will stop Somin from going all out.
- How pretty! - Listen.
There are a lot.
Having a lot of diamonds may be a bad thing.
I don't know if we should get 10 diamonds.
Should we get nine?
(How many diamonds will Jae Seok and Somin get?)
- Here are 5. - Let's get those 5 and...
Your briefcase is heavy.
Seriously.
- I bet you got five diamonds. - Your briefcase is heavy.
I bet you got five diamonds.
As you can see... Excuse me.
I can't believe Da Hee!
To guess the weight, she lifted my arm.
- She's a professional. - I can't believe her.
I bet you got five diamonds.
(Security check, sir)
As you can see... Excuse me.
That was unbelievable.
- What? - How was it?
I think they took about half.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young enter.)
We're here!
It's not always best to have more.
Let's take about 5 or keep it at lucky 7.
- 5 or 7. - Let's take half.
- Half? - Why seven?
It's a lucky number.
You sound like my grandma.
Hold on.
Only old people say that seven is a lucky number.
- Should we take half? - Yes.
How about three?
- Or... - Because we're in a love triangle?
(They were in a previous episode.)
Sure, we were menaces in a love triangle.
All I want is this one.
- Me too. - It's settled then.
Okay, sure.
Let's take a chance.
We'll either hit or miss.
- Of course. You have luck. - Let's go.
Next up are Kwang Soo and Da Hee.
This is what I think.
I feel like those two will win today's challenge.
Still, they'll end up on one of the grueling trips.
They'll also win in a dirty manner.
Let's see.
I felt the weight of Jae Seok and Somin's briefcase...
when I lifted his arm.
You felt the weight?
I did.
I felt the weight of their briefcase,
and it was heavier than this.
- Really? - Yes.
Hold on a second.
I'm sure of it. I have a knack for these things.
Take 10. What's there to think about?
I said theirs was lighter.
We can only win every battle if we know our opponents.
Get it?
What does that have to do with this?
Jae Seok and Somin...
took at least five.
- Let's take 10 then. - 10?
What if having too much gives us a disadvantage?
Should we take 10?
I'd take them all if I could.
We can only take 10 though.
Haha, how many did you take? Five?
I bet he played safe.
Since his partner's Ji Hyo, he probably took six.
- Seven. - I'm sure of it.
- Lucky 7. - 6 or 7.
(She wanted to take seven earlier.)
No one would take seven. That's too obvious.
Of course not.
I think that means Jin Young took seven.
No, I was just saying.
When you said it,
Jong Kook's face twitched a little.
Only old people care about seven being a lucky number.
You're old.
Yes, Turbo.
(Haha and Se Chan's joint attack.)
He must think of you as his friend to say that.
Why would you tell on me?
- What? - I was just saying.
- Are you really friends? - We are.
We're friends.
We went on a trip as one.
No way.
He adores Se Chan.
- Are you jealous? - Yes.
What's your secret?
(How do you get him to adore you?)
- What? - By Jong Kook.
Just grovel.
(It's simple.)
Don't try anything.
Don't try anything, and grovel.
(Groveling)
- Good boy. - That's how you do it.
(So that's what he's been doing.)
You're out early.
You easily came to a conclusion.
- That was fast. - Right.
- You took 10, didn't you? - No.
Se Chan and Hanna, you're up.
Look how flushed they are.
- They took a gamble. - You don't look great.
You went big or small. It's either 1 or 10.
- You're wrong. - It's obvious they took 10.
We weren't sure, so we didn't take the risk.
Da Hee is quite hot-blooded too.
(How did he know?)
They took 10.
5. Let's take 5.
- Let's take 5. - Sure.
(Did you hear that?)
Hanna!
Let's take three instead.
(How many did each team take?)
Okay, good.
Let's power through.
(All 6 teams have chosen their diamonds.)
We chose a number you'll never guess.
You've all chosen your diamonds.
So here are the rules of today's race.
You will steal your opponents' diamonds in today's...
Romance Goes Away.
The teams with the most and the least diamonds...
and the teams with the same amount of diamonds...
will be on the Shuddering Package.
(Teams with the most, the least,)
(and the same number of diamonds are out.)
(They'll all be on the Shuddering Package.)
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee has 10.)
It's best to have about half.
(Kwang Soo, the best liar ever)
- Nice. - We can't have the same amount.
Right, that too.
It's best to have about half.
- Right. - The remaining couples...
will win the Luxury Package.
(The remaining teams will win the Luxury Package.)
You all seem defeated.
We can't have too many or too less.
What are we supposed to do?
- What do we do? - We need to steal each other's.
Just stay back!
If you have too less, you have to steal more.
If you win a game,
you'll get the chance to view a team's diamonds...
and receive an opportunity...
to either steal some or give some of yours.
When you win, you must choose from either option.
You can't maintain your amount.
Let me reveal the number of diamonds.
Out of all teams,
the one with the most...
- has 10. - Of course.
Gosh, did someone really take 10?
The team with the least number of diamonds...
- 1? - is 1.
That's obvious too.
The number of teams that have the same number of diamonds...
is three total.
(3 teams have the same amount?)
I bet they all have five.
The same amount?
Three teams have the same amount.
I think that 3 teams have the same amount of 10.
I agree.
I see people like to gamble.
Let's head out to play the first game then.
- Sure. - Let's go!
(The diamond war begins!)
Out of all the couples here, I think only one...
- looks compatible. - Which one?
(One couple looks compatible?)
Seok Jin and Sang Yeob.
Did you know that we both turned around?
- I know. - We thought it'd be us.
We were hoping.
You'll witness our team winning today.
This is in the way.
It won't be long enough.
Of course, it is.
What are you two talking about?
- What? - She was fidgeting with this.
You'll develop feelings for each other at this rate.
Kwang Soo's ears are getting red.
(Did feelings develop after just two meetings?)
I know you want a satisfying visual,
but you look ugly after losing weight.
(The leading man is too ugly.)
- Gosh. - For a romantic scene...
- Unbelievable. - Your hair...
is too short to play a love interest.
What does that have to do with anything?
- Why does that matter? - You just...
don't look your best.
Do you know the Ernest films?
Are you kidding me?
"Ernest Goes to Jail".
"Ernest Goes to School".
"Ernest Goes to Camp".
Try putting on your cap backwards.
To the side.
Put it to the side.
To the side? Do you take me for a fool?
Who wears a cap like that?
Ask Da Hee what she thinks.
What do you think?
I think shooting the TV series wore him out.
He does seem uglier than before.
She's the kind of person that...
smiles and says whatever's on her mind.
Even my stylist said that...
you were very handsome then.
But I feel a different vibe today.
He looks like a living corpse.
(A living corpse dressed in white)
How could you call me that?
A living corpse!
Gosh.
He's not even a squid anymore.
(He'll be a ghost if he loses weight again.)
Here's the first game that'll redistribute the diamonds.
- All right. - Let's go.
The first game is Say in Three Syllables.
I'll say one syllable, and each couple will individually...
say 1 more each to make up a 3-syllable word.
The 3-syllable word?
You'll immediately be out if you fail to make a word.
For example, if I say, "Blue",
"Blue jeans".
You succeeded by making up a word.
- What about "Green grapes"? - That's good.
Somin, do you get that?
(Let's do a practice round.)
"Blue".
- "Green". - "Grapes".
That's the word I came up with.
(Da Hee's being competitive.)
Da Hee.
What's wrong with you?
Da Hee, I'm sorry!
(Has the battle already begun?)
- What was that? - Is the game on?
- Come on. - What was that?
- Unbelievable. - Why are you so on edge?
You're right about that.
She surprised me.
(Round 1 begins amidst the competitiveness.)
We'll play in the order you all decide upon.
- Da Hee should go first. - Why?
We'll go counter-clockwise.
- Are we up first? - Here we go.
Ready,
set, go!
"Ear".
- "Wax". - "Dig".
(Ear wax dig?)
What's that?
(Does it mean "remove ear wax"?)
It should form a proper word.
- Well... - What was that?
What on earth did you do?
Why would you say "wax"?
There's "earrings".
Yes, you're right.
- That was a practice round. - Kwang Soo...
It's a new game, so cut us some slack.
Okay.
Since you had to go first, I'll give you another chance later.
We're given another chance.
Do you all understand the rules now?
- What? - We get it now.
We'll start with Haha.
- Okay. - Keep the order.
- Ready, - Let's do this.
set, go. "Foot".
- "Sole". - "Of one's foot".
- "Blue". - "Colored".
"Bird".
- "Oc". - "To".
"Pus".
"F".
"Fashion".
(He spits out a random word.)
(Jae Seok scores big once again.)
- What was that? - What is he?
- Let's do it again. - "Lung capacity".
- "Fashion". - Come on.
- What was that? - Let's play it again.
Play it again.
What's wrong with him?
- "Fashion". - I thought he was talking in sleep.
Play it again. Look forward.
Look forward. Play it again.
Come on, Fashion King.
Okay.
Let's start from Da Hee and Kwang Soo again. Get ready.
- Do we always start? - You can do it.
Shall we change the order?
- Yes. - They already started.
- Shall we go in this order? - Let's start with Hanna.
- Okay. - The one whom I point starts.
- Okay. - Okay.
Get ready, set, go.
"Window".
(The first word is window.)
"Stew".
- "Bean stew". - "Window bean stew".
(The word doesn't make sense.)
(They think of something savory.)
- They lost. - "Mulberry bark paper".
- "Mulberry bark paper". - Why did you say that?
- It's over. You lost. - Why did you say that?
- They lost. - I thought of Changdeokgung Palace.
- Changdeokgung Palace? - Yes.
- It's over. - There are many answers.
It's not easy.
(Se Chan and Hanna are eliminated.)
Let's start with Da Hee next.
Get ready, set, go. "Tang."
- "Dy". - "Nasty".
- "Roe". - "Roe stew".
"Jawbreaker" could have worked.
(Jawbreaker!)
Goodness, Jong Kook.
(Jin Young can throw punches as hard as jawbreakers.)
"Jawbreaker".
- What were you thinking? - He's selfish.
We have three teams left.
- Seok Jin will start. - Okay.
Get ready, set, go. "Gui".
- "Llo". - "Tine".
"Ho".
(The first Korean word is "ho".)
- "Ri". - Time's up.
- Time is up. - First of all,
- Ji Hyo's turn was already over. - Was it over?
(Ji Hyo was so out of it.)
The game is over when it's Ji Hyo's turn.
Da Hee and Kwang Soo still have a chance.
- It's the final round. - Final round.
Let's go.
- With Kwang Soo's team? - Yes.
- We'll definitely win. - Of course.
- We'll definitely win. - Which team will start?
- This team will start. - Get ready.
- It's over if they lose. - Start. "Pine".
- "Tree". - "Pine tree".
(The word is pine tree.)
They did well.
"Bul".
(The given word is bul.)
"Guk".
(Sang Yeob, it's Bulguksa Temple.)
(Bulguk...)
"Bap".
(What is "bulgukbap"?)
What did he say?
- "Bul". - "Guk".
(They make up a new dish.)
Bulgukbap doesn't exist.
- There's Bulguksa Temple. - That's right.
- Come on. - He misheard it.
- That's good. - Okay.
- We won. - It was Bulguksa Temple.
We're looking at the big picture.
The winning team is Da Hee and Kwang Soo.
(A Korean restaurant in Changwon)
As the result of the first mission Say in Three Syllables,
Da Hee and Kwang Soo won a chance to distribute their diamonds.
Please come forward,
and find out if you're safe or in danger.
It's a big advantage.
Kwang Soo will definitely be dangerous.
- Is it necessary to find out? - We can't know.
I tell you whether you're safe. If you're in danger, I explain why.
- Listen closely. - What is it?
Da Hee is so determined even in her pose.
- They're so ambitious. - They are.
- Da Hee is obviously ambitious. - They're so ambitious.
- They could be conscious of it. - Excuse me.
Can you keep quiet? I can't hear well.
She makes so much fuss.
- She makes so much fuss. - I know.
- I'm sorry. - She's so fussy.
I'm not making a fuss. I'm asking you.
- Seriously. - She's asking you to shut it.
Please.
Hey, you jerk.
Here's your current status.
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee have 10.)
You have the highest amount. You even have the same amount.
- Really? - You're in danger.
(They have the same amount.)
(Three teams have the same amount.)
(That means 2 other teams have 10 diamonds.)
(Which are the other 2 teams that chose 10?)
Choose one team.
Open their briefcase, and count the number of their diamonds.
Then decide if you'll give more or take their diamonds.
Decide which team you'll choose.
I saw what Jae Seok did.
His team doesn't have 10 each.
We should give some to them.
- Can I take it? - Aren't you being secretive?
The winning team decided to give their diamonds...
to Jae Seok and Somin.
(They decide to give their diamonds to Jae Seok and Somin.)
Take their briefcase. Come to the front, and open it.
They can check inside the briefcase.
- Why us? - Others will see it too.
- Right. - They'll hide it.
Come on, we have 10 inside.
- They have 5. - They have 5.
(Laughing)
(Is it what you expected?)
They must have only one. I have...
- Did I make a mistake? - Kwang Soo.
Come here for a minute.
Look, Kwang Soo.
They took the ones of the same color as ours.
(They were in the diamond room at Jinhae Station.)
(Let's go with 10.)
(Just like Somin, Jae Seok acts based on his feelings.)
(1 of the 2 teams that have 10 was Jae Seok and Somin.)
Did Somin match the color to the color of your outfit?
- Yes. - Did you pick blue ones?
Yes, Somin matched the colors.
We'll give them five.
- Are they taking them out here? - If they do...
Shall we give them four?
- It means that they don't have 10. - 4?
Another team may have five.
- It could coincide. - Five might be possible.
We'll make it ambiguous and give them three.
- They're taking a long time. - I got it.
What do you think?
They could take any amount from 1 to 10.
- They have to take at least one? - Yes.
We can't know how it will turn out.
- It doesn't make a difference. - Won't you show us?
- No. - If you took one...
I'll announce the current status.
- The highest number as of now... - 10?
is 13.
(The highest number is 13.)
(7 versus 13)
- It could also increase. - The lowest is...
one.
(The lowest number is still 1.)
Two teams have the same number of diamonds.
(Two teams have the same number of diamonds.)
Was it four teams before?
- 3 teams had the same. - 3 teams.
- Now it's 2 teams. - 2 teams have the same amount?
- That's right. - What happened?
What's wrong?
- Why? - Come on.
Listen to them.
It was three teams before.
- No. - One team...
Two teams...
You're such an actor.
That means the ones that we changed...
They also had 10 diamonds. They gave out 3.
- We could lose if we stay still. - Now,
let's go to the next location for your second mission.
(They go inside the restaurant for the next mission.)
There are 3 teams that have 10.
- There were three including us. - Right.
Now we have 7, and Jae Seok's team has 13.
- No team should have the same, - Right.
but two teams have the same number.
They can't have 13,
so seven can be the only coinciding number.
Another team also has seven.
- Isn't it a one-time payment? - Really?
Isn't it...
- What? - You're right.
Come on, please concentrate.
- Da Hee. - I'm not good with numbers.
- That's why... - You seem bad in general.
I don't understand games easily.
- No. - Two teams have the same.
That's wrong, Kwang Soo. Stop confusing me.
You don't understand. Why do you keep getting angry?
Aren't there five teams in total?
Our team, Team Blue, Team Red, Team White,
and Team Red and White. There are five teams.
- Two of them... - You talk as if you understand.
- Wait, think about it. - Seriously.
1 and 2.
(Somin approaches secretly.)
1 team had 1, and another had 10.
- Right? - 3 teams had 10.
We didn't know the exact number.
We didn't know there were 3 teams that had 10.
You startled me.
Get away from us. Do you want to get yelled at?
You really startled me.
Somin.
She understands the situation anyway.
She doesn't understand anyway.
I think everyone except you understood.
Goodness.
Da Hee, wake up.
If you don't understand, don't get angry or raise your voice.
Gosh. Come on, Kwang Soo.
3 teams had 10 diamonds.
We aren't sure if there are 3 teams with 10 diamonds.
They told us.
- Did you? - I'll hit you.
3 teams had 10. The numbers coincide.
How many do you have?
Get away. What do you mean?
- Seven? - How many of what?
- Do you have seven? - No.
We don't have seven.
Why are there two teams with the same number?
- We don't understand it either. - It's strange.
(Both of them are the same.)
- It's strange. - We shouldn't talk about that.
Don't talk about that.
- Ji Hyo. - Don't talk to her.
Don't talk unnecessarily. Don't tell her that.
Don't tell her why there are two teams.
Two teams of what?
Goodness.
Stay quiet. Just focus on the game.
Sit with your partner behind you.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
- Come on. - One sits in front of the other.
Sit front and back with your partner.
Front and back?
- I don't know what's going on. - Let's sit first.
- All right. - Are we playing for food?
You can win Diamond Distribution Card and meal tickets.
Let's play a relay game called Express with Drawing.
I'm bad at drawing. I'm in trouble.
- Me neither. - Can you draw well?
No, I can't.
Hanna, I'm sorry. I can't draw well at all.
I can draw. Okay.
Look at the word that the staff gives you.
Six members will draw in a relay and complete a drawing as a group.
Four cards among the distributed cards will have keywords on them.
The other two cards will say "Mafia".
(The remaining 2 cards will have "Mafia" written on them.)
Mafia.
The members with the keyword will be civilians...
and figure out the mafias who won't know what the keyword is.
The mafias must figure out the keyword before the civilians...
discover their identity.
(Mafias must figure out the keyword.)
We must fish them out.
The civilians will get a point if they name both mafias.
If three or more teams name both mafias correctly,
they will win an additional point.
The mafias will get a point if they can figure out the keyword.
And if no one names them as mafias, they will get an additional point.
This is hard. Mafias will have a hard job.
Then the civilians can't draw in detail, right?
- It'd be easier for the mafias. - Think however you like.
- But if you're bad at drawing, - That's right.
- we might think you're a mafia. - You'll be suspected as a mafia.
4 members will know what it is, and 2 members won't know.
That's right.
We will tell you what the keyword is to those in the back.
However, your partners won't know what it is.
(The key lies in the subtlety.)
(Jong Kook, Somin, Haha, Hanna, Da Hee, and Sang Yeob will play.)
- Let's start. - Let's get this started.
- What if he wins first place? - Jae Seok's was nice.
Getting the mafia card in the first round is nice.
(6 cards are randomly distributed among the members.)
(Two of them, who don't know the keyword, are the mafias.)
You cannot discuss it among yourselves.
That's right.
- When will... - This is fun.
- The fun has tripled now. - My gosh. I don't get it at all.
Don't show it to us when you read it.
- Make sure we can't see it. - Don't show it to us.
When you put your heads down, we'll reveal the keyword.
- Put your heads down. - What could it be?
The object is this.
(The keyword is the microphone.)
This is... My gosh.
- My goodness. This one is... - It will be so obvious.
It will be easy to spot.
But we never know how this will pan out.
- Let's start. - Go ahead.
(Jong Kook starts.)
Jong Kook will start acting now.
- Is he a mafia? - It looks like...
(Thinking)
(He's still thinking?)
Seeing how Jong Kook is thinking about this for long,
- He must be the mafia. - Jong Kook seems...
It seems like he's struggling.
Jong Kook, do you want to take a break?
Is that a facial expression?
(Is he the mafia?)
Okay.
- This game keeps us on our toes. - If you are a civilian,
- you must show us that you're one. - We will know anyway.
When you're drawing it, you should be reasonable.
(After thinking hard about it, he draws a circle.)
- I see. That. - Now, I get it.
You get it, right?
(Did he draw that for a reason?)
- He wants them to continue with it. - It's so round.
- It's not continuous. - She can continue with it...
- if she knows what it is. - Didn't I do a good job?
When Jae Seok was drawing it,
- his picture wasn't all connected. - That's right.
- But this is... - Someone can continue with that,
- but that person has to know. - She didn't draw it.
Someone can connect it later.
No, that was a good addition.
- That was good. - Somin is imaginative.
Somin, my gosh.
Somin, I think you did well.
I don't know what she is, but she did well.
(Haha starts drawing without a hint of hesitation.)
- Hey, what's up with you today? - Is that a man with glasses?
(A man wearing glasses...)
- Why didn't you say it out loud? - That's Jae Seok.
- That's Jae Seok's mouth. - My gosh.
- That's Jae Seok's mouth. - That's Jae Seok.
Wait a second. He's drawing it while looking at Jae Seok.
- I get what he's trying to draw. - I see.
(Did Haha draw Jae Seok, the host?)
Okay, I got it.
- Haha. - That was smart.
(Yu Jae Seok)
Okay.
Great.
It's Hanna's turn. Look, everyone. She's really smart...
from my experience.
- She's drawing stars. - I see.
(Hold on. She's drawing stars?)
- It makes sense. - Yes, it does.
- It's logical. - I see it. That's right.
- Hanna is good. - The stars fit.
That's my wife.
(Hanna drew stars all over the drawing.)
It's Da Hee's turn.
(No one seems suspicious so far.)
She had been fooled once.
- What's wrong? - What should I do?
What was that? Was that part of her act?
If that was, she's one good actress. What is that?
(What did Da Hee draw?)
- What is that? - My gosh. "Laughing out loud"?
(Laughing out loud?)
- "Laughing out loud"? - I think she's a genius.
This makes sense.
- This fits with the keyword. - That makes sense.
(If she's a civilian, she must draw things to prove she's one.)
- That can fit. - That's right.
- This could work. - Exactly.
(It seems as if she knows the answer.)
I get it. This makes sense.
- This is understandable. - It works.
I don't get this one.
- It took a weird turn. - I can't see it.
If you're a civilian, you must show that you are a civilian.
(Sang Yeob draws an image of a microphone.)
We completed a drawing together.
(Which members are the mafias?)
The civilians can write down the names of the mafias.
(Mafias have to write down the keyword.)
My gosh, seriously.
What should I do?
The mafia game is so fun.
- This is so much fun. - It's fun.
It's a fun game to watch too.
- It's fun to watch too. - Everyone can...
This week's episode is fun to watch.
- Make sure you watch it. - Stay tuned!
(Stay tuned)
It's so funny!
(Falling)
Somin, you and Haha can't get along.
(Was that obvious?)
- She was uncomfortable, right? - Yes, she was.
That was uncomfortable, wasn't it?
All right. The keyword was...
You won't be able to figure it out.
- It was a microphone. - That's right. A microphone.
The mafias...
(Then who are the mafias?)
(It seems as if everyone knew the keyword.)
(It seemed difficult because no one stood out as a mafia.)
(Who are the mafias?)
They were Somin and Da Hee.
- You weren't the mafia? - My gosh.
You weren't the mafia?
(Somin and Da Hee were the mafias.)
- Hanna wasn't the mafia. - It was Da Hee?
Hanna.
- I wrote Somin's name, - Hanna.
- but changed it last minute. - Hanna, you were so good.
- My gosh. - You were acting.
- Didn't Da Hee wrote that to rhyme? - Did you get it right?
- I thought it was for rhyming. - People think differently.
- I thought you were a mafia. - This is incredible.
- I thought that was a sign. - My goodness.
How did you manage that, Hanna?
- Did you know the keyword? - No, I had no idea.
- I thought you did it to rhyme. - I didn't know.
- It's the top of the microphone. - That's right.
(Jong Kook drew the top part of the microphone.)
- Somin drew the sun. - I just drew the sun.
- It was good to that point. - It was good.
- It looked like a microphone. - It looked like the sound waves.
- The sound waves. - That's right.
- The sound was coming from it. - This was...
- He's the host. - Jae Seok holds the microphone.
- He's the host. - Haha did well.
- Haha did great. - On this drawing,
Somin drew the squiggly lines.
I thought it was my chance to confuse the others.
Singers are like stars, and they hold microphones.
You were trying to mislead them?
- Yes. - You went a step further.
- I wanted to look like a mafia. - I did suspect her.
That's why a lot of people named you as a mafia.
- My gosh. - Hanna.
You did well. We'll get more points.
(She stopped the mafias and other civilians from getting points.)
The sun confused me.
- I didn't know what it was. - She got lucky then.
I thought about what to draw, so I ended up writing this instead.
- I had nothing to draw. - I thought that...
- she was a civilian. - I thought that it was a good sign.
- I thought she knew the answer. - She really got lucky.
- Microphone. - I drew an obvious one.
I just drew a microphone.
- It's the microphone stand. - I didn't know it was a microphone.
No one has guessed the mafias except Hanna.
Hanna won this mind game.
- Hanna, you were so cool. - My goodness.
Hanna figured out that the mafias were Somin and Da Hee.
Only Hanna and Se Chan will get one point.
- Okay. - Oh, no.
(Only Se Chan and Hanna get 1 point.)
She was amazing.
- Hey, look at that. - This is confusing.
(Intense 2nd and 3rd rounds ensued.)
(After guessing the mafias, Haha and Ji Hyo lead with 4 points.)
(Final Standings)
(Haha and Ji Hyo acquire a Diamond Distribution Card.)
All right.
As of now, you two have...
(Where do Haha and Ji Hyo stand in the race?)
the least number of diamonds which means you are in danger.
However, you don't overlap.
(They only have 1 which puts them last.)
(We must take diamonds from other teams to avoid being last.)
(Haha and Ji Hyo choose Se Chan and Hanna's briefcase.)
Se Chan. Hanna. Give us your briefcase.
- Ours? - My gosh.
Hanna.
(They chose our briefcase?)
As of now, the team with the most diamonds has 13.
- It hasn't changed. - It's still the same.
The team with the least diamonds has three.
(The lowest number is 3.)
Only two teams overlap.
(2 teams overlap.)
13 and 3.
- It means you gave them 2. - That means Haha had 1.
They took 2 from a team that had 5 diamonds.
(How many diamonds did Haha and Ji Hyo take?)
(It's time to eat after the game.)
Let's dig in.
My gosh, what's all this?
(The excellent meal is extravagant.)
There's so much food for the excellent meal.
You have beef?
(Haha, Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, and Somin get the excellent meal.)
There's a huge gap.
- This is great considering. - Hey, this looks great.
Poor Jin Young and Jong Kook.
(Soy sauce, dried laver, and rice)
- Do you want to switch? - No.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young get the poor meal.)
Enjoy your modest meal.
- Eat a lot of your poor meal. - Enjoy your food.
- Enjoy your meal. - Enjoy your food.
Thank you for the food.
(Munching)
- Isn't it good? - It's good.
(Meat never fails us.)
(The more they eat, the healthier they feel.)
They serve great mung bean sprouts.
- The rice itself is really good. - Mung bean sprouts are the best.
Hey, can we...
get some sesame oil?
Sesame oil.
- Don't we deserve sesame oil? - That's a reasonable request.
- I really want some meat. - It's so good.
I want some pumpkin.
- Does anyone want some meat? - Yes, me!
- Me! - I'd like some.
(Yes! These people would like to get some meat.)
Me too.
If anyone wants to eat this meat...
If anyone wants to eat this meat,
you can endure the toe-pinching.
Then I'll give you a piece of this meat.
You'll pinch each other's.
- I'll do it. I can endure it. - Okay.
Which area will we pinch?
I will give a piece to anyone who doesn't scream or frown.
I will do it. Are you game?
(I'm game.)
I wasn't going to do it, but I'll do it because it's you.
I won't lose. I never lose at this kind of game.
I won't skimp out on it. I'll give you the whole chunk.
- The whole chunk? Okay. - Yes.
- Sang Yeob, you can do it! - Okay, Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Bring the meat.
Why am I doing this twice today?
(He's doing the toe pinching twice today.)
Where are you going to pinch me?
Your arm.
- I'll do the same. - Hold on.
I'll record it for you.
In slow mode?
(They use a high-quality camera for an accurate judgment.)
All right.
I'm strong.
- I won against Shinhwa before. - I'm looking forward to this.
Kwang Soo is really strong.
- I'll try. - If you scream first, you lose.
- You can't frown either. - Okay.
This is super-slow mode. Go.
Ready.
(A man's pride and a chunk of meat depend on these toes.)
Set, go.
(Start)
(They start attacking fiercely.)
(Their faces look peaceful.)
Smile, Sang Yeob.
- You can win. - His face is red.
(They said they'd pinch the arms, but he goes for the neck.)
- Sang Yeob. - Do I have to...
Do I have to do this to eat?
(This won't work.)
(Fluttering)
That one's good.
What was that?
That was super-slow mode.
- Didn't we win? - Right?
Slow.
It's slow mode. It works.
(According to the detailed review,)
(Sang Yeob frowned first.)
Who won?
Sang Yeob wins.
But I didn't make any sound.
But Sang Yeob wins.
(Sang Yeob wins regardless.)
(I endured the pain without making any sound.)
(How could this be?)
Lee Sang Yeob.
I didn't make any sound.
That's not the important part.
That's what the game was about. Why is it not important?
Why did I lose?
Because Sang Yeob is handsome.
(Do you really want to know?)
(The answer was already given.)
(Sang Yeob gets a chunk of meat because he's handsome.)
Can you take a picture for us?
(It's photo time with Somin and the meat.)
Why did I lose?
Because Sang Yeob is handsome.
(Kwang Soo lost because of Sang Yeob's handsome face.)
I think my mom will cry if she watches this scene.
Everybody, here's a chunk too.
We'll play a game and see who can get the shortest spinach.
How do you play it?
Female and male?
You'll start from both sides and try to make it the shortest.
I'll do it.
No.
(We'll withdraw.)
Hold on.
- No. - She doesn't want to do it.
She said "no".
(I'm a vegetarian today.)
There's grilled short rib,
duck, and the pumpkin too.
Pumpkin too.
Deal. Let's go.
(Let's do it.)
- Let's go. - But...
- Be quiet. - Ask me.
Just do it. Go.
- Why would you do that? - Let's go.
- You have to do it. - Is that all you're going to eat?
(This is driving me nuts.)
Hurry.
(He stands up eventually.)
Jong Kook came forward.
How is that possible? She made him do it.
That's not it.
They have so much ambition. How can we beat them?
We can.
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee are the ambitious giants.)
- Who will go first? - The spinach is really good.
Is it?
- We will... - We have to pick one.
Pick a spinach.
(They pick their spinach.)
(Which one is better?)
- Do you want this one? - Which one's long?
Do you want to use a bean sprout?
It's not that strong.
Let's go.
- Hold on. - What?
(Hold on.)
- Kwang Soo. - What?
Did you eat something?
(Look at him.)
What?
Did you eat while I was picking a spinach?
What are you?
(You're so sneaky.)
Swallow. We have to play the game.
(How did she know?)
(Da Hee was focused on picking a spinach.)
(He left and had a spoonful of rice.)
(He was planning to eat spinach after as a side-dish.)
(He got caught.)
Swallow. We have to play the game.
She keeps on nagging.
(He clenches his teeth.)
She told me to play the toe pinching game earlier.
Meanwhile, she finished the seaweed soup.
(She told him to play the toe pinching game.)
(How did he know?)
(Earlier when Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob were playing a game)
(Slurping)
(I'm going to eat regardless of what happens to him.)
You guys have so many problems.
You have too many issues.
(You can't stop their sneakiness.)
Do you see this? There's grilled short rib,
duck, and pumpkin.
It's hard to cut the spinach.
You can't finish it. You have to leave some.
Of course.
If there's some stem left, it counts.
It counts.
(The ambitious giants are ready.)
Start.
- Let's start. - Ready.
Ready.
Go.
(The spinach game starts.)
(Oh, my eyes.)
(The duck is ours.)
Their lips touched.
(Sighing)
Cut it.
- They did it. - Please.
There's some left.
(There's only a trace left.)
It's this.
(It's the power of ambition.)
Jin Young and Jong Kook are next.
You have to be pretty close.
That's my tip. You have to be close.
(It's my turn.)
We don't need a long one.
Come here.
(Bite this.)
Do we have to do this for meat?
Is your heart pounding?
(It's just a game.)
Goodness.
Don't get your feelings involved.
It's a game to get meat.
Stay still.
He listens to her.
Stay still. I'll go to you.
- I'm coming. - Hey.
(The spinach game starts.)
- Hey. - Gosh.
(I have to see this.)
They might win.
This is no joke.
(Cutting)
Bite. Bite.
Cut it.
Don't move.
(Cutting)
- We don't know yet. - I think it's a tie.
- This is close. - We don't know yet.
- I think it's a tie. - This is Da Hee and Kwang Soo's.
We have the stem.
Why did you chew on the stem?
(For goodness' sake)
- The stem... - It should have been the leaf.
Is it my fault that spinach has stems?
No, don't cut it.
(She uses her nails to cut it while she's talking.)
- No, don't cut it. - Hey, Da Hee.
You cheater.
- Goodness. - She can't do this.
She was cutting it.
- She cut it? - She did.
You look good with Kwang Soo.
It's close. We didn't lose.
It's kind of close.
(What's the result?)
(Jong Kook and Jin Young win.)
Jong Kook wins.
Let's go. Come.
Jong Kook likes it.
Jong Kook met a good woman. She's feeding you.
- You met a woman who can feed you. - That's right.
I want to play the game with Sang Yeob.
(She tries to squeeze in.)
What? Me?
- Why would you do that? - Why would he do it with you?
My gosh.
- Open up. - "Open up."
(Dashing)
Goodness.
(They have no meat, so they need to eat more rice.)
They're fighting over this.
Are you kidding me? Hey.
(The two actors are fighting over plain rice.)
The seaweed soup is mine.
(We'll give you extra rice.)
- Oh, dear. - How's this?
If you can imitate a duck, I'll give you some duck meat.
What? Imitate a duck?
- Can you do a duck? - A duck?
That's Donald Duck. Are you trying to do this?
(Flapping)
(It's the real duck.)
My goodness.
She's an expert at imitating.
What's this, Somin?
(Everyone has a hard time mimicking the sound of a duck.)
- What's that? - Donald Duck.
- What's that? - A duck.
(What are you doing, Hanna?)
What are you doing, Hanna?
(Hanna is shameless.)
(Hanna, you can do anything you please.)
That's the best. Who else can make the sound?
Can anyone do it better than Hanna? Or else, I'll give it to her.
No one can be better than her.
Whoever does it, I'll give it to you.
- I wouldn't pretend to be a duck. - Okay.
- I'll walk with confidence. - Go ahead.
(He quacks like Jang Hyuk.)
(He makes a surprise attack as Jang Hyuk.)
"Un Nyeon!"
(Their talents come together as a fantastic show.)
(This is great.)
- That's funny. - Didn't he do a good job?
Yes, that was hilarious.
- Who else... - Wait!
Go, Jong Kook.
(She's very resolute.)
(Do I have to make a duck sound?)
Me?
He'll do it.
(She forces him to do it.)
Our team will go.
- Will Jong Kook do it? - Here he goes.
(Jong Kook never volunteered to do a mission like this.)
(He does it.)
Look.
(He writes a new history on Running Man.)
Look at his leg muscles.
(Jong Kook duck is strong.)
(Give some duck meat to Jin Young.)
Jong Kook does it.
(Jong Kook has changed after meeting Jin Young.)
He normally wouldn't do that.
- Why do I find it so moving? - I agree.
I almost cried.
- Jin Young is... - She's a trainer.
Seriously.
- You're on the show for four weeks? - Yes.
(You're on the show for 4 weeks?)
(The next 4 weeks will be like 4 years.)
Take care of him, Jin Young.
Don't worry, I'll be responsible.
(I don't know anymore.)
Hanna and Jong Kook did well.
Jong Kook is the best so far.
- Why? - Wait.
Da Hee disappeared.
Where did she go?
She said, "Do I have to feed you all the time," and went in.
- That's amazing. - I'm jealous.
There she is.
- My goodness. - She overdid it.
My goodness.
Look at her.
She overdid it.
Goodness.
(She has a bad feeling about this.)
(He's speechless.)
(Gosh, Da Hee.)
Keep your head up, Kwang Soo.
Look at her directly.
Keep your head up. She's working so hard.
Come back, Kwang Soo.
(I have to go.)
(Keep going without me.)
(He wants to turn away from Da Hee's efforts.)
Take care of your partner.
(He feels embarrassed for the first time.)
Come back, Kwang Soo.
(She was thorough in her preparation,)
(but something seems pathetic about her.)
Kwang Soo.
- After two times... - She works so hard.
(Jae Seok brings it for Da Hee.)
Go back in.
(Da Hee worked hard until the end.)
(Jae Seok approaches her with the savory duck.)
Jong Kook will eat the meat.
(He says it clearly.)
(Jae Seok makes a very objective judgment.)
Da Hee, go in and return the jacket.
I even squatted.
Da Hee, go back in.
- Goodness. - Da Hee.
She's crying.
- Why is Kwang Soo so embarrassed? - Hey.
I was never turned off by someone so instantly.
It was embarrassing.
I did it so that you could have some meat.
(After her first difficulty, their meal is over.)
This is where the World Shooting Championship...
Changwon will be held this coming August.
(It's the place where the championship will take place.)
Is that water? What's that?
- What? - Is there a penalty?
(Water bombs for 6 people)
- No way. - It's not time yet.
- It's so cold today. - Come on.
I will protect you from water.
I'm suddenly cold after seeing the water.
- It gets cold when there's water. - It's suddenly so cold.
It's the last round of Romance Goes Away.
It's the last mission to find true entertainment experts.
It's called Rank the Numbers.
(Rank the Numbers)
- "Rank the Numbers"? - What's that?
We need a chance to turn the tables.
It's based on response from 200 single people from age 20 to 39.
The team that guesses...
answers that ranked first the most wins.
This is important.
There are seats numbered from 1 to 5 under water bombs,
and there's one penalty seat.
Upon hearing the question,
take a seat based on the answer that ranked first in 30 minutes.
Answer and penalty seats will get the water bomb.
(Water falls on answer and penalty seats.)
The person who answers correctly wins a point.
- You can get a point? - It's better to be correct.
I like this.
Somin is an entertainment expert.
I know all about romance.
The first question will be given to women.
- Women including Sang Yeob. - Sang Yeob is considered a woman.
Somin, you're an expert. Answer it correctly.
Okay, Jae Seok.
- Here you go, sir. - Okay, thank you.
- Thank you, Manager Lee. - You can do it.
- This question was asked... - Let's go.
to 100 single women from the age 20 to 39.
You must answer it correctly, Somin.
The first question will be on the monitor.
"Which comment that men make turns you off?"
- Okay. - I know this.
It's number one.
- Right. - It's unclear.
I think it's number four.
(Somin guesses number 4.)
Number one.
Isn't this it, Ji Hyo?
(Isn't it number 1?)
- Women hate number one. - Okay.
- Which one? - Which comment turns you off?
- It's a comment that turns you off. - Right.
- "I'm not in the mood to talk." - Which one do you think it is?
Number two?
Saying "I'm busy," makes women feel bad.
It's not a comment that turns you off.
- No. - It's either 4 or 5.
Listen.
How about each of you say a line?
- They'll do it. - Say a line each.
Number one.
"Fine, let's say that I was wrong."
- Goodness. - "Let's say that I was wrong."
(It's a big turn-off.)
Even I feel angry.
(He's my partner, but it's terrible.)
How about number two?
"I don't feel like talking."
Women would casually say, "Okay."
- What about number three? - That sounds okay.
I don't think that's it.
- I don't think it's number two. - "I was busy."
- How about number three? - "I was busy."
- "I don't feel like talking." - Right.
- They hate number one the most. - Right.
How about number four?
"What's wrong this time?"
("What's wrong this time?")
- It's terrible. - I hate this one.
I hate it too.
He hates it too.
What about number five?
- Here's number five. - Go.
"I said that I'm sorry, so what's wrong?"
- I feel upset. - Come on.
- They're good. - It gets more confusing.
Excuse me.
Aren't you upset by who said them?
They seem upset by men who said them.
- Didn't I sound too realistic? - Right.
It could depend on the man's looks.
Are you ready?
- Get ready. - It may be unexpected.
- Set. - It's up to you.
- Number two? - I'll go, Jong Kook.
- Here I go. - Get ready.
Start.
Somin, Somin.
- Number one is empty. - Why doesn't anyone take it?
(Run fast, Somin.)
(It's my seat.)
Somin, come on.
(Only the penalty seat remains.)
Look at Somin.
Come on.
I couldn't take that seat.
It's not number three.
(Sang Yeob 1, Hanna 2, Jin Young 3, Da Hee 4, Ji Hyo 5)
(Shall I take my chance?)
- Hey. - Da Hee.
How dare you do something so terrible?
(How dare you do something so terrible?)
You.
- Get off my seat. - "How dare you..."
"do that"?
Where did you learn it?
"How dare you do that?"
She learned it from Running Man.
Somin, have you done something terrible to Da Hee?
No, you can't do things like this.
- Seriously. - What she said is what guests...
say that turns me off the most.
(Her comment turns him off the most.)
- That was incredible. - What's wrong with you?
"Where did you learn this from?"
- No. - I'm dumbfounded.
Responded by 100 single women from age 20 to 39,
which comment that men make turns you off the most?
35 percent of women chose the comment that ranked 1st.
(35 percent of women chose the comment that ranked 1st.)
It's number four.
It's number one.
1, 2, 3.
What?
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee answered correctly.)
- It's number four. - I knew it.
It's number four.
- I knew it. - Number four is correct.
(Somin gets scolded and drenched.)
It was number four, Somin. You should have taken the seat.
- It's because of "this time". - I know.
- Right. - That's what they hate.
The phrase "this time" makes you feel bad.
When we said the comments out loud,
- people reacted immediately. - Right.
What Jae Seok suggested was very helpful.
You reacted, but the staff also reacted.
- They reacted a lot. - Right.
"What's wrong this time?"
(It sounds terrible.)
- That comment makes you feel bad. - Really?
Ji Hyo seems particularly sensitive to it.
- The phrase "this time"... - Right.
- hurts women's feelings. - "What's wrong this time?"
Is it okay without "this time"?
"Why are you doing that?" is okay.
Not "What is it this time?"
That makes me sound like a weird person.
I get disgusted by that.
- What if we say it more politely? - How?
"What is it this time, ma'am?"
(He sounds like an old person.)
I think it's good.
Why would you do that?
That doesn't make you feel bad, right?
"What is it this time, ma'am?"
(It sounds old but friendly.)
On the other hand,
is there something women say...
that make men feel bad?
- I have one. - What is it?
"You're so ugly."
(It comes from experience.)
Really?
In what way?
It was a serious situation.
What about this?
"What do you know?"
- I think I know what you mean. - "What do you know?"
Maybe you got looked down a lot.
"What do you know, Se Chan?"
Why are you tearing up?
Why can't I just speak?
"What do you know, Se Chan?"
What do you mean? I know how things work.
- "What do you know?" - Did women say that to you?
And this too. "You think you're a man?"
"You have some pride of a man."
- Se Chan, whom did you date? - Men hate that.
Hey, bring her here.
How are you doing?
(I'm sorry for thinking I was a man.)
- "What do you know?" - I know.
- "What do you know, Se Chan?" - "You think you're a man?"
He has resentment.
Next question...
was also answered by 200 unmarried men and women...
between the age of 20 to 39.
Okay.
- Here's the question. - We have to win.
"Looking at my ex's social media".
What about number four?
- That one's insane. - That's not the answer.
Number two is really bad too.
"Asking for old gifts back".
- Goodness. - What a loser.
I get so disgusted by that.
Pretending to be happy?
The top choice had 40.5 percent of votes.
They were adamant.
- 40 percent? - Excuse me,
but I apply to all of these cases. What do I do?
- What you think is the worst. - You did all of them?
I did all five of them. Which one do I choose?
Number four is really bad.
I know. Who asks for the gifts back?
- Jong Kook. - People do that.
- People do that. - It happens.
- Expensive gifts. - Don't look down on them!
(Those people do exist!)
Just because you don't do it, don't look down on those who do.
- Gosh. - Some people do that.
"Don't look down on them."
Please pick a representative.
- All right. - I'll go.
- Somin. - We can do this.
- People do that a lot. - Can you give us three points?
- Which one? - You can do whatever you think.
(Go with number 4.)
- It's up to you. - Okay.
- It's up to you. - You can pick whatever.
- Get ready, set... - Be quick, Somin.
(One person from each couple runs towards the answers.)
Somin.
- Somin. - Take the other one.
(They get to the spot without fighting over it.)
(Only Da Hee didn't get a spot.)
- No way. - Da Hee.
- What? - Steal it.
- Should I steal it? - Da Hee, steal it.
Steal it.
(Okay, I'll do that.)
(Give me that cushion.)
Steal it.
(She takes Hanna's cushion and runs away.)
Go back.
Stop it. Bring it back.
You told Somin not to do it earlier.
Sit down.
That wasn't nice. I'm sorry.
You're pretending to be nice.
You told Somin not to do that.
You're doing the same thing.
Hey.
- Were you going for number five? - Yes.
Do you want to stand here on behalf of me?
The rules don't allow that.
- What? - The rules don't allow that.
Really?
You can do that.
- But the director said... - They said you can do it.
Can I do that once then?
He said you can't do that. We can't?
- I didn't say anything. - We can't?
Whom are you talking to?
- He said no. - He said we can't?
He's sneaky. No, Da Hee.
- It's not true. - No?
- Can we switch once? - Do it.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, let's do that.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo loses.)
He lost.
(No? We can't do this either?)
I didn't say anything.
(The director doesn't know what to say.)
(We really can't?)
(We can't do this?)
Whom are you talking to?
Forget it. I'll go back.
He said we can't do that.
I'm telling the truth, Da Hee.
Oh, gosh.
(You're impossible. I'll do it.)
Goodness, Kwang Soo.
I love how filthy you are.
- Here's the answer. - Okay.
It's unlikely, but let's go with number three.
- Let's go. - One...
(1st choice had 40.5 percent of votes.)
- Number 5. - 2, 3.
(Who will take the water bomb along with Da Hee?)
Three.
(Haha and Ji Hyo get it right.)
- Haha. - Yes.
(My partner is the best.)
Let's go to Switzerland.
They said we can't do that. The rules don't allow that.
- Stop it. - That's what he really said.
The most pathetic move was number one.
But it's the easiest to act on.
It's also cowardly.
That's why it's 40 percent.
Everybody does it.
All right. Let's ask.
What about you, Hanna?
Two things applied to me.
Number 1 and 5.
Many people use KakaoTalk.
What kind of profile photo would you post to look happy?
Pictures of me on trips.
(It's perfect to look happy.)
That's so classic.
- With a nice scenery. - Where you look happy?
- What about you, Da Hee? - Sorry?
How many applied to you?
(Well...)
- Maybe all of them? - All of them?
- All of them. - I see.
No, four of them.
- Which one didn't you do? - Which one is it not?
I can't date somebody I don't like out of anger.
I love myself too much, so I won't do that.
I can't do it out of anger.
I plan how I date people.
What about not dating?
Maybe do something out of anger.
- Eat something out of anger. - I know.
- Eat by myself. - Out of anger...
Punching yourself out of anger.
That works.
(Punching)
"What a fool."
Hold on.
They asked for old gifts. It wasn't me. It was my ex.
- Did you give them back? - Yes.
- Really? - That's cheap. Just give it back.
You're asking for them back...
not because you want the gifts,
but you're making an excuse to see the other person again.
(You're trying to see the other person again.)
You're trying to see them again?
That's pathetic.
- That's more pathetic. - That's pathetic.
- How pathetic. - You're pathetic.
What do you know, punk?
- It's because you love her so much. - Why would you do that?
Just call them.
It's because you love her so much.
Worse thing is...
getting the gifts back...
and posting them online to resell them.
(That's even more pathetic.)
- That's the worst. - Hey.
(That's so pathetic.)
When my friends broke up,
we would go to them and share the gifts.
If you broke up,
all my friends would go together and take the gifts.
"I take this."
(What?)
I'm sorry for saying this, but why did you do that?
Why would you take your friends and blow it out of proportion?
They don't need the gifts anymore,
so we divided them.
- That's possible. - You won't use them again.
- It's possible. - Give us one last question.
Last question.
Give us 2 to 3 points.
Should we make this two points?
- Give us 2 points. - Let's do 2 points.
This question is worth two points.
- That sounds good. - Pick a representative.
This question...
was answered by 100 unmarried women...
between the age of 20 to 39.
That's an advantage for us.
Unmarried women?
This is what women think.
(What is something men do that makes your heart flutter?)
I read this somewhere a few days ago.
- It's something small. - This is so difficult.
Isn't it number one? It has to be.
I say number five.
(I pick number 5. I'm certain.)
- What is it? - Number four.
Did you pick one person?
Don't women like it when somebody you like pats your head?
Some people hate getting their hair ruined.
- Should we start? - Yes, let's go.
- Did you choose one person? - Yes, we did.
You have to win, okay?
She gives me an order and leaves.
But she's always wrong.
Jong Kook is always right.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Please step on the white line.
You automatically lose if you cheat.
- Get ready. - Jong Kook, how far are you going?
What?
I think we're going in different directions.
Do you think so?
We're going in different directions.
Please step on the white line. If you cheat,
you automatically go to number six.
Set...
(They run towards the spots.)
Kwang Soo.
(Number 1, 2, and 3 didn't involve much fighting.)
Please, Jae Seok.
I sat down.
(Sang Yeob ran to the penalty spot, so he has nowhere to go.)
(He's forced to receive the penalty.)
Sang Yeob!
- What do we do? - Lies! This is a lie.
I hope I'm right.
We'll turn the game around. This is the final round.
I think it's between number 3 and 5.
- No, it's number five. - Really?
It's number five, Jae Seok.
This might be right. It's the most simple.
- I know. - Number two?
- Number 2? - What if it's 5?
(This question is worth 2 points. If you get it right, you win.)
(What is something men do that makes your heart flutter?)
- Two... - This is the final round.
Kwang Soo.
(Which couple will get the question right in the final round?)
Three.
("Remembering what I said". Jae Seok and Somin are right.)
- It is five. - We won.
(Remember what I said?)
- See? - It's right.
You're right.
- I knew it. - I picked this one...
because Somin told me.
You say something casually,
and if they remember it, it makes your heart flutter.
- I told you it's number five. - Right.
I thought number five was something you just do.
(Glancing)
48 percent picked this.
Somin and Jae Seok won two points.
That was fierce. We came from behind and won.
(Jae Seok and Somin win Rank the Numbers.)
"We came from behind and won."
Let's go to the final location. That'll be the final mission.
- Let's go. - Let's go over.
(What will they do with the last Diamond Distribution Card?)
- What's this? Where are we? - We can't have the same amount.
Let's go.
(What's waiting for them?)
That's scary.
Lucky.
I would hate to go.
I'm telling you. I won't go. I can't do it.
I won't go.
- I can't go. - You can't do this to us.
- All right. - Okay.
Jae Seok and Somin won Rank the Numbers,
so I'll tell you if you're safe or in danger.
Please come forward.
- Jae Seok. - They won five points.
- Take ours. - Good luck.
- Do something unexpected. - Pick us.
Currently, you two are...
dangerous with the highest number.
- This is too dangerous. - I know.
Two teams have the same number, right?
2 teams have the same number, and the lowest number is 3.
- I think they'll push hard. - I think they have 13.
We can all survive, Jae Seok.
(Please choose well.)
If we make the wrong decision...
(If they pick something uncertain, they might get the same number.)
We might get the same number. We have to pick a team we know.
- Let's pick Kwang Soo. - He gave us the diamonds.
I think it's the most certain. If we pick somebody else,
- we won't know, right? - That's true.
(The two couples' fates lie in Jae Seok and Somin's hands.)
Please bring your briefcase forward, Kwang Soo and Da Hee.
Think again. You can save everybody.
- Really? - Somin.
- Good job, Jae Seok. - Think again.
- Really? - Good choice.
- You're so wise. - Everybody,
we're not doing this as a payback.
We don't know how many the other teams have.
- I'll tell you. - We only have this information,
so we have to take yours.
Yes, that's enough.
(Accept it, losers.)
Accept it.
They really don't want to go.
(Are you going to do this?)
I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
I looked back earlier,
and your team was the only one that I thought wouldn't win.
That's why I picked you, and in the end...
Go away. Go.
- But then... - You reap what you sow.
- They might not be in last place. - Do we decide?
You can decide how many you want to give them.
How many you'll give them.
Why do we have so many?
Let's...
We can all survive, Jae Seok.
Let's give them this many.
(Let's send off this many.)
(How many did they give Kwang Soo and Da Hee?)
- The team with the lowest number... - The lowest number.
That's three.
- I think it's three. - It has to be.
The team with the lowest number...
(Which team has the least diamonds?)
Seok Jin and Sang Yeob with three diamonds.
Yes!
(Seok Jin and Sang Yeob have the lowest number.)
- I don't think more is better. - Should we take a lot?
Trust me. Three?
Let's do three. Okay.
(They kept 3 diamonds all day.)
We should have taken six.
We should have taken 6 or 7.
The highest number...
(The team with the highest number also gets the Shuddering Sticker.)
(They wanted to escape this by giving their diamonds away.)
Kwang Soo and Da Hee.
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee have the highest number.)
They took it all back.
That's exactly right.
- Good job. - They're so sneaky.
- Good job. - And...
from the four remaining teams,
two teams have the same numbers.
- Please not this one. - Please, no.
Please.
(The teams with the same numbers get the Shuddering Stickers.)
If you don't have the same number, you get the Luxury Stickers.
Please.
- Please, not this. - The teams with the same numbers...
Please, we can't be the two teams.
I really want to win.
I don't think they will lose.
The teams with the same number...
are Jong Kook and Jin Young, and Jae Seok and Somin.
(These two couples have the same numbers.)
(Why did we get the same number?)
You fool.
(Haha and Ji Hyo, and Se Chan and Hanna get Luxury Stickers.)
They switched.
(How did they end up like this?)
I think it's bad to have the same number.
- Let's do seven. - Okay.
- You wanted 7. - 2 more.
That makes us 7, and Jae Seok has 13.
Then nobody has the same numbers.
We'll give them seven more.
Please focus, Da Hee.
(We got the same number again.)
I'm bad with numbers.
Let's give them six.
(Let's give six to Kwang Soo and Da Hee.)
(They are bad with numbers too, so they ended up with 7 diamonds.)
(That's how Jong Kook and Jae Seok both ended up with 7.)
3 teams had 10 diamonds,
- so that's why we did that. - Don't even talk to him.
- I thought we were going to win. - Let's go to Switzerland.
We had the same number,
and now we have the same number.
(Jong Kook's team got away and got stuck with Jae Seok's team.)
I didn't think about that.
- I thought we were going to win. - Let's go to Switzerland.
Four people will go on the Luxury Package.
That means we have space for two more people.
That's right.
2 more people. There are 2 more spots.
- There are spots. - What?
- There are two more spots? - Yes.
- They only have four people. - Really?
That's right.
This is your last chance to avoid the Shuddering Package.
This is called Back to the Future.
In the briefcases in front of you...
are Exemption Card, Shuddering Package Card,
and Shuddering Package Plus One Card.
You can do rock-paper-scissors and decide who goes first.
Each couple will pick a briefcase.
If somebody picks the Exemption Card first,
they get the Luxury Sticker. The rest lose.
(The couple that picks the Exemption Card wins.)
- We can do this, Seok Jin. - Okay.
We have to win.
(There's an advantage to picking the briefcase first.)
You have to win rock-paper-scissors.
- No. - I'll do it.
- I'll go. - Go.
If you lose, you don't get to choose.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Only Jae Seok is "paper".)
- Yes. - I win.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok and Somin lose. They get the Shuddering Sticker.)
- You don't get to pick. - It's him again.
(They don't get to pick. They get the Shuddering Sticker.)
He's so unlucky.
(Sighing)
(How does that feel?)
This is the worst.
Somin,
- you should get away from Jae Seok. - Somin.
You shouldn't be in the same team as me.
- Gosh, I'll never do it again. - This is the worst.
- We make the worst team. - I know.
This is the worst.
- We make the worst team. - Please continue.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin and Sang Yeob are in 1st place.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jong Kook and Jin Young are in 2nd place.)
- It's possible. - It's okay. We can win.
(Let's pick the Exemption Card.)
If Seok Jin picks the Exemption Card, this is over.
- Can I pick? - Go ahead.
I'll pick.
(Sang Yeob is confident, so he wants to choose.)
If you pick the bad card, you get the Shuddering Sticker.
If you pick the Shuddering Package Plus One Card,
you can choose another team to go with you.
- I think it's this one. - This one?
What about you? What do you think? You'll pick.
They want this one, so I pick this.
Okay. I have a bad feeling about this.
Sang Yeob is not lucky today. Maybe you should switch.
You never know. The sun rises out of nowhere.
- It's true. - He can't be unlucky forever.
- How will I keep living? - I trust you, Sang Yeob.
If they pick the Exemption Card,
- we all get the penalty? - It'll be over then.
- Just go with what you picked. - Let's go.
- You can't be unlucky forever. - Let's go.
(They open the 1st briefcase that'll decide the 3 teams' fates.)
(If Sang Yeob picks the Exemption Card, it's game over.)
(His team will get the Luxury Sticker.)
(If he picks the Shuddering Package Card or Plus One Card,)
(his team will get the Shuddering Sticker.)
(There's 1 in 3 chance. Will Sang Yeob finally get lucky?)
Oh, my goodness.
- Hurry up. - Let's go.
You can't be unlucky forever.
- Let's go. - Here it is.
(They open the 1st briefcase that'll decide the 3 teams' fates.)
(If Sang Yeob picks the Exemption Card, it's game over.)
(His team will get the Luxury Sticker.)
- Hurry. - Let's go.
You can't be unlucky forever.
- Let's go. - Here it is.
(Seok Jin and Sang Yeob get the Shuddering Sticker.)
(Thank you, Sang Yeob.)
Yes.
This is insane.
Sang Yeob is insane.
(That's right. It's possible to be unlucky until the end.)
How can you be unlucky until the end?
(Thanks to Sang Yeob's bad luck,)
(they have a better chance of getting the Exemption Card.)
- Poor you. - This is great.
I'm getting my hopes up.
He's the leader of unlucky people.
(Seok Jin and Sang Yeob get the Shuddering Sticker.)
- We're almost there. - One more time.
Let's win one more time.
One is the Exemption Card, and the other one is the penalty.
You can also pick another team.
I think it's this one.
(I have a feeling.)
I'll pick the other one then.
- I think it's that one. - Sang Yeob is bad luck.
- Jin Young. - Yes?
- Goodbye - Goodbye
- I'm leaving - Goodbye
If they pick the penalty, this is over.
Please pick Plus One.
- Open it right away. - In 1, 2, 3
(This briefcase will decide who gets the Luxury Sticker.)
(If they pick the Shuddering Package Plus One Card,)
(they automatically join Jae Seok and Somin.)
(If it's the Exemption Card, they get the Luxury Stickers.)
(There are only 2 spots left.)
(Which couple will come one step closer to enjoying this dream?)
In 1, 2, 3.
Exemption Card.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young pick the Exemption Card.)
2, 3.
Exemption Card.
This is crazy.
(I did it, Jong Kook.)
(She's excited.)
Exemption Card.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young get the last 2 Luxury Stickers.)
(That couple is so lucky.)
(He avoids her.)
You should have won rock-paper-scissors.
(Don't you think that's what I wanted too?)
- You met the right woman. - Jong Kook.
- Be good to me. - Okay.
- All right? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee get the Shuddering Stickers.)
Okay.
Goodbye
After the first week,
- the results have come out. - I'm sick of this group.
Who went to see the crocodiles?
(It's me.)
Who went to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?
- Me. - Me too.
Who went to Indonesia?
(I went to Indonesia too.)
Who had soba?
- Team Soba. - Me.
- Osaka. - Osaka.
(They went on all the penalty trips.)
This is strange. Why does it keep happening?
He made all the decisions today.
- He made all the decisions. - He's the worst.
- It was all him. - Sang Yeob was in the heart of it.
Even I find it hard to believe.
- You are the unluckiest. - How am I supposed to live?
Don't ask me. You are responsible for your own life.
(How am I supposed to know?)
Sir!
- For goodness' sake. - He abandoned me.
This isn't the end. We still have three weeks.
- We don't know what will happen. - Right. This is the beginning.
This is the beginning. And Somin,
- let's not team up from now on. - Seriously.
Make sure the two of them are a team.
- That's the best option. - It's the worst combination.
It's the worst combination.
See you next week!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Look forward to the 2nd week of Family Project.)
(Running Man's 36-Strategy Olympics)
(Instead of walking, we run.)
(Team Bobsleigh)
(We are popular around the world.)
(Team Song of curling)
(Life starts at 50.)
(Team Gateball)
(The official mascots of Running Man's Olympics)
(Soohorang and human-faced bird)
(Are there more athletes?)
Are more people coming?
(The real Olympic heroes are here.)
(Team Skeleton, Yun Sung Bin and Kim Ji Soo)
(Am I really seeing the masters of skeleton?)
(Okay.)
(They are the fittest men...)
(who can fly on land.)
This is embarrassing.
(It finally happens.)
(The biggest match of strength in 2018)
(However,)
(3 coaches are hiding...)
(among the athletes.)
They are among us.
(The athletes are chased...)
(by the mysterious coaches.)
(Who are the 3 coaches?)
(Family Package Part 2, The Lost Sticker)