- Hello. - Hello.
- Did you film the TV rating notice? - Yes.
- We asked you to wear nice clothes. - That's right.
- The clothes are colorful. - I see some bright colors.
We wore nice clothes today.
It's nice.
Haha could be the SMPTE color bars.
I counted the colors. I am wearing 14 colors in total.
(He is SMPTE color bars personified.)
I am amazed, but it suits him. It's a good outfit for him.
- The disorderly fashion. - The cute fashion.
The disorderly fashion.
I am amazed.
- Seok Jin, are you a prisoner? - Be quiet.
(His top is reminiscent of the prison bars.)
Don't say a thing about my clothes.
- The others can but not you. - Are you a prisoner?
Are you a prisoner somewhere?
- What are you talking about? - It seems that way.
You know nothing about fashion.
Kwang Soo attended...
Song Joong Ki's fan meeting.
- There are videos. - He attended it.
- Of course, he did. - They are good friends.
You didn't say much, but you annoy me already.
Joong Ki is so nice. He keeps finding a use for him.
He keeps finding a use for me?
Yes. That's exactly what he is doing.
I received an official invitation as his friend.
Are you sure you didn't crash it?
Perhaps you just walked up to the stage.
- What are you talking about? - I watched a video...
and he did this throughout the interview.
- That's not true. - "Yes, I revere him."
- "Yes." - I don't revere him.
It's in his nature.
Do you know how Kwang Soo exited the stage?
Do you think I am a eunuch?
(Please allow your humble subject to leave now.)
Do you think I am a eunuch? Why would I leave like this?
"Yes, Your Majesty." Didn't you say that?
- "Yes, Your Majesty." - I didn't say that.
That's right.
- I exited confidently. - Really?
- I was invited. - Really?
In any case, we are grateful for Joong Ki.
- That's right. - You should be grateful to me.
- He looks after you. - We thank him for looking...
- after Kwang Soo. - Seriously.
We hope he will invite Kwang Soo...
- to the 11th anniversary as well. - That's right.
Please do that.
Song Joong Ki forever!
"Song Joong Ki forever"?
He needs to be popular for Kwang Soo to be popular.
My popularity has nothing to do with him.
(May the friendship between them last forever.)
You didn't learn the secret of the briefcase last week.
- That's right. - That's right.
- The briefcase. - I forgot about that.
(For the secret, Running Man had the Dangerous Delivery Race.)
(They succeeded to deliver the briefcase.)
(The staff promised to reveal the secret this week.)
What's the secret of the briefcase?
- The secret will be revealed today. - That's good.
That's only right.
- Bring in the briefcase. - Will we open it right away?
(Bring in the briefcase.)
(It's only the opening.)
- Will we open it right away? - Will we open it?
Will we open it?
- What is going on? - What is going on?
Why is there music?
("Sexy Back"?)
- "Sexy Back". - Why is there music?
(Is "Sexy Back" announcing a guest?)
What is going on?
- Do Yeon! - Jang Do Yeon.
- Do Yeon. - What are you doing here?
- Do Yeon. - Jang Do Feet.
(The tall femme fatale, Jang Do Yeon)
(She shook up Running Man with her big feet.)
(Jang Do Feet is here.)
(Sexy)
- Hey! - My goodness.
(She exudes the charms they can't handle.)
- Her feet are really big. - My goodness.
- Jang Do Feet. - Don't talk about my feet.
It must be true that you wear size 300mm.
I wear size 300mm.
You wear size 300mm.
I should bring her shoes that are big for me.
Share your shoes with her.
- You shouldn't be rude to me. - We aren't rude to you.
I am the briefcase girl.
- That explains "Sexy Back". - "Sexy Back".
Do Yeon, I heard that you rarely have a day off.
The thing is, I don't have any work that represents me.
I am the peddler of variety shows.
(She goes everywhere.)
- You are looking to settle down. - I go everywhere.
- You will get to settle down. - That's right.
Today, my work is here.
I am looking for a show to pick me up.
You should visit different shows...
and stick your foot in a show you like.
- That's right. I am busy. - How is Running Man?
Don't you want to stick your foot in it?
I have made many attempts,
but they have no place for me.
(They have no place for me.)
- I will come and go. - Okay.
I will come and go before they forget about me.
- That's good. - Do Yeon is quick-witted.
She is sharp.
Do Yeon is quick-witted.
Some people are slow-witted.
(Glancing)
- Some people are slow-witted. - You are too kind.
(He glances at the slow-witted member.)
Hold on. Who were you looking at?
- Where did you look? - Do you mean him?
- Make this work. - What do you mean?
- Did you just look at me? - His face turned red.
Seok Jin's face turned red. That means he's really angry.
- I didn't. - You little runt.
- Did you look at me? - What did I do?
I think you looked at me the longest.
You were just standing there when I turned.
By the way,
- Do Yeon brought us the briefcase. - Right.
- Exactly. - Actually, today,
- I'll have a major role. - Is that so?
- My gosh. - You brought us the briefcase.
I'll play the role of Heo Cham, the host.
- I brought this for a reason. - What is that?
- Can I look at my script? - Sure.
- You're hosting today. Nice. - She's honest.
Today, we must reveal the secret behind this briefcase...
- you safely delivered last week. - You should let us know today.
- All right. - Right.
Dangerous Delivery Part Two. The Secret of the Briefcase.
(She's cheerful and energetic.)
(Everyone gets excited at her old style of hosting from the 90s.)
- The Briefcase's Secret. - Hold on.
- You're good. - This is an old style of hosting.
- Everyone, brace yourselves. - She prepared this. Okay.
In this briefcase,
- there is a three-digit passcode. - Is that so?
You will complete missions in order to acquire hints.
You must open it with the hints to find out what's inside.
If you don't find out the secret of the briefcase in the end,
two members will be chosen by the roulette for the penalty.
If you fail the mission,
you must put your names on the slots...
in order to acquire hints from us.
You must put your name up for the hints.
If you can't open the briefcase before you fill up the roulette,
you will fail the final mission.
- After filling up the roulette... - Excuse me.
Do you need to be somewhere after this?
It feels like she's rushed.
I have a specific role today.
I used to come here for an easy time,
but trying to host this now is kind of hard.
All right.
We'll meet after you change into your team uniforms.
- We have to change into uniforms? - Yes, yes.
- Okay. - You're a great host.
No, I'm not.
(A mission to obtain the first hint about the briefcase's secret)
(Why is there a balloon set in the empty studio?)
- What is this? - Welcome.
- What is this, Do Yeon? - There's a balloon.
- How many roles do you have today? - Come this way.
I'm just doing this and that.
- What is that? - I'm scared.
- Isn't that a water bomb? - All right.
- Is that water? Darn it. - This is water.
Everyone, you will start your mission to find out...
- the briefcase's secret. - Okay.
Everyone, what's our national holiday?
- Chuseok. - That's right.
What do we look at on Chuseok?
- Full moon. - That's correct!
The name of this mission is...
When the Full Moon Sets
(The name of this mission is When the Full Moon Sets.)
- Full moon? - She's a little weird.
- Did you prepare it or improvise? - Is that your theme?
The theme of my hosting is retro.
- Retro? I get it. - I'll go back to the old style.
- This is a vintage style. - I see.
- It's vintage. - That's trending now.
Let me explain about When the Full Moon Sets.
- You'll sit in this chair. - Okay.
You must lower the balloon to the Safe Zone.
- We have to stop it? - Yes.
- You grab, let go, and grab again. - We can do this.
- But when Kwang Soo sits down... - That's not the problem.
- He will go over the line. - What if...
I sit down and go over the Safe Zone?
But he has long legs.
- Your upper body isn't that long. - Right.
No, Kwang Soo has a longer upper body than a lower body.
No, no.
- That's not true. - He's upset.
Stop lying. You're 190cm tall.
Isn't your upper body about 150cm long?
Then are my legs about 40cm?
- Is that why you always... - My legs are only 40cm long?
Those legs are only 40cm long?
- Aren't I right? - No, you're wrong.
- I'm wrong? - You're wrong.
- You're wrong. - Do you know what this is?
This is Kwang Soo.
What are you doing?
(She artistically interprets the giraffe's sadness.)
- What is that? - What do you think? It's you.
- Tone it down. - Okay.
- Lower your hand. - I'm sorry.
(She's unbelievable.)
You must make it look like his head.
(He can't refute it.)
- This is unbelievable. - Every one of you...
will try to complete this mission,
but you will choose the number of members that...
must succeed with a die.
(The die will decide the number of members that must succeed.)
- It purely depends on luck. - The lower it is, the better it is.
If we get number one, it'd be awesome.
- Here's one important point. - What is it?
- I'm the Briefcase Girl today. - Yes.
- Is hosting my only job today? - Okay.
You may have a chance to use me.
(They can get 1 more chance to try with Do Yeon Chance Card.)
- What is it? - If I join you on the mission...
and if you succeed, you'll get two hints.
- We must use that chance then. - We should.
- Is that so? - That's important.
- However, there is a twist. - We should use that chance.
If you fail the mission, you'll get the forehead flick.
One of you must face it.
- We must use Ms. Feet well. - The forehead flick.
- Excuse me, "Ms. Feet"? - Hold on.
- Everyone. - You wore smaller shoes on purpose.
You wore smaller shoes on purpose.
- I think your toes are touching. - Are you scrunching your toes?
Here's what you must look out for.
That time when I was on Running Man,
I measured my feet with Jong Kook and Se Chan.
- A lot of people messaged me. - What did they say?
They all have big feet.
"Do Yeon, my feet size is 290mm."
"Where can I buy my shoes?"
- "Keep your chin up, big foot!" - How nice of them.
- I got so many messages. - That's nice.
- Ms. Feet, that's awesome. - It's great.
- She's Grand Feet. - So...
- Grand Feet? - Yes, Grand Feet.
Having big feet is great.
- Hold on. - Grand Feet.
- Ji Hyo will try it. - Go ahead.
- Ji Hyo gets lucky. - Yes.
All right. Start. Start, Ji Hyo.
- Start. I'll throw it higher. - Start.
- Go rough with that. Don't mind it. - I don't know.
(The die has been cast.)
(Please let that be a low number.)
Be rough with that.
(The number of members for the 1st mission is 3.)
- Three. - That wasn't bad.
- That wasn't bad. - She picked a good number.
- She picked three. - See?
- She's pretty good. - Right.
- Three is a great number. - That's nice.
Which one of you will go first then?
- Okay. Jong Kook will go 1st then. - Jong Kook, you go 1st.
- That must be hard to do it alone. - Put this fur cap on.
- It won't be easy. - It's not easy.
- It's not. - Pull it all the way up.
It's not easy.
(He puts on the fur cap with tacks.)
(He feels nervous after sitting under the massive water balloon.)
- All right. Say, "start". - It will pop at once.
- My goodness. - You passed now.
- About this much? - This would pass.
- Is this good enough? - You have to raise a bit higher.
- Raise it higher. - That would count as a success.
- I can raise it higher? - Raise it up to this point.
You have to know when to stop.
- Move back. The water will splash. - Start!
- Everyone, count for him. - Look at the water balloon.
1, 2, 3.
- Start! - Start!
All right.
(Will Jong Kook, the first member, be able to complete the mission?)
(He survived without popping the water balloon.)
- It's almost touching. - How could he do that?
- It's almost touching. - This is amazing.
- It's incredible. - He's so good.
- What is this? - What should I do?
- It's a success! - This has to count as a success.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
- Gosh, I almost popped it. - That was awesome.
(It's hard to believe their eyes.)
- You're so lucky. - My gosh.
- One of us succeeded it. - All right.
(So Min will try next.)
I'm so certain.
- I'm so certain that she'll fail. - No, I won't.
So Min will definitely pop it.
- No. - We should move back.
Since Jong Kook succeeded, if you also succeed,
- We need 2 members to succeed. - we just need 1 more person.
All right.
- I'll count and grab it. - Right.
You have to count in your head.
Here I go.
Start.
(She fails within 1 second.)
My goodness.
(It's expected of her.)
- My goodness. - Darn it.
(What just happened?)
(The huge balloon was so scary.)
Poor you.
- That was huge. - Wait.
So Min grabbed the rope after the balloon popped.
(After the water balloon popped,)
(she grabbed the rope but to no avail.)
- So Min. - You didn't grab it?
- That's all right. - She did, but she was late.
I grabbed it right here.
- I grabbed it here. - You did grab it.
So Min, your hair looks great.
- It looks awesome. - It's all right.
- She looks like Byung Ok. - Great. Great.
- You look like Byung Ok. - Byung Ok.
Byung Ok in "Lady Vengeance".
- He played my father in a drama. - Right.
- "Dad". - She looks like Byung Ok.
(It's the same bob haircut, but it looks different.)
- You are so lucky. - I know, right?
- I had no idea it'd be this bad. - Seriously.
Seok Ju, isn't this fun?
- Who is Seok Ju? - Seok Ju.
Are you talking about Ha Seok Ju?
- What are you talking about? - Ha Seok Ju.
"Seok Ju, isn't this fun?"
(As of now, only Jong Kook succeeded.)
- Kwang Soo, just take a seat. - Take a seat.
- Here I go. I'll do it. - Just take a seat for now.
- Seok Ju, you must succeed. - Okay, okay.
I'm not Seok Ju.
- Ha Seok Ju. I'm serious. - Let me really try.
Why did you do that in the match against Mexico?
- What do you mean? - You tackled the player.
Why did you tackle that player all of a sudden? Hold on.
(My gosh, you little...)
(Do you want me to hurt you with this fur cap?)
Don't bump your head into him.
- You look so cool right now. - You look great now.
- You look great now. - You look handsome.
- This looks great on you. - You look great.
- You look great with accessories. - You're a man from the future.
You look great.
- You look like a robot. - He has three eyeballs.
- Can you make robot sounds? - Yes, try that.
Try it.
Hold on.
- If you're late, it's futile. - Yes, do it before it pops.
- It happened to So Min too. - That's right.
- Kwang Soo, take this seriously. - Okay.
By the way, am I the only one who thinks that...
he looks pathetic right now?
- Kwang Soo is always like that. - You just need to win.
- He's always like that. - I hunched forward for the game.
- I did it for the game. - Great. That's great.
You just need to complete the mission.
You can feel it coming down. You can feel it.
Start.
I can't do this. I can't. Listen.
(I can't do this.)
In my head, I let go of the rope, but I can't do it in real life.
- Just do it. - Fine, I'll do it.
- It feels like diving, right? - Please understand me.
- Yes. - It feels like that, right?
- I know how that feels. - He's not mentally ready.
You can't let go of it, right?
- I'll do it. - Go ahead.
(He will really try it this time.)
- Start. - Start.
Come on.
(Kwang Soo was bound to fail anyway.)
You should have grabbed it sooner.
That's all right.
Gosh, the water splashed on you completely.
It completely splashed on you.
Kwang Soo, you didn't know when to stop.
- Gosh, this is bad. - Hey, you got a new hat.
You look great.
- It looks nice on you. - What is it?
(The future human receives a kindergarten hat.)
- It looks like a kindergarten hat. - Right.
It won't be easy to succeed three times.
Kwang Soo is completely wet on the front.
Kwang Soo, your pants...
- They're completely wet. - He was almost lying down.
Why were you lying down?
I mean. I wanted to succeed.
- They're completely soaked. - What?
What?
- You can go now. - Go where?
Your pants are too wet. Go home.
It's been blurred out.
What are you talking about? What's wrong?
(If you're wet on the front, you get blurred out and must leave.)
Go home.
- Why would I go home? - Your pants are wet.
I think yours will get wet soon. Let's go home together.
Give me a ride.
Be quiet.
We're going in the same direction anyway.
I'll show you I can succeed.
I've done it before.
- Done what? - When?
- We've done it many times. - We have.
Have you ever succeeded?
No.
(Embarrassed)
- Show us how to succeed. - I'll show you.
Jae Seok is good at this kind of games.
(Will the fourth player, Jae Seok, succeed?)
I'm not doing it yet.
- I'm just practicing. - Check the distance.
- That's perfect. - That's perfect.
- It has to touch the line. - I did it on purpose.
(He remembers the distance.)
- You'll remember the distance? - I just have to hold there now.
Okay.
- That's a great plan. - See?
(Jae Seok is so experienced and clever.)
(He even marks the spot.)
I remembered the spot.
(He is well-prepared.)
Are you sure you can hold it exactly there?
- Of course. - It sounds difficult.
(Has he really thought it through?)
Be quiet.
- If he succeeds, we'll do this. - Right.
- Hold on. Take off your glasses. - Why?
Just in case.
It doesn't matter at all.
It doesn't.
Are you...
feeling sad?
(Depressed)
(It seems like he's laughing.)
He looks like he's about to cry.
He's about to cry.
(Is it just me or is he really about to cry?)
I always thought he smiled a lot,
but he actually looks like he's about to cry.
I look like I'm about to cry?
- What are you talking about? - I mean...
He needs his glasses.
- He should never get surgery. - He needs his glasses.
Start.
(Even his face is well-suited for variety shows. Jae Seok starts.)
Show us that you can succeed.
He's going to hold that?
I'm worried he can't see the mark.
- I can't see it well. - He can't see it.
(He really can't see it well.)
- I can't... - Can you even see it?
Why can't I see it?
- Or... - If I throw it forward...
You can do it.
- I can do it. - Why don't we tie this around it?
- Okay. - Do it.
- That's a great idea. - Is this really necessary?
(Now it'll be impossible to miss it.)
If he still fails...
It's impossible.
Okay. Done.
I'll grab that. I'm sure I can do it.
- It'll get in the way. - Start.
(He really starts.)
(The balloon is supposed to get in the way.)
(Will this variety show master succeed?)
- When you feel it, just grab it. - Okay.
Oh, no. My goodness.
(What?)
(The balloon just passed.)
(Crying)
You completely missed it.
You completely missed it. It wasn't even close.
You're holding a lot lower.
That was completely pointless.
It's not easy.
Did you use a ruler when you cut your hair?
(Jong Kook notices something.)
How can it be so neat?
It just happened.
There was a boy in my class who looked like this.
Did your son cut it?
- It just turned out this way. - For fun?
(Jae Seok fails.)
I thought it'd work, but it didn't.
- Gosh. - The rest of you.
- Should we use Do Yeon Chance Card? - How many are left?
- 4. - Out of the 4,
- 2 have to succeed. - That's too...
Let's try. We can do it.
You have to succeed.
- Let me try. - Please succeed.
- It's too fast. - You just have to guess.
- There you go. - Don't move.
All right. Haha.
Drop, pull.
- Let's do this. - Start.
- Good luck. - Start.
(Determined)
You have to succeed.
- No. - No.
- I knew it. - He looked...
(Scared)
Hey, come on.
That was so embarrassing.
He looked like a coward.
I've never seen a man who's so pathetic in my life.
Let me try again.
(He is such a coward that he gets another chance.)
He's such a coward.
With your foot...
(Cheating)
- Me? - Okay.
(Give me a sign with your foot.)
Haha. Look.
Start.
You won't be able to see it.
(I'll trust your foot.)
I'll give you a sign. Look at my foot.
(I'll give you a sign. Look at my foot.)
(Splash)
(Se Chan gave a sign when the balloon burst.)
(Identity Change 2)
I gave a sign when the balloon burst.
Me too.
- When the balloon burst. - When the balloon burst.
- When the balloon burst. - It doesn't work.
- It's too difficult. - We'll probably fail.
I think we should use Do Yeon Chance Card.
Let's do that.
We should keep it for later.
Two have to succeed. We'll play Race of Wits.
- Okay. - The three of us?
You can do it.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 3.
You.
(Puzzled)
(He lost while being too careful.)
- You. - You guys planned it, right?
- We didn't. - You did.
What is he talking about?
- We've never cheated. - You guys cheated.
We've never cheated in Race of Wits.
How can three people play Race of Wits?
- What's the problem? - What's the problem?
- It's no problem, right? - It's no problem.
(Will he be able to succeed?)
- He might succeed. - I...
- Okay. - How do you do it?
- Hold it... - It's so heavy.
Lower it.
Don't lower your head.
Say, "Start."
Please succeed.
He has to succeed.
Seriously.
- We have only two chances left. - Okay.
(Will he succeed?)
- Ready. - Start.
I'll do it.
(Will the oldest member succeed?)
- Gosh, it hurts. - What hurts?
- What's wrong? - What hurts?
Where are my gloves?
He has no gloves.
Jae Seok, take care of Seok Jin.
Why didn't anyone give me gloves?
- Last time, you forgot your cup. - You should have taken them.
- Don't forget things again. - It hurts so much.
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
(He's like a big baby.)
- Give him a sign. - Gosh.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Say, "Start." - Start.
(Jae Seok is ready to play a trick.)
(Seok Jin looks so serious.)
- My son is watching. - It's important.
My son is watching.
He said, "My son is watching."
Oh, my.
What...
(Seok Jin starts.)
What's wrong?
(Jae Seok is stepping on the rope.)
(The balloon is not coming down.)
(Gosh, that brat.)
My timing was perfect.
It was incredible. 1, 2, pull.
(Is he my enemy?)
Gosh. What's with you?
(I love playing tricks.)
- Don't do it again. - I won't.
I might punch you.
(If you do it again, I might punch you.)
How manly.
I haven't had candies in a while.
(You mean your honey punch?)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I can't believe their conversation.
(Their combined age is over 100.)
They're like that.
It's so funny. I don't think his punch will hurt.
(Hurt)
It's a honey punch.
I'm going to succeed.
Start.
(He really starts.)
1, 2, 3.
He succeeded!
(The balloon didn't burst.)
(Seok Jin succeeds for the first time in a long time.)
Unbelievable.
(He looks like a different person.)
Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin did it.)
Now, we have a chance. We have a chance.
(Jong Kook and Seok Jin have succeeded so far.)
What happened?
Wasn't it incredible?
- I grabbed it just in time. - It was amazing.
It was perfect.
- Only one more needs to succeed. - We have a chance.
- Only one more. - Between Ji Hyo and me.
Se Chan, if you succeed, we're done.
(The seventh player, Se Chan, starts.)
Is it "drop, pull"?
Drop, pull.
Not "drop, pull".
- Drop, pull. - Drop, pull.
- Drop, pull. - It works.
If Se Chan succeeds, we're done.
(If Se Chan succeeds, the first mission will be complete.)
- Start. - Start.
(Will "drop, pull" work this time too?)
Start.
(Drop...)
He failed.
(The balloon drops,)
(and he pulls too late.)
It worked last time.
(Se Chan fails.)
(No one can imitate my "drop, pull" skill.)
I ran out of luck.
- We still have Ji Hyo. - Yes. We can do it.
It's our last chance.
(If Ji Hyo fails, they won't get a hint.)
- Higher. - It's too fast.
Drop, pull.
- Drop, pull. - Drop, pull.
- Drop, pull. - There you go.
It should work.
- Drop, pull. - Drop, pull.
That's enough.
We should be fair.
We should be fair. She can't keep practicing.
How long are you going to practice?
He's so cold.
What are you doing? It's for our team's success.
Still...
She shouldn't succeed every day.
Oh, my.
(Seok Jin is jealous.)
(He accidentally speaks his mind.)
What are you doing?
- Oh, my. - What is this?
- You should succeed too then. - Come on.
- What is this? - We're a team today.
He wants Ji Hyo to fail so that he'll stand out.
He wasn't even trying to be funny. He's just mean.
He's just mean.
Seriously...
- We're a team today. - Good luck.
- I just wanted to motivate you. - "Good luck"?
- He wanted to motivate her? - I just wanted to motivate you.
- Ready. - You have to succeed.
You can do it, Ji Hyo. Drop, pull.
- Start. - All right.
(The last try)
(Everything is in Ji Hyo's hands now.)
(If she fails, they won't get the first hint.)
I'm scared.
(What will be the result?)
- Start. - Go.
Let's do it.
(Drop, pull.)
- Drop, pull. - Pull.
She got it.
You did it.
(She's safe.)
(She does it perfectly.)
You got it.
(They clear the first mission.)
- Okay. - We got it.
That was amazing.
- You made it. - Okay.
- Good job. - That was unbelievable.
- My hand is trembling. - That was amazing.
We're safe from the roulette.
That's right. I'll give you a hint about the passcode.
- Really? - The passcode.
Can we guess it right away?
"It's bigger than Jae Seok but smaller than Haha."
What?
(Something bigger than Jae Seok but smaller than Haha.)
- Wait a minute. - It can't be someone's height.
Can we say it here?
- Wait a minute. - Is it okay?
- Wait. - What are you saying?
I mean... His is fine too.
- What's funny? - You'll become a great man.
If it's bigger than Jae Seok but smaller than Haha, it's Se Chan.
Stop it. I said stop it.
- Goodness. - Come to the back with me.
Fine. I'm confident about it compared to you.
They're leaving. Get the camera ready.
- Kwang Soo. - Where are you going?
- What are you trying to say? - Wait.
I'm getting really upset. I'm very upset.
It was the cutest fight in the world.
- Stop it. I said stop it. - Don't brag.
(What could it be?)
Isn't it the size of their feet?
- Haha's feet are bigger than mine. - It's bigger than Jae Seok...
- but smaller than Haha. - What's your foot size?
- Mine is 270mm. - That must be it.
- Mine is 280mm. - It's the foot size.
It must be 275mm.
(Is it 275, between 270 and 280?)
- What else is there? - Birthday.
- Their birthday? - 0814.
- His is the 14th. - Mine is the 20th.
- 814. - 815 and 822?
- 820. - Mine is 814.
- There's some difference. - It's 15.
Don't you know his birthday by now?
- What I mean is... - When I call him...
and say, "I'm disappointed. Today is my birthday."
He says, "I'm sorry."
He says, "Why didn't you tell me before?"
- Even if it's tomorrow? - He'd definitely say that.
- Right. - Is she leaving today?
- Really? - Yes.
- That's right. - Oh, no.
- That's sad. - Are you leaving?
We haven't seen you in a while. I'm sad.
If you're sad to see me leave, you'll invite me again.
Please remember me.
- Do Yeon. - She's very busy these days.
- Right. - Thank you for coming.
- Thank you. - It was good to see you.
- Thank you, Do Yeon. - It was my pleasure.
Thank you.
What's this?
(It's lunchtime.)
It's bibimbap.
Fried eggs.
It's perfect with an egg.
(There's a raw egg instead.)
- Are you hungry? - Yes.
- Your lunch is prepared. - It's bibimbap.
We invited a special guest to have lunch with you.
- Again? - We invited a special guest.
We have a guest for each section.
- "Section guest"? - That sounds funny.
- Who is it? - Won't it be a chef?
(Will it be a famous chef?)
Will it be Hong Yoon Hwa in disguise?
- Hong Yoon Hwa? - "How delicious will it be?"
(It's a special lunch guest.)
Goodness.
(Who is the guest for this section?)
(Chef Jang Do Yeon)
Hello.
- It's Do Yeon. - We thought you left.
Hello, I'm someone else. I have a mole.
(I'm not Jang Do Yeon.)
(She's obviously someone else.)
She does have a mole. That's right.
Why did she get a mole?
What are you doing?
It's the first time we meet, so I'll introduce myself.
I will be clearing the mission with you today.
I'm Big Foot, not Big Mama.
(Chef Big Foot)
I'm Chef Jang Do Yeon.
What do you mean?
- I thought you left. - I thought you left.
- I know. - What do you mean?
- I should do as much as I can. - That's good.
- Yes. - That's good. I'm glad.
For today's lunch,
we prepared bibimbap for you.
However, there's no fried egg in your bibimbap.
That's not a big deal.
- It isn't, right? - Right.
(The essential part of bibimbap is missing.)
You must make your own fried egg.
That's simple.
- Here's your mission. - What is it?
This mission is...
(Their second mission)
Dangerous Egg Yolk.
(Goodness, Dangerous Egg Yolk)
(She mimics him again.)
"Dangerous Egg Yolk"?
- I like jokes like this. - No.
(Embarrassed)
Seriously?
- What do you mean? - The egg yolk can't be popped.
You're given 100 seconds.
- Use only your fork. - We can't grab it?
You can't touch the frying pan. Put the egg yolk...
over your bibimbap without popping it within 100 seconds.
(Success)
Six people must succeed?
Let's do it 1 by 1.
- Shall Haha start? - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Haha has lived alone. - Haha is good at cooking.
He's lived alone for a long time.
- Here we go. - Yes.
- In 2, 3. Start. - Start.
(The countdown starts.)
Turn on the gas first.
(He's relaxed.)
Put some oil first.
- It takes time. - It needs to be heated.
100 seconds are not that short.
Haha, drop it close to the pan. That's right.
- He uses one hand. - Nice.
He's good. Look at that. It's perfect.
(It's the level of the owner of a barbecue restaurant.)
That's right.
He's like a chef.
Don't pop the egg yolk.
That's how chefs cook.
(Being careful)
You have 30 seconds left.
- Be careful. - That's all that remains?
- It's a short period of time. - He'll succeed if he makes it.
How many seconds are left?
- 9, 8, 7... - Hurry up. Put it in.
- 6, 5... - Hurry.
(It's slippery.)
- 4, 3... - Look at him.
(He places it inside the bowl.)
- He got it. - It isn't popped.
It isn't popped.
(Did it get placed safely inside the bowl?)
- It's leaking. - What do you mean?
It popped during the process.
- It did pop. - Gosh, that's unfortunate.
(It completely popped.)
(Haha fails.)
- Gosh, Haha. - You try it.
- I'm disappointed. - Try it.
I believe in you, Ji Hyo.
You should have made it.
If two more fail, we all fail.
Get ready.
Start.
(The countdown starts.)
- Just crack it open right away. - Right away?
No, it gets stuck on the pan.
(She pours in a lot of oil.)
- That's enough. - That's too much.
- It won't stick. - That's enough to deep-fry the egg.
- That's too much. - It doesn't matter how it tastes.
- Goodness. - I don't think she can do this.
- Gosh. - That's not how to do it.
Make sure the egg yolk doesn't pop.
Open it up.
- That's not how you do it. - Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
Put it lower!
- Put it lower. Open it up. - Open it up.
(The egg white spills.)
(How does the egg yolk look?)
It didn't pop.
(Miraculously, it didn't pop.)
- Keep it low. - Goodness.
(Despite her tactic, the egg yolk is safe.)
- That was scary. - The egg yolk came out...
like a baby.
That was close.
- All I have to do is transfer well. - You're running out of time.
You should make it small.
- I'll give it a try. - That's good.
- 10, 9... - You got it.
- Do it slowly, Ji Hyo. - Do it slowly.
- Right. - Gosh.
(It's not easy to move it with a fork.)
- Seven... - Lift it up.
- Six. - Lift up the bowl.
- No way. Seven. - Lift it up.
(She lifts it up carefully.)
- Okay. - She got it!
Okay.
(It's perfect.)
- Okay. - That was hot.
(Ji Hyo succeeds with a perfect transfer.)
- She looked very awkward. - Ji Hyo.
- I got it. - It was a success.
(Ji Hyo is as good as always.)
- Okay, I'll start. - It looks hard.
- All right. - Seok Jin.
It's his first time making a fried egg.
- I did it in the military. - Take a look.
- Gosh. - He's a beginner.
- Yes. - Get ready.
Start.
It's on.
I've done it in the military.
(He'll make a perfect, fried egg based on his experience.)
- Oil. - Pour some oil.
Seok Jin, oil.
(Is he frying an egg without oil?)
Seok Jin.
(Now, he pours some oil.)
We have to take care of him.
If he was alone, he would've poured the oil after cracking the egg open.
(He cracks open an egg with one hand.)
- Okay. - He can't do it.
- Okay. - The pan should be heated.
- It's okay. It'll be cooked. - The pan should be heated.
It's starting to cook.
I can hear the sound.
- No, Seok Jin. Oh, no. - Wait.
(What is he doing?)
(Pouring)
(Pouring a lot more)
- What are you doing? - It's slippery.
(Half of it is oil.)
The egg yolk is about to pop.
You shouldn't put oil on it.
- The egg yolk is about to pop. - What are you doing?
I'm covering it with oil.
He poured oil on the egg yolk.
The heat is getting low.
- It's not ready yet. - It's hot.
(Oil is splashing.)
- Leave it alone. - It's okay.
(The oil splashes.)
It's like a volcanic eruption.
- 10. - Look at the oil.
- You have to transfer it. - There's too much oil.
- It's hot. - It's too much oil.
- 9, 8... - You have to transfer it now.
- Be careful, Seok Jin. - Put it in the bowl.
- Get the other side. - It's separating.
Do it.
- Let it go. - Don't do it that way. Let it go.
Just drop it.
(The egg yolk loses its shape.)
- What are you doing? - Goodness.
Everyone, express your condolences. The egg yolk has passed away.
(Everyone, express your condolences. The egg yolk has passed away.)
Egg yolks are things that we eat.
Why did you destroy the egg yolk?
(You were a great egg yolk.)
(Egg Yolk, 2018 to 2018)
- How could he? - I'm sorry.
You're so mean.
Please succeed.
You can do it. I mean it.
- Chef Yu, show us. - Show us.
I'll show you guys.
I'll show you how beautiful...
- a fried egg can be. - Good luck.
Chefs don't break eggs on edges.
They use the surface.
That's what I do.
Why would you do that?
- Why would you do that? - I just do that.
Aren't you just pretentious?
I think you're just pretentious.
- I'll show you. - He's definitely pretentious.
Ready.
(Good luck, Pretentious Chef.)
(He's given 100 seconds.)
It's important to remain calm.
He's so calm.
(He checks the temperature relaxedly.)
- He looks like an expert. - When you fry eggs,
you shouldn't fuss.
Hurry up.
- Don't worry. - Hurry.
He's talking too much. I'm getting worried.
He usually fails when he does this.
(Pouring)
He's even bad at pouring oil.
It looks so bad.
- Even the oil looks ugly. - Don't worry.
- You don't have much time. - It doesn't look natural.
You have less time than you think.
(Breaking)
The yolk broke.
(What is this?)
(As soon as he drops the yolk,)
(it breaks.)
It's already broken.
What is this?
Your thumb...
- Why did you poke it? - Why did you break it?
I'm sorry.
He's so bad.
- He poked it with his thumb. - Why did you break it?
Can I try again? Chef Big Foot.
Offer your condolences.
(Rest in peace.)
Where did you put your thumb?
I'm sorry.
Your thumb...
Turn off the stove. You might get burned.
Gosh. What a shame.
We should use the chance card.
- We should. - But if we use it...
and Jong Kook fails,
- it'll be over, right? - It'll be over.
Let's use it a bit later. Let me try first.
Okay.
Try first.
I think he'll do a good job.
He's eaten...
about two chicken farms' worth of eggs so far.
He's eaten even more.
(He has contributed to the poultry industry.)
- Should I start? - He's the chickens' worst enemy.
Let's go.
(Since he's eaten so many eggs, he'll probably be good.)
Thank you.
Start. Let me start.
(He's given 100 seconds.)
(He can't control his strength.)
(He is overzealous.)
- He's too strong. - He's too strong.
Can't you control your strength?
You don't need a lot of oil.
But I need at least this much.
You need more. Otherwise, the egg can burn.
Don't be so stingy.
- Don't try to save the oil. - What do you mean?
I'm not.
With one hand.
Like this.
This is how you do it.
(The egg lover can control eggs very well.)
- The yolk is right in the middle. - Yes.
(Impressed)
That looks perfect.
It looks beautiful.
- It's going well. - Then after that...
Gosh, it's about to burst.
(It's about to explode.)
The yolk is about to explode.
- The yolk is boiling. - Hey.
It's boiling.
- Transfer it now. - No.
There are 10 seconds left.
- 10 seconds? - You should transfer it.
Go.
(Transfer it into the bowl.)
You have to do it now.
Go.
(Will he be able to save the yolk?)
- It's about to burst. - Oh, my.
(It's lifted.)
The egg white is protecting the yolk.
(If Jong Kook fails, their mission fails altogether.)
- There you go. - The egg white is protecting it.
(It safely lands in the bowl.)
- There you go. - Oh, my.
We don't know yet.
- Please take a look. - Okay.
Don't touch it. Put the camera...
- inside. - Save it.
It didn't burst.
(Is the yolk safe?)
You brat.
Is it bleeding?
- It didn't break, did it? - You brat.
(The side is bleeding.)
It's bleeding?
There's a crack on the side.
The ribs are cracked.
- It's bleeding. - He almost succeeded.
- We'll use Do Yeon Chance Card. - We'll use Do Yeon Chance Card.
That's too bad.
It broke?
- Yes. - It broke?
He was almost done.
Give him another chance.
Since it was so close,
if you put one name on the roulette,
we'll reduce the number of successes you need by one.
- Okay. - Jae Seok.
(Okay. We choose Jae Seok.)
He must know why.
- I'm sure he knows. - Hey.
He was the only one who failed even before starting cooking.
I vote for Jae Seok too.
- It's not okay. - Then...
let's choose from those who failed.
- From those who failed. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. Only those who failed. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- I succeeded. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(They're deciding whose name to sacrifice.)
(Haha loses.)
Okay.
Haha.
(Haha's name goes on the wheel.)
It's a deal.
Haha's name will go on the wheel.
We reduced the number by 1. 2 have failed so far.
- Let me go first. - Okay.
Since Kwang Soo lives alone, he might succeed.
Fried eggs...
- You've never made it? - I'm good at making them.
Kwang Soo...
His ex-girlfriend...
- loved fried eggs. - I see.
(Kwang Soo's ex-girlfriend loved fried eggs.)
(What?)
Why do you bring her up now?
(Lee Kwang Soo and Fried Eggs, the Secret Relationship)
Okay.
You have 100 seconds.
- Is that okay? - It's okay.
Why are you doing this to me?
What's with you?
Fold the white.
Pour some more oil.
- Hey! - It didn't break.
(It started interestingly, but Kwang Soo fails.)
We'll write one more name.
It's your last chance. If you write one more name,
we'll reduce the number of successes you need by one.
- We'll write another name. - Kwang Soo.
The rest of you should play Race of Wits.
Race of Wits?
We haven't done anything yet.
- We haven't even played the game. - Race of Wits?
We played rock-paper-scissors.
The rest should...
- play Race of Wits. - I played rock-paper-scissors too.
- You did? - I can't believe you.
You want me to burst you with my thumb?
(Like your egg)
What?
You want to end up like your egg?
- Even his cap is yellow. - You want me to burst you?
- From his head. - Should I push you?
(He might end up like an egg.)
- You played before? I'm sorry. - Gosh.
- Try to remember things. - I'm sorry.
We played together.
Ji Hyo, you should play it too. That's the right way. I'm right.
My judgment is accurate.
- That's what old people say. - I'm right.
They say, "I'm right."
(I succeeded, so why do I have to play?)
- Right? - Gosh.
- I'm right. - Why?
Ask hundreds of thousands of people on the street.
Hundreds of thousands?
It'd take too long.
Listen carefully.
- Ji Hyo... - The four of you should play.
Although Ji Hyo succeeded...
- If we fail... - She shouldn't play.
(Jae Seok cuts in.)
Just write your name.
Stop talking!
(Jong Kook explodes.)
I was talking.
Gosh.
Let me finish.
- Stop talking. - Goodness.
I feel so uncomfortable.
- Let me go home. - We do this every week.
Okay. Let's do it.
- The four of us? - He wants to do it.
- Race of Wits? - The four of them.
Race of Wits. Ready.
- You should sit down. - I'm going to succeed.
- Ready. - Hold on.
We can't play like this.
- What? - We're supposed to sit down.
What's wrong?
We have to sit down.
- Really? - Ready.
- Ready. - Start.
- 1. - 1.
(Seok Jin said, "1".)
Wait, what?
(Where is my chair? I did sit down.)
Guys.
Wait, what?
(Pathetic)
Who took my chair?
Who took it?
(No one did.)
We have to play rock-paper-scissors.
- Seok Jin and Jong Kook. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay. Play rock-paper-scissors.
(As Seok Jin and Jong Kook lost, they play rock-paper-scissors.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jong Kook loses.)
- I win. - I wanted to tell you.
All right.
I wanted to tell you.
- Are we writing Jong Kook's name? - Yes.
(Kim Jong Kook)
- Who is going to try? - So Min and I.
Okay.
Give me an egg.
- I just need to save the yolk. - That's right.
She succeeded.
(So Min succeeds by removing the white.)
It's so round.
It looks very stable.
(Se Chan succeeds perfectly.)
We're using Do Yeon Chance Card.
If we fail this time, it's over, right?
Yes. And you get flicked on the forehead too.
- Oh, right. - Right.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Let's do this, Do Yeon. - You can do this.
You use this to fry eggs?
- Yes. - Really?
Let's do this.
- She used the surface. - It's the chefs' style.
(The yolk drops smoothly.)
- Nice. - Good.
- It was incredible. - Look at this.
(She makes a "V" sign.)
Good job.
I think she'll succeed.
But around the yolk...
- It's bubbling. - It...
- It's boiling. - The white is broken.
- 10 seconds. - Cut it away.
- Should I cut it? - 10.
- You have to transfer it now. - Nine.
(The yolk is about to burst, but she has to transfer it.)
- Slowly. - Put it deeper.
(The mission relies on Chef Big Foot.)
- Slowly. - You have to transfer it.
- Turn it. - You have to go.
If we fail this time, it's over, right?
I think she'll succeed.
(Will Chef Big Foot pull it off?)
Lift it!
(Moving)
(She lifted it well, but the yolk breaks.)
We'll write Do Yeon's name.
But don't forget to turn off the stove.
(Turn off the stove even if your mission fails.)
What's that?
(I'm sorry, guys.)
Your mission failed.
You'll receive a hint,
but you have to write two more names.
Let's choose someone who isn't on the wheel yet.
- Okay. - Okay.
Then the two of you are excluded.
The remaining 6 will play Race of Wits while the 2 sit.
You're deciding which two will write their names on the wheel...
and which one will be flicked on the forehead by Do Yeon.
The person will have two penalties.
One person gets it all.
Start.
- 1. - 2.
(Race of Wits starts.)
- 3. - 4.
- Five. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo is selected.)
(Wait, is it me?)
Why are you pretending to be calm?
Kwang Soo was being too careful.
One more person?
- Kwang Soo gets it all. - Right.
He gets a flick on his head.
- There should be 2 names. - There should be 2 names.
Two? That's right.
Shall I pick one person?
(Pick a person?)
That's good.
What do you think about that?
- That's good. - It sounds good.
- What do you think? - I agree.
I agree.
What do you think?
I asked what you think. What do you think?
Three people agreed with my picking another member.
Three votes. What do you think?
- Kwang Soo. - What do you think?
- I agree. - You agree?
- What should I do? - Kwang Soo.
- I agree. - Everyone agrees.
Listen.
I'll do this.
Jae Seok and I will play rock-paper-scissors.
If I lose,
my name will be attached twice, and I'll get the forehead flick.
- Really? - Yes.
If you lose,
your name will be attached twice, and you'll get the forehead flick.
That's great.
Gosh, Kwang Soo knows how to fight.
This is good.
Kwang Soo gets competitive.
- One person takes it all. - That sounds good.
What if I don't play?
You'll seem like a coward.
- Pathetic? - You'll be a coward.
Pardon?
You're a tiger moth.
Jae Seok won't refuse.
(Jae Seok wouldn't refuse this.)
- Will I be pathetic? - You'll be a pathetic coward.
Okay.
I'll be one.
(He agrees to be a coward.)
(He refuses to fight.)
- What? - Are you a coward?
Will you be pathetic?
(What's wrong with being a pathetic coward?)
- Will you be pathetic? - A coward.
I'll be a pathetic coward.
- That's what I will be. - Put his name on.
- I'll only put my name on. - Kwang Soo will get a flick.
- Jae Seok is quite wise. - Yes.
- He isn't reckless. - He isn't.
Kwang Soo's name will be attached and get a flick on his forehead.
Let's do this.
Let's play a simple game.
If you win,
I'll get the forehead flick, and my name will be attached twice.
I'll take all the punishment.
What else?
What if you win?
If I win, Jae Seok gets the flick, and his name will be attached.
I'll put my name too.
If he wins, you take all the punishment?
(If he wins, he'll put his name once.)
That's strange.
(In that case...)
I won't do it.
(He rejects his second proposal.)
In that case...
- Be more extreme. - Okay.
Propose me something more extreme.
- Then... - How about this?
If you win,
I'll take all the punishment.
- One flick on your forehead? - Yes.
Your name will be attached twice.
- What if you win? - This is important.
What if I lose?
You can flick my forehead.
- What? - That's not bad.
- What if I lose? - That's more important.
What would you like to do?
- Don't get a flick. - Put your name on.
Okay.
- Put your name once. - Put your name once.
Just once.
- He doesn't get a flick? - You take it all.
If not, he has no reason to accept it.
- Let's do that. - Do what?
I get flicked on my forehead.
What are you trying to do?
- I don't know. - You can pick a person.
- Wait a minute. - Will it ever end?
It's the same as picking a person.
What would be more advantageous?
How can I survive?
Each of your names will be attached, right?
If he wins, your name will be attached twice.
Is that what you're proposing?
Will you also participate?
I'm just a spectator.
I'll play if Seok Jin plays.
- Why would I play? - Play with us.
If not, pick Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Why me?
If he won't play, pick Seok Jin.
What will the spectator do?
I'll make it short.
Will you play or not?
(He really makes it short.)
- If the spectator... - If he plays,
- I'll select him. - Okay.
Seok Jin, if you refuse this offer, you're done for.
(What do you mean?)
Otherwise, you're done. You must do it.
- Do you surrender? - Wait.
- Why are you doing this to me? - If not, you'll be punished.
- You must play. - You have to.
- I'll pick you. - I'll play.
Okay.
Okay, that's good.
If Kwang Soo loses,
he gets a flick, and his name is attached twice, right?
If Kwang Soo wins,
he gets a flick on the forehead, but both names will be attached.
- That's right. - Okay.
- It's clear, right? - Yes.
It's clear.
What about throwing a die?
It turns out that all of them are unlucky.
- All right. - You have no complaints, right?
I must win no matter what.
- Yes. - My name will be attached anyway.
Good luck.
You can do it, Jae Seok.
- Okay. - It must be high.
- Higher number wins. - Yes.
It must be high.
The higher number wins.
Throw one.
(The higher the number, the more advantageous Kwang Soo gets.)
(Kwang Soo isn't good at missions. How will it turn out?)
Okay.
(He throws 5.)
(He has hope.)
You should say, "start".
- You didn't say, "start". - He didn't.
- That's right. - Wait.
- That won't work. - Why didn't you say, "start"?
- It's an official game. - That's right.
You should have said it.
Isn't this an official game?
- It's necessary for official games. - Kwang Soo.
Even the viewers recognized that you didn't say it.
That's right.
(Is this an official game?)
- You must say, "start". - I'm sorry.
- Say, "start". - Start.
(This is Running Man's annual campaign.)
(Remember to say, "start" before starting official games.)
- Start. - That's good.
This is for real.
This is an official throw of a die.
(When did it become an official game?)
(This is more competitive and important than the yolk game.)
(What will his number be?)
- Two. - Okay.
(It's a small number.)
It got worse.
That was very clean.
It's two for Lee Kwang Soo.
Right.
Did you hear that?
(How dare you?)
- If Jae Seok throws one, - Okay!
he's really unlucky.
- Start. - Okay.
(He hopes for anything but one.)
(Kwang Soo hopes that he throws 1.)
(Whose side will the die take?)
Six.
(It's amazing. It's 6.)
(Compared to Kwang Soo, Jae Seok is quite lucky.)
- Give me one more chance. - Suddenly?
I got six anyway.
He got six.
How about this?
If I lose, I'll get flicked twice.
(He accepts the offer.)
If I win, your name will be attached once.
- That sounds good. - Just one.
(If Kwang Soo wins, his name is attached once.)
Let's start.
Start.
His eyes got wide.
(A small bet became very serious.)
(Will their names be attached?)
(Or will Kwang Soo get flicked twice?)
- Five. - Okay.
(Okay, it's 5.)
If I win, your names will be attached.
I won't play anymore.
Start. I almost didn't say it.
(Will Jae Seok throw 6 twice in a row?)
(If Jae Seok throws 6, Kwang Soo takes all the punishment.)
(If it's lower than 5, Jae Seok and Seok Jin's names are attached.)
(Goodness, it's 6.)
(He throws six twice in a row.)
Jae Seok.
(Kwang Soo makes his opponents lucky.)
- Jae Seok. - No way.
This is unbelievable.
- It's unbelievable. - It's unbelievable.
(Should I go home?)
My goodness.
Between 1 and 6...
- It will be his name tags. - So...
His name is attached twice, and he gets flicked twice.
Put your name twice.
I'll flick his forehead later.
(I'll flick Kwang Soo's forehead later.)
- When will you do it? - Later.
- When you want to? - Yes.
Have a seat. I'll flick your forehead later.
- How did I throw six? - I know.
(Current roulette status)
I'll be leaving now.
- Are you really leaving? - Do Yeon.
- See you in Part Two. - You'll be back anyway.
Will you be back later?
I'm leaving. I'm busy.
- Really? - I'm leaving.
- See you. - Bye.
- Enjoy your food. - See you, Do Yeon.
(We thank Jang Do Yeon for joining us.)
- You didn't give us a hint. - That's right.
(It's the second hint.)
"It's bigger than Jae Seok but smaller than Haha."
- What is it? - What's that?
- Two. - What is it?
- Is it someone's hand? - It's right.
The 1st is 2.
What could this mean?
(What is this?)
It's the foot size.
- It's 200... - 275mm?
It could be 275 or 276.
That's not how shoe size is measured.
It's by 5mm.
Okay, it has something to do with two.
Next game is called...
Nationwide Zero Human.
(Nationwide Zero Human)
- What is that? - "Nationwide"?
"Zero"?
There's a special guest who will join you.
- Isn't it Do Yeon? - She's on her way.
If it is, she's working hard today.
- Is it Do Yeon? - Do Yeon is working hard.
Why is she covering her face?
- Jang Do Man. - Why are you back?
What's wrong with her nose?
(They burst out laughing.)
I came after Big Nose Seok Jin.
What did you do to your nose?
(This is Jang Nose Yeon.)
That's very detailed.
- You didn't have to do that. - She really came back.
You don't have to do that.
- It's all right. - What's wrong?
(She tries to take off the burden.)
Let's get going.
This mission is called...
Nationwide Zero Human.
You will be given five minutes.
Within five minutes, you must bring someone...
who's from your hometown.
(Bring someone from your hometown in 5 minutes.)
Where would I find someone from Gangwon Province?
No one is from Dongducheon.
(It's impossible to find people from their hometowns.)
I can't find anyone.
It can be anyone from the same province.
- Gyeongsang Province? - That's right.
- There are many from Gyeonggi. - Right.
- There are many from Seoul. - Of course.
There are many from Gyeongsang Province.
Can it be a staff member?
That's possible.
- Start. - Start.
There will be a few from Seoul.
- How about Gyeongsang Province? - Isn't he from Gyeonggi Province?
- Yu Ri. - I'm from Seoul.
Are you from Seoul? I can bring you. Come here, Yu Ri.
Anyone from Gyeongsang Province? No? Why isn't there anyone?
Where's your hometown?
- I'm from Seoul. - Seoul?
Where were you born?
In Gyeonggi Province.
(She finds someone easily.)
Gyeonggi Province? Come with me.
Are you from Gyeongsang Province?
- I am. - Come with me for a moment.
- It doesn't matter to me. - All right.
- Where are you from? - Gangwon Province.
Gangwon Province! Where specifically?
- Chuncheon. - Let's go.
- Have you all gathered? - Yes.
Let's start from the left. Please introduce yourselves.
- Introduce yourselves. - Hi.
Where are you from?
Hello, I'm from Mungyeong, North Gyeongsang Province.
- Mungyeong. - Mungyeong.
I'm from the south.
That's not the right accent.
You're so bad at it.
If you try to do the accent, it sounds awkward.
What do you think?
- It sounds awkward. - You sound awkward.
- Do you think so? - People don't do that.
Is that right?
- That's cool. - I have an accent.
- That's not it. - The weather is great.
- What do you think about that? - It's not right at all.
Why?
He's so bad with accents.
How are you supposed to say it then?
- In Gyeongsang Province... - Say, "The weather is nice."
This is nice.
(It's simple.)
You don't overdo it.
It has to be light.
- Did he kind of exaggerate? - He exaggerated too much.
(That's what the expert says.)
How embarrassing.
(I'll protect my accents.)
- Next to me... - All right.
is the scriptwriter Yu Ri.
- She's been with us for a while. - Right.
You're the scriptwriter for Running Man,
so do you have any requests for us?
- Be honest. - I hope...
I hope you don't break any rules.
Rule breaker. Who are you talking about specifically?
Some people destroy the rules.
(They destroy rules.)
Somebody destroys the rules.
- She didn't say who. - Don't take it the wrong way.
She didn't say it was you.
Right. She didn't.
Is there somebody else?
There are two more people who keep destroying the rules.
- They destroy rules? - Right.
So Min, I see.
I agree. It's them.
Let me ask you this.
Who's worse? The rule breaker or the rule destroyers?
Who's worse?
Who is it?
(She's been with us for 2 years. She never had this dilemma before.)
(Rule breaker...)
(versus rule destroyers)
The rule breaker.
- She didn't say who it was. - This is great.
To be honest, Jong Kook bends the rules,
- so our staff has to work harder. - They improve.
- That's right. - They're on alert.
- If not, we would have stalled. - Of course. I agree.
I agree. Next. What is your role?
I am part of the camera team.
She's part of the camera team.
- The cameras. - What's hard...
and fun about your job? You can say what's fun first.
It's fun to watch you guys...
- without any editing. - You can watch us live.
You're in the moment.
- I agree. - You're in the moment.
You sound so pure.
You watched many segments that didn't make the cut, right?
Are there some people who may be banned from TV?
(Gazing)
- She looked at Kwang Soo. - Me?
- She can't deny it. - It's okay.
- She was looking up. - She was.
- But... - She looked at Kwang Soo.
Watch your mouth. You have to watch yourself.
Is there anything you would like from us?
Don't block the shots.
- We block the cameras. - That's right.
Who keeps blocking your camera?
(Gazing)
Me again?
- Kwang Soo. She looked up again. - No, wait.
Why did you block it?
I didn't mean to.
- I was trying to look. - Be careful.
I will.
She told me directly, so I know now.
- Pay attention. - I'll be cautious.
That was Eun Ji. Who's next?
- He's our scriptwriter. - Right.
I don't have anything to do, so can I interview him?
- Sure. Go ahead. - I'm really bored.
- Hello. You're our scriptwriter. - Yes.
He used to be on "Infinite Challenge".
Why are you here?
(Why are you here?)
- Goodness. - Why are you here, punk?
(I'm trying to move on.)
Stop it.
(I get to see you a day late, but it's still nice to see you.)
- What a coincidence. - I know.
Don't insert the skull faces around us.
You keep inserting them in the subtitles.
They're trying to make fun of us.
They can insert the running skeletons.
- Goodness. - All right.
- Then... - I'm looking forward to this one.
She's Jae Seok's stylist.
She's my stylist.
Let's ask her all the questions we have.
Is there anything you want Jae Seok to fix?
Is there anything?
(He's anxious.)
(A close associate of Jae Seok reveals his secret.)
His pants are too tight.
(That's not presentable.)
She said his pants are too tight. He wears skinny jeans.
I can't give them up.
Excuse me. Why is it so tight around the hips?
He prefers those types of clothes.
- He likes tight clothes. - Does he?
You can't put it that way.
If he likes tight-fitting clothes so much,
you should paint his body.
It'll look like he has clothes on.
Stop it.
Goodness.
(That's Jae Seok's secret fashion style.)
- Let's start the Zero game. - Okay.
This is tough.
- How? - This is too hard.
You must sit or stand at the same time...
- I call out a number. - Okay.
You win if the number of people who stand up...
is different from the number I call.
You have to win five times in a row.
- All right. - We have to be different from her.
- In a row? - You must win in a row.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Start. Let's start.
1, 2, 3. 7 people.
(Do Yeon yells out "7".)
- What a relief. - We won.
We won once.
- She'll do "zero" too. - She will.
All right.
(This is a mental game.)
1, 2, 3. 4 people.
2, 3. 4 people.
Bravo.
(They lose...)
(after the second attempt.)
Did you stand up on purpose?
(If Running Man loses, there's more material to air.)
You are on the staff's side, right?
- Did you stand up on purpose? - No.
(Yu Ri is hardworking.)
- Did we lose? - Did we?
You failed the mission. You have another chance.
- If you give up a name tag, - Hold on.
- we'll give you another chance. - Okay.
(They get another chance if they give up a name tag.)
Okay.
Stand up. Stand up, Yu Ri.
- Who stood up earlier? - Who just stood up?
We can get Jong Kook's name tag.
Look. We're in this together. I don't want another chance then.
This is what Yu Ri was talking about.
You're a rule breaker.
- Listen to me. - Okay.
We're doing this for everybody's good.
- I'm not entirely responsible. - Fine. Then the four of you,
- do rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- If they lose, - Sounds good?
- their partner gets the penalty. - Okay.
- You have to win. - Do rock-paper-scissors.
Good luck.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok and Se Chan win. Jong Kook and Ji Hyo lose.)
All right! Nice.
Great.
Do you want a fist fight?
What? Why would they do that?
I don't know who'll win then.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo loses, and Jong Kook wins.)
- We take Ji Hyo's name tag. - Okay.
- Her name wasn't on the roulette. - That's right.
Let's do better.
Let's go, Gyeongsang Province.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's get started. - Ready.
1, 2, 3. 7 people.
(First attempt)
- I almost stood up. - This is good.
- We won once. - You won once.
Let's go again. 1, 2, 3. 3 people.
(Second attempt)
- Okay. - All right.
(They win the second attempt...)
(this time.)
- Good. - All right.
Here we go. 1, 2, 3. 5 people.
(Third attempt)
- That was close. - We have four people.
Good thing I didn't stand up.
- 2 more times? - We only need to win 2 more times.
Here's the fourth attempt.
1, 2, 3. 6 people.
(Six!)
(4 people stand up...)
(and 2 more on either side of Haha.)
We lost.
(Did they fail the mission?)
(7 people stood up.)
We got seven.
Good thing I stood up, right?
- We did it. - Last one.
- There's one left. - Last one.
- This is the last one. - We only have one left.
(Let's keep going.)
Here's the last one.
(If they win this time...)
1, 2...
(If they win this time, they can obtain a hint.)
3. 7 people.
(Seven!)
- 2... Hold on. - It's 7.
(Did seven people stand up?)
Seven.
(8 people stood up.)
2... Hold on.
2, 4, 6, 8.
Okay.
(They succeed the mission.)
- We did it. - What a relief.
- We won. - What a relief.
- That was so close. - We did it.
- We got it. - We did it.
Thanks, Yu Ri. Thank you.
We did it. All right.
We'll be able to open it once we see this.
- I think so. - It's this.
- This... - What?
- Chuseok? - It's a half-moon-shaped rice cake.
Half-moon-shaped rice cake.
- Chuseok? Two syllables? - Chuseok.
- Moon. Chuseok. - Is this it?
(What is this?)
- 2 syllables. Chuseok. - 2 syllables.
Chuseok.
- Half-moon-shaped rice cake. - Half-moon-shaped rice cake.
- I think that's it. - What?
It's larger than me.
I think it's a date in between.
- It is a date? - Birthday?
Right? Three syllables.
- Your birthday is August 20, right? - Yes, August 20.
My birthday is August 14.
That works.
- August 15. - That's you.
(Ji Hyo's birthday is on August 15.)
- Me? - Her birthday?
- 815? - But...
there are so many numbers in between.
What does this mean then? August 15 and...
- That's the confusing part. - That is.
- Victory. - Do we only get one chance?
(They only get one chance to open the briefcase.)
(If they don't open it in one try, they all get the penalty.)
Do you want to try another one?
- We have to. - Just one more?
Let's be certain.
Let's be certain. We only get one chance.
(What is the passcode of the briefcase?)
Here's the game.
What's the most important thing about going home on Chuseok?
- Safe driving. - Safe driving is important.
So this mission is called...
Drive Safely on Your Way Home on Chuseok.
(Fourth mission: Drive Safely)
This is nice.
- Drive safely. - Drive safely.
The rule is simple.
You have to reverse park this car...
without touching the paper cups.
I'm an expert.
(They have to reverse park without making the paper cups fall.)
Let's roll the die...
and decide how many people will play.
A certain number of people have to do it.
I hope it's one.
Kwang Soo is a horrible driver.
- I'm even worse at parking. - Oh, dear.
- Roll the die. - I'll do it.
(Nobody asked him to do it.)
Will you?
- Hey, it's Chuseok. - Do it.
- Start. - Start.
(They're worried.)
(He rolls the die as if he's throwing a yut.)
(Is he lucky today?)
(Please let it be 3.)
- No... - It's six.
(Of course.)
It's six.
(This is driving me nuts.)
6. 6 people have to do it.
Let's do this.
Okay, who's starting?
- I'll go. - Make the best driver go.
- Jae Seok, - I'll show you.
- you're the best driver. - Go ahead.
You can do it.
Here he goes.
- Start. - Go.
It's slow.
You need to reverse park without making the cups fall.
It has to be at the level of your shoulders.
There's a rear-view mirror.
You have to go a little bit more. That's good. Stop.
That's good. Reverse.
(He just needs to reverse now.)
- The opening is too narrow. - It's so narrow.
(He adds some background music.)
(Wait)
Stop!
(He's about to bump into it.)
Be careful!
Stop fooling around.
Don't enjoy this.
- You have to go a little bit more. - I think I'm good.
- No! - Watch the left.
- Straighten out your wheel. - It has to fit perfectly.
You have space on the right.
- Straighten out your wheel. - Keep going.
- Watch the left. - Go forward.
No, reverse.
You almost had it.
(He goes forward again.)
(He's the only one who's excited.)
He's having fun.
- It's breezy, - What a rascal.
and there are people around, so he's happy.
- They're watching him too. - I'm so happy.
He mentioned that.
He wanted to ride this when he was a child.
- I really wanted to ride this. - He did.
(He reverses abruptly as he talks.)
They didn't fall.
- You have to go out. - Go out.
- Go straight slowly. - Straighten out.
- He touched it. - Keep going.
That's good.
(He has a little bit more to go.)
- You did it. - I did it.
(He passes the mission while humming an addictive tune.)
Great job.
(They complimented him too much.)
He's cute.
Hey, come back.
(It took him 47 years to realize that he enjoys speed.)
(He drives the convertible in the vast plains.)
What is wrong with you?
- He likes to drive. - He must be so happy.
- He likes to drive. - Yes.
I'll return the car.
This is valet parking.
- Is it? - This is a valet.
- You have to pay me two dollars. - Okay.
You know it's four dollars now, right?
- Oh, dear. - My goodness.
- I have to use the door. - Right.
Who's next?
- Seok Jin. - Should I go?
Go ahead, Seok Jin.
He'll be fine.
- Drift. - He's a good driver.
He is.
I'm amazing. Start.
(Can he recover from rolling a bad number?)
(That's drifting.)
He can be on the Gangbyeon Expressway.
You can go to your in-laws' with this.
(He can ride this to his in-laws'.)
He has to leave two days before.
- Slowly. - Come on.
(He lines up the back of his car with the opening.)
(He reverses at full speed.)
- Seok Jin. - Goodness.
Gosh...
Hold on.
- This... - What is your problem?
I didn't...
do it on purpose.
- I swear I didn't. - What is your problem?
- No, listen. - What is wrong with you?
I couldn't stop it.
My foot won't come off.
He's stuttering.
Get out.
Can I try another time?
- You can't. We failed. - You can't.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
(The third driver is the lucky Ji Hyo.)
Stop!
(She fails because of one cup.)
That was so close.
You're supposed to turn it once, right?
This is small...
(Driving in real life is different from the manual.)
(She slams on the pedal and knocks over the cups.)
(This is a true muscle car.)
(The fifth driver is the talented Jong Kook. He succeeds.)
(It suits him 100 percent. Is this his car?)
He drives this at home occasionally.
(He tried it at home thanks to his son.)
- Success. - You did it.
- More, more. - Okay.
(Se Chan succeeds as well.)
Kwang Soo, you have to succeed.
- You can do it. Go ahead. - We'll use the chance card
You have to succeed so that we can use Do Yeon.
This is easy for him.
- We're almost done. - Okay.
How is Kwang Soo's driving?
- He's... - He's dangerous.
not very talented.
He pretends like he's a good driver.
Yes, that's how bad drivers are.
(That's how bad drivers are.)
- Start. - I'll do it my style.
- Start! - Okay.
He put the lights on.
You have to succeed so that we can use Do Yeon.
Kwang Soo, you have to make big turns.
(He has to succeed so that they can use Do Yeon.)
What's that? That looks cool.
(His left hand is barely holding on.)
(He looks pretty cool.)
You have to do this.
(Version 2 of his awesomeness)
Women like that move.
Your backside looks beautiful.
(Is it time to show my skills?)
He's turning the wheel the other way.
(He doesn't know a thing about driving.)
- Like this? - Of course.
How did you get your license?
- Hey, how did you get it? - This is driving me nuts.
- Stop. - No, don't come.
(He's close.)
- Go forward. - You have to go forward.
Good. Come.
- More. One more time. - Keep coming.
- The front side... - Good.
(Moving)
(That's a new way of using the wheel.)
Good. Good job.
- Go in. - Go straight in.
Keep going. Okay.
Okay. Good. A little bit more.
Your front is not straight.
(If I'm not straight in the front...)
Not too much.
- Stop! - Stop!
(He was almost done, but he moves back abruptly.)
(He went too much.)
Stop.
- No, he got it. - He's good.
- Go forward. - Do I go forward?
- I'll go forward. - He's good.
You have to watch these two.
(Did he fail or succeed?)
Let's see.
(Please don't fall.)
- Let's see. - He's good. All right.
(They didn't fall.)
Go. Go straight.
- You're good. Go. - Go straight.
Your wheel.
You're good.
- He's good. - Okay.
(The last driver, Kwang Soo, gets lucky and succeeds.)
- Let's use Do Yeon. - Success.
- Do I go? - Do Yeon Chance.
Kwang Soo, you looked cool.
Jang Do Yeon Chance.
- Jang Do Yeon... - Jang Do Yeon Chance.
Let's do this.
The gas is on the right, and the brake is on the left, right?
- Do Yeon. - This...
- It's this. - Bring it down.
That's reverse.
- That's drive. - I see.
- Drive. - This is reverse.
- Don't leave your door open. - Hold on.
- Stop! - There's a camera.
(She almost collides with the camera.)
- You almost broke the camera. - Do Yeon.
- What is this? - There's no brake.
- Is there no brake? - No, there isn't.
- Drive. - What do we do?
She has big feet, so she can't take her feet off.
We're in trouble. We can't do it.
Go towards the right. Good.
Take your foot off.
- Take your foot off. - Reverse.
- Do Yeon. - Yes?
Turn the steering wheel the other way.
(He didn't tell her to move.)
- Stop! - The other way.
Turn the wheel the other way.
- Go forward more. - This is too different from my car.
Whose car is it like?
Go forward more.
- Good. Stop. - Good.
Reverse, Do Yeon. Change the gear.
She's too serious.
Come. A little bit more.
- Stop. - Good.
- A little bit more. - Press on it lightly.
- Put your foot on it. - You're good.
- Turn the wheel. - To the right slightly.
- Do Yeon, reverse. - Reverse.
- Stop! - Good.
(Stop)
- Move slightly. - Keep it at that.
- Move very slightly. - Keep it at that.
- A little bit more. - One more time.
One more time. Just once.
- That's right. - Move as much as you did...
- one more time. - Reverse.
- Reverse. - A little bit more.
- One more time. - Reverse.
Go a little bit farther.
- One more time. - A little bit more.
- Go a little bit farther. - Mind the handle.
- Okay. - A little bit more.
- Yes! - Yes!
(She did it.)
Gosh, she did it.
It's not an easy task.
You completed a difficult task.
- Do Yeon. - Her foot got stuck.
She has big feet.
- Good job, Jang Do Feet. - Jang Do Feet.
- Thank goodness. - Good job.
(She is moved.)
Thank goodness.
Since you succeeded, you will get two hints.
Bravo.
We will know the passcode now.
I am 100-percent sure of it.
- Hangawi. - Hangawi.
"Hangawi" and "Scissors" sound similar.
On the lunar calendar, Chuseok is August 15.
That means the passcode is 815.
- Ji Hyo's birthday is August 15th. - 815.
- That's right. - The passcode is 815.
- It's 815. - Let's go.
Do you want to try the passcode or try the next mission?
- We will go and try the passcode. - We will go.
(They decide to open the briefcase.)
(Is the passcode 815 as they think?)
(The lobby of Mok-dong SBS)
There is the briefcase!
We found it!
- Move out of the way! - 815!
It's mine.
- It's the briefcase! - 815.
- Hold on. - Let's open it. Try 815.
Which way do the numbers go?
- 8 should go first. - 815.
Eight.
- Eight. - Maybe it won't open again.
(Nervous)
1, 5.
(They only have one chance. Let's see if the briefcase opens.)
(Clicking)
(The passcode is 815.)
There is the mission card.
(Expectant)
(What is the secret on the mission card?)
"Go to the ninth floor."
(Go to the 9th floor.)
- What is this? - Did we wait a week for this?
- Did we wait a week for this? - Is this it?
- Is this it? - What is this?
Something else will begin.
The ninth floor? Okay. Let's go and see what's there.
Maybe Do Yeon is running over to the ninth floor.
If Do Yeon is there again, I am going to have a word with her.
The ninth floor? Do we go that way?
- Let's take the elevator. - I can't believe it.
I saw Do Yeon remove the microphone.
- What a letdown. We waited a week. - Is this it?
- Let's go. - The ninth floor.
(They are on their way to the 9th floor.)
So Min, wear this.
Why?
(You look cute when you wear it, So Min.)
- I think it's cute. - It's cute.
Kwang Soo is wearing it.
(He has the same hairband.)
(Peek-a-boo)
(The same bunny-ear hairbands look different on them.)
(Hello, I am Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo is such an eyesore.
Kwang Soo, they want you to go to the 10th floor.
(Do you take me for a fool?)
All right. All right.
(I heard everything too.)
Don't hit me. It hurts. All right. All right. All right.
I was joking.
(I promise I will kick you if you do it again.)
(The violent bunny goes to the 9th floor with everyone.)
All right.
We came back to where we started.
We could have stayed here.
- What? - What?
Kwang Soo, there is a panel.
What? There is something.
(A mysterious panel stands in the garden.)
- Chuseok. - Chuseok.
(Chuseok)
- What is that? - There are Seok Jin and Jae Seok.
(It's a Chuseok panel with the faces of Seok Jin and Jae Seok.)
What is this?
- Jong Kook. - There is something.
There is a final mission.
(They find the final mission card.)
The final mission?
(What's the final mission?)
"Arrest the Chuseok Brothers who are hiding in the building..."
- "in 20 minutes." - Seok Jin and Jae Seok?
Seok Jin and Jae Seok?
(Search the building,)
(and find Jae Seok and Seok Jin in 20 minutes.)
They both have "Seok" in their names.
"Chu" from Chuseok can mean "to chase".
- "Chase Seok Jin and Jae Seok." - Let's go.
We have 20 minutes.
(The 2nd floor of the SBS building 30 minutes before the shoot)
What?
Will we have a special mission today?
Today is the day.
This is that briefcase.
This is that briefcase we saw before.
- Right. Where are the others? - Hey.
Can't you tell?
The two of us must have an important task.
I carried it everywhere.
Why is there a phone?
What is this?
There is nothing.
What's inside this briefcase? Can we open it?
- No? - They told us not to open it.
(Clicking)
- I can't believe you! - It opens.
Come on, I didn't open it. It's unlocked.
(He wants to know what's inside.)
Shall I open it?
(Let's take a peek.)
- Let's open it. - What is inside?
- We are the only ones here. - What's this?
(They open the Pandora's box.)
- What is this? - What is it?
"We told you not to open it."
- For goodness' sake. - "Why did you open it?"
(Are you kidding me?)
What?
"You must go where the staff tells you to go..."
"because you received the Blank Penalty Ticket."
(You must go where the crew tells you to go...)
(because you received the Blank Penalty Ticket.)
- What is this? - You are a bad person.
(Where do they want us to go?)
- Where do you want us to go? - Where do you want us to go?
- Hold on. - Why did you open it?
They told me to do whatever I wanted.
What is the Blank Penalty Ticket?
Hello.
(Nervous)
Last week, I told you not to open the briefcase.
- The Blank Penalty Ticket? - That was last week.
Seok Jin opened it. I don't know anything about it.
- I just opened... - I will put him on the phone.
(He tosses over the phone.)
- What are you doing? - You flipped it open...
- after I unlocked it. - You opened it.
You flipped it open.
- You opened it. - I simply unlocked it.
- Why did you fiddle with it? - Hello.
Hello.
Last week, the briefcase contained...
the Blank Penalty Ticket.
(My goodness.)
Don't act when you heard the mission.
- Hello. What did you say? - What are you doing?
Please tell me once more.
Why are you doing this with the two of us?
Last week, Seok Jin...
- lost the briefcase twice. - That's right. He lost it twice.
Last week, you said,
"I will take the briefcase now."
(Last week, you said, "I will take the briefcase now.")
I said it once,
but Haha took the responsibility.
(I just said that out of frustration.)
(Jae Seok saw Seok Jin lose the briefcase.)
(I will take the briefcase now.)
(He regrets saying those words.)
There is a way to avoid the penalty.
Find out the passcode,
- open the briefcase, - And?
and come back here in secret. Then I will tell you.
You want us to come back here without telling the members?
Where? Here? Without telling the members?
(When the members went to the 9th floor)
I need to use the restroom.
(Jae Seok excused himself in a natural way.)
(Okay. I can follow Jae Seok.)
For goodness' sake.
Is there a way to go to the second floor from here?
- No. - We have to go that way.
They will see us right away.
What are these?
- What are these? - What are these?
- Bells? - There are bells.
(There are 10 bells and new uniforms for them.)
What's the final mission?
"Hide from the members who are pursuing you."
"If you don't get arrested, you are exempt from the penalty."
"Two members who are chosen by the roulette get the penalty."
"If you get arrested, you get the penalty."
This is driving me crazy.
"You must wear the 10 bells among yourselves."
(10 bells?)
This is driving me crazy.
If we wear the bells, it's a given.
We are likely to get caught as we are,
but they want us to run with the bells.
(They change into red uniforms.)
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
Put one bell on your sneakers.
I will wear one bell.
(Wear 9 bells, Seok Jin.)
I will wear nine bells. I will wear them all.
(Seok Jin gets 9 bells.)
Don't get caught.
- Will you wear all the bells? - Yes, I will.
Seok Jin, I will survive no matter what.
- You need to survive. - That's right.
I really don't want the penalty.
"If you fail to arrest them, the Chuseok Brothers get exempt."
"Two members who are chosen by the roulette get the penalty."
Two members? The chance is too great.
Shouldn't we run?
We parted ways on the first floor.
Where would you go?
They said they were going to the restroom.
5, 4.
- Already? - Are we getting started?
Four.
(If they get arrested, they get the penalty.)
- Three. - We are getting started.
Why don't we split up?
- Two. - Let's not get penalized.
- One. - Seriously.
- Let's go. - We have 20 minutes.
(The Chuseok Brothers are out if they get touched.)
(Can they arrest them in this big building...)
(in 20 minutes?)
(The Chuseok Race starts.)
Kwang Soo, good luck.
Let's search the first floor and go underground.
Let's go underground...
- and check out the other side. - The other side.
They could be on the first floor.
Jae Seok likes...
the open space.
Where are they?
They must be hiding.
The first floor.
I will get going.
Go.
(Jae Seok goes first.)
(His movements are light since he has 1 bell.)
Where should we go?
(While Jae Seok moves around the 2nd floor,)
(Se Chan appears on the 1st floor.)
They must be... I hear the bells.
(I hear the bells somewhere.)
(Kwang Soo hears Jae Seok's bell from the 1st floor.)
(Let's run away.)
(Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, Se Chan)
(I hear it from above.)
(Kwang Soo begins chasing after the sound.)
- What is it? - I hear the bells.
Did you hear it? Was it above you?
Yes, above.
- Jong Kook. - Okay. Let's go upstairs.
(The hunters close in.)
(Jae Seok is at the top of the staircase.)
(Jae Seok runs away through the side door.)
(As soon as the door closes,)
(Kwang Soo enters by a close call.)
(He passes by the door Jae Seok disappeared into.)
(I definitely heard the sound from here. Did he go that way?)
(What a relief. I almost got caught.)
This is too dangerous.
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin with 9 bells...)
Which floor is the editing room on?
- 6th floor. - Let's go to the 6th floor.
- Does that go to the sixth floor? - Yes.
The editing room is complicated to get around.
(Clattering)
(He goes to the elevator while making a lot of noises.)
6th floor. Let's go to the 6th floor.
If I last for about 15 minutes,
Jae Seok can probably last five minutes by himself.
(He can manage from then on, right?)
(He arrives on the 6th floor where the editing room is.)
(The editing room is across the hall.)
No one is here, right?
(Let me hold out for 15 minutes in this complicated-looking floor.)
I'm going to run. I'm going to run there.
(He runs to the editing room with a big plan in mind.)
(What? He runs into Haha right away.)
(His grand plan has failed, and he runs away.)
(I got you! Freeze!)
(Haha was checking the editing rooms on the 6th floor by chance.)
Excuse me.
(He spotted Seok Jin on the 6th floor.)
Hold on a second.
(Is this destiny?)
(What a lucky find! Seok Jin is given to him on a silver platter.)
(Hello, Seok Jin!)
(Forget about 15 minutes. He's on the run in his 1st minute.)
(He runs into a dead-end studio.)
I'm sorry. Please excuse us.
(Seok Jin desperately runs one last time while Haha says hello.)
(Let me stay in the race for a bit longer today.)
(Haha touches him.)
(Seok Jin is arrested.)
- I'm sorry. - I'm so sorry.
I had a feeling he was on this floor.
How could we meet there?
- How could we meet there? - Are you all right?
I'm fine.
The race starts. Jae Seok.
This was our plan. It was our plan. Make sure you stay alive.
Jee Seok Jin is eliminated.
What? Already?
- Already? - We started about two minutes ago.
- Really? - Yes.
Already?
(They're happy but fascinated.)
It's great since we don't have time.
Why did you give Seok Jin such an important assignment?
This is no fun.
This is no fun. I didn't get to watch it.
What? What did you say?
- He's out. - He's already eliminated?
(Seriously, Seok Jin? I must last 15 minutes all by myself?)
My gosh, this guy is ridiculous.
- Where was that hall earlier? - You pressed 13th floor.
- Ji Hyo, let's go down. - 13th floor?
Let's check the 13th floor.
I don't think Jae Seok went up to a high floor.
But think about it. He has to hide, so...
Goodness.
Ji Hyo, that's awesome!
(Jackpot)
Jae Seok is here!
(Jae Seok was trying to hide in the open hall.)
(He was caught at an impeccable timing before their eyes.)
(He's the sole survivor! Catch Jae Seok!)
- Where is that? - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
Hold on. Hold on a second, Ji Hyo. Give me a second, Ji Hyo.
How did we meet so quickly?
- How could we meet there? - We met face to face.
- This is not right. How could... - We got him right away.
How could this happen?
- How could we have met here? - Hold on. Hey.
- Why did you come up here? - She said she wanted to come here.
Besides, when the elevator doors opened up,
you passed by us right there then.
Why did you pass by at that time?
(This was only 1 minute ago.)
(I'll stay in the open hall on the 13th floor and hold out there.)
(I got a feeling from the open hall on the 13th floor.)
(Like telepathy, they both thought of the open hall.)
(And out of 1,200 seconds, they came face-to-face in that 1 second.)
- Out of all the time, why now? - Exactly.
Why did you pass by us then? What is this?
- Already? - What's more is that...
(Touching)
When the door was open...
I didn't mean to touch him. What should we do?
I didn't mean to touch him. I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
I touched you by accident when I was stroking my hair.
I was just doing this.
(Touching)
- Your hand was just there. - You've been arrested.
(She even perfectly reenacted the scene.)
- Let's go. - My day is just like that sunset.
(Just like the sunset...)
That was so futile.
- Yu Jae Seok is eliminated. - We'll go to the lobby now.
Yu Jae Seok is eliminated.
This is no fun. What is this?
- It already ended? - Yes.
Really?
(Only 6 minutes passed, but it's over?)
(He didn't even see the Chuseok Brothers.)
Seriously? What did they do to get caught?
What is this?
You guys had a great plan. 1 of you had only 1 bell.
It was a great strategy.
Why did you get caught so quickly?
What about you?
What do you mean? You guys had about a 30-second difference.
- Stop it. Be quiet. - It was about the same.
Gosh, this is crazy.
- Are you all right? - She's back?
You're wearing the same outfit from this morning.
(The Briefcase Girl shows up for the last time.)
- This is crazy. - You didn't go home yet.
Dangerous Delivery Part Two. The Secret of the Briefcase.
Last week, the staff had put in a Blank Penalty Ticket...
where the member had to go wherever the staff chose.
(We would've been in a royal mess.)
Had we opened this, we would've been in big trouble.
(Feeling dizzy)
- If someone opened the briefcase, - We could've been in trouble.
all of you had to leave right away.
- Where would I go with Seok Jin? - Seriously. I have a lot of work.
- What about us? - They will leave next week.
(They will be dragged to wherever the staff chooses next week.)
- Good for you. - My goodness.
- Kwang Soo. - This could've been terrible.
We should congratulate them.
All right. I hope you will spend...
- a nice Chuseok. - Right.
I hope you'll be blessed with an abundance.
I'd like to thank Jang Do Feet...
- for joining us today. - Great work, everyone.
I don't know where we'll end up next week.
We'll see you from somewhere next week.
- We don't get to choose, right? - They'll go anywhere.
We'll see you next week. Bye.
Bye!
Seok Jin, that sounded rude.
- Just like that character. - They'll edit it out if it is.
You said that the other day too.
(Screaming)
(What am I doing here?)
(Dangerous Delivery Finale: Dangerous Trip)