(Last week)
(Team Bobsleigh, fast-chasers on the ice)
(Team Curling, Ms. Glasses and her cool gang)
(Team Gateball, life starts at the age of 50.)
(Soohorang and the human-faced bird, mascots of Pyeongchang Olympics)
(And the impressive guests were invited.)
(Kim Ji Soo and Yun Sung Bin from Team Skeleton)
(They thrived on the ice, and last week, on the show.)
(They're the strongest pair. Is there anything they can't do?)
Can a national athlete do that?
(They were exceptionally witty too.)
(Sung Bin and Ji Soo ruled Running Man.)
You joined us today for a brief moment today. How was it today?
- I laughed a lot. My cheeks hurt. - Really?
- My gosh. - Stay for the whole show next time.
Yes, stay for long just like his face.
"Just like his face"?
- Only my side hair is long. - It's so long.
- It's long. - It looks longer than usual today.
After the first mission,
Ji Hyo won the Luxury Sticker.
Sung Bin will hand out the briefcase with her name on it.
- Briefcase? - What's that?
This? What is it?
(Congratulations, Ji Hyo.)
- I'm so envious of her. - Is that it?
What? It's empty.
(There's nothing.)
There's nothing inside.
What?
What? Did someone steal it?
(What? Someone stole it?)
(The Luxury Stickers got robbed?)
- Did someone steal it again? - It's empty.
- What? - What was that?
Do we need to get going?
(There's a mysterious message.)
- What? - What's this now?
There's a list.
(Scout List)
- They won't make it easy for us. - What is this?
Kwang Soo!
(Why is this list thrown at the members out of nowhere?)
What's this?
(Some people are watching.)
- There are 3 people. - 3 people?
(It's a message from three people.)
(Scoffing)
Are you surprised?
You must have been excited about receiving the Luxury Stickers.
The stickers are in our hands.
We are the coaches who got rejected when we tried to scout you...
for aerobic exercise club. We are currently among you.
(We are currently among you.)
They're among us.
The coaches are here.
(Are the 3 coaches among us?)
We came here today...
to eliminate the gold medalist who is hiding among you...
and overcome a blow to our egos.
(Are the 3 coaches targeting the gold medalist?)
If we find the gold medalist first,
your names will be listed for the Shuddering Package.
(The losers' names will be listed for the Shuddering Package.)
However, if you find us first,
we will list our names for the package.
- Shall we begin the real race? - Shall we begin the real race?
(Laughing)
- There are 3 coaches? - Yes, 3 coaches.
Let's find them.
(The three hidden coaches have sent them a video message.)
(Who are the three coaches that are among us?)
This is the Family Package Part 2,
and we're about to start today's actual race.
The 36th Olympic of Running Man,
The Sticker That Disappeared.
(The 36th Olympic of Running Man, The Sticker That Disappeared)
Among you, there are three coaches that are holding a grudge...
against the players that have turned them down.
And there's also one gold medalist that they're hoping to find.
If the gold medalist gets caught during the final race,
the victory will go to the coaches.
Their names will go up on the Luxury Package slot.
And six players out of the group...
will have their names put up on the Shuddering Package slot.
On the other hand,
if the players and the gold medalist succeed...
in finding the three coaches,
the victory will go to the players.
Thus, the three coaches will end up on the Shuddering Package slot.
Each member who wins a round will be given a clue...
about who the coaches and the gold medalist could be.
(The winner of each round will be given clues.)
The players have the upper hand since there are only three coaches.
And you're one of the coaches.
- Exactly. - You're one of them.
You and Da Hee are one of them.
- It's you and Da Hee. - It's not me.
I get accused every episode, but it's really not me.
Wait until they give you a clue.
- Don't you all think he's weird? - Yes, he's weird.
It's because of my outfit.
It's really not me.
First of all,
Ji Hyo won the first mission.
So instead of giving her a stolen sticker,
she'll be getting a clue about the coaches.
Steal it!
(Running)
What are you doing?
- I was going to check for you. - It's okay.
But she might be the coach.
Yes, she might be the coach.
(Ji Hyo herself might actually be the coach.)
(The three coaches all have different last names.)
The first clue always points out at everyone.
(Lee Da Hee, Lee Sang Yeob, Lee Kwang Soo)
(These three people can't all be coaches.)
- Let's move onto the next mission. - Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
- This is insane. - Come to think of it,
I think they're all women.
- The gold medalist is a woman. - That's possible.
- The gold medalist is a woman. - The three evil women.
- And the coaches are women too. - Right. Because if that's the case,
- I think I'm right. - the clues will be hard to get.
- No. - It could actually be Seok Jin.
It's Seok Jin.
I'm not a coach.
- Really? Are you sure? - Yes.
Then it could be the remaining four.
(Then it could be the remaining four women.)
He's so sharp.
(That was sharp, wasn't it?)
There are 3 coaches, not 4.
- 3 coaches. - 3 coaches and 1 gold medalist.
Seok Jin doesn't really know what's going on.
Wait. What's going on? Tell me.
- My gosh. - I don't get it.
Maybe Seok Jin's a bronze medalist.
(Seok Jin could be a bronze medalist without anyone's knowing.)
- A bronze medalist? - He makes things up.
You'll all be able to get a clue about the coaches...
through the mission we're about to do now.
It's Talk Backwards.
(Talk Backwards)
- "Talk Backwards"? - What's this?
After you listen to a word I say, you all need to take turns...
and say each letter of the word backwards.
I'll start with a word that has three syllables,
and it'll go up to seven syllables. If you all succeed,
you'll all be given a clue about the coaches.
That's too hard.
For example, if I say, "Yu Jae Seok".
- Seok, Jae, Yu. - Seok, Jae, Yu.
Then I'll move onto the next word. For example, "Please do not park."
- Park, Not, Do, Please. - Park, Not, Do, Please.
It's so hard.
And if I say, "Team that scouts talented people".
You'll have to say "People, Talented, Scouts, That, Team".
- It's so hard. - It's so difficult.
This is so similar to the other group game we played.
- You're right. - Okay.
- We only have to do it once. - It starts here.
- It's just once. - And it moves onto here.
But wait a minute. Think about this, Sang Yeob.
They're giving us a clue about the coaches.
That means the coaches won't want this game to succeed.
- The coaches will try to ruin it. - Exactly.
- The coaches will get in the way. - They'll get it wrong.
The coaches will purposely make a mistake.
We need to doubt the person that makes a mistake.
- That person is the coach. - The overall race is important,
but we need to pay attention right now.
Ji Hyo, you can do it properly this time.
Da Hee.
Don't wear your hat if your scalp itches.
(Just take your hat off if your scalp itches.)
- My gosh, stop scratching. - Da Hee.
- Wash your hair. - Da Hee.
It's okay. You don't need to wear it.
I guess her scalp was really itchy.
Yes, she was scratching like this.
But your hair probably doesn't smell as bad as So Min's.
- My hair smells nice. - Does it smell?
- It doesn't smell, right? - No, it doesn't.
- What about mine? - They're both...
- They're both smelling their hair. - What?
Hey, don't lie. I washed my hair.
Turn around, and smell Jin Young's.
Mine?
(Gosh, my nose!)
Hey, So Min. So Min.
Come over here.
Your hair smells too.
You smell too.
- You should smell her hair. - Smell it.
- Jin Young. - Do you want to?
Smell Jin Young's hair.
I'll be really objective and see if it smells or not.
I'm so upset.
I washed my hair.
(Surprised)
- Does it smell? - It must smell really bad.
- Jin Young. - Is it as bad as So Min's?
- This is... - Let me try.
Jin Young, your hair...
smells...
really unpleasant.
- Wait. - What's wrong?
- Yes, that's right. I'm serious. - Let me try.
- You... - I'll really be honest.
- Don't overreact. - Okay.
- I'll be really honest. - Does it really smell?
(Angry)
Really?
- We're not lying. - Really?
- It's really serious. - I really washed my hair.
It smells like...
the old real estate agency that used to be in my neighborhood.
(It reminds him of the real estate agency from his childhood.)
- I'm being serious. It really does. - He's not lying.
Do you understand why I said it smells a little unpleasant?
(The national tours gifted her with the smell of the countryside.)
- Seriously. - You should smell it.
- Me? - You smell it.
I'm not really sensitive when it comes to smells.
If he says it smells, it'll be the truth. Does it smell?
- It doesn't smell, right? - I'm not sensitive with smells.
He's so cool.
(I'm not sensitive with smells.)
(I don't care what they say. Your hair doesn't smell to me.)
- My gosh. - He's so considerate.
- Stop lying. - Your nose is bleeding.
(Jong Kook, your nose is bleeding.)
(They can't stand him being sweet.)
He probably held his breath.
He must not have smelled it.
What is this?
Are you trying to show your affection for her?
- I'm so sick of this. - I'm really not sensitive.
My gosh, I'm sick of this whole affection thing.
Jin Young will start, and it'll carry on...
by going in a zigzag until the last line.
- I can't get it wrong. - We can do this.
Let's start.
- Finale. - Le.
- Na. - Fi.
- Blow a whistle. - Whistle.
- A - Blow.
Let's eat omu-rice.
- Rice. - Omu.
(Incorrect)
(It's his turn, but he didn't say anything.)
- Kwang Soo, why are you quiet? - It's your turn.
- You're being weird. - No, it was supposed to...
- It's obviously this way. - It's this way.
- He's a coach. - You're a coach.
- Seriously. - I'm not a coach.
- You're being too obvious. - It's not me.
- Haha, you know it's not me, right? - Unbelievable.
You know it's not because I'm a coach, right?
This is so wrong.
- I can't believe this. - This is not the way to go.
Should we start with Haha and go this way?
Then let's start with Haha.
- Then it'll go this way. - It'll go this way...
and come down to Jong Kook and continue on.
Get ready.
Let's begin.
- Watercress. - Cress.
- Ter. - Wa.
Water strider.
- Der. - Stri.
- Ter. - Wa.
The Battery of Love.
- Love. - Of.
Ry.
Of.
- No, it's "Ry". Come on. - What?
Hey, you.
Are you a coach?
- No. - You...
- Listen. "The Battery of Love". - I know.
You should've said, "Ry".
You got it wrong.
Da Hee's mad again. Look at her all angry.
Then why don't you try it? Say it backwards.
Love, Of, Ry, Ter, Bat, The.
Was that so hard to do?
(So Min, was that so hard?)
- Why are you angry? - No.
(Da Hee's desire to win the game made her explode.)
Tell her you're too old.
If my mom was like this, I might actually die.
That would be so funny.
(A shouting mother that's obsessed about winning)
- I know. Think about it. - My gosh.
If So Min was your girlfriend...
and your mom was Da Hee, that would be a disaster.
If she was my mom, I really could've died.
- No one will be on your side. - I'll be discarded in no time.
And what if you're the dad?
(What if you're the dad, Jong Kook?)
(It's funny just by imagining them as a family.)
(A girlfriend that's full of suspicion)
(A mom who's obsessed about winning)
(A Spartan dad)
(My goodness.)
How terrible.
This is your last chance.
- We'll start with Jin Young. - Okay.
It's our last chance.
Come on. Let's do it properly.
Come on, guys.
We need a clue about the coaches.
Get ready.
Let's begin.
Ear syringe.
- Ringe. - Sy.
Ringe.
(Incorrect)
(That's not what the word was.)
Da Hee, how can you get it wrong? It only had three syllables.
(How can you get it wrong when it only had three syllables?)
(Embarrassed)
- How could you get it wrong? - No, that's not it.
Jin Young already said, "Ringe". How could you say it again?
It's because she's a coach.
- Do you think so? - She's a coach.
She's Coach Lee. I know who she is now.
- Let's try just 1 more time. - Give us 1 more chance.
- This is really the end. - Okay.
- If anyone gets it wrong, - That means...
- that person is really the coach. - he or she is the coach.
- No doubt. - Let's start with Jin Young.
I made myself clear. Whoever gets it wrong this time is the coach.
Let's begin.
- Work and life. - Life.
- And. - Work.
- Labyrinth of fear. - Fear.
(Hesitant)
- Of. - He's a coach, right?
No, I'm not.
You said it way too late.
Jae Seok must be a coach.
- You're right. - My gosh.
(They're doubting him for nitpicking at Seok Jin.)
Oh, my gosh.
- He's right, isn't he? - He did that on purpose.
- So Min, I'm... - He was quick to judge.
If he answers incorrectly,
- he gets caught. - You know I'm not, right?
I expected it from him as soon as the game started.
- I knew it. - Come on.
- That's right. - He's a coach after all.
- Jong Kook. - Long time no see.
Long time no see.
- This is unbelievable. - He returned as a coach.
- It's time that you were a coach. - That's right.
I won't be giving you a hint.
- Give us a chance. - Give us one more chance.
- 1 more time, please. - Let's play 1 more game.
As the last game,
will you play Subtract Multiplication or Song Ji Hyo Game?
- Song Ji Hyo Game. - What's that?
If I say, "river", make a word such as "river port".
- Let's play Song Ji Hyo Game. - Three-syllable word?
- This is difficult. - Song Ji Hyo Game?
- Let's play it in this order. - Okay.
- Get ready. - Three syllables?
Make a three-syllable word.
Get ready, set, go. Dog.
Bird.
(Dog bird)
- What? - Dog.
(She says a curse word unconsciously.)
- What? - My goodness.
I'm sorry. What is it?
- I'm sorry. - How could you?
- Jin Young. - I'm sorry.
How could you say that?
- Jin Young. - You're the boss.
Shall I complete the curse word?
- So Min. - How about "kki"?
- Stop it. - I'll say "kki".
You could say, "Is anyone there?"
- How about "Is anyone there?" - "Ridgeback prawn" is possible.
- It's a shrimp that's like a dog. - "Ridgeback prawn"?
It's called ridgeback prawn.
(They're trying too hard.)
You're amazing.
Song Ji Hyo Game requires you to think...
in a short period of time.
You say words that you use often without realizing it.
(You say words that you use often without realizing it.)
- It shows how you've lived. - Seriously.
- No. - Be careful.
- "Dog bird". - I was in a rush.
The hint on the coach will not be given.
- Do the coaches know each other? - Yes.
Then they can help each other out.
What's this?
(There's something.)
- Really? - Yes.
- What's the cushion for? - It's so funny.
Is it for one person again?
Why is there a cushion?
- It's called Catch the Tail Quiz. - Catch the Tail Quiz?
(Catch the Tail Quiz)
Catch the Tail Quiz?
- Choose members of your choice. - Catch the Tail?
(What is Catch the Tail Quiz?)
Make a team of four with members of your choice.
(To make a team of his choice,)
(he wants to be on Jong Kook's team.)
(He makes a move.)
Catch the Tail.
It's connected to the previous team.
- Go away, Jae Seok. - Why are you coming?
- Why? - It's embarrassing.
I want to play with Jong Kook.
Rules aren't important.
- Wait. - Stay out, coach.
Stay out, coach.
(He keeps a distance.)
- Where will you go? - Listen.
- Do you know what makes me angry? - What?
There's always So Min lurking around.
What? Go away, So Min.
- Look at her. - We're his children.
Pop the balloon. You'll find a question inside.
The team that puts the question on the sitting cushion first...
- can answer it. - That sounds fun.
- Let's go, team. - Let's go.
Each member of the team guesses a syllable.
The first team to answer wins.
The winning team gets a hint about the coaches.
If no team answers correctly, there won't be any hints.
Let's determine the teams with the spoons.
- Teams? - Let's do it randomly.
Do you see the colors on the spoons?
(The ones with the same color become a team.)
- Let me be on Jong Kook's team. - It's random.
Jong Kook will pick last.
(He's worried about competition.)
- You pick last. - Okay.
I wish I could be in his position.
- At the top? - Just once.
- You can't. - Where everyone wants me.
Let's start with Ji Hyo. Pick one.
- Mine is green. - Green.
- It's not bad. - Okay.
- It's red. - That's not bad.
- Blue. - Blue isn't bad.
We have three teams.
The rest will overlap.
- Does it start now? - Yes.
Everyone wants to be on Jong Kook's team.
(They hope for Jong Kook.)
(That's needless to say.)
- All of us want him. - It's one person.
- Please. - Let it be me.
It doesn't matter which team Da Hee, Ji Hyo, and Han Na are on.
- It doesn't matter. - Please.
I hope everyone else is on other teams.
- It starts now. - Which team is Jin Young on?
Don't we know the results later?
- There is one man - I haven't picked yet.
- It's blue. - It's blue.
It's blue.
- Whose team is she on? - It's Han Na.
Is it Da Hee?
(How about Sang Yeob?)
Mine is blue too. Who's team is blue?
Come here and join us.
- In this case... - We need one more person.
One more person will join.
- Someone should pick blue. - That's right.
- You only get one more member. - Pick blue.
- Seok Jin, pick the blue spoon. - Get rid of it.
What if he picks the blue one?
- No. - No way.
- Blue, blue - Blue, blue
- Don't pick blue - If he picks the blue one,
your team is complete.
The one who picks the blue one.
- Let's go. It's green. - It's green.
Why did you pick it? I don't want you.
- Come on, Seok Jin. - Just accept it.
Jong Kook will join us.
Even if I join, it'll be difficult.
Seok Jin will make it hard.
- Please. - We're doomed.
- It'll be blue. - It's red.
He's with Da Hee.
(Kwang Soo joins Da Hee.)
(Are you red too?)
What? Da Hee.
- Am I that bad? - No.
- I'm not that bad, am I? - I'm happy.
- Seriously. - It's great.
Pick the blue one.
- Pick the blue. - Go on.
- Please pick the blue one. - Please pick it.
- Please pick the blue one. - Pick the blue one.
- No way. - Pick the blue one.
- Let's go. - Please.
Please pick it.
- Come on. - Let's go.
(Se Chan joins Team Blue.)
(Team Blue is complete.)
Yes.
- It's okay. - Kim Jong Kook.
Let's go.
That's upsetting.
Play with me and Kwang Soo.
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook
Pick a green one, Jong Kook.
So Min is the worst player.
Pick a green spoon, So Min.
- Don't pick a green one. - Join Team Red.
- Pick a red spoon, So Min. - Next is So Min.
Please.
- She picked it. - She got one.
(Which team will So Min join?)
Is it green?
(So Min joins Team Green.)
- That's good. - Good job.
(We're doomed.)
She really picked green.
(Green spoons are thrown to the ground.)
- My goodness. It's unbelievable. - That's right.
- It's the worst. - Team Green is the worst.
Even Jong Kook can't save Team Green.
- Hey. - Jae Seok belongs to green.
- If I join Team Green... - Seriously.
- It'd be bad. Seriously. - I refuse.
- I can't join Team Green. - Please.
- Join Team Red. - Let's pick green.
Let's pick green.
- Shuffle them well. - Please.
Don't join us.
Only Jong Kook can save our team.
- Let's go. - Pick a green spoon.
- Let's go. - Pick well.
(If Jae Seok picks green, Jong Kook joins Team Red automatically.)
(Jae Seok's selection determines the fate of Team Red and Green.)
- Please. - Don't join us.
(Avoid the green one.)
Yours is the last one.
(He can't believe it.)
(Jae Seok joins Team Green. Haha and Jong Kook join Team Red.)
This is unbelievable.
Come here.
(They become the worst team.)
- Hey. - Did you see him?
He grabbed the green spoon directly.
(It's surprising.)
- Listen. - He must be...
attracted to green.
I can't believe it.
It's the worst.
Why can't I get away from Seok Jin and Jae Seok?
Who went to Okinawa with me?
(He's tired of them.)
- Mongolia. - How about Mongolia?
Where's Team Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?
How about Australia?
- Why am I in here? - This is too hard.
- I don't belong with them. - Seriously, it's too tiring.
I can't get away from them.
- It drives me crazy. - Why?
Random selection doesn't work either.
Why am I so unlucky?
What about me? I'm going to lose my mind.
(Team Blue, Team Red, and Team Green)
- Please step back. - Okay.
We should do well since there are only three teams.
Only the person in the front can pop the balloon.
If another team member grabs the question,
the other team keeps it.
Let's grab it when the balloon pops.
Grab it when the balloon pops.
Let's avoid Jong Kook's team and steal from Team Green.
Let's steal from Team Green first.
- Grab the other teams. - Right.
- Shall we? - Just grab them.
Let's stand when they come near us.
Get ready, set.
I'll be sitting down here.
Are you scared? Are you afraid?
- Hey, Glasses. Try to attack us. - "Glasses"?
Look at him.
- That guy... - This is frustrating.
(We have Jong Kook with us.)
- You don't scare us at all. - He's a coward.
Let's go to the coward.
(Did you call Haha a coward?)
- Are you going forward? - Hey.
(Team Red attacks Team Blue.)
- Go, go. - There's a camera.
We should do something.
Let's get them from the back.
Target Se Chan.
Target Se Chan. Go this way.
- Hey. - No.
(Ji Hyo attacks Se Chan.)
- That's right. - Grab it quickly.
(It was a close call, but Se Chan runs away.)
- We almost had it. - Get closer, Ji Hyo.
- Hurry. - Don't catch me.
Come on.
- Hey. - Be careful.
- Come on. - Get a little closer.
- Be careful. - Get a little closer.
Get a little closer.
(They chase at full speed.)
Stop. Grab it.
(Sang Yeob grabs Team Green's balloon.)
- He's coming. - Get him.
- Let's go. - Grab the question.
(Grab the question.)
- Grab the question. - What?
(Did they drop the question?)
No!
Give it to me.
I got it.
Okay.
- Let's go. - We have to put it there.
We have to put it there.
Move to the left.
- 1, 2, 1, 2. - Let's go!
(We have to hurry.)
(Where are you going?)
Get Han Na!
(Charging)
(Team Red attacks Team Blue's balloon.)
Get it!
(We have to get there first!)
- Go! - Go!
Hurry!
(Kwang Soo touches down first.)
Where is the question?
- It hasn't burst yet. - Where is it?
It's burst.
Put the question down.
- It's burst. - It's here.
It's here.
It's here. You saw it, didn't you?
Tear it.
- It's here. - Ours is here.
Sang Yeob's team gets to answer the question.
It's torn.
(Kwang Soo puts Team Blue's question paper in his mouth...)
(and puts his down.)
That's ours.
- I'm so exhausted. - That's ours.
- Did you put it in your mouth? - Yes.
Sang Yeob gets to answer the question.
(Sang Yeob gets to answer the question.)
Do we get a chance if they fail?
- Ours is on the cushion. - It's here.
Decide the order, and say the four letters.
Sang Yeob should go first.
Like this.
You have to answer right away.
- Each person says one letter. - Start.
What is the name of the technology...
for wireless local area networking...
based on radio waves or infrared rays? Start.
(The correct answer is WiFi.)
(Sang Yeob, just say, "W".)
WiFi. W.
(He says all four letters.)
(Fail)
Hey!
- Just one letter! - Sang Yeob!
W, I, F, I.
Just one letter!
Why did you say the whole word? We all knew the answer!
We have a chance.
- We all knew the answer. - I mean...
Is he stupid?
- How could you? - I did my best.
- Come on. - Sang Yeob, you're doing great.
- You're doing great. - Way to go!
Don't steal my stupid image.
It's Haha's.
- It's Haha's. - It took me three years.
- It's Haha's. - Sang Yeob is doing great.
(Sorry)
Each person says one letter.
We talked about it.
I'm too impatient.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
(Could Sang Yeob be the coach?)
- Here goes the next question. - Let's go.
Let's go!
If we say the correct answer, we'll get a hint, right?
- Yes. - We need to...
- win the hint by all means. - We'll move.
We'll move...
and attack them.
Look for a chance.
- Ready. - Jong Kook...
Let's go for Jong Kook's team.
Okay.
Wait for us. Approach them.
Come here.
(Team Blue wants to attack Team Red head-on.)
Let's attack Jong Kook.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Kwang Soo, get them.
(Kwang Soo, get them.)
- Get them! - Stay away.
- Get them. - Get them.
Attack Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - I got their balloon.
(Team Red gets Team Blue's balloon.)
We got it. We can go now.
(Jae Seok has an eye on Team Red's balloon.)
- Come on! - We got the balloon.
(They have the balloon.)
(The question paper drops.)
- Get it! - Let's go!
Go!
(Ji Hyo picks up the paper.)
Come here.
- Go! - Where is the paper?
- Where is it? - Go!
- Go! - Let's go!
(To get the chance, they have to get to the cushion first.)
(What?)
So Min. Hold on.
- What happened to her? - So Min.
(So Min falls.)
- Get up! - So Min.
- So Min. - Get up!
- Hey. - That was close.
Hey.
So Min fell. Move!
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo touches down.)
Gosh. So Min.
- So Min. - So Min.
So Min.
Kwang Soo will say the first letter.
- Okay. - It's okay.
They won't get it right.
- Ready. - I'll go first.
You have to say the answer right away. Ready, start.
What is the name of the organization...
that pursues to preserve the world's natural and cultural heritage?
U.
(The correct answer is UNESCO.)
(The first letter is right. Da Hee, say, "Ne".)
- Well... - Hey.
(What?)
- Hey. - Hey.
It's UNESCO.
- UNESCO. - Da Hee.
Even I knew the answer.
Even I knew it.
Was that a goat?
- I was going to say, "Ne". - Goodness.
I give my title to her.
(She can be the stupid one.)
- I can't believe this. - It's okay.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
(Puzzled)
We did a good job.
You thought it was UNICEF, didn't you?
What?
(Nodding)
You thought it was UNICEF?
Seriously?
- Really? - Gosh.
- UNICEF offers money. - Seriously?
- Is that true? - Stop it now.
I'm so sick of it.
Really?
I said, "It's UNESCO," after hearing someone say it.
Was it a coincidence?
Someone over here said it's UNESCO.
Da Hee must have frozen.
It'd be understandable if Kwang Soo did.
Da Hee was the second player.
I even said U.
You knew it was UNESCO, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
Even I knew it.
Let's take a break.
(Did Da Hee say the wrong answer on purpose?)
So Min, why did you fall?
- Well... - You should never run.
It suddenly felt so heavy.
There was a huge stone.
(Team Green failed because of So Min.)
(Could So Min be the coach?)
Let's go to the final race place.
- Let's go. - I'm disappointed.
(Will they identify the coaches during the final mission?)
(Final Race)
It's time for the final race.
Let me explain the rules for I Am on the National Team.
(I Am on the National Team)
Find the hints about the coaches and the gold medalist...
hidden in this building. Using the hints,
pick out and eliminate the coaches at the trial...
which is held every 30 minutes.
- There will be trials? - Trials?
- It's been a long time. - Indeed.
(They need to find as many hints as possible.)
Okay.
(The highlight of the race)
You'll also find invitations to the gala show.
- Gala show? - Gala show?
(Gala show)
Once you find it, you can't transfer it to anyone.
You have to attend the show with a person of your choice.
The venue and time will be announced later.
- What's that? - Gala show?
- Are we going to perform? - Are we going to?
Only four people can attend the gala show.
If there are less coaches, the coaches will be eliminated,
and it's the same the other way around.
(The group with less people will be eliminated.)
For example, if there are 3 coaches and 1 player...
The player will be out.
If there are three players,
the coach will be out.
(The minority will be eliminated.)
Three coaches will try to bring a player.
I guess.
If there are 2 coaches and 2 players...
or if all of them are players, nothing will happen.
(Nothing will happen.)
If there are 2 and 2, it'll be fierce.
We need to choose the right one.
Please go to your positions now.
- Let's get it! - Let's get it!
(Will they be able to eliminate all the coaches?)
(Everyone is in position.)
All right. I'll win...
and experience the Luxury Package.
I'm suspecting Jae Seok and Da Hee.
I want to be careful today.
Let me think after finding some hints.
Da Hee has been a little suspicious.
Da Hee.
The thing is,
when she couldn't say anything after I said, "U",
it was too strange.
It showed in the bus too.
(It showed.)
Da Hee has been talkative today.
(Jin Young suspects Da Hee too.)
I suspect Da Hee.
(Meanwhile, Da Hee...)
(sighs deeply.)
Let's start the race.
Five.
Four.
Three.
2, 1.
The race starts.
Let's go.
(The final race starts.)
I need to find the hints.
(They have to find the hints.)
It can't be here, right?
It can't be...
(Coaches should be eliminated at the trial 30 minutes later.)
In the trash can? I guess not.
(The coaches need to eliminate the gold medalist.)
Have you found anything yet?
- No. - Are you...
a coach? No, right?
I'm just a player.
- Right? - I'm nothing.
- Whom do you suspect? - Jae Seok is definitely suspicious.
And Da Hee.
- So Min! - Hey.
Have you found any hints yet?
What? Yes.
- You've found something? - What?
So Min, come here.
Are you really not a coach?
- No. - Are you sure?
They don't let me do these things because I get caught easily.
- You get caught? - They don't let me.
- Ever since I messed up once. - You messed up?
Did it show too much?
I'm looking for the medalist and the coaches.
- I see. - You can't find anything there.
Jong Kook and Jae Seok are there.
You haven't found anything yet?
I'm going to look somewhere else.
- Where? - In the main building.
- Really? - Come with me.
Okay.
(Jong Kook is looking for hints in the annex lobby.)
"Love Battery"? What's that?
What's that? What is this?
"Scout list"?
I didn't know about this list.
What's this?
(There's another scout list?)
(Two lists in different colors are in the main and annex buildings.)
When we started, they didn't explain about the list.
My guess is that...
the coaches will probably scout their players.
That's to put things simply. That's what the word means.
(He listens to Se Chan for a while.)
You seem to be well-informed.
- Pardon? - You seem to know a lot.
Jong Kook, it's not rocket science. Don't you know English?
Are you usually...
- this sharp? - I'm on top of my game today.
(Did he always have good reasoning skills like today?)
In my opinion, they will try to pick the card for the Luxury Package.
Once they get six members, it's over.
My gosh. They startled me.
(The sound of the staff passing by...)
(scared him this much?)
They startled me.
- Is that how you should play this? - What do you mean?
You think this is good enough?
(He sounds threatening.)
- You think this is good enough? - What's up with your right fist?
Hold on. I might be in trouble. Everyone, don't move.
(He retreats right away.)
Hold on a second.
Jong Kook.
Are you a coach? Hold on.
- One second. - If you put names on the list...
- Let me make a round. - Hey, I'm not a coach.
I was just sharing my opinion.
(His pupils shake.)
Why did I come here?
Jong Kook, I'm going to go.
Pretend you didn't see me. You never saw me.
Why did you come here?
I was just passing by.
(He becomes Jong Kook's target.)
Okay. Tell you what.
For now...
(You scared me.)
I think I might've peed.
Let me go to the restroom and check.
- We'll part our ways for now. - Okay.
I got it. I didn't come here for you.
- Scout? - Scout. Okay.
- Thank you for the information. - Why is there a scout list?
(What is the purpose of that scout list?)
(Jong Kook comes upstairs to find a hint.)
It's not easy to find one.
What's this?
Wait.
No way.
(He finally finds a hint.)
It's in black.
What is this? A pair of sunglasses?
(What? Sunglasses?)
When you put them on, you'll be given the hint.
The sunglasses?
(The hint will be given by a voice message.)
Stop lying. If I wear them,
I'll get the hint?
Coach A is a member of Running Man.
(This is a hint about Coach A. Coach A is a member of Running Man.)
Hold on.
If the coach is a member of the show...
(Sang Yeob, Da Hee, Jin Young, and Han Na aren't Coach A.)
The four special guests we have aren't official members of the show.
(Coach A is 1 of the 8 members of Running Man.)
It's Jae Seok then. It's Jae Seok.
I must meet up with him then.
(Jae Seok is looking for a hint in the wardrobe department.)
(He spots a hint.)
(He puts on the sunglasses for the hint.)
It's been 10 years or more since Coach C's debut.
Except Han Na, everyone debuted 10 years ago.
(Everyone's debut was 10 years ago except Han Na's.)
(Kwang Soo finds a hint too.)
Coach C is a woman.
One of them was a woman.
(Ji Hyo, Da Hee, Jin Young, and So Min debuted at least 10 years ago.)
- Da Hee. - Yes?
I bet you'll be eliminated after 10 minutes.
- What? - You'll be out in 10 minutes.
- Kwang Soo. - It's a sure thing.
- You... - Whatever you do, you'll be out.
Don't eliminate me.
Try to find a lot of hints.
- Coaches can eliminate us, right? - What?
They can eliminate the gold medalist or other members, right?
Of course.
How?
They can remove the name tags to check.
(They can remove the name tags to check.)
- Is it Name Tag Elimination? - What?
Can't they? Don't you have a name tag?
(In the race, you can remove name tags.)
In this race, we don't do that.
Of course, we do.
- Am I wrong? - Yes. You don't know the rules.
My gosh.
- Let me tell you one thing. - What is it?
If you're not the coach,
go to a clinic as soon as we're done with the shoot.
You...
Or it could be that you're truly dumb.
No, I'm not dumb.
Hey.
It's because I haven't played a game like this on TV.
I'm just new to this.
- I never played this with friends. - What is this?
Can't she manage her anger? What was that?
(Why is she angry at me?)
I mean, seriously.
Why are you angry at me? You...
- Hey. - Listen.
- Are you drunk or what? - What?
- No, that's not it. - Hold on a second.
- Try to see it from my perspective. - No, let go. I don't get you.
Sorry?
(The staff members urgently pull Da Hee away.)
- Hey! - No, no. Come.
- Let's talk in private. - What's happening to me?
(For the first time, she gets a crash course about the race.)
(Isn't this how you play?)
Hey, you. What's going on?
- Did you find a hint? - It's not that.
- She's explaining the rules again. - Is that so?
(She's embarrassed.)
Is that a high-level strategy? Did you get a mission?
- What will I do? - Haha.
- Isn't she acting weird? - She said we're tearing name tags.
No, listen. She was having a meeting with the writer.
- She was explaining it again. - Hey, don't make it obvious.
- It's not fun then. - Exactly.
- All right, Da Hee. - No, listen.
You can do better next time, okay?
- Okay. - It's not over yet.
- Don't be so chatty next time. - Come again?
You weren't supposed to tell the rules.
If you tell everyone that, everyone knows you're the coach.
I'm not the coach, Kwang Soo.
No. Okay.
- Do you want to walk together? - No, stop doing that.
- Don't ask me things like that. - Why not?
You're too scary. Go away.
- Please go away. - Hey.
- Hey. - Get lost! Don't talk to me.
When I don't know the rules, you should teach me nicely.
I just didn't know the rules.
We could've found a hint, you know.
- Don't distract me. - You fool.
(She's full of mysteries. Is she really a coach?)
(Se Chan finds the scout list on the 1st floor of the main building.)
What's this?
(Scout List)
(What is this?)
(On the scout list,)
(there are photos?)
That's Haha.
Is someone taking photos of us?
(What are these photos for?)
There are photos of Kwang Soo, Haha, and Jae Seok.
(Kwang Soo, Haha, and Jae Seok are in the photos.)
Is someone taking photos of us here?
(Why are these photos on the list?)
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, I have something to tell you.
Come here. We were sharing information. Come quickly.
Hey, this will probably shock you.
- Right now... - We shared everything here.
- Someone is taking photos. - What?
- Someone is taking photos. - Hey.
- They will put photos on that list. - Listen.
There are two photos on the board now.
- The photos on the list are... - Whose photos are they?
- Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, - Okay.
- and Haha. - My photo is on it?
- Hey. - They are on the scout list.
- You'll be eliminated soon. - In my opinion...
- You should stay away from this. - Listen.
- How will I stay away? - Say that Haha gets eliminated.
Say that Haha gets eliminated.
My reasoning will be correct.
To eliminate members, coaches must put their photos on the list.
(Photos will lead to elimination.)
(When their photos are on the list, they will be eliminated?)
- This is my opinion. - Then I...
- Listen. - Okay.
It's highly likely that Jae Seok staged this.
(It's highly likely that Jae Seok staged this.)
(His photo on the scout list is staged by Jae Seok?)
He took a photo of himself.
- He did the same thing before. - He did that once.
It's because he's known for staging set-ups.
- He even sprayed his name tag once. - Exactly.
(Last summer, during the race between thieves and the sheriff,)
(he sprayed paint on his name tag to thwart suspicions.)
(With years of experience as a spy, he fooled everyone.)
- He even sprayed his name tag once. - Exactly.
He's the best at staging set-ups.
(Don't trust him.)
Jae Seok.
There's something I want to tell you.
You're in a sticky situation now.
- During the first trial... - What about the hint?
- Seok Jin. - You're in danger.
Hints are your weapons in court.
Your gibberish isn't.
(Your gibberish is useless in court.)
I wasn't talking nonsense.
As an old friend, I'm giving you an advice.
You might be eliminated during the first trial.
Don't worry about me. I'll let the hints speak for themselves.
I've already acquired supporters.
I can't say this because I'm worried a coach might be among us.
(I'm being careful.)
That's you.
- Seok Jin, go on your way. - Okay. I'll be on my way.
- Do your best. - All right.
He's in a pickle now.
I think he will be eliminated in the first trial.
(Is Jae Seok, the expert in staging set-ups, a coach?)
Where are the hints?
(To Jin Young, this race is too hard.)
I can't find any.
(She finds the scout list now.)
What's this? What is it?
(Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Haha, and Sang Yeob)
- So Min, come here. - What's that?
What? What is this? Did they get recruited?
(So Min sees the list too.)
- This is how they get recruited. - No way.
- Coaches must've taken them. - Who took these photos?
- Who took these? - I don't know.
(It seems the people in the photos...)
Hold on a second.
(aren't affected for the time being.)
- Kwang Soo. Who is this? - Sang Yeob. Haha.
Seok Jin. Isn't this Seok Jin? Yes, it is.
(Jae Seok, Haha, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and Sang Yeob are on it.)
(Then why were these photos taken?)
Why can't I find any hints?
When did we meet? It was taken on the second floor.
(He's shocked after seeing it.)
But Haha is the ultimate idiot.
- He won't remember. - He probably can't remember.
It was taken upstairs. Right there.
Da Hee was there too.
Where we got our photos taken isn't important.
- Think about whom we were with. - At that time?
- It's because... - Player Seok Jin is out.
(Is Seok Jin eliminated?)
(Why is Seok Jin eliminated all of a sudden?)
Here's a hint on Coach B.
Se Chan.
(Here's a hint on Coach B.)
- What is it? - We get a hint on Coach B.
His main profession is acting.
(Coach B's main profession is acting.)
- What? - Acting?
- Gosh. - Coach B is an actor.
- Wait. - Are you an actor?
- Is he... - What are you?
(Aren't you an actor?)
- Is it you? - What are you?
Come on, I've been on Running Man for eight years.
Are you an entertainer or an actor? Answer the question.
Tell us accurately.
- Listen. - Are you Coach B?
(I make people laugh, and I also act.)
Coach B is...
The trial is about to start soon.
Please gather to the courtroom.
- We only got one hint on Coach B. - Coach B?
We need to find out how Seok Jin was eliminated.
Is there a photo of Seok Jin at the first-floor cafe?
- There is. - Right.
- I brought it right now. - Is there one?
- His photo was taken. - Listen.
The one whose photo is taken and attached is eliminated.
- That's how you get eliminated. - Right.
- Here's what's funny. - Really?
Among the members in the photos,
some of them staged a set-up.
- We must remember it. - Definitely.
- Let's see who they are. - They're over there.
(They check the scout list one last time.)
(Only Da Hee's photo remains on the scout list.)
Who is it?
- It's her. - She staged it.
- It's Da Hee. - It's a set-up.
We suspected that it was Da Hee from the beginning.
That's why she did it.
It's very clear to me now.
I know all except the gold medalist.
(Everyone heads to the trial.)
How did Seok Jin get eliminated?
I'm scared to be in the courtroom again.
(1st trial session starts.)
I figured everything out.
Really? You have a sixth sense.
You'll be very surprised.
So Min, do you have a younger brother?
- I do. - Really?
- Is that a hint? - Yes.
What is it, Da Hee?
- What is it, Jae Seok? - Goodness.
- What is it? - This is crazy.
Da Hee.
What is it, Jae Seok?
You'll make a big mistake.
- If I get eliminated... - He's here.
- You're here, coach. - Me?
(Everyone's present including Kwang Soo who's been suspicious.)
(Who are the 3 coaches?)
One of the members is eliminated.
That's right.
We can't let the coaches trick us.
As you know,
- the losing teams will compete. - No way.
Remember this. There are lies...
to what people said.
- There are groundless rumors. - So keep that in mind.
I'll tell you one hint of mine that's most accurate.
- It's a general hint. - A general hint.
- It's not Se Chan. - Right.
(It's not Se Chan.)
- Stop it. - Let me participate in the game.
Let me participate in the game.
- He's not suspicious at all. - Let me...
be a part of the game. Why are you denying me?
- Let me say it again. - Why do you deny me?
According to the hint I have, it isn't Se Chan.
It's not specific to any coaches.
- In general, it isn't Se Chan. - Then what is he?
Who am I? Am I someone who will be eliminated?
Wait a minute.
Is it possible the hint said that it excluded Se Chan?
- That makes no sense. - What do you think?
This is possible.
Jae Seok's hint may be related to the gold medalist.
What's certain is that it's not Se Chan.
- Shall I just go home? - I said it several times.
I'm not needed here.
- Se Chan. - Why do you give me a hard time?
Go start your car.
It's not you.
(Go spend time for yourself.)
"Start your car"?
Let's share hints related to the coaches.
- Coach C. - C?
Let's catch Coach C.
- Any hints about Coach C? - I have one.
- I do too. - I do.
We know a lot about Coach C.
What do you know about Coach C?
- Coach C is female. - It's a female.
- She uses her legal name. - It's her legal name.
That's right.
Coach C...
has over 10 years of experience.
10 years?
(The candidates are Jin Young, Da Hee, and So Min.)
Han Na is excluded.
- She also has a younger brother. - She has a younger brother?
(Coach C has a younger brother.)
Who has a younger brother?
Da Hee and So Min.
Wait a minute.
I think Da Hee is lying about having a younger brother.
That's wrong, Han Na. That hint is...
Just go to prison later.
(He cuts her off.)
- You'll go to prison first. - Da Hee looks so tired.
(Da Hee looks tired today.)
You rank zero place, Da Hee.
- That's not it. - Just go.
- All I do is deny that it's not me. - Wait a minute.
Everyone.
It's time to point out one person.
Please discuss amongst yourselves.
Let's catch Coach C.
C?
- Coach C is... - It's most convincing.
- Han Na, it's So Min. - We have to make it clear.
I'm about to lose my mind.
I tried to convince them in the past,
- but I was eliminated. - Really? Should I not say anything?
- No. - Then everyone will suspect me.
Then get on the list.
- I'm not it. - Why don't you...
- To be honest... - Don't lose a talented member.
(Don't lose a talented member.)
Are you losing yourself?
- Are you losing yourself? - Don't say anything.
Don't say anymore.
What is she saying? Talented what?
She claims to be precious.
What did you say?
I bet everyone thinks this.
"She's a coach."
- Will we accuse her now or later? - Hey.
- Give me a chance. - She's like an insurance.
Da Hee, can you give us a reason why you're not a coach?
Let me explain.
(Sighing)
- I'd be surprised if she's acting. - Let's listen.
My goodness.
Let me say one thing.
I asked Da Hee how the coaches eliminate other members.
At first, she said by tearing off their name tags.
- Then at the same place, - She knew it already.
I saw her getting scolded by one of the writers.
I witnessed it.
(I witnessed her getting scolded by one of the writers.)
- At the same place, - Kwang Soo.
- I was there. - We saw it.
- We saw it. - Did you see it?
- I saw it. - We witnessed it.
- Each person... - The writer was frustrated.
- No way. - Who should be the first?
- Tell us, Da Hee. - Da Hee...
- kept patting my back. - Really?
You and you...
are coaches. I'll expose you.
- I'm only telling the truth. - Da Hee.
- Jae Seok. - You have one minute to talk.
- Da Hee... - Please say your last words.
The writer was about to slap her.
I was there too.
- The writer looked frustrated. - I was shocked.
I was talking to other members on the second floor.
I heard Da Hee coming, but she stayed outside instead.
Are you suspecting me too? You sided with me before.
It's so easy to embarrass someone.
(It's so easy to embarrass someone.)
- Wait. - Fine, fine. I'll just go up.
(She's completely upset.)
- Don't. - Wait, Da Hee.
- That's not what we meant. - No, it wasn't.
Da Hee, what was the hint that you found?
Da Hee is crying!
No, I'm not.
(He's surprised.)
- Da Hee is crying. - This is frustrating.
No, I'm not a coach.
- I'm not it. - Cry in prison instead.
Why are you ruining the atmosphere?
- Da Hee. - It's so unfair.
- I won't do this with Da Hee. - Kwang Soo.
Da Hee might sign with her blood.
It'd be amazing if it wasn't her.
Please say whom you suspect.
- I think it's Da Hee. - It's Da Hee.
I also think it's Da Hee.
- What do you think, Kwang Soo? - I think...
- I'm not it. - Tell us.
- Is it Da Hee? - Yes.
- What do you think, Jin Young? - It's Da Hee.
- Does everyone think it's Da Hee? - Yes.
- Then... - Go up.
- She's going up. - Let's go, Da Hee.
- Let's go, Da Hee. - Da Hee.
We'll reveal Da Hee's identity.
Is Da Hee a coach or a player?
Or is she the gold medalist?
It's either Da Hee or So Min.
It's definitely So Min if it isn't Da Hee.
You're terrible.
- So Min, you're the worst. - 1, 2, 3.
(If she's a player, 2 players will be eliminated in total.)
- What if she's the gold medalist? - 2, 3.
(If she's the gold medalist, the coaches win.)
(Is Da Hee a coach as everyone expected?)
(Player)
- What? - Was she a player?
Don't make that face.
- Was she a player? - What's this?
- This is creepy. - I knew it.
Da Hee is a player.
This is creepy.
(They're creeped out.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Turn around, Da Hee. Show us. - I knew it.
You suspected me, right? You're a coach.
- What? - Calm down, Da Hee.
It's not like we have a lot of money at risk.
- It's possible to make mistakes. - It's just a show.
- How could she cry? - What did I do so wrong?
They're in a relationship as she called him a coach.
- No. - That must be it.
- That's not right. - Look at them.
- That's wrong. - It wasn't Da Hee?
- That means it's So Min. - It's So Min.
- Me? - It's definitely her.
- You suspected me. - Seriously?
(Coach C has over 10 years of experience.)
(It's a woman who uses her legal name.)
(Coach C has a younger brother.)
(Coach)
(Jeon So Min)
(Coach C is So Min.)
(Coaches have the ability to eliminate the gold medalist.)
(Take a photo of a member suspected to be the gold medalist.)
(Put it on the red scout list.)
(Coaches can eliminate members by tearing off their name tags.)
(Hints about the coaches are given if they eliminate a player.)
(When Seok Jin was eliminated, a hint about Coach B was revealed.)
(Was Seok Jin not the gold medalist?)
I'm not a coach, I swear.
(Let me deny it for now.)
Someone must be framing you.
You're being framed like I was.
I'm always the first one to get eliminated.
Then again,
they wouldn't let you be a coach, would they?
- That's right. - What?
(They wouldn't let you be a coach, would they?)
What are you talking about?
Are you serious?
- Da Hee, you should smile. - I am smiling.
- How could she say such a thing? - Why would you diss her?
(How could she say such a thing?)
I quit.
(I quit.)
- Hold on. - What is this?
- Hey. - Are you kidding me?
- She is new. - Goodness.
Come back.
- Are you scared? - What is this?
Let's go back and get ready for round two.
Let's go.
Everyone will suspect me now. What should I do?
It'll be my turn next time.
I can't find a way out.
Jin Young doesn't have a little brother.
I can't guess who the gold medalist is.
Also, what about Da Hee? I never took a picture of her.
(I never took a picture of her.)
Now that I think of it, I never took a picture of Da Hee.
But a picture of her was on the blue list.
Someone else must have taken it.
But it can't be anyone on my team.
I guess the gold medalist took the picture.
(Someone who is not a coach is taking pictures?)
(Is the gold medalist taking pictures too?)
(She needs to find the gold medalist soon.)
Han Na has been suspecting Da Hee.
She suspected Jin Young at first, but she changed her mind.
(Han Na was active during the first trial.)
(Did Han Na try to eliminate Da Hee because she is a gold medalist?)
She was so active. I suspect she is the gold medalist.
Should I put a picture of Han Na on the list?
Han Na...
(Is Han Na really the gold medalist?)
The race will begin again.
No one has taken a picture of me. Let me check the pictures.
And...
Someone is there.
Is that Jae Seok?
(When he sticks his head out,)
(he sees Jae Seok standing still.)
(What is he doing?)
What are you doing?
- What do you mean? - Why are you...
I'm just looking around. I don't know who the coaches are.
(Jae Seok looks suspicious.)
I think he took a picture of me.
(What was he doing?)
Gosh.
(Jae Seok finds a nobody.)
- Hey. - Yes?
Go find hints.
I can't find anything.
- You should... - Se Chan.
- Yes? - Come here.
There he goes again.
- He's making me uncomfortable. - Hey.
- Don't let him see you. - I should run away.
- Just go. - Bye, Jong Kook.
(I'm running away.)
Why would you tell him?
I'm different from you.
(Weak)
I wish I could just leave.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
- Come here right now. - Okay.
We're friends. Come over here quickly.
We're friends?
(We're uncomfortable friends.)
Come here.
- Between Friends. - Between Friends.
I was just sitting here.
- I was watching Jin Young. - Okay.
Look at this. This chair.
- Do you remember it? - Yes.
- I took a picture... - Hold on.
Please leave us alone.
- Jong Kook. - Just pass by.
- We need to talk. - Se Chan has nothing to do with...
- today's game. - No.
But I do.
Jong Kook.
It's the same as talking to any pedestrian.
I think he took a picture of me...
or something.
- You think... - If you see...
a picture of me,
you can be sure.
- Jong Kook. - We can be sure even now.
He definitely is a coach.
- To be sure... - To be sure...
If something happens to me, just keep that in mind.
(Screaming)
What happened?
What's wrong?
What is it?
(Jin Young receives a hint.)
- What happened? - Haha.
Did you find it? What is it?
(Share it with us.)
- Are you just a player? - Yes.
Coach A is over 40.
(Coach A is over 40.)
(Jong Kook)
(Jae Seok)
It must be Jae Seok. We should consider Jong Kook too.
(Coach A is among these three.)
Jae Seok came to my mind right away.
All right. Keep it in mind.
- Okay. - Keep looking.
- We have to. - Saved in my heart.
(Saved in my heart)
- Saved. - Saved...
- In our hearts. - In our hearts.
Saved...
- In the players' hearts. - In the players' hearts.
Hurry up.
(They're closer to identifying the coaches.)
This is my last chance.
I need to risk everything.
There's only a picture of Da Hee.
This board must be...
for gold... What's the word?
(Behind So Min...)
(is Han Na?)
It must be the list for the gold medalist.
I think this picture was taken in the lobby.
On the way to the dressing room. She is looking a little up.
She must have been looking at Kwang Soo.
I'm suspecting Han Na. She was attacking Da Hee.
(What is she saying?)
Should I take a picture of Han Na?
(Peekaboo)
(Surprised)
Han Na.
I've been hiding here...
to find a coach.
(And the most suspected member has shown up.)
I've been hiding here...
to find a coach.
(And the most suspected member has shown up.)
(I hope she didn't hear what I said.)
I'm here to find you.
- Why? - I suspect you.
- As what? - As a coach.
- A coach? - Yes.
When I got here,
you were touching the machine.
- I was just curious. - I thought...
you were going to print a picture. Then you'd be a coach.
No.
I have nothing to print.
Then you're not a coach.
(You're not a coach.)
I've been suspecting you.
Everyone is suspecting me.
Are you the gold medalist?
- No. - Really?
Are you just feeling a bit down?
- Do I look down? - I mean...
- You're a bit quiet. - But even if...
I am the gold medalist, I wouldn't tell you.
Okay. Because I might be a coach?
- Yes. - Okay.
- But... - Then...
you should tell me the truth.
If I die during the next trial...
(Han Na, take the bait.)
- If you're the gold medalist... - I don't know what to do.
She must be the gold medalist.
(So Min must be the gold medalist.)
I don't know what to do.
- Everyone is suspecting me. - So Min.
I can't tell you anything more.
I can't trust you. Everyone is suspecting me.
- What should we do? - I have to find a coach.
- Okay. Go now. - I'll get going.
What is this? So Min must be the gold medalist.
(She's completely fooled.)
I need to run away.
Gosh, I'm so scared.
What should I do?
I don't want to be a spy ever again.
(It shortens your life.)
It shortens your life.
(What will happen to the novice spy?)
I'm a bad liar.
Who is it?
So Min shouldn't be eliminated.
I need to find another hint.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Whom are you suspecting?
- It's definitely So Min. - No, I don't think so.
- The hints point to her. - No, you're wrong.
We shouldn't eliminate her.
- We shouldn't. - Why not?
It's not her.
She's being framed.
I'm here to defend her.
I don't think it's So Min.
My goodness.
We need to decide based on the hints.
- It's my hunch. - What?
Have you found any hints?
I found a hint that So Min is not a coach.
Really? We've all been suspecting her.
That's the problem. So Min shouldn't be eliminated.
- So Min is not a coach. - She isn't.
I went to the scout list.
I was hiding...
She was trying to find the coaches.
Stop depending on your hunch.
- Hold on. - Coach Jeon So Min is out.
Who?
Coach Jeon So Min is out.
(Coach Jeon So Min is out.)
Coach? She's a coach?
- She is. - "Coach Jeon So Min is out."
- She's a coach? - She was a coach.
- How did she get eliminated? - You should be quiet.
- Keep your mouth shut. - I shouldn't do anything.
Keep your mouth shut.
- Ji Hyo. - She said So Min was not a coach.
- Hey. - But...
I think...
- Hey. - Ji Hyo.
- You don't even have any hints. - She kept on saying...
So Min was not a coach.
Come to think of it,
when the writer asked why I thought she was the gold medalist,
she pulled out her phone.
(After So Min deceived Han Na)
What's going on? I think So Min is the gold medalist.
Let's wait here.
I think this spot is where you can get some hints.
(She gets closer.)
- Why are you still here? - What?
- Why are you hiding here? - I'm looking for the coaches.
(So Min was going to walk up to her and take a picture from behind.)
Are you taking a picture?
No.
(I can see it.)
- I didn't take a picture. - What did you do with your phone?
- I didn't. - Hold on. What's this?
I didn't take any pictures.
- Really? Let me see your phone. - I didn't.
- I didn't take a picture. - Let me see your gallery.
- So Min. - I didn't take any pictures.
But what about your phone?
- I didn't. - You were looking at it.
I wasn't looking at my phone. I was looking at you from behind.
I looked at the mirror here.
- Why would you look at me? - No, I looked at the mirror.
- I looked at myself in the phone. - Oh, okay.
(That resolved her doubt.)
What was that? I thought you were the gold medalist.
- She was looking in the mirror. - Hey.
I guess that was that. Was she taking a picture of me to kill me?
(She comes to a big realization.)
(She got tricked by So Min's nonsense.)
What am I doing, Ji Hyo?
I think I shouldn't do anything.
- Han Na, you should stay still. - I got everything wrong.
I might get eliminated this way.
I think I'm hopeless in solving mysteries.
(She confesses that she's hopeless in solving mysteries.)
You have to talk based on evidence.
Stop talking based on your hunch.
- Hey. - I shouldn't do anything.
- Stop abusing yourself. - You don't have any evidence.
(She won't try to help So Min now.)
(By the way, how did So Min get eliminated?)
- Come here. - Hey.
- Come here. - You're a coach, right?
(She arrests Coach Jeon So Min.)
- She's a coach, right? - Seok Jin.
- Look at her. She's like this. - She's a coach.
- She's this kind of person. - Oh, gosh.
- She said this to me. - You're so shrewd.
- "I swear it's not me." - I'll never trust you.
- So Min. - Somebody is worse than me.
(They feel betrayed.)
- Who? - What?
Can I say who it is?
(Can I say who eliminated me?)
(Who's the gold medalist that got Coach So Min out?)
(At that moment, Haha finds a hint.)
The gold medalist uses their real name.
(The gold medalist uses their real name.)
(They use their real name?)
My gosh.
It was right next to the white box.
(Ji Hyo finds a hint in the corner too.)
The gold medalist has been to Daema Island.
(The gold medalist has been to Daema Island.)
(If they've been to Daema Island and use their real name,)
(the gold medalist is either Sang Yeob or Kwang Soo.)
(Is the gold medalist Sang Yeob or Kwang Soo?)
- Han Na. - Yes?
- What? - You might eliminate me.
I won't.
- Did anything happen? - Do you want to talk?
Was there any information?
Information? About whom?
About everybody. About Coach A or B.
- About A or B? - Yes.
- Are you the gold medalist? - What?
(By any chance,)
(is Sang Yeob a gold medalist looking for hints about the coach?)
I have to find some hints.
Should I take a picture?
(He wants to take a picture?)
(Kwang Soo can take a picture.)
(What is his identity?)
You saw this and didn't tell me.
Please give me the hint.
Coach B is a male.
(Coach B is a male.)
(In an earlier hint, they said Coach B's occupation was acting.)
(Then Coach B is an actor.)
My goodness.
It's either Kwang Soo or Sang Yeob.
(Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo are strong candidates for Coach B.)
- Did you find anything? - I found nothing.
(The hints about the gold medalist and Coach B both point to them.)
What about you? Did you find anything?
No, so nobody wants to share information with me.
(One of them is the gold medalist, and the other is Coach B.)
Let's take the pictures first and send it.
(What are their identities?)
Tell me the results of your investigation.
The investigation result is...
(Give me your name tag!)
(My investigation result leads to you.)
- What was that? - There.
What was that?
(Han Na is out.)
- What was that? - I'm sorry.
Who are you?
- Isn't it you? - What?
Isn't it her? Isn't she...
Aren't you the gold medalist?
(Sang Yeob is after the gold medalist.)
(He's a coach who got turned down by the players and held a grudge.)
(Let me see who's on our scout list.)
Who's this?
I have Seok Jin too.
(He found out that the gold medalist is a coward.)
The gold medalist is a coward.
(He hunted down Seok Jin.)
(Ripping)
(Seok Jin is out.)
(He got an innocent player out.)
It's Han Na.
(His next target is Han Na.)
(I think she's the gold medalist.)
(He hunted her down right away.)
- What was that? Who are you? - I'm sorry.
Who are you?
- Isn't it you? - What?
Aren't you the gold medalist?
- Are you a coach? - I am.
(I'm a coach.)
(Oh, dear.)
(I can trust anybody here.)
I'm sorry. I guessed wrong.
Han Na is out.
(Sang Yeob was Coach B who got Han Na out.)
(Who is Kwang Soo who can take pictures?)
(This morning, in a secret place)
This is the 36th Running Man Olympics.
The stickers are gone.
Kwang Soo,
you're the gold medalist.
(Kwang Soo was the gold medalist.)
(Da Hee was suspicious and slandered him,)
(so he took a picture of her right away.)
(Like the coaches who glued the photos on the red scout list,)
(the gold medalist could also glue the coach's photo on the blue list.)
- Da Hee? - Yes.
- What about you, Jin Young? - Da Hee.
(He thought she was a strong candidate, but she was a player.)
(As the gold medalist, I'll get the coach out next.)
- It's So Min. - It's her.
- It's So Min. - It has to be her.
According to the list...
- No, go. It's okay. - Why?
(He finally bumped into her. This was his chance.)
(He got his phone ready to take a picture of her.)
(I'm the gold medalist.)
(But I'm the gold medalist.)
(You must be a coach then.)
(Typing)
(Hold on.)
Give it to me.
Give it to me. What are you doing? Give it to me.
(He flapped his long arms to send a picture of her.)
(The picture was glued on, so he just had to get her out.)
(Struggling)
(This is an intense struggle between the coach and the medalist.)
Why are you doing this to me?
- You know better. - You can't do this.
(Ripping)
(He got So Min out.)
(It was Kwang Soo who got Coach So Min out.)
Oh, dear.
(Coaches versus Gold Medalist)
- Player Kang Han Na is out. - What?
(Han Na is out?)
- Hey. - See?
(They're startled by the news.)
- Here's a hint about Coach B. - Who? B?
Coach B is...
a male.
(Coach B is a male.)
It's a male?
It's either Kwang Soo or Sang Yeob then.
It's Sang Yeob.
I'll repeat.
(Kwang Soo hears the hint.)
(Coach B was Sang Yeob!)
I got goose bumps. Come here, Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo is Coach B.)
I didn't know Kwang Soo was like that. Don't be like that.
Hold on.
(What? It's not me!)
I have to get ready to defend myself.
(Let's say it's Kwang Soo.)
Wait. You have to watch what you say.
The identity of the gold medalist can be narrowed.
You have to be careful.
You have to be careful from now on. You have to be very careful.
(I have to get Sang Yeob out.)
Oh, wait.
(He has to take a picture of him to get him out.)
Wait.
- Hey. - Wait.
(Where is he running?)
(Coach Sang Yeob keeps on lurking around the scout list.)
(He sees a picture of Kwang Soo.)
I was going to take a picture of Da Hee,
but Sang Yeob was in the picture.
I'll send that one.
(He accidentally took a photo of Sang Yeob.)
(He sends the picture over.)
Okay, it got sent.
If I go back now, they're going to think it's me.
(There's no time.)
I have to get him out. I have to get Sang Yeob out.
The gold medalist. That's the important thing.
(Meanwhile, Sang Yeob keeps on searching for the gold medalist.)
Can you go out that way as well?
Where were you?
I went around this way.
(Se Chan and Haha are on full alert.)
Why?
Han Na is out.
Really?
I can't hear the announcement in the hallway.
(He acts obliviously.)
(Isn't he weird?)
There are three guys.
(It's him.)
- It's So Min... - Sang Yeob is weird.
It's So Min, Sang Yeob...
It's either Kwang Soo or Sang Yeob.
Is it Sang Yeob then?
(I'll finish off...)
(Coach B.)
Kwang Soo.
(This voice is...)
(They finally meet.)
(Kwang Soo is ready...)
(to prepare his innocence.)
(If he gets Coach Sang Yeob out,)
(there will be only one coach left.)
The gala show starts now.
(The gala show...)
(is starting?)
What?
(The invitation was found, and everything pauses now.)
(The coach is right in front of me.)
(Everybody stops and puts on blindfolds.)
(The gala show has begun, and it'll provide important hints.)
(4 people can participate in the gala show.)
(From the 4 participants, the minority, whether it be...)
(the coaches or the players, is out.)
(If there are 3 coaches and 1 player, the player is out.)
(If there are 3 players and 1 coach, the coach is out.)
(If there are 2 coaches and 2 players...)
(or all players, nothing happens.)
(Somebody just found...)
(the gala show invitation.)
All I needed was 10 seconds.
Please.
I didn't know this would happen.
(Moments ago)
(The first person who found the invitation was Haha.)
You must participate with one person of your choice.
Hold on. Let me come up with a strategy.
(The result of the gala show depends on whom he brings.)
In any way, it has to be 3 to 1, right?
Or four?
(There are two coaches left.)
(Sang Yeob is a strong candidate.)
(Sang Yeob was acting suspiciously, so Haha became certain.)
(So he decides to invite...)
Sang Yeob.
(So he decides to invite Sang Yeob, a strong candidate.)
(Gala show invitation list)
(Jae Seok found the second invitation.)
What's this?
You can pick one person,
and we'll invite that person to the gala show.
(The person Jae Seok chose was...)
Se Chan.
(In contrast to Haha, he picked somebody who is likely a player.)
(Gala show invitation list)
(They have different plans. What will be the result?)
We'll know once we see it.
All four of you participated in the gala show.
As I said before,
if there's more of one side,
the person on the lesser side will get eliminated.
(Sang Yeob will be out if he's the only coach.)
But if there's an equal split or if you're all players,
nothing will happen.
(Nothing will happen if there are 2 players and 2 coaches.)
I'm getting goose bumps.
(This is a golden opportunity to figure out Coach A's identity.)
All right. According to the result of the gala show...
(The result is revealed.)
The number of people who are out is...
(The person who is out from these four...)
(Who is going to be out?)
None.
I got goose bumps.
(Nothing happened.)
(Sang Yeob wasn't eliminated.)
Is there more to this?
That means...
there could be 2 coaches and 2 players...
What's going on?
Or there could be four players.
Wait. Who's left?
Hold on.
See?
The trial has started.
(With the shocking result, the last trial begins.)
Please participate.
(Coaches versus players. Who will win?)
(The last trial)
Nobody got out?
- Come inside, and listen to me. - It's 2 and 2 then.
- Let's talk. - Nobody got out?
This is complicated.
Why? Why?
(There are less possibilities now but this is more complicated.)
For this trial,
you can discuss amongst yourselves and submit two names.
Two people with the most votes will come up.
Okay.
Who has hints about the coaches?
Everybody, we shared all these,
but Coach A is a Running Man member in their 40s.
From my point of view, that's either Jong Kook or Haha.
- That's Jae Seok's point of view. - Yes, that's right.
Oh, gosh. I'm 40.
The hint about Coach B...
(The hints about Coach B point to Sang Yeob.)
- Near the end, Han Na got out. - Yes.
- It was a decisive hint. - It was a male.
Coach B is either Kwang Soo or Sang Yeob.
- Actor? Yes. - Right.
Then let's organize this.
The three people we are certain about should go there.
Me?
Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Jin Young are not it.
- They're not coaches? - No.
- And the suspects should come here. - Come here.
Don't take this personally.
(I'll sit next to Se Chan.)
Come here. Kwang Soo, come here.
Don't go there, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo,)
(where are you going?)
- You belong here. - It's really not me.
It's really not me. You want me to sit here?
- Sit here. - It's really not me.
- Come here. - You have to be here.
- Oh, gosh. What? - You have to be here.
(In everyone's eyes, he's just a suspicious candidate.)
All right. We don't have much time.
- Hold on. - You're acting weirdly.
I'm the gold medalist.
What?
- I'm the gold medalist. - All of a sudden?
(He reveals his identity since he's getting accused,)
(but others tell him off.)
- Really? - All of a sudden?
- The gala show... - I got So Min out.
There are no medalists here, right?
- Who's a medalist here? - There are none. I told you.
It has to be Sang Yeob then.
- Because... - It's not you then.
You, go there.
(If Kwang Soo is the medalist, Coach B has to be Sang Yeob.)
What I want to say now...
- is that I'm the gold medalist. - Wait.
Because this has to be certain.
- If you're the medalist... - How did you get So Min out?
- We're all players. - How did you get So Min out?
How did you get So Min out?
(He asks Sang Yeob to testify.)
- I got her out? - How did you get her out?
Did you say, "I got her out?"
Isn't that what he's talking about?
Only the gold medalist can eliminate her.
The gold medalist is supposed to get her out?
- You should go to jail. - Wait.
That must have been a mistake.
- Somebody got her by mistake. - Fine.
It's So Min, Sang Yeob, and Haha.
It's So Min, Sang Yeob, and Jae Seok.
I'm serious.
Sang Yeob is 100 percent.
Do you have anything else?
- Jong Kook. - I'll reveal a hint about Coach A.
- Tell us. - Did you get one?
Here it is.
Coach A...
(These three are the candidates.)
- Coach A has a son. - He has a son?
(Coach A has a son?)
(20 minutes before trial)
(Jong Kook found a decisive hint.)
Coach A has a son.
(Coach A has a son.)
(That's right. It's him.)
This is for certain. It's him.
(That excludes him too. This is a decisive hint.)
- Coach A has a son. - He has a son?
- It's either Haha or Jae Seok. - Yes.
(That narrows down to 2 people for Coach A.)
- Then... - Okay.
in my point of view, everything fits like a puzzle.
- All right. - All right. I get it.
- The son... - You have to share the information.
Why are you playing solo?
(Are you here to solve mysteries for fun?)
You have to share the information. Share!
That's why... Hold on.
That's why the gala show was decisive.
That's why the gala show... Gosh, it was decisive.
I know for sure too.
I went to the gala show.
I am just an ordinary person.
- Right. - Let me say something.
- Ordinary people change the world. - That's right. Please hear me out.
To whom did Jae Seok give the gala show invitation?
Me.
(Moments before the start of the gala show)
- Jae Seok, did you invite me? - Yes. Of course.
(Yes, of course.)
(Did Jae Seok know Se Chan was a player and invited him?)
The important point is this. Why do you think I chose Se Chan?
- Because you're not a coach. - You're a player.
I have to bring a player to be safe.
- Right, right. - One more.
- Haha brought Sang Yeob. - That's right.
Haha came and said this.
I didn't think this was important at first.
"Haha, whom did you pick?"
"Sang Yeob". "Why?"
"He's acting weirdly."
(Haha said Sang Yeob acted weirdly.)
Let's finish this quickly.
- Who invited you, Haha? - Did you get the invitation?
- I picked somebody. - Whom did you pick?
Sang Yeob.
- Sang Yeob? - Yes, he's acting weirdly.
(In the same situation, Jae Seok and Haha made different choices.)
There's a hole in this.
The weird person will pick another weird person.
If you think they're weird and you still bring them,
that means you can fall into a trap.
No, because I was certain about Sang Yeob.
My intention was if Sang Yeob...
Because we're all players, right? He'll be eliminated.
(If Haha took Coach Sang Yeob, Sang Yeob would be out.)
- He'll be eliminated. But... - Right.
(If there were three players, Sang Yeob would've been out.)
If either he or I...
- is a coach, it'll be a tie. - Right.
(Even if there were two coaches, it'd be a tie.)
If either he or I is a coach, it'll be a tie.
(The players will not get eliminated.)
I had nothing to lose. It was a test too.
No, that's not true.
- To be honest, both makes sense. - You're right.
This is driving me crazy.
- My point is this. - This is way too easy.
If Jae Seok was a coach, he wouldn't have invited me.
- Exactly. - Because...
if he was a coach, he had the risk...
- of getting eliminated. - Exactly.
- You guys are so frustrating. - This is...
so obvious. The answer's already so clear.
But Haha also has a point.
- Seriously. - It was a safe bet for him.
- Exactly. - Because...
- So Min got eliminated. - He was testing the waters.
That doesn't make any sense. He could've gotten me eliminated.
Okay, it's time to vote.
- This is insane. - This is...
This is really driving me crazy.
I'll just trust my instinct.
- Seriously. - We just held a small meeting.
- I'm suspicious of him as well. - A and B are so obvious.
It's Sang Yeob and Haha.
I'll repeat what he just said but with a different name.
It's exactly the same.
- Everyone. - Pay attention.
- You need to concentrate. - Seriously.
I'm being really serious right now.
- I'm serious too, everyone. - Yes.
- I'm being sincere. - Let me repeat myself.
- Don't end up regretting. - Trust me.
Come on. We're almost there.
(They finish voting.)
If the gold medalist gets eliminated,
the players will end up losing.
And it'll be the same if you fail to catch the remaining two coaches.
(Team Coach loses if both Coach A and Sang Yeob are caught.)
(The winning team will get the Luxury Stickers,)
(and the losing team will get the Shuddering Stickers.)
Gosh, this is such a close bet.
The first candidate got seven votes.
(The candidate who got the highest number of votes)
Lee Sang Yeob.
- See? - Sang Yeob is definitely a coach.
(A single mistake has led him to get eliminated.)
- Almost everyone... - Everyone voted for him.
That means even a coach voted for you so that he could live.
I know.
The 2nd and 3rd candidates each received...
4 and 3 votes. It was a close match.
(The 2nd and 3rd candidates only had a difference of 1 vote.)
(This is crazy.)
- Just one vote? - That's so close.
(There's only a difference of one vote.)
The one who got four votes...
(The teams' results depend on that one vote.)
(Please don't let it be the other coach.)
(Who will join Sang Yeob?)
Haha got 4 votes, and Jae Seok got 3 votes.
- Haha, please come up here. - Okay.
(Haha gets 4 votes.)
(He's shocked.)
- That one vote saved me. - My gosh.
(Their destiny gets divided due to a single vote.)
(He can't believe Haha got voted out.)
Who...
- See? - My gosh.
That means one of you voted for me.
This is crazy.
- My gosh. - But it's still a relief.
- I'm so relieved. - Who voted for Haha?
Why can't you guys tell?
- You voted for me, didn't you? - No way.
- Was it you? - They both voted for Haha.
You guys voted for Haha?
Let's just get the penalty.
- We did it. We're done. - Who did this?
Who voted for Haha?
- You voted for me, didn't you? - Of course.
He's definitely a coach. I just didn't point him out.
You're so stupid!
Are you serious?
Let's just get the penalty.
Let's check their identities.
1, 2, 3.
(What are they?)
(Sang Yeob is definitely a coach.)
You completely got fooled.
(Both teams depend on Haha.)
(Is Haha a coach or a player?)
(Coach)
(Haha was also a coach.)
See? I told you.
(Team Players wins for having caught both coaches.)
He was a coach?
- They're both coaches. - Nice!
- Are you serious? - I told you so.
(What a pity.)
(I'm a player.)
Good job.
That was so close.
I can't believe this.
We were so close!
(He tried his best to survive, but he lost by just one vote.)
I'm so angry.
You guys are coaches, and you're holding a grudge against...
the players for having turned down your offer to train them.
Right. How could I forget?
(He starts acting right away.)
- Seriously. - No one accepted my offer.
I know.
I really got so angry. I'm serious.
I was about to quit coaching.
(Role-playing as the spy is so fun.)
People might doubt So Min,
but they'll never doubt me.
- They won't doubt me. - Really?
I failed so many times.
I heard you're like a drain.
(I heard you're like a drain.)
- A drain? - You're the worst spy ever.
- I know. - Because she fails?
- Yes, that's it. - It's true though.
- I heard she's really bad. - It's true.
I heard that about her.
I'll be working with amateurs.
- Don't worry, I'll be... - This is the worst.
- How will they get hints? - I'll surprise you today.
- This combination is funny. - I won't let you down.
But it's the worst.
(Haha had already prepared himself for the worst.)
(He started framing others.)
(He made people like him by acting naively.)
(He tried so hard to survive.)
- I'm the gold medalist. - You?
(But So Min got eliminated by lying to the real gold medalist.)
I'm the gold medalist.
(Sang Yeob made a sudden move after feeling threatened,)
(but he got caught for not knowing the rules properly.)
(They both ended up making mistakes just like amateurs.)
(I can't believe we lost by just one vote.)
But I really...
The coaches were Haha, Sang Yeob, and So Min.
Are we three getting the stickers?
I already have two of those.
We could've won.
And Kwang Soo, who performed greatly as the gold medalist,
will get a Luxury Sticker.
Good job, Kwang Soo.
So Min will end up going no matter what.
(The coaches and the gold medalist get their designated stickers.)
- Sang Yeob's almost settled to go. - I know.
- But... - However,
the Shuddering Sticker slot needs three more people.
Exactly.
- What? - Do we choose?
Please bring out the briefcases.
- Again? - There's more?
- This is insane. - Not all of you will be safe.
- This is... - I can't believe this.
There are eight briefcases.
And three of them have Shuddering Stickers inside.
(3 out of 8 briefcases have Shuddering Stickers inside.)
We'll find out who gets to go.
The ones who voted for Jae Seok should pick first.
- That's a good idea. - Let's do that.
Haha, I still remember.
- You almost got it. - You can go ahead and open them.
- Jong Kook, open it. - Okay.
(I almost made a big mistake today.)
(What? Luxury Package?)
It's the Luxury Package. My gosh.
(This is ridiculous.)
- He's so lucky. - This is absurd.
- I'm sorry. - He's so lucky.
This is all thanks to you. You did well today.
I can't believe he got that.
- I'm sorry. - Seriously?
This is just how things turned out.
You need to...
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
I hope you get the Shuddering Package.
(He picked the briefcase with the Shuddering Package.)
(Se Chan always ends up being pitiful.)
What's wrong? What is it?
My gosh.
I was told to go home all day.
And I doubted the wrong person.
I run over to Jong Kook whenever he calls me.
And I go when he tells me to go.
I really enjoyed your company today.
Se Chan, stick your name on the board.
There are two more people left.
There are only two more?
That's 4 against 2.
- Let's take one each. - Yes, let's do that.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(The remaining 6 each choose a briefcase.)
Let's all take turns opening them. Han Na, you go first.
Okay. I hope I get the Luxury Package.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- You need to unlock it first. - It's locked.
(She was trying to open it when it was still locked.)
- Wait. - You need to unlock it.
- Come on. - She's unbelievable.
(Her briefcase opening skills are as bad as her problem-solving skills.)
- She's unbelivable. - It's the other way around.
- She's a little off. - Like this?
- Like this? - Yes.
Okay. In 1, 2, 3.
- My gosh. - No, come on.
In 1, 2, 3.
(She's using one hand to open it and the other hand to close it.)
- That's not it. - What's wrong?
You need to open it like this.
(This moment is supposed to be very tense.)
- You need to hold it like this. - Oh, okay.
She probably voted for Jong Kook instead of me.
Yes, probably.
I think I picked the wrong one.
- Open it. - Come on.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In, 1, 2, 3.
- She got the Shuddering Package. - My gosh.
Oh, gosh.
(She opened it the wrong way and got the Shuddering Package.)
- She got the Shuddering Package. - My gosh.
(She ends the day with the Shuddering Package.)
She got the Shuddering Package.
(There are 5 people remaining.)
- There's just 1 more ticket. - There's 1 more.
I can't believe she got that.
It's so funny.
In 1, 2, 3.
I got the Luxury Package.
(Even Da Hee ends up getting the Luxury Package.)
- She got the Luxury Package. - My gosh.
- Oh, please. - It's 1 of you 3.
(One of them will be getting the Shuddering Package.)
Jae Seok, change briefcases.
Take Ji Hyo's.
Take Ji Hyo's. Exchange your briefcases.
- Why? - What?
Let him have yours.
No reason.
- I feel sorry for him. - No, I don't want to change.
No, I don't want to change.
- Really? - Then let's keep going.
- Let's go. - Keep going.
I feel like there might be feces inside Jae Seok's briefcase.
There might be a huge feces.
- Open them all at once. - Really?
- You're not going to change it? - No.
- All at once. - In one,
- 2... - 3.
(Who will end up getting the Shuddering Sticker?)
Three.
(Ji Hyo ends up getting the Shuddering Sticker.)
- It's the Luxury Package. - Ji Hyo got it.
It's Ji Hyo.
(The briefcase she almost gave away had the Shuddering Sticker inside.)
(I'm glad I didn't get it.)
- She should've switched briefcases. - You should've switched.
(Jae Seok should've gotten it.)
You should've switched.
- I feel so sorry for her. - My gosh.
I almost even considered switching briefcases.
But I didn't because Ji Hyo got angry
I figured I shouldn't bother her
(What a great day.)
- You should've switched. - Can we pick again?
(The Family Package Project has come to an end.)
- I got the Luxury Package. - I can't believe...
I got the Luxury Package.
(2nd Week Results, Luxury Package, Shuddering Package)