(SBS Open Hall, Deungchon-dong)
Hello. Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Seok Jin, your steps are light.
- What? - Your steps are light.
- He is in a good mood. - You know why.
His steps are bound to be light since his legs are so thin.
(He attacks Seok Jin's paper-thin legs.)
Hey.
I think you will fly soon.
For goodness' sake.
- Perhaps he will fly like this. - Gosh.
Gosh, you have so much mold on the back of your neck.
Why did you tell him that?
They are pimples!
Seok Jin is getting attacked left and right.
Seriously.
What is that?
- It startled me. - It's a drone.
- What is going on? - Is it delivering a mission card?
It really has a mission card.
(The drone delivers a mission card.)
- How fascinating! - Is it delivering a mission card?
- Do we need to catch it? - Look over there.
Is this how we are getting a mission card?
Catch it gently.
- Step back. - Come on.
- Catch it gently. - Step back.
- Catch it gently. - There you go.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Seok Jin. - My goodness.
(Snapping)
- What? - My goodness.
- Jae Seok! - Hey!
(The drone catches on the string Jae Seok flicked.)
- Hey. - Do you know how much it costs?
Do you know how much it costs?
- I am sorry. - I am sorry.
- Pay for it. - For goodness' sake.
It was Jae Seok. It was Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. Jae Seok. - Seriously.
Here is the drone. I am sorry.
Jae Seok, what do you think you are doing?
What do you think you are doing?
I will pay back for it.
- It's okay. - I am sorry.
Jae Seok will pay back for it.
- I am sorry. - He is a troublemaker.
It's not like that.
There are people who always break machines.
I will be sure...
- to pay for it. - He is a troublemaker.
Don't touch anything.
- He gave me a scare. - Goodness.
- My goodness. - What is this?
What does it say?
"Dangerous Delivery, Briefcase Delivery".
(Dangerous Delivery, Briefcase Delivery)
"Deliver the briefcase to the final destination within six hours."
"If you deliver the briefcase, only one member will face the penalty,"
"but if you fail, only one member will be exempt from the penalty."
- Only one? - "Roulettes will pick the member."
"You can find out the address if you complete three missions."
"Warning. You cannot open the briefcase."
(The moment they open it, everyone will face the penalty.)
If you do, you fail the mission, and everyone will face the penalty.
If we open it, we all fail?
We have to deliver this within six hours?
Don't give it to Jae Seok.
- He can't be in charge of that. - He will destroy the briefcase too.
Don't let him touch the roulettes. He might break them too.
Jae Seok, be careful with your hands.
- Ji Hyo is the safest bet. - I can't believe you all.
- You're too mean. - Right?
- I'm begging you. - Yes?
How about we give it to Seok Jin? He hates carrying things.
(How about we give it to Seok Jin? He hates carrying things.)
- That's a good idea. - Yes, let's give it to him.
(Let's have the lazy guy carry this.)
- Hey! - We must change things around.
- I don't even carry umbrellas. - Listen.
- Hey. - He should carry this.
- He should. Right. - That was a good idea.
He should...
- He should carry the briefcase. - He hates carrying things.
- He should give it a try. - I agree.
- This is crazy. - Don't use it as a pillow though.
- What a hassle. - He should carry this.
It's better that I carry important things.
(He changes his stance.)
The first hint is at stake on this mission.
It's called Snack from the Drone.
- Drone? - What?
(First mission, Snack from the Drone)
For three minutes,
one of you will control the drone that will carry the snack.
To succeed, the rest of you must eat five pieces of snacks...
with mouthpieces on.
If you succeed, you will receive a hint about the destination.
- Is this the controller? - What is this?
(Before the game, everyone practices flying drones.)
- My gosh. - It worked!
- What happened? - Whose drone is that?
(Jong Kook flies the drone skillfully as soon as they start.)
(Then let me try too.)
This is working nicely.
(Crashing)
What did you just do?
(Seok Jin's drone crashes into Jong Kook's in the air.)
(What is going on with that guy?)
What are you doing? You're scaring me.
The instructor is here.
- Hey! - We have the instructor here.
(It's fine. Let me try it one more time.)
- It's flying. Hey, it's flying. - It's flying.
- Come here. - No, no.
- Where are you going? This way! - We invited the instructor.
(It makes an emergency landing on top of the staff.)
(What? Why did that end up there?)
- What's up with him? It's scary. - Where is mine?
- Bring it down. - Bring it down.
- Here it is. - My gosh.
- We have instructors here. - I like this one.
This moves the drone to the left, and this, to the right.
I got it. I mastered this.
(As they learn how to control it, they're getting a hang of it.)
Gosh, I'm really good at this.
(They eagerly try to fly the drones in the air.)
I can do this too. I don't need the controller.
My goodness, this is awesome.
This is perfect.
Look at this.
(Completing the mission won't be a problem.)
- Hey, this is easy. - That's mine.
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin is...)
(Gosh! That startled me.)
(Even after the lesson, he's not good at flying the drone.)
This is so easy.
The staff is in trouble. It's so easy to fly this.
To the left.
Go straight.
(This middle-aged man has lost the sense of directions.)
How am I supposed to do this?
Look at this. You must be able to do this, at least.
(He patiently continues to practice despite their teasing.)
Hey, it went over the fence.
(The drone goes over the fence.)
Wait, the drone went over.
(As he's unable to control the drone, it goes out of the set.)
I can't fly this.
How am I supposed to fly this?
(Seok Jin is in big trouble just like the size of his big nose.)
Choose the member that will fly the drone.
- Pardon? - I'm really confident I can do it.
- I'm serious. - Let him fly it.
- Even the instructors approved. - Let's play a game.
- Anyone should do it. - I'll do it.
- I'm really good at this. - Then...
- Gosh. - Let's play Race of Wits.
(Let's play Race of Wits.)
- Again? - Hey.
- He's addicted to that game. - That's enough.
- Get out if you don't want to play. - He's addicted to the game.
- Fine, let's play it. - Why do you like that game so much?
- Get out if you don't want to play. - You're addicted to that.
- Let's play it. - Start.
- 1. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
- The three of you are out. - You're out.
(Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan are out.)
The three of you are out. They are out.
(I knew it. It's so much fun.)
- Let's stop playing this game. - This is unbelievable.
- Come on. - This is so unfair.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 3.
(Jae Seok and So Min are out.)
- What's wrong with you? - Jae Seok.
Should we play rock-paper-scissors?
(The last 3 members play rock-paper-scissors.)
- Darn it. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin is chosen to fly the drone.)
- No! - My gosh.
Okay!
(That guy is going to control the drone?)
He's going to ruin our faces.
- What are we going to do? - He can't fly that.
- No, no. - How could you be so clueless?
- He's not delicate enough. - My gosh.
- Why not? - You know what?
- We have to get the hint. - Exactly.
Someone who can fly it well should do it.
(The hint depends on Seok Jin's drone.)
- It has to go up after that. - Right.
Up, up, up.
- Try again. - Turn it on again.
- Fly it up again. - Turn it on first.
(Whizzing)
(The drone heads underground.)
Seok Jin, is this a drill?
I don't think we can hang the snack on it.
You did it. You got it, Seok Jin.
- You have to fly it high. - Hold on.
My goodness, come on. Seriously?
(His out-of-the-set flying makes them more anxious.)
What are you doing?
What will we do? We're in trouble.
Can you bring me that back?
(He's shameless.)
- What are you doing? - Whom are you talking to?
- Whom are you talking to? - What?
- Whom are you talking to? - What do you think you're doing?
- What's wrong with him? - What are you doing?
(The middle-aged man is about to fly the drone.)
- Let's do this. - Hey, I'm going to do this well.
(They must eat 5 pieces of snack within 3 minutes to get the hint.)
- Let's go. - All right.
Get ready.
(Seok Jin's drone takes off.)
- Bring that here. - Move it to the front.
- Move it to the front. - To the front.
Okay, okay. Wait, Seok Jin.
You have to change the direction.
- Wait, no, no. - Bring it down.
Lower the drone.
(You just need to lower it from where it is now.)
- Lower it. - Lower it. Kwang Soo...
(He did lower it, but he lowered it too quickly.)
(Who knew he'd lower it like that?)
(Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.)
(1 minute has passed already.)
Hold on. We'll go there.
- We got it. We got it. - It's close.
It's close. Eat it.
Eat it. Hey...
(They're only darting their tongues.)
Hey! Get your tongue away!
(What on earth is going on?)
Get your tongue away from mine.
(Slapping)
- Move it away. - Eat it.
Why can't you eat it? I can't make it easier for you.
- I can't make it easier than this. - Lower it.
- Lower it. Lower it! - Ji Hyo will go for it.
(The best player, Ji Hyo, will try.)
- Give us a new one. - Give that to me.
- She ate it. - Okay. She ate it.
- She ate it. - She ate it.
Okay, we did one.
Gosh, that was really hard.
- Bring it here. - Wait.
- Ji Hyo. - Okay.
(Laughing)
Why?
(Give me my snack!)
(Why did you hit me?)
- Lower it. - Where is this going?
- Lower the drone. - What's he doing?
This isn't supposed to...
(This lovely snack runs away when they approach it.)
(Slapping)
I almost had it.
(He slaps Kwang Soo out of strong enthusiasm.)
Jae Seok, I almost had it.
Eat it. Come on, eat that.
- Lower the snack. - It hurts.
- Okay. - The time is up.
- We should've kept going. - Hey.
This is impossible.
- It was too high for us to reach. - No, no.
- It's the drone. - You just had to lower it.
- I did an excellent job. - Flying drones is easy.
- Let me give it a try. - It was too hard.
Let's win this. We have to deliver it in six hours.
(The time is ticking. We only have 5 hours left.)
Start.
(During the practice, Haha was able to fly the drone well.)
- Haha is good at this. - Yes, he's good.
Let's do this.
(The direction is good. And so is the height.)
- Bring it closer. - Closer.
- Jae Seok. - It has to come closer.
- Bring it closer. To the left. - Slowly.
(He skillfully flies it to the tall guy, Kwang Soo.)
- Okay. - Okay, okay.
(Haha feeds 1 piece as soon as he starts, thanks to Kwang Soo.)
- Fly it. Okay. - Come here.
(Let me help too.)
- Okay. - It's Jae Seok's.
- Jae Seok. - I'm literally feeding it to you.
It's Jae Seok's.
(It's my chance. I just need to munch on it.)
- Lower it. - It's Jae Seok's.
- Jae Seok. - It's Jae Seok's.
- Come here. - Don't shake the snack.
It keeps shaking because of the wind.
(When I move in,)
Come on, Jae Seok.
(you make a retreat.)
- What are you doing? - Eat it.
Eat it.
- This isn't hard. - Move!
- This isn't hard. - Come on. Move! Move!
(Tired of Jae Seok's playing, Jong Kook sets out.)
Raise it. Fly it high.
(He bites the string first with his teeth.)
There you go. Good job. Good riddance.
You'll end up eating the drone.
Come here. Come to us.
- Lower it. Lower it. - Lower it.
- It's yours, Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
That's it.
(They successfully eat 3 pieces in a row.)
Wait.
- Is he a man or a machine? - Wait.
(They're shocked.)
(They must eat 2 pieces in 1 minute.)
- Lower it. - It's Seok Jin's.
You can do it!
(Haha skillfully flies the drone right in front of Seok Jin.)
(He's so close.)
- Did he eat it? - No, no.
- He can eat it. - He can reach it.
Use your teeth. Use your teeth.
(The snack is playing hard-to-get.)
Why can't you eat this?
- Why can't you eat this? - Ji Hyo, you go for it.
(Crunching)
(She eats the snack on Seok Jin's back.)
- She ate it. - She got it.
My goodness.
- Bring it to us. - Haha.
Move this way.
- Come quickly. - Why can't I fly this higher?
(The snack is even playing hard-to-get with the pilot.)
- Gosh, seriously, Haha? - Wait.
(Due to his terrible flying, Jong Kook falls into the trap too.)
Hey.
(We only had one piece left to go.)
- You're unbelievable. - You said you were good at this.
- I'm sorry. - He's drooling.
(They fail their 2nd round by a close call.)
- Ready. Hook your arms. - Ready.
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
- We can do this. - We can do this.
(Time is running out. We have to succeed this time.)
Let's do this!
- You can do this. - Let's go.
Ready, go.
(Jong Kook's drone takes off.)
Good. Keep going.
(The dark horse's drone flies stably.)
Higher.
- Higher. - Lower it.
Lower it.
- Lower it. - Lower it.
- Lower it. - A bit more.
- Lower it. - Even more.
(It is approaching Se Chan.)
(Se Chan eats the snack as soon as they start.)
- Done! - Okay.
(So Min, it's your turn.)
Move!
Eat it!
(So Min eats the 2nd snack.)
- Done. - Done.
(Hey, your mouthpiece came off.)
(So Min's mouthpiece comes off.)
Put it back on.
(She was overzealous.)
- Put it back on. - Here we go.
Let's do this.
Stay there.
- Good. - It's for Se Chan.
Hurry!
(Biting)
(Se Chan gets the 3rd snack.)
- Done. - Done.
We've eaten three.
Two more to go.
We can do it.
- Is it good? - Stop.
Stop.
(The 4th snack approaches Seok Jin.)
Good. Go near it.
(Will he make up for his previous mistake?)
Seok Jin.
(Falling)
(Seok Jin makes everyone fall.)
Gosh.
What is this?
(Jong Kook can't believe it.)
- We need to hook our arms. - Hurry.
(There is only 40 seconds left now.)
Slowly.
Good.
(It's so close.)
I'm doing such a good job. Why can't you eat it?
- Good. - Eat it.
Here!
(Ji Hyo eats the 4th snack.)
Done!
- Done! - Go!
There's 30 seconds left.
Okay. We have to eat just one more.
- Move! - It's here.
(Let's succeed by all means.)
- Stay there! - Stay!
Eat it. Be careful.
(Screaming)
(Jae Seok bites Kwang Soo's neck.)
What happened?
- Why were you there? - Okay.
Why were you there?
The snack was right in front of me.
Mission complete!
(They complete the Snack from the Drone mission.)
I bit something soft, and it was your cheek.
(I bit something soft, and it was your cheek.)
You completed your first mission.
That's a relief.
Where's our briefcase?
(By the way...)
- Where is it? - Where is it?
(Where did our briefcase go?)
- Where did it go? - Where is it?
Our briefcase is gone.
(They lose their briefcase while trying to win a hint.)
What's wrong with you?
- It's gone. - It was here before.
- It's here. Gosh. - Why did you take it?
(Relieved)
Whom are you talking to?
Whom are you trying to blame?
- What is this? - You shouldn't leave it with me.
- I... - We're leaving it with you.
Please don't.
It's dangerous.
- Gosh. - Here.
(They receive a hint regarding the delivery place.)
- Yangcheon District? - We've gotten the address.
It's close from here.
- It's close. - That's right.
(They have to deliver the briefcase to Yangcheon District in time.)
(If they fail, everyone except 1 person will be penalized.)
The two roulette wheels will be filled with your names...
according to the game results and votes.
There will be votes?
To decide who will be exempt and who will be penalized,
you'll play 4-on-4 Drone Soccer.
- Drone soccer? - Drone soccer?
(4-on-4 Drone Soccer)
2 teams of 4 players will compete to fly drones through the goalposts.
The team who gains 3 points 1st will win.
(They gain a point by flying a drone through the goalpost.)
(The team who gains 3 points 1st will win.)
The winners' names will be put on the Exempt roulette wheel,
and the losers' on the Penalty roulette wheel.
(Winners on the Exempt roulette, and losers on the Penalty roulette)
Please divide into 2 teams of 4.
- Young members should team up. - Right.
Are you sure you belong there?
(Haha is 40.)
When you said that, I wanted to go there too.
You're 40. Go away.
- Come here. - If you're in your 40s, go away.
- Come here. - This is not okay.
If you're in your 40s, come here.
It doesn't feel like I'm in my 40s.
You're in your 40s. If you're in your 50s, go away.
(If you're in your 50s, go away.)
(Seok Jin, you're in your 50s. Go away.)
- If you're in your 50s... - I'm alone on my team?
Shouldn't someone in his 50s be excluded?
(All the other members are in their 40s.)
He should be...
I'm alone?
So Min and Ji Hyo will play rock-paper-scissors...
- They'll choose their members. - and choose their members.
- Okay. - Okay.
Having flown a drone makes a big difference.
I fly drones as a hobby.
- I have one at home. - I didn't want to say this.
He's obsessed with drones.
(He's obsessed with drones.)
What? What was that?
You're very good at it.
- He's obsessed. - You're so good.
He's obsessed.
I am.
- I am obsessed. - Is that...
- It should be your nickname. - He's very good.
(Team members)
(So Min and Ji Hyo have chosen their team members.)
1st half and 2nd half?
I'll play in the first half.
Jong Kook and I seem to be the best players among us.
Be quiet.
- Let's do this. - Seriously.
I'll be Lee Seung Woo. You want to be Son Heung Min?
I'll be Jo Hyeon Woo. The goalkeeper.
Jo Hyeon Woo?
You should attack. I'll defend.
- Okay. I'll be Lee Seung Woo. - I'll be Jo Hyeon Woo.
Can you even control your drones?
Of course.
(We're on the national team at heart.)
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
- We can do this! - Here we go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Ready.
Win just three points.
(In case they fail to deliver the briefcase,)
(they have to aim to win this game.)
(The first half starts.)
That's so cool.
(Yang Hyeon Woo and Ha Seung Woo start to move.)
(Kwang Soo's drone moves forward.)
(Kwang Soo's drone approaches the goalpost.)
(This is not okay. I have to stop that.)
(Se Chan's drone comes back immediately.)
(Se Chan blocks Kwang Soo.)
I blocked him.
(This is how goalkeeper Yang Hyeon Woo plays.)
- I blocked him. - Good job.
Se Chan blocked Kwang Soo.
Good job.
(Se Chan, good job.)
- Way to go, Se Chan! - Defend!
Get it in!
(I won't let you make a goal.)
- Get it in! - Get it in!
(It's time to attack.)
Okay. Haha.
Get it in.
(Haha wins a goal with Se Chan's help.)
(Team So Min 1, Team Ji Hyo 0)
Good job!
(Let's make another goal.)
Goal! Okay!
(Se Chan makes the 2nd goal.)
One more.
(The 1st half ends 2 to 0.)
- Good job. - It wasn't bad.
- That was good. - You did a great job.
- It wasn't bad. - You did very well.
Why are you so bad?
- Show me how good you are. - Kwang Soo did well.
Show me.
(The players are switched.)
(Seok Jin and So Min versus Ji Hyo and Jae Seok.)
(Second half)
Higher!
Here we go!
(We need to make just one more goal.)
(Bumping)
(Seok Jin is lost from the beginning.)
(So Min is wandering too.)
Get in the right direction.
Get in the right direction first.
(The atmosphere is completely different from the first half.)
To the right. Okay. Higher!
Higher!
Go up!
(The drone is near the goalpost.)
Keep going. Okay!
(With Jae Seok's goal, the score is now 2 to 1.)
Just one more goal.
Ji Hyo, just one more goal!
Try again.
- Hold on! - Come here!
(Ji Hyo moves forward calmly.)
Turn it!
(Bumping)
(The drone bumps into the goalpost.)
Ji Hyo, lower it!
Move.
Lower it!
(Flying)
(It just passes by the goalpost?)
(Hitting)
(It hits So Min's head.)
So Min...
- Get it in! - It's in!
It's in.
(Thanks to So Min's header,)
(Ji Hyo scores an equalizer.)
- It's in! - It's in.
It's in.
(Team So Min 2, Team Ji Hyo 2)
It's a tie. Just one more goal!
- Go straight. - Hold on.
Seok Jin!
(Seok Jin's drone moves straight towards the goalpost.)
- Jae Seok, stop him! - Seok Jin!
(Will he be able to make a goal?)
Goal!
(Seok Jin scores the winning goal.)
(Seok Jin did it!)
- It's in. We win, right? - It's over.
- It's over. - We win.
- Seok Jin. - At the end...
Seok Jin.
- I scored the golden goal. - Golden goal.
I couldn't do anything.
(Too bad. We almost won.)
It was so close.
(Team Ji Hyo loses by a narrow margin.)
(Their names go on the Penalty roulette wheel.)
(Penalty, Exempt)
- What's this? - What's this?
We have to do a good job.
(Two drones?)
I'll do a good job this time.
I got it.
(Kwang Soo intercepts it.)
(Jae Seok might damage it again.)
Very good.
You did a good job.
What are you doing?
I wanted to catch it.
(They receive a new mission.)
- Street dance? - Street?
(Street dance?)
- Flying yoga? - Flying yoga?
You can choose between street dance and flying yoga.
You'll divide into 2 teams of 4.
I choose street dance.
- I don't like yoga. - I quit dancing.
(I choose flying yoga.)
Yoga?
The dance style I pursue is...
I choose yoga.
I pursue street dance.
Not strip dance?
(Not strip dance?)
- No. - Is it strip dance?
Are you sure it's street dance?
Is it strip dance or street dance?
- Street. - Street?
I don't even want to imagine Jae Seok strip-dancing.
(They move to their mission spots.)
Flying yoga isn't going to be easy.
- It's very difficult. - Have you done it?
- I've done it once. - Have you?
- Yes. - Have you really?
- It's not that. - That's cheating.
You're up-to-date.
I did it once for a show.
- How was it? - It was difficult.
Physically?
You are hardened, aren't you?
(He gets playful.)
- I'm very inflexible. - A long time ago...
What do you mean that I'm hardened?
Stretching is difficult.
At least you have muscles.
I worked out my legs yesterday.
Kwang Soo doesn't care about anything...
except seeing the yoga teacher.
(He came to see the yoga teacher.)
Okay.
That seems like it.
Is there a yoga teacher?
(He pretends not to know.)
Of course there is.
Why do you ask when you already know?
There aren't many male yoga teachers.
- They're always female. - Generally,
women teach yoga.
It won't be one of our guests...
who's teaching, right?
The worst case would be Park Na Rae.
- That's what I thought too. - Me too.
Na Rae taught pole dancing...
- before. - Right.
During a shoot.
She taught us with a seductive look.
It was uncomfortable.
That would be uncomfortable.
Okay.
We're here. What's that?
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They must succeed and get a hint.)
When it comes to yoga, there's a teacher.
My heart is fluttering.
(Who will be their yoga teacher?)
- Seriously. - It's true.
- Wait a minute. - Is someone hiding?
The teacher is hiding inside.
It's definitely Na Rae.
Her knees are protruding.
- Look. - The toes look strong.
The toes are clearly visible.
There's a person inside.
I'm leaving if it's Na Rae.
Na Rae isn't that tall.
- She's quite tall. - She is.
How long have you been in there?
She seems to be struggling. Shall we wait?
Is she shuddering?
Let her come out on her own.
- Who's there? - Are you the teacher?
Are you our teacher for today?
How can the teacher look so uncool?
(Who could it be?)
(He expected the teacher to look cool.)
- Teacher? - What are you doing?
Peek-a-boo. Hello.
(They welcome her.)
- Hello. - It's Yu Seung Ok.
- She's an actual teacher. - It's her.
- It's Yu Seung Ok. - Hello.
We get to see her in person.
(1 of the top 5 Asian bodybuilders, Yu Seung Ok)
We invited Yu Seung Ok for today's yoga class.
(It's nice to meet you.)
It's an honor.
I was going to stand near her. Why did you block me?
What do you mean?
- He pushed my shoulder. - It happened naturally.
- He took my place. - It just happened.
(A few minutes ago while setting up the camera)
(Pushing)
(He blocked him from her.)
(Kwang Soo took his place next to the instructor.)
Are you blocking me?
- Okay. - Seung Ok is tall.
They look good together.
That's why you blocked me.
(They laugh shyly.)
No, you can stand here.
No, you can stand there.
He blocked me.
- How tall are you? - I'm 172cm.
172cm?
- How old are you? - She seems as tall as you.
- I'm 29. - You're 29.
Our age difference is five years.
Really?
(Will they become a couple?)
Why do you ask that?
She has to introduce herself anyway.
She's our teacher.
Now that I see you in person...
(She talks to Kwang Soo.)
(Now that she sees him in person...)
(How do I look?)
You look very interesting.
(She's never seen a face like his.)
What about his face?
Doesn't he look like a cartoon character?
- His head... - I look interesting?
looks similar to that of a horse.
(His head seems like that of a horse.)
- I look like a horse? - No, he looks like a giraffe.
(Be more accurate.)
- He looks like a giraffe. - You know...
- His nose is long. - We just met. How can she say that?
- She's our teacher. - That's true.
- Okay. - She's our teacher, so just listen.
Seung Ok will explain the mission herself.
Here's your flying yoga mission for today.
Eight yoga positions of different levels...
are attached on the shoe throw board.
Each member throws their shoe and chooses a position.
If all members hold the position of their choice successfully,
the mission is cleared.
Once it's cleared, you're given a hint on the final location.
- It's difficult. - We must win.
- We'll succeed. - Definitely.
How do we do a chandelier?
- What's its level of difficulty? - Isn't it difficult?
(That position...)
That position looks very good.
- What I mean is... - It's not about the looks.
- I don't have to look good. - We just have to do it.
- It's not about the looks. - I don't have to look good.
How difficult is it?
- It's easier than the Da Vinci. - Is it easy?
- Yes. - Let's try it.
Monkey looks difficult.
Wouldn't you fall off if you have no bottom?
(By the way...)
(Kwang Soo will definitely fall off.)
- It has nothing to do with me. - If you have no bottom,
- It has nothing to do with me. - you'll fall.
- Kwang Soo is in trouble. - It has nothing to do with me.
That's possible.
I won't fall.
Each member will throw their shoe.
Here we go.
We have to succeed within six hours.
- Try to pick the butterfly. - All right, I'll go for that.
Butterfly?
There it goes.
(Jong Kook isn't good at throwing his shoe.)
(He gets the chandelier that's harder than the butterfly.)
He got the chandelier.
You'll break your back.
His shoe fell on the chandelier.
- Okay. - In one go?
She got it.
(Ji Hyo gets the monkey.)
Monkey is very easy.
Get something easy.
(Se Chan gets the crocodile.)
- What is it? - Crocodile?
(He gets an easy one.)
- You got it. - It's easy.
It's the easiest one.
Get the easy one.
It's butterfly.
- You got the butterfly. - Butterfly is good.
- I got the butterfly. - Butterfly is good.
- It's easy. - Based on your shoe throw,
you picked chandelier, monkey, crocodile,
- and butterfly. - That's great.
- Butterfly. - The positions are determined.
- You'll stretch with Seung Ok. - Before we start,
- we'll stretch. - Let's do that. It's important.
- It's important. - Sit down on the floor.
- Yes, we sit on the floor. - Okay.
- I should explain this first. - What is it?
(She almost forgot.)
- Were you confused? - No.
You seemed confused.
- There are two points. - Yes.
Put an imaginary dot in the middle.
An imaginary dot?
Then extend it to the bottom.
This is called the plumb line.
- Pardon? - Plumb line.
- "Plumb line"? - Plumb line.
Sit along the plumb line.
- Sit down? - On the floor?
- Do we sit there? - Right in the middle?
No, go back a little.
If possible, try to keep the knees straight and pretty.
(Keep the knees straight and pretty.)
Straighten the knees prettily.
Our teacher likes pretty things.
Like this?
(Do I look pretty?)
(She's satisfied.)
With your knees straight, grab the hammock.
Turn your wrist to make a knot.
(Do we do it like this?)
She's good at teaching.
Imagine that a ghost is pulling up your torso...
from the top.
(Seung Ok's special stretching)
As if a ghost is pulling us up?
How does that feel?
- A ghost is pulling us up? - But why a ghost?
Imagine that I'm pulling you up, Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Imagine that I'm pulling you. - Now I understand.
I understand now.
Toward the hand that's grabbing the knot,
stretch your body as far as possible.
Goodness.
- Like this? - Goodness.
(Stretching)
It's hard to do.
You must trust it.
Trust the hammock and stretch to the side as much as possible.
It's hard to trust when you've been on Running Man for a long time.
I'm sorry. It's an occupational disease.
Next is crossing the body.
- Cross? - Cross your feet.
(Cross your two feet.)
Put your right hand on the left side.
(While crossing your feet, put the right hand on the left.)
- Were you confused? - No.
- I'm certain. - No.
Wait, I'm not the only one who thought she hesitated.
- I'm not the only one, right? - No, put it on your left.
(She's flustered.)
(I'm getting angry.)
- She made a sound. - Is she angry?
Okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Put your right hand on the left.
Put your arm behind your head.
- Behind? - Yes.
- We can turn? - Stretch the side of your body.
- Can you twist your body? - Stretch farther.
- Wait, this is... - So that your body twists.
Is this correct, Seung Ok?
(It feels and looks strange. Is this correct?)
Yes, that's correct. And now...
- You look like you're flying. - Is this right?
You look like a rocket. It's correct.
(The position is correct.)
Exhale.
- It feels good. - Okay.
This position feels very good.
Come back to your original position.
- Again. - What about the other side?
- Now, take your elbow. - What about the other side?
(She continues without listening.)
- Take your elbow. - She just keeps going.
- He asked you a question. - She should take a look at us.
She does it alone. She's satisfied on her own.
Put your elbow on the floor.
- Then... - She doesn't listen.
She doesn't listen to us.
- She isn't listening. - Take a look at us.
What do we do about our legs?
I think my position is wrong.
- What should we do? - My hand hurts. What's wrong?
Tell us what we're doing wrong.
Don't the instructors usually fix our positions?
Let's do the other side.
Right, we're finally doing the other side.
Push your body toward the hammock.
- Like this? - Yes.
(Is this correct again?)
Is everyone correct?
Yes, that's right.
Don't look at me. Look toward the other side.
(Are you sure this is correct?)
I can't do it. Am I doing well?
My position seems wrong. Am I doing well?
- It's correct. - Is it right?
No, it isn't.
(I'm sorry.)
Can you tell me what's wrong?
Tell us if we're doing something wrong.
Are you feeling lazy?
(Suspicious)
- You look like a mermaid. - Me?
Yes.
(She finally fixes their positions.)
- A bit more... - Oh, my.
Oh, my.
There you go.
Try to stretch your side.
Jong Kook is doing very well.
I am? Thank you.
My side is stretching so much.
(The teacher goes back.)
- Seung Ok. - Yes?
Am I invisible to you?
(Why do you just pass me by?)
Why do you skip me?
I didn't mean to.
(Seung Ok tries to console him.)
Is your arm too long?
(Kwang Soo receives a private lesson too.)
Am I doing it right?
(He becomes suspicious again.)
(It's obvious that he's not doing it right.)
(He looks so interesting.)
Is this right?
Why?
(Why aren't you saying anything? Is this wrong?)
He's weird.
This guy is a bit weird.
(He's not just interesting anymore.)
I'm not weird.
How can you...
- Fix his position. - I'm following your instruction.
I need to focus.
(He's not weird.)
Is it normal that I can't breathe?
I need to focus.
- Is it normal that I can't breathe? - Stay there.
Right hand...
And then...
(Glancing)
Are you copying us?
- Why are you copying us? - Why are you looking at us?
- Seung Ok. - Seung Ok.
Hold on.
She did it wrong.
- Goodness. - Why are you copying us?
I did it wrong.
And then...
- She was confused? - Are we moving on?
Put your elbow down...
- Oh, this one... - This one is okay.
Are we skipping the other one?
We just did it.
What? We didn't.
We didn't do this one.
We skipped this one.
We did it.
(She's not listening.)
- We didn't! - We didn't!
We know we didn't!
We did it? We didn't!
We skipped it!
So what's your plan?
(Kwang Soo talks casually.)
Why do you talk that way to our teacher?
- What are you doing? - Give me a second.
We're done. Please get up.
(She doesn't listen to anyone.)
We're done?
We're getting up? We're done?
(So suddenly?)
Hold on. What's with her?
- We want an expert. - Seriously...
Trust me. I'll focus from now on.
You weren't focusing before?
You weren't?
Are we done stretching?
(Will the yoga class go all right?)
There's a dance studio here.
It looks nice. I didn't know it was here.
Street dance.
Dance, dance, dance.
Oh, my.
(Who is our teacher?)
(Who are today's dance teachers?)
- Hello. - Mmary.
J-black. J-pink.
(Mmary is the most popular dance queen these days.)
(Every dancer has heard of J-black.)
- Hello. - I'm your huge fan.
- Hi. - He dances in high heels, right?
- Hi. - Right?
He's incredible.
He is.
You two shot a hamburger commercial, right?
Yes. The one where she flies.
(These two soulful dancers...)
(turned into a human hamburger in the commercial.)
Yes. The one where she flies.
They run a hamburger store?
(Hold on.)
They shot a commercial.
- I'm just joking. - You see it very often.
- I'm just joking. - His jokes are weird.
Seriously...
By the way, J-black is good at fighting.
What?
I'm pretty good too.
(Is that so?)
I'm pretty good.
Why are these two here?
Please explain.
Today,
you'll learn to street-dance...
to a one-minute-long song.
You'll give a performance too.
- Where? - Where?
We'll give a performance? That's a problem.
- We're doomed. - We're doomed.
There's a condition.
You have to get every move right.
(Things get worse and worse.)
If you succeed,
you'll receive a hint about the delivery place.
I don't think we'll succeed.
- It's too difficult. - It's too difficult.
We'll fail.
- What should we do? - What should we do?
I don't think we can do it.
(Will they be able to win a hint?)
Where's our briefcase?
- Where's our briefcase? - Keep an eye on it.
Our briefcase.
- Why didn't you bring it here? - Our briefcase...
Hold on. Let me go find it.
This is why you shouldn't have left it with me.
(Seok Jin lost the briefcase again?)
Gosh. Our briefcase...
I completely forgot about it too.
Me too.
- Our briefcase... - I completely forgot.
It should be here.
(He returns to the previous location.)
It's there.
(Relieved)
It's left right here.
I haven't even danced yet, and I'm already tired.
(He uses all his energy to find the briefcase.)
If we lose the briefcase, there's no point in shooting this.
Guys.
- Did you find it? - What a relief.
You shouldn't have left it with me.
Don't lose it again.
Don't you remember?
I even lost my baby on his first birthday.
(Don't you remember?)
- On his first birthday. - It's true.
It could have been bad.
- All right. - This is our mission.
Please don't make it too hard.
- Please consider our skills. - Don't worry.
(What kind of dance will they learn?)
We're complete beginners.
(It's a famous song.)
This song is too good for us.
We couldn't dance to this.
(Mission Song: "Treasure" by Bruno Mars)
(The two teachers start to warm up.)
Look at her face.
(Are you ready, honey?)
We can't do that.
(Part 1: Powerful beats and waves)
I can't do the waves.
(Sassy)
Look at her face.
She looks so relaxed.
(Even their facial expressions are phenomenal.)
We can't...
(Part 2: Quick steps and couple dance)
(Fancy)
- We can't do that. - How are we going to do that?
We can't do that.
(Part 2 looks more difficult than Part 1.)
(In addition to the quick steps, they have to act too.)
We can never do that.
(Part 3: The male dancer's difficult, solo dance)
(Relaxed)
- I mean... - We can never do that.
It's too fast.
- Are you kidding us? - We can't do that.
We can't...
This is what only pop singers can do.
(Part 4: Making circles)
What is this?
I can't believe it.
(Good job, my treasure.)
(The couple's acting plays an important part.)
It's what suits the teachers' levels.
Even the facial expressions are hard.
- You're just bragging, aren't you? - Exactly.
(The demonstration is over.)
This is...
How are we going to do this?
- I'm more worried about... - It's too difficult.
your facial expressions than the moves.
Just by imagining it...
(You can already picture Jae Seok's facial expressions.)
It'll be terrible.
We can never do this.
It might look difficult now,
- but it's easier than you think. - I don't think so.
- You can do it. - No.
To speed things up...
- You want to know our levels. - Yes.
- If you show us, we'll adjust. - Okay.
We want each of you to dance briefly.
- Let's do it briefly. - I'm not good at these things.
You'll dance one by one.
Let us warm up first.
What are you talking about?
Gosh.
I'm getting competitive.
- Let's start. - Let's just start right away.
(How good are they?)
We should get into the rhythm.
I'm so embarrassed.
We don't usually dance to this kind of songs.
- Haha is a good dancer. - Haha. There you go.
(The ace, Haha, goes first.)
That's so cool!
Gosh.
He's good.
He's so cool.
Gosh. I wish I could dance like him.
He's so good.
(Sexy)
(Haha is challenging the teachers.)
This wasn't embarrassing.
So Min. She's good too.
So Min is good.
(Bouncing)
Here it comes.
(She shows off her charms.)
She's so cute.
- So Min is good. - So Min is good.
- Is it my turn? - Yes.
(Wriggling)
(That's getting too old.)
There's something he does when he's desperate.
(His specialty)
Stop it!
(The teachers now know.)
Oh, my.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin is the last one.)
He has his own style.
(They're looking forward.)
Here it comes.
That's Lim Ha Ryong.
(His dance is old-fashioned.)
- Lim Ha Ryong. - Ricky Martin.
(Worried)
His dance is...
Go right.
(I'm doing well, right?)
Go left.
That's all we can show you.
- But seriously, - yes?
your sense of rhythm...
- You all have it. - You all have it.
We can do that much.
What are you talking about?
(Shameless)
We can do that much.
We have a sense of rhythm.
- That's all you need. - We do.
You can definitely do it.
We'll make the dance a bit easier.
I think we can do that.
- It'd be a miracle. - You'll be surprised.
1 of you 3...
- should be a woman. - A woman.
I think these guys...
1 of the 3 men should play the female role.
The men's part is a lot more difficult.
So I think...
(The teacher has an idea.)
Jae Seok and Haha should do the men's part.
- Us? - Because you have experience.
- You'll be a woman then. - What?
No way.
I don't like him already.
- It'll be terrible. - You'll do it.
Can we learn it quickly?
- I can't do it. - I know.
Seriously.
I'll make magic happen.
Magic? Okay, let's give it a try.
(Their official lesson starts.)
Let's take it slow and start.
Relax your arm...
and hit the side three times.
Slowly. 7, 8.
(They break the beat first.)
That's right. You just did it.
(The two women...)
(as well as the two men are doing a good job.)
That's right. Now, you called it a wave,
but you're just making it look like a wave.
(Seok Jin isn't good at waves.)
Here,
pull the arm toward you and lean back.
Lower your body, and that makes one wave.
How did he do it? I can't do it consecutively.
Let's try it slowly.
From the top, seven, go.
(Number 1, hit the beat)
(Number 2, wave)
Then turn around.
- You have a good sense of rhythm. - You're very good.
Let's say that you turned around.
- Are you teasing us? - Seriously?
They're both teasing us.
You dance very well.
- You're good. - You really are.
How about this?
We also prepared movements that are easier.
You can do this part, so let's keep it.
- I can't do it. - Then...
turn around.
Come back to where you were and jump.
Okay.
(He keeps the transition simple.)
That's great.
Yes, that's good.
Please make it simple.
He has easy moves for people who aren't good.
This is the woman's part.
I have to learn the man's part.
- You're a woman. - You're a woman, So Min.
You're a woman, aren't you?
(Aren't you a woman?)
- You're a woman. - Am I?
The two of you are women.
- Me and Seok Jin? - Yes.
- Yes, we are women. - Both of you are women.
So Min, you're the most popular here.
(You're more popular than him.)
- Everyone wants to dance with you. - All of you are married.
- All of them are married. - The women's part is...
(He's jealous of So Min.)
Here's the woman's part. After the jump,
turn away from your partner and act like a prude.
Then look at the male partner.
Act like a prude.
I've never been a prude.
I hate imagining Seok Jin as a prude.
- I've never been a prude. - I don't want to do this.
You complain a lot.
I've never been a prude in my life.
Just do it. You have to learn it.
- Start from the top, 7, 8. - 8.
(They repeat.)
(Act like a prude after the beat and do a wave.)
1, 2, 3, jump.
- Turn away and look at the partner. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
Turn away and look at the partner.
(He follows the instructor.)
- What? - Let's repeat the step.
1, 2, 3, 2, 2, 3. It's three steps each.
(Quick-step couple dance)
It goes like this.
(The second part becomes harder.)
- No, we can't do it so quickly. - We can't do it.
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3.
- This is good enough. - That's the woman's part.
That's the woman's part.
The men's part is different.
What's the original dance?
Originally...
(They move quickly.)
Then the man sits down.
Can you do it slowly?
Goodness.
This is when you sit down.
You're starting to show off again.
(You're starting to show off again.)
You're showing off now that you can do it.
You can't stay in the back, can you?
There you go again.
You come to the front to show off.
- Right. - Slowly.
(His swag is exploding.)
- There he goes again. - Okay.
- This is why he shouldn't be here. - He can't do that.
I love it.
He's so annoying.
We need Ji Hyo here.
He's really annoying.
He's starting to show off again.
Watch me for the woman's part.
This part is key.
This is important.
You have to move the hips lightly.
Move the hips and make it look pretty.
- This is so terrible. - That's correct.
I almost kicked him.
(I almost kicked him.)
Can we kick someone once?
- Just once. - Can we kick someone once?
Please allow us to do that.
- Let us kick each other just once. - Just once.
- Right here. - We get one kick.
- We get to kick someone once. - Kick someone who's annoying.
Just once.
- Let's do it. - Promise...
- Everyone gets a turn. - that you won't get upset.
- Kick someone who's annoying. - Seriously.
1, 2, 3.
We can kick someone once.
After this,
take one more step forward...
- and wait. - You approach...
- and grab the shoulder. - When he grabs your shoulder,
push him off like this.
Gosh.
She's acting irritated even though she likes it.
- Come on, you like it. - Gosh.
"Come on, you like it."
(He gets into it immediately.)
You and I would make a good pair.
Gosh, come on.
(He gets too into it.)
(Kicking)
Gosh, that hurt.
- You kicked once. - He took his turn.
(One kick allows people to release their anger.)
He was so annoying.
In this part...
(It's the third part.)
the music goes like this.
Then...
drag your opposite leg.
Take three steps.
- He looks good doing it. - The women's part is the same.
- It's the same. - Did you hurt your leg?
(Did you hurt your leg?)
(What do you mean?)
Did you hurt your leg?
I'm dancing right now.
I thought you were bleeding.
(He was only doing what he learned.)
- Seriously. - Let's change his foot.
I thought his right foot was bleeding.
(The one without any injured leg...)
- In this part... - I'm good at this move.
Dragging the foot.
- Haha looks amazing. - No way.
- He does. - He's detailed.
- No. - You're amazing.
(Am I that amazing?)
Look at the hat.
(When he wears his hat differently...)
Whenever I praise him, he wears his hat like that.
He failed when he tried to copy H.O.T.
- Then he failed. - That's right.
(It's a sad memory.)
(He tried to copy H.O.T.)
(He goes out of the frame in 1 second.)
(It's a sad story.)
That's what you do.
(That's what happens to people who show off.)
(He's crying.)
The dance is amazing.
I can't do it anymore.
Dance it your way.
That's what I like.
(Will they clear their dance mission?)
This is the real flying yoga.
(How is the yoga team doing?)
Put your right ankle on the hammock.
Then lean forward.
Keep the left heel on the ground.
(They follow the instructions without a problem.)
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. It hurts a lot.
(He can't understand them.)
Push, instead of pulling.
- Push? - Yes.
(She pushes slightly.)
(He spins.)
(He spins in the air.)
(This isn't right.)
I don't think this is right.
(He spins the other way.)
(Is this really correct?)
- No, you shouldn't spin. - Okay.
What do you mean you don't think it's right?
I must concentrate.
Put it on the hammock and keep the knee straight.
(She concentrates and teaches him again.)
Hold your pelvis still.
Lean forward.
Go forward.
(Why isn't it working?)
He can't do it.
What are they doing?
What are you doing?
(It's a passionate and dynamic turn.)
(A teacher inexperienced with variety shows and her student...)
(have a passionate and thrilling connection.)
What are you doing?
Are you dating or something?
(It's not what you think it is.)
- I give up on you. - I can't do it.
Do you give up on me?
(She gives up after trying once.)
Teach him how to do it.
What?
How can she give up on her student so easily?
I can't do it.
How can she give up after 1 or 2 attempts?
That's right.
Ji Hyo is good.
You're flexible, Ji Hyo.
If it's possible for you,
- take the heel off the ground. - Like this?
Is that better?
You look good together.
- Like this? - Yes.
Thank you.
- Now... - Shall we do the other side?
- Are we doing the other side? - Are we?
Lean forward.
(Put the other ankle on the hammock and push forward.)
If it's possible for you...
(He turns the other way.)
- I can't do it. - What's going on?
- It's strange. - I keep turning.
It's very strange.
(What's the problem?)
Is the ceiling too high?
- I know why. - Why?
It needs to be higher.
(He tries again with the hammock higher.)
Keep your feet strong.
It feels really good.
Don't go to the side. Push forward.
(Turning)
(His body keeps turning.)
Hey, what are you doing?
- What are you two doing? - Of course I turn.
Pulling the hammock makes me turn.
No, your body is strange.
(It's not my fault.)
My body is strange?
What do you mean?
Seriously.
Your body is strange indeed.
- My body is strange? - You're hurting his feelings.
The teacher is hurting his feelings.
Can you teach him?
- Him? - Where are you going?
Teach him? His body is strange.
Put your leg on it.
Put your ankle on the hammock. That's right.
Keep the leg straight.
Hold still.
Straighten the leg and push forward.
Go straight.
That's right. Go straight.
(What's going on?)
- Does it work or not? - It works because you force me.
(It's the power of teaching by force.)
(Even his strange body becomes the ideal body.)
Let go. Please let go of me.
Let go of my left side.
- Jong Kook! Ouch, it hurts. - You have to do this.
- It works, right? - It works.
- That's right. - It works.
A teacher needs strength.
He can do it.
(His mind and body are bruised.)
Good. The stretching is done.
Okay.
(After many accidents, the stretching is finally done.)
It works. It's refreshing.
- It's refreshing, right? - I am sweating.
It's refreshing.
Now, I will teach you...
- the crocodile pose. - Okay.
- It's the easiest pose, right? - Yes.
- Let's put one leg on the hammock. - All right.
(They must complete the 4 poses to receive a hint.)
(Crocodile pose involves stretching with one leg on the hammock.)
Then stretch.
- Do we stretch? - Stretch.
- Stretch. - A little at a time.
If you can do the dove pose,
- move onto it. - The dove pose is nice.
It's nice.
If you can't do it, support yourself on your knee.
My knee doesn't touch the floor.
(I want to do it,)
(but my knee doesn't touch the floor.)
His knee doesn't touch the floor.
- He is in the air. - I can't do it.
My knee doesn't touch the floor.
Really?
(His body is strange as well.)
The hammock should be longer.
Then Kwang Soo and I should change places.
Really?
I am in the air.
- This isn't my size. - You are right.
It's too high up in the air.
- It's very high. - Look at me.
Look at me. It works now.
It should have been this way from the start. It works.
- Put your leg on it. - It's too high.
She must have made it short for Kwang Soo.
(Struggling)
(My knee doesn't touch the floor either.)
(He shows off his strange body.)
This hammock is strange.
I don't know.
(He is the tallest, but his legs are the shortest.)
Straighten out this leg and go down.
- There you go. - Put your knee on the floor.
- There you go. - Good.
- Am I doing it right? - Nice.
(Good. Nice.)
What was that? What was that?
Is that a popular phrase?
It sounds like she is being sarcastic.
No, you did well.
- Really? Thank you. - Do this.
- This? - Yes.
- This is the pose. You succeeded. - Okay.
We succeeded.
- This is the butterfly pose. - It's what you showed us first.
Move your buttocks up and down and put them on the hammock.
- Up and down? - Move your buttocks up and down.
Now, pull the fabric toward you.
- Like this? - We pull the end.
- After you do that, - Do we bring it forward?
- insert one foot. - What?
Where do you insert one foot?
- Does it go in? - Yes.
Push it in. Did you do it?
Yes, I did.
My feet are big.
(Struggling)
Kwang Soo, you got on the hammock without distributing the fabric.
How am I supposed to do that?
Distribute the fabric, you jerk.
(Listen to your teacher.)
Why are you so greedy?
Didn't you learn mathematics?
Excuse me.
(Kicking)
(What? "Didn't you learn mathematics?")
You always add a comment when the older members are talking.
All right. I only made one comment!
- I am sorry. - You ignored the basic.
(Thank you for assisting me.)
Sit down...
and insert one foot.
- One foot? - Yes.
- Hold the hammock. - Insert that foot.
- Insert that foot. - He did it right.
(Kicking)
- He did it right! - Insert that foot.
- I did it. - You did it right.
I got it. Okay, okay.
- Please help me. - Since Kwang Soo is struggling,
we should hurry up.
- What? - Insert your foot over here.
That's right. Did you get to this step?
I can't see anything.
(They can't see the outside.)
Your left foot goes in here.
Next... Watch carefully.
(Here comes the next step.)
- What? - We can't see anything.
- We can't see anything. - We can't see anything.
It's impossible to watch.
I can't see anything.
- You inserted your feet, right? - Is there a mirror?
Now, grab the top of the hammock and stand up like this.
- How pretty! - How do you do that?
Do I split my legs?
Like this?
- Yes. - I did it.
- Do I stand up? - Don't pull out your legs.
Now, grab the top of the hammock and stand up like this.
- How pretty! - How do you do that?
Do I split my legs?
Like this?
- Yes. - I did it.
- Do I stand up? - Don't pull out your legs.
(He manages to stand up.)
(What?)
- Isn't this it? - Isn't this it?
Hold on.
Is it okay to have my head touch the ceiling?
(Is it okay to have my head touch the ceiling?)
My goodness.
It's okay, right? It's not dangerous, right?
Hold on. How did it happen that way?
This is incredible.
(It's a unique sight for even a yoga teacher.)
- It's not an easy pose. - This is nice.
I thought it would be easy.
Now, bring your feet together and sit down.
(Bring your feet together and sit down in the hammock.)
It's hard.
(Does she want us to sit down?)
(After saying that it's hard, he sits down perfectly.)
It's a butterfly.
(It's the shape of a butterfly.)
- It's comfy. - It's comfy inside the hammock.
Close the opening.
It's like, "Young Gu isn't here."
(The butterfly pose is a success, right?)
- Like this? - Do we come out like this?
Close the opening.
1, 2, 3. Peek-a-boo.
(Open the hammock and say, "Peek-a-boo" to succeed.)
- What are you doing? - "Peek-a-boo"?
- "Peek-a-boo"? - We aren't in kindergarten.
It's a mission. Peek-a-boo.
(You have to do this to succeed.)
- Is this the butterfly pose? - Yes.
- Peek-a-boo. - Peek-a-boo.
How cute.
- For the monkey pose, - The monkey pose is hard.
your feet point outward.
- Outward. - After that,
lean back...
and spread your legs.
Like this.
(Turning)
(This is easy.)
- Jong Kook is good. - This is the monkey pose.
Spread your arms and this is the monkey pose. It's easy, right?
It's easy.
- Good. - It's easy.
It's really refreshing.
(This pose is easy and refreshing.)
- Put your arms down. - It hurts.
Put your feet down.
(Screaming)
(She steps on Kwang Soo's fingers.)
(I think my fingers broke.)
I think my fingers broke.
(I need to concentrate.)
I am sorry. I didn't do it on purpose.
It's okay.
- I think you did it on purpose. - I'm okay.
- I am sorry. - Okay.
- You succeeded. - Okay.
- Next is the chandelier pose. - The chandelier pose.
Let's wrap this up cleanly.
Okay. We have one pose left.
Let's do the last pose successfully.
Let's go. Let's go.
(He flips over to stretch his body.)
Are you okay?
(He is amazing.)
Don't you feel dizzy?
It's okay.
Jong Kook might set this up at home.
- He likes it so much. - I could do it at home.
- It's nice. - Since Jong Kook lives alone,
he can do this naked.
(Since Jong Kook lives alone, he can do this naked.)
- Are you out of your mind? - Naked!
You live alone.
It will be more comfortable.
- Shall we go? - Shall we go?
Lean back and do the monkey pose...
you learned earlier.
So that you don't move, balance yourself...
with your hands.
So that you don't get dizzy, put your hands on the floor and...
Kwang Soo. My goodness.
(They make an unexpected eye contact.)
- What? - It's embarrassing.
- What? - You shouldn't be embarrassed.
Face forward.
I need to watch you to copy the pose.
I need to look at you to copy the pose.
- Okay. - Now,
untangle one leg and bring it backward.
- Backward? - I did it.
- I can't do it. - I grabbed my ankle.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo succeed in one go.)
Bring it backward as much as you can.
I feel nauseous.
(Se Chan succeeds as well.)
Kwang Soo, that's wrong.
- My goodness. - Hold on.
Put your feet on the hammock. No, no. You are doing it wrong.
Bring it to the side and then back.
- Kwang Soo's face turned red. - Please.
- Good. - My goodness.
(That's good.)
- This is it. Yes. - Did I get it?
- Okay. - Did you get it?
- Yes. - You succeeded.
Yes!
(Success)
(Let's see what their hint is.)
- This is... - My goodness.
I feel dizzy.
You succeeded.
(We thank Seung Ok for teaching the challenged students.)
Men's part and women's part.
The dance routine becomes different for men and women.
- It becomes different. - Yes, the men's part is like this.
(Part 3: Challenging men's part)
Like this.
You two are so good.
They're so good.
They're good dancers.
This is the women's part.
While men do that move,
your right shoulder comes forward twice.
1, 2.
Pretend like you're whining.
One...
I'm never whiny.
Start.
1, 2. 1, 2.
So Min is good.
- Then move your hip to the right. - He makes me look better.
- 1, 2, 3. - I can't do this.
Start.
1, 2.
Right, left.
(He moves awkwardly.)
I think Seok Jin needs to pee.
No, it goes like this.
(I learned to dance like a pretty woman.)
Right, left.
(Like this.)
I can't do it.
(Kicking)
(Stop doing that, Ms. Jee.)
He did it wrong.
(Was I that bad?)
I can't do it.
(Twitching)
Are you all right?
- I'm all right. - "Are you all right?"
That's funny.
Get close again.
Right.
It's more powerful this time.
- It's more powerful. - You try to hug her,
and she goes forward.
She's running away.
(When the man comes close, the woman moves away.)
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Why are you doing it to her?
Hey.
- Let go. - I'm standing next to you.
- Why are you doing it there? - What's wrong with you?
Do it here.
What are you doing?
Why? Try it. Hey.
Do it.
Do it here.
I need to practice too. Who am I supposed to practice with?
We should be allowed to dance with whomever we want.
I think we are set.
- What are you doing? - Let's get it started already.
There's one difficult part left.
There's one difficult part left. It's done after this.
Yes, it's done.
(Part 4: Drawing a final circle)
(This dance is done by pop artists.)
- From the top. - I'm impatient.
Bow your head first,
jump,
and as you land,
slide.
From here, draw a circle with your left foot...
and finish off with your right foot.
(Slide with one foot first and form a circle with the other foot.)
This...
is the first part.
(There you go.)
(This is difficult, but she's doing pretty well.)
That's how you finish.
This is fast.
It's kind of fast. The middle part is fast.
How do you jump from here?
Is it this?
I got it. Like this.
(Haha gets it right away as well.)
Why does my left foot move first?
Like this.
(Unlike the other two, he's having a hard time.)
(I can't believe he's my partner.)
This is over for me.
It's not good enough for only you two to pass.
- Do we all have to get it right? - Of course.
Obviously.
So teach me.
(The last-minute special lesson begins.)
I can't do the next part.
Lean back,
switch your feet and lean again.
(They have no time, so they have to complete the mission fast.)
(Time keeps on passing by.)
You do it right away.
- Is it right away? - Yes.
(Sweating)
(Practice is the only way.)
(They keep practicing the difficult part.)
Like this.
(Will they successfully complete the street dance mission?)
- The timing is confusing. - It's confusing.
Let's get started.
Oh, gosh.
(They've already changed.)
You should have stayed home, Ms. Jee. Why are you here?
Why are you saying that?
Gosh, Seok Jin.
(How do I look?)
You look like Kim Kyung Ho.
(You look beautiful, Ms. Jee.)
Let's go.
Cue the music.
(They have to keep dancing until the instructors are satisfied.)
(How will their first try go?)
- Cue the music. - I'm Bruno Mars.
(The intro is freestyle dance.)
Gosh, you scared me.
(Gosh, you scared me.)
I'm going to be serious.
(Part 1: Dancing with the beat and body wave)
(Ms. Jee does the wave too.)
(They're coy.)
(Part 1 is good.)
(Part 2: Quick-step couple dance)
(The couple dance is perfect as well.)
(Cheering)
(Part 3: Challenging men's part)
(They do it perfectly.)
(Ms. Jee does it perfectly up to Part 3 as well.)
(This is the most difficult Part 4.)
(Startled)
(The ace couple...)
(and the one-sided lovers...)
(do a lovely finale.)
(They are full of street dance soul until the end.)
(Great job.)
I wasn't sure if I should express my emotions or act normal on TV.
(Goodness)
I had a huge dilemma.
I almost elbowed him.
- Goodness. - Hey.
When he was going back and forth,
he blew out of his nostrils so hard.
(That makes it worse.)
(It's difficult to dance with a guy who has a big nose.)
That was so much carbon dioxide.
I think dancing is about confidence.
- I agree. - You need to be confident.
- I'm confident now. - You're doing very well.
I can do this.
Back and back.
"Back and back".
(Sliding)
(The battle of confidence starts all of a sudden.)
I'm going to keep thinking about this.
(What are you guys doing?)
(I can't stop moving. I love to dance.)
(Weren't we good?)
You did very well,
but you got one move wrong,
- Seok Jin. - Did I?
- Did I? - Yes, you did.
(First attempt a moment ago)
(Creaking)
This time,
let's not stand around.
Let's start far away...
- and come together. - That's a good setup.
(He's looking forward to it.)
- It's like going clubbing. - That's so true.
He's already into it.
(He's already in the club.)
(Seok Jin is going to the bathroom.)
Where is he going?
Okay, let's get started.
He locked it.
Open the door, sir.
There's nobody to hold you.
It's okay. I'll do it by myself.
- Sir. - I'll do it by myself.
- I'll do it by myself. - I think this will look great.
Hurry. You two, go to the front. I can do it by myself.
- Sir? - Cue the music.
(Ms. Jee gets isolated, and the club version starts.)
Cue the music.
(Three young people's romance in the club)
Sir!
(They can't focus.)
I left something in there.
I left my phone.
(The club is getting heated up regardless.)
(Knocking)
(Are you here by yourself, lady?)
(Excuse me.)
(What?)
That sounds fun.
- Open the door. - This looks great.
(Why do they look better with one less person?)
I think this might look better.
(She's the only lady, and she's excited.)
(They're absorbed in the story until the end.)
This looks great.
Sir.
(Playing hard-to-get amongst three people)
- I paid the admission fee. - This is good.
That was great.
Hey, what was that? You left me out.
That was practice.
- Great job. - We have to practice together.
We were just practicing.
Why does everybody look happy?
(There's no end to this love quarrel.)
- The atmosphere was great. - Was it?
You looked great.
I felt like I was watching a musical.
You're all naturals.
- Let's try it again. - Okay.
(There's no more practice. It's time for the test again.)
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go. - Let's go.
(Let's take this seriously.)
(So their first of many tries begins.)
I got it wrong.
(I got it wrong.)
(People who were good start making mistakes in easy parts.)
Oh, dear. I missed it.
(They are almost at the end.)
Why are you touching my legs?
What are you doing?
This is going to be on TV.
Why did you touch my legs?
(Can they complete this mission?)
- We'll try again. - Yes, one more time.
- We'll do it until we get it. - This time,
- make sexy faces. - Faces.
I'm also Yuruno Mars.
Yuruno Mars.
(There are two hours left. They don't have time to waste.)
(Can they get it this time?)
Cue the music.
(This is freestyle dance.)
(They're enjoying it too.)
(They dance in unison.)
(Part 1 is a success.)
(Part 2: Quick-step couple dance)
(Both couples are lovely, and it's perfect.)
(The challenging men's part is also great.)
(They're almost there.)
(They have to draw a circle which Seok Jin struggled with before.)
(This time,)
(he does it easily.)
(Great. Nice.)
Nice.
(It's time for the couple's finale.)
(Please let us succeed.)
(They're pleased and satisfied.)
(They keep dancing.)
(My body won't stop moving.)
(The performance is over.)
Great job.
How was it?
(His heart is pounding.)
You had little time, but you did so well.
I'm serious.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The dance mission is a huge success.)
Thank you for joining us, J-black and Mmary.
- We'd like to thank you. - Thank you very much.
It was great.
Thank you.
- Great job. - They were perfect teachers.
Great job.
(They obtain a hint.)
(Here are the 3 hints put together.)
(161 Mokdongseo Avenue, Yangcheon District, Seoul)
- Do we vote? - Yes.
You have to exempt a person excluding yourself.
So Min.
I mean it.
Can't you write your own name?
I have to write somebody's name, right?
I'm heartbroken that I have to write somebody's name.
- This is a huge dilemma. - I'm done.
(Both teams finish voting.)
I'm worried.
Did you have a good time?
- Yes. - Yes.
161 Mokdongseo Avenue, Yangcheon District.
161 Mokdongseo Avenue.
(They have to deliver the briefcase...)
(to this address.)
Where did the briefcase go again?
- The briefcase. - Please.
- Can we give it to somebody else? - What's wrong with you, Seok Jin?
He lost it earlier too. Gosh, Seok Jin.
This is driving me nuts.
I should tie the briefcase to my body.
(If you're not smart, your body has to pay for it.)
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
Here it is. What a relief.
Nobody took it. I'm relieved.
(He was scared to death.)
Can we do a prank on Seok Jin?
Should we hide the briefcase?
We can try doing a prank on him,
- but it won't affect him. - That's true.
What should we hide?
Don't you remember he forgot about his son?
Somebody else should take this. This won't do.
Give it to me.
- I'll take it. - This is the baton.
You can't take care of it.
He doesn't care about anything but his own.
You have 1.5 hours left.
- That's it? - Right. It was six hours.
- We have to hurry. - I didn't know.
This is the last round.
(This is the last round to earn hints.)
Is this it?
(Why is a song playing all of a sudden?)
- Is this rap? - What's that? You scared me.
(You scared me.)
Jackson. Jackson.
Jin Young. Hello.
(GOT7 is back with their 3rd album, "Lullaby".)
(They are not boys anymore. They are men.)
You scared me.
Please say hi, GOT7.
- All right. - 2, 3.
- Come and get it. GOT7. Hello. - GOT7. Hello.
That was great.
That was much better.
It looks like GOT7...
was here in 2016.
- That was two years ago. - Right.
- It was for the Mark Menu. - Right. Mark.
We also had them during the summer at the train station.
That's right.
- We ripped name tags. - That's right.
- They were strong. - I remember.
I don't know what we're doing today,
but I'm getting nervous about facing GOT7.
- They're very competitive. - I know.
They're competitive.
- They didn't go easy. - They didn't at all.
What are we doing with GOT7 today?
The final mission is...
(Running Man has to win 2 out of 3 games to get the final hint.)
Out of the three games we have,
the team that wins 2 of them 1st takes the victory.
(Can they beat GOT7 and take the hint?)
I want to win.
Of course.
(They get more competitive because they're facing GOT7.)
(So Min is the only one who wants their attention.)
- Do you like them, So Min? - No, Jong Kook.
- She's blushing. - No.
Why would you say that? What's wrong?
Please.
- I'm sick of this. - Goodness.
- You're much older than them. - That's not why.
We've never had seven male guests before.
(It feels like there's a rainbow in my heart.)
Gosh...
I don't know where to look.
Look at the cameras.
What were you looking at? Look at the cameras.
She keeps on running her fingers through her hair.
So Min, your ears will bleed.
(If you keep doing that, your ears will bleed.)
Why do you keep doing that?
Gosh, So Min.
(Mini Long Jump)
Three people from each team will play.
You must grab your big toes with your hands,
and the person who jumps the farthest wins.
(You must grab your big toes and jump the farthest to win.)
- So Min is the frog. - The frog.
- Let's get it. - So Min has really long toes.
I have really long toes. I can do a thumbs up.
(Thumbs up)
I hate how she was trying to be appealing.
(He's being honest.)
I hate how this is supposed to be appealing.
Ready...
(How far can she jump while holding onto her toes?)
Set, go.
(Collapsing)
Try again, So Min.
(She tried to look pretty in front of the 7 guys.)
- Try again, So Min. - Should I?
- What was that? - Try again.
Hey, what are you doing in front of GOT7?
- No... - She's a frog.
- That wasn't intentional. - They're laughing.
- Don't fool around. - Be serious.
Hey, GOT7 is watching.
So Min, the back of your ears are red.
- Stop doing that. - You'll get an infection.
You'll get an infection.
You'll scrape it.
- Okay. - Give her one last chance.
1, 2, 3.
Ribbit. Okay.
(She gets herself together.)
(It's the same as before.)
You can't jump.
This is not bad, So Min. You're in first place.
(So Min jumps 8cm.)
- Yu Gyeom is next. - Okay.
You have to hold your big toes properly.
- This is his first time playing. - Right.
- Will you be okay? - I'll try it.
- He'll be fine. - You can do it. This is simple.
- One, - I'll try it.
2, 3.
(He grabs his big toes.)
(He does a somersault.)
If we did that, we would've reached the end.
Why are you doing acrobatics?
Is he Kwang Soo of GOT7?
- You're right. - He's...
dirty.
- Their hairstyles are similar. - That's true.
- He's Kwang Soo. - I live in the same apartment.
- Really? - Really?
You're similar.
They're pretty similar.
- Really? - They're similar.
(They do look alike the more you look at them.)
- You two look alike, - Yu Gyeom is handsome.
- but you look much better. - Thank you.
- No. - No, he doesn't.
- Kwang Soo is not handsome. - He looks funny.
You are in the same category, but you are much more handsome.
No, he just doesn't look bad.
(He just doesn't look bad.)
(This always happens when a guest looks like him.)
I'll try again.
Ready...
This is really hard.
This is hard.
Your feet don't come off the ground.
1, 2, 3.
(He jumps high...)
(and lands very close.)
Okay.
- He's similar to So Min. - Good job.
- He's similar. - It's 11cm.
(Yu Gyeom jumps 11cm.)
Okay. Young Jae.
Good.
- He got 22cm. - That's a lot.
- 1, 2, 3. - Great job.
(Se Chan jumps 30cm.)
- 30cm. - Great job.
(That was farther than they thought.)
- Next is... - Shall I go?
Okay, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. He's always good. - Go.
- He's good at everything. - Dream team.
- Jong Kook. - Start.
I can already tell that he's going to jump far.
It'll be over.
I'll go.
He's good at everything.
(A tiger jumps on its prey.)
(He hops...)
(and hunts the prey.)
- He did it. - 32cm.
I respect him.
(He's so shocked that he chokes.)
Jong Kook, that was 32cm.
You looked so cute.
- That was a hop. - You jumped lightly.
- This is the last one. - Jackson.
- Jackson is the last person. - Will he become the hero?
(Let's go, Jackson.)
(Sighing)
I'm sorry.
(He lets out a big sigh.)
What was that?
(Why are you saying what's on your heart?)
- I... - I understand.
- I know. - But you can't do that.
It's okay.
- He wasn't ready yet. - It's okay.
(He calms down...)
(and grabs his big toes.)
(I'm going to beat Jong Kook.)
(Goodness)
He did it.
(That was on another level.)
(What's the new record?)
He won.
It's 57cm.
(It's 57cm.)
Did we win? Did we?
(Running Man versus GOT7, first game)
(GOT7 wins Mini Long Jump.)
- Good job, Jackson. - Great job.
- Jackson. - He jumped so well.
Jong Kook, what if you do a regular long jump?
- What? - Do a regular one.
A regular one? But this...
No, just a regular one.
- But this... - Jong Kook.
Jong Kook...
can't accept what happened.
- I'm not good at long jumping. - Do a regular long jump.
Why don't you try it?
- I think he's good. - I can jump really far.
- Really? - Try it.
- From standing? - Standing long jump?
(Look at that.)
You're really good.
Did you see his face after he jumped?
After he jumped...
(He stared at you.)
He was only looking at you.
- You. - There were laser beams.
(He jumped far and then...)
(Are you watching, Jong Kook?)
He was only looking at you.
(I'll face you.)
(This is Jong Kook.)
He won.
(He got a bit farther.)
(He disappeared from the camera.)
He won.
- Jong Kook! - You won.
You did it.
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
- What's the matter, Jackson? - Did I win?
We need to be accurate. Let's be precise.
- I don't need the microphone. - Stop it.
Stop it, Jackson.
- Let's measure precisely. - My gosh.
(I don't care about the show. Let me beat him first.)
- Where did he end up? - Let's measure precisely.
(That's almost 3m.)
- Where did he end up? - That's 280cm.
Both of them jumped really far.
(Come on, Jong Kook.)
(Gosh, that punk.)
Let's just settle that you won.
What was that? He even took off his sweater.
- Let's say that he won. - Okay, sure.
- Fine, you won. - Jackson was great.
- Jackson won. - You won.
He's the prince of long jumping.
- He jumped really far. - That was really far.
Start.
I wonder who will win this time.
- My goodness. - Come on, hurry.
(They must win the second game by all means.)
Excuse me.
(Jong Kook goes off to get the hint.)
At this rate, he will be hospitalized.
- Are you all right? - He's tired now.
- He's tired. - Bam Bam is tired.
He's exhausted.
He looks tired now.
- My gosh. - One.
- Team Running Man wins! - Okay!
(The second match, Dirty Face)
(Team Running Man wins.)
(Team GOT7 and Team Running Man win a round each.)
(Why Did You Come to My House?)
I see tents.
(This round will decide the result.)
- What's going on? - Those are tents.
Are we all going to go into the tent?
Everyone has to go in?
- The team that fits more will win? - Really?
6 members must fit into this 1-person tent.
The team that zips up the tent first will win.
(The remaining member must zip it up.)
- All right then. - What should we do first?
- Big members will stay in the back. - Okay.
- Jong Kook and I won't go in. - Okay.
He has to go in first no matter what.
If he takes long in the middle...
- Take off your watch first. - Yes, take it off.
- Take off your shoes first. - Take your shoes off.
- Take my shoes off? - Take them off.
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, and 6. This is the order.
They crouched down. Should we do the same?
- Get down. - Should we do that?
Let's go in right away.
Get ready.
Wait, hold on.
- You startled me. - Why did you put your hand there?
(He gets competitive.)
- You should move back a bit. - Come on, Jackson.
- He's fussy. - Okay.
- He makes a fuss. - Gosh, Jackson.
(Running Man advocates playing fair.)
Get ready.
They're fast.
(6 members must fit into a 1-person tent.)
- Go in. - There you go.
(They enter at a fast speed.)
(It's neck and neck.)
- They're fast. Hurry. - Hurry.
- Hurry. - Go all the way inside.
- Hurry. Hurry up. - He went in.
Okay. Zip it up.
- We're all in. - Zip it up.
(It's a battle of who can zip up faster.)
I'll zip up now.
(Can they zip up first and obtain the hint?)
(Or will they lose out to GOT7?)
- Okay, we're done! Okay. - Okay.
(The members went in almost at the same time.)
(Team Running Man finishes first by a close call.)
- Let's open it. - Hey, we did it.
- We won! We won. - Okay!
- Did we win? - We lost.
I just zipped it up.
- We totally beat them. - We did.
It was really tight in there.
(The final score is 2 to 1.)
(Team Running Man wins!)
We'll proceed to the last individual voting.
GOT7 will vote for the last slot on the roulette.
(GOT7's votes will determine the last slot.)
They're going to vote.
Haha and So Min's names aren't on the roulette, right?
(Thank you for the tip.)
Haha's name isn't on it?
We have to choose who will get the penalty...
- and who will be exempt from it. - Someone who won't face it?
Haha is chosen to receive the penalty.
- It's Haha. - Okay.
(Gosh! Kwang Soo.)
Three members were chosen to be exempt from the penalty.
- Really? - 1, 2, 3.
(They drew lots to narrow down to one member.)
(And Ji Hyo gets the exemption ticket.)
- This member will face the penalty. - It's too obvious.
It's Jong Kook.
(It's Jong Kook, naturally.)
Why me? Hey.
- Hey. - This member will be exempted.
It's So Min.
- She won't face the penalty? - Yes, we voted for her.
My gosh, this is amazing.
(Running her fingers through her hair paid off.)
(Congratulations on getting exempted from the penalty.)
- That looked a bit weird. - I can't believe this.
(I won't get the penalty today!)
(We wish your new album will be a hit.)
(All the slots on the roulettes are filled out.)
I'll give you the last hint of the final destination.
We'll have the whole address now.
(What is this?)
- What is it? What? - "First floor".
- It's on the 1st floor. - 1st floor.
- We must go to the first floor. - Let's go.
Yes, the first floor of that building.
I'll sit in the back.
(They have only 30 minutes left.)
What is this?
Did you enter the address?
(1st floor, 161 Mokdongseo Avenue, Yangcheon District, Seoul)
I did.
Let's go.
(If this is the address...)
- Is that in Mok-dong? - Mok-dong?
Do we have to take that road?
- No, it's the next one. - Yes, it is. Take that exit.
- This is it. - This is the one.
- I had no idea. - We're going there again.
This is it. We're here.
- It's the building for SBS. - See?
It's SBS' building.
- Look. - We just need to deliver this?
- What's inside the briefcase? - I'm curious about that.
- We can't open it though. - I wonder what's inside.
It's like the Pandora's box.
It'd be funny if we opened it now.
Imagine Kwang Soo opening it to be funny.
(They want to open it more because they're told not to.)
Imagine that.
(The briefcase isn't locked?)
(He presses it just in case, but it's unlocked.)
- Stop it. Don't open it. - No.
No, no. I was just checking.
- You little runt. - Hey, stop it.
- I didn't open it. I'm serious. - They told you not to do it.
- Don't do it. Put your hands away. - I won't open it.
I was just checking if it worked.
- All right. Let's get off. - Thank you for driving.
Let's get going.
Dangerous Delivery, Briefcase Delivery Race.
You successfully arrived at the final destination.
Okay!
Nice.
(They manage to deliver it within 6 hours.)
Since you delivered the briefcase on time,
7 of you will be exempt from the penalty.
Only one of you will face the penalty.
- You're not on the roulette. - But the race...
- What's inside? - What is inside the briefcase?
Can we open it now?
As for the briefcase...
(What's inside the briefcase?)
What could be inside?
(And the secret hidden inside the briefcase...)
- It will be revealed next week. - What?
- That's too mean. - This is frustrating.
- I'm so curious. - You'll tell us next week?
(I'm so curious. How can I wait until next week?)
(What on earth is inside the briefcase?)
All right. Here's the roulette that will choose the member...
who will face the penalty.
- I'm not on it. - I just need to dodge this.
Only one of us will face the penalty, correct?
Since Jong Kook has two slots right now,
- he has the highest chance. - Let's go.
Probability-wise, it'll be me.
- I don't want to get the penalty. - Probability-wise, it'll be me.
Please.
1, 2, 3.
(Just like the probability, will Jong Kook be chosen?)
What is it? Please. Please don't let it be me.
(Or will an unlucky member...)
- I have a bad feeling about this. - No, no.
(get the penalty?)
(Will it be Kwang Soo?)
(Or will it be Seok Jin?)
- I have a bad feeling about this. - No, no. It went over.
- It's Se Chan. - It's not me.
(Se Chan, the unlucky member, is chosen.)
- My gosh. - It's not me.
(He plops down right away.)
(Lady Luck, why did you abandon me?)
What have I done wrong?
We have prepared the biggest water bomb.
We never got 3 bombs at once. It's our 1st time.
- Right. - I'm curious to find out.
All right. Drop the water bombs.
- 2, 1. Go. - I'm nervous for him.
Go.
(His knees give way with the water bombs.)
(The water bomb turns him into the biggest law-breaker.)
(He disappears from the screen.)
- His hair in the middle fell out. - My gosh.
- His hair fell out. - Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - Poor him.
I'm going to take care of my fan!
- I'll take care of him. - Se Chan.
- That was strong. - Se Chan.
(What's the secret hidden inside the briefcase?)
(The secret of the briefcase is revealed at last.)
(However,)
(they receive a mysterious call.)
(Strange incidents happen as they get closer to the secret.)
(Strange incidents...)
(centering around the briefcase are happening.)
(Strange behaviors are spotted here and there.)
(Someone already knows the secret of the briefcase.)
(Some are trying to conceal the secret.)
(Some are trying to uncover it.)
(Everything will end once the briefcase is opened.)
(To open the briefcase, the race for Chuseok will be held.)
(Without a break to catch their breath,)
(the laughter bombs keep on coming.)
(They desperately struggle to unravel the secret.)
(Will they be able to uncover the secret?)
(Dangerous Delivery Part 2, The Secret of the Briefcase)