- Hello.
Where is Jae Suk?
There are only five chairs.
- You are right.
- Aren't the others coming?
- What is that?
- Birthday punch.
Birthday cake and birthday punch.
Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo's
birthdays...
- are in August.
- That's right.
- It's only a few days from now.
- Are we throwing them a party?
- Really?
- I think we are holding an event.
My feelings were hurt
on my last birthday.
- Why?
- There was no birthday punch.
I can give you one.
(It's a piece of cake.)
- Suk Jin.
- We can give you...
- a belated birthday punch.
- You should stay out of it.
I can give you
a belated birthday punch.
Why do people describe birthdays
as "The day your ears pop up"?
- What?
- "The day your ears pop up".
When you are born, your ears
get caught and pop up like this.
- I see.
- So that's what it meant.
Suk Jin knows these things well
because he is ancient.
He probably saw
a lot of people give birth at home.
I was born in a hospital!
- What?
- I was born in a hospital.
Didn't your mom use
a rope that hangs from the ceiling?
I bet he stood outside the room
when his wife gave birth.
I bet he did that
because he was nervous.
- When he heard the cry of a baby,
- What is wrong with you guys?
- "Is it a boy?"
- he'd say, "Is it a boy or a girl?"
"It's a boy!"
I bet he did that.
Today, Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo
will be born again...
through Happy Death Day,
Along with the Birthdays Race.
Happy Death Day?
(Happy Death Day,
Along with the Birthdays)
Along with the Birthdays?
- It's like the new movie.
- "Along with the Birthdays".
- That's ingenious.
- Your idea shines.
Between a birthday cake
and a birthday punch,
which one would you give
to the members?
- Are we choosing separately?
- Yes, you are.
To be honest,
I don't care which one they get.
It's just that I don't know
which one will benefit me.
- Birthday punch is the best.
- That's right.
You need a good birthday punch...
- to live a healthy life.
- Of course.
You will remember
a birthday punch from Jong Kook...
- forever.
- That's right.
You will have a memory
as well as a scar.
I had a bruise for a month.
- I will choose the birthday cake.
- I choose the birthday cake too.
(Everyone finishes choosing.)
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook
choose the birthday punch.)
(Se Chan, So Min, and Kwang Soo
choose the birthday cake.)
The three people whose birthdays are
in August will soon be eliminated...
and become the deceased
with an embarrassing nickname.
They will be the deceased.
(Haha becomes New Identity.)
(Ji Hyo becomes Cheon Sung Im.)
I hope Jae Suk comes back
as a more handsome man.
(Jae Suk becomes Ugly Man.)
Kwang Soo, So Min, and Se Chan,
you chose the birthday cake.
You will be the Grim Reapers who try
to prove the deceased innocent...
and reincarnate with them.
Suk Jin and Jong Kook,
you chose the birthday punch.
You will be the prosecutors who try
to prove the deceased guilty...
and reincarnate instead of them...
- throughout the mission.
- Prosecutors.
- He is an expert nitpicker.
- That's right.
- I will be the Jerk from Anyang.
Hold on. Among the three of you,
who is Joo Jin Mo?
- It's Ju Ji Hoon.
- Joo Jin Mo?
- He didn't star in that movie.
- Ju Ji Hoon.
- Isn't Joo Jin Mo in the movie?
No, he isn't. It's Ju Ji Hoon!
- Ju Ji Hoon.
That means
we are the main characters.
The Grim Reapers were played by
Ha Jung Woo,
- It gets confusing.
- Ju Ji Hoon,
- and Kim Hyang Gi.
- Kim Hyang Gi.
- She is really cute.
- Kim Hyang Gi is really young.
- I can't see So Min as her.
- Are you saying So Min is old?
That's not what I said.
I said Kim Hyang Gi is young.
I just said she's young.
I didn't say you are old.
She is more like Jo Hyang Gi.
(She's not Kim Hyang Gi.)
(They are practically in
the same age group.)
- I didn't hear her name recently.
- Are you doing all right, Hyang Gi?
- Jo Hyang Gi.
- Jeon Hyang Gi.
Jeon Hyang Gi? That sounds weird.
The team
that fails to reincarnate...
will suffer an incredible penalty.
- An incredible penalty?
- There is a penalty.
- Are we playing individually?
- If there is a penalty...
The person who has the best chance
of reincarnation...
- is Jae Suk.
- Why do you say that?
He is upright. He has a good image.
He is the national MC.
You forget that
we are the prosecutors.
- You are right.
- We know all about his past.
To avoid the penalty, you would have
a better chance with Ji Hyo.
She rarely receives the penalty.
- To reincarnate...
- You have a point.
I want to team up with Ji Hyo.
- Really?
- Are you set on your choice?
- Yes, I am.
- Then team up with Ji Hyo.
Why did you give up so readily?
- Why did you give up so readily?
- Team up with Ji Hyo.
- I will consider my options.
- You should have insisted.
- You are set on your choice.
How about Haha?
Does he have a good chance?
- Jong Kook knows Haha even better.
- I know Haha well.
Since Haha is a weasel,
he would be able to overcome
any obstacles.
No, no. It won't be so easy
to reincarnate.
- That's right.
- He did launder his identity.
- This is bad.
- Jong Kook is already in character.
- He is strict.
He committed the gravest sin.
Laundering your identity
is a grave sing.
This is already suffocating.
(Along with the Birthdays,
Reincarnation)
(He is guilty by ruining people's
eyes with his shocking looks.)
(Ugly Man's Grim Reaper
is Jeon So Min.)
(She is guilty for confusing others
with her aggressive nature.)
(Cheon Sung Im's Grim Reaper
is Lee Kwang Soo.)
(He is guilty for covering up
his promiscuous past.)
(New Identity's Grim Reaper
is Yang Se Chan.)
(The three deceased,
we are on our way to take you.)
(She arrives
in the land of the living.)
(Is this where Jae Suk is?)
Where is the deceased going?
(When the Grim Reaper calls
the deceased's name three times,)
(the soul leaves the body.)
(Hello.)
Can't he see me?
(She struggles with calling
the deceased.)
Yoo Jae Suk.
(Yoo Jae Suk)
What are you doing in a running car?
Yoo Jae Suk.
- What is this?
- You are out.
- What?
- Come with me to the underworld.
What do you think... Hold on.
What do you think you are doing?
- You passed away...
- Go away.
- because you are too ugly.
- Excuse me?
(She stifles her laughter.)
Come with me to the underworld.
I will help you reincarnate.
I am your Grim Reaper,
Jeon Hyang Gi.
(I can relieve your resentment.)
Jeon Hyang Gi?
You are more like Jeon Fart.
- Jeon Hyang Gi.
- Jeon Fart.
- Did you see "Along with the Gods"?
- Yes, I did.
What is that?
You will now be the deceased...
- under my care.
- This is crazy. This T-shirt...
What is this?
(Shocking)
(Ugly Man)
- Let's go.
- What is this?
(If you want your name back,
reincarnate.)
Do you want me to go away?
(I realized my mistake.)
(He goes along with it.)
Come.
(Let's see...)
(if they will be able
to reincarnate.)
(The second Grim Reaper gets ready
to pick up his deceased.)
(Is this where Ji Hyo is?)
(Knocking)
Song Ji Hyo.
(Song Ji Hyo)
- What?
- Song Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo isn't here.
(This isn't how it goes.)
What?
(He focuses once more.)
For goodness' sake, you startled me.
(What is he doing?)
Song Ji Hyo, you are out.
Come with me to the underworld.
Why am I already out?
- You are out.
- We haven't even begun anything.
- What is up with that weird outfit?
I am the Grim Reaper.
- I am the Grim Reaper.
- Grim Reaper? When did you die?
I didn't die.
You did. I am the Grim Reaper.
You must have become the Grim Reaper
because you died at some point.
- I was born as the Grim Reaper.
- You have a problem.
Why did you kill me already
even before we get started?
I didn't kill you.
Is this how it goes?
- Why did you kill me already?
- Shouldn't she be scared?
Why would I be scared?
- I am the Grim Reaper.
- His outfit is too small.
- This is ridiculous.
- Why didn't I get a bigger outfit?
Is this a miniskirt?
- It looks like a dress.
- Why didn't I get a bigger outfit?
I have something like this at home.
No, this isn't the same one.
The deceased must accompany me.
(He gets into his role
all of a sudden.)
Where are we going? Fine, let's go.
(This is unbelievable.)
- When did you become a Grim Reaper?
- I don't know how to play this.
I'm not sure
what I'm supposed to do.
(This Grim Reaper gets into his role
too much in front of the restroom.)
(Walking)
(Knocking)
(Knocking back)
(Look at this deceased.)
- Haha.
- I'm in here.
(His eyes get shaky.)
Haha.
This stall is already occupied.
Sorry.
Haha, you are eliminated.
(He's acting.)
The deceased must accompany me.
(He was eliminated while pooping.)
(He's about to start his skit.)
I'm out already?
(To the underworld)
(Hold on, Grim Reaper Yang.)
I'm out?
(He takes the set-up a bit too far.)
(He heads to the underworld with
lingering feelings of this world.)
- Reincarnation isn't easy.
- What?
It's not a place where they can
just come and go so easily.
- They can't look down on our world.
- Exactly.
By the way, where is Queen of Death?
I think she's in that black car.
(Queen of Death?)
Queen of Death.
- Shouldn't we be on a palanquin?
- Exactly.
- Gosh, she drives a car instead.
- This is a new model.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- My gosh. Hello.
(I'm the Queen of Death.)
(Noh Sa Yeon)
- Thank you for coming all this way.
- Thank you.
- I'm the prosecutor, Ji Suk Jin.
- Right.
- I see.
- What are you eating?
Are you eating red bean buns?
- Come inside.
- Sure, we'll go in.
Since our outfits today
are a bit unusual,
- we ought to hear what it's about.
- That's right.
Your Royal Highness.
- Am I a queen?
- Yes, you're Queen of Death.
- Queen of Death, not the king.
- Queen of Death.
- That's right.
- I like it.
Nowadays, you don't ride
the palanquin.
- You get around by car.
- Right.
- This is quite up to date.
- Yes, it is.
- The world is changing.
- I see.
Then am I here as a queen today?
- You're the Queen of Death.
- Queen of Death.
Anyway,
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Since I had some buns,
this royal highness is thirsty.
- Bring me some water.
- Sure, I'm on it.
I see you had red bean buns.
My goodness, you even have a fridge.
- This is a hotel, not a car.
- Gosh.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
Thank you for giving me a raise.
- Let me have a bit of my buns.
- Please do.
- She's better than King of Death.
- Definitely.
- She provides good benefits.
- Exactly.
Your Majesty,
should I put this on now?
Let's take a look.
- Your Majesty, please take a look.
- My gosh.
This deceased is trying to
get reincarnated.
The first deceased is Ugly Man.
He displayed distasteful looks
for others to see.
- He lived his life with that face.
- That's right.
No crimes can be worse
than this one.
Especially, his jaw area
is infuriating me.
That's right. It's protruding a lot.
He didn't put any disguise
on his mouth area.
- He is ugly indeed.
- Right.
- That's a serious offense.
- I see.
- The next deceased.
- Let's take a look at the next one.
Look at this deceased.
- This deceased is Cheon Sung Im.
- Right.
She's too aggressive.
First, she looks like a delinquent.
Look at her side bangs.
I despise these kinds of girls.
- You do, don't you?
- Yes.
She's very aggressive,
so I bet the Grim Reaper
who was to bring her down here...
- He probably had a hard time.
- probably had a tough time.
- How terrible.
- Your Highness.
- Right.
- That's her.
- This guy.
- My gosh, this guy.
Doesn't even his appearance
upset you?
- His name is New Identity.
- Look at this guy.
- He's one of us.
- That's right.
This is New Identity.
- Look at this guy.
- He got a new identity...
when he got married.
Doesn't he live in our neighborhood?
- That's correct.
- Yes, he does.
He was the most despicable man
you could ever lay your eyes on.
- After he got married...
- He pretended to be righteous.
- Right. He's living a fake life.
- I see.
- Okay.
- Strangely,
I want this one to be reincarnated.
- From his photo,
- Is that so?
- it looks like he's struggling.
- You think so?
- You can't be weak.
- You should never be.
- We must punish them accordingly.
- Okay, okay.
I'll only give you the facts.
- I'll be strong today.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I'll be fair.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Let's go to court.
- Let's go.
(Can the deceased convince her
and be reincarnated?)
Come this way, New Identity.
- I lived a bad life.
- You got a whole new identity.
- No, no. I did nothing wrong.
- Come this way.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- Why am I being dragged?
Let go of me. Look here.
If any of us here are guilty,
- these Grim Reapers must be guilty.
- That's right.
(Grim Reapers, my foot!)
- What? We're the Grim Reapers.
- Hey, that was a bit harsh.
- We're the Grim Reapers.
- You have to be in our graces.
You're nothing
like the Grim Reapers.
- No, we're the Grim Reapers.
- Yes, we are.
Goodness, this is unbelievable.
By the way, what's this?
Why did you put this on my shirt?
Mine says New Identity.
My mother-in-law keeps asking me
about my past.
- You committed a lot of sins.
- What is this?
This photo is scarier
than a Grim Reaper.
- Come on, what is this?
- Look at you, Ji Hyo.
- Gosh.
- Look at her side bangs.
- She totally took money from kids.
- My gosh, I can't believe this.
This photo was from ages ago.
Listen to me. You took away
these innocent people's lives.
Is this how you're going to
run the show?
You look so shameless when
you said you were innocent.
Your life was a mess.
It was such a mess.
Where are Jong Kook and Suk Jin?
If anyone is guilty, his record
must be the longest.
- Here comes the Queen of Death.
- What?
- There's the King of Death?
"Queen of Death"?
Here comes the Queen of Death.
Here she comes.
- Look at these punks.
- My goodness.
- Hello, sir.
- Gosh.
- Feel the wrath of the underworld.
- That's right. Okay.
- He looks like a traitor.
- He's the eunuch.
- He's a traitor.
- What? A traitor?
- How dare you?
- How dare you say that to me?
- Okay.
- Sure, sure.
Hey, we're the prosecutors.
- Hey.
- Be on good terms with them.
- Sure, sure. I got it.
- We're the prosecutors.
- Look at that.
- Don't you know what day it is?
- My gosh, Your Majesty.
- Gosh.
(The underworld's leader shows up
while exuding a strong presence.)
- My gosh.
- Hey, Sa Yeon.
- She's the Queen of Death?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Queen of Death?
- My goodness.
Have you been well?
- How dare you approach her?
- Your Highness.
- How dare you?
- The deceased must step back.
- You're the deceased.
- Hello. Hi.
- How dare a deceased...
- Hi.
- Have you been well?
Gosh, Ms. Bambi.
Everyone, hold on.
Don't give her secret signs
or anything.
- I'm so happy to see her.
- How dare you point at her?
- We're really close.
- How dare you?
You're in the underworld.
You'd better behave.
- Don't act all friendly here.
- By the way, there's...
- no regulation on hair styles.
- what did you say?
- Your bangs are curly.
- We're free to do whatever we want.
Can your hair look like
the Niagara Falls?
What? Niagara Falls?
What on earth are you saying?
- How dare you?
- What?
- You pushed back your hat.
- I ought to teach you a lesson.
- He got off on the wrong foot.
- Prosecutor.
- Gosh, this is unbelievable.
- You know what?
If the deceased causes trouble,
the Grim Reaper will be punished.
(He makes a threat.)
The Grim Reaper will be punished?
- He's going to hit us?
- Seriously?
- You can hit us?
- What?
- Of course, we can.
- Yes, we can.
- Exactly.
(What?
This isn't how you play this.)
- You'll hit them in the underworld?
- You bet.
Before we put you in the fiery pit,
I can...
- Everyone, let's all sit down.
- Yes?
- Yes, ma'am.
(Quiet down.
Let's start our first trial.)
All right.
"Before your birthdays, you had
to leave the world of the living."
"Ugly Man, Yoo Jae Suk,"
"New Identity, Haha,"
"and Cheon Sung Im, Song Ji Hyo."
"Your reincarnations
are at stake here."
"Happy Death..."
(Their reincarnations
depend on this trial.)
"Along with the Happy Messdays..."
- Did you write it in English?
- Pardon?
Did you write that in English?
You should've written in Korean.
(Her eyes get bad on an empty
stomach. She needs more buns.)
The Queen of Death is quite old.
You ought to show her some respect!
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Why don't you read this scroll?
- Yes, ma'am.
Let me read this.
"The first trial is
the Fiery Pit of Betrayal."
"We'll bring up charges
about the times..."
"when you betrayed and deceived
others and punish accordingly."
Fiery Pit of Betrayal.
They must prove their innocence
with the help of the Grim Reapers.
Each team will get a penalty
depending on the trial's result.
They must carry out a mission
based on the results.
Reincarnation Balls will be
distributed based on their rankings.
Only the team chosen at
the final gate can be reincarnated.
(3rd place, New Identity,
reincarnated)
If this is the theme,
Ji Hyo will definitely win.
- She has never deceived anyone.
- That's right.
- I've never betrayed anyone.
- You're an angel.
- Right, So Min?
"The whole nation recognizes these
three's betrayals and deceits."
"Prosecutors already demanded to
punish them..."
- "with five water slaps."
- That's right.
"But I'll show mercy on you.
Depending on the weight..."
"Depending on the weight
of your crimes, "
"I can reduce the sentence
from 1 to 3 slaps."
- My gosh.
- "Water slaps"?
- What have we done? This is crazy.
- "However,"
"the prosecutors will face
the reduced water slaps..."
"since they couldn't prove
your crimes..."
"and charged you
with a wrong sentence."
We'll face them?
Hey, make sure you read it right.
- This is a great set-up.
- If we defend them well,
- the prosecutors will face it.
- That's right.
Your Majesty,
your decision is outstanding.
(She's a fair Queen of Death.)
Hey, make sure you read it right.
(This can't be true.)
- Are you serious?
- That's what it says.
- Yes, you're right.
- Right.
- Make sure they get all 5 slaps.
- 5 water slaps.
We'll get to see
the water turning black.
"All right. Prosecution,"
"you may accuse
the deceased of their crimes."
- It's our turn?
- Yes.
Go make your case.
I was reading this
on the Queen of Death's behalf.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but the Kingdom of Death
has changed.
Ma'am,
can you have the juice
and the buns next to your throne?
(Hey, look.)
- Things have improved around here.
- Listen.
- Hold on.
- Those are real buns.
Is there a snack bar
in the Kingdom of Death?
- She always eats it.
- She always eats that.
- That's included in the contract.
- Wait a second.
- Hey, you two.
- Yes?
- I have something to say.
- How dare you point at us?
I don't know about that.
You look like those people
who take photos with tourists.
Hey, we're prosecutors!
(We take photos for 1 dollar.)
(Welcome to
the Running Folk Village.)
When it comes to betraying
other people,
that guy can betray others
with his eyes wide open.
- That's not true.
- You're in no place to charge us.
Working with me means
pure torment for him anyway.
(Just so you know.)
(Nodding)
- Is he being punished right now?
- Yes.
- He is.
- All right.
This is the worst possible torture.
He is being punished right now.
Suk Jin suddenly looks so thin.
It's already been years like that.
(I'd rather be dead.)
Keep talking. I'll eat some bread.
(This is probably going to
take a while.)
(She suddenly eats bread now?)
- Is she really going to eat now?
- For real?
She's really going to eat.
It's so noisy in here.
I need some rest...
while you guys talk.
Usually, those things
are just for show,
but Sa Yeon actually eats them.
(I love red bean buns.)
- Let's hear about Jae Suk.
- Okay.
I have an allegation to make...
- against Jae Suk.
- All right.
(The trial starts.)
(The first defendant, Yoo Jae Suk)
It was Ji Hyo's week.
(Do you remember?)
We used a lie detector.
We asked him if he'd marry
his current wife in his next life.
- Yes.
- And he answered...
- I answered yes.
- that he would.
- Of course.
- And it turned out to be a lie.
(The lie detector said
it was a lie.)
(My goodness.)
(Evidence of Jae Suk's lie)
(I'll definitely marry her
in my next life too.)
(He sounded so confident.)
(Electric shock)
(It was determined a lie
right away.)
(This is not okay.)
(It's understandable.)
Don't get the wrong idea.
(There's evidence that
Jae Suk lied.)
(That evidence is false.)
I still remember it.
Do you think a machine can
read a human's mind?
You looked...
very anxious at that time.
(Another piece of evidence)
(I didn't look anxious.)
- It's not true.
- So Min, talk to him.
That machine doesn't work well.
I've used it a few times too.
It gives you an electric shock
if your hand is sweaty.
So if you sweat a lot...
or the weather is hot...
Do you sweat a lot?
Yes. My hands get sweaty
when the weather is hot.
In that case,
everything I say can be determined
a lie by that machine.
Cut it out!
Everything I say can be determined
a lie by that machine.
- But...
- Cut it out!
it was my week,
so I remember it clearly.
It was a snowy winter day,
and we were in Gangwon Province.
It was in winter.
- That's right. Way to go!
- We didn't sweat.
(It was a cold day.)
(Oh, right.)
Seriously.
Ji Hyo, what are you doing
right now?
What is this?
We were wearing winter jackets.
It was really cold.
That's right. Keep going!
It was impossible to sweat.
(It doesn't seem like Jae Suk will
be brought back to life.)
(Whispering)
(What is he doing?)
We'd like to submit
the lie detector as evidence!
(The lie detector as evidence?)
Do we have it here?
You may try the lie detector.
(Will Jae Suk and So Min
be able to prove their points?)
Everyone,
this is the lie detector...
- in question.
- That's right.
You sound like a real lawyer.
(Witness number 1, lie detector)
Okay.
(Will this prove
Ugly Man's innocence?)
What is that?
You can try...
It's not a bun!
(It's round and white,
but it's not a bun.)
What kind of bun is that?
It's a lie detector.
You can try it.
- Do you want to try it?
- How do you use it?
Your hand...
- My hand?
- Like this.
Wait. Let me help you.
(You're not doing it right.)
(Your Highness)
- What's this?
- It's the wrong way.
(I'm sorry, but it's the wrong way.)
Put your hand on it.
(Queen of Death will test
the lie detector.)
"In my next life,"
"I'll marry..."
"Lee Moo Song again."
(In my next life, I'll marry
Lee Moo Song again.)
No.
(Determined)
"No."
(This question made Ugly Man
a betrayer.)
If it's false, it'd be touching.
(Is the queen's answer true?)
(It's true.)
(I've already married him once.
Why do it again?)
Hold on.
(The machine seems to work fine.)
She really doesn't want to
marry him again?
That machine is flawless.
It's flawless.
It works perfectly fine.
You said the truth.
(Honey,
don't believe what they say.)
(What will happen to my defendant?)
- It's true.
- Yes.
Jae Suk, you should try it again.
- You should try it too.
- Me?
Try it.
I've already tried it.
Prosecutor Ji will prove...
the accuracy of the machine
once again.
- Prosecutor Ji.
- Yes?
Would you marry your current wife,
Ryu Su Jeong,
in your next life?
Of course.
(Determined)
(Suk Jin is known
for his love for his wife.)
(Is his answer true?)
(True)
It's not right.
Did you see that?
He shook his hand on purpose.
It wasn't true?
This machine is unreliable.
That's right.
It's been proven.
This machine malfunctions...
from time to time.
- Jae Suk is innocent.
- I'm innocent.
- That machine doesn't work, right?
- It doesn't.
What I said was a lie too.
(She takes it back.)
But it was true.
- Let me try one more time.
- You want to?
- Yes.
- All right.
(I don't think it's a good idea.)
Queen of Death will try it
one last time.
Would you marry...
Lee Moo Song...
in your next life too?
Yes!
(Confident)
She is Queen of Death.
She never lies.
It's definitely true.
(She says the opposite this time.
Is it true?)
Gosh, it hurts.
(Her answer is false.)
(Surprised)
(It's impossible to defend her now.)
- It's false.
(She doesn't want to
marry her current husband again.)
The machine...
is so accurate!
Everyone, that machine is accurate.
(Flustered)
I'm so surprised.
- It's accurate.
- It's so accurate.
See?
This machine malfunctions a lot.
It's unreliable.
What are you talking about?
Also, I've overheard...
Jae Suk's phone conversations
with his wife...
so many times.
What does he say?
For example, when we shoot abroad,
right before we get on the plane,
"Kyung Eun, we're about to
get on the plane. Okay."
(Embarrassed)
Stop it.
I said to him,
"You're such a loving husband."
He became embarrassed and said,
"I'm not."
It's happened many times.
- That's all.
- What about afterwards?
After he gets off the phone,
he sighs. I've seen it.
(Haha accuses Jae Suk.)
That brat...
It's not true.
I've never seen that.
How do you know
if it was Na Kyung Eun...
or Choi Kyung Eun?
(Suk Jin is desperate.)
What are you talking about?
- What is that supposed to mean?
- What is he talking about?
- How do you know that?
But doesn't every husband
do that much?
- Not everyone does.
- Who doesn't?
The one next to you doesn't.
(Prosecutor Ji doesn't.)
I don't call my wife often.
Why? Our love is so deep.
Jae Suk calls his wife
as if it was his homework...
because their love is shallow.
It's even been aired a few times.
Suk Jin often says,
"I don't want to go home."
(I've heard it.)
"I'd rather work."
"I want to go home late."
He's said that many times.
(Suk Jin is no help.)
Are you okay?
I'm not.
(He might lose his position
as a prosecutor and a husband.)
- That's all.
- Good job, So Min.
You can see that...
Jae Suk is guilty, right?
- Not really.
- No?
(Fail)
- Let me make a decision.
- Okay.
(Verdict)
Jae Suk...
(Ugly Man tried to defend himself
against his charges.)
(What's the verdict?)
Since I can't trust the machine,
you'll get one less slap.
(As the machine is unreliable,
Jae Suk gets 1 less slap.)
(Then who gets the slap instead?)
And Prosecutor Ji will slapped.
(Suk Jin pretended to be a loving
husband and framed Jae Suk.)
The prosecutor will be slapped
instead of Jae Suk.
Nice!
Me?
(The prosecutors will be slapped
instead.)
All right. Haha,
do you know why you're a betrayer?
Me?
- He's not.
- You betrayed something huge.
- Me?
- You betrayed yourself.
Haha betrayed his past.
I did?
(The second defendant, Haha)
His life?
He betrayed...
his own life.
Gosh.
We all know that...
Haha used to be
Seorae Village's trash.
(Haha used to be
Seorae Village's trash.)
Was I alone?
(I wasn't alone.)
This guy.
(This guy was with me.)
Me? I was just sitting here.
(Frustrated)
Look.
The thing is, that guy...
is still a piece of trash.
Me?
He hasn't...
tried to hide his past.
I don't want him
as my Grim Reaper anymore.
It's not true.
I'm worried.
He doesn't deserve to sit here.
It's not true.
I just...
had some fun.
I'm not a bad person.
He's been working hard
since he got married.
We need to...
find out the truth...
of the charges against Haha.
That's why we brought a witness.
- What? A witness?
- We brought a witness.
Really?
Who could it be?
Witness, please come in.
(The witness has been
stabbed in the back by Haha.)
(Who is the witness?)
Where is he?
- Sang Yeob?
- Okay.
It's Sang Yeob.
(Witness Lee Sang Yeob)
- Over here, Sang Yeob!
- Really?
Sang Yeob!
You're not allowed to speak to him.
(Your Highness, I'm Lee Sang Yeob
from the mortal world.)
You're handsome.
(What's the New Identity crime
that Sang Yeob will reveal?)
What happened to you?
It's a long story.
- It was early 2008.
- And?
I was happy
after receiving an award...
when I got a call.
I was told that I was a teenage star
that made 2017 shine.
I congratulate you even to this day.
(First recording of the year
on January 2, 2018)
(Haha and Kwang Soo call Sang Yeob
for their mission.)
(They lure him by offering
a teenage star award.)
(Come and get your award.)
(Sang Yeob is very excited.)
I got ready in one hour
to receive the award and prize.
- I came to Hongdae.
- That's right.
However, what I received was...
- a piece of paper.
- A piece of paper.
- A piece of paper?
- It was a piece of paper.
(Paper award and
plastic bottle as a trophy)
- I got a plastic bottle.
- A plastic bottle?
That's so disappointing.
I could accept that,
but on top of that,
they called Geun Sik.
- That's right.
- That's true. I remember.
I was only given
a small portion on the show.
You had me share it with Geun Sik.
That's how you and Geun Sik
became close.
That's not all.
You get free food when you come
to my barbecue restaurant.
(You get free food
at my restaurant.)
That's...
It's all thanks to Geun Sik.
- Does he get free food?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Two restaurant owners
feel uncomfortable.)
He accepted it.
- I see.
- What's going on between you two?
What's going on between you two?
There's more.
- I was sleeping in the morning.
- Right.
I got another call.
They said I was number one celebrity
whom people want to travel with.
- Congratulations.
(Early March in 2018)
(Even Ji Hyo joins this time.)
(Within three months in 2018)
(They tell that he's number one star
whom people want to travel with.)
(Sang Yeob ends up on
Tsushima Island.)
(He's number one celebrity whose
step counter people want to shake.)
- They're crooks.
- They told me to bring my passport.
(He's a terrible man.)
- Look at him.
- They told me to bring my passport.
The witness's feelings got hurt
a lot.
- I certainly did.
- Right.
My goodness. Seriously?
- There's one more.
- One more?
One more?
They wanted to assign me a character
as I'm new to variety shows.
- I became Vicarious Man,
- Right.
and I had to do zip-lining.
(They made him zip-line instead.)
(Haha creates Vicarious Man
to make him zip-line instead.)
(Sang Yeob was a fool to accept it.)
You said I'll be on commercials
if I become Vicarious Man.
I didn't get any commercial offers.
(They sweet-talked to him.)
Make people call me.
You ask for too high of a price.
(It's not my fault.)
(I'll lower my price, so call me.)
You aren't good enough yet.
I was there when he became
Vicarious Man.
- He isn't good enough indeed.
- Witness.
- Yes?
- What did Suk Jin say?
Did he say anything
when you got the nickname?
- I was quiet.
- That I'll get commercial offers.
(He encouraged me that
I'll get offers.)
(He was bad too.)
He asked me,
"Who makes pizza deliveries?"
"I'll do it."
(He even told him what to say.)
(You'll get a call soon.)
When I asked, "What if you became
Vicarious Man?"
You could have said no.
But who accepted it?
- He's very smart.
- Who was it?
He tricked me.
- I didn't trick you.
- No, he didn't.
- I have text messages.
- Who tricked you?
He's submitting text messages.
- I'll submit text messages.
- He's submitting text messages.
He thanked me for making him
Vicarious Man.
(The witness thanked him.)
His boss made a phone call himself.
He thanked me for naming Sang Yeob
Vicarious Man.
- How can we even trust the witness?
- I have it all.
- Read them.
- Please read them.
- We should read them.
- It's just one of many messages.
Please read all of them.
"There's still penalty,
but thank you so much, Haha."
"Thanks to you,"
"I got to be on my favorite show
Running Man."
"I got close to other members."
"It's all because you invited me
and took care of me."
"Thank you so much."
What's "yes, man"?
Then he definitely wrote it.
- Wait. Goodness.
- Yes, man.
The judges brought
the wrong person as a witness.
The evidence is clear.
- Right? It's clear.
- It is.
I have a similar story.
(He counterattacks.)
When I was a rookie on Running Man,
I was at home,
and Haha called me
out to Garosu-gil.
He said he didn't have proper shoes
for a wedding tomorrow.
And he added that
his mission is to buy...
brown dress shoes sized 285mm
in 10 minutes.
(Haha's betrayal)
(He tells Kwang Soo
to bring him shoes.)
- It's true. I swear.
- Look at him.
It was in the middle of summer.
I ran across Garosu-gil
soaked in sweat.
I bought him brown dress shoes.
- He cleared the mission.
- I bought him a pair.
- I cleared his mission myself.
Gosh, he's a terrible man.
Listen, it's true.
It's true that it was a mission.
Now I'll deliver my ruling.
I conclude that
Haha committed serious betrayal.
No, I didn't.
- I sentence you to five buckets.
- This is unfair.
- How can you do this to him?
- This is so unfair.
- Come on.
- I won't accept it.
Mr. Witness, he made your character.
(I'll call you after
I shoot a commercial.)
I don't think Ji Hyo is guilty.
- No?
- No one has attacked her.
(They accept it.)
I reduce your sentence
by two buckets.
- Reduce by two buckets?
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo's sentence is reduced
by two buckets.)
(Jae Suk and So Min get 3,
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo get 3.)
(Haha and Se Chan get 5,
Jong Kook and Suk Jin get 4.)
The first game to
repent your betrayal...
is Deity's Quiz.
Deity's Quiz.
There are a total of three problems.
Play The Rose of Sharon Has Bloomed
according to Sang Yeob's order.
Pick the flag
with the correct number.
When you answer correctly,
you can pass your water bucket
to any team of your choice.
Reincarnation Balls are distributed
according to the ranking.
(Reincarnation Balls are distributed
according to the ranking.)
The team standing last must
get all the water buckets...
to move to the next round.
(The team standing last
must get all water buckets.)
(Water buckets as a penalty
and Reincarnation Balls on the line)
Okay.
There's no point of going there
if we don't know the problem.
- Right.
- I don't know the answer.
We should pick a flag first.
- Here's your first question.
- Okay.
The penalty is one water bucket.
- One bucket.
- Okay.
(They can pass one water bucket.)
(Move out of my way.)
This refers to a special blessing
given by the Christian deity.
It usually means the ability
to control the mass...
- and make people follow.
- Okay.
- "Make people follow"?
- It means "Deity gives blessing"...
in Greek. What is this word?
1, talent. 2, charisma.
3, chic. 4, catharsis.
- "Catharsis"?
- What?
(It's a confusing question.)
I have no idea.
(What is he doing?)
- It's not yet.
- Do we go now?
(He runs anyway.)
It's not yet.
(You must hear my order first.)
- You're ugly.
- Did you see that?
He deserves one water bucket.
Eliminate him.
- Eliminate him.
- I didn't know.
Queen, I'm very sorry.
I didn't know.
- I'll forgive you once.
- Okay.
Queen of Death is too nice.
- She's extremely nice.
- She's too nice.
- You'll be out next time.
- Yes, ma'am.
She's too soft-hearted.
I'll start
The Rose of Sharon Has Bloomed.
- I'll go easy at first.
- Okay.
Stand on one foot,
the rose of Sharon has bloomed
He moved.
(They run first.)
(Hopping)
(Standing on one foot)
(It's very difficult.)
- You're out.
- Someone pushed me.
- Kwang Soo is out.
- How?
- Do you know the answer?
I'm Christian.
(I know the answer.)
(Kwang Soo was too eager.)
You sat down instead of standing up.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
You're out.
(He goes back to the start line.)
Be sexy.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
- That's sexy.
- Ji Hyo and Jae Suk ran.
- They're out.
- That's sexy.
- Why...
That wasn't sexy.
Be sexy, Ji Hyo. You must look sexy.
(Like this?)
(What do you think, Queen?)
(She's very content.)
- Look at his sexy leg muscles.
- They aren't sexy.
- Look at him.
- He isn't sexy.
He is sexy indeed.
He is sexy. Come here, Suk Jin.
- Why?
- You aren't sexy at all.
(Wait a minute.)
(How can I look sexier than this?)
- How can I look sexier?
- You deserve a hit.
- Come back to the line.
- How is this sexy?
- This is sexy enough.
- It's not sexy.
- Come back to the line.
- Go back.
(Isn't this sexy enough?)
Next is...
grab another person by the collar.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
(By the collar?)
(They grab him first.)
Everyone who didn't grab
other's collar, please go back.
- So Min didn't grab anyone.
- She didn't grab anyone.
Why is everyone doing this to me?
- This is...
- Why are you doing this to me?
I think Kwang Soo grabbed
my shoulder.
- Is it the collar?
- He moved his hand slowly.
Express your love
for another member.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
(Kwang Soo gets number 1,
and Jong Kook number 2.)
(I really love you.)
This doesn't count.
So Min is faking it.
- You're out.
- Who?
You're just being loved. You're out.
- What? What is this?
- It doesn't count.
- I love Haha.
- Haha, you're out.
Haha, you're out.
- You're out.
You look so frustrated.
Love is not like that.
I love Jong Kook.
I was expressing my love too.
- Jong Kook doesn't love anyone.
- He's gone.
The one I love is gone.
I love Se Chan,
but he's gone. Gosh.
Someone please stop Kwang Soo!
Hey!
Please stop him!
You two are left, right?
- Please do something.
- Yes.
My answer is
number two, "charisma".
(Is "charisma" the right answer?)
Okay. Number two, "charisma".
My answer is
number two, "charisma".
Okay!
(Jong Kook is right.)
(That's strange.)
Good.
(It's not number 1?)
Okay.
- You're a Christian.
- You...
(You're a Christian.)
I'm sorry, Lord.
(Embarrassed)
(My faith is not strong enough.)
Who should get the slap?
- The slap?
- Yes.
Let's give it to the team
with the least slaps.
We'll give it to the team
(Team Ugly Man has 4 slaps now.)
- Yes!
- Seriously.
This time,
you can transfer two slaps.
(2 slaps)
(Let's do this.)
Here goes the question.
Which of the following...
has never played
as the Grim Reaper?
That's hard.
Number one, Lee Dong Wook.
Number two, Jung Il Woo.
Number three, EXO's Kai.
- I know this.
- Number four, Gang Dong Won.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
(There is
no additional instruction.)
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan
fail to stop.)
You're all out.
- Someone pushed me.
- Who pushed him?
Kwang Soo pushed me.
(Please listen to me.)
- That's right.
- These two are out.
I should stay here.
- I stay here.
- You pushed him?
He pushed me.
- I didn't!
- He pushed me.
Jae Suk is such a smooth talker.
Everything he says
sounds so convincing.
Sa Yeon.
(Ugly Man is a smooth talker.)
Your Highness, it's true.
He pushed me.
That's why I couldn't stop...
- and ended up here.
- I know that.
The rule says that
the one who moves should be out.
But you sound so convincing.
(You sound so convincing.)
- I can't eliminate you.
- Let's say I'm out.
I won't get you in trouble.
I'm out.
All right.
- She trusts him completely.
- Here we go.
Get a member on your back.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
They're all out.
- They're all out.
(It's a mess.)
Hold on.
It hurts!
- Jae Suk...
- I have someone on my back.
You survive.
Jae Suk survives.
- Jong Kook survives too.
- I had someone on my back.
Jong Kook survives.
You guys are out.
Go to the back.
Why am I out?
I should have gotten
on someone's back.
Let's continue.
(The correct answer is
number 4, Gang Dong Won.)
(The one who gets the flag first
will win.)
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
(Suk Jin gets flag number 4.)
(Jong Kook blocked
the other players.)
There you go.
- He got the flag.
Suk Jin got the flag.
- Why couldn't you get it?
- I touched it.
This is our answer.
- Number four.
- Who?
(Who?)
- Number four?
- Who?
Don't tell him.
5, 4...
(You know it's Gang Dong Won,
right?)
Lee Bong Won?
(What?)
(His name ends with "Won" too,
but they're very different.)
It ends with "Won".
"Won"...
You're doing this on purpose, right?
- Lee Bong Won?
- Jong Kook is angry.
I gave you the chance.
- Gosh.
- It ends with "Won".
I know it ends with "Won".
- Lee Bong Won...
- Stop it.
I don't remember his name.
(Laughing)
Do the wave.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
Number four,
Gang Dong Won.
(Haha says the correct answer.)
(It's confusing.)
We can transfer two slaps, right?
Who should get it?
Hold on. Who should get it?
(Team New Identity can
transfer 2 slaps.)
- You should avoid finishing bottom.
- That's right.
- Give everything to one team.
- Right now...
Give it to New Identity.
Team Prosecutor has four.
- We're New Identity.
- Yes.
(Oh, right.)
(Thank you for the tip.)
- Let's give it to Prosecutor.
- Did you try to make us lose?
- Give it to them.
- We should give it to Prosecutor.
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
Why would you make things worse?
They have five now,
- and we have four.
- You're right.
Gosh.
I don't want to be on the same team
with Suk Jin.
1, 2, 3.
- Prosecutor.
(Team Prosecutor gets 2 slaps.)
We had   no choice.
If you hadn't said that, we might
have given it to another team.
(Team Prosecutor is at the bottom
with 5 slaps.)
This time,
you can transfer three slaps.
(You can transfer 3 slaps
for the last question.)
- 3 slaps?
- 3 slaps? Now, you're talking.
(Here goes the question.)
"Which of the following..."
(But...)
(What?)
(Puzzled)
- It's the other one.
(I was wondering
why my voice wasn't louder.)
Your Highness!
(Queen of Death makes
the members laugh.)
She thought the hammer was
the megaphone?
Ms. Bambi is the best!
They do look similar.
(Cute)
- You can transfer three slaps.
- Okay.
"In Greek mythology, this fairy..."
"has an upper body of a woman
and a lower body of a bird."
"Its singing voice lures sailors
to their deaths."
"There is also a sound device
that has the same name."
"Number one, megaphone."
"Number two, siren."
"Number three, speaker."
"Number four, amp."
Shout, "Long live Lee Sang Yeob!"
sincerely.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
- Long live Lee Sang Yeob!
(Sincere)
(Striding)
Hey, he moved.
Let me see your faces.
(Sang Yeob checks
if they look sincere.)
Kwang Soo moved.
He looks so sincere.
- Long live Lee Sang Yeob!
- Let's try again.
Kwang Soo looks so sincere.
- Yes, I am.
- I love your sincere face.
Let's try again.
Hold your shoe in your right hand.
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
Gosh.
(They all hold their shoes
in their right hands...)
(except Haha.)
(He manages to take his shoes off.)
It's your left hand.
The others are okay.
Put your shoe back on.
(Put your shoe back on.)
The rose of Sharon has bloomed
(Kwang Soo gets flag number 3.)
(Jae Suk stops him
from putting his shoe back on.)
I put it back on!
I put it back on! This is not okay.
(Meanwhile,)
(Ji Hyo gets flag number 2.)
- What's your answer?
- Number 2, siren.
(Confident)
(Ji Hyo has been doing well.
Is she correct this time too?)
It's correct!
(Ji Hyo's answer is correct.)
(She might become the quiz queen.)
(Team Cheon Sung Im can
give 3 slaps to another team.)
You can choose.
(Ugly Man 4, New Identity 3,
Prosecutor 5)
(Their decision will determine
which team finishes as the bottom.)
- What's your choice?
- Ji Hyo has made up her mind.
(Their decision will determine
which team finishes as the bottom.)
(Who will finish as the bottom
and be slapped?)
1, 2, 3.
- Team Ugly Man.
(We choose Team Ugly Man.)
Gosh. How could you?
Suk Jin was quiet this time.
You should be quiet.
Every time I'm on the same team
with Jae Suk,
I lose.
Don't you realize
I might think the same?
So Min.
We're not meant to be together.
(Cheon Sung Im 20, New Identity 10,
Prosecutor 5, Ugly Man 0)
- I mean...
- Eight slaps is too much.
- Please start.
- How do you do it?
- Splash the water on his face.
- You want the blue bowl?
- Seriously?
- It's okay.
- It's just water.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(Powerful)
(It's like a typhoon.)
(Sang Yeob splashes
the second bowl of water.)
Sa Yeon did a great job.
Seriously.
(This is so much fun.)
- I'm excited.
- She's excited.
Here we go.
One...
(Team Prosecutor is ready.)
2, 3.
(The sound is so loud.)
(Shocked)
Gosh.
- Suk Jin.
- Seriously.
What is this?
- So Min...
- Are you okay?
Seriously...
- I didn't know it'd be that strong.
- Is my nose bleeding?
(Confused)
Suk Jin should be slapped.
This is too much.
- You should be slapped too.
Why?
Do it later.
You should be slapped too.
- Why would I be slapped?
- You should be.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Here's my verdict.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin hit So Min too hard.
- That's right.
He should be punished for it.
You're really good at acting.
All of you can splash water on him.
I want to do it.
Let's all do it.
- Why are we doing this?
- I want to do it.
- Do it.
- You hit So Min way too hard.
Why should I get hit?
He's making me so angry.
1, 2, 3.
(Slap)
(Here's one.)
Goodness.
No.
(He gets six water bucket slaps.)
(Suk Jin becomes a new person.)
(Kwang Soo finishes.)
(He gets dizzy.)
Who went last?
(It hurts so much.)
Are you okay?
You were too harsh.
- Kwang Soo.
- What do you mean?
Why are you accusing me?
- How was I too harsh?
- Hey, you.
That was too harsh.
Who went last?
Kwang Soo also deserves
to get slapped.
Let's do it.
Wait a minute.
Hey, wait.
Suk Jin.
Boogers came out from his nose.
(He asked to blur the sight.)
He has boogers.
It was too harsh.
Wipe it off for him.
(Don't just stare at him.)
He's over 50 years old,
and his nose is running.
Suk Jin.
(Isn't he pitiful?)
Take care of Suk Jin.
- Okay?
- I saw him from afar.
I hoped it wasn't his booger.
But it really was.
You guys are worse. Come here.
I took care of him.
1, 2, 3.
Goodness.
(A loud thud)
(It's clear whose turn it is next
after Kwang Soo gets slapped.)
- Switch roles.
- Switch.
Switch roles.
- It was too harsh.
- He punched me.
- It feels like he punched me.
- Kwang Soo.
Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Are you okay?
- Hit Suk Jin.
- He's a terrible man.
- It felt like a punch.
- He's a gangster.
- It feels like I was punched.
This bucket is an apology.
- After this one, hug each other.
- Okay.
- Kiss each other on the cheek.
(It'll end the battle.)
1, 2, 3.
(A clear slap)
(I love you. Thank you,
Suk Jin.)
(It's heartwarming.)
No matter how much I think
(Kiss)
They did it.
(I'm sorry too.)
That's good.
We made up.
- Goodness.
- That's beautiful.
(They head to the next underworld.)
What's this?
Is it another trial?
There's another one.
- Is it another trial?
- It's another trial.
(What kind of trial awaits them?)
Give us your orders.
(The second underworld)
(Meal tickets and
Reincarnation Balls depend on it.)
The second trial will be held...
(Goodness)
(She hits herself
with her squeaky hammer.)
(It's very embarrassing.)
(Queen of Death's funny underworld
starts.)
That was a funny act.
- Are you okay?
- It was her funny act.
What do we do?
How did you do it?
In this way,
how many times can you make
people laugh?
Seriously.
It has various functions.
(I need to keep my face.)
The second trial will take place
in Greed Underworld.
Avoid it.
Greed Underworld.
It's a place for those
who harmed others out of greed.
Their time to get food
depends on their greed.
(Their time to get food
depends on their greed.)
(They must defend themselves
to enjoy the buffet.)
It's a buffet.
- There's a variety.
- It's a buffet.
(What will their sentences be?)
I'll punish Cheon Sung Im.
(Judge Suk Jin starts.)
- For what?
- What kind of greed?
What about me?
Cheon Sung Im is greedy about sleep.
- That's right.
- She sleeps too much.
(She feels nervous.)
She's famous for sleeping
on top of Jenga pieces.
(That day is memorable.)
(While playing a game
on top of Jenga pieces,)
(she takes a deep nap.)
(It's a nap that left
a mark in history.)
You should pay for sleeping.
I've been partners with Ji Hyo
quite often.
I talked to myself for 10 minutes.
I didn't know she was sleeping.
Her greed for sleep is...
It's a serious sin.
Something should be done.
- It's been long.
- She's too greedy for sleep.
She sleeps too much.
She's greedy about sleep.
What else?
As her representative...
(Kwang Soo has a chance
to defend Ji Hyo.)
I have nothing to say to defend it.
(As her representative,)
(her lawyer gives up.)
- You admit it?
- Yes.
- I see.
- I have nothing to say.
She sleeps so much.
She's greedy about sleep.
- Talk to us.
- Explain to us.
(Only Ji Hyo can turn it around.)
- I accept it to an extent.
- Really?
However,
I stopped myself from sleeping
as much as I could.
- Is that so?
- You did?
- How?
- I did my best.
- Really?
- She's greedy about sleep.
That's true.
Also...
(Suk Jin makes an accusation.)
I was very disappointed in Jae Suk
during our last shoot.
Why?
Instead of taking care
of his younger colleague...
Do you remember when
Kwang Soo took off his belt?
- That's right.
- Who grabbed it and ran away?
(Kwang Soo tries to sell his belt
to get money.)
(Kwang Soo is full of hopes.)
(Jae Suk takes it and runs away.)
(He runs after him
with all his might.)
(Falling off)
(His private life is revealed
unexpectedly.)
(Kwang Soo's tears fall
like his pants.)
- You took my belt.
- Why did you take it and run away?
It was worth money.
- It's like he stole money.
- He's a thief.
He's greedy.
He took Running Money and ran away.
- It was for himself.
- You said a good thing, Suk Jin.
Let me say something.
Do we actually get paid for that?
(Do we actually get paid
for the belt?)
- No, it's Running Money.
- No, right?
Did your pants fall off
because I took it?
They did.
Did you get on camera?
(Did you get on camera?)
(He's shown on camera
thanks to Jae Suk.)
If you say it that way,
there's nothing he can say.
He got one cut on the show.
Just because I took it,
does it bring me money or gold?
Wait, listen to me.
I didn't get on camera.
It was this part of my body.
I didn't get to be on camera.
- Listen.
- It was my crotch.
I was considering Kwang Soo.
However, because of what happened,
Kwang Soo did get on camera.
- My friends ask me.
- Ask you what?
If Kwang Soo is really a fool.
(He's being serious.)
(Anyone on Running Man
gets asked the same question.)
That's what happens.
- Right?
- Yes.
Even when my friends ask me that,
I don't say a word.
Why not?
Why wouldn't you say anything?
- You should deny it.
- You should.
You should say that I'm not.
- How can you say nothing?
- If...
If I say that he's not,
they'll think that I'm lying
because I'm close to him.
- They'll think you're lying?
- That's why...
- I don't say anything.
- Who thinks like that?
I don't say anything.
Let me ask you now.
Is Kwang Soo a fool or...
(She's serious.)
What are you talking about?
- It's ambiguous.
- From...
the perspective of someone
who cares about Kwang Soo,
let me tell you accurately.
Seriously.
We cannot say...
Kwang Soo isn't a fool.
- I see.
- What do you mean?
(Today's conclusion is that
we cannot say that he isn't a fool.)
- That's right.
- Kwang Soo.
- Honestly.
- How can you say that?
- Kwang Soo.
- That's even worse.
- It sounds stranger.
- We cannot say no.
- He's right.
- I agree.
- Okay.
- Next,
- it's Haha.
- Say it.
What about Haha?
- I'm not greedy at all.
- He isn't greedy at all.
- We get to say it today.
- It's time to say it.
- They're so serious.
- Haha.
(He says it carefully.)
He's ambitious about singing.
(He's ambitious about singing.)
- He's already a singer.
- That's not being greedy.
He's a singer.
He isn't a comedian.
He may simply like reggae
and other types of music.
Right.
However, he never sings live...
wherever he goes.
(He doesn't ever sing live.)
No, I've seen him.
I saw him recently.
You know what?
- He sang live.
- I've made music with Haha.
I also performed with him.
- Doesn't he sing live?
- I asked Haha...
to send me his accompaniment.
- And?
- I asked him to send it.
However, he sent me
his entire song.
- No.
- I asked for accompaniment.
- It was...
- The volume...
- What?
- was lower than AR.
Right, that's true.
(That's such a small detail.)
The recording of my accompaniment
includes my breathing.
(Haha defends himself.)
It sounds like I'm singing live.
- Really?
- He sings well live.
(Let's analyze Haha's recording
used for the performance.)
(Recording of "Dang Diggi Bang")
(It sounds like a recording
of Haha's singing.)
(It's definitely accompaniment
for performances.)
(Is it the secret behind
their live singing?)
I agree.
I use sound effects
more than others.
- Wait a minute.
- He says it's okay.
Apart from greed,
how can you humiliate
your colleague like that?
(That's not just greed.)
- This is not humiliating. Listen.
- Is it not?
- You are...
- How is that humiliating?
- asking him to compare the audio...
- Come on.
- and the accompaniment.
- How is that humiliating?
- You're humiliating him.
- Haha said it was okay.
- Are you all right?
- He said so.
His greed is
about humiliating others.
(He gets up.)
(He's the best in the underworld
for humiliating others.)
- I'll give him that.
- I agree.
I sometimes get confused.
I can't tell if he's serious
or if he's joking.
- I get confused too.
- If he's funny, it's a joke.
- But if he's not, it's my fault.
- I agree.
No, that's not true.
This is his crime. Please be aware.
- All right.
- I get it.
I'll be persistent.
Queen of Death has made
wise decisions so far.
We made our points.
(What's the mission
before the final ruling?)
"The plates that will be used are
small dishes for soy sauce,"
"regular plates,
and buffet plates."
"There are three different plates
at various distances."
It's all different.
What would you eat
with such a small dish?
"For your reference, the losing team
will have to carry me..."
"when we are going
to the final location,"
"so please keep that in mind."
(If you lose,)
(you will get the honor of carrying
Queen of Death.)
(Jong Kook can't keep
a straight face at the news.)
That's the biggest penalty.
(He can't read the situation.)
- That is...
- What?
- It was him.
- That's rude.
- You've been doing this all day.
- You are so clueless.
What is wrong with you?
(He's clueless, and Queen of Death
doesn't like him. What will happen?)
From this side, it's small dish,
regular plate, small dish,
and the red area is
for the buffet plate.
- This...
- This is too...
There's a bomb.
You're telling us to choose
a regular plate.
- Exactly.
- I know.
- Go first.
- Let's go.
- Haha.
- Haha, go for the regular one.
I'm hungry.
You don't have to go for
the small dish.
Which one are you picking?
He's going to be a coward
and go for the regular one.
He's going to be a coward.
Go for it. Come on, Haha.
- Good luck.
- What if he can't reach?
He got it.
You're tough.
Don't grab it too high.
- You look like a gymnast.
- Swing more.
- That's more than enough.
Swing more.
(Many people are cheering for him.
How far will he jump?)
- No...
- That's not enough.
- Swing more. That's not enough.
- No...
But...
(What?)
- Regular plate.
- No, that's not enough.
(He got near the buffet plate.)
(Why is he doing a somersault?)
- Regular plate.
- Small dish.
(He goes back to where he belongs.)
(I jumped far. Why am I here?)
Goodness.
(This is why
it's called Greed Underworld.)
Small dish.
- It's a small dish.
- Why is nothing working out?
- It is.
You landed on the small dish
in the end.
- It's a small dish.
- I...
So Min, do you want to go,
or should I go?
- You should go.
- Okay.
But Jae Suk is going to land
on the small dish.
He has a small heart.
He'll get a small dish too.
- He has good arm strength though.
- That's right. You never know.
All right. Regular plate.
(What's going on with Jae Suk?)
The grasshopper is flying.
He's flying.
- Good luck, Jae Suk.
- Good.
- I think he can do it.
- Look at his face.
(He jumps at the highest point.)
(His heels...)
(land on the buffet plate.)
- He crossed it.
- He made it.
(With a clean jump,
he lands on the buffet plate.)
- He got it.
- He went over it.
- I did this.
- My heels were on it.
- He went over it.
Your heels were on it, so I accept.
Okay!
Weren't we supposed to stand on it
for five seconds?
- Exactly.
- I'm going.
- It's an advantage for Kwang Soo.
- There's too much advantage.
- He has big feet.
- His feet can't touch.
All right.
(I trust you, Kwang Soo.)
(Swinging)
- Your feet can't touch.
- They can't.
- Oh, dear.
- Wait.
(Tickling)
Wait. You can't do this.
- Don't do that.
- Your feet can't touch.
- I said your feet can't touch.
- Take your time.
- Your feet can't touch.
- He's ticklish.
- Kwang Soo, your feet...
- You can't do this. Hold on.
- Kwang Soo...
(Kwang Soo falls
without getting a try.)
- Hold on. What do I do?
- Your feet can't touch.
- You can't do that.
- It's a rule.
- That's cheating.
- How's this a rule?
- I think he's really ticklish.
- Kwang Soo.
- He can endure it.
- He can.
- I can try.
- If you can endure it, I accept.
- But I...
- Why would you fall?
- I'll do the same as before.
- Do whatever.
(He's confident.)
- We'll try it on him.
- Go ahead. I'm fine.
- Jong Kook.
- Do more.
- I'm totally fine.
- See? He's fine.
- He's fine.
- Do more.
- I tickled him more.
- I'm totally fine.
I feel like my nails will fall off,
so I can't do more.
(Suddenly)
(He's mad.)
(I don't know anymore.)
(The tiger's privacy gets exposed.)
- I'm mad.
- What are you doing?
- You brat.
My bad.
I'm so sorry. I got so mad.
(Everybody gets awkward
all of a sudden.)
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I got so mad.
I'm so sorry.
- Jong Kook.
- I'm sorry.
Hey, So Min was in front of me.
She was right in front of me.
- Why are you sitting here?
- Hey.
I didn't see it. I'm so unlucky.
Can you do it again?
- I couldn't help it.
- Are you out of your mind?
I was so mad
that I couldn't help it.
- I'm sorry.
- You're out.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook's teams
both fail the 1st attempt.)
- I'll go.
- Go ahead, Jong Kook.
Sorry, but I have a trauma.
- What happened earlier...
- I'll stay far away.
I'll stay far away.
I have a trauma.
- Go first, Jong Kook.
- Oh, gosh.
- Don't do it again.
- He's focusing.
You have to jump
farther than you think.
- Good luck, Jong Kook.
- You can do it.
You can do it, Jong Kook.
(This is his last chance to overcome
the trauma and get a buffet plate.)
This is not easy.
It's not easy to land on it.
(He's redetermined.
What's the result?)
It's not easy to land on it.
Okay, he's not even close.
It's here. It's a small dish.
(His heels don't touch, and
his toes land on the small dish.)
It's a small dish.
It's a small dish for sure.
You have to jump
farther than you think.
- It's a small dish.
- Hey, what is wrong with you?
You have to jump
farther than you think.
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook
get a small dish.)
- Give it a try.
- Be serious.
- You have to swing more.
- Let's go.
- This is enough.
- The angle is tricky.
(Suk Jin's negative view
always brings the opposite result.)
(There's a good vibe.
Will he get a satisfying result?)
Okay. It's perfect.
(He lands inside the buffet area.)
The angle is tricky.
(It's a perfect landing.)
(It's perfect technique.)
It's perfect.
- Do you approve? That looked cool.
- That was awesome.
- That was amazing.
- He approves.
(Of course the staff approves.)
Did you do gymnastics?
(Haha and Se Chan's small dishes
get upgraded to buffet plates.)
Okay. We'll go too.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'll go.
(Despite his superior physique,
he was retired by being tickled.)
- If your feet touch, it's over.
- He's serious.
- Kwang Soo...
- He can reach here.
(He swings with his entire body.)
He looks serious.
He might go over it.
(He's very serious.)
- Why are you creaking?
- Kwang Soo...
- You'll get tired.
- You need to swing more.
He's getting lower.
(His arms run out of energy.)
His feet touched.
(His feet touch,
and he's disqualified.)
That's too low.
(He had a good swing,)
(but he dragged himself.)
(That's too low.)
That's too low!
(What am I supposed to do?)
(He's too tall for the equipment,
so he's disqualified.)
- Other people's feet don't touch.
- It's okay.
- Their feet won't touch.
- It's over.
I tried to jump,
but it stopped me!
It's over.
- I tried to jump, but I stopped.
- It's over.
- Can they not eat?
- They can't.
You should have made...
- It's over.
- Is it? Fine.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
His feet touched.
(Results from Fiery Pit of Greed)
- They look so good.
- There's pork.
- Oh, dear.
- This looks so good.
Is that bulgogi?
(The food is unlimited within the
allocated time using your plates.)
- Is it our turn?
- That's pretty.
Time starts
when you pick up the first tong.
- All right. Is it seven seconds?
- It is.
We can't eat at all.
- So Min, we have to skip these.
- Ready,
set, go.
What do you want?
- Pork cutlet.
- Help him.
- Help him, So Min.
- Dumplings, Jae Suk.
- Dumplings. Jae Suk.
- Is it just one person?
No, they can both do it.
(He was listening to So Min,
and 7 seconds are over.)
- It's done.
- Stop.
- Take the last two out.
- So Min, why are you watching?
- You should have helped.
- No, only one person can do it.
- That was it.
- That's right.
- Is it just one person?
- Can't both do it?
- Why did he do it alone?
- Why was she watching?
- Come on.
- Wasn't it just one person?
We thought it was one person,
so she didn't do it.
- Wasn't it one person?
- That's what she thought.
- That's your fault for not knowing.
- 10 seconds.
- Let's take our time.
- Start.
We could have done that too.
Come here. Move.
- Move.
- Hurry.
You have to take that out.
Take your hands off.
Wait, what's that?
Get away from it.
We're next.
I'm looking forward to this.
It's a small dish.
Five seconds with the small dish.
- We can both do it, right?
- We can.
- We're starting. Get ready.
- Okay.
- Ready,
- Hold on.
- start.
- One...
(What?)
(Are they putting a bowl
on top of the small dish?)
(No way.)
- Oh, dear.
- Get more.
Don't be greedy.
(5 seconds are over in shock.)
You have to put that down.
(That's plenty.)
(He's satisfied.)
- That's good.
- He did it.
That was a great idea.
They got the most.
- That's shocking.
- This is our birthday.
- This is a birthday cake.
- See?
Amazing.
That's why I don't like
playing games with him.
(He's sick of it.)
Why not?
- Why?
It feels like we lost.
There's so much.
- Enjoy.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo starved,
and they have a job to do.)
I'm confident.
- Do we start now?
- Yes.
- Don't fall.
- Of course not.
- I trust you.
- Yes.
(He's shocked.)
(He can't speak.)
Oh, gosh.
Stand up.
(The Queen had a lot to eat.)
Let's go.
(That's our queen.)
It feels great to be
on Kwang Soo's back.
Are you doing good, Queen of Death?
- Yes, this is great.
- This is funny.
Thank you.
(She doesn't know how he feels
and starts moving.)
I'm lighter than you thought, right?
I'm as light as a feather.
- Yes, I mean it.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm as light as a feather, right?
- I swear.
- Push her up.
1, 2, 3.
Push.
(He almost saw real Grim Reapers
for a second.)
You're lighter than...
It's just hot.
It's like I'm on an elevator.
This feels like
I'm on top of a tower.
I can see everything. This is wide.
(If there is a fiery pit,)
(this must be it.)
Your weight...
That's good. You can put me down.
- Sorry?
- That's good.
- Do I put you down?
- No, not here.
- Why are you so sweaty, Kwang Soo?
- It's hot.
(Shaking)
Oh, dear.
(We're here.)
I'm okay. I'm totally okay.
We came far.
(It looks like he went between
this world and the underworld.)
I saw a new side of you.
(Coughing)
(I... I'm totally okay.)
I'm really okay.
(What will happen to the deceased
and the Grim Reapers?)
- What's this?
- What kind of underworld is this?
(They get to the final underworld.
Something is floating on the pool.)
- Is this the last one?
- It is.
There are short and long ones.
(There are short and long weapons.
What's this underworld about?)
"The last trial will be held..."
"in Fist Underworld."
(Final round: Fist Underworld)
Fist Underworld.
- "Fist Underworld"?
- Fists.
Fists.
There's only one person here
who uses his fists.
What do you mean?
- He's on the top.
- I don't use my fists.
- He hit me earlier.
- What?
He did this and thrusted at me.
- My arm almost fell off.
- He does that a lot.
- That's a massage.
Back in the day,
I don't know how things are now,
but school bullies would...
punch you, and...
- Right here.
- What did you say?
School bullies did that a lot.
And only the bully found it funny.
- They were entertained by it.
- Right.
"Look at that."
"That's the spot, right?"
"You'll be able to
move it less today."
I think Jae Suk got that
done to him a lot.
- You are all laughing.
- I see.
To best honest,
when it comes to fists,
(She's being honest.)
I can't deny it.
- Right? Way back when...
- I know.
She's known for using her fists too.
I admit it,
but Jong Kook is just as bad.
- Why?
- You're almost as bad as me.
- Me?
- I think so.
So you take the smallest one.
(She decides to give him
the smallest weapon.)
The rest of you can take
the long ones.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Do you admit it or not?
- Do you admit it or not?
- The short one...
(Do you admit it or not?)
Do you admit it or not?
Your fist...
She looks so natural
with the weapon.
You can't use the weapon.
- Just admit it already.
- I admit.
This is the final mission.
We'll start Floating Boxing.
"Floating Boxing"?
It's a tournament format
with two teams playing at a time.
One person moves the float,
while the other person attacks
the opponent with their weapon.
The team that makes the opponent
fall in the water wins.
We got this.
You're tall,
so there's an advantage.
You can attack from far away.
(This is their last chance
to collect Reincarnation Balls.)
(When the whistle is blown
while they dance,)
(the first 2 teams to get the floats
get a match with each other.)
(They dance and observe
at the same time.)
As long as
Jong Kook doesn't go on it.
(They all want to avoid him.)
(They're trying to get this float
and avoid Jong Kook.)
(Round 1 of Floating Boxing starts.)
Go on it.
(Se Chan gets on a float
as soon as the game starts.)
Se Chan.
- Did he go on it?
- Don't go on yet. Watch Jong Kook.
(They want anybody but Jong Kook
to go on the other one.)
(He looks around and hesitates.)
(Se Chan is better than Jong Kook.)
- Did he go on it?
- Don't go on yet. Watch Jong Kook.
(I'll go on then.)
It's not bad to go first.
If we don't go on now,
we'll have to play Jong Kook.
(He avoided Jong Kook,
so that's a plus.)
(The opponents have been set.)
Ready...
(Team New Identity
versus Team Cheon Sung Im)
- Good luck.
- You have to direct me.
It's shallow.
(There's tension in the air
for round one.)
(Splashing)
(They start cheating
like people of no class.)
- Come on. Cut it out.
- They're splashing.
Goodness.
(How messy.)
Look at those weaklings.
Water punch.
You need to use your weapons.
Such cowards.
(Pushing)
(Haha pushes it all of a sudden.)
What is he supposed to do?
Let's move back.
Hold on.
(Why did you push it, Haha?)
Stop. I'm dizzy.
(Go back when I'm getting punched.)
What are you doing, Haha?
Go back when he's getting punched!
(There's a big difference
in the length of their arms.)
(He keeps on getting hit,
and something occurs to him.)
(Mother,
why did you make me so short?)
(It's the first time he's envious of
Kwang Soo's long arms.)
(His arms are short,
and the bigger problem...)
He keeps on getting hit.
(is that Haha is a horrible driver.)
Hold on, Haha. I keep getting hit.
He moves back when Se Chan attacks
and stays still otherwise.
He's Inspector Gadget.
(He stretches out his long arms.)
Oh, gosh.
(His face turns ugly
as he receives more punches.)
- Kwang Soo.
- My fist...
(Se Chan's one last attack fails.)
(Sandbag Se Chan
falls in the water.)
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo move on
to the final round.)
- Kwang Soo wins.
- Good job, Kwang Soo.
(Haha is ashamed.)
Jong Kook will hit him
in the final round.
(He tries to comfort Se Chan.)
(Are you kidding me?)
This game...
- makes the loser look ugly.
- One of them will go up?
- This is short, so...
- Give us the weapons.
He's not within reach.
That's true.
So Min, you have to do good. Don't
go near him. He can't reach you.
Let's go.
We have to stick
the floats together.
We'll do out boxing from far away.
(In-fighter versus out-boxer)
Bring it to the middle.
(They meet on a single bridge.
Who will be the winner?)
Don't stick to him. Move back.
- Hold on.
- Move back, So Min.
Hit him.
(He moves back
and hits with his long weapon.)
(You call that a punch?)
- He dodged.
- Move back.
- Use the entire space.
It's boxing.
(How do I beat him?)
Ugly Man, 1, 2.
Was that an attack?
(Jae Suk is cornered.
What is he supposed to do?)
Take this.
(He splashes water
at Jong Kook's eyes.)
(The cheater starts to play dirty.)
You were criticizing them earlier
for splashing water.
We're all the same.
Stick the floats together.
Hey, take this.
What are you doing?
(He punishes So Min
for the dirty play.)
It's too short.
Suk Jin, you need to
change the direction.
You have to come this way.
(Hitting)
Come back.
Why are you hitting me?
(Jae Suk hits Suk Jin
out of nowhere.)
(Why are you hitting me?)
(He distracts them
by attacking Suk Jin...)
Go for it.
(and attempts
to attack Jong Kook.)
Good job.
(Try to hit me if you can.)
Where are you taking me?
Let's go.
(The out-boxer gets cornered again.)
- Hold on properly. He's cornered.
- Move back, So Min.
He's cornered.
(There's nowhere to hide.
This is war now.)
Hit his face, Jae Suk.
(He tries to get out of trouble
by being annoying.)
(If he takes too long,
he might lose.)
(Jong Kook moves
to the other float.)
(In-fighter Jong Kook tries to
get on the other float.)
(He decides to fight close-up.
What is the result?)
(Hitting)
(Jae Suk gains victory!)
(When Jong Kook lost balance,
Jae Suk pushed him slightly.)
(There's nobody you cannot defeat.)
Goodness. How could this be?
How could this be?
Didn't you get lucky?
- What do you mean?
- He just got lucky.
- He did it.
- It's okay.
I overcame a big obstacle.
That's so true.
(Team Ugly Man overcomes
the huge obstacle and advances.)
(Team New Identity versus
Team Prosecutor for 3rd place)
We'll play each other.
Bring it on.
(This is going to be a cute match.)
Mapo Cotton Punch...
and Suyu-ri Honey Punch
finally meet.
I'm so curious
how this will turn out.
- I'll make sure you don't get hit.
- This is going to be the highlight.
This is a battle
between a spear and a shield.
(Do you remember?
We created all those highlights.)
(They're both bad, so their battles
were always sorrowful to watch.)
(They were both winners back then,
but the loser gets decided today.)
What? Look at me.
Are you intimidated?
("Dang Diggi Bang" plays
for the super match.)
You have to do this.
(Here it goes again.)
I'm sick of this.
(Get your reggae swag ready.)
(His dance is as fierce as ever.)
Dance, dance.
(It's a fun reggae party
in the underworld.)
(He shows his passion
in the highlight.)
(Whistling)
Hold on. He exhausted his energy.
- You have a chance of winning.
- Get up here.
Even if you have a short glove,
you have a chance of winning.
My goodness, there he goes.
Go to the left.
Stick out your glove.
I am a big fan of their fight.
(Haha throw punches
with his long weapon.)
He became lively.
(What is this liveliness?)
Know that my punches will hurt.
(Let's put an end to this rivalry.)
He is determined.
(Smacking)
(Haha hits Suk Jin in the stomach.)
My goodness.
Suk Jin has no chance of winning.
(I am scared. Stop it.)
Don't hit so hard.
Can't you see this?
(Suk Jin is at a disadvantage
in both spirit and weapon.)
(He attempts a close combat.)
(Let's see if Suk Jin's attack
will be a success.)
(His legs are short as well.)
Okay!
(He goes into the water,)
(not onto the float.)
Okay!
(Team Prosecutor comes in last...)
(and Team New Identity
comes in 3rd.)
- Let's go.
- This is the final match.
Okay.
(Team Ugly Man
versus Team Cheon Sung Im)
(It's a match
between the female members.)
- I've never seen this before.
- We've never seen this before.
- This is the first time, right?
- Yes.
- Do this right.
- Let's go.
I have no idea who will win.
- That picture makes this scarier.
- Ji Hyo is strong.
This is the final.
Ji Hyo is strong.
This is Ji Hyo's past.
(It's hard to meet eyes
with the woman in the picture.)
Look at that hairstyle. She's scary.
It's a delinquent's hairstyle.
- Get ready.
- Look at the picture.
(The war between the queens starts.)
She has a chance.
That was strong.
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo lands a strong punch first.)
She has a chance.
- Stab her.
- You can do this.
So Min is intimidated.
I can tell from her face.
So Min, go.
(So Min counterattacks,
but Ji Hyo blocks it with her hand.)
(So Min,
you can't win against me.)
(She attacks
when So Min is staggering.)
- So Min, go.
- Get her off of the float.
- Ji Hyo.
- Get me closer.
- I will do that.
Jae Suk, let's run away.
- My goodness.
- Run away.
Corner her.
So Min, jump over to her float
if everything fails.
(So Min, jump over to her float
if everything fails.)
(Se Chan is right.)
(This isn't working.)
Attack!
(It's time for a close combat.)
(You can do this, So Min.)
Attack!
(Is she stretching her legs?)
(She plops into the water.)
(Her ambitious attempt
ends as a slapstick comedy.)
(This isn't what I had in mind.)
So Min lost.
I thought So Min's legs would rip.
So Min, are you okay?
(The lively and funny
final match ends.)
- Seriously.
- For goodness' sake.
You fell face-first into the water.
She was like Jong Kook.
(The female Kim Jong Kook wins
20 Reincarnation Balls.)
Ji Hyo is really strong.
Seriously.
Her strength rivals that of a man.
(Team Cheon Sung In has 40,
Team Ugly Man has 30,)
(Team New Identity has 20,
and Team Prosecutors has 5.)
Here are the Reincarnation Balls
you have collected.
Put the Reincarnation Balls
in a machine for a lottery.
A team reincarnates
when its ball comes out.
If the chosen team's ball
comes out again,
it's a lost chance
for the other teams.
(Then the lottery moves on
to the next round.)
A single team might get chosen
three times in a row.
In that case,
only one team will be saved.
Team Prosecutor
doesn't have a chance.
- There are three chances, right?
- Yes.
You never know.
That's right. We should have hope.
- Please.
- I don't see my name anywhere.
It says, "Prosecutors".
- Really?
- 1 to 3 teams will get chosen.
- That's right.
- All right.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Please press the button.
Press it gently.
- Press it gently.
- It came out!
- It came out.
- Whose name is on it?
- I didn't see it.
I didn't see it either.
(If the deceased's name is on it,
both team members reincarnate.)
- The first team to reincarnate...
- Which team is it?
On which side is the team?
(On which side is the team?)
Okay!
- It's on that side.
- That side?
It could be us.
- Do you want to know?
- Yes.
(Which team is
on the first Reincarnation Ball?)
Song Ji Hyo!
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Thanks to the lucky Ji Hyo,)
(even the unlucky Grim Reaper
reincarnates.)
Will the next ball belong
to Ji Hyo as well?
We are done!
It's time to pick the second ball.
(It's time to pick the second ball.)
If Ji Hyo's ball comes out again...
- Please.
- Haha! Haha!
- Jae Suk.
All right. Push.
(If Ji Hyo's ball comes out again,
other teams lose their chance.)
(Team Ugly Man has
30 Reincarnation Balls.)
Please let it be us.
Team Prosecutors.
(Team Prosecutors has
5 Reincarnation Balls.)
Yoo Jae Suk!
(Yoo Jae Suk)
(They reincarnate
with 30 Reincarnation Balls.)
- No way.
- Congratulations.
- Did a different ball come out?
- We reincarnated.
For goodness' sake.
- Did that really happen?
- Let's go this way.
(I wish I had won
more Reincarnation Balls.)
We should have won in the last game.
Let us tell you
when to press the button.
- When we say, "Now!"
- We have a good feeling about this.
- Okay.
- Sure.
(Let's try anything we can.)
The last team will be chosen.
Let's go.
- I love you.
- Haha.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Stop!
(This is it.)
- Okay.
- Okay, it's stopped.
You were a bit late.
The timing was off.
- That wasn't very clean.
- It was a bit off.
You stopped the machine.
Why did they get to stop
the machine?
- We have 20 Reincarnation Balls.
- Do you want to do it?
- Do it.
- You should do it then.
(While the two teams are arguing...)
You already did it.
Shall we do it again?
If it's one of the chosen teams...
It isn't.
It's not one of the chosen teams.
(It's either Team New Identity
or Team Prosecutors.)
- Really?
- Is it one of us?
Queen of Death.
(In Queen of Death's hands...)
(lies the fate
of the last chosen team.)
(20 Reincarnation Balls
versus 5 Reincarnation Balls)
Haha!
- No way!
- Are you serious?
(Probability saves
Team New Identity.)
(All teams with the deceased
reincarnate.)
- For real?
- All the deceased were chosen.
(All teams with the deceased
reincarnate.)
My goodness.
We all got reincarnated.
All the deceased got to reincarnate.
(What's the penalty?)
Since the prosecutors failed
to reincarnate,
they must gather
three drops of tears of repentance.
Do they need to cry?
Will this make us cry?
We will cry in no time.
Open your eyes wide.
- I am not sure about this.
- Since we are tired,
we will shed tears in no time.
(He puts the onion near his eyes.)
Will this make me shed tears?
Maybe your eyes are too dry.
(Jong Kook is in tears already.)
I think it went in.
Big drops of tears fell just now.
Look.
They are falling.
I can't see it.
- Look at this.
- You are shedding tears.
They are falling, right?
Mom!
(Mother, I promise
to reincarnate into a good son.)
Mom!
I am going to think
about something sad.
about parting ways with my wife.
Suk Jin, you look too happy.
(Suk Jin, you look too happy.)
(I am not really laughing.)
Suk Jin, you look too happy.
No, it's sad.
The idea of parting ways
with my wife is really sad.
(Laughing)
(He is so sad
that he lost his mind.)
It's sad.
Does thinking about it
make you happy?
No, it's heartbreaking.
It's unthinkable.
(I am sure you will know
how I feel if you get married.)
- I think it's working.
- I gathered a lot of tears.
Look at this, Suk Jin.
(Jong Kook quickly succeeds
to gather three drops of tears.)
- You've succeeded.
- Aren't those just two drops?
- Okay!
- I am in tears, right?
Okay!
Tears won't come out.
This is driving me crazy.
You have no emotions.
You must be a robot.
(He even puts the onion on his eye.)
Why won't my tears come out?
That's so strange.
Why won't your tears come out?
(Suk Jin struggles with the onions
until late at night.)
(Next week)
(Suk Jin gets a question.)
Truth or dare?
(I choose dare.)
(Ji Suk Jin is out.)
Am I really out?
(Suk Jin is out after
only 20 minutes into the shoot.)
Is he out?
(Also,)
(they get locked...)
(inside a room.)
(There is only one way to escape.)
(Truth or dare)
(The tantalizing truth
they want to hide)
(They expose each other
in order to escape.)
(I did...)
(Face the dangerous truth...)
(or choose the harsh dare.)
(A desperate attempt to escape)
(The game slowly gets unveiled.)
(How will this game end?)
(Another truth visits Running Man.)
(A charming and talented actress,
Lee Elijah)
(A rising scene stealer, E Xi A)
(A multi-talented actress,
Lee Ju Yeon)
(A national comedienne, Kim Ji Min,
and a charming singer, Sun Mi)
(Bobby and B.I of iKON,
and Seung Ri, the great Seungtsby)
(The Dangerous Choice Special,
Truth or Dare)