(Previously)
(Get Your Number Eights began.)
(Will the winner be getting amazing benefits?)
(The winner will be able to change the profile of every member.)
(For 8 long days, he will be able to change it however he wants to.)
(He could put a photo of grasshopper on Jae Seok's profile.)
(It's easy to become the winner.)
(The first 3 people who get the number 8 will go to the finals.)
(The final mission will determine the winner.)
(Hoping to win, they came up with ideas for the profiles.)
(The members' competition gets out of hand.)
(Which would be the most extraordinary idea?)
I came up with a lot of ideas.
(The board is packed.)
Jong Kook is "Sulky"...
- and "Hong Jin Young's boyfriend". - What?
For the latter one, I will put a photo of Jin Young.
Jin Young... You should ask Jin Young for permission.
I will choose the photo of her doing this. "You!"
I plan to choose that photo.
He shouldn't win.
Kwang Soo will be "Beanpole".
- So... - I hate this even more.
I will put a photo of a really tall tree.
I will make that his profile picture.
And another one is "Stop, Song Joong Ki."
It means he's coming after him.
- It's his goal. - No matter what happens,
I will stop him from winning.
"The Accidental Detective 2: In Action" was successful.
That movie had three million audience mark.
- My gosh. - Dong Il and Sang Woo...
- brought in about 1.5 million each. - 1.5 million each.
- Right. - What about me?
(His fellow actors each brought in 1.5 million audience.)
(What about me then?)
- Did I bring in zero viewers? - You did your best.
You promoted it.
- Okay. Fine. - Calm down.
- But you did well for a cameo. - Right.
(Haha praises him.)
- You did really well. - You did well for a cameo.
Why was I a cameo?
The director was generous enough to give you a lot of parts.
I grew my hair for a year just for that. Why am I a cameo?
Stop it.
That's it for me.
Let's check mine.
- Haha is "Ha the Coward". - "Ha the Coward".
- Okay. Yes. - Do you accept it?
Kwang Soo is... He was "Asia's Prince" before.
Are you done with Haha?
(Is he done with Haha?)
I am done with Haha. Why?
- It's boring. That's all. - Why?
(He's utterly honest.)
(Seok Jin hits him.)
(One attacks with facts and another physically attacks.)
- It's boring. - Just listen.
- It's just that it's too boring. - Is everything you do fun?
- There's no wit. - Is everything you do fun?
Jae Seok tilted his head.
If you say that, it will sound boring.
- We will listen some more. - Wait.
Kwang Soo was previously known as "Asia's Prince".
(Yawning)
Now everyone thinks I am boring.
He was previously known as "Asia's Prince".
So Min is "Fart".
("Fart".)
Will you really do this?
- Will you not react? - But "Fart" is...
What is "Fart"?
- You have to react. - You...
You have to let us be able to react.
You have to work, you know?
- Let us be able to react. - All right.
Wait. There's something amazing coming up.
Wake me when that amazing thing comes up.
(He goes to sleep.)
Seok Jin is desperate.
(He finishes presenting his ideas.)
(Who will be the winner that will actually get to use these ideas?)
- I want it. - I want it too.
All right. This is the 1st mission to win 8.
You have to find acquaintances that are related to eight.
- What? - That are related to eight?
Acquaintances?
(Acquaintances related to 8?)
- I don't have friends. - You will be given...
4 keywords. The 2 people who choose...
the same keyword will cast a guest who meet the requirements.
Then you will have a match against the guest.
The winning member will be given an eight.
Really?
- 2 people will compete? - 2 people will compete?
We will be competing.
It's really important whom you become a team with.
I have to win.
Before we begin the race, let's play Pick a Suitcase...
to win the 1st 8s.
- What? - The 1st 8s.
- They are offering the 1st 8s. - I need to start with them.
In these eight suitcases,
there are 1, 3, or 5 of them.
You can start with five of them from the start?
The person who picks the case with five will be the winner.
- He will surely win. - That's amazing.
I need to choose it.
(They laugh.)
How can you with that unlucky hand of yours?
It amuses me that he manages to have such expectations.
I will pick it. Watch me.
- All right. - Let's go find the case with five.
(Who will be picking the case with 5 cards of number 8?)
Let's do this.
I will choose the last one remaining.
I can't trust my hands.
Let's change.
No. No. I am certain that this has five cards.
It's obvious. This has five cards.
- Yes. - You can't see it.
(Who will get 5 cards and who will get 1 card?)
(As Jae Seok wished, he got 5 cards.)
(He tries to keep a poker face.)
(Who will be getting the other case with five cards?)
(It's Se Chan.)
I'm the winner.
Don't laugh.
If you get five cards, you will most likely win.
(Kwang Soo gets...)
(1 card.)
Okay. Okay. Okay.
(He's flustered.)
(The other person who got as unlucky as Kwang Soo...)
(is Seok Jin.)
This is it.
(We have a feeling that today will be another bad day for him.)
(Jae Seok and Se Chan get 5 cards of number 8.)
(Jong Kook, So Min, Haha, and Ji Hyo get 3 cards.)
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin get 1 card.)
You will choose a keyword related to eight.
Choose one.
(The 2 people who choose the same keyword will form a team.)
All of them have different colors, right?
All right. Can we open these?
Yes. Open and check them.
Whom would I go with?
- I have a bad feeling. - What? "Celebrity born in August"?
My gosh.
(Is it you again?)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin have to cast a celebrity born in August.)
I got the same one as Ji Hyo. "Celebrity who's won 8 awards".
You got "Celebrity who's won 8 awards"?
(Haha and Ji Hyo have to cast a celebrity who's won 8 awards.)
"Someone who's worked on a title with 'eight' in it."
There's no such work. Which movie or TV show has eight in the title?
(They have to cast someone who's worked on a title with 8 in it.)
"A celebrity with a perfectly proportioned body". Great.
But it's...
Okay, Se Chan!
(Why is it me again?)
Okay! Nice! I will be with Jong Kook today.
(They will cast a celebrity with a perfectly proportioned body.)
- You're with me! - Yes! Jong Kook!
(They will now start casting the keyword-related guests.)
I am with Ji Hyo again!
(Each team's mission)
Let's go.
I have to wear the belt.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan's awkward partnership begins.)
- Okay. - Yes, Jong Kook.
("Yes, Jong Kook"?)
When I say "okay", you should say "okay" too.
Why would you say "Yes, Jong Kook"?
- It means it's great. - It lowers the energy.
- Okay. Okay. - Okay. Okay.
- Great. - Great.
(Jong Kook is happy again.)
- What do we do now? - What do we do?
You need to start casting people.
- Is that right? - Someone with a perfect body.
- Wait. - Okay.
(Let's see who's there.)
- Perfectly proportioned body? - Wouldn't...
Wouldn't they be models or actors?
(He thinks carefully.)
Should I give Bo Gum a call?
(He thinks of calling Bo Gum.)
- Bo Gum? - Really?
He certainly has a perfectly proportioned body.
Bo Gum has a perfectly proportioned body.
(He calls Bo Gum.)
- Hello? - Bo Gum.
- Yes, hello. - Have you been well?
Are you well?
Yes. I am doing well.
Bo Gum, actually, we are shooting Running Man.
Don't walk. Run. Running Man.
(He's too excited to talk to Bo Gum.)
You know Yang Se Chan, right? He's right next to me.
Hello. I am Yang Se Chan.
- Hello. - I am your big fan, Bo Gum.
- Bo Gum. - I am your fan too.
Yes. We have to find a celebrity with a perfectly proportioned body.
We are given a mission to complete.
Your face to body ratio is about 1 to 8, right? Is it 1 to 9?
No, it's not 1 to 8.
- What's wrong with you? - Come on.
Don't be humble.
What's wrong with you? What are you doing?
(Will Bo Gum be willing to join them?)
(What are you doing right now, Bo Gum?)
I am on the way to the office.
- To the office? You are good. - Right.
Why are you going to the office? For work?
I have a meeting today.
- I see. - Meeting is good.
Have the meeting then.
Thank you for answering my call.
- No problem. - Always...
The weather is really hot. Take care of yourself.
You are so good.
- You are such a good man. - Take care of your health.
- I will call you again. - Thank you.
By the way, your face to body radio is 1 to 9.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Thank you, Jong Kook.
You mostly asked all the questions,
and Bo Gum gave short answers. So I only heard your voice.
I wanted to hear his voice.
- Hey. - It's just that it's a shame.
You kept talking.
- Whose fan are you? - I wanted to hear his voice.
- Whose fan are you? - I am your fan.
- How dare you say that? - You are my fan, and yet...
- You talked t0o much. - You are the president of...
Kim Jong Kook celebrity fan club.
- Am I the president? - You are.
- Really? - Yes, act like one.
I do, but I just wanted to hear Bo Gum's voice.
He's been on many dramas.
Right. But still...
- It would've been great if he came. - We're not that close.
- All right. Let's call this guy. - Okay.
- It's Loco. - Loco?
- Yes. - "Above Live"?
- Yes, Loco. - Goodness, Loco.
- The phone is turned off. - His phone is turned off.
- He must've had too much to drink. - He's probably sleeping now.
Should I give Dong Wook a call?
Yes, let's call him.
- He's favorable toward our show. - That's right.
(Calling Dong Wook)
Gosh, I can't reach him.
That leaves us no choice, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, we have no choice. I'll just call this person.
- Who is it? - It's...
It's our secret weapon. I'll call now.
(Who is Jong Kook and Se Chan's secret weapon?)
A lot of celebrities were born in August.
Yes.
- Eun Ji was born in August. - Se Hyeong was born in August.
- Se Hyeong? - Yes, Yang Se Hyeong.
- Goodness. - Whom should we call?
Hold on. Let me see who else was born in August.
- Gosh. - What should we do...
Oh, right. Shin Hae Sun. She was born in August too.
(The most sought-after actress, Hae Sun, was born in August?)
- Who? - Shin Hae Sun.
- She was in "My Golden Life". - Yes, I know her.
Actually, Hae Sun...
It's a bit uncomfortable to mention this on here, but...
- "Happy Together" made her popular. - Hey.
You're talking nonsense.
- Her drama made her popular. - You're talking crazy.
- She's the fruit of the program. - Gosh, you're unbelievable.
- You're full of yourself. - No, I'm not full of myself.
- Hey. - Listen to this guy.
Let's give her a call then even if she can't join us.
- Do you know her phone number? - Of course not.
- You don't even have her number. - I can call her agency.
Don't you know my name makes everything possible?
I have... What did you say?
- My name makes everything possible. - Makes what possible?
- Should I call her then? - Call my house.
If it's you on the phone, they won't put you through.
- Hey, I'm talking business here. - Say that...
- Say that it's you, it won't work. - I'm talking about this show.
- What are you talking about? - Why not?
I have Hae Sun's phone number.
If you have her number, I'll buy you lunch for the rest of my life.
Forever.
- Look. - Only if you have her number.
(Does he really have her number? He's calling someone.)
- Hello? - Hello.
Hae Sun!
- Hello? - Hey, Hae Sun!
"Hey, Hae Sun"?
- Don't be so casual. - Hello.
- Goodness, hey, you. - Don't be so casual with her.
- Hae Sun. - He has lost it.
- It's great that you're doing well. - Thank you.
- It's her? - Of course. Ask her.
Hello.
- Hi. Hello. - I'm Jee Seok Jin.
- Oh, hello. - See? Did you hear that?
Her voice pitch got lower.
- Hae Sun. - Do you know Jae Seok?
- Of course. - What did I tell you?
Isn't your birthday in August?
- Yes, it is. - On what day is it?
It's August 31.
- Goodness. - Goodness. It's the last day.
It's the last day of August.
- Gosh. - It's the last day.
- I'm sorry to call so suddenly. - Yes?
We must meet with a celebrity who was born in August and do a mission.
I see.
Are you free right now?
Yes, I'll be at SBS in Mok-dong for the entire day.
- Really? - That's great.
- Then can we meet for a second? - This is great.
(Please say yes, Hae Sun.)
- Yes, of course. - This is great news.
- We got her on our first try. - This is great.
- Hae Sun. - Yes?
Can we head over there now?
- Yes, yes. Please come. - Okay. I got it.
We'll be there soon.
- Sure. See you later. - Okay, see you soon.
Hae Sun.
Hey!
- I had a question for her. - Listen.
Hae Sun must be tired. She said her drama is premiering today.
You didn't let me talk to her.
Hae Sun is probably tired.
- I should've called her. - All right.
- You invited your guest. - Yes.
- I'll give you the hidden mission. - What is it?
- What do we have to do? - This is important.
- I'll win no matter what. - The member who finishes...
the hidden mission first will be paired up with the guest.
Keep in mind that pairing up...
- is more advantageous. - Is that so?
Draw the hidden missions that you will carry out.
- Our missions are different. - I see.
- You choose. - I'll choose this one.
(What kind of missions will they do?)
- Should we keep this a secret? - It's better to keep it a secret.
Gosh, how am I supposed to do this?
Mine is impossible to complete. You won.
This is impossible. How... How could...
- Gosh, unbelievable. - She must say you're full of life.
(She must say that you're full of life.)
(No way. How did he figure that out?)
How did you know?
It was reflected over there. You must've been more careful.
- You could see that? - It was reflected.
- I can see that. - Gosh, yes, you can see that.
I can see through it because the paper is very thin.
- She must say you're full of life. - You have good eyes.
Goodness.
I have to act like I'm full of life.
Dear me. This is crazy.
You must invite a guest whose project's title has number eight in.
- That's hard. Number eight? - It's hard.
The mission is hard, and teaming up with her is hard too.
- Me too. - Today won't be easy for me.
It's a hardship after a hardship. He's the biggest hardship.
He's as big as Mount Paektu.
I just thought of this one. "Christmas in August".
- Han Seok Kyu and Shim Eun Ha. - Shim Eun Ha.
(The main leads of the best romantic movie?)
- Do you know their numbers? - No.
I do want to meet them though.
- It'd be awesome if they joined. - It's my wish. Exactly.
The staff can really compliment us for our job this time.
Right?
- Do you know them? - We...
We might even win the Grand Award.
(Grand... Grand Award?)
But are there other films or dramas with number eight?
- Number eight. - She would be the biggest guest.
Who is she?
- Anne Hathaway in "Ocean's Eight". - That's amazing. That one counts.
Do you know her number?
(Can they invite her and win the Grand Award?)
Direct message her.
Direct message?
(Should I really try that?)
- Who? - "Reply" series.
- The drama. - "Reply..."
- "1988". - "88". "1988". In the drama...
Ryu Jun Yeol, Ko Kyoung Pyo,
- Bo Gum, Ahn Jae Hong, - Kyoung Pyo is in the army.
And Lee Dong Hwi...
- Jeon Mi Seon. - Park Jung Min was in it.
Jung Min made a special appearance before.
But I can't.
I can't call him out anymore.
For the show, he rode his motorcycle from Seongnam.
I saw that show. Wasn't that show...
He wasn't on the show. How could you have seen it?
(It only took Kwang Soo's phone call.)
(Jung Min is a loyal actor friend who came all the way to Gangnam.)
(Thank you.)
- Hello. - You rode the motorcycle here?
I didn't recognize you for a second.
(However, he didn't get much airtime after he made his appearance.)
Jung Min.
(You know how I feel, right?)
Can you come here for a second?
- Should I give him a call? - Yes, call him.
- Call him. - I feel sorry to even call him.
Just call him. See what he's up to now.
(He musters up his courage...)
I don't think he'll answer it.
(He cautiously calls Jung Min.)
He said he'd give Kwang Soo his number. Or was it a wrong one?
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Jung Min.
- Yes? - Are you sleeping?
Yes, I was sleeping.
Jung Min.
I'm sorry. This is for Running Man again.
(Sighing)
What is it again this time? They'll edit me out again.
I'm really sorry.
(What is it again this time? They'll edit me out again.)
No, they won't. Jung Min!
I won't let this slide.
- He came all the way from Seongnam. - Exactly.
Jung Min, I'm sorry. You won't be edited out.
- Jung Min. - He's hurt. He's hurt.
I'm not joining you today.
(You probably won't want to, right?)
- Okay, get some more sleep. - I'm sorry.
- Bye. - Have a good day.
I'm sorry, Jung Min.
(I like you very much.)
Good luck with "Sunset in My Hometown"!
(I'll be more famous and invite you then.)
Whom else can we call?
Sung Dong Il was in the drama too.
- Right. He was in the drama too. - Yes, he was in it.
If it's not too much to ask, why don't we invite him?
But Dong Il lives in Incheon.
It is quite far.
He lives in Incheon.
We can go to him.
(But should we still give him a call?)
I'm nervous.
(Calling Dong Il)
Would he know who I am?
Tell him we're wrapping up. Hey, what's up?
Hello, Dong Il.
What's up?
- Hello, Mr. Sung. - We're filming Running Man now.
So?
I'm Jeon So Min. Hello, Mr. Sung.
Oh, hello.
I'm a big fan.
I see. I'm a fan too.
Thank you. I think he knows who I am.
- He might not. - Really?
Dong Il.
(Laughing vigorously)
- Dong Il. - What is it?
Where are you now?
I'm here and there. I'm in Korea.
- This is crazy. - Gosh.
He must've had a few drinks last night.
- Dong Il. - Yes?
I'm in Seoul.
- You're in Seoul? - He's in Seoul.
I have a shoot and other stuff.
- If you have some time to spare, - If you can...
- can we meet up? - Yes, just this once.
Why would we meet up? And you out of all people?
- Give him a call time to time. - You never call me.
Dong Il is a busy guy.
Do you have a bit of time?
I was wondering if we could meet for a few minutes.
Where do I have to go?
(He sounds like a cool guy.)
(This is awesome. He might meet with us.)
Are you in Gangnam?
Yes, I'm in Gangnam.
We're in Gangnam too.
- Then Dong Il... - I'm in Yeoksam-dong.
- Are we in Yeoksam-dong? - I see.
(They'll meet at this cafe.)
Dong Il, I will text you the address.
- It won't be long, right? - Yes, yes.
If it's long, I'll leave.
- Yes, I know that very well. - It will be short.
- Okay. - Thank you, Dong Il.
- Sure. - Thank you.
(This is awesome! They've invited Sung Dong Il.)
(20 minutes later)
- Hello. - Gosh. Hello.
(At last, he has shown himself.)
(He's the national treasure, Actor Sung Dong Il.)
Hello.
- Let me use the restroom. - Sure.
(He freely goes to the restroom as soon as he arrives.)
That's... That's the women's restroom.
Dong Il, it's on the right side.
(They're restless.)
He's... He's free-spirited by nature.
He's like a bohemian.
Why are you waiting out here?
Hello, Mr. Sung.
- Hello. - It's nice to meet you.
- Let me wash my hands first. - Sure, sure.
(This bohemian is very hygienic.)
There's no tissue.
(Wiping)
(It seems he's close with the cameo of his movie, Kwang Soo.)
- Hello. - Hey.
- I had to wash my hands. - Hello. Thank you.
So Min is...
- a big fan of yours. - I'm a big fan.
- I looked you up on the way here. - Thank you.
- He didn't know who I was earlier. - No, no.
A long time ago,
he appeared when "The Accidental Detective 1" was released.
It's been a while.
- That's right. - With Kwon Sang Woo.
Yes.
- Let's put a microphone on you. - You haven't?
(The staff gets him ready.)
Is coffee okay? Or do you want juice?
- Coffee... - Well...
I'd love some morning coffee.
(Dong Il is so funny.)
Don't forget your microphone. I have a dozen at home.
He just leaves with the microphone still on.
He's like that.
(Dong Il seems at home. What will his team's mission be?)
I think we're here.
(Meanwhile, Haha and Ji Hyo...)
So many people work here.
Hello.
(This is where we're supposed to meet our guest.)
(Who is the 8-time winner guest?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Mamamoo)
(Summer 2018, their new song, "Egoistic", tops the charts.)
(In 2016,)
(with "You're the Best", they topped the charts 8 times.)
- Hello. - Hold on.
- Hello. - Hello.
They don't seem ready yet.
(Hold on.)
- Hold on. - They're practicing.
Some of them seem ready.
(These don't seem ready.)
But not everyone.
They were in a hurry.
Is it really okay?
- Can we come in? - Yes.
Okay.
Mamamoo.
(Nice to see you.)
Hello.
My goodness.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
(The race starts.)
We found out something on our way here.
- What a coincidence. - Seriously.
- What is it? - Is it Hwasa's birthday today?
- That's right. - How did you know?
(It's Hwasa's 23rd birthday.)
How did you know?
So...
- We were in a hurry. - we prepared a present.
Really...
- Are you serious? - That's why we're a bit late.
We wanted to celebrate together.
- Is this for real? - Hold on.
(Wait for the surprise gift.)
Really?
- For real? - Is it a cake?
- Happy birthday, dear Hwasa - Happy birthday, dear Hwasa
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
A gopchang cake!
(A gopchang cake)
It looks tasty. I love it.
- We made it. - Really?
- Ji Hyo and I made it. - It's incredible.
(This is how this gopchang cake was made.)
(They picked hidden missions after contacting Mamamoo.)
(They had to make all 4 members do the mission.)
(Make the guests feed you.)
They might think I'm crazy.
It's Hwasa's birthday today.
- Really? - Really?
- It's Hwasa's birthday? - It's Hwasa's birthday?
(It's Hwasa's birthday today?)
Is it July 23 today?
- It is. - It is.
- Oh, my. - It's her birthday.
- We should bring a cake. - What about this?
Why don't we make a gopchang cake?
(Why don't we make a gopchang cake?)
If we don't cut it...
We could just roll it and stick candles in it.
It'll be amazing.
(Does it make sense?)
She'll love it, right?
Like this. It's working.
(Gopchang turns into a cake.)
It's working.
Yes. Like that.
That looks great.
(They made the world's first gopchang cake.)
It should look neat.
(It looks perfect.)
- Happy birthday, Hwasa. - Happy birthday.
(A gopchang cake for Hwasa)
(I've never received a birthday cake like this.)
We made it ourselves.
How did you get gopchang?
- We went to a restaurant. - We went to one.
- It's touching, right? - Yes.
Let me try it.
(She takes a bite right away.)
You're eating it already?
(Shocked)
(This is Hwasa style.)
It looks tasty.
(Their mouths water.)
She makes it look so tasty.
(We want some too.)
All right.
(Well...)
We knew this would happen.
(Haha prepared something to accomplish his mission.)
- Did you prepare scissors? - We cut some up.
(You're so thoughtful.)
Can we eat it now?
Of course.
- Happy birthday, Hwasa. - Take good care of yourself.
Thank you.
Like this...
(Give me some too.)
It's warm.
It tastes good.
- Try some. - Does it taste good?
(The way Hwasa eats gopchang made it sell like hotcakes.)
- Does it taste good? - Yes.
(They have no idea what Haha's plan is.)
- It tastes so good. - It tastes good, right?
Is there an age limit?
Our concert is...
That's big.
(She's enjoying it.)
Your hair looks like gopchang.
(Your hair looks like gopchang.)
It's ready to eat.
(Reggae gopchang style)
- Right? - Do the onions taste good?
Yes. Try some.
I don't eat onions.
- You don't? - Try some.
I like them.
(Give me some. I feel dizzy.)
- It's okay. - It tastes so good.
(Hold on.)
(While making the cake, )
(he only ate gopchang.)
I like them.
(Why is he asking for onions?)
What?
- It's okay. - It tastes so good.
(He must be trying to complete his mission.)
- You don't like gopchang? - What?
- Why do you only eat onions? - Oh, my. Moon Byul...
I like gopchang too.
- Is there some? - Try it.
- Yes. Try it. - Try some gopchang.
Why aren't you eating any?
I want you to feed me.
(He tries to be cute.)
(Ji Hyo is now sure.)
There's no gopchang left.
It's okay for me.
- I like onions. - Onions?
They look so tasty.
The onions look so tasty.
(Ji Hyo intercepts the onions.)
(As Ji Hyo steals the onions, )
(Haha's opportunity is gone.)
I love onions.
You must love onions.
- We do. - It tastes so good.
Is there more? I really like it.
But...
(Haha's second try fails too.)
- All right. - The onions taste great.
I love onions.
I can't believe it. I love mushrooms too.
- Mushrooms? - Ji Hyo likes them too.
She likes them.
She must love them.
That's a lot.
Do you eat aluminum foil too?
Eat it.
What are you talking about?
What's with her?
- Why are you doing this? - I can't eat the foil.
I'm just trying to have some fun.
- Is this a mission? - No.
It'd be too childish.
(Yes, we have a childish mission.)
It can't be...
It tastes so good.
Green onions?
- What's going on? - You brat.
I want to punch you.
(His mission fails, and he hates Ji Hyo.)
I want to be friends with Hwi In.
It's mine.
(Ji Hyo ruins Haha's plan every time.)
They have to eat more than the other?
It seems so.
(What should I do?)
They have to get more food from us than the other?
Mamamoo is here.
(He goes back to the beginning.)
The eight-time winner.
The legend.
Mamamoo is here.
Why don't you teach us your dance moves?
- So suddenly? - Yes.
Right now?
I want Hwasa...
to teach Ji Hyo...
your dance moves.
- Please stand up. - Me?
Yes. Please stand here.
Something must be going on.
Why...
- Please stand here. - Something must be going on.
You should put them down.
They might have a dance move where I can...
use these.
- The balance dance. - Oh, okay.
(Haha fails to make Ji Hyo put down the food.)
Oh, that's right.
We have the balance dance.
That's the worst dance move you have.
(He becomes restless and criticizes their dance moves.)
Put down the food.
Let's be more serious.
Oh, I have an idea.
(Ji Hyo suddenly has an idea.)
I have a dance move...
- I want to recommend to Mamamoo. - Okay.
- For their new song. - All right.
- Please do as I do. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo is usually a bad dancer.)
Like this?
- Like this? - Yes.
And then...
a wave and...
(Wink)
(Worried)
Let's do it all together.
Hold on. It's so old-fashioned.
(Hold on. It's so old-fashioned.)
(He stops them.)
It'll make you all look so old-fashioned.
- Don't do it. - Stop it.
Seriously. It's the bullet of love.
(Get out of my way.)
A wave and a wink.
Start.
(Singing)
(Haha tries to interrupt.)
Wink.
(They wink too.)
All right.
Done.
Ji Hyo's mission is complete.
- Right? - Ji Hyo's mission is complete.
What was the mission?
(What was her mission?)
All right.
(Exchange winks with the guest.)
I had to make the guests wink at me.
(Ji Hyo took advantage of Haha's plan and succeeded.)
I knew what your mission was.
You had to make them feed you, right?
(How did you know?)
You can feed Haha now.
(The mission is already over.)
He likes mushrooms and onions.
He likes green onions too.
- I like pork belly. - Give him everything at once.
(Let us feed you.)
(This is our love for you, Haha, )
(who helped Ji Hyo win.)
Eat a lot.
- Everything at once. - He ate them all.
(Ji Hyo and Mamamoo become a team, )
(and Haha will compete against them alone.)
We have to sit facing each other?
(Jong Kook and Se Chan are at a cafe in Sangam-dong.)
Facing each other?
I'm sitting with my fan club president.
I was your first fan club...
- president. - That's right.
(It's about time that she arrived.)
(I'll call the secret weapon.)
(He called the secret weapon to come.)
(Okay, I'll see you in Sangam-dong.)
(Who is Jong Kook and Se Chan's secret weapon?)
You're the president, so act like one.
(We're waiting for you.)
She's here.
- Is she here? - Where is she?
(Their secret weapon is here.)
(She obviously has long legs.)
(She arrives on her long legs.)
It was you.
(Who is their long-legged secret weapon?)
Goodness.
(A celebrity with long legs, Jang Do Yeon)
- Put on a microphone. - Goodness.
- Put on a microphone. - Do Yeon.
Aren't you too dressed up?
- These are my pajamas. - Pajamas?
I dressed up as an enka singer going to an event.
(She dresses up as a Japanese singer.)
(Singing in Japanese)
- Put on a microphone, Do Yeon. - I see.
- Your shoes look uncomfortable. - They're fine.
Put on comfortable ones.
- These are comfortable. - Come on and put these on.
- Do Yeon. - Put these on.
(Wait a minute.)
(That looks suspicious.)
- No, why are you... - Put on comfortable shoes.
Hey.
(Their hidden missions were...)
(Time to select their hidden missions)
(Change shoes with the guest.)
(Will it be possible?)
(Make the guest hang onto your arm.)
(That's your mission, isn't it?)
These are more uncomfortable.
- Put these on. - What are you doing?
- What's going on? - That's not allowed.
- Why not? - You can't take her shoes.
It's because her feet hurt.
- My feet don't hurt. - Do Yeon.
These are 280mm.
- No, they aren't. - They're 280mm. They're too big.
- No. - You have such big feet.
- Do Yeon, you can't balance. - Do Yeon.
Hold onto my arm.
(He's acting suspiciously.)
No, don't do it.
Just hang onto me.
(He fails as her feet don't come off the floor.)
Don't your feet hurt?
(Se Chan clears his mission.)
Keep those shoes on.
(Okay, give me the other shoe.)
- Give me the other shoe. - No, stop it.
You can't do this to a woman.
(He kicks away his shoe.)
- You can't do this... - Why did you kick it?
You can't do this to a woman.
- Are you advertising something? - Why did you kick it?
- You can't do this to a woman. - What are you doing?
- Keep my shoes on. - Hang onto my arm.
- Can you be so violent on SBS? - We're not.
- Come on, Do Yeon. - I can't wear them with bare feet.
- Stop. - What are you doing?
Go outside and fight. Why did you even invite me?
(What is going on with you two?)
- Jong Kook. - Do Yeon.
Hang onto my arm. You can't balance alone.
- Put these shoes on. - What are you doing to me?
- What are you doing to her? - It's done.
- Gosh. - Se Chan clears the mission.
Okay.
- Was that his mission? - Did she have to hang onto you?
I'd feel bad to hang onto his arm even if he has big arms.
You tried to hang onto it.
- I'm sorry. - You almost did.
I didn't think I'd have another chance.
May I leave?
- No, we're starting now. - No.
(I'm sorry, but this is the start.)
No, we're starting now.
Is this how you invite guests on Running Man?
(She's flustered.)
(I'm sorry, did we surprise you?)
I guess things have changed quite a bit.
Usually, I'm invited by a writer on the show.
The members usually invite the guests.
- Is it like impromptu interviews? - Yes.
Guests come when they're available.
- It's real time. - Do Yeon.
Your shoes are quite big.
Even I fit in them. Is your size 280mm?
- No, it isn't. - My feet fit in your shoes.
- It's done. - What are you doing?
(Se Chan put on Do Yeon's shoes.)
(Do Yeon's feet didn't fit into Se Chan's shoes.)
My feet fit into your shoes.
The size isn't written on it. That's annoying.
(Disappearance of big-footed Do Yeon's 280mm)
The first mission is Pinching Toes.
(Mission 1: Pinching Toes)
Three of you pinch each other with your toes.
The first to scream is eliminated.
- Okay. - It's a total of two rounds.
I'm not ticklish either.
What if we can't pinch Jong Kook because he's muscular?
He's softer than you think.
You can choose which body part to pinch.
- His nose? - "His nose"?
It's protruding the most. It's where I can pinch.
You can pinch anywhere that's allowed on TV.
Really? That's not fun.
(Only what's allowed on TV?)
(She's very witty.)
- I knew it. - What about his ear?
(They sit down, ready to pinch.)
Pull up your shorts more, Se Chan.
They won't go up higher. You'll tear them.
Gosh, do celebrities even wear shorts like these anymore?
(Aren't these too tight for a celebrity?)
That's embarrassing.
- Jong Kook. - Do Yeon.
- That's embarrassing. - What has the stylist done?
Aren't these too short to wear?
I wear them, Jong Kook.
(He loses his temper.)
People wear them.
- Is that so? I'm sorry, Se Chan. - People do.
Get ready.
(They're about to start the game.)
(She wraps it around herself.)
You're wrapping it around you? I see.
Everything below his neck is metal.
(You must brace yourself.)
My toes won't pinch any part of his body.
Put your leg up and grab his hair.
Grab his hair.
Get ready.
Start.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan pinch each other's thighs.)
(Round 1 starts.)
(She pulls his hair.)
(He feels pain on his scalp.)
(He transfers the pain to Se Chan's thigh.)
(Screaming)
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
(That hurts.)
- What's wrong? - This game is for Jong Kook.
How could he pinch me like this with his toes?
- Let me see. - He practically slapped me.
- It's bruised. - Did it hurt?
- Of course it did. - Really?
- Of course it did. - He's so strong.
- Are you okay? - Okay.
(After being pinched by metal toes, Se Chan is eliminated.)
- Next up are Jong Kook and Do Yeon. - Okay.
- Get started. - I can't win by strength.
Jong Kook is too strong, so I should pick...
- Pick what? Wait. - a stimulating body part.
(I'll pick a stimulating body part.)
Pick a sensitive part.
- Sensitive part. Shall we start? - Yes.
(The part that Do Yeon attacks is...)
(his ear.)
Put your big toe in his ear.
- Inside his ear? - Yes.
Push it right in.
That's a good place. They're ready.
- He loses if he makes a sound. - That's right.
- Get ready, set. - Hold it for a minute.
(Round 2 starts.)
(Laughing)
It's over.
It's over. He made a sound.
Instead of pinching my ear, she was picking at it.
(Do Yeon makes a deep attack that's only possible with her long toe.)
Your toes are like fingers.
- Good job. - Your toes are like fingers.
It's because her feet are big.
- It went right in. - It's because they're 300mm.
- My earwax was picked. - That's okay.
- Is it okay? - It's okay between celebrities.
- Really? - The score is 1 to 1.
Okay!
(The scores are tied.)
Let's move onto the last game.
- Last mission is called Toe Zero. - "Toe Zero"?
When the offense calls out a number...
and equals the number of toes, the offense wins.
The team wins a point.
The losing team gets a hit on the head.
(The losing team gets a hit on the head.)
"A hit on the head"?
The 1st team to win 2 points wins.
(The 1st to get 2 points wins.)
- I know what it is. - That's a penalty.
What do you think, Jong Kook?
Do Yeon's feet seem as big as mine.
Stop it!
(Stop talking about my feet.)
I couldn't help but notice. I'm sorry.
- She's our guest. - Goodness.
Should I throw them out?
You should invite Lee Bong Geol instead.
(He's a wrestler with big feet.)
If you want to make fun of people.
(Order of attack: Do Yeon, Jong Kook, Se Chan.)
The number is from 1 to 6. Is there 0?
There is.
(Do Yeon starts.)
Okay.
Four.
(She calls out 4.)
(Do Yeon fails as the number of toes is 5.)
It's five.
Next.
(I will do better next time.)
Zero.
Okay.
(He looks at others carefully.)
(He takes a chance and calls out zero.)
- Wait a minute. - What?
- Didn't he say it too early? - No way.
I called out the number when we calmed down.
I waited in case someone complains.
- You'll be penalized. - Get ready, Do Yeon.
- Come here. - It's one of us.
Only one of us gets hit.
He's a bully.
- "A bully"? - I can't hit well...
because I hurt my right hand.
- You make people bleed with it. - No, I don't.
(He's very scared.)
(They don't bleed.)
- You can make others bleed. - My right hand...
- hurts right now. - Please start.
(He picks his slightly injured right hand.)
I'll use this hand.
I'll get hit next time.
- Like this. - Don't hit my eyes.
I'll hit right here.
(It's a hitting contest between a fan club president and an artist.)
(The sound is powerful.)
(He hits him with love.)
(It's a thrilling physical contact.)
- You didn't punch me, right? - Se Chan.
- One more. - Gosh, that was nice.
- Who's next? It's your turn. - Let's go.
Start.
Zero.
(The number of toes is 0.)
- Okay. - Zero.
(Do Yeon succeeds.)
(Her attack is a success.)
(Karma visits Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook gets hit once, and the other team gets a point.
It goes up to three points.
How can I do it?
- Let's see. - How can I hit him?
- He has such a smooth forehead. - And I'm the president.
Are you okay with this?
(The sound is once again powerful.)
- Gosh, your forehead is dented. - Okay.
(Gosh, your forehead is dented.)
- It's okay. - It's just a game.
It's just a game.
- It's only a game. - Of course. I know.
(It's Do Yeon's turn again.)
- Zero. - I'm safe.
(Do Yeon's attack fails.)
I've been waiting.
(I've been waiting for you to fail.)
I got a cramp.
(Jong Kook gives Se Chan a cramp.)
(That's not necessary.)
It hurts so much. Okay.
(I better not fail this time.)
Whose turn is it?
- It's your turn. - It's your turn.
You look a bit annoyed.
He just looked so scary.
- "Whose turn is it?" - His position...
- I didn't do that. - You didn't?
Was it just me?
It's 1 to 1 now.
(It's Jong Kook's turn to attack.)
Two.
Gosh.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
- Did you raise your toe? - Yes.
Why?
- What about you? - I raise my toe all the time.
- So do I. - You two...
(Jong Kook can flick them in the forehead now.)
(Singing)
He reminds me of Choi Min Sik from "I Saw the Devil".
(Choi Min Sik from "I Saw the Devil")
(I'll flick you in the forehead when you're suffering the most.)
This would make it easier for me.
(Jong Kook carefully decides to use the other hand.)
My right hand would be better.
Why are you doing this?
(Extremely scared)
(Moaning)
(Full power)
(It's unbelievable every time.)
I should have scratched his forehead.
- Is it already over? - Is it over?
Jong Kook wins.
We'll give him a badge.
I haven't been in the SBS building in a while.
Me neither.
She has a press conference...
for her new drama.
- Is this her room? - Yes.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin arrive at Hae Sun's waiting room.)
You should knock first.
(Seok Jin opens the door without knocking.)
We're sorry.
Gosh. You have such bad manners.
- She knows we're here. - Still...
My goodness.
You can't just open the door like that.
Why would a door make a sound?
- We're sorry. - Why would a door make a sound?
- Seok Jin. - It means you should get ready.
You should let the person know that...
you're coming in.
You shouldn't just open the door.
Are you there?
(Knocking)
Why are you trying to be so polite?
- This is why stars don't like you. - Hae Sun, are you in there?
(Will Hae Sun open her door?)
Hae Sun!
Oh, my.
- Hello. - Hae Sun.
My goodness.
(Her drama got the highest viewer rating of 45.1 percent.)
(Shin Hae Sun is the queen of viewer ratings.)
Hae Sun is here!
(This is my first time on Running Man.)
It's been such a long time. You're very busy these days, right?
No, I'm not.
- You're not? - No.
In the lobby,
I saw you and Yang Se Jong on the screen.
And there are so many fans.
What changed the most...
after you became very popular?
- I sleep less now. - You sleep less.
You must be earning more money too.
- Right? - Right.
(He asks her about money from the start.)
You get paid more for commercials now, right?
Before, I got paid so little.
(She is so honest.)
So compared to before...
- But I don't get paid very much. - Seok Jin.
I'm sorry, but stop doing this gesture.
Don't do that.
Anyway...
- You have a press conference today. - Yes.
- What time is it? - I have...
a radio show at 1pm.
- And then... - A radio show at 1pm?
Including Tom Cruise,
our guests have only one hour these days.
(Just-1-hour guests)
- Don't worry. - Okay.
We're used to it.
One hour is enough.
We're so happy to meet you.
- We have so many questions. - We do.
This is so frustrating. I want to talk to her,
but Seok Jin keeps doing ad-libs.
How do I look?
(Jumping)
- What? - You already started?
How do I look?
(He is breathing heavily.)
- You look hot. - I look hot?
(Why is he jumping?)
(I am hot, indeed.)
I am hot.
(It won't be easy for him.)
Why do I look hot?
Today...
Because you're jumping?
(That's obvious.)
He's trying to do something.
8... 8...
(Seok Jin is gesturing "8".)
Gosh, I think I'll lose.
(Exhausted)
- You look exhausted. - You look exhausted.
(Is this it?)
- That's not it. - It'll be hard.
What kind of music do you listen to these days?
(Is that his mission?)
Do you listen to "Ddu-du Ddu-du" by BLACKPINK?
This song.
(What is Jae Seok's mission?)
(Make the guest copy your dance.)
Don't do it.
Preserve your dignity. Don't do it.
- I have no dignity though. - Just don't do it.
An actress should protect her image.
(But he can't protect his own image.)
- Am I supposed to say something? - No.
(It's a race against time now.)
It's not very hard.
- Try it. - Don't do it.
Don't do it.
You can't do it? It's so simple.
Try it.
(She realizes what she should do.)
Like this?
Try it. Start.
(She seems to have realized something. Will she dance?)
How do I look?
(Dancing)
- You look busy. - Busy?
(Am I wrong?)
- Jae Seok wins. - Why?
Thank you.
Thank you, Hae Sun.
She danced.
- This? - Yes.
Let's start the 2 to 1 competition now.
We'll play...
the Spot the Difference game in the waiting room.
(Spot the Difference)
Spot the Difference?
There will be offense and defense.
Within a minute, you have to find...
- 5 differences in this room. - 5?
- Find more differences to win. - Within a minute?
- We'll find the differences first. - Okay.
(Jae Seok and Hae Sun will find the differences first.)
What should I do?
I'll put it here.
(He is thinking hard.)
- I'll sit here. - We have a big advantage.
We're two people.
In addition,
Seok Jin is...
someone who doesn't pay attention to things.
(We're confident.)
Come in.
Can we come in? So this is the original version?
(The original version)
(They can observe for 3 minutes.)
- It's very unique. - We should pay attention.
- Hae Sun, pay attention. - Okay.
Pay attention to things like this. Remember the direction of it.
(I'll remember everything.)
I hope he won't be so mean as to mix these up.
There are six of them.
(Shaking)
My arm hurts.
(The bottle is heavy.)
You should keep your arm up.
There are two of them.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
There are five of them.
(If no one's watching, I can put my arm down, right?)
Keep your arm up.
- Don't put it down. - Hurry up.
You shouldn't put your arm down.
All right.
- You're very observant. - We're done.
- Okay. - We checked everything.
You can move things around for a minute.
A minute after they leave the room.
He won't be able to change anything. He's so bad at games.
- There will be five differences. - Okay.
What if he fails to change five things?
- What if he changes only two? - I wouldn't be surprised.
They paid attention to such details.
They checked everywhere.
(Noises)
He's obviously moving the chair.
(He moved five things.)
- Time is up. You can go in. - Should we go in?
Let's find everything at once.
(They have 1 minute to find the differences.)
He's holding a different bottle.
(Is it that obvious?)
The bottle has changed. The chair has changed too.
- The chair and this. - It moved.
(They've found 3 in 10 seconds.)
- It's back here. - That's right.
Oh, these got switched.
- This and that. - They got switched.
- I think we're done. - We're done.
- Aren't we done? - There's one left.
- There's 1 left? - There's 1 left?
(He tells them the truth himself.)
You shouldn't tell them.
Thank you.
(Thank you for letting us know.)
(What's with me?)
What could be the last one?
I have no idea.
There's 10 seconds left.
10, 9,
- 8, 7, - What is it?
- 6, 5... - Hold on.
Hold on.
The towel?
- No. It's the same. - It's the same?
(The minute is over.)
Okay.
(They couldn't find the last one.)
What is the last one?
(They have to say the 5 differences now.)
I don't know the last one.
That's a relief.
If they didn't find everything, I still have a chance.
- Then... - Hold on.
(Hold on.)
Should I tell you?
- You have three seconds. - This.
(The mirror looks different.)
One more time.
That's right!
- That's right! - The mirror.
(Is it one of the differences?)
The mirror.
It's correct.
(That was amazing.)
I knew it.
- You're the best. - The mirror.
The bag, the chair, the pot, the bottle,
- and the mirror. - The mirror.
- Now... - Leave the room.
Gosh. I'm bad at this.
(I'm bad at this kind of game.)
I'm bad at finding differences.
We'll do something simple to show how terrible Seok Jin is.
You'll see.
We'll make it much simpler.
- This is the original. - Yes.
Come in.
Shall I take a look?
What happened?
(The original version)
Okay.
The mirror is over there.
Here's the chair.
(He pretends to be detailed.)
What are you trying to do?
There are two of each.
2, 2, and 2.
There are six chairs.
On the ceiling...
The ceiling?
There are four lights.
(He checks useless places.)
- Okay. - See how dull he is.
No, I'm very sharp.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Here we go.
- Okay. - Okay.
(What simple changes will they make?)
There's nothing to change.
You have one minute.
Change the watch.
(He puts his watch on the other wrist.)
I'll move them...
like this.
(She moves the snacks.)
He won't recognize this.
(He changes to a different color hat.)
If I roll up my sleeve, won't it be easy?
(She rolls up her sleeves.)
Switch places.
Okay.
(They switch their places.)
- Please come in. - Okay.
Five things.
(He has 1 minute.)
(Will Seok Jin recognize that they switched places?)
Two people.
(There are still two people.)
(How can he be so inattentive?)
(He passes by the disorganized snacks.)
Are there five differences?
(Are there five differences?)
(He's much duller than the rumors say.)
(He stares at them. Did he notice the difference?)
(He passes by.)
(His indifference doesn't disappoint them.)
That's impressive.
What is?
Wait, give me more time.
The mirror is the same.
He's an icon of indifference.
Seriously.
- I know. - It's unbelievable.
He's only interested in himself.
Goodness.
There's something on top which wasn't there before.
On top.
(It has been there.)
(He stares.)
(Did he finally recognize it?)
Weren't you doing this before?
(Weren't you doing this before?)
(His mistake is so frustrating that it's impressive.)
Were his hands by his side?
Were they by his side?
There must be something here.
- 10. - Weren't you wearing heels?
Eight.
- Seven. - Wait, I have no idea.
What is it?
- Seriously. - Okay.
I'll say five differences.
(The time is up.)
I need to guess.
I'm sure this one is different.
I think it was over there.
These moved from here to there.
That thing on top wasn't there before.
That plastic bag on top.
What are the last two?
Did that many change?
Please say the answers.
We switched places. We thought you'd notice.
Goodness.
My watch moved to the right wrist.
- How would I guess that? - Why not?
How would I guess that?
Why couldn't you?
- You're so dull. - How can I guess that?
Why not? This cap...
isn't mine.
It isn't?
(It isn't?)
- How would I guess that? - Why wouldn't you?
- They're so different. - The color is very different.
How can you not see that?
How could I?
Did you see how surprised Hae Sun was?
- She was so surprised. - It was unbelievable.
- All we did... - I had no idea.
Was switch places.
- How could you not know? - Jae Seok won.
He wins an eight.
(Jae Seok gets an 8.)
- I knew it when we teamed up. - Thank you.
Thank you.
This is for Hae Sun.
(Hae Sun gets a red ginseng gift set.)
It's not much, but we'll give a present to Hae Sun.
Thank you.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
(Thank you, I enjoyed it.)
Let's go.
- Let's finish it. - Okay.
Here's your mission with the guests. It's called Challenge 88 Points.
(Challenge 88 Points)
Each of you will sing one song.
The team to score closest to 88 points wins.
- We shouldn't sing so well. - That's right.
Score as closest to 88 points. This is our 8th anniversary.
- It's so difficult. - What on earth?
(Mamamoo and Ji Hyo versus Haha)
("Tears" by So Chan Whee and "Don't Laugh" by Haha and Skull)
(Will Mamamoo score 88 points for Ji Hyo?)
("Tears" by So Chan Whee)
subtitles synced and corrected by riri13
Look at her.
(They get ready.)
- She's different. - She's completely ready.
(The performance queen starts off differently.)
(How will Mamamoo sing?)
1, 2, 3, go.
(Everybody, shake your body.)
Look at her.
(She dances against the wall.)
(It seems like she had a drink at a gopchang restaurant.)
Everyone, please score 88 points.
(Don't sing too well.)
(Nothing is going on with me)
Mamamoo
(She shows off her talent as soon as she grabs a microphone.)
(Scoring 88 points isn't her priority.)
(Rapper Hwasa's high pitch part)
(She sings in high pitch.)
That was good.
- You're Mamamoo. - Get ready!
Don't sing too hard.
(They know the mission, but they get too excited with the high pitch.)
Mamamoo
(She's worried that they'll score 100 points.)
Don't get so emotional.
(Their singing makes the viewers content, but Ji Hyo anxious.)
(Nice, Mamamoo.)
(Erase everything)
(They remember their mission of scoring 88 points...)
(only at the last moment.)
What's wrong with you today?
(They can't control their excitement.)
That was amazing.
You sang so well.
"Tears" is...
(They sang "Tears".)
(Did they score close to 88 points?)
Please.
(They score 99 points.)
- What? - 99.
(It shouldn't be 99 points.)
It's because Mamamoo sang.
(We sang so carelessly.)
- It's because of them. - How could we score 99 points?
You scored 99 points.
(If Haha scores between 78 to 98, he wins.)
Give me the microphone.
("Don't Laugh")
It'll be easy. Okay.
(He chooses his own song with confidence.)
(Ji Hyo approaches.)
(She disturbs him.)
You're the best
(She disturbs him with Mamamoo's song.)
(Mamamoo also starts to disturb him.)
You're all bullies!
(Despite the disturbance, )
(he continues his Korean, reggae song.)
(He's annoyed.)
(Despite Mamamoo's interruption, )
(Haha does his best.)
(Haha's song is over.)
(Ji Hyo and Mamamoo scored 99 points.)
(Haha wins if he scores 11 points lower or higher than 88 points.)
(Haha's song is over.)
(Ji Hyo and Mamamoo scored 99 points.)
(Haha wins if he scores 11 points lower or higher than 88 points.)
(The score is exactly 88 points.)
(Haha scores exactly 88 points.)
(Is it for real?)
(How is this possible?)
That's a lie.
(He's so happy that he can fly.)
- 88 points. - How is it possible?
It gives me goosebumps.
(The problem is that Mamamoo sang too well.)
I thought that...
Something went well.
(A miracle moves him.)
I'm a little disappointed...
because I tried my best.
(However, he only scored 88 points.)
- Don't you feel sorry to Skull? - 88 points...
You tried your best, but you only scored 88 points.
I concentrated and did my best.
(Haha wins an 8.)
So Min cleared the mission.
- Thank you. - So Min is...
on Dong Il's team.
You're on your own now. I'm on your team.
It's 2 against 1.
- We'll definitely win. - Now,
I'm tired of you.
(I'm tired of you.)
What do you mean?
I've been with you for two years on dramas and films.
We've worked together for two years in a row.
If you win by yourself, that'll be highly rewarding.
There's favoritism too.
- That's right. - I may lose on purpose for you.
That's right.
(That's an important point.)
- Yes. - We'll keep seeing each other.
Yes, that's right.
That's right. We'll last forever.
I got this far with that type of personality.
- You don't know what I'll do. - That's true.
My wife doesn't trust me either.
- No, she trusts you. - My kids don't trust me either.
- No way. - I argued yesterday again...
- with the kids. - Stop it.
Don't say that.
Your mission is called 3 Watermelon Games.
- Watermelons? - Yes.
It's best 2 out of 3, and it's 2 on 1.
The first mission is called Fold the Watermelon Tube.
The team that deflates the watermelon tube first...
and puts it in a container wins.
That?
It's better to have two people then.
I can do it. I'll do this. Okay.
- Let's make a plan. - Okay.
(You're making a plan?)
- The stopper comes up, right? - Yes, we have to push it down.
We have to push it down, so you can push it down...
- while I take the air out. - Okay.
All right.
He's so...
(He calls Kwang Soo over this time.)
(Is he telling Kwang Soo his plan?)
Try your best.
(This is Dong Il's incredible plan.)
I will. He told me...
to try my best.
Once you close the container, you are done.
- Okay. - He said he's on my side.
He's like a spy.
(Trust me, Kwang Soo.)
Ready,
set, go.
Take it out.
Pull it.
(Struggling)
Why can't I open this?
(With Dong Il's help, So Min opens the stopper.)
Hold onto it.
(He's very focused.)
(He pushes with his whole body.)
(Air escapes.)
You have to hold with both hands.
(What?)
You said you'd help me.
I'll push down.
That's what you said.
- What? - He's taking a break.
(I'm just taking a break. Why?)
He's taking a break.
(With Dong Il's hard work, So Min and Dong Il get ahead.)
I'll do this.
(He's behind.)
Okay.
(I'm going to rip this apart.)
You can't do that.
- He's ripping it. - You can't push down. Take it out.
He's ripping it.
(There he goes again.)
He's always like that.
(It's all about the victory. He doesn't hear a thing.)
Look at him. Look what he's doing.
He already lost.
My kids are watching.
(Kwang Soo, my kids are watching.)
Jun, Bin, and Yul are watching.
That's right. They'll watch and learn.
They'll watch and learn from you.
Jun, watch "King of Mask Singer" for a moment.
(He begs urgently.)
Jun, change the channel for a moment.
(He's the biggest cheater in town.)
(He cheats and starts folding the tube first.)
Jun, change the channel for a moment.
(I don't know anymore.)
Hey.
(So Min runs away with the container.)
(Goodness)
(I'm going to keep going.)
(Kwang Soo runs after her.)
Dong Il, give me a few moments.
(This game becomes messy.)
That little...
(She runs out.)
Where did she go?
Will this fit?
(Dong Il does it the right way.)
Where did you go?
(This is a noneducational scene that kids shouldn't watch.)
(She goes into the scorching heat.)
I'm barefoot. What do I do?
Goodness.
What is wrong with her?
(The two biggest cheaters roam around Gangnam.)
(He folds it one by one.)
This is not the stopper.
Where did they go?
Isn't it better to be doing this?
Why do they live like that?
(It must be tiring to live like that.)
You don't even have shoes on. What are you doing?
You're an idiot.
(This is ridiculous.)
Do you think Dong Il's done?
(She steals the lid again.)
This is not how you play this game!
(She is about to go into the building.)
(She hides the lid in the entrance.)
When you get old, you have to do things slowly.
It's dangerous. I have high blood pressure.
(He's worried about his health.)
I didn't have my shoes on.
I hid it.
Why is she doing this?
- Where's the lid? - What?
- Where's the lid? - I don't know. This is ours.
- Hold this down. - What's this?
This game isn't supposed to be like this.
I just have to close this.
- It won't work. - It won't.
This is not a searching game.
(He searches everywhere.)
(He finds an extra lid.)
We have no time.
(Both teams try to close the lid. They have to close it completely.)
It worked.
(He forces it in.)
(Will it be this team that has more people but is slow?)
(Or will it be Kwang Soo who's alone but uses all kinds of tactics?)
(Which team will close the lid first?)
- Dong Il and So Min win. - Hold on.
(Dong Il and So Min win.)
Hold on.
(He's almost there.)
Come here. Bring it.
Bring it.
I thought you'd be on my side. Why are you mad?
You said you'd be on my side.
- Why are you mad? - This is so tiring.
You said you were on my side.
- Hey. - You said there's favoritism.
If he can close this in 10 seconds,
we lose.
(He makes a suggestion.)
- Really? Okay. - Sure.
If not,
So Min can slap your cheek.
(That's if you can't do it.)
- Oh, gosh. - 10 seconds.
- But... - I'm giving you a chance.
I thought you were on my side.
That's why I'm giving you this opportunity, you fool.
- Okay. - I tried it.
- You can close it in five seconds. - Ready.
- 10 seconds? - Ready... 10 seconds.
(He's finally taking my side.)
- Okay. - Set, go.
(The additional 10 seconds start.)
10 seconds is enough. You can do it in 5 seconds.
Once I close it, this is over.
(This is Dong Il's bonus for Kwang Soo.)
(Can Kwang Soo live up to his expectation?)
- It's done. - It's over.
- You're done. - Slap him.
(He automatically tells her to slap him.)
You can't do it in 10 seconds.
We did it.
- I'll go for your forehead. - I can't...
(This is ridiculous.)
You said there's favoritism.
I can go the other way too.
See? I can.
- I see that. - I can go both ways.
- He told me to. - This is a penalty.
There are rules. You cheated.
You need to be penalized. The viewers who are watching...
with their kids can say, "You get hit when you cheat."
(He represents the viewers.)
(Do you have to get hit?)
- You get hit? - Yes,
- this is public broadcasting. - I though he was on my side.
Families watch this.
Be gentle.
It's been such a long time. I don't want to hit your eyes.
I'd close my eyes. It feels better.
(Children, if you cheat, you get slapped.)
(This is a lesson for many young viewers.)
Oh, dear. I'm sorry.
It's okay. You've sinned.
Goodness.
You're making a fool out of us honest people.
- Okay. I'm sorry. - We took the air out.
- Apologize to the viewers. - I'm sorry.
- You get hit when you cheat. - That's right.
You get hit when you cheat.
(Running Man creates a world where you get hit when you cheat.)
(So Min and Dong Il win the first mission.)
The second mission...
(Following is the second mission.)
It's Watermelon Seeds Lottery.
It's a lottery.
There are three small watermelons in front of you.
You can pick a watermelon you like and split it in half.
You pick a side,
- and you win with the most seeds. - This sounds fun.
(The person with the most seeds win.)
This is like an old game.
- Is it? - We play by ourselves.
Okay, you never know.
Please pick one each.
Which one do you think has more seeds?
- The ripe one? - Right.
(Which one has more seeds?)
- This... - "Authentic Masterpiece".
- Please cue the music. - Pick one.
All right.
- Okay. Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo gets to pick second.)
Okay.
That's fine.
This one's the widest.
(He has a good feeling.)
- Good. - Okay. You go first, So Min.
(So Min goes first.)
It's better to cut it vertically.
Can we cut it vertically?
- Of course. - It doesn't matter.
Hold on. Mine's the smallest.
It is.
(His is the smallest vertically.)
- You can cut it vertically? - I was ready...
- to cut it vertically. - We can cut it vertically?
Of course. As long as you cut it somehow.
This is an apple.
(So Min's watermelon looks long.)
You can stick one side out.
Is it left or right?
- I say left. - Left.
It's this side.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
It's the same regardless of where I cut.
- It's small. - It's circular,
so it doesn't matter where you cut.
The widest part.
(He finds the widest side. What will be the result?)
- Pick one side. - There are not that many seeds.
I pick left.
(He picked first.)
It's ripe.
(He's careful.)
(He takes a peek inside.)
- Hold on. I'm not in the middle. - I thought...
(Is he changing the direction?)
I'm not in the middle.
Wait.
I'm not in the middle. Let go.
(Is he changing directions again?)
- I have to cut it properly. - Why do you keep cutting it again?
- I'm not in the middle. - Once you cut, it's over.
That's not true.
- I didn't cut it completely. - He didn't. It's okay.
- This is good. - It looks like...
he's cutting fish. He's making thin cuts.
I'm right in the middle.
It's ripe.
This is the biggest watermelon.
- You should pick this side. - That's right.
This is the side you're not picking, right?
Let's check one by one.
Do I go first?
I hope there are many seeds.
- Let's go with So Min. - Okay.
I'll show you.
(She picked last. How many seeds does she have?)
Ta-da.
(It's filled with seeds.)
There are so many.
(This watermelon is filled with seeds.)
- There's a lot. - There are so many.
- Kwang Soo is next. - Kwang Soo.
(Next is Kwang Soo.)
(He has to have more than those two.)
I'm looking forward to this.
He's done.
Okay.
(It's filled with black seeds.)
Okay. These are dots.
(She's shocked.)
(Dong Il is the last to go.)
Dong Il.
(He picked the biggest watermelon. What's the result?)
(Goodness)
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8... - You have...
- around 10. - There are hardly any. Oh, gosh.
He hardly has any.
I looked at his and started blushing.
I've never seen one with so few seeds.
- He tapped on it too. - 1, 2, 3, 4...
You're on TV. Say it properly.
I don't have seeds? I have three kids.
- No, that's not what I mean. - How dare you...
call me a seedless watermelon?
- What about my kids? - That's not it.
(Dong Il loses out. It's So Min versus Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo is next.
28, 29, 30.
(He has 30 seeds.)
I have 30.
- 30? - I'm winning so far.
- Lastly, it's So Min's turn. - Make it fair.
(He's confident he'll win.)
I...
- have too many to count. - 1, 2, 3, 4...
(For fair play, the director counts.)
(If So Min loses, they have to play another game.)
(Counting)
(28, 29, 30, 31...)
What are you doing?
(His finger doesn't move with the counting.)
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I was counting with you. What are you saying?
- I was counting too. - Let him be.
You were pointing in the air.
- You can count to 10,000. - Let's see. Count it.
- I'm serious. Count it. - Count it, Kwang Soo.
(He doesn't trust anything. He starts counting it himself.)
6, 7, 8...
(Is that necessary?)
- 25, 26... - 27.
(He's almost at 30.)
(He tries to flick one out.)
Why are you taking it out?
(He's mad.)
I have more.
Besides that, there are three more.
Yes. I have over 30.
- She has 31. - 31?
It's 31, right?
Yes, it is.
(Good for you.)
(So Min and Dong Il win 2 to 0. So Min takes another 8.)
(All teams are done. They go to the last location.)
(Number 8s per member)
There must be a way to turn the tables.
It's been a while since we've been at the ring.
(This is where you get physical. What will they do here?)
Do we fight?
It looks like we're fighting in the ring.
You got your eights, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
The final mission is going to be held in the octagon.
- What's this? - This is important.
It's the Eight Colored Shoes Quiz.
(Final mission: 8 Colored Shoes Quiz)
- What? - Is it a quiz?
- I'm in trouble. - "Eight colored shoes"?
You'll put on shoes of eight different colors...
and solve quizzes that have to do with the number eight.
Okay.
The buzzer is the shoe that a staff member picks.
A member who puts the shoe in this basket first gets a chance.
If you get your shoe stolen, you can stand by the whip cream cannon.
If it's the right answer,
the person who got their shoe stolen gets the penalty.
If you say the wrong answer, you get the penalty.
Goodness.
If you get a question right,
you can take as many number eights...
from a member's bag.
- As many as you want? - Yes.
Is that good?
You're right.
The 1st 3 people to collect 8 number 8s...
move onto the final round.
(The 1st 3 people to collect 8 number 8s, move on.)
This is so...
- This is the end. - Let me move onto the final round.
But they ask you...
- random questions. - I know.
- They ask you ridiculous questions. - I know.
They're too difficult.
Who knows that a toilet is a swan?
No, it's a pony. It's "bidet".
Be quiet.
- Why are you mad? - Why are you...
- doing that to her? - Stop it.
She could've just moved on.
She gave him the correct information and he got mad. He almost hit her.
I smelled something sweet.
Be quiet.
- I smelled honey. - This is funny.
"Be quiet."
(Everyone has picked their shoes.)
It's all about who takes your shoe,
so it's better to get it taken by people who are bad in quizzes.
(This is Jae Seok's tip.)
(He finds a good spot.)
(Let's do this together, idiots.)
Wait.
In a row?
- Thank you. - You know what?
She got them all right before.
She's the queen of quizzes.
- She's the best. - She's the queen of quizzes.
- Here's the first question. - Okay.
To commemorate the hosting of 1988 Seoul Olympics,
Olympic Expressway was named. Where does it not pass?
- Jae Seok has to know this. - 1988?
- I don't know. - You know too, right?
- I know 100 percent. - I have to see.
Number one, "Seoul".
Number two, "Daegu".
Number three, "Damyang".
Number four, "Namwon".
- I got it. - I know too.
- This is hard. - I don't know.
The buzzer for this question is...
(What's the shoe color for this question?)
- I think it's blue. - It's purple.
Who's purple?
- It's Ji Hyo. - Come here.
(People are going after Ji Hyo.)
How far is she going?
- How far is she going? - Don't go there.
Ji Hyo.
(She's faster than others and different from them.)
(Grabbing)
Take it from her.
(She gets away.)
(She avoids Kwang Soo's attack.)
Take it from her.
(But a dangerous insect snatches it.)
(He touches down.)
- I got it. - I did it.
He took it out.
That was so...
Fine, I got it.
(She's enraged.)
(They've heard that tone of voice before.)
That's my voice. Okay?
- Fine, let's do this. - All right.
- Ji Hyo. - Let's do this. Okay.
- You have to come here. - Okay.
(I get that you're angry, but can you come to the front?)
Okay.
Get it wrong, Jae Seok.
I have no chance.
- What's the answer? - The answer is...
number one, "Seoul".
(It was to commemorate the Seoul Olympics, and that's the answer?)
- It doesn't pass Seoul? - He's wrong.
(What city does Olympic Expressway not pass?)
(Number 1, "Seoul" is correct.)
- It's Seoul? - Is it?
(She's even more mad.)
It's east to west.
- It connects east and west. - Isn't it Namwon?
No.
How could it not pass Seoul when it's for the Seoul Olympics?
Jae Seok, you got it right, so you can pick a member's bag...
and take as many number eights as you want.
- As many as I want? - Which member do you pick?
You have to pick the person with many number eights.
I can't...
really pick anybody,
so be honest and tell me how many you have.
You have to be honest.
(Look at his face.)
I'll tell you.
Let me tell you this.
- Be honest, and I'll exclude you. - Okay.
(He'll give leeway to those who are honest.)
(Whispering)
Zero?
It was 1, 3, or 5.
You have zero?
- You can't have zero. - That's true.
I'll take yours.
His?
- You can't have zero. - He can't.
Why is he saying he has zero?
I'm serious. I have zero.
- I have none. - That's not possible.
You can look in the bag and take as many as you want.
Does he get to look?
Kwang Soo...
- Does he get to look? - Yes.
He said he had zero.
- Zero? - I don't think it's true.
(Kwang Soo is flustered. How many 8s does he have?)
- Does he really have zero? - Take as many as you want.
Let's move onto the next question.
(Let's move onto the next question.)
- I think he has none. - He does?
- Really? - Does he have zero?
- Why? - Really?
You really have none?
Let's ask a question about ourselves.
Okay.
Guess what my mom's blood type is.
If I lose, I'm going home.
(They bet an eight and guessed each other's mom's blood type.)
1, 2, 3.
- Blood type O. - Blood type O.
- Blood type B. - Blood type O.
I got it.
Give it to me. Hurry up. Give it to me.
B?
I have five now.
(He only had one, but he got it taken away.)
(Sighing)
- Goodness. - He had zero?
How can he have none?
- Here's the question. - Is this a riddle?
- You have a good chance. - Okay.
Which song won the Grand Award in 1988 Gangbyeon Song Festival...
that was held in August?
- 1988? - Grand Award?
Number one, "Love Like a Sad Picture" by Lee Sang Woo.
Number two, "Always Think of You" by Lee Sun Hee.
Number three, "Damdadi" by Lee Sang Eun.
Number four, "Is There Anybody?" by Han Young Ae.
- I know this. - I got it.
(Which song won the 1988 Gangbyeon Song Festival?)
(The older members are excited.)
- I know this. - You do?
- I'm certain. - The buzzer is...
blue.
(It's Jae Seok.)
It's him.
(It's him.)
Take it from him. Hurry.
(He does a tap dance to escape.)
Take it.
Take it from him. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
(Kwang Soo steals it and touches down.)
- I had it. - No, no.
(Which song won the 1988 Gangbyeon Song Festival?)
Did you know?
I tried not to get it taken by Seok Jin.
- I know this for sure. - Kwang Soo doesn't.
He was born in 1985.
He was four years old.
I think it's number 2 or 3.
- You were three. - What's the answer?
- That's not your real age. - Do you want me to tell you?
Should I tell you?
(It's number 1.)
What's the answer?
This is a mental game. Seok Jin swayed you.
(Go with number 1.)
What's the answer?
Number three, "Damdadi" by Lee Sang Eun.
(He goes with his gut.)
(Did he just ignore me?)
What?
Okay!
(Number three, "Damdadi" is correct.)
I knew.
This is the right answer.
- Because... - "Damdadi".
- It's correct. - Were you in the song festival?
I haven't even seen it.
- He could have been on it. - I don't even know what it is.
I heard he was born in 1958, not 1985.
- 1958? The year of the dog. - What are you saying?
Kwang Soo, you got it right.
- Yes. - That was so close.
You can pick a member's bag and take as many eights as you want.
That was so close.
Can I just say it?
I'm going to kill you.
- I want to take So Min's bag... - I'm going to kill you.
(He picks So Min's bag without hesitating.)
- Why? - Hey!
That's not what we said.
- I want to take So Min's bag... - Hold on. Come here.
- I'll take five. - What?
- 5? - She has 5.
(She had 5?)
Is that possible?
- Hey. - She has five?
- Then So Min has zero, - Oh, gosh.
- and Kwang Soo has five. - Oh, gosh.
- Here's question three. - Okay.
Get ready.
- Oh, gosh. - My bad.
Here's the third question.
Out of all the kings in Joseon...
(Goodness)
(They give up.)
I...
A few people should be sitting down.
You never know. They could be in movies.
- Sit down, Ji Hyo. - Oh, gosh.
(I'll stand back up when I have to get physical.)
Come on.
Out of all the kings in Joseon,
who's the eighth king?
- I only know up to seventh. - Hold on.
Rat, cow, tiger, rabbit...
(He's serious.)
What are you talking about?
- What are you talking about? - What is it?
(He's incredible.)
Number one,
"Taejo". Number two, "Sejo".
Number three, "Yejong".
Number four, "Yeonsangun".
Okay.
The buzzer is...
green.
(It's So Min.)
It's green.
I'm sorry.
(It's a chaos.)
(As soon as Kwang Soo picks it up, they run like piranhas.)
(Where did Jong Kook come from?)
(The herbivores may fight, but Jong Kook always wins.)
Goodness.
We don't know the answer, and we're weak too.
Jong Kook went for it.
I thought this was the Super Bowl.
- What's the answer? - It's number three, "Yejong".
(He's confident.)
(Is it the answer?)
(Jong Kook is correct.)
That was strong.
Yes!
It was Yejong?
(For your information, this is So Min.)
I...
I got my number eights taken away,
and I have whip cream on my face.
- Look at the cream. - Can I have some bread?
(Can we dip it in bread?)
(She wipes off the whip cream and reflects on the day.)
There's so much whip cream.
It's your fault.
(It's your fault, Kwang Soo.)
How's this my fault?
Taejo, Jeongjong, Taejong, Sejong, Munjong, Danjong, Sejo...
That's right.
Jong Kook, pick a person and take as many as you want.
Then Kwang Soo...
(It's obvious.)
It's obvious.
- It's obvious. - Jae Seok...
He took five, right?
- It's obvious. - He took five.
Hold on.
- Listen to me. - Wait.
Give me a minute. Okay.
- I have five, but... - Fine. I'll think about it.
- If you had 4, - He has 4.
Whose would you take?
I would have taken mine, but...
(He can't deny it.)
(It makes sense to take Kwang Soo's.)
You have to see which two people move on.
I'll take Kwang Soo's then.
(Is that right?)
That's right.
I'll take four.
It's obvious. There's no point talking.
Jong Kook, you move onto the final round.
Okay.
(With 4 more, Jong Kook gets 8 8s and moves on.)
That was good.
I was waiting for it, and there was one question I knew.
I got it.
Answer. Number three, "Never Go Back".
This isn't it. I swear.
(Haha said it wasn't right, but Jae Seok was correct.)
I'll take two.
- Did he have that many? - Really?
(Se Chan miraculously answers a question right.)
Okay!
Come on.
(Jong Kook, Se Chan, and Jae Seok are in the final round.)
This is the final round.
It's My Four Line Fate.
(Final round: My Four Line Fate)
This is a bomb quiz.
Is it a quiz again?
There are four lines attached to a bomb.
There are 3 correct lines, and 1 incorrect line.
Listen to the question,
and you'll cut the correct lines one by one.
If you cut the incorrect line,
the bomb will explode.
That person is eliminated immediately.
(If you cut the incorrect line, you're eliminated immediately.)
The last person remaining becomes the winner.
This sounds fun.
Please pick the order.
Is there no lighting for the remaining people?
(An unprecedented question)
(They're already sad because they are out.)
- This is too dark. - Am I on TV?
Be quiet!
The main characters are on TV.
(Be quiet.)
What was that?
(The lights come back on for the losers.)
- What's this? - We're the main ones.
- Turn it off. - This is not intense anymore.
Focus on us. It was good earlier.
- Our faces don't show. - Be quiet!
Keep your mouth shut!
Our face doesn't show.
(He's strict.)
(Keep your mouth shut!)
- "Keep your mouth shut." - Keep it shut.
Keep it shut.
Be quiet.
- Jong Kook. - Keep it shut.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok loses.)
You're going last.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Okay.
(Se Chan is 1st.)
(This is the first question. He gets to decide who goes first.)
If you look at the probability, I should go first.
I'll go first.
Jae Seok will go second,
and Jong Kook will go third.
(You have to survive until the end. Who will be the winner?)
Here's the question.
In August 1998...
August?
Which song won first place in "Inkigayo"?
Hold on. What year again? 1998?
1998?
Jong Kook has the advantage.
- Okay. - This was...
- when he was active. - Okay, 1998.
Number one, "To My Boyfriend" by Fin.K.L.
Number two, "Breakup with Her"  by Kim Hyun Jung.
Number three, "Good Love" by Kim Min Jong.
Number four, "Road Fighter" by Sechs Kies.
- I have no idea. - They all got first place.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
You have to go with...
people's inclination back then.
Let's go. Hurry, everybody.
(Se Chan gets to go first.)
- Let's go. - I don't know.
This is hard. I don't remember.
Pick the most popular one.
Number two, "Breakup with Her" by Kim Hyun Jung.
(After some thinking, )
(he picks number 2. He has to cut the line.)
You have to guess.
1, 2, 3.
(If it's right, nothing will happen. If it's not, the bomb will explode.)
(Cutting)
Okay.
(Number 2 is correct. Se Chan survives.)
("Breakup with Her" got 1st place on August 9, 1998.)
- Is he right? - Is he?
(I knew it.)
It's for August, right?
There's an advantage for people in my age group.
I have no idea.
I know the wrong answer.
I don't know if "Good Love" was in August 1998.
No, it was from that time,
but there's a song that didn't win first place.
Don't ballads...
usually get released in autumn and winter?
I'll go with the one I'm certain about.
It got first place for sure. "To My Boyfriend".
(It has to be 1st place.)
- It has to be. - I don't know if it's that time.
That I'm not sure.
- I don't know. - Number one,
- "To My Boyfriend" by Fin.K.L. - It's the most famous.
1, 2, 3.
(Cutting)
It's wrong.
("To My Boyfriend" won 1st place in September 1998.)
(That's not it?)
- This is not it? - It's not.
- Yes. - This wasn't it?
Good thing I went last.
- President of my fan club! - Yes, sir!
That wasn't it.
(He leaves the star and the president of his fan club.)
Okay.
Se Chan, what's going on?
Let's win.
(The winner is 1 of these 2.)
(Se Chan is the 1st candidate.)
(He doesn't think about his bucktooth. He's daring.)
(He was being annoying and picked out all the weaknesses...)
(of the members in 7 People Profile.)
Why am I a grandpa?
Okay.
(Jong Kook is the 2nd candidate.)
(He thought Haha got a new identity.)
(His idea of members' profiles were absurd but truthful.)
- He's my fan. - He's a big fan.
- Here it is. - Okay.
Which incidents happened in 1998?
Number one, "France wins the World Cup".
Number two, "First visit to Mount Geumgang after the division".
Number three, "'Titanic' is released in Korea".
Number four, "g.o.d's debut".
1998?
I'll go.
Number one, "France wins the World Cup".
(He goes for the most obvious one.)
(That's for sure.)
1, 2, 3.
(Number 1 is correct.)
- It's right. - That's for sure.
I'll go with number two.
"First visit to Mount Geumgang after the division".
What?
- Okay. - All right. One...
(Did the 1st visit to Mount Geumgang after the division happen in 1998?)
(If it's incorrect, Se Chan will win.)
(Is the 2nd multiple choice the right answer?)
- 2, 3. Look. - I think it'll explode.
It didn't go off.
I think it'll explode.
(The 1st visit to the mountain took place in November, 1998.)
The second one's the only one not related to entertainment.
That's too hard.
(Now, the correct answer is either the 3rd or 4th choice.)
I have no idea.
(If Se Chan gets it wrong, Jong Kook will win.)
(If not, they'll solve another problem.)
- I have decided. - Go ahead.
I'll go with number four, g.o.d's debut.
(Se Chan chooses number four.)
- I think he's right. - This is the right answer.
- You think so too, right? - This is the correct one.
(Is it correct or incorrect?)
1, 2, 3.
(The 4th multiple choice is wrong.)
- That was wrong? - Hey.
(The group debuted in 1999.)
(Hey, did I just win?)
- Did I win the whole thing? - He won.
All right. Today's race's victory goes to Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook will get to change their online profiles.)
I haven't won for a long time. I didn't expect anything, but I won.
- I'll consider your opinions. - Give that to me.
It won't be just my idea.
Sir, here you go.
- It has started again. - Mr. Kim Jong Kook.
- Do you need anything? - I see.
- All right. Okay. - Are you all right?
- Excuse me, Mr. Kim. - Okay.
- Let's have naengmyeon together. - What?
- What? - Let's get naengmyeon.
(Profiles on other search engines will change after screening.)
(Yes, it's summer!)
(They go on a summer vacation.)
(And queens of vacations will join.)
(Jennie, a queen with endless charms)
(Jin Ki Joo, multi-talented beauty)
(Okay! It's a real vacation!)
(However, )
(the biggest heat wave hits Korea.)
(On the day of their vacation, the heat wave strikes.)
(But we're with the queens of vacations.)
(These ladies don't spare themselves.)
(Thanks to their effort, the laughter cools down the heat.)
(Everything will be decided by these unlucky hands.)
(Vacation to blow away the heat wave)
(What's wrong with Jennie?)
(What is this? This feels nasty.)
(Unlucky Vacation)