(Last week)
(Year End Special with Si Young, a special team leader)
(Try the missions the members failed once again!)
(Each team chose their mission after thinking hard about it.)
(Team Si Young got the mission to gather 4L of sheep milk.)
(After many hardships, they finally got a ranch to agree.)
(They arrive in Wangsan-myeon, Gangwon Province for the mission.)
You can get in the passenger seat in the front.
(They can complete their mission after milking 4L of sheep milk.)
Not yet.
This will be a long and hard trip.
(The owner of the ranch says something insightful.)
A long trip?
(They set out on a long and hard trip to the ranch.)
Are you all right?
(They must pass through a brook.)
- It is quite rugged. - We're passing through a brook.
- That's the ranch you mentioned. - I see.
My sheep are outside over there.
- They are out? - Really?
- I can see them. - There they are.
(I fooled you, didn't I?)
- You're right. Seriously. - It is in the woods.
- I do see the ranch. - Even the puppy is so cute.
The ranch is bigger than I thought.
(A home for the puppy and sheep)
- Shake it? - If you shake it,
they come to eat it.
Hello, girls.
Do you want to see it?
This one is big.
- They're eating it. - I can just shake it.
She's eating a lot of mine.
(Munching)
(Dashing away suddenly)
Hey, baby. Baby.
It's so quick.
- Hello. My gosh. - Aren't they running away?
- Byul. - This...
(They can't even try their mission.)
I think this will be a bust.
(He tries to ring the bell to call the sheep.)
(Ringing)
(Can the bell get the sheep to come back?)
Your dad rang the bell.
They're responding to it. They're coming down.
(Rushing back)
This is so fascinating.
Haha, shouldn't we stay away? Shouldn't we?
- They're fast. They came down fast. - This is fascinating.
This is so fascinating.
Everyone, come back in.
(There are no more guests, right?)
(Coming in after hearing the bell)
- Come inside. - My gosh.
- Close the door. - Get the door behind you.
Come inside. Come in.
(They hesitate at the door.)
- Come inside, everyone. - They feel something is off.
Go to the back, and drive them inside.
Come in.
- Come in, babies. - Hey, come in.
- Let's go. Come this way. - Let's go inside.
(They try to drive the sheep inside.)
- Let's go in. This way, girls. - Come in.
Let's go to where your daddy is.
- To where your dad is. - Go inside.
- No, no. Please. No. - Gosh.
(They run away for the 2nd time.)
Don't go there.
(Team Si Young is in a crisis.)
What are we going to do?
(The sheep run away farther this time.)
(The bell rings again.)
(They need a plan as they can't film it.)
- Everyone. - He keeps ringing. What must we do?
We should get the sheep inside without the cameras...
- and start filming them. - We will turn off...
- the lights and get them in. - We'll get the sheep first.
Let's try that. They won't go in.
We should get rid of the cameras first.
- Should we stay away? - You should stay here.
(Sheep don't move at night. They must start before the sunset.)
(Unlike the previous time, they don't come back at the bell.)
- I think we're doomed. - Right.
What should we do?
They went all the way up there.
(They stay still at a deeper point.)
Come on in.
(The owner is getting anxious.)
(Team Si Young is even more anxious.)
(The sun will set soon.)
Everyone.
(Look over there.)
They're coming down. They're coming down. It's our last chance.
Hey.
(They run down the mountain at full speed.)
It's over if we don't get them now.
(This might be their last chance.)
If we don't get them this time, we'll fail this mission.
(There you go. Come inside.)
Go out of there. Go.
There they come.
(Come back into the house just like that.)
(There are no strangers, right? Shall we go inside?)
(They approach all the way to the door.)
(However...)
(They stop at the door again. It still must feel unfamiliar.)
Turn off the lights.
(I think they're scared.)
(They turn off the last light along with the rest of the lights.)
What should we do?
(After observing the scene...)
They're going back. What are we going to do?
(They run away for the 3rd time despite their efforts.)
Sir, they're doing back up.
Babies.
(Even his gentle calling doesn't work.)
Babies, come inside.
(The sheep full of milk goes to the mountain.)
Byul!
(She runs away to a deep part of the mountain in the darkness.)
I think they're scared of the cameras.
- Exactly. We should hide. - We won't disturb them.
- Turn off all the lights. - Okay.
Let's turn off all the lights and head over there.
Babies.
(The owner will ring the bell alone in the ranch.)
(They go into deeper hiding soon.)
I think this might take longer than the mission in Hong Kong.
Don't you think? We didn't even start yet.
Come inside. Let's eat.
(They can only wait from afar.)
Come here.
(The trip here was long and hard.)
Come inside. Let's eat. Come here.
(But we won't be able to try our mission even once?)
Babies, come here.
(Glancing)
They're coming down again.
(This is the last chance. The sheep are coming down again!)
- Stay still. - They're coming down.
They're going in.
(A few of them enter the ranch.)
Don't go there yet.
Wait. Wait for the right time.
Come back in.
Let's eat. Come in. Come inside.
Come in here. Where are you going again?
(They head back outside since something still feels off.)
Babies.
(Oh, no. They're out again. I thought they were going in.)
- Hold on. - Why are they out again?
- They're looking at us. Don't look. - My goodness.
- Really? - All of them are out.
Everyone is out.
I have a bad feeling about this.
(This must be our last chance. I have a bad feeling about this.)
- Please go back in. - Babies.
- All of them are out. - Yes.
Come back in.
If they run away again... One of them is going in.
- They're going in. - They went in.
- They're going inside. - We can't lower our guard yet.
Go inside. Go, go inside.
- I think all of them went in. - All of them went in.
(It's packed.)
It's done.
He said it's done. It's done.
Come inside. You can turn on the lights if you need to.
(There's no time to hesitate.)
- Young Goo. - You should go away. Go that way.
I'm sure the sheep are very startled.
- That's all right, girls. - Hello, there.
Ari, you're so cool. Your beard is really cool too.
Try this, Ari.
(Who is this man?)
(It won't work on her.)
Hey, girls. Byul.
(Si Young tries to talk to Byul.)
You're so pretty, Byul.
- You're eating a lot. - Don't be scared.
Can I pet her?
- Can I pet her, sir? - Yes, pet her gently.
- Gently. - You must approach gently.
When they know you're safe, they are relieved.
Here.
- Byul, do you want to eat this? - Here.
(I feel pretty comfortable around this guy.)
She feels at ease with you. Now, you do a headlock on her.
(We've just gotten close.)
That was sudden.
- I have to do that on her? - Yes.
When you do it, pretend you're playing, and someone must feed her.
One of you must milk her.
Then one of us can do the headlock. Another one will feed her.
- And the other one will milk her. - Right.
- You can milk these 2 sheep. - These 2?
- These two. - Who?
- Her and her. - These two here.
If you milk these 2, you can fill up 5 bottles.
- Where is Al Tu? - Here.
- I should get her. - Al Tu.
- You got to know her earlier. - Try this. It's fine.
(What are these guests doing?)
(Haha will feed her, Kwang Soo will hold her neck,)
(and Si Young will milk her.)
Let's eat.
- Wait, hold on. She bites. - Feed her. Haha.
- Okay, okay. - She has to eat.
- Should I try milking her? - Okay.
I'll wipe it for you.
- All right. - Should I get the bottle?
- I brought it here. - Hurry.
- Feed her more. - Milking her from the back is...
- easier than from the sides. - From the back?
(Switching her places)
- From the back. - Here you go.
- It stings. It sings. - Hold on.
- Wait, hold on. She bites me now. - Hold on.
Hold on. She's on top of me. She's on top of me.
(It's true. The sheep settles down on Kwang Soo's knee.)
(As everyone struggles, they kick up a ruckus.)
My knee.
Hold her. Hold her. Wait a second.
(She escapes furiously.)
(Their first attempt is a big failure.)
I had it in my hand.
(She really bit me.)
- People can't withstand her power. - Of course, not.
She's as powerful as an ox. Seriously.
(You will have to use every ounce of your energy.)
(They try for the 2nd time.)
Al Tu.
I'm not here to bother you. I mean it.
Byul. I'm not bothering you. I'm serious.
Hey, I was born in the Year of Sheep.
Byul.
(Byul stays still as if she understood Si Young.)
(Come and milk me already.)
Can we get some food for her?
(Kwang Soo calmly embraces the sheep unlike his first try.)
Try not to scare Byul.
- Haha, feed her from the front. - Okay.
(Haha and Si Young take their places.)
All right, Byul. Eat this. Let's eat.
(My wife's name is Byul too. Let's eat, Byul.)
This is how you do it.
(Let me demonstrate.)
You grabbed it, right?
(Dripping)
- Great job. - Is it coming out?
Yes.
Yes, it's coming out.
(Luckily, the sheep milk is coming out.)
- You can eat this. - This won't take long.
You can eat this.
Gosh, it smells savory. It smells like milk.
That's right. You're getting a hang of it now.
(Doing her best)
I filled up a bottle. I filled it up.
(She successfully fills up 1L out of 4L.)
- Okay, hand it over, please. - My gosh.
(The bottle is warm.)
Gosh, it's really warm.
Byul is feeling comfortable now. She's not moving anymore.
- Her body feels light after this. - I see.
Holding a bottle of this is heavy.
- Imagine carrying it on your back. - Imagine you have to...
- carry 4 to 5 bottles. - Exactly.
- We have to milk them then. - Right.
Their bodies get lighter. It feels good for them too.
Their bodies feel light.
(Gushing out)
It's coming out so easily. It won't take long now.
Gosh, Si Young. Our team leader is awesome.
(This is nothing.)
(With her soft touches, she milks the sheep without hesitation.)
Byul, I'm almost done.
- Okay. - Massage it.
- Haha, do we have one more bottle? - Okay, here you go.
Did you finish already?
(He's scared of the tail and spills the milk.)
She startled me.
(This is the skill of a national athlete.)
(Si Young quickly fills up 3L of sheep milk.)
- Byul, I'll milk a different one. - Gosh, seriously.
- It smells really savory. - I'll get one from the other side.
- I'll milk one from the other side. - It's all right.
Seriously. Mothers are amazing.
You can fill up two bottles of sheep milk...
- from just one udder. - Right.
- I'm tearing up now. - You can milk more than that.
(Byul starts dozing off while getting milked)
- Sir, I think she's sleepy. - Pardon?
- I think she's sleepy. - I guess you have soft hands.
- She's closing her eyes. - She feels comfortable.
She's blinking her eyes slowly. She must be sleepy.
It'd be nice if she could fill up all the bottles.
This is your last bottle.
(At that time, she cries.)
(Did she try to speak her first line?)
I think she just thanked her, right?
It sounded like, "Thank you."
(He translates it very liberally.)
"Gosh, it feels nice."
"Thank you."
You're welcome.
(Did he learn the sheep language?)
(They accomplish their mission by gathering 4L of sheep milk.)
(Thank you. I feel like I can fly as my body feels light.)
You successfully gathered 4L of sheep milk.
(Team Si Young accomplishes their first mission.)
- This is so touching. - It's so warm.
- I can't smile. - It feels weird.
I would like to give this glory to Byul.
Thanks to you, we got to experience something so special.
- Thank you. - Good job.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Great job. - Thank you.
We'll give you a chance to select your next mission.
Since none of the teams completed their mission...
Really?
That is why you will have three choices to pick from.
(They can pick the mission they want out of 3 remaining missions.)
(Trying the most recent hairstyles in Osaka)
(Fishing king crabs along with 10 types of fish in Russia)
(Catching the fish you tasted at a restaurant on Tsushima Island)
As for this one,
can you two do this?
(Can you do the Osaka mission?)
- Actually, I... - The Chinese queue is trending.
As for me,
until I finish filming the movie, I cannot cut my back hair.
Is that so?
I'm shooting a drama right now.
As for me, next month,
I am to get the dreadlocks again.
- Let's give that back. - We will...
- exclude this one. - Sure, sure.
This won't work.
We went to Russia and came back after a crushing failure.
We couldn't do this even in Russia.
What's the next one?
- Let's look at the next one. - Goodness, this.
- "Catching fish you tasted"? - We tried this mission.
- We did it with Sang Yeob. - Right, right.
(When the staff gave them a generous meal, they ate it up.)
(But their gluttony led to a complete failure of the mission.)
By the way, it's the fish we will taste.
We don't have to eat them.
- In that case, - Exactly.
we don't have to eat the assorted sashimi.
(Everyone uses their brain capacity to the fullest at times like this.)
- Exactly. We won't eat that. - We should just avoid that.
- Isn't this doable then? - I agree.
- The side dishes are the tastiest. - Right.
- I love the corns with cheese. - I love it.
- That's my favorite. - Corns with cheese.
- We'll pick Tsushima Island. - We'll settle on Tsushima Island.
- 1, 2, 3. Tsushima Island. - We've decided.
- We'll head to a sashimi place. - Okay.
- We'll go to a sashimi place. - We'll reveal the mission there.
- I see. - Okay.
- It's perfect for our dinner. - There must be a twist.
(What will be the modified mission for Tsushima Island be?)
(As for Team Ji Hyo's mission is...)
(treating 100 people to a meal.)
- This is hard. - We have so many ingredients.
It'll take a long time to prepare them.
We're doomed.
(They must cook potato dough soup, pancakes, and suyuk.)
Since the elders of the village go to sleep early,
- you must serve them by 6:30pm. - What did you say?
(They must prepare it by 6:30pm to fit their regular dinnertime.)
This is terrible.
- What should we do then? - First,
let's wash these ingredients.
(There's no time to lose.)
It's really heavy.
Hello, ma'am.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan go around to spread the word.)
We would like to cook a meal for you.
You should come by and tell us when everything is ready.
(There's only one way to spread the word about the meal.)
Hey, shouldn't we go up there?
(They must go around the whole village to spread the word.)
We'll serve it at 6:30pm I know it's slightly late.
(They must serve the meal by 6:30pm and gather 100 people by 7:30pm.)
Do you know what's happening at 6:30pm?
- We'll serve you food at 6:30pm. - Come over there later.
We'll give you delicious food.
(Will Team Ji Hyo be able to cook a meal for 100 people?)
I'm serious. I mean it.
We'll see you later.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo and Byul start preparing the ingredients.)
When will I wash all of them?
Since the elders go to sleep early...
I'm rushing it now.
So we should hurry, shouldn't we?
Gosh, there's so much we have to do. We're in trouble.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
We don't have much time left. Seriously.
(She prepares the ingredients one by one under the pressure.)
You know what?
We have so many potatoes. We need to peel them quickly.
Where's the newest producer who seemed to be a terrible cook?
Can you at least get us someone?
Will you use one of your ballots?
Fine, I will.
We'll offer you a deal.
If you give us back one of your ballots,
you'll get a new producer as your assistant.
You just used one of your ballots.
- Okay. - This is Producer Yoo Jung Chan.
Jung Chan.
Hurry.
By the way, have you cooked before?
- This is my first time. - What?
(He knows nothing about cooking.)
Goodness, it's driving me crazy.
But even if he hasn't done it, he might have a knack for it.
Do you see the sides here?
You have to carve this part out.
(Under Ji Hyo's instruction, he's trying to find his secret talent.)
(Come out, my talent.)
Stop right there. Do you job right.
What is this? Look what you did.
This is for the elders. Do your job right!
- I was trying to do it faster. - Faster?
You're so frustrating!
I would like to ask for my ballot back.
- He's still on his first potato. - I think...
- he's more like an obstacle. - Goodness, he is...
- still on his second one. - He might just cause trouble.
- How could you be so slow? - I'm trying right now.
- I'll pick up my speed. - You're unbelievable.
By the way, I'm curious.
Are they preparing for the meal? We don't have any helper.
- I can't trust that producer. - You mean the new producer?
- He seemed he knew nothing. - Right.
(He looks like he knows nothing about cooking.)
- They're back. - They're back.
(They finally return after going around the village.)
- Hold on. - Hurry.
- What is this? You already got him? - Are we using the new producer?
Yes, I did. I had no choice.
- Come on. You shouldn't have. - Why not?
- We thought he wouldn't be of help. - He won't be helpful.
We were talking about that before coming in.
We thought that he wouldn't be much help anyway.
We thought about getting someone else even if...
- we had to use more ballots. - What's that?
- That... - Why are you holding the camera?
- Me? - Yes.
We went to interview people.
When I asked them if they knew who he was,
they said they knew.
They asked if Se Chan wasn't the cameraman.
- Se Chan? - That's what they said.
Since then, he became a cameraman.
Let me wash my hands first.
- What should we do first? - The dough soup.
- We should peel the potatoes first. - Yes.
- What is he doing? - He's peeling potatoes.
- That's not how you do it! - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Are you sharpening pencils? Let me see how you did it.
Jong Kook, we're not lying. We used him for two minutes.
Ji Hyo got angry only after a minute.
Why did you get this delicate guy?
Can we get someone else instead of him?
He said we couldn't.
Hey.
(Hey, Mr. Producer. Please do a good job.)
(I'll do a good job.)
We have to grind the potatoes as soon as we can.
- How will we do that? - Then potatoes will have layers.
- Jong Kook. Here. - Okay. Where? I see.
- Grind it, and pour it there. - Into this?
Okay.
(Jong Kook, the human blender, starts working.)
(Se Chan starts peeling the potato with an invisible motor.)
I have a question. I'm really curious.
- Do you cut your bangs? - My bangs?
(His bangs are crooked.)
(The new producer's harsh struggle at his job)
I was really curious.
- Are you all right? - I asked him because...
- I was curious. - Hang in there. I was there too.
I thought his hairstyle was cute.
(Getting his microphone)
- Hold on. - Where are you going?
(Where are you going? You were working!)
Come back.
(Meanwhile, when the new producer is getting used to this environment...)
We're done peeling the potatoes.
- You're done? - Yes.
- Great! - I'm done.
- Jong Kook, use a blender. - Yes?
- That will take forever. - We don't have time.
- We can use a blender? - Yes, we can do it with a blender.
Then why did you give me this?
It was...
We're busy right now. Just use the blender.
Byul, she said I could use a blender. Why am I doing this?
(She said I could use the blender.)
Isn't it nice? It makes you look like you're working hard.
(It makes you look like a helpful guy.)
- This is crazy. - Jong Kook.
- I wanted you to stand out. - That's why.
You can show off your arm muscles.
(If so, I'll work harder.)
- Jong Kook, seriously. - But I grated a lot of potatoes.
- It's been a while. - I'll make the broth then.
- Okay. - Se Chan will replace me.
The knife is not very sharp.
(Se Chan starts julienning the carrots.)
(It's not perfect, but he does his best.)
Gosh.
Use that.
(Mandoline?)
- That one. - Like this?
Wait.
(Convenient)
Byul, it works.
Why were you using a knife?
It's so fast this way.
We had a mandoline?
It's so fast.
We have to make 100 servings.
Why were you using a knife?
Okay.
I need to scoop them out.
(Everyone is busy preparing the ingredients.)
Let me have a taste.
(Byul starts making the stock.)
(The star chef leads the project of making 100 servings.)
(She chose the dishes herself and studied the recipes.)
(She even considered the balance between carbs and protein.)
We have to boil the meat too.
We have to make pancakes too.
That's going in the batter anyway.
(Her charisma makes even Jong Kook obey her.)
You don't have to stir it.
Be generous with ingredients.
(Everyone, follow me.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Don't forget to julienne the zucchinis.
Okay.
(Okay. As you say.)
I have to julienne the zucchinis too?
- Yes. - Okay.
(I was nobody until the star chef called my name.)
Chop the onions too.
Okay.
(I was nobody until the star chef called my name.)
Gosh.
It's separating, right?
We're using only what's at the bottom.
But it takes a while for it to separate.
Do we need more zucchinis?
Use more.
We're making 100 servings.
(Ji Hyo, the knife girl)
(I can chop everything.)
(There's nothing she can't chop.)
Jong Kook, put these in...
and add a bit of water.
- Right. Otherwise, it won't blend. - No.
It needs water.
(It won't blend without water?)
(But his glare would blend anything.)
(He cooks with his eyes.)
Okay, good.
It's perfect.
(His glare makes potatoes melt.)
This step takes the longest.
(It takes the longest time to make the batter.)
Give me that.
(Trust me.)
(Glaring)
(Like ripening rice plants,)
(Jong Kook bows down while blending potatoes.)
My back hurts.
(Jong Kook blends the potatoes with his eyes.)
I can't believe we were going to use a grater.
We wouldn't have been finished until tomorrow morning.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook work together.)
I hope it'll taste good.
So do I. We're making it with care.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook are making dough soup.)
- It'll taste good. - Se Chan.
- Let's prepare water for the meat. - Okay.
Byul.
We should chop the pork first.
You're right.
It's okay with big chunks, right?
Just as big as fresh pork belly.
That looks good.
That's how big the chunks should be when boiling.
Like this.
- It looks good. - It looks good.
- It looks very good. - It's going to taste so good.
It's going to taste good.
Ground coffee...
I read on the internet that ground coffee helps.
It removes the bad smell.
It's okay with just beer.
- Instead of water? - You need water too.
- Coffee is better. - Coffee?
I used just beer a few days ago,
and it tasted very good. It became really soft.
If you have different opinions, why don't we just order it?
I know this old lady. I can ask her for help.
She can prepare a lot.
It'd be better than fighting like this.
(Every family has a different recipe.)
I think we can put everything.
Put everything.
Okay!
Making 100 servings is no easy task.
- Of course. - It's so much work.
Gosh.
- I'm adding beer. - Okay.
- Okay! - Good!
Good!
And some coffee.
(Ground coffee is added too.)
It smells like cappuccino.
Bay leaves.
(All the good ingredients are added.)
Are you sure it's not too much?
It's not.
- Just put a lot. - We're making 100 servings.
We have to serve delicious food.
It's hot.
(The meat goes in.)
It smells good.
- It smells good. - Peppercorns.
- It smells good. - It's already cooking.
(All the preparation for suyuk is done.)
We have to make pancakes too.
- Se Chan, prepare chili peppers. - Okay.
What should I do now?
- Please remove the shrimp tails. - Shrimp tails.
Squid, onions, zucchinis, and carrots.
(There's so much to do.)
Can we make it?
Can we make it? Do we have enough time?
My goodness.
(They speed up.)
I don't think we have enough time.
(But time passes by faster and faster.)
How are we going to finish everything?
I removed all the tails.
I'm worried about time.
I've never prepared so much food at once before.
- What is this? - How much chili peppers?
(The sun is setting.)
100 servings is a lot.
Let's start frying the pancakes now.
Se Chan and I will do it.
Jong Kook and I will make dough soup.
Gosh.
My goodness.
(They divide up the work.)
100 servings is so much.
Luckily, the dough soup will be...
more than 100 servings.
(Will they manage to prepare 100 servings in time?)
It smells pretty good.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
That looks great.
(They put a lot of care into every dish.)
That was smart, right?
- It looks amazing. - I used chili peppers.
- Chili peppers? - Yes.
It looks great.
(They try their best to make the food look tasty.)
Look at this.
It looks amazing.
Green onion pancakes...
Gosh.
What time is it?
(They have about 40 minutes left.)
We're in trouble.
We have to finish in time.
A lot of people came already.
- Oh, no. - Really?
(A lot of people came already.)
(Some villagers have been waiting for an hour.)
Jong Kook, we're being a bit delayed.
Why don't you and I go and tell them?
I think the cameraman should go.
(He's reminded of a bad memory.)
I'm a cameraman. Talking is not my job.
I think the cameraman should go. What do you think?
I want the actor to come with me.
(Cameramen follow actors.)
Cameramen are supposed to follow actors.
(Persuaded)
- You have your camera ready? - Yes.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Film me while I put this on. Does it look good?
What should we tell them?
Let's tell them we're being a bit delayed.
- They'll have to wait. - That's right.
(How many came?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Full)
Sorry you had to wait.
Many people came.
(So many people came.)
We're sorry.
We've been preparing food,
and it's taking a lot of time.
So we came to apologize.
You're a bit bored, right?
- Yes! - I see.
- But now I feel good. - Are you sure?
- Are you happy to see us? - Yes!
- I don't feel hungry anymore. - For our guests...
We should sing a song.
(We want to hear a song.)
(Excited)
- While we wait, we should have fun. - Of course.
Let's have some fun.
- Let's go. - While we sing,
the staff will count...
how many of you are here.
(The number of guests will be count until 7:30pm.)
Please stay here.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They suddenly start to sing.)
(They sing "Unconditional", hoping they get more than 100 guests.)
(Fun)
Unconditional!
(Dancing)
(Enjoy our performance...)
(while you wait for food.)
(Their stage presence...)
(makes you stop feeling hungry.)
(Smiles...)
(come to the faces of the guests.)
(While Jong Kook and Se Chan are buying some time,)
(Byul is cooking with both hands.)
My goodness.
It's so much work to prepare 100 servings.
Does it work?
I hope it does.
(What if we don't get 100 guests?)
Come on in.
We're still counting the guests.
Delicious food will be served...
shortly.
You have to sing along.
Here we go.
(They sing "The Southbound Train" while waiting for more guests.)
Let's sing "The Southbound Train"!
Please sing along!
Let's have some fun!
Let's hear Jong Kook sing.
Here we go!
(The train leaves, hoping for the success of the mission.)
(The first table is full.)
(The other tables are almost full too.)
(But the food is not ready yet.)
(The performance makes it easier to wait for the food.)
When will the food be ready?
(Time is running out.)
How long do we have to wait?
(Only 10 minutes remain.)
We have to cut suyuk too.
I should check on it.
(Suyuk is ready.)
It looks good.
It looks delicious.
People have to eat it when it's still hot.
(Suyuk is marinated with various ingredients.)
- Look at this. - Goodness.
It's amazing.
(She plates the meat after cutting it into pieces.)
My goodness.
It looks delicious.
Chan Young.
- Yes? - Come here now.
Line up the plates.
- I'm Jung Chan. - Jung Chan.
(Don't forget. I'm Chan Young.)
We can count one plate for each table.
(Food is getting ready.)
(Jong Kook is having his year end concert in Gangwon Province.)
(Absorbed)
What is it?
I will love you
Give him a round of applause.
(They don't know how many people came.)
This is great.
You should sing one more.
All right.
Here I go.
(At that time)
Hello.
(Food arrives on time.)
(Did you wait a long time? Food is here.)
- Let's go. - Hello.
They're Ji Hyo and Byul.
Here's one.
Help yourselves.
Food is being served.
You haven't gotten one, right?
(Seafood pajeon and kimchi jeon are served.)
Enjoy.
- Enjoy. - Enjoy.
Here's some dough soup.
Ma'am, we worked very hard.
- Thank you for the food. - Please enjoy.
(Everyone regardless of age enjoys the food.)
How many minutes do we have left?
I don't know.
How many people are inside?
(Only 13 minutes remain.)
(Current number of people)
There are 95 people.
(It's 95 people.)
- We need 5 more people. - 5?
Five more people?
It won't be easy for five to come at this time.
We don't have time. Let's try to do something.
Wait, I'll check over there.
(How can we invite five more people?)
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
You should eat.
Excuse me. Please put a sticker on him.
You haven't eaten yet. You should go eat.
(They need 4 more people.)
- The village leader? - He was the last.
He's sitting at the edge of the table.
He didn't put the sticker on.
- Someone doesn't have the sticker. - There's someone.
At the end on the right?
Is any of you brother of the village leader?
- Brother of the village leader? - Do you not a number?
- Do you not have a number? - He doesn't.
(He is the 97th guest.)
We have 97 people.
Do you know anyone who is on his way?
Do you need more? Shall I call them?
- Ma'am. - Everyone came.
If they can come, invite them.
Please bring anyone you can.
- We need 3 more people. - We need 3 more.
- Three more. - Three more people?
Are they coming? Really?
- Three people are coming. - Where?
- Hurrry. - Go get them.
Here they are.
There they are. Ma'am.
Ma'am, here you go.
- Are we done? - We need one more person.
- Put one on the baby. - I'll put it on his head.
- That's cute. - He's so cute.
Enjoy your meal.
(They need 1 more person.)
Where?
Is the light on?
Is your husband coming?
(She calls her husband at home.)
- He should come. - I'll ask him.
We need one more person. I beg you.
What happened?
Is he coming?
It'd be disappointing If we're short on one person and fail.
(All their efforts could be in vain.)
- I'd feel so empty. - Me too.
(They have 2 minutes left.)
We only need one more person. Please.
Someone has to come quickly.
He must come fast.
- Someone is coming. - I think she's bringing him.
Someone is coming.
She's bringing him over there.
- He's coming. - Sir.
Ma'am.
(They have one minute before the time is up.)
(Behind the woman...)
(is her husband.)
Sir, you can take your time.
(They've been waiting for their last guest.)
- He came. - Sir.
Gosh, thank you for coming.
He ran here.
(100th guest arrives with 1 minute on the clock.)
He's here.
- Thank you, sir. - He arrived.
Please give him a round of applause.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Take a seat over there.
- Enjoy our food. - Goodness.
(We thank the residents of Songcheon, Gangwon Province.)
- Thank you. - Good job.
(Their busy night continues.)
- Good job. - Good job, everyone.
It's impressive how we cleared a mission.
- That's true. - Seriously.
To be honest,
we don't know the whole mission.
Though we're hungry, we didn't eat in case we suffer.
- Right. - We hardly ate anything.
Little bit of hunger is bearable.
We only had water and rice.
Why are we going to a sashimi restaurant?
It's for us to clear the mission.
Like sheep!
- We, who spare nothing to give! - Nothing to give!
- Are the best! - Are the best!
(They forget their hunger and temptation with the chant.)
Let's take a rest.
Could you turn off the lights?
(Team Si Young finally enjoys peace after a long fight.)
(Ruffling sounds)
(Wait, what is this ruffling sound?)
Turn on the light.
(This won't work.)
I'm sorry.
I wanted to take a rest.
Are you eating something alone?
(He starts to interrogate.)
(Gulping)
(All right.)
I had some.
(Yes, I ate a donut.)
Did you think I was sleeping?
(He starts to criticize.)
Is it delicious?
- Are you happy? - I'm low on sugar.
You should have some too.
No, you ruined my appetite.
No thank you.
Give me the ballot.
Or become our enemies.
I'd really like to know why you're angry.
- Listen. - Don't you know why?
No.
What? How can you eat?
This is all of my fault.
It's my fault.
I'll take out the ballot.
Take it if you really want it.
(He takes it immediately.)
(Gangster friends, always be happy and friendly to each other.)
(Punching)
(She takes back the ballot.)
Are you okay?
Am I okay?
- Excuse me, driver. - I'll turn them off.
(She's flustered.)
Thank you.
(After half a day, the driver realizes how to break their fight.)
Like sheep!
(Whenever they feel tempted)
- We, who spare nothing to give! - we, who spare nothing to give!
- Are the best! - Are the best!
(We're gangsters.)
Let's forget about it.
- I'm sorry for getting upset. - Okay.
(They arrive at a sashimi restaurant in Gangwon Province.)
(They're very hungry, and it's a feast.)
There's such a variety of dishes.
- Isn't this too harsh? - Look.
Is that what I think it is?
Everyone.
We prepared seasonal fish caught the most in Gangwon Province...
as well as other side dishes.
Help yourselves.
Excuse me.
(It's a luxurious yet resentful seafood course meal.)
Is this...
(We don't know what the mission is. Shall we just eat?)
What's our mission?
We'll tell you after the meal.
(Their mission in Gangwon Province will be announced after the meal.)
Pardon me?
(They must eat without knowing how the mission has changed.)
Isn't catching shrimp difficult?
Snow crabs are also difficult, right?
Don't we have to go to Jeju Island to catch sea urchin roe?
What we can eat is potatoes, kimchi...
(If we can't eat seafood)
Rolled omelette.
Excuse me.
Can we get three bowls of rice?
(She tears up.)
You should eat what you want. I'll do what I should.
- Are you about to cry? - Thank you for the food.
(He pours soy sauce.)
My goodness.
May I get some sesame oil?
Why is he pouring that?
This is rice with soy sauce and eggs.
(Peeking)
They keep taking down notes.
(The staff is taking down notes.)
(The staff is checking what the members eat.)
- Haha. - No.
Stop being so rash. We're a team.
What did you eat?
He ate something.
Eggs are fine.
They're writing something down.
We haven't eaten much.
- It's delicious. - It's delicious.
- It's delicious. - What's this?
- Did you serve some for yourself? - No.
(She served herself rolled omelette.)
No, I stopped myself.
You have three minutes left.
Let's eat one thing.
Only three minutes remain. It's better to hold back.
Let's try.
Let's eat one dish.
Listen.
We're at a sashimi restaurant.
(She looks for hint.)
Could you please stop doing that?
(He binges on rice with soy sauce and eggs.)
- Si Young. - Stop it.
You're scaring me. Stop it.
(Let's eat one fish.)
Aren't we going to eat anything?
Time is up, and we'll clear the table.
Before clearing the table, here's your mission since...
- Our mission is... - you really want to know.
We should have hard the mission earlier.
Let me pull it off.
Why are you pulling off everything?
(She's so sensitive as she hasn't eaten anything.)
Don't you think you're full of anger?
(Worried they'd have to catch a fish they ate,)
(they didn't eat any fish.)
(Was their guess right?)
"Get one of the ingredients you didn't eat."
(Get one of the ingredients you didn't eat.)
I told you we should eat!
Hold on. "Get one of the ingredients..."
"you didn't eat."
Let me tell you what we didn't eat.
This, this, this...
(There are too many.)
This, this, and this.
(Flounder, sea pineapple, sandfish, seabream,)
(shrimp, abalone, crab, sea urchin, rockfish, flatfish,)
(seaweed, cockle)
There are so many ingredients you didn't eat.
So we narrowed it down...
rockfish, sea bream, crab,
flatfish, sandfish, flounder, and shrimp.
We narrowed it down to seven.
- You'll pick... - The sandfish was full of roe.
I hope we'll pick sandfish.
It's in season, so it'll be easy to catch.
Flatfish is easy to catch too.
Pick one person who will make the choice.
- Si Young. - No.
- Please don't do this. - You're our leader.
You're our leader.
You should pick.
(They suddenly agree with each other.)
(Si Young will pick a kind of fish.)
I want you to pick one of the two.
- Flatfish or sandfish. - Sandfish.
If you succeed,
you'll be our hero.
You'll be our hero all day.
You know that it's an important choice, right?
Relax.
(Will she be a hero or an enemy?)
I'm not going to think too much.
(The success of their second mission is in Si Young's hands.)
I'll choose between the first and the last.
(She drops the rest.)
I'll choose one...
of these two.
Which one do you want?
(Which one will they choose?)
This one?
Then I'll choose the other one.
(Then I'll choose the other one.)
(Kwang Soo is always wrong.)
(That's a good idea.)
(They made a logical choice.)
(Will they get either sandfish or flatfish?)
(Let me see.)
(Is it something hard to catch?)
What is it?
(Worried)
Is it crab?
No way.
(Haha takes a look.)
(Is it either sandfish or flatfish?)
(Or is it something more difficult?)
No way.
(Worried)
(Sandfish)
Yes!
(The sandfish hero)
Like sheep...
(Let's shout it together!)
We, who spare nothing to give!
- Are the best! - Are the best!
(Like sheep, we, who spare nothing to give, are the best!)
(Their second mission is decided.)
(In Tsushima Island, they had to catch a fish they ate.)
(In Gangwon Province, they'll catch sandfish, which they didn't eat.)
All right.
After catching a sand fish, there is an additional mission...
you have to complete.
(They have to complete an additional mission too.)
- What? - There's another mission?
Please hear me out.
It turns out...
sandfish are caught early in the morning.
So you'll have to wake up at 3am.
(They have to wake up at 3am.)
Can we even say we'll "wake up"?
We'll have to stay up all night.
You can go back to the guesthouse now.
Like sheep!
(Whenever things get tough...)
- We, who spare nothing to give! - We, who spare nothing to give!
- Are the best! - Are the best!
(What will the sandfish mission be like?)
- That's right. - It was here.
This is where we got on the taxi.
It was right here.
- It was here, right? - Gosh.
(Where did it go wrong?)
We must be possessed by noodles ghosts.
(Are we in a wantanmien trap?)
(But the worst part starts here.)
(The steak mission started in Okinawa.)
(Soba, ramen, soba, ramen...)
(They were caught up in a noodle maze.)
Taxi.
(They resume the steak mission in Hong Kong.)
(The noodle torture starts again.)
I don't believe we'll eat noodles after this too.
(They can't seem to escape.)
(They get a taxi to get out of the area.)
(But...)
(they're back to the wantanmien place.)
(Will they be able to wake up from this nightmare?)
- We must be possessed. - It's driving me crazy.
- It's like the Mobius strip. - It's unbelievable.
They already closed, and we're back here.
When we went far away...
Is it closed?
Yes, we're closed.
Okay.
Guys.
(The wantanmien place is closed.)
Please try again.
Do you want to spin it? Should I do it?
Seriously...
We have to meet a taxi driver.
We have to get out of here.
We have to get out of the area.
Please.
(As So Min wishes, will they meet a taxi driver?)
(A convenience store clerk?)
- Convenience store clerk. - Convenience store clerk.
- Convenience store clerk. - Convenience store.
- Let's find a convenience store. - Convenience store clerk.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They look for a convenience store.)
- Let's find a convenience store. - But...
I have a feeling they'll say noodles again.
- That's not okay. - I have a feeling.
I'm traumatized.
(Don't even say that.)
We're shooting Running Noodles, not Running Man.
Running Noodles.
- Running Noodles. - Running Noodles.
We're shooting Running Noodles now.
Running Noodles.
(They still haven't given up completely.)
Noodles.
(They arrive at a convenience store.)
We're here.
So Min, do you want to go in alone?
(For a change)
- So Min, try it again. - Try it again.
(1 unlucky person is better than 3.)
- Please bring us a good result. - So Min.
Please.
(Let me try.)
Good luck.
(No more noodles.)
This is just like last time.
(Let me think.)
- Heo Kyeong Hwan... - He went in alone.
asked a convenience store clerk,
- and she said ramen. - Ramen.
(Kyeong Hwan went into a convenience store alone...)
(and asked the clerk.)
(Ramen)
(The situation is similar.)
Excuse me.
(If the clerk recommends steaks, the mission is complete.)
Here.
Your favorite food...
(Is it noodles again?)
One dish.
(Or will they finally have steaks?)
Please.
So Min is talking to him.
- We have to get out of here. - She's talking to him.
- No more noodles. - So Min is talking to him.
Please.
How does her face look?
- I can't see it. - You can't?
It can't be wantanmien again.
No way.
All the wantanmien places are closing down right now.
What's your choice?
(The clerk finally decides on the dish.)
(Let me write it down for you.)
(If it's steaks, the mission is complete.)
(If not, they have to eat the food and try again.)
Her eyes became so big.
It must be something new.
Please.
- Here she comes. - She's coming out.
So Min.
- Jae Seok. - What did he say?
Is it something good? She's laughing.
(So Min is just laughing.)
You looked surprised.
What is it?
Stop it.
(It doesn't feel right.)
Be quiet.
Jae Seok.
I'm going home.
(What does it mean?)
- What is it? - The clerk wrote it down.
- What is it? - Last time...
(What did the clerk write?)
- Fishball noodles? - Fishball noodles?
(Fishball noodles?)
(Noodles again?)
(Noodles for the 4th time in a row?)
- It's noodles. - Is it different from wantanmien?
- It's noodles again. - Fishball noodles.
(The clerk kindly writes down the name of the food.)
(So Min can't take her eyes off.)
(I recommend it.)
- Noodles? - Yes.
(Hold on.)
(It says, "noodles".)
(Dizzy)
What am I going to say to the guys?
(Worried)
Think about it.
In Japan, Kyeong Hwan went into a convenience store,
and the clerk wrote down the name of the food.
It was ramen.
At that time, it was either soba or ramen.
But this time, it's wantanmien every time.
Only wantanmien.
- I mean... - All right.
(3 wantanmiens in a row)
All right. Running Noodles.
Running Noodles.
The noodle trap.
The second part.
Last time, we were in Japan. And now we're in Hong Kong.
We're the hosts this time too.
- We're having our 3rd wantanmien. - Our 3rd wantanmien.
Let's go.
- Running Noodles! - Running Noodles!
- Running Noodles. - Are we really doing it?
- I can't believe it. - Seriously?
Gosh. Let's go.
(Already full of noodles, they find a fishball noodles place.)
It's our third noodles.
I can't eat anymore.
- Me neither. - We're not going to succeed.
After eating here,
we'll have to ask the staff...
to get us out of this area.
I want to go far away.
There's a famous night market around this area.
- Mong Kok night market? - Yes.
Isn't this the night market?
No. Shall we go there?
They have various types of food...
- including steak. - Let's go somewhere else.
A touristy place.
- Let's go to a place like that. - Right.
Many people are eating noodles.
- Everyone is eating noodles. - Wantanmien is...
- very famous in Hong Kong. - It must be their staple food.
(People in Hong Kong love noodles.)
(It's their soul food as it's simple and satisfying.)
(Fishball noodles are made with taut fish cakes and rice noodles.)
Let's search wantanmien in Hong Kong.
When we got off for the third time...
- I was surprised. - Seriously.
I wanted to cry.
- Wantanmien is famous. - I told you.
Wantanmien is famous in Hong Kong.
- Why don't people mention dim sum? - I know.
In Hong Kong, dim sum also means lunch.
- People recommend it for lunch. - They eat it for lunch.
They don't recommend it for dinner.
It's a simpler meal.
Here are the best five dishes in Hong Kong.
Number one, dim sum.
What's number two?
See? Dim sum is for lunch.
Number two is wantanmien.
(I knew it.)
What's number three?
Food is here.
(Food is served with shocking news.)
It's a lot.
It's a game of loyalty.
(Their loyalty to noodles starts again.)
- This much is enough. - You should eat more.
- Take some more. - I can smell it.
Hey.
(Piling up)
My stomach is about to burst.
We have to eat it.
- Gosh. - This is interesting.
Does it taste different?
Aren't there any toppings?
- It's different from the last one. - How is it?
The broth color is different.
- It's like beef bone broth. - It's completely different.
- Do you mean the taste? - The taste is different.
- Are these called fish balls? - It's fish cake.
It's fish cake.
- It's fish cake. - Let me try it.
(How are fish balls different?)
It tastes like...
fish cakes.
(He makes an obvious statement.)
We're in Hong Kong.
Why are we only eating noodles?
(He's getting annoyed.)
You should have asked better.
Why didn't you ask more carefully?
(He's not content.)
These are similar to udon noodles.
There's nothing I like about you.
(Forget it. There's nothing I like about you.)
(There he goes again.)
He's blaming me.
I wanted to get closer to you in Hong Kong.
My goodness.
Seok Jin.
(I'm 53 years old.)
These are delicious.
The broth is good too.
It tastes like rice noodles.
(It's still tasty.)
We finished.
That was our third noodle dish.
(Unhappy)
- I'm tired. - Look at the time.
- My stomach is so full. - It's 9pm.
Why don't we leave this neighborhood?
- Please. - Let's go somewhere else.
Let's go to the city center.
- Let's go somewhere else. - This neighborhood...
Seok Jin did some research...
on the Internet.
This place is famous for wantanmien.
- It's famous here. - It's a famous street.
- Is it number two? - It's second most popular food...
- Many people eat wantanmien. - among people in Hong Kong...
- It's wantanmien. - is wantanmien.
- I didn't know. It's dim sum. - What was number one?
Dim sum is usually eaten for lunch.
We'll go to a different place.
- Okay. - Let's go to the car.
- Let's go. - Let's go to the city.
- We'll leave this neighborhood. - Let's go far.
Restaurants are starting to close.
- They're closed. - Right?
I hope they'll close earlier than later.
- Hurry. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(They move in a hurry.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Is there a way to lead them to steak?
What about wear a T-shirt...
that has a steak on it?
A steak printed on it.
- If there's one, we should buy it. - I know.
- We need steak t-shirts. - Right.
Do whatever it takes.
It's time for people in Hong Kong to turn out the lights and sleep.
How will we get food?
I know.
Parental guidance is advised for viewers under the age of 12.
(She says it all of a sudden.)
- Be quiet. - What is she doing?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
This is what I wish.
After 7pm,
it changes to viewers under the age of 15...
during the shoot.
(What is she saying?)
- During the shoot? - Yes.
I think you should be on a show...
that's aired after midnight.
- She'd be good at it. - Right.
Your acrostic poem with "Haha" was fun.
(While selecting her partner)
(Haha, you're very sexy.)
(Breathing hard)
(It's not for viewers under the age of 12.)
(She surprised everyone then.)
That was for age over 12. If the age was 15,
- Would it be different? - it'd be different.
How would you do it?
- Ha. - Since the age was 12,
I did this. If it were 15,
I'd do this.
(She sticks out her tongue.)
(Here is promiscuous So Min.)
My goodness.
She's so annoying.
Look at you.
It's different if the age limit is 19.
- Stop it. - What is it?
Stop it.
(I won't hurt you.)
What should I do with So Min?
(We love Jeon So Min. Late night show, let's go.)
She's slowly getting loose.
Isn't she?
- Look at the night view. - It's beautiful.
- It's amazing. - It's beautiful.
It's a priceless night view.
It's famous for its night view.
It's really amazing.
- Goodness. - Look at this.
- It's great. - This is a great place.
It's a perfect place for steak.
There's a steak restaurant.
Here's a steak restaurant.
(He gets excited.)
It's written "Steakhouse".
(His tone rises.)
- Seok Jin, lower your voice. - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I got excited.
How could I not get excited when there's a steakhouse?
Here it is.
What if we ask in front of it?
This is the street.
(We may clear the mission.)
- It's beautiful. - This is the street.
(Stars whisper on the night street in Hong Kong)
(They're the most excited they have been in Hong Kong.)
- How do you know this song? - I do.
How?
(After a long bus ride, they arrive at Mong Kok Night Market.)
Look how bright it is.
It's starting now.
- It's like during the day. - It starts during the day.
It's like during the day.
(Mong Kok Night Market)
Hello.
It's the most popuar Mong Kok Night Market in Hong Kong.
I know.
You will give it a try again.
Goodness.
- Spin it, Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
(He spins the roulette.)
(Who will be the one to recommend?)
Someone whose last name is Wang.
- That's good. - Someone whose last name is Wang.
- Wang. - Let's go over there.
We should ask people's names.
This is a touristy place.
Mong Kok Night Market is a touristy spot.
It must be a famous place.
- It's a night market. - Is this it?
Doesn't it look fun, So Min?
- Yes, it looks fun. - Is it your first time?
I've never been here before either.
There are a lot of things.
- Look. - I want to look around.
Goodness.
- Don't you want to shop? - Yes.
Is there anyone whose last name is Wang?
I heard that there are many.
Really?
How will we ask someone whose last name is Wang?
Asking will be hard.
(How should we ask?)
- Shall we ask? - How do we ask...
- for people's names? - We should ask people's names.
(They learn how to ask.)
Pardon?
(Stammering)
(What is your last name?)
(They go to a wider road than a small alleyway.)
- How about him? - Let's ask him.
(Shall we ask him?)
(They ask the first local person.)
Let's ask him.
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
What is your last name?
- What? - What is your last name?
(How will he respond to their first question?)
(My last name is...)
My last name is Lei.
- "Lei"? - "Lei"?
(Of course it is.)
(What about the man next to her?)
(His last name is Zhang.)
(Neither of their last name is Wang.)
- He's Mr. Zhang. - Zhang?
(Thank you for answering.)
Didn't they say that there are many Wang's?
That's what I heard.
(Among the crowd, who has Wang as their last name?)
Excuse me.
What is your last name?
My last name?
It's Tan.
Tan? Tan.
Lao? Thank you.
They are not the ones.
(It isn't easy.)
Thank you.
- Aren't they Wang? - No.
Her last name was Tan.
(Wang sounds similar to Korean.)
What is your last name?
(They'll recognize it once they hear it.)
- Lan? - Lan.
What's your last name?
Tung.
- Tung? - I see.
- Thank you. - Thank you for your answer.
(They fail again.)
It's difficult.
- It's hard to find. - There's a variety of last names.
How about her?
- What's your last name? - What's your last name?
It's Tung.
- "Tung"? - That's not it.
What is your name?
It's Isaac Lim.
- Lim. - "Lim"?
What is your last name?
(Wang is impossible to find.)
Okay.
- Zhi. - What's your last name?
Cheon?
- There's no one named Wang. - Hello.
What is your last name?
It's Wong.
- Wang? - Wang?
(Is his last name Wang?)
- Wang? - W, o, n, g.
W, a, n, g?
- W, o, n, g. - W, o, n, g?
Is it correct?
(Wong is also correct.)
We have to say this.
(They found him! It's time to get a menu recommendation.)
(They're in Mong Kok and hope to succeed the mission.)
(What menu does Mr. Wong recommend?)
(Is it steak this time?)
(He recommends...)
(They found him! It's time to get a menu recommendation.)
(They're in Mong Kok and hope to succeed the mission.)
(What menu does Mr. Wong recommend?)
(Is it steak this time?)
(He recommends...)
(Taiwanese noodles.)
(Noodles again?)
(Oh, dear.)
Taiwanese noodles? Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(It's noodles again.)
It's noodles again.
(They didn't even get close to steak since they got to Hong Kong.)
(They've been around noodles the whole time.)
(Again?)
(Yes, again.)
(They couldn't get away from noodles.)
(You can't be eliminated even if you wish to.)
(They had three bowls of noodles.)
(Taiwan noodles is their fourth.)
- There's meat this time. - Thank you.
- It's red. - Hello. Thank you.
- Beef noodles? - Thank you.
Right. I like how red it is.
- This... - It's different.
- is still... - It's Taiwanese style, right?
It's thick.
(The noodles are really thick.)
(That was a surprise.)
- It's thick. - I see the noodles.
I knew, but I looked just in case.
There's so much noodles.
There are carrots and meat.
The carrots and meat make it look like...
- Those noodles... - the noodles in Okinawa.
They look like those noodles.
This looks like the noodles in Okinawa.
Noodles in Okinawa had meat.
Well...
Should I try the meat? There are dumplings.
(Hold on. Are these dumplings?)
Thank you.
For free? It's not necessary.
(Goodness, she doesn't have to.)
- We had too many. - She doesn't have to do that.
(Hong Kong people are too nice, so they don't know what to do.)
- I'm too full. - There's so much to eat.
(They have noodles plus the dumplings.)
- She didn't have to do that. - I'm too full.
My stomach is about to explode.
- I feel drunk. - We keep eating.
(They have to finish the noodles fast.)
- Thank you for the food. - I'll have this.
(They feast on flour, carbohydrate, and protein at night.)
You're having as much noodles as you want.
This tastes like the noodles in Okinawa.
- Does it? - Really?
(They reminisce the old memory and slurp on the noodles.)
(It's clean.)
That was good.
- I'm full, but that was good. - Good.
All right.
(That was good. Thank you for the food!)
That was good.
- Bye. - Bye.
(They can't give in. They have to try again before it's too late.)
- I'm so full. - Where are you going?
(He has to vomit.)
(The noodles are about to escape.)
- I... - I can't walk.
This is so hard. I miss my mom.
I... Be cautious.
Don't irritate me. If you poke me,
I'll spit noodles at you.
I'll spit noodles from my mouth.
How many bowls did we have?
(They start acting odd after having four bowls.)
Dumplings.
(Eating one food only is dangerous.)
It had meat in it.
It wasn't steak, but it was boiled.
(It doesn't even look like steak.)
Do you want one last chance?
- Yes, please give us a last chance. - Let's do it.
- Spin this for the last time. - Okay.
- This is our last chance. - Okay.
This is your last chance.
- You should spin it. - I will try it.
I'm sick of this.
(Can they finally succeed this time?)
(The last person to recommend a menu is...)
- Someone whose last name is Wang. - Wang.
(It's Wang again.)
This is our last chance.
(If they take too long again, they'll be in trouble.)
Let's go. That way.
(Let's hurry.)
- Let's look for them. - Okay, let's split up.
(Where is Wang this late at night?)
Let's split up and look for Wang.
(Let's split up and look.)
Hello. Excuse me.
(Is your last name...)
(Mine is Liu.)
You?
- Mine is Hao. - Hao? I see. Thank you.
(There is nobody named Wang.)
- What now? - Excuse me. What is your last name?
(It's late, so there's less people and the restaurants are closing.)
(If they take too long, they will fail the mission.)
There's nobody.
(Where is Wang?)
What is your last name?
Choy?
(What about the person next to you?)
- My last name is Wu. - Is that so?
What is your name?
It's Wong.
Are you Wong?
(Are you Wong?)
(Are you really Mr. Wong?)
(They find a person whose last name is Wong.)
Is it right? Is he Wong?
Okay, I found him!
You did? Seok Jin, did you find him?
I think he found somebody.
- Did you find a person? - I did. Thank you.
This is Wong.
- We'll try for one last time. - We're serious.
All right!
(A food recommendation? Let's see.)
What menu?
- One. - Best menu.
(Please recommend one dish.)
- Tell us. - Please.
(If he recommends steak, they succeed right away.)
- Name of the menu? - A menu?
(Mr. Wong is the last person.)
(What does he recommend?)
("Gon Chow Fun"?)
- What's that? - Beef...
(Beef?)
(Did he recommend steak?)
Beef fried noodles.
(Stop dreaming.)
(They were hopeful for a moment,)
(but he doesn't recommend steak.)
(Beef what?)
Thank you.
(Is this for real?)
- Beef. - Really?
- Beef fried noodles. - Beef fried...
- Is it noodles? - Fried noodles?
- It's noodles, right? - Is that what he said?
- Sir. - Where's the restaurant?
I don't think that's what he said. He didn't say noodles.
I'm serious. It's in Cantonese.
Is it beef fried noodles?
Why do Hong Kong people love noodles?
I'm sorry!
(I'm sorry, Producer!)
- Stop this! - I can't eat no more.
Let's just say we failed.
- We'll stop eating noodles. - Please send us home.
- Goodness. - Don't do this.
Mister. Mr. Producer. Please let us stop eating.
- We can't eat anymore. - Please.
- We can't eat. - Let's just say we failed.
We can't have beef fried noodles.
All right. Your failed...
your mission today. From nine people,
at least one person has to get the punishment.
That's a relief.
- 1 in 9 people? - There are ballots.
- That's not bad. - That's fine.
- It might not be us. - We can vote for one person.
Let's give our votes to one person.
- That's right. - To end this off,
let's eat beef fried noodles and conclude today's mission.
How do we eat more?
We tried to get away, but it's noodles again.
(What?)
They sell steak?
- Where? - They sell steak here.
They sell steak.
Look.
- This is it. - There's steak.
There are so many.
This is a steakhouse.
They are open.
This was our last chance.
Let me loosen the mic and go in.
(Excuse me.)
People are watching.
(She reached her limit.)
Finished?
Not finished?
- Are they closed? - That was so funny.
Seok Jin asked if they were closed and they said,
"Not finished".
(We're open for business.)
I would have been happy if they were closed.
Thank you.
(At the steakhouse, they have beef fried noodles.)
This smells good.
This is a noodles trip.
(Meanwhile, at a cottage in Gangwon Province)
(Team Ji Hyo and Si Young are both staying here.)
(Team Ji Hyo prepared meals for 100 people.)
(They'e exhausted.)
I'm very...
worn out.
We're filthy.
I didn't know preparing 100 servings was this hard.
(It feels like they aged 100 more years.)
How will Haha react? Will he be surprised?
- He will be, right? - Of course.
- He'll be shocked. - He will be.
I was extremely careful.
There's a chatroom in our agency where our schedules get posted.
I posted it...
as a meeting for my concert.
Because he might ask where I'm going.
I had to come up with something.
- How meticulous. - Right.
(She's a perfect secret guest.)
(Team Si Young returns after completing their mission.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I think they're here.
(Haha and his team are here.)
(He's tired.)
(Haha has no idea Byul is here.)
He's here.
Jong Kook.
(How will Haha react?)
- Welcome back. - What's going on?
(What's going on?)
(Welcome, honey.)
(It's me, Go Eun.)
Why?
(Why are you here?)
Hello.
She's our guest.
She's today's guest. Why?
(He freezes on the spot as well.)
Hello.
Really?
She worked so hard.
- I'm a celebrity. - Hey.
That's not what I meant.
(Long time no see, Mrs. Ha.)
I can be on the show too!
I can be on Running Man too.
- She worked really hard today. - I did. Come here.
- Comfort her. Massage her. - Give her a hug.
It's so nice to see you.
Why... I didn't...
- Hello. - You didn't tell me on purpose.
- Hello. - Hello.
You didn't... Goodness.
I'm getting goosebumps. You...
Give her a hug.
Great work.
What happened?
- I... - How did this...
She's separate from you.
That's not what I mean.
I got goosebumps.
How did this happen?
They had a guest?
Since we're on the topic,
can I check your jackets in the corner?
Me? Mine?
Both of you.
- Are you doubting me? - No.
If you keep doubting me, I'll be hurt.
(Si Young's ballots disappeared.)
I'm sorry if I'm mistaken.
(She has a hunch, but there is no evidence.)
Me? Mine?
Both of you.
Did she hit you?
They stole your ballots.
This is a real situation.
- I got offended. - Why?
I'll show you my jacket.
We didn't vote yet.
Don't worry about me.
I'll check for five minutes.
This is a real situation.
- This team... - She's investigating.
She's investigating.
(I'll catch you!)
What happened?
- We did it. - We succeeded.
We worked so hard.
Our feelings were hurt.
I know.
(You saw her style, right?)
We couldn't trust each other.
This was the toughest episode of the year.
- Are you looking for something? - What is that?
There's nothing, right?
Wait. Hold on.
I'm worried you'll steal mine.
Kwang Soo probably did it.
I'm hurt.
I'm very hurt in this situation.
- Si Young. - Yes?
Kwang Soo hides in his body.
- You didn't check his head, right? - He doesn't hide in his clothes.
No, I didn't.
Look. You can look.
She looked everywhere.
Look at the back of this head.
- His hips. - You have to check his head.
He has long hair for a reason.
(You can search.)
She looked everywhere.
(I'll help.)
(She's an expert when it comes to his stealing.)
Check the back of his head.
(She's been on Running Man for 8 years.)
(Kwang Soo, is this it?)
Please.
(I'll give you one.)
It's really not me. You can rip it.
(I got you.)
No way!
No way.
It's not me!
(They don't know where it is, but he's incredible.)
- It's not me. - Come on.
(Here it is.)
(Goodness)
(She gives him a hard punch for cheating.)
This team probably got their feelings hurt.
She hit you.
- That was awful. - I told you it wasn't me.
Do you give me new ballots?
They might smell.
(That was a dirty hiding place.)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Si Young.
I'm sorry.
He improved.
He was serious too.
He acted so well.
He said it wasn't him because he doesn't do bad things...
when the camera is off.
I stole it when the camera was on.
(He's an expert entertainer.)
(When the mission was over in the restaurant...)
(Rustling)
(Kwang Soo's bad hand searches Si Young's pocket.)
(He stole the ballots!)
(He acts like nothing happened.)
I've never seen somebody like him.
(I've never seen somebody like him.)
(We've seen him for 8 years.)
Hey, you...
(She takes them back.)
- Are you fine now? - Yes.
We're a team, so I have to accept him.
We've been doing that for eight years.
(We're a team, so we accepted him for 8 years.)
He's on his knees.
Stop acting like you feel guilty.
You're going to do it again.
Stop acting.
It looks like you find it unfair that you got caught.
That's what your face says. You are hoping you resisted.
So did you succeed the mission?
- We did. - Yes.
- You did? - Really?
Did you catch them?
- I didn't. - Right? You didn't.
He was just feeding them.
He can't catch them.
There was no car in front of your team...
(Rolling)
(Goodness!)
(A cup scares him.)
He's a coward, Byul.
He's such a coward on Running Man.
I'm sorry. I didn't curse at you.
(I'm sorry for yelling.)
I didn't curse at you.
Oh, my.
I saw all sorts of things, so I got goosebumps.
- Don't do this. - I'm sorry.
It's strange you got scared by a cup.
- He's like that. - I got goosebumps. That's why.
Do you find him cute when he does that?
What do you think?
When we go to a theater,
he...
- he's like... - I'll give you a ballot.
(He tries to make her be quiet.)
If something pops out...
I'm not kidding.
His knees go up.
(If a ghost pops out...)
(He shouts and kicks.)
- He shouts. - Aren't you embarrassed of him?
- Every day. - "Every day".
We don't go.
- We watch movies at home. - That's cute.
Thank you for your hard work today.
We'll give you a chance to earn additional ballots.
(They worked hard all day, so they get another chance.)
There are two additional ballots.
- 2. - 2?
- This is a mission. - Two ballots?
That's a lot.
It's Toe Wrestling.
(The game is Toe Wrestling.)
It's 1-on-1 Toe Wrestling.
The team that survives until the end gets two additional ballots.
(She's competitive.)
One person from each team should come forward.
I think Si Young is strong.
Haha has big feet too.
First person from Team Si Young...
is Kwang Soo.
(Skills and length are proportional.)
Intimidation factor is important.
From Team Ji Hyo...
(Who do you think it is?)
(It's me!)
(Tallest versus Strongest)
(It's hard to predict.)
It'll feel somewhat different.
(My gosh)
- I'm serious. - Why?
- Really? - They're purple.
(As soon as they lock their toes...)
Are your toes broken?
Say it if you're in pain.
I'm in pain.
This is painful! How many times do I have to say it?
Don't be scared.
Let's start.
I'm sorry. I don't think I can do this.
- I really can't do this. - Try it first.
- This is so painful. - Give it a try.
This is better.
How do you work out your toes?
Hold on.
(When did he work out his toes?)
You won. You're a champion.
He's sweating a lot.
Why are you sweating so much?
I don't know.
Okay.
It's this foot.
(Se Chan, I'm right-footed.)
Se Chan, it's this foot.
Okay, okay.
Okay! This is good.
He's genuine.
(He's my favorite.)
I'll hold you.
(We can't lose!)
Let's be scary.
How is that scary?
How is this scary?
(His toe looked gentle.)
(It's angry now.)
Did you get a pedicure?
It's scary.
(It's cute, so it doesn't achieve the purpose.)
(I feel like I lost already.)
- Ready. - Okay, I'm ready.
This is one last time.
- Ready, - Good luck.
set...
Hold him.
(He tries desperately.)
(Look at him. He's pretty good.)
- Use your body. - Let go.
(This is a close race.)
He's trying to win.
Look at Kwang Soo.
(I want to win!)
(Do you want to win?)
(Maybe next time.)
(Kwang Soo loses with a moan.)
All right! I did it.
(Don't try to beat me when it comes to using strength.)
He's so...
He's so strong.
Are you okay, Kwang Soo? Wipe your sweat.
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
I wiped my feet with this earlier.
(She realizes now.)
I'm sorry.
(Why are you doing this to me, Byul?)
I am really sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
(Gosh, Byul.)
(He is in tatters.)
Team Song Ji Hyo won...
- two ballots. - Okay.
When do you go to work tomorrow?
In the morning.
- We go to work at 3am. - Really?
Let's play another round.
(He doesn't give up.)
- What shall we bet? - Let's bet our ballots.
- What shall we bet? - I am for it.
Let's play a game that depends on luck.
Sure.
The shoot is just getting started.
(Kwang Soo comes back to life.)
A shoot for Running Man should make you sweat.
"A shoot for Running Man should make you sweat."
- Let's use this. - What?
- Write down your names. - Okay.
- Let's bet 2 ballots each. - Okay.
Who will spin it? Who spins the roulette is important.
- Shall we play rock-paper-scissors? - Let's do that.
Can we play muk-jji-ppa instead?
(She asks to change the game.)
- That team... - Let's keep it simple.
- always wants to drag things out. - Come on.
Let's keep it simple.
We have a plan.
- We have a plan. - Let's keep it simple.
- We have a plan. - What shall I play?
- Muk-jji-ppa? - Rock.
- Shall we play muk-jji-ppa? - Play rock-paper-scissors.
You lose if you don't play. Rock-paper-scissors.
(Team Si Young gets to spin the roulette.)
That was great.
They will spin the roulette.
- Don't kick the roulette. - We know that.
You can do this. You did well so far.
Like sheep!
(She suddenly begins the chant.)
- We, who spare nothing to give! - Are the best!
Forget it!
(Like sheep, we, who spare nothing to give, are the best!)
(They have to think about their chant.)
There is no teamwork whatsoever. Forget it.
- We have a good teamwork. - Forget it.
You don't need to do it again.
Like sheep!
- We, who spare nothing to give! - We, who spare nothing to give!
- Forget it. - Are the best!
- What was that? - Stop it.
- For goodness' sake. - The best.
- They are ridiculous. - She spun it.
- The best. - They are ridiculous.
(The roulette of fate begins to spin.)
(They will either win back the ballots they lost...)
(or lose 2 more ballots.)
(Team Ji Hyo wins.)
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
(Team Ji Hyo wins 2 additional ballots.)
- Is it us? - Yes.
- Okay. - Yes.
This is good.
(Their greed brought on a disaster.)
All right. Go away.
(We shouldn't have done this.)
- Okay. - This is good.
We lacked the fighting spirit.
You shouldn't have shouted the chant.
(Team Ji Hyo wins 4 ballots.)
- Are we done? - Okay. The last round.
Let's go.
(Their instinct as tiger moths comes out.)
(Let's play the last round.)
- If people ask for more rounds, - Seriously.
- I will give them a beating. - That would be wrong.
In that case, let's bet three ballots.
- Bring it on. - Hold on.
- Byul, hold on. - No?
(Haha and Byul are tiger moth couple.)
- Byul likes challenges. - I mean...
She is a tiger moth.
- Really? - She hasn't spun a roulette.
You should spin a roulette.
Will you let us spin the roulette?
- Of course. - Okay.
- How many ballots? - We will spin the roulette.
Three ballots.
(It's a roulette with 3 ballots on the line.)
- We won't play more games. - We will end after this.
However, you shouldn't leave if you are on our team.
We are sorry about that.
It's not over until it is.
We will be done in 15 minutes.
- Don't kick. - We won't do that.
Don't do it. Here I go.
(3 ballots are on the line.)
(This is the last game.)
(What will be the result?)
All right. Bring in the clapperboard.
Come on.
(Let's end this as we promised.)
Pick up the ballots.
Did you pick them up?
In 1, 2, 3.
Okay.
(This is where the shoot ends today.)
(This is how scary game addiction can be.)
Today is our lucky day.
We need to go to bed with these ballots.
We need to keep the doors locked.
- How many ballots do you have? - It's plausible.
- Right? - It will be hard for us to lose.
Seriously.
Hold on. Si Young whispered to me...
that Haha and Byul might be a scammer couple.
(Are they a scammer couple?)
For goodness' sake. Si Young.
- Tell us honestly. - Si Young.
- I am honest. - Si Young whispered that.
Seriously.
- Si Young has doubts. - I am not like that.
Byul.
(Everyone is asleep at 3am.)
(These people come out after barely wetting their faces.)
(A vehicle that is headed to the sea awaits them.)
How many jobs do we have?
I don't know.
We are fishermen now, right?
(A few hours ago, Kwang Soo was an employee at a ranch.)
I don't even know.
(Is this "Experiencing Life" or Running Man?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(They get in the van to experience the life of a fisherman.)
(Si Young, who picked sandfish gets in the van as well.)
Did we sleep an hour?
(They go to catch sandfish and complete a mystery mission.)
This is my first time to forego a shower on a TV show.
(It's her 1st time in 11 years to forego a shower.)
You didn't wash up?
I washed my face, but I didn't take a shower.
- You styled your hair nicely. - You are diligent.
I just went to bed after washing my face.
(Team Si Young arrives at their destination.)
All right.
We are here.
Go, go!
- All right. - We got here on time.
All right.
(They can't stop laughing.)
Your mission is to catch fish you haven't had at the restaurant.
- We chose sandfish. - That's right.
You succeed this mission...
if you catch sandfish and complete an additional task.
There is an additional task.
We will reveal the additional task once you return to land.
What could it be?
I advise you to remember everything...
that happens on the boat.
(Does it have to do with what happens during fishing?)
Gosh, let us rest.
(Do we need to remember everything?)
(Fishing is hard as it is.)
Let us focus on our work.
- Let us be at ease. - Stop making us anxious.
- Stop making us anxious. - Seriously.
(They board the boat with an anxious heart.)
What could be the additional task?
(They set out to catch sandfish.)
(A self-proclaimed expert of reel fishing, Haha)
(A regular at Running Man's fishing-related missions, Kwang Soo)
(A former fisherwoman and a passionate leader, Si Young)
(A group of fishing experts,)
(Team Si Young boards a sandfish boat.)
(Will they succeed? What could be the additional task?)
(Meanwhile, Team Hong Kong arrives at the accommodation.)
All right.
You failed your first mission.
- I am disappointed. - I am not disappointed at all.
- I am disappointed. - We couldn't eat more.
- Seriously. - I am grateful that it's over.
I am grateful that it's over.
Right now, Team Gangwon Province...
completed all the missions...
and picked the missions for the second day.
Your last mission is...
what you had in Russia.
(They had "Catch a king crab" when they were in Russia.)
- What? - Catch a king crab.
Is that our mission?
- Is that our mission? - Don't worry.
You have the last chance.
What is it?
(The last chance?)
Will you choose the mission you had in Russia...
or a new mission?
- A new mission. - A new mission.
- How will we catch a king crab? - Seriously.
- We can't catch it. - It's impossible.
In 1, 2, 3.
- A new mission. - A new mission.
(Team Hong Kong chooses a new mission.)
We will reveal the new mission tomorrow morning.
- Okay. - Tomorrow morning?
(Why are they telling us tomorrow morning?)
- You won't tell us now? - Why not?
You will know...
- tomorrow morning. - Will we know naturally?
I am curious.
If it's something about noodles or steak,
I won't stand still.
Look forward to it. Have a good night.
By the way,
- I need a digestive medicine. - Please give us some.
- Okay. - Please deliver it to my room.
- All right. - Good night.
See you tomorrow.
(The first day ends as noodles bloat in their bellies.)
(The next day, early morning in Hong Kong)
All right.
(Production crew is in front of a room.)
- One. - Clap.
2, 3.
(They get ready for the shoot.)
(Unlocking)
(They sneak into Jae Seok and Seok Jin's room.)
(They move in an orderly manner.)
(Be quiet.)
Gosh, you startled me.
(They walk past Jae Seok...)
(and approach Seok Jin, who is still sleeping.)
(What are you doing?)
(What are you planning so early in the morning?)
(The crew doesn't care about Jae Seok.)
What are you doing?
(What is going on?)
(They spot Seok Jin, who is fast asleep.)
(Excuse me.)
(Why did you wake him up?)
What comes to your mind when you think about Hong Kong?
5, 4, 3...
Chow Yun Fat.
(He is a Hong Kong actor.)
(Hong Kong reminds Seok Jin of Chow Yun Fat.)
(Chow Yun Fat)
- Can you repeat that? - Chow Yun Fat.
See you later.
What was that?
What? Is that all?
What was that about?
Why didn't you ask me a question?
I was awake.
(A worrisome sneak attack ends.)
Did you sleep well?
Hello.
- I passed out. - I totally passed out.
I must have eaten a lot of noodles. Look at my face.
(The size of his face doubled.)
I could barely open my eyes when I woke up.
I wondered if someone stepped on Seok Jin's face during the night.
This isn't bad at all.
My face was more swollen in the morning.
I woke up three times during the night...
- to go to the restroom. - The noodles...
- Really? - I produced some noodles.
(It's too much information.)
(She talks about producing noodles in the morning.)
- For goodness' sake. - The things you say...
- I can't believe her. - For goodness' sake.
She talks about these things when she is with us.
This is how she starts her morning.
(They are her reliable conversation buddies.)
(Feeling satisfied)
You chose this mission over the mission in Russia yesterday.
I will reveal the new mission to you.
- What is it? - Yes, this is important.
- I almost forgot about that. - What is it?
(What is the 2nd mission of Team Hong Kong?)
"Take a photo..."
"Take a photo with Chow Yun Fat, the most famous figure..."
(Taking a photo with Chow Yun Fat? They can't believe their eyes.)
- Take a photo with him? - You want us to meet Chow Yun Fat?
(What are you talking about? Chow Yun Fat came out of nowhere!)
- Where is... - Chow Yun Fat...
- Mr. Chow Yun Fat? - We don't know him personally.
(Here's an introduction of him.)
(He's a boss in "A Better Tomorrow" who led the Hong Kong noir movies.)
(Chow Yun Fat, the man we loved back in the days)
(You want us to take a photo with this famous actor?)
- All right. A while ago, - This is...
we asked this question to Seok Jin, the oldest,
- for the whole group. - Right.
(It was 30 minutes ago before the shoot this morning.)
(The member in sleep was to answer this question.)
(That's how this mission became about meeting Chow Yun Fat.)
No way.
- You can't do that. - You woke me up from my sleep.
- He's already all over the place. - Come on.
- But he was probably half asleep. - Come on, Seok Jin.
Why did you... Why did you say his name?
I was sleeping. He asked the figure of Hong Kong. It's him then.
- Chow Yun Fat. - Or you could've said...
Jae Seok's name or Running Man.
- Exactly. You should've done that. - Had you done that...
- You could've completed right away. - If I said his name,
- we would've be done now. - You would go home then.
- How can we meet him? - How can we take a photo with him?
He's a famous guy.
(Everyone thought that it wasn't possible at that time.)
(He was here today?)
(We might be able to meet him.)
(Traces of Chow Yun Fat are found all over the place.)
(And something miraculous happened to Team Hong Kong.)
(What is the miracle they faced?)
Memories of Christmas!
(Merry Christmas)
(A guest visits Running Man like a present on Christmas.)
(He's pretty nice.)
(Miraculous stories no one imagined)
I guess it's a match too.
(However,)
(Running Man opened something that they aren't supposed to do.)
(What on earth happened on their Christmas?)
(Christmas Special, The Miracle of Christmas)