(Last week)
(It's already been a year since So Min and Se Chan joined them.)
(To celebrate, the members came up with their own retreat schedules.)
(However, the distribution of minutes depended purely on luck.)
(They had to carry out 6 tasks on their schedule for 365 minutes.)
(Members who give up on the tasks will get the penalty badge.)
(The member with the most badges will choose 2 members.)
(Those chosen members must sign 365 autographs to get off work.)
(Thus began a new retreat that you'd never seen before.)
(Whether you want it or not, finish the schedule within the given time.)
(After finishing 3 tasks, they began the 4th task on the schedule.)
(Twice came to congratulate So Min and Se Chan's anniversary.)
(Twice lifted the spirits of the Running Man members.)
- She's so sexy.
- That's amazing.
(Twice had a dance battle against themselves to stand out.)
(Ji Hyo and Mom won the dance battle.)
To which members will you give the badges?
Momo, give the badges to whomever you want to give.
Members I want to give these to?
(The member with the most badges will choose 2 members.)
(3 members must sign 365 autographs to get off work.)
It's bad if we get the badges.
No, no. I did my best.
(Don't give it to Kwang Soo.)
(However, Momo stops in front of Kwang Soo.)
- It can't be.
- I did my best for him.
Why...
- Kwang Soo has the most.
- It's Kwang Soo.
It's me?
(What a great choice. Momo is the best.)
- She's smart. She's smart.
- Kwang Soo has the most.
Momo is so smart.
- I really like you, Kwang Soo.
- It's bad if I get the badge.
- Good work, Kwang Soo.
- I heard this is...
- a good badge.
- What?
- Good job.
Momo, you're great.
- She's so good at this.
- I heard it's a good badge.
You're giving me both of the badges?
- I heard it's a great badge.
- Well done.
My gosh, I only had 1, but now, I'm in 1st place.
(He's shocked.)
- It's a token of my support.
- Thank you.
- It is.
- Great.
A mission from the staff only remains now.
(The only remaining mission is the mission from the staff.)
- What? It's over soon?
- Really?
- Seriously?
- What happened?
Before that, I will reveal the rest of their special talents.
It's a shame not to reveal them. Tzuyu wrote...
- She had 1? - 3 physical talents.
Tzuyu wrote that?
What are three physical talents?
First of all, I can move my ears.
- Her ears can move.
- You can move your ears.
Show us.
(What's the talent with her ears?)
Her ears are moving.
- She really did it.
- Her ears are moving.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but can you do it without that expression?
(Her facial expression catches their eyes more than her ears.)
- Stop it.
- What else can you do?
- It's my tongue.
- Your tongue?
- I can flip it.
- Is that so?
(She can flip her tongue? He's intrigued.)
(She can freely flip her tongue?)
She can do everything.
Not everyone can do that.
I can fold my tongue.
- Do it then.
- My gosh.
(What? He folded his tongue in half?)
Actually, that's more interesting.
(His is more interesting than Tzuyu's.)
- I can do this.
- What is it? Show us.
Look at that.
- Look at this.
- Wait.
Mina can do it too!
- Mina can do this.
- I only heard about this.
- But no one can do what I did.
- What did you do?
(Can you fold it in half?)
But why is this important?
- I mean...
- It's great you can fold it.
Seriously. I mean...
How is folding your tongue useful? What is it good for?
- Think about it.
- I just wanted to show you. Gosh.
- What's the last one?
- The last talent is...
- bending my arm.
- I can't do that.
It's my arm.
Don't do it!
(She folds her arm twice at a right angle.)
You can't turn it around though.
(You're done already?)
I thought she'd turn it around.
- Is that it?
- It's...
Yes, it looks easy, but it's hard.
It looks easy, but it's hard. Do you want to try it?
- Do you want to try? Try it.
- Hold on.
Try it yourself. Is it easy or hard?
Is it hard, or is it easy? Answer me.
- Isn't it hard?
- That little...
Tell him this isn't how he should behave on shows.
(My gosh, he's embarrassing me in front of Twice.)
- How did she do that?
- It's a hard thing to do.
- Bend the arm toward the inside.
- It's very difficult.
- Where does it go?
- Toward the inside.
My finger is just as impressive.
- What is that?
- What?
- What did you do?
- I bent my finger.
Hey, your finger is broken.
(You idiot.)
- Go to the hospital now.
- I broke my own finger.
- So what?
- He's insane.
- Why are you enduring the pain?
- The bones will recover.
I can do that too.
- What? You can? Mina can do it.
- Mina can do it.
- Hey, Chae Young can do it too.
- Wait.
(He's flustered.)
- Chae Young can do it.
- Hold on.
(Hold on a second. Let me show you.)
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Hey, everyone can do it.
- Everyone can do it.
- Mine goes as low as this.
(I can do it too.)
- Everyone can do it.
(The battle of special talents with Twice finishes.)
Anyway, please give out...
- 2 penalty badges.
- Let's count the badges 1st.
If you have four badges, raise your hand.
- I have four.
- Step forward, and speak.
- Yes, sir. I have four!
- There you go. Great.
(He's well-disciplined.)
(He doesn't want the badge.)
- Go back to your spot.
- Yes, sir.
All right. Three badges.
- Yes, sir. I have three.
- Great.
Hey, you. How many do you have?
I have five, sir!
(He overdoes it.)
Okay. The rest of you don't have badges, right?
- Tzuyu will choose one...
- Okay.
- Of the three and give this badge.
- Thank you, Tzuyu.
If Jae Seok gets another one,
- He and I will both have five.
- My gosh.
- Ms. Tzuyu.
- Hello.
I've been rooting for... Hold on. Listen to me.
(She says hello to Seok Jin...)
(and goes straight to Kwang Soo.)
Please listen to me.
I'm in last. If I get another, I'll still be last.
- I see.
- And besides, I thought...
(Tzuyu isn't affected.)
- Are you sure?
- Please accept the badge.
I'll take 1. I'll take 1 for now.
- Congratulations.
- It's a gift. Accept it.
- It's from Tzuyu.
- Why is it me?
- How could you turn it down?
Why are you giving it to me?
- Why?
- I just wanted to give you one.
- You have 1 left.
- 1...
- My gosh.
- Why didn't you give that to him?
- You can give it to him.
- Okay.
My gosh, you didn't have to give me one.
I had so much fun at your radio show the other day.
(Since it was fun, she gives him the badge?)
You were supposed to give one to someone you don't like.
- That was great.
- Thank you, Tzuyu.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
- Thank you, Mr. Jong Kook.
- Sure, sure. My gosh, Tzuyu.
Thank you so much for joining us today, Twice.
I hope you will join us again.
- Seriously. It was too short.
- It was too short.
- Let's give it up for Twice again.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
- Goodbye.
(The cutthroat battle to get off work begins now.)
We have two more left.
- We have 1 slot for 30 minutes.
- We have the misty time.
We have 2 slots for 30 minutes.
It will be a disaster to pick foot volleyball again.
I want to use the restroom.
- It's an option.
- I want to use the restroom.
Please, please.
- Please.
- It could be...
Restroom break!
- Okay.
- Restroom break.
- Number 1. Yellow, number 1.
- Yellow, number 1?
(Yellow, number 1)
"Remaining Silent".
- Really?
- "Remaining Silent".
- Can we do that?
- That's harder.
You have to do absolutely nothing and remain silent.
(We can't do anything?)
I don't want that.
- This is too much.
- Seriously.
Doing nothing for 30 minutes will make us go crazy.
You will be fine as long as you stay silent.
- We have to stay silent.
- What can we do silently?
(Can they remain silent?)
This is...
Do we remain silent?
Can we sleep?
Yes, you can, but you will get the penalty as soon as you snore.
- We must remain silent.
You must remain silent.
I don't remain silent for 30 minutes...
- even when I am at home.
- 30 minutes is too long.
- Get ready.
- We must remain silent.
Set.
(Remaining Silent for 30 minutes begins.)
(I have a lot of badges.)
(Do you want to carry out the penalty with me?)
(Stepping)
(Se Chan steps on his foot.)
(Why does everyone pick on me?)
(As Se Chan and Kwang Soo cause a scene, )
(Haha leaves to remain unscathed.)
(I am leaving as well.)
(Don't you dare try anything with me.)
(Se Chan looks something up.)
(Look at this.)
(He almost bursts out laughing.)
(It's Kwang Soo's look-alike, Han Gi Beom.)
(They laugh silently.)
(Rustling)
(Chuckling)
(Kwang Soo gets the penalty for making a sound.)
(Jae Seok calls him.)
Is it within the rules to call someone?
Why did you call me?
Hold on. Fine.
Let's do this.
(Good bye, Kwang Soo.)
(What's the Hidden Penalty of this mission?)
Okay, okay. Okay.
(The penalty involves flogging.)
(The oak flogging instrument is fast and efficient.)
What is this?
This is wrong.
Dong Geun, you...
(Na Dong Geun is a veteran staff member...)
(who is known to deliver strong blows.)
Get someone else!
(The angle of his elbow shows that he is on a different class.)
(Hitting)
Hold on. Girls, leave!
(Twice is leaving.)
Don't look at me!
Girls!
Thank you for your hard work!
Bye!
Don't look at me!
(I am not always like this.)
Don't look at me.
(Turn your eyes away from me.)
(He is flooded with a sense of shame.)
(I am okay!)
(Kwang Soo is screaming.)
(What's the penalty?)
(Seok Jin, look at this.)
(Ji Hyo attacks with a picture of a young Seok Jin.)
(Jae Seok attacks with a picture of Sae Ho's look-alike.)
(Seok Jin staggers due to 2 consecutive attacks.)
(Laughing)
(Haha's bare face knocks him out.)
I got three consecutive attacks.
(I need to hold back.)
(Seok Jin receives a penalty badge and leaves to get flogged.)
(Kwang Soo, come over here.)
(Jae Seok hurriedly calls Kwang Soo over.)
(I want to study law at Seoul National University.)
(He can't control his laughter.)
(Kwang Soo gets knocked out by Jong Kook during his Turbo days.)
It's impossible not to laugh at this.
(This is driving me crazy.)
(Jae Seok tries to show it to Se Chan as well.)
(Se Chan strikes with a picture of himself.)
(Laughing)
(The shocking picture sends Jae Seok to the flogging instrument.)
Hey!
I have that picture, too.
(Why does he have that picture?)
This is driving me crazy.
(He attacks with a picture of Sae Ho in his early days.)
(She is about to collapse.)
(Remaining Silent turns into a battle of shocking pictures.)
(Jong Kook begins to attack.)
(Han Gi Beom, the basketball player, makes another appearance.)
(They are nearing their limits.)
(Jae Seok gets a penalty thanks to Se Chan's counterattack.)
(He gets flogged.)
(It's payback time.)
(He gets a penalty badge.)
(Everyone is absorbed in looking up funny pictures.)
(My goodness.)
(He performs acupuncture on Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin gets a penalty for making a sound.)
(I can't believe you pricked me.)
Okay.
(Jae Seok's acupuncture brings energy back to Seok Jin.)
(He now approaches Kwang Soo who is clueless.)
(Jae Seok, look at this.)
(Yelling)
(What is this?)
(Kwang Soo gets energy back, too.)
Fine. Just fine.
Fine.
I decided on my path now.
(He takes the familiar path toward the flogging instrument.)
Okay.
(He lies on his stomach without being told.)
(What?)
(Is that Yoon Sang, the cameraman?)
(Screaming)
(Why are you doing this?)
(Kwang Soo's cameraman, who suffered the penalties with him, pays back.)
(Kwang Soo, let's stop receiving penalties.)
Okay.
Okay, okay.
(As he continues to say okay, )
(his eyes become unfocused.)
(He is angry at the members and the staff.)
(Haha beckons Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok ends up looking out of curiosity.)
(He shows a picture of Jae Seok's doppelganger.)
(They almost stop breathing.)
(Laughing)
(A Japanese vet who resembles Jae Seok has lethal charms.)
You have 10 minutes left.
(The funny picture contest is at a standstill.)
(Rumbling)
(So Min's stomach is making a noise!)
It was my stomach!
This shouldn't count!
My stomach rumbled!
Okay. Se Chan, I will get you.
I will get you.
This is your fault.
(Noisy)
(The members see something and burst out laughing.)
(So Min brings a weapon.)
(Se Chan, you deserve a beating.)
(Look at that.)
(What? A vacuum cleaner?)
(Hitting)
(Okay, let's do this.)
(Thor with a paddle versus Iron Man with a vacuum cleaner)
(What is Kwang Soo trying to do?)
(He is working hard.)
(Jae Seok runs over to the vacuum cleaner.)
(Where is the power button?)
(Pressing)
(Groaning)
(He vacuums Kwang Soo, a big piece of dust.)
(My goodness.)
(Hit him with this.)
Fine.
I know what to do.
(I hope this ends soon.)
(They have 5 minutes left.)
(Please get him.)
(Jae Seok?)
(May I borrow the vacuum cleaner?)
(Anxious)
(When Jae Seok doesn't listen, the members gather.)
(Let's get him.)
(The committee for Jae Seok's penalty begins.)
(He gets a mouth massage...)
(as well as an eardrum massage.)
(Don't do this at home.)
(They realize how precious laughter is.)
You almost ruined my cochlea.
(He gets dragged away.)
My ear... For goodness' sake.
I can't believe Se Chan.
(Se Chan is a man who can make anyone talk.)
(Peace comes right before the session ends.)
(Farting)
(I am sure you heard it.)
(He farts while he is walking.)
(He throws in a fart at the end.)
(He is incredibly embarrassed.)
(A Running Man member farts in front of the viewers.)
(The person who farted gets arrested at the corner.)
(It's impossible to deny it.)
Hey.
It's because you made me nervous.
(He farted at the moment of silence.)
(Kwang Soo is used to being flogged by now.)
(How do I take revenge?)
(He picks something up.)
(Is it a fistful of dirt?)
(It was Se Chan and Jae Seok's fault.)
(Se Chan has no idea what's about to happen.)
(I'm so glad to see you.)
(Kwang Soo corners Se Chan with a fistful of dirt.)
(He explodes in laughter.)
(Kwang Soo gasps for air.)
(Coughing)
(What's going on?)
(Kwang Soo hoped to take revenge.)
(Is he giving up after drinking water?)
(Kwang Soo isn't coming back home.)
(Se Chan cleans up quietly.)
- You go first.
- No.
You go first, Jae Seok.
What's in your pockets?
(So Min gets ready.)
My goodness!
There isn't much in them.
(She hits him on his lower back.)
Jae Seok, weren't they your buttocks?
I thought they were.
Were they your buttocks? I'm sorry.
I hit you on the buttocks, right?
He doesn't have fat on his buttocks.
(That hurt.)
(His buttocks are numb.)
(They take turns flogging each other.)
(Get off of it.)
Get off of it. Promise me that you won't hit me.
- Okay.
- Leave.
- Leave now.
Hurry and leave.
My goodness.
(She slowly turns around.)
(She notices them.)
Hurry and leave, Kwang Soo.
(He's being suspicious.)
(He heads to the room.)
(He quickly turns right.)
Go in.
Kwang Soo, what's wrong with you?
It's going to hurt.
It'll hurt.
Seriously.
I really won't hit you.
- Come on.
- I won't hit you.
- Stop lying.
- I won't hit.
- You'll throw it.
- No, I won't.
- You'll jump off.
- No, I can't jump off from here.
- Stop lying.
- I really won't.
Please.
You can't do this. This isn't how you play it.
Lie down.
- Lie down properly.
- This isn't how you play the game.
Stop it.
Hey, hey.
(Screaming)
(He jumps off and flogs her.)
(He asks for forgiveness immediately.)
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that it'd be that hard.
If I get the penalty, I'll choose you.
- I'll pick you.
- Let's see who loses.
(Let's see who loses.)
I'm sorry.
(Remaining silent for 30 minutes is being chaotic.)
You have one minute left.
(1 minute is easy.)
(Let's stay quiet.)
(They have 1 minute before they're free.)
(The game isn't over yet.)
(Pressing hard)
(His attacks are the best.)
Goodness.
(Jae Seok gets another penalty badge.)
(Darn it.)
Hey!
You almost broke my legs.
(You'll feel better after some flogging.)
(Shall we stay quiet now?)
(30 minutes of Remaining Silent are over.)
- That was difficult.
- The time is up.
- Goodness.
You're really good, Se Chan.
- Se Chan is such a cheater.
- What's this?
He brought me dirt.
- What were you going to use it for?
- Did you bring the dirt?
I wanted to throw it at his eyes.
(He's so simple.)
- Were you going to throw it at me?
- You mean these rocks?
- It's dirt.
- It's not even dirt.
- I wanted to sprinkle on his eyes.
- He hit me, and it hurts.
These are rocks.
Thank goodness that he drank water.
Here's the last thing on your schedule.
- It isn't over yet.
- It's a 35-minute...
session.
- What is it?
- Is someone coming?
(It's a 35-minute session.)
(It's Misty Time 2.)
(What kind of activity will it be this time?)
That's enough. Let us go home.
(I don't care. Just let us go home.)
- Let us go out.
- Seriously.
Except when Twice came on the show,
it wasn't fun at all today.
(You enjoyed foot volleyball.)
The last session on 365 Retreat is...
Rolling Paper.
(Rolling Paper)
(Is it Rolling Paper for us?)
What?
Just give me paper for signing.
(He's going to lose anyway.)
It applies to six members except Se Chan and So Min.
Write anything you'd like to say to Se Chan and So Min...
on the rolling paper.
Write over 10 lines.
- "10 lines"?
- I like this.
- It sounds fun.
While they write,
So Min and Se Chan will wait outside.
- Really?
- It's so heart-warming.
Let's go, So Min.
(Feeling moved, the youngest members leave hand in hand.)
- Se Chan.
- Let's go.
(Feeling moved, the youngest members leave hand in hand.)
(What's this?)
What's this?
Is there another mission?
What are we doing?
(Each of them gets 6 notebooks and a pen.)
(Are they also given a mission?)
(Meanwhile, inside...)
(they write how they sincerely feel.)
I don't usually write these, so it's hard.
Isn't it hard?
(How is everyone writing it?)
- Gosh.
- Give me one more piece.
(Seok Jin asks for more paper.)
What? What's going on with you?
Suddenly, I have a lot to write.
I'm getting emotional.
(It's embarrassing, but he gets emotional.)
(Six members finish the Rolling Paper.)
Why is it making me nervous?
- They look...
- They don't look happy.
Did you write well?
- No.
- We wrote well.
We wrote sincerely.
You should have written sincerely.
- What?
- Have a seat first.
(Is there something?)
(You'll see.)
The last is...
Dangerous Rolling Paper.
(Dangerous Rolling Paper)
What? Dangerous?
What is it?
While you were writing on rolling paper,
So Min and Se Chan...
guessed a word...
- that you'd use the most.
- What?
- Goodness.
- What kind of game is this?
(Few minutes ago)
(Se Chan and So Min predict a word that was used the most.)
(Haha probably wrote about farting.)
He'll definitely mention it.
(They guess a word per member.)
That was it. I shouldn't have written it twice.
I shouldn't have written names.
So Min and Se Chan will read your rolling papers.
Each time their predicted word is said,
water will fall on the member and a penalty badge will be given.
If there is no predicted word,
So Min and Se Chan will get the water bomb...
and a penalty badge.
While we were writing,
- we thought about it a lot.
- Right.
- I'll definitely be the first.
- The first rolling paper is...
written by Jong Kook.
- It's Jong Kook.
- I'm sure I wrote it.
So Min and Se Chan...
will announce the words they predicted for Jong Kook.
Don't look, Jong Kook.
For whom are we playing?
Can we look?
- What?
- He uses them often.
Now, read his rolling paper.
I'd like to hear "One Man" as I read it.
(He sings right away.)
The staff will play it later.
(You don't have to sing.)
They'll play it, so be quiet.
(So Min loves his singing.)
"Se Chan and So Min, a year has passed by already."
"It feels like yesterday when you gave me a water bomb in a trailer."
(The newcomers gave him a water bomb.)
"I'm glad that things have gone well so far."
"I know joining an old variety show gave you a lot of pressure."
"However, you adjusted yourselves without losing confidence."
"You do your best to make the audience laugh."
"I'm grateful and apologetic at the same time."
"I'll work harder to become a better friend to you."
"From Jong Kook".
Is that it?
- There were no words that applied.
- Really?
(Both of their predicted words weren't written.)
(Why didn't he write our words?)
- It was also moving.
- That's amazing.
He didn't get penalized.
You use those words quite often. You could have written them.
Is it that much?
(That's so much water.)
(Se Chan and So Min get wet and receive penalty badges.)
(This isn't a joke.)
Se Chan's word was "punk", and So Min's word was "time".
I didn't write "time"?
Didn't I say, "for a long time"?
Didn't I write it?
I thought he would start by saying,
"That's right, you punk."
- All right.
- I won't get a pass.
- Is it Ji Hyo's letter?
- Water falls when the word is said.
("Always" and "1 year")
(So Min predicts "always", Se Chan predicts "1 year".)
That's smart thinking.
(Se Chan was smart.)
- That's smart thinking.
- She definitely wrote that.
I'm sure she wrote it.
- That's...
- I should move away a little.
Me too.
I didn't bring any extra underwear.
I can lend you mine.
(He has a lot of underwear.)
- Lend me one.
- Kwang Soo has small buttocks,
- so it'll fit.
- I have an XS size too.
Why?
Just in case.
(Just in case?)
All right. Please read the letter.
Okay. It's Ji Hyo's letter.
Judging from So Min's face, I think I wrote the words.
No.
"So Min and Se Chan, it's already been a year."
- Oh, my.
- From the beginning...
(1 year)
(Ji Hyo is splashed with water and receives a penalty badge.)
It's starting.
Oh, my.
- I shouldn't be sitting nearby.
- I feel uncomfortable.
- I saw through Ji Hyo.
- Really?
"I remember what you said..."
"on our Mongolia trip."
"You said you wanted to run away from the cameras."
- Will the guys get angry with us...
- They will.
If we buy these?
(1 year ago, the two of them went on a penalty trip to Mongolia.)
We'll get in trouble.
You're very positive.
(So Min opened up to Ji Hyo.)
(I'm pessimistic.)
(Variety shows are hard for me. Sometimes, I want to run away.)
"You must have had a lot of worries."
"But you've managed to give new energy..."
"to our show. So Min and Se Chan,"
"I'd like to thank you guys again. From Ji Hyo."
(I'd like to thank you guys again, Se Chan and So Min.)
(Touched)
Well...
The other word didn't appear.
I haven't guessed a word right.
- So Min will be splashed again.
- Again?
So Min is catching up.
I never seem to escape penalties.
(Instead of being moved to tears, she gets splashed with water.)
But So Min, you must be so touched.
(Teasing)
- You haven't guessed 1 word.
- I want to guess at least 1 word.
Among so many words...
Let's read Haha's letter.
You have to splash so much water?
Oh, my.
(Fart, "Ya man")
(These words will definitely be in the letter.)
They'll definitely be in the letter.
- Hold on.
- Definitely.
Of course.
They'll probably be in the letter.
- Definitely.
- I'd be surprised...
if they're not.
- Please read the letter.
- I'll read it.
"To So Min and Se Chan."
"You brought good luck to our show."
"And I learn a lot from you guys."
"You guys always work so hard."
"When So Min won the Best Rookie Award,"
"Se Chan was genuinely happy for her."
"It moved me."
"Your friendship is beautiful."
"But when Se Chan got drunk, he did say that..."
"he was very upset."
(Se Chan said he was upset.)
"He thought it was unfair..."
"and wanted to make a scene at the awards ceremony."
"He wanted to be popular."
"He wanted to be a star."
"He did say that."
"So Min, I heard you passing gas during the shooting."
(I heard you passing gas.)
"But I didn't say anything."
- I didn't.
- "From Haha."
I passed.
- He passed.
- No "ya man"?
Haha passed.
Unbelievable.
That was close.
- Why...
- Why didn't you add "ya man"?
I had no space left.
Why...
So Min and Se Chan will be splashed with water.
"Ya man"!
- "Ya man".
(Se Chan and So Min get another penalty badge.)
Gosh.
- Now, no one knows.
- No one knows.
Why am I bad at not only games but this too?
What am I good at?
So Min...
- "1 year"...
- There was no "1 year".
- I didn't write, "one year".
- So Min.
(So Min failed to guess what Seok Jin wrote too.)
It's cold!
(Surprisingly...)
You're not good at this.
So Min is getting ahead.
I haven't guessed one word.
Let's see.
(Jeon Clumsy, Cheater)
My guess is that they'll appear about three times.
- I'm not sure.
- You think so?
Let's start.
"To Se Chan and So Min."
(To Se Chan and So Min)
"It's already been a year since you guys joined."
"Se Chan, I'm so happy to have you on our show."
"Thanks to you, I don't even look in the mirror before shooting."
(What?)
- "I also throw whatever clothes..."
- That...
- doesn't make sense.
- He's going to get the penalty.
I knew it.
"You gave me such confidence."
(Thank you for your extraordinary looks.)
"Thank you so much, Se Chan."
- "I'd like to thank Kwang Soo too."
- Why me?
(Why me?)
I feel so grateful to Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
(Thank you for your interesting looks.)
"So Min,"
"we always get penalized together. You're just as unlucky as I am."
"Thanks to you, I'm not as afraid of penalties anymore."
"So Min, let's work hard from now on too..."
"and do our best to make our viewers laugh."
"So Min and Se Chan, thank you for being with us."
"Long live Se Chan and So Min."
What's that?
- "Yu Clumsy".
Gosh. I wrote, "Jeon Clumsy".
(He didn't write the words.)
He didn't write those words?
- "Jeon Clumsy" and "Cheater".
- He didn't write them?
- He wrote, "Yu Clumsy".
- How is it possible?
- I didn't write them.
Just so you know, he wrote, "thank you", five times.
- Exactly.
- They wrote the wrong words.
(Se Chan and So Min get another penalty badge and water bomb.)
This was better than the last time.
- How could you not guess it right?
- I haven't guessed any word right.
Not a single word.
This is why I'm not as afraid of penalties anymore.
This is hard to believe.
(So Min sets a record with 6 badges total.)
365 Retreat is over.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
The 1 with the most badges plus 2 people will be penalized.
The loser will choose one person,
and that person will choose another one.
- How many do you have?
- Today's loser is...
Kwang Soo with 13 badges.
- 13 badges?
- Congratulations.
I didn't come in last.
- You have 10 badges.
- Despite your last spurt...
Kwang Soo, please choose one person.
(Please choose one person.)
(Hello?)
(Ignoring)
He seems to know.
One person knows.
I feel sorry whenever this happens.
(What should I do?)
Hold on. I'm meeting someone later.
(Ignoring)
- How many does So Min have?
- 10.
She caught up at the last minute.
- 10?
- She got so many badges.
She didn't guess any word right.
I got splashed so many times.
(Staring)
(Ignoring)
(Looking away)
It should be among the three people.
- I should include Se Chan too.
- I have only four.
Whom do you choose?
I'll push the person from behind.
(Who will be penalized alongside Kwang Soo?)
(Jae Seok is chosen.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo will be penalized together as always.)
There's someone with more badges than me.
I chose the person who gave me the most badges.
The moment I heard the rules...
(What's the surprise?)
I decided to choose you if I lost.
All right. Then...
(Jae Seok will choose one person.)
I'll announce who can go home.
- Ji Hyo, you can go.
- She can go home?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Se Chan can go home too.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- You should take care of your kids.
- "Ya man".
- Bye.
- "Ya man"!
(Jong Kook looks away.)
(Seok Jin is in denial.)
(Thinking)
If I choose Jong Kook, I think he'll make a scene.
(If I choose Jong Kook, I think he'll make a scene.)
- You'll make a scene.
- No.
I won't.
You can go home.
You gave a badge to someone else.
- All right.
- In the end...
(Maybe I should follow Jong Kook.)
You can go home.
So Min, come here.
So Min.
(She fails.)
Here we are again.
Why do we keep going after each other?
I don't know.
We could go after those people, but why?
(I wonder as well.)
All right. Let me whisper in your ear.
Come here. I'll tell you one by one.
Do as I say on the count of three.
(Whispering)
1, 2, 3.
Bye.
(So Min is going home.)
- Bye.
- Okay.
Okay.
So Min.
- Congratulations.
- Good job.
The three of you have to sign autographs in the room.
- That's a lot.
- That's too much.
- That's 365 sheets of paper?
That's so much.
(It is a huge stack.)
As I told you earlier, you'll sign 365 autographs...
for our fans. We'll chose 365 fans...
- on social media.
- I see.
- Okay.
What if not many people want Kwang Soo's?
(What if not many people want Kwang Soo's?)
I'm making more than you, so there might be some left.
I'm making 65 more.
I haven't signed 100 autographs in a long time.
(They start signing.)
Back in 2007, you asked me for an autograph.
I'm finally giving you one.
(It's for you, Seok Jin.)
- Seok Jin.
- It's for my son.
- Sure.
- It was for him.
I just remembered you asking me in 2007.
Why did you write my name?
It's for my son.
It's been more than 10 years.
I can't believe it.
(And...)
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
You asked me for an autograph. Here's your autograph.
- Hey, 10 sheets...
- Hold on a second. You wrote,
"Grow more, and be 3m tall."
(Jae Seok wrote, "Grow more, and be 3m tall.")
- What nonsense is this?
- I want you to be taller.
- What's this about?
- I want you to grow more.
- I can't be 3m tall.
I would like you to grow more...
and be 3m tall so you can be taller than a giraffe.
- What do I get in return for that?
- I mean...
I only wrote that because I wanted you to be taller.
Let's rock-paper-scissors for 10 cards.
- Pardon?
- The loser will take the cards.
Seok Jin.
Why don't we do it for 50? It will be just 1 game.
Hold on. I'll bet everything I have left.
- How about the rest of the cards?
- Okay.
- That's great.
- The loser will take them all.
- I have exactly 25 cards.
- My gosh.
- I have more than 65 cards.
- Exactly. This is more than before.
- That's a lot.
- Will we do rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Let's draw lots.
My gosh, please.
(The one who draws the card with an X mark gets them all.)
All right. Among these cards,
- only one card has an X mark.
- Okay.
It's better to get whatever is left.
When it's against them, it's better that way.
I always picked the one in the middle, but this time...
(Seok Jin chooses the card first.)
(He grabs one confidently.)
- I'll take this one.
- Give me the card that fell.
(I'll take the one that fell.)
Give it to me.
Are we filming the episode for next week?
(By the way, are we filming the episode for next week?)
- You guys wanted to play this.
- Are we?
Won't this episode end?
- It's amazing we still have games.
- My gosh, this retreat...
There's a card with an X mark.
(The one who drew that card gets 75 cards.)
Please.
Okay. Okay!
(Seok Jin's card is empty. He's exempted.)
Okay!
(Kwang Soo gets an empty card too. He's exempted as well.)
- Okay!
(Jae Seok takes all 75 cards.)
- Let's play one more.
- No way.
- Come on. Let's play one more.
- For how many?
- For whatever you have left.
- For my leftover cards? Okay.
Play for the leftover cards.
My goodness.
Hey, I had 25 cards left. Now, I have 75 cards left?
(Jae Seok who initially had 25 cards wins 75 cards now.)
I smell a gas leak from somewhere.
Right? It's quite strong.
- Go check on it.
- What if something blows up?
(They continue signing autographs.)
So Min is still here.
What are you doing here?
You didn't go home yet?
- What's she doing here?
- She didn't leave yet.
Are you spending the night here?
(Here's a mysterious guest who didn't check out.)
- What's wrong with So Min?
- My goodness.
What did you do?
- Has she lost her mind?
- What's going on?
- What are you doing here?
- I got too drenched.
Maybe I should take a shower too.
You guys started it. How is it going?
- We're almost done.
- We're about done.
(They are still signing autographs.)
Hey. That smell from earlier.
(That mysterious gas smell)
(Was the source of the smell...)
- We smelled gas earlier.
- What?
I get your fart smells awful, but how could it smell like gas?
(Exactly. This is unbelievable.)
Seok Jin.
- It wasn't me. I'm serious.
- Wait.
I'm leaving now.
- Seok Jin, I'm almost done too.
- I'll practice my autograph.
- We can finish at the same time.
- You're done too.
- I'm done too.
- Here's one from me.
- All right, everyone.
- Yes?
You finished signing 365 autographs.
- Yes, we did.
- Goodness.
(Yes! We can finally get off work.)
- It's finally over.
- We did 364 cards.
- We'll send them out to our fans.
- Okay.
What's wrong with you? Who's that old lady?
(I'm going home now too.)
My goodness.
Everyone, you may go home.
- Okay. Good job.
- Good work, everyone.
(And finally, )
(It's the final week of the 4-week Family Package Project.)
(Depending on the results of the weekly races, )
(the winning team puts their names on the Luxury Package roulette.)
(The losing team puts their names on the Shuddering Package roulette.)
(It's the grand finale of the Family Package Project.)
(Their fates will be determined at last.)
(On the day of the 4th filming for the Family Project)
(It hints that this will be the final race.)
(This is the roulette with names that accumulated for 3 weeks.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- My gosh, where are we going?
- Hello.
I don't want to see this roulette!
(Go away.)
Stop it. I already gave up.
Stop it.
- This is a nightmare.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hello, Seok Jin.
- How have you been?
How have you been?
Be honest. You don't care if Jin Young had been good or not.
Exactly. When he asked me if I had been good,
he shifted his attention to somewhere else.
I didn't think about you at all for a week.
(I didn't think about you at all for the time I didn't see you.)
(He's completely honest.)
- Then you shouldn't have asked.
- It's the same with you too.
- My gosh.
- Haha, come here.
- My gosh, Haha is...
- Haha.
Are you...
Is Dream studying colors now?
- Is Dream studying colors now?
- Haha.
- Jae Seok.
- Come here, Haha.
Is your son learning colors now?
- I can't believe him.
- Hello.
He's studying colors?
- You look adorable.
- My goodness, our outfits...
- My gosh, look at our outfits.
- There's a clear distinction.
The outfits are visibly different.
- It's funny. Your outfits are dark.
- They're colorful, and we're dull.
Our outfits are colorful.
(This is a color TV.)
- Good people versus bad people.
- Right.
- You bad jerks.
- Do you like black outfits?
Da Hee isn't here today.
Her filming for a drama is getting longer than she originally thought.
She can't join us only for the opening segment.
- It hasn't ended yet.
- She's on her way now.
- We must be understanding.
- But Da Hee...
- must be here for So Min, - Right.
So she can scold her.
She needs to be scolded.
- I felt the catharsis.
- Exactly.
No one could scold her.
- Da Hee bluntly scolded her.
- Precisely.
- It was nice that she was blunt.
- It was nice.
In the back, you can see...
- Come on. This is...
- No.
- This is the final week.
- I'm so scared.
- The final week.
- Don't you think you're too mean?
- Will it be decided today?
- I thought hard about this.
What have we done wrong for them to keep doing this?
So Min is certain that she'll get the Shuddering Package.
- No way.
- There's a lot.
Sang Yeob is sure to be chosen for the Shuddering Package.
- It's a done deal for Sang Yeob.
- It's over for him.
- He will definitely get that.
- It won't be otherwise for him.
I signed up at a gym.
- You want to get in shape?
- I want to train myself.
- Ji Hyo ran out of her luck.
- Exactly.
She usually wins rock-paper-scissors,
- but she's not lucky with the rest.
- Just wait.
- My luck will be recovered soon.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Rock-paper-scissors)
Be quiet.
(What's wrong with you?)
Look at an empty space, and play it by yourself.
(She isn't able to read the room and adds fuel to the fire instead.)
This is great. Ji Hyo and Da Hee...
are teaching So Min a lesson these days.
So Min, I think you'll get a beating soon.
That's why So Min told the staff...
that she was most comfortable with Han Na.
She chose Han Na because Han Na is nice.
She said that...
- she's comfortable with Han Na.
- She's younger than me.
So Min is most comfortable with Han Na.
I like Han Na the best.
(I like Han Na.)
All right. So today's race will...
decide the final result of the Family Project...
regarding the Luxury and Shuddering Packages.
It's the final race. It's called You Take the Shuddering Package.
(You Take the Shuddering Package)
- You Take the Shuddering Package.
- Okay. We're almost done.
You'll get Running Balls depending on the missions' results.
Six members who are chosen by the draw of the Running Balls...
will list their names for the Shuddering Package.
(6 chosen members will be listed for the Shuddering Package.)
We'll use the Running Balls.
- I see. Okay.
- My gosh.
Since we're at Incheon International Airport, are we going somewhere?
We're going abroad.
- Are we all going abroad?
- They asked...
- me to bring the passport.
- You told us to bring the passport.
- You brought my passport.
- I did bring it.
- You all brought your passports.
- Yes.
You will split into 3 teams of 4.
You will participate in the race from different locations.
Bring in the backpacks.
- What's that?
- What is it?
- There are only three.
- Those are backpacks.
- Those backpacks are familiar.
- My gosh.
- They are so colorful.
- Yes, they are.
They say, "Family", "Global", and "Package".
- Is that so?
- There are three.
For the locations, the oldest members,
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Jong Kook, will be the team leaders.
You will choose the backpack which has the final location.
Do missions at the location you find from your backpack.
Here's my concern about this.
You're saying that Seok Jin, Jong Kook, and I are team leaders?
I know that Seok Jin is the oldest,
but he's not ready to be a team leader.
- Right.
- He's not suitable...
Are you looking down on Seok Jin?
- Seok Jin.
- Come here.
- Teach him a lesson.
- I will...
It's because I didn't give him a beating when he was young.
- You, come here.
- When he was young?
- I will...
- It was when he debuted.
That little brat. I'll punch you in the philtrum.
(I'll punch you in the philtrum.)
- He's never hit anyone.
- Listen.
- Seok Jin isn't ready yet.
- I heard that...
- I can... - you've never punched anyone.
I've never punched anyone.
This is what I'm most worried about.
What if Seok Jin punches me, but it doesn't hurt me at all?
- Seok Jin might be flustered?
- I think...
- He might cry.
- Right.
- It would make him cry even more.
(We'll root for you until you get your strong punch.)
- "It doesn't hurt at all."
- His wrist will be bent.
- He cries even more after that.
- He will hurt his own wrist.
What's this?
(What are in these backpacks?)
- Do we need to choose one?
- My gosh.
- "Global" doesn't look good.
- We'll go according to our choice?
Inside the backpacks, you can find the locations for the missions.
If you accomplish the mission, you will get four Running Balls.
If you fail, you'll get 40 Running Balls.
(Failing means 40 Running Balls.)
- What?
- That's a huge difference.
Regardless of the mission's outcome,
if you cannot arrive at the location for the closing segment...
(If they can't arrive where the closing segment will be held...)
You will get an additional 40 Running Balls.
- You must arrive within today.
- Why wouldn't we be able to?
- We might not be able to arrive?
- If you can't arrive...
Why can't we? Are you sending us somewhere?
(Where will they depart for?)
Okay. Let's choose.
- I like yellow.
- Sure, take it.
I like yellow, but in my opinion,
- It says, "global" on it.
- "global"...
- might not be a bad one.
- It will be the contrary?
- It may be the opposite.
- Right.
It says, "global", but we won't go abroad from here.
"Global".
This is the hottest color of 2018.
- That's right.
- Which one? This one?
- I like yellow.
- Is that so?
- The hottest color suits black.
- I think...
- I'll take the "package".
- Okay.
(Seok Jin takes the backpack with "package".)
- You chose your backpacks.
- Okay.
- Check your locations.
- Really?
Do we open up the big compartment?
- What if it follows the name?
- My gosh, look.
- Hey, "global"...
- I'm sure that won't be the case.
- It can't be.
- It won't be predictable, right?
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
- Are you going abroad?
- What is it, Jae Seok?
What does it say?
(He holds his breath.)
- Are you serious?
- What's in it?
- Are you going to Europe?
- Isn't this crazy?
(He wins a trip to Hong Kong.)
- Good for him.
- Time for Hong Kong.
(You want me to go to Hong Kong? I must be back here by today.)
- You're going to Hong Kong?
- I mean...
- We...
- You're going to Hong Kong?
- Jae Seok has the worst luck.
- We're going to an island.
(The card in the backpack with "family" says "island".)
It's an island.
It says "island".
(Both of you are doomed.)
- Is it an island?
- My goodness.
- An island?
- Jong Kook is wearing shorts.
- What about Seok Jin?
- Is it an island in Korea?
- It's land.
- Land?
(It says "land" in the "package" bag.)
- Land is good.
- It's the best.
It's the best.
"Package" was the best.
- I made a mistake.
- Land is in Korea.
Jae Seok thought "global" wouldn't be going abroad.
- He was wrong.
- I thought it would be "package".
- How can we go to Hong Kong?
- Is it outside of Seoul?
- Is this actual Hong Kong?
- After clearing the mission...
- Do you mean Chinatown?
- Is it actually Hong Kong?
You'll arrive there today.
- Before that...
- He pretends not to listen.
(The producer ignores Jae Seok.)
Here's the mission.
This is harsh.
(Hong Kong is already determined.)
We aren't going to Hong Kong now, are we?
- Now is perfect to go.
- Of course.
It's the perfect time.
How can we go to Hong Kong now?
Hong Kong is a place to go for leisure.
We can't go there for one day.
We need to stay there for about three days.
It's a place to go leisurely.
- How can this be Hong Kong?
- This is important.
Doesn't it take 3.5 hours to go to Hong Kong?
- Going back and forth...
- Are you still talking about it?
(Are you still talking about Hong Kong?)
- Stop it.
- Seriously.
- That's enough.
- I wondered what you were saying.
I really like...
- I like Hong Kong.
- Stop it. Just go to Hong Kong.
- Just go.
- How can I go there for a day?
Goodness.
He's getting scolded.
Let's divide into teams.
You'll play Door to Your Fate to determine the teams.
"Door to Your Fate"?
(Door to Your Fate to determine the teams)
Here's how you divide into teams.
Three team leaders will hide behind the curtains.
Team leaders will stand behind each curtain door.
The rest of the members will choose a door each.
You'll team up with the team leader behind the door of your choice.
- We don't know what will happen.
- This is all luck.
As each member chooses, team leaders may change the door.
I see. Can we keep changing?
- The three stand behind a door.
- Okay.
My team stays on land.
Let me make myself clear.
I really like yellow.
- Will you choose yellow?
- Yes, yellow.
I will avoid yellow.
- I told you that mine was yellow.
- Avoid yellow at all costs.
Will Da Hee join the last team?
Right.
She doesn't get to choose.
Who will go in first?
I'll go.
- Kwang Soo.
- Guess whom it will be.
- Follow your feelings.
- Isn't land the best?
Your outfit matches well with Hong Kong.
- That's right.
- Go to Hong Kong.
You look like Chow Yun Fat.
(You look like Chow Yun Fat.)
- Chow Yun Fat?
- I'm just saying it.
You look like Chow Yun Fat.
How do I look like him?
- How so?
- He's an actor.
Your jaw reminds me of him.
- I have no idea.
- Just go.
I'll decide.
Please get unlucky.
I choose number three.
(Kwang Soo chooses the red curtain.)
- That's the unlucky one.
- Let's avoid number three.
The team leader is standing behind the curtain.
(Everyone hopes that Kwang Soo will go to Hong Kong.)
(Which one did Kwang Soo choose?)
(Hello, Kwang Soo.)
Jong Kook.
(Kwang Soo joins Team Island.)
- Come in.
- It's an island.
- That's a good choice.
- He's pretending to be happy.
- It's an island.
(He's pretending to be happy.)
I choose number two.
Seriously.
Team leaders change randomly.
- Who's next?
- It's you.
- It's me.
- So Min.
- Good luck.
Good luck, So Min.
I bet So Min will be attracted to Jae Seok.
No way.
You and Jae Seok...
- will pair up today.
- Just go, So Min.
- Ji Hyo.
- You'll choose...
- Hold my hand.
- No.
- Just once, please.
- It's okay.
Please go.
(Go away, unlucky hand.)
You'll team with Jae Seok today.
Did Jae Seok go in here?
- I bet Jae Seok is smiling.
- In that case,
Jae Seok definitely switched doors.
Here's my final decision.
Are you picking yellow? That was Jae Seok's choice.
- They keep switching.
- Go ahead.
(He can't be behind the yellow curtain.)
He may be behind number three.
Open the curtain.
In 1, 2, 3.
(She had a doubt, but she was wrong.)
I knew that they'd be on the same team.
I'm tired of her!
- They attract like magnets.
- She's on my team again.
- They're the opposite ends.
- Why didn't you switch curtains?
Goodness, So Min.
Why did you choose this curtain?
(So Min joins Team Hong Kong.)
I clearly told you that I like yellow.
Didn't you hate yellow?
- Goodness, So Min.
- I'm in trouble.
I'm definitely doomed today.
She's so unlucky.
I'm doomed today. I'm in trouble.
- What do I do?
- Good luck.
It's my turn.
If Jin Young joins Jong Kook's team again,
you two should date.
If she picks Jong Kook, this will be fate.
It can't be helped.
- Goodbye - Goodbye
(Goodbye)
(She reacts by dancing.)
- Let it be Jong Kook.
- It has to be Jong Kook.
(Whose team will Jin Young join?)
(There is one man.)
Jong Kook.
- You two should date.
- You should date
How is this possible? How did it happen again?
- You should date, you should date - Why did you do that?
Jin Young was surprised too.
- I was surprised too.
- Were you?
- How are they connected?
- They attract like magnets.
- Jin Young is excited.
(She's happy even if she's going to an island.)
Is it my turn?
Is it mine?
It'd be funny if no one chooses Seok Jin.
- No one picks Seok Jin.
- He'll be lonely.
I'll stay on land alone.
(No one has chosen Team Inland.)
(Whom will Haha choose?)
Luxury.
(Dear deity of luxuries)
Please let me be with a good team leader.
(Please let me be with a good team leader.)
(He unveils the team leader.)
(Here's a good team leader.)
Welcome.
- That's perfect.
- Welcome.
No.
- Good luck.
- No.
He joined Seok Jin's team.
That was his fate.
I'll go next.
- Go.
- You may go.
Here I go.
(Next is the notoriously unlucky man.)
(Which team will he join?)
I pick here.
(Welcome, Sang Yeob.)
Is it Sang Yeob?
- Welcome.
- Is it Sang Yeob?
- Stay on land.
- You're with us.
- What's going on?
- Come here.
- What's this?
- Welcome to my team.
- We're definitely getting penalty.
- Welcome.
He's the most terrible.
No, I'm not.
Is it me?
To be honest,
I want to avoid Jong Kook the most.
- You want to avoid him?
- Yes.
I prefer the other teams than Jong Kook's.
Let's avoid Jong Kook.
It can't be Jong Kook.
Go to Jong Kook, go to Jong Kook.
It'll be Jong Kook, it'll be Jong Kook.
- It'll be Jong Kook.
- If it isn't him...
Welcome.
It's Hong Kong.
- Welcome.
- It's so far away!
- It's far away.
- Welcome.
- It's too far.
(Se Chan joins Team Hong Kong.)
This is so difficult.
I'll keep it cool.
I choose the middle one.
(Han Na picks the blue curtain. Whose team will she join?)
(She walks with confidence.)
1, 2, 3.
Welcome.
(Welcome to Hong Kong.)
- Han Na is coming to Hong Kong.
- Welcome.
- Hong Kong!
- So Min is the most excited.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- Our team is closed.
- Okay.
- Really?
- Is our team complete?
The team that Ji Hyo doesn't pick will be joined by Da Hee.
There's Da Hee left.
(The remaining slot will be Da Hee's.)
(Whose team will Ji Hyo join?)
(It's me, Seok Jin.)
Welcome.
- Welcome.
We are on land.
Welcome to our team.
I wanted to avoid you, Sang Yeob.
- Why?
- I wanted to avoid you.
- I'm doing well today.
- I don't know about my team.
Jong Kook feels uncomfortable with Da Hee.
(There are many charismatic members on the island.)
This team will be crazy.
Jong Kook doesn't like people like Da Hee.
(Da Hee is headstrong.)
(He feels a lot of pressure.)
That's true.
We must do well on the mission today.
(He doesn't want to be scolded by Da Hee.)
(Team Land, Team Hong Kong, Team Island)
This is Family Project Finale.
Your last mission is...
You Clear That Mission.
(You Clear That Mission)
Teams choose a mission for another team.
Each team submits a mission that they want others to clear.
Among the 2 missions suggested by the teams and 1 by the staff,
one is chosen randomly.
Clear the mission today in your designated locations.
(Clear the mission today in your designated locations.)
I know what Team Hong Kong should do.
Team Hong Kong is in trouble.
(It takes a total of 7 hours.)
Here's a mission suggested by the staff.
For Team Hong Kong,
find a Hong Kong Banjum in Hong Kong.
(Find Hong Kong Banjum in Hong Kong.)
- Have jjajangmyeon there.
- Stop it.
- No way.
- It doesn't exist in Hong Kong.
Seriously.
Stop it.
(Why would we find that in Hong Kong?)
(Hong Kong is full of fancy food.)
(They clear the mission by eating jjajangmyeon at Hong Kong Banjum.)
- Hong Kong Banjum?
- Wait.
- That's nonsense.
- It makes no sense.
We can't find that restaurant and travel for seven hours.
There are many Hong Kong Banjums in Mapo.
(There are many in Mapo.)
(Are you making fun of us?)
There are many by Sinsa Station.
Seriously.
Why do we always eat noodles?
(Dear director, why do we always eat noodles?)
- What?
- Why do we always eat noodles?
- Be quiet.
- Team Hong Kong should...
eat buckwheat noodles in Hong Kong.
Stop it.
Let me announce Team Island's mission.
You'll visit the "three brothers" island,
Shinshimo Island, in Incheon.
Incheon?
Incheon is so close.
- It's close.
- Shinshimo Island?
(Shinshimo Island consists of 3 islands.)
(What mission will they have to accomplish on that island?)
You'll have to find three brothers and play yut against them.
You have to beat them with "mo" or "do".
(They have to win the yut game with "mo" or "do.)
(Beat three brothers in a game of yut?)
- That'd be hard.
- That's easy.
It'd be hard.
- We have to find three brothers.
- I mean...
- It won't be hard.
- It'll be hard.
Playing yut is not hard.
Eating jjajangmyeon is not hard either.
(Eating jjajangmyeon is not hard either.)
How could you say that?
(Jumping)
What are you doing?
- What's that?
- What's what?
How are you going to attack him?
It's a jump kick.
No one can help him.
What are you doing?
How can you be just standing there?
No one can help you. We'll die.
Han Na and So Min, aren't you going to help me?
- We can't.
- We have no power.
Gosh. What about us?
Let me announce Team Land's mission.
(Team Land's mission)
You'll visit rest areas and eat there.
(Eating at rest areas)
(We can eat?)
That sounds fun.
I'm jealous.
(The oasis on the road)
(Team Land has to eat at rest areas.)
(Jealous)
Choose either Yeongdong, Gyeongbu, or Honam Expressway.
You have to visit every rest area on that expressway...
and eat their most popular dish.
(Visit every rest area and eat their most popular dish.)
- Every rest area?
- Yes.
- All of them?
- All...
What does that mean?
(I knew it.)
Every rest area on the way?
(There's nothing to be jealous of.)
If their stomachs explode, do they fail?
If their stomachs explode?
Those are the missions we've prepared.
Now, come up with a mission...
you want to give the other teams.
- We can decide?
- We can give them a mission?
- What should Team Island do?
- What should we write?
- Should they dig something out?
- I don't know what's there.
- They should dig out clams.
- Clams?
My goodness.
Jae Seok is so scary.
How many clams?
- They should go into the mud.
- Are they in season?
- 3 kinds...
- More than 20kg?
Han Na, you're full of ideas.
- Per person?
- No.
- Han Na, you're mean.
- I was just asking.
I can't believe you.
75kg.
(Meanwhile, Team Island...)
That one is hilarious.
- And then...
- Isn't this too much?
These guys are so mean.
- You guys are full of ideas.
- We're done.
(They've decided on their missions.)
We have your mission ideas.
But some of them are impossible...
to finish today.
- We'll have to make adjustments.
- Who wrote them?
I mean...
We have to find them...
and punish them.
All the unreasonable ideas should...
- There he goes again.
- It's been a while.
Let's look at Team Hong Kong's mission first.
This was what one team wrote.
"Find an old lady..."
(Find an old lady.)
"And share a strand of noodle with her at Hong Kong Banjum."
(Share a strand of noodle with an old lady.)
- You wrote it, right?
- What?
What's wrong?
(Do you remember it?)
Everyone does the noodle game.
- You...
- What's so wrong about it?
(What's wrong?)
(It'll look like this.)
That's absurd.
- What?
- It's ridiculous.
You're clever.
The person should be either over 80...
or under two.
(Either over 80 or under 2)
I mean...
- You jerk.
- What?
(You jerk.)
- What did you say?
- You're a jerk.
The next one is problematic.
"Get a waiting number of 1001..."
- "at a restaurant."
- Who wrote it?
(Get a waiting number of 1001.)
That's absurd.
- We want you to go to a restaurant.
- You just have to wait.
- Ji Hyo was...
- But...
Wait. Waiting number 1001 is impossible.
- I mean...
- We were trying to be flexible.
You could let other people go first.
(Go to a famous restaurant in Hong Kong, )
(and get a waiting number of 1001.)
1001? Think about it.
We should do something fun in Hong Kong.
To get 1001,
- we'll have to wait all day.
- It'll be so easy.
It'll be boring.
It'll be so boring.
It already sounds boring.
(Team Land is in panic.)
Get a waiting number, and eat noodles with an old lady.
- What should we do?
- Then...
how about we wait in line every time we see a waiting line?
About 100 times.
- 100 times?
- Yes.
Every time we see a waiting line, we have to get in.
What about at bus stops?
Get in every waiting line you see.
Do we have a waiting line fetish?
Get in every waiting line.
They have to use the bathroom if there's a line there.
- Make sure they do.
- You have to use the bathroom?
Yes.
Every time we see a line...
- You have to get in the line.
- You have to wait in line.
(Eat jjajangmyeon at Hong Kong Banjum.)
(Share a strand of noodle with an old lady.)
(Get in every waiting line.)
Missions for Team Island are problematic too.
Let me read you one.
It's the mission given by the staff...
plus digging out 15kg of clams in 3 kinds.
That sounds fun.
Jong Kook is strong.
It sounds fun?
You want to join?
No. I have to go to Hong Kong.
The next one is the real problem.
- You have to find someone.
- Okay.
"Go to the island,"
"find a Pyo who was born in May of 1943."
"He has to have curly hair, is blood type B, and is stubborn."
"He should be handsome and have ingrown toenails."
"He has to know at least 4 of your names in 5 seconds."
"You can't show him your name tags."
Ingrown toenails?
What's that?
There are not many with that last name.
A blood type B born in 1943 would be hard to find.
If we can't find him, what do we do?
Let's say we can't find him.
- Are you getting upset?
- Get off of me!
(Don't stop me.)
- If we can't find...
- You have to find him.
What if we can't find him?
What if no such person is registered at the district office?
(What if no such person is registered at the district office?)
You'd have to dig up graves.
(Extreme)
What do we do?
- I mean...
- What are you talking about?
(You're so extreme.)
- Dig up graves?
- What are you talking about?
We wouldn't be able to go any further.
(Will this ever end?)
(Beat three brothers in yut with "mo" or "do.)
(Pyo born in 1943 has to guess 4 of the members' names.)
(Dig out 15 kg of clams in 3 kinds.)
Missions for Team Land are hard too.
"At every rest area, park 10 SUV cars..."
"in the order of..."
"black, white, black, white, and blue."
(Park 10 SUV cars.)
That's easy.
"Don't buy any food."
(They can't buy any food.)
"But if you are given walnut cakes, you can eat them."
(They can eat walnut cakes if they are given to them.)
If they receive fish-shaped buns, they can't eat them.
Only walnut cakes.
The next one is a big problem.
"The mission given by the staff..."
"plus trying Korea's longest zip-line in Hadong."
(Staff's mission plus zip-line)
(Korea's longest zip-line)
- Korea's longest.
- That sounds fun.
That sounds like a penalty.
We were going to go there, right?
Is that the one you were talking about?
(That zip-line?)
I saw it on TV.
(It all started from what Jae Seok said a few months ago.)
- Zip-line.
(Asia's longest zip-line is in Hadong.)
(I'm curious, but I'm too scared to try it myself.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
It's supposed to be a penalty.
I recently went to a suspension bridge.
You should go.
Didn't you do that on "Infinite Challenge"?
- Yes.
- Why...
Don't talk about "Infinite Challenge".
(Don't talk about "Infinite Challenge".)
Why would you talk about what you did on that show?
- Why did you bring it up?
- Every week...
(I want you to try the zip-line.)
It's making me sad.
Why are you mentioning another program here?
You should go.
(They feel foolish about the challenge.)
(Choose one expressway, and try the best dish in every rest area.)
(Do valet parking for 10 cars, and don't buy any food.)
(First mission plus longest zip-line in Korea.)
Team Land can pick first.
The first mission is the best.
(They'll choose 1 out of the 3 given missions.)
I know it is.
They picked one.
I'm worried.
Please flip it toward us.
- Hey.
- Really?
Gosh, no way.
(Screaming)
What is it?
Zip-lining.
(They picked zip-lining.)
Oh, gosh.
I can't do it. You two do it.
- You two do it.
- Why did you pick?
- This isn't good.
- What are you going to do now?
We tried so hard so that we could avoid this.
Why would we do this now?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- Pick a good one.
- Okay.
- Pick a good one, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- Choose a thin one.
- I picked one.
(Kwang Soo is usually very unlucky. What did he choose?)
Okay!
- Okay!
- Okay! You did it.
The mission by the staff.
(He picks the mission suggested by the staff.)
"Find three brothers and win in a game of yut."
- Okay.
- That's so easy.
- We'll win Luxury Stickers.
- Yes, it's good.
- Youngest.
- Ms. Detective,
pick one.
- Look at them first.
- Are you strong or weak?
Trust your instincts.
- Middle one.
- Are you strong or weak?
(Team Hong Kong's fate is up to Han Na.)
- Is it good? Come here.
- Your jacket is all over the place.
I hope it's the line one.
It'll be good.
- What is it?
- Hong Kong...
It's the line one.
This is what we wanted.
- This is not bad, right?
- Right.
- That's what we wanted.
- Right?
- Fine, this one's not bad.
- It's good.
It's good.
(At least we won't have to meet an old lady.)
(Team Jae Seok must stand in line if there are more than 5 people.)
(Team Jong Kook has to find three brothers and win a game.)
(Team Seok Jin has the staff mission plus longest zip-line in Korea.)
How am I supposed to zip-line?
Why did you pick it then?
- You shouldn't have picked it.
- I know.
Valet parking would be so easy.
- I didn't pick it on purpose.
- We'll just be parking.
I didn't do it on purpose.
- Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
- I didn't.
- Do you want to go to the back?
- Okay, I will.
I didn't bring my backpack.
- It's behind you.
- What?
- It's on your back.
- It's behind me?
- You're carrying it.
What was that?
- What happened?
- I didn't know I was carrying it.
Oh, gosh. You're unbelievable.
(They hate zip-lining.)
I hate this.
You know what? Sang Yeob...
is going on the Shuddering Package for sure.
Really?
I still have one chance.
- Not really.
- It's for sure.
You're going on the Shuddering Package, so just do it.
Shouldn't you do it so that you can go on the Luxury Package?
- First game, - If I go on it...
Majority Vote Game.
If I can go on the Luxury Package, I'll do it.
Point with your finger.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- 2, 3.
- Okay.
- I know.
I know it's me.
- Ji Hyo likes this type of thing.
- I don't.
What do you mean? This is how people think of you.
- No.
- It is.
When you jumped off the Macau Tower,
- you were awesome.
- You looked so great.
I saw that too.
- Wasn't that great?
- Girl crush.
That was years ago.
- You're so old.
- So you should do it again.
How far away are we?
- We have 20km left.
- 20 minutes?
- 20km.
- 20km...
(Did he mishear it, or did he forget?)
"We have 20 km left." "20 minutes?"
Have you ever held a car key...
in your hands then started looking for it?
- I have.
- Right?
I've done this too.
I was walking and talking on the phone,
and I was like, "I forgot my phone."
I went back home.
- You went back home?
- It's a disease.
- It's not.
- You actually went home?
- I did go home.
- That's serious then.
The person I was talking to said this too.
"Why didn't you bring your phone?"
Really?
That's insane.
- Who is this?
- That's insane.
My brother.
(That's why they are family.)
Sung Moon?
Somebody I know...
came back from his baby's birthday party...
without his baby.
(He didn't bring his baby back from the baby's birthday party.)
(Who is this man?)
Seok Jin.
(It's Seok Jin.)
"Hey, where's Hyun Woo?"
"Didn't you bring him, Mother?"
It was me.
"I thought you took him."
"Where's the baby, Soo Jeong?"
"Oh, dear."
"Where is he?"
Everybody is asking.
"The baby is gone."
(What if he goes on the zip-line without the rope?)
It was my baby's first birthday party.
This is really nice, right?
- Yes, I feel relaxed.
- Right?
- It's close too.
- Right.
We just need to meet people.
- Once we find them, - That's it.
We just need to play yut.
And...
I remember playing yut...
with my family during Lunar New Year.
My grandma...
got the highest point seven times in a row.
- Really?
- Is that hereditary too?
- I'm her grandson.
When is Da Hee coming?
She'll probably join us before the cruise leaves.
I see.
Who wants some jelly?
(Jin Young brought some jelly to replenish sugar.)
- No.
- My sugar level hasn't dropped yet.
We didn't eat that long ago.
Do you keep wanting... No, I'm okay. I'm fine.
- Just take it.
- Eat some.
Okay.
Kwang Soo. Use your hands.
(This is sad.)
- Okay.
- "Okay"?
I think our mission will be easy,
but the difficult part is...
The important thing is...
- How will Jong Kook...
- No.
This...
How will he not be annoyed by Da Hee?
- That's your problem.
- No.
- He'll get annoyed.
- That's not it.
We can do this mission while having fun.
But... But...
I might see that face again.
(What if her angry side comes out?)
Da Hee has this face she makes.
She's so nice, but she doesn't suit Jong Kook.
We have to pay attention.
(They drive for 15 minutes from Incheon Airport.)
This is the coast of Incheon.
This is so nice.
- The weather is so nice.
- How is this possible?
It was this sunny in New Zealand.
Jong Kook.
You didn't pronounce "New Zealand" right.
Jong Kook, can you not talk like a gangster?
What are you talking about? I'm not a gangster.
Say, "Disney Land".
Diesel Land.
"Diesel Land"?
- This is so nice.
- I know.
Da Hee couldn't join us in the introduction,
- but she's here now.
- Is she here?
- She must be so tired.
- I know.
- Da Hee.
- Because I'm your lady - There you are.
(It's like seeing a friend after 20 years.)
Hello.
- This looks so awkward.
- I know.
It must be tiring. She's shooting a drama.
- Of course.
- For sure.
- Don't sound so fake.
- What?
You sound like you're reading lines.
Do you know the rules for today?
I heard the rules in the car.
- You heard?
- Yes, I know for sure.
- You have to pay attention.
- It's yut.
She pays more attention than anyone.
Don't you know?
- She focuses more than others.
- Yes, I can do it.
You can't cross the line though.
If not, Jong Kook...
- Your ambition...
- I know.
He actually finds you uncomfortable.
Me?
I didn't say that.
- What are you talking about?
- He's so uncomfortable.
- What are you talking about, punk?
- I...
I watched that episode.
I didn't know I was like that.
I almost crossed the line.
(I didn't know I was like that. I almost crossed the line.)
They actually edited it nicely.
If you say that, that makes me look more weird.
You did look weird.
(You know well.)
You're a very weird person.
I looked weird because you told me to see a doctor.
I looked like I had mental problems.
- You do have mental problems.
- I don't.
(Quarreling)
Why are you acting normally?
My mom told me to cut down a bit. She said I was too weird.
- There's something going on.
- You look good together.
Why are you quarreling? Is this a lovers' quarrel?
- You are dressed like a couple too.
- That's right.
They didn't talk to each other ahead of time, right?
- They're dressed similarly.
- I know.
Jong Kook. You two are matching for sure.
What?
- Why are you so black?
- You have eye boogers.
Hey.
Eye boogers.
(Is this a couples' race again?)
Da Hee is really a bit like this. When she talks,
- she does this.
- Like this.
She does this.
"You did that."
"You did that, Jong Kook."
(Like this.)
(What is that?)
- Come here.
- It's different.
- Fine.
- You're so...
They're like Nam Cheol and Nam Sung Nam.
(They're like Nam Cheol and Nam Sung Nam.)
They get along...
very well.
(This duo has such great teamwork.)
It won't be easy to find three brothers on the island.
Won't there be three brothers though?
- I think so.
- It won't be easy.
What time is the last cruise?
The last cruise is at 9:30pm.
- At night?
- If we fail, we can't come back?
It's tomorrow at 10am.
Back in the days, people tell you to go on dates...
on the islands.
People used to say that. It's an old thing though.
What year was that?
When I was young, I heard that somewhere.
- So what year?
- I didn't have to go to an island.
(Why would you go to an island?)
I was fine without going to one.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
Kwang Soo, this is Shinshimo Island.
(Shinshimo Island? The cruise?)
- Why are you changing the subject?
- No.
Kwang Soo needs it.
(He needs the power of the island.)
- What are you talking about?
- Kwang Soo...
- You two look good together.
- People do that.
- What do you think?
- They look very good together.
You two look even better. I'm serious.
Everybody around me is rooting for you.
- We look good together?
- You do.
I'm serious.
Are you serious?
- With this one?
- I'm serious.
- "With this one"?
- No.
I meant you and me.
You don't like it?
That's not what I meant.
If they become a couple,
Jong Kook will lose 20kg in a month.
(Jin Young's love slave diet is very effective.)
They kind of look like a college couple.
- A college couple.
- Yes, I know what she means.
I keep looking at him, and this looks like my dad's jacket.
(What are you talking about?)
What are you talking about? This is not your dad's jacket.
He's going on an island,
so he's dressed like the head of the village.
(He looks friendly and warm.)
He wanted to look friendly.
"It's the same jacket as mine."
(That was an unexpected attack.)
He's like that.
When it comes to fashion... Never mind.
Fashion?
Let's throw the yut, and the person with the lowest points...
will get hit in the head with the yut.
Let's do it.
We have the yut, so let's do it.
- Hey.
- Yes?
- Why would you do that?
- Let's do it.
- This is so funny.
- It'll be fun.
Why would you get hit in the head with the yut?
Your head might break. You have to control the power.
- With this.
- Just a tap?
- Let's do it.
- You can hit the head,
but not like this.
You can't use your entire arm. You can snap your wrist.
- Deal. Let's do it.
- Deal.
- Use your wrist.
- Let's do it.
- The person with the lowest point?
- Lowest?
- You can pass with Do and Mo.
- What about Back Do?
You can pass with Do or Mo?
- That's what we need.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook is first to go.)
(He gets Gurl.)
- Gurl.
- That's in the middle.
Gurl isn't bad.
Do is a pass, so Gurl is pretty high.
- It's pretty high.
- Yes.
(Jin Young is next.)
Jin Young.
(She gets Mo.)
You're so lucky.
(She's the new lucky one.)
She's so lucky.
- What should I do?
- She has a funny laugh.
I kind of saw her.
Instead of raising it, you have to push it.
(Push it sideways instead of throwing it up.)
(She actually got Mo.)
- You were serious.
- Just push it.
- She found out?
- Push it.
Just push it.
No, you have to throw it.
That's true. You do have to throw it.
Women can do that, but men have to throw it.
(He still pushes them forward.)
(He gets Mo too.)
- Mo!
- Hey.
- You have to throw it.
- Do you get hit in the head?
(Jong Kook gets the penalty.)
You have to throw it.
Please take a good video of this.
If I see him use his arm, I'm going to hit him 10 times.
10 times. Which camera are you going to use?
Which one? Zoom in on his arm.
- His arm...
- Look at his face.
If he moves his arm...
- You can't practice.
- No, that's not it.
As soon as you move this, I'll hit you 10 times.
Okay. Let me practice once.
(Let me practice once.)
(Hitting)
(That sounded like lumber.)
(Punching)
- I didn't move it.
- Hey.
You moved this much.
You moved it.
(This much?)
- I didn't move it.
- You're going to break his head.
It sounds like something is breaking.
Isn't this much okay? I didn't move my arm.
I'm going to look at the camera.
Ready.
(He finally gets a chance. He can only use his wrist.)
- Count down.
- Look at his face.
You need to count.
1, 2, 3.
(Hitting)
(It's the sound of wooden percussion made with his wrist.)
That sounded so loud.
Doesn't it hurt?
- We're here.
- We're here. Oh, dear.
- That was clean.
- Hey.
Let's do it again.
- You moved it, right?
- No, I didn't.
- What?
- Sorry?
Let's do it again.
Why?
- Are we here already?
- We arrived.
- It's over.
- Hold on.
- I think you're bleeding.
- I'm sure it hurt a lot.
That was so funny.
- Fine. Okay.
- Okay.
Give me the yut.
- Why did you do this?
- What?
If you do this, you can hit harder.
- That's true.
- You don't have to move your arm.
- Hey.
- No.
Look. You can do this.
(You can hit it like this.)
You won't move your arm.
Why did you hit like this? I watched him...
and wondered why he kept on doing this.
- You can't hit it hard.
- He looks ugly.
If you do this...
- You look so ugly.
- Did it hurt?
Does it hurt?
You should try it, jerk.
(You should try it, jerk.)
(He expresses himself rather violently.)
(They've never seen this on TV before.)
What do I do? The pain won't go away.
Why does it keep hurting?
It keeps on hurting.
What will you do?
It's so painful.
The pain won't subside. What happened?
(Everybody, this is how dangerous yut can be.)
We can't go to Hong Kong all of a sudden.
The flight is 3.5 hours.
We can't go to Hong Kong right now.
- Jae Seok, - This is a first.
Why did you stand in the yellow area?
I said I would be there.
Why did you come?
So Min is drawn to you like magnets.
- No.
- To you.
Jae Seok is always...
I think you and I had...
an ill-fated relationship in our past lives.
- You know what I mean?
- It was an ill-fated relationship.
- Was I a frog and you, a fly?
(Did he get eaten by Frog So Min and was reborn as Jae Seok?)
Oh, gosh.
You two have a great chemistry.
You were a blow fly because you like colorful things.
Blow flies are colorful.
Are you going to let somebody younger than you say that?
(Let's go party in Hong Kong with the colorful fly Jae Seok.)
(Incheon to Hong Kong)
Look at this.
- I'm fascinated again.
- The weather is different.
Are we in Hong Kong?
It's kind of humid.
- It's high.
- Right.
It's 70°C.
- 70°C?
- Really?
- No?
- I don't think it's that high.
I looked at the weather.
So Min said this.
There was a screw on the ground,
so I joked and said, "Is this yours, So Min?"
She said, "No, it's Han Na's."
(Do you have a loose screw?)
(She tosses it to Han Na since she wasn't there.)
It's yours.
She heard that and said this.
"I think she's so weird."
- "She's so weird."
- So Min...
So Min is not normal.
They think they are compatible, but when they're not together,
they talk about each other.
- They're no joke.
- They are not.
We have arrived in Hong Kong.
We only have four hours to film.
- Come on. This is driving me nuts.
- We can't finish the mission.
We can't do it.
If you can't do it, you get 40 Running Balls.
We should have stayed in Korea then.
You picked those backpacks.
Why did you pick it? You should have picked something else.
I picked it for myself.
You chose the curtain and came to me.
- We can't blame anybody.
- Right.
So...
we have a car ready for you.
If you want to go somewhere, we'll take you there.
- We have to go to Tsim Sha Tsui.
- It's the main street.
Let's go to the main street. We need to do the mission...
- In a crowded place? - where there are many people.
You all haven't been to Hong Kong.
- You haven't either.
- I've been here.
Stop pretending like you know.
- I've been to Hong Kong once.
- This is driving me nuts.
- And...
- The flight attendant...
didn't know what to do because of you.
- I asked for some information.
- And she fell asleep.
The flight attendant didn't know what to do.
She asked if she should wake Han Na up, and I said no.
- I...
- She was sleeping like this.
She slept so prettily.
I was wondering if there was a popular restaurant with a line.
I asked carefully.
- Where is the paper?
- Where is it?
Hold on.
(Where is the paper? Hold on.)
It was in my pocket.
Han Na, I don't expect too much from you.
- I don't expect too much.
- Goodness.
(She's hopeless with her reasoning and collecting information.)
- Look. You have to do this first.
- What?
Is this the line?
- Look at you.
- Goodness.
(He's spreading his wisdom in an arrogant tone.)
It's loading.
Is this the line?
What was that?
You can do this in Korea.
- Hold on.
- You have to do this in Korea.
It works now.
Is this the line?
We have to know this.
Did you see it? Are these two lines?
This is driving me nuts.
- Two lines? - "Are these two lines?"
Your mouth looks weird, so it's not recognizing it.
You should try.
I think I know how to say it.
What?
(She was on a Chinese drama. Is she fluent?)
What does that mean? "Is this the line?"
It means to line up.
- Is that right?
- Or not?
I'll speak in Chinese, and it can translate it to Korean.
- That works.
- Try it.
(She speaks in Chinese.)
- "This party..."
This party is facing each other.
What does that mean?
What happened?
- What's this?
- Where did you go?
- I mean...
- Whom did you hang out with?
- This isn't it.
- Let's stop.
Let's just line up.
(Forget it. Let's just line up.)
I'm getting tired. You're making me tired.
You started it. You asked about the line.
- Are you getting mad at me?
- No.
- It's kind of hot.
- She's mad.
- "It's kind of hot."
It's kind of humid. Hold on.
So Min is in love with Jung Hae In.
(She's in line to treat Hae In to a meal.)
Her ideal man changed again.
When he smiles...
- Is Han Na into him too?
- No.
When he smiles, he brightens up.
- Right.
- His face brightens up.
The screen brightens up when he smiles.
When we smile, does the screen get darker?
- Does it?
- It's dull.
(It's not just dark.)
- Are we dull?
- It's kind of humid too.
- It's because of Se Chan.
- Is it?
Why is it because of me? I'm so bright.
- My gums show. It's so nice.
- Hey, don't be mistaken.
You don't say these things when you are with Jong Kook, right?
- You are different.
- That mouth...
You are different from Jong Kook.
Ask Jong Kook to open his eyes.
(Jong Kook has small eyes.)
I will die. He will beat me up.
Seriously.
I am so happy that Jong Kook isn't here.
I couldn't be happier. The atmosphere is relaxed.
Are you watching this, Kim Jong Kook?
Are you watching this? Watch yourself.
- Say some strong words.
- Whenever you are gone,
- people are...
- People are cheerful.
You always wear black clothes.
I will take this off later.
Watch yourself, Kim Jong Kook.
- Are you watching this?
Are you watching this?
Han Na, say something. Say some strong words.
- I don't find him scary yet.
- Say something.
What do you think about his fashion sense?
What? It's not that great.
(He only wears black.)
- Good job.
- He looks dark.
Good job, Han Na. That lightens my heart.
Please remove my audio.
My audio.
Are you telling the staff in advance?
Please remove my part.
(Jong Kook is the best.)
In that case, remove mine too.
Don't use this scene.
- Cut!
- We filmed it.
- Remove scene 22 for Hong Kong.
- Cut!
(The scene is saved for eternity.)
(The bus runs.)
- Tsim Sha Tsui.
- This is the place I know well.
I can be the guide here.
Han Na, this is a good place to travel.
- I want to sit in the terrace.
- It's really nice.
This is a good place to travel.
(Accumulate 100 in queue numbers at Tsim Sha Tsui.)
(Since there are many options for sightseeing, )
(eating, )
(and playing, isn't success guaranteed?)
- The weather is really nice.
- The weather.
- It's nice.
- It's neither cold nor hot.
It's warm.
- Let's go.
Hold on, don't look.
All right.
- Look elsewhere. Look at the sky.
- The sky is clear.
(They don't want to waste time in a long queue.)
There are queues everywhere.
Look elsewhere. Stare into the distance.
We must choose our queue wisely.
Jae Seok, we must go that way. That way.
- Calm down.
- I will calm down.
- I will.
I have done shootings outside of Korea quite often.
- Okay?
- He hasn't done this.
He hasn't acted as a guide.
- People are in a line!
- Gosh, you startled me.
- We have to line up.
- Over there.
(If there are many people, they can finish their mission soon.)
(Can the queue in Tsim Sha Tsui help them?)
- I thought they were people.
- That startled me.
Shouldn't we line up?
So Min, come here. We don't have much time.
(So Min runs toward the sculpture.)
So Min, it's not a queue.
I can't believe you. Come on.
Line up.
- How many people are there?
- 10 people.
Shouldn't this count?
- It doesn't involve an experience.
- Shouldn't this count?
No, it shouldn't.
Listen. Listen, Mr. Producer.
Listen.
- There are 10 people.
- No, no.
- No, no, - We can have an experience...
by posing like statues and taking a picture.
- What are you doing?
- I am giving an autograph.
My goodness.
(Han Na and So Min are uncontrollable.)
- Is it a fan signing event?
- She is...
Come here.
This should count.
I know. There are 10 people in the queue.
- No, you need real people.
- Real people?
- Let's cross the road.
- Let's go.
This is nice.
(The main street is that way.)
- My goodness.
- I can feel it.
- I remember this.
- That line...
Jae Seok, there is a cafe where people line up.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Jae Seok sees a line for the bus.)
- There...
- Since you saw the line,
you have to line up.
(It seems like the producer heard him.)
It's not like that.
- Wait, do we need to ride the bus?
- You saw the line.
Jae Seok, why did you see the line?
- It's not like that.
- Why did you do that?
- How many people are in the line?
We need to get on it.
- 1, 2, 3,
- Hold on.
- 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
We were going to eat.
- 11 people.
- Why did you look at the line?
I couldn't help but look.
- What do we do?
- This is the main street!
(Se Chan is annoyed that Jae Seok looked at the line.)
(Where are we going?)
Why did you look at it?
I didn't look.
- Seriously.
- I didn't look.
It just happened so suddenly. Hold on. Producer Cheol Min.
- Yes?
- You are so inflexible.
We were going to eat.
I looked at it by chance. I didn't want to get in the line.
Like I said before, you must line up the moment you see the line.
I can't believe you. I told you, didn't I?
I told you to look at the sky! Why did you look at the line?
The trip might end after a series of bus trips.
Suddenly,
- I was reminded of it.
- Okinawa?
I was reminded of Okinawa.
- Jae Seok, keep your mouth shut.
- Right, right.
Keep your mouth shut.
- I should watch what I say.
- Keep your mouth shut.
(The mission of lining up in Hong Kong starts.)
Is this the right place?
(They are willing to go anywhere as long as there is a line.)
(However, they get caught up in an incident.)
(Can they return safely from Hong Kong?)
(Team Island plays a game of yut.)
(However)
(The best player appears.)
(The best player's skills put them in a daze.)
(Even Jong Kook is defenseless.)
(Can Team Island complete their mission?)
(A place that touches the sky)
We are in the air.
(One man is suspended in the air.)
My mind is blank.
(At this moment, )
(they don't feel like they are on a variety show.)
(Also)
(Luxury Package versus Shuddering Package)
(A round of the final decision makes them shudder.)
(Who will end up where?)
(Family Project Final)