(Last week)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin went to Busan to receive a penalty.)
(They must make number 100 by working part-time jobs...)
(in 100 in a Day Race.)
(One man got dragged to Busan to pay his debt.)
(To make number 100,)
(the 100-year-old Couple worked hard...)
(with Kwang Soo.)
(Then they went out to the sea for another part-time job.)
(Team Seoul got to enjoy a vacation with 50 dollars.)
(Jong Kook suggested...)
(a new style of vacation at a gym.)
(They cycled and enjoyed a cold sauna.)
I feel so refreshed.
You completed the second vacation plan...
which involved eating eggs and sikhye at a sauna.
Now, three vacation plans...
and 43 dollars and 90 cents remain.
The 1st 2 plans were cheap.
Which plan will you complete next?
- We have three plans left. - An escape room,
- pork belly meat, - Shall we do an escape room next?
and surfing remain.
- Let's do an escape room next. - An escape room?
- Surfing. - To do an escape room,
we will use our brains...
to solve a crime.
We can do an escape room in any room, right?
(He has quick wits.)
- It can be anything we choose. - We didn't set the details.
We can do it in any room.
- An escape room. - The one who removes my name tag...
gets to escape.
Then none of us will escape.
- It will go on all night long. - That's how an escape room works.
- I will never escape. - Right?
We can decide on the rules later.
- Okay. - Whose place is available?
(We need to save money.)
- Let's go to your place. - My place?
Let's go to your place.
- Is it the same place? - What?
Is it the place we visited?
Yes, it is.
Is it the place we visited? Let's go there.
There were many rooms. There were many.
- Let's go there. - You should ask for my opinion.
(I have human rights.)
You shouldn't talk as if it has been decided.
- Let's go to your place. - When I was single,
they used my place four times.
We didn't tell him in advance.
- Really? Okay. - They used my place.
(Then it can't be helped.)
Is there food at home?
Food? Of course, there is.
- Is there pork belly meat at home? - Pork belly meat?
I bet there is.
I will look for it. I don't think there is pork belly meat.
- We will see. - Maybe it's pork neck meat.
You could ask your brother to buy the meat.
- He isn't home today. - Why?
He works, too.
(My brother works, too.)
I see. Let him rest. Tell him to work.
- Okay? - Okay.
- Shall we go to my place? - Let's go to Se Chan's place.
- Okay. - Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go and do an escape room. - Okay.
I am very happy.
Before you go,
- I have a notification. - What is it?
26 dollars have been deducted from the total amount.
- Why? - Why?
(So suddenly? Why?)
- Why? - Tell us why.
We told you the money will be given to the members.
- Did the others use it? - Yes.
(Without any permission?)
- The part-time jobs are exhausting. - Seriously.
I will pay for lunch. Enjoy it.
Suyuk set.
I will also have the suyuk set.
I will have sundae soup.
I will pay for lunch.
Thank you.
I can't believe it.
- Call them. - For goodness' sake.
What did they eat? Perhaps, they ate cold jokbal.
(We are saving up money.)
(We must know where they spent the money.)
Pick up the phone.
- What are you eating? - Hello.
- Hello. - What is that, ssambap?
(What are you eating?)
- Kwang Soo. - They are eating.
- Pork gukbap? - They are eating delicious food.
We are eating pork gukbap.
- They are eating pork gukbap. - Pork gukbap.
- We ate quail eggs. - We ate quail eggs.
We are saving money.
Why would you do that? Eat.
(He is...)
(really annoying.)
- We should use the money quickly. - It seems that way.
If they use up all the money,
- we will have to go to Busan. - We will have to go to Busan.
- We are in a different position. - Be quiet. They don't know that.
- That's right. - They didn't hear me.
- What? - All right.
- We are hanging up. - We are hanging up.
We are hanging up. All right.
- Let's go. - How much money do we have left?
- At this rate... - Let's use the money.
Let's eat. I am hungry.
We should use the money. What can we buy with 17 dollars?
- Tteokbokki. - Tteokbokki is a good idea.
- Tteokbokki is a good idea. - Let's go.
- Tteokbokki is a good idea. - My goodness.
- Let's go. - Sundae.
- They were stuffing their faces. - Seriously.
We must use the money before Kwang Soo does.
Shall I order tteokbokki?
- Go ahead. - Let's order it.
- Hello. - I would like the twin set.
It's 17 dollars. How would you like to pay?
I will pay with cash.
Okay. The food will be delivered as soon as it's ready.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Tteokbokki will be tasty.
If we use all the money, how will we get pork belly meat?
(By the way)
Pork belly meat? Oh, we have to eat pork belly meat.
I forgot about that.
(He is relaxed.)
We need a favor from a friend.
(He is a problem-solver.)
You have...
(Jong Kook, the problem-solver, remembers everything.)
(He remembers a friend can provide the place and goods.)
Whom should we ask?
Shall we brainstorm? Does anyone come to mind?
Meat... Meat reminds me of Moon Se Yoon.
Se Yoon is a good choice.
- Right. - I also think he is a good choice.
- Se Yoon. - Se Yoon is a good choice.
There is also Hwang Je Sung.
- Je Sung is a good choice. - Je Sung.
- Hwang Je Sung. - I want to meet him in real life.
He is a member of my fan club.
- That's right. - I am a big fan.
- Really? - Yes, I am a big fan.
- Je Sung. - Shall I call him later or now?
- Now. - Try calling him.
This is cool. I am a big fan.
(They are fans of each other.)
I was going to bring up Je Sung.
- We had the same idea. - That's right.
(I look after my fan.)
- Is he nice? - He is.
- He isn't picking up. - He is good friends with Je Sung.
- Se Yoon. - Je Sung didn't pick up.
He didn't pick up.
What is he doing?
(Let's think of someone.)
Let's go.
- Let's go. - That's good.
(Team Busan goes to a wharf after lunch.)
- Rock cod! - Rock cod!
- That's good. - I'll introduce the captain...
who will help you fish.
Here comes the captain.
Hello.
- Hello. - It's nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you. This way. - We are in your care.
- You are a veteran, right? - Yes.
Today,
- Please help us. - we have to catch about 72 fish.
- Okay. - Is this possible?
We'll see when we get there and check the nets.
- What do we need to do? - What should we do?
I threw out the nets the day before.
- We just have to reel them up. - Yes.
We have to haul up the nets today.
- We hit the jackpot. - He did all the work.
- Just help me with those. - Okay.
We're not here to help. We're your part-timers today.
- Part-timers? - Yes.
I don't have that much money.
(Is this a joke from a man from Busan?)
- Goodness. - We don't need money.
- We just have to catch fish. - Okay.
We'll put our trust in the captain.
Captain, hasn't it been about 60 years...
since you've been a fisherman?
- Not 60 years. - How long has it been then?
What's wrong with you? It's been about 45 years, right?
- Right? I knew it. - Yes, 45 years.
- He's very reliable. I can feel it. - I can tell right away.
- Captain, let's get started then. - Okay.
- Let's start now. - Okay.
(Captain, please put an end to this torment of part-time jobs.)
Put on your life vests.
(They get ready to set sail for net fishing in the village.)
Seasickness is all about your confidence.
(Lee Kwang Soo, fish-looking man)
(Jee Seok Jin, a former navy)
(Yu Jae Seok, claims to be a fishing master)
(Fish in Busan, brace yourselves.)
(The trio of the best fishermen are on board.)
This kind of weather is rare.
I can't believe I'm on a boat again.
- Today, - Today's part-time jobs...
it's full of twists and turns.
That's what our show is for.
(Teasing)
I meant about today.
How exciting.
Anyway,
- Bye. - let's catch a lot of fish.
We can catch flatfish, rockfish,
and rock cod.
Goodness, today's part-time jobs are hard.
- I agree. - It's really exhausting.
- How many jobs did we do? - I had no idea...
(They cleaned the windows on top of the cliff.)
I had no idea we'd be on a boat.
- This was your penalty. - Yes, it was.
(Why am I here?)
You were supposed to carry this out.
- Right. - Anyway,
trust me.
Why?
(He has 0 confidence in Jae Seok.)
You've never done this before.
Don't you know me?
I spent a lot of time at the sea.
- Stop lying. - If so...
What are you talking about? I'm from the navy.
- Unbelievable. - Seriously.
(I can't trust these guys.)
(The refreshing autumn breeze washes away their fatigue.)
- It's nice to be out on the waters. - Of course.
- How nice. - The ocean breeze is nice.
I'm glad.
(They arrive at the spot for net fishing.)
- We're at the spot. - Is this the spot?
- Yes. - It's over there.
- There it is. - We'll grab the buoys.
How many nets do we need to haul up?
- 2. - I see. 2 nets.
Captain, flatfish, rockfish, and rock cod are important to us.
- Flatfish, rockfish, and rock cod. - Should we start now?
- Do you see that over there? - Okay.
- Grab the buoy. - Okay.
Go, go.
- Should I start reeling up? - Yes.
- Do we use that to reel up nets? - Yes, we must reel them up.
- I saw that on TV. - Okay.
I've never seen this in person.
- Net fishing. - Same here. It's interesting.
- Do we need to haul it up? - Yes.
- I just turned on the net hauler. - I see. Net hauler.
- We'll use the net hauler. - Right.
- Just like this. - It's coming up now.
I guess there are a lot of fish.
- Get ready to receive the fish. - Where should we put them?
The net will be reeled up.
(Isn't that a rock?)
- Hold on. Wait. - Gosh.
- Something is hanging. - That's fine.
- What's that? - It holds the nets from floating.
- It weighs them down. - I see. You unload that first.
(The weight holds the nets from floating away.)
Get moving. Put this rock away.
Put it on the bottom.
Keep a lookout for rocks.
- Okay. - Get a grip when you're out here!
(Don't be so clumsy.)
- What do you know? - Hold on a second.
- You don't know anything. - You're just hauling up the net.
- Are you playing a tug of war? - Get a grip when you're out here.
(You should get a grip, Jae Seok.)
(He keeps pulling.)
Hey, grab this rope.
- Be careful. - It's coming. It's coming.
- Be careful. - Is it coming?
- It's coming. - Let's see.
Here comes the net!
- Here it comes. - The fish are coming.
(It's their first catch after they started pulling the net.)
(They can only count it if it's a flatfish, rockfish, or rock cod.)
A conch is coming up.
(This won't count.)
- A conch? - It's a sea urchin. It's a conch!
- Take it out. Take it out. - A conch.
- Take out the conch. - Do I take this out?
- Gosh, this is a conch. - Take it out from the net. Hurry.
- Why don't I see any fish? - Take out the conch.
There's no fish here.
- It's stuck there. - Hold on. I'm pulling it up now.
- Then how should I pull it? - Take out the conch.
- Hold on. How do I get this out? - Conch, conch
(Struggling over a conch)
(It's a shaky start. Will we be okay?)
- Move aside. It's a fish. - Here's a fish!
(A fish-looking creature is pulled up this time.)
- Where is it? - It's a fish.
- It's a rockfish. - What is that?
Isn't this a rockfish?
- It's a scorpionfish. - Pardon?
(This won't count.)
- A scorpionfish. - A scorpionfish.
(It was on the board.)
- Pardon? - I see. A scorpionfish.
- A scorpionfish. - Gosh.
Here it comes. What is this?
- It's a big one. - What is this one?
- It's a fish. - It's a rockfish.
(It's definitely not a scorpionfish. Can this one count?)
What is this one?
- A filefish. - A filefish.
(This species won't count.)
This is driving me crazy.
- Gosh. - A filefish.
- We got scorpionfish and filefish. - Do I let this one go?
(Give it some time.)
What is this one?
It's a filefish again. My goodness.
- Here comes the filefish. - My gosh.
- What's this one? - A scorpionfish.
- A scorpionfish. - A scorpionfish?
- What a shame. - It's making sounds.
- What? What is it? - It's making sounds.
(Is the filefish making sounds?)
- Stop lying. - I'm serious!
- Stop lying. - Stop conning us.
- It's really making sounds. - Seriously.
(Grinding)
(It's really making sounds!)
- This one makes a noise. - It makes a noise.
I told you so. I said it makes noises.
It made a sound.
- Do I just take this out? - A filefish...
- Is it because it's stuck? - It was grinding.
That sound comes from grinding teeth.
- This fish has teeth? - Yes, it does.
- It has teeth? - Otherwise, how can they eat?
- Gosh, but look at its mouth. - Look at this fish.
- Look how big they are. - It does have teeth.
- Its teeth are like piranha's. - They are sharp.
But this one resembles you.
- Me? - Yes.
- What are you talking about? - Don't you look like this?
Kwang Soo, look at this. It's you.
(It resembles the startled look of yours.)
- I don't look like that. - You try it.
You try it.
See? You two look alike. You look like the filefish.
(Trivia: Startled Kwang Soo looks like a filefish.)
- You should try it. - I think it might hurt.
- I can't pull it hard. - I'm scared of that too.
- You'll kill the fish. Hurry up. - Okay.
- You'll earn nothing at this rate. - The filefish...
- has thorns on it. - That's fine.
- Be careful. - Just grab it by the mouth.
Grab it like this, and pull it out.
(This is the skill of a captain with 45 years of experience.)
It has horns on its head.
- This one is almost dead. - It's not dead.
- It's not dead? - It's pretending to be.
He's more energetic than you.
(What are you talking about?)
- Did you seriously just say that? - I'm serious.
- Hey, how could you say that? - Listen.
- The net... Seok Jin. - I'm energetic. Don't you know?
- You were mean to the fish first. - Hey.
Listen. Why did you say the fish was dead when it wasn't?
- But this one is dying. - What do you mean?
- We have to hurry up. - Stop chatting.
How many of these small nets do you have?
About...
10 of 75m nets make up this one.
- 10 nets? - Yes.
It's 750m long.
- My arms are about to fall off. - I know, right?
- Jae Seok, should we switch? - No.
This is hard work.
How do you do this all by yourself?
- This is no joke. - I've been doing it for years.
Pull it. Keep going.
(He stays away as he only cheers them on.)
- Do a good job. - What are you doing?
- What? - What are you doing, Seok Jin?
- What do you mean? Hey. - You're not going to work?
I'm working here. If I join, I'll mess up the set-up.
(To keep the line going, he won't join them.)
Here comes the net!
(He volunteers to be in charge of shouting.)
Here it comes.
It's coming up.
(Thanks to him, the set-up is perfect.)
- Go over there, and work. - I'm working.
- You're unbelievable. - Hey.
What are you doing?
(You want me to work? Fine then.)
There aren't that much fish unlike what I expected.
- The weather might be too good. - Is it because of the good weather?
When the weather is too good, they go away.
How many kilograms does a big flatfish weigh?
- A big one weighs 15kg or 20kg. - 5kg?
There's one that weighs 20kg?
How many fish can you catch when it's in season?
- When it's in season... - Is this for "Hometown Report"?
- We have to catch 72 fish. - Please help us out.
How many times do we haul up the net?
Stop interviewing him.
Get to work. You're here to work.
- Why are you interviewing him? - Why not?
- I was just curious. - Why?
I was wondering for how long we needed to haul it up.
Seok Jin, can you stay in the water for a second?
(Can you just go in there?)
(If I keep this up, people will criticize me.)
You're unbelievable.
(Working hard)
Hey, you know what?
Stop pulling up the net for a second.
Why?
Let them film me pulling it up.
(I'm not working in any of the clips.)
- Did you just hear him? - What did he say?
- He wants them to film him working. - Move.
Go away.
- What's the matter with you? - Come on.
- What's wrong with you? - What do you think you're doing?
They can insert the clip in the middle.
- What are you doing? - You told them that.
I think I'm not working at all.
All right. Here it goes.
(Seok Jin tries to haul up the net.)
(Empty)
There aren't much fish in the net.
We're in trouble. We can't finish...
- the part-time jobs today. - What are we going to do?
I thought we would catch a lot, but I guess not.
- I know, right? - There's no fish.
(As soon as Seok Jin grabs the net, the net is empty.)
- It's coming. Gosh, here it comes. - What is it?
(At that time, something is in the net.)
(This is a chance for Seok Jin to get a clip of working hard.)
(Will it be a flatfish, rockfish, or rock cod?)
- Here they are. We have two fish. - I see.
- It's filefish. - It is?
- They're all filefish. - We have a lot of filefish.
We caught four of them.
We should have picked filefish.
I thought we would catch a lot, but I guess not.
- I know, right? - There's no fish.
(Is it because of his bad luck? There's no more fish.)
- What are we going to do? - We won't be able to finish today.
(They keep hauling the empty net, and time is passing by.)
- It's a scorpionfish? - We got more fish.
- Where? Let me see. A filefish. - Here's one.
We should have picked filefish.
- Filefish is in season. - Seriously.
You caught six filefish now.
- We should have picked filefish. - We should've gotten filefish.
We didn't pick filefish.
- Kwang Soo, why didn't you pick it? - What?
(He picks on Kwang Soo.)
(Are you talking to me?)
Do you want to be pricked with a filefish?
Here.
(Where are all the flatfish, rockfish, and rock cod?)
Be careful.
You should be careful with jellyfish.
- Jellyfish? - Jellyfish?
There are jellyfish.
Pull it.
The captain says we shouldn't touch them.
Kwang Soo, stay away.
(As soon as the captain holds the net...)
Here it comes!
What's that?
(Something is in the net.)
- I've never seen this kind of fish. - What's that?
What's this fish?
- It's a bass. - Unbelievable.
(They catch a huge bass.)
- It looks... - It's incredible.
How much is it worth?
It's worth as much as a flatfish.
I've never seen such a big bass.
(With the captain's help...)
- What's that? - That sea urchin is so big.
(I've never seen a live one.)
It's a sea urchin.
It's moving.
- The spines are moving. - Yes.
(Each spine is moving.)
- There's something in the net. - It's a John Dory.
- What? - It's a John Dory.
- What's the name? - John Dory.
- John Dory? - It looks interesting.
- What's the name again? - It has a pattern.
- It looks like an eye. - John Dory?
President Moon Jae In and Kim Jong Un ate it together.
- They ate it? - What?
It's a shrimp!
We caught a shrimp.
Look at this shrimp.
(Jae Seok finds a large shrimp.)
Where?
They do this on the fishing channel.
(Part-time Fishing Job)
(Let me join you.)
It's a huge shrimp.
Put that in the container.
It's so big.
This fish has the nickname of "golden fish".
- What? - A golden fish.
It's a golden fish.
That looks so interesting.
(The fish is covered in gold scales.)
It's so interesting.
This fish is rare. It's a golden fish.
(Kwang Soo was jealous of Jae Seok.)
(I caught a golden fish.)
(Isn't it cute?)
(Let me put it in my mouth. I'm just joking.)
(Part-time Fishing Job)
(Young fish are released.)
We've only caught rare fish so far.
(We shouldn't be laughing.)
Kwang Soo, come here.
- There's a camera, Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
The captain said they catch a lot of flatfish.
But we haven't caught any. What should we do?
How are we going to catch 72 fish?
You'll catch 70 fish soon.
But we have to catch certain types of fish.
(The type matters more.)
(They haven't caught any of the 3 types of fish that count.)
(They've only caught rare but unimportant fish.)
(They've caught every kind except flatfish, rockfish, and rock cod.)
(They might have to go back without catching any.)
- Can we take a break? - We need to hurry up.
- Hurry up. - Please stop for a moment.
(Where are all the flatfish, rockfish, and rock cod?)
(Let's keep going!)
That's a flatfish.
- It's a flatfish! - It's a flatfish!
(Finally,)
(they catch a flatfish.)
(They finally catch a fish that counts.)
(Flopping)
Look at that.
We caught it.
Unbelievable.
- It's so big. - It's incredible.
It's huge.
Is it usually this big?
It's so big!
(Is a flatfish usually this big?)
- It's so big! - Look at its mouth.
(Flopping)
(They're making a fuss.)
Take it out,
- and put it in the tank. - It's so big. What should we do?
- Tear the nest a little. - Tear it?
- Tear it? - But not too much.
- Don't tear it too much. - Look at the teeth.
Its mouth is so big.
(It has a big mouth.)
It has teeth.
- This is... - It's...
(They're about to faint.)
(When the fish flops,)
(they become terrified.)
Hold on.
Don't be more startled than the fish is.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
Hurry up and...
(What is it doing?)
(Startled)
Gosh, it's so strong.
Don't be so startled.
Put it in the tank.
- Put it in. - Put it in.
Please move your foot.
(Panicking)
Kwon Ryeol, move!
Move! Pull yourself together!
(Kwon Ryeol, stay on alert while you're at the sea.)
Put it in here.
(I was just trying to film you.)
It's a filefish.
- Put it in. - Here.
We've caught only one flatfish?
(They've finally caught a flatfish.)
I feel so happy.
We caught a flatfish.
The flatfish is so big.
It's incredible.
We're almost done.
We're done.
- We're done. - We're done!
(The first net is in.)
- Let me finish up. - Okay.
Gosh, it's not easy.
Gosh.
How many fish did we catch that count?
One.
(Just one? We worked so hard.)
- Just 1? - Just 1?
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
Let's check the second net.
- The second net? - Yes.
How are we going to catch 72 fish?
(They move to the next spot, hoping they'll catch more fish.)
- Come on in. - It smells so good here.
He even lit scented candles.
Will you play escape room first?
- Sure. - Good.
- Then... - The time...
Are you going to make a game just for me?
Or are we playing it together?
We should make one for Haha.
Haha wanted to play it, so we should make it for him.
But if you fail to escape, you'll be penalized.
Then let me stay here for a while.
(He's not interested in escaping.)
No.
I think we should do this.
Haha will compete with a member in each room.
Since there are many rooms?
He can escape when he's done.
But don't make me arm-wrestle with Jong Kook...
- or something. - We should be realistic.
You're supposed to use your brain.
But it'd be boring if you just used your brain.
You should use your body too.
- That'd be more fun. - He's right.
Why would people watch this show instead of a quiz show?
- Right? - I'm not talking about a quiz show.
- It should be more dynamic. - He's right.
But you don't use your body in the escape room.
- They don't do that. - You can do it.
We'll have different kinds of games.
If I fail to escape,
what's the penalty?
We'll slap you on the forehead.
Or a water slap.
- Water slap. - What do you think?
So I'll be hit either way.
(There is no difference.)
(What's the big deal? I'll be hit anyway.)
- No. - The fun part is...
- when you escape. - Yes.
It's already decided.
- It can't be an impossible game. - Right.
Also, in the escape room,
you're given up to three hints.
- There are hints? - You can call the staff.
- All right. - Je Sung is calling me.
Really? Okay.
- Ask him for pork belly meat. - Where are you?
- I'm at Sogang University. - Hello.
- What? - I'm at Sogang University.
- You're nearby. What are you doing? - Let me talk to him.
I just finished shooting.
He's finished.
- Je Sung, are you done? - What?
- Are you done? - Hello?
- Je Sung. - Yes, I'm done.
Don't you recognize my voice?
- Hi. - What?
It's our Protein Man.
(He sure is a member of Jong Kook's fan club.)
- Protein Man? - Yes.
You're my number one fan.
- Je Sung. - Yes?
- Are you free? - What's the matter?
I only have "Comedy Big League".
Really? That's great.
Je Sung, you won.
What do you mean?
You're 2019's Rising Comedy Star.
It's not 2019 yet.
Yes. You're expected to be one.
(He is expected to be 2019's Rising Comedy Star.)
Can you appear on our show?
Of course, I can.
(He immediately agrees.)
Congratulations!
(2019's Rising Comedy Star will appear on the show.)
But to come here, you have to pay a fee.
What?
You can't come here empty-handed.
You can just get some pork belly meat on the way.
You just needed someone to bring meat, didn't you?
(He's quick.)
Je Sung. I'm not like that. What's with you?
- Are you sure? Should I be happy? - I just missed you.
Of course.
- I'll gladly do it. - All right.
Our viewers have never seen you...
on our show.
Then I'll prepare a few funny outfits.
(He sure is the rising star.)
Good. That's great.
Then we'll be looking forward.
- Okay. - Okay. Hold on.
- Please wait a moment. - Okay. Hold on.
- Hurry up. - Okay.
Je Sung is amazing.
- He's bringing pork belly meat. - I love him.
- I know. - He's amazing.
He's incredible.
I think our tteokbokki is here.
- Do you hear it? - It's here.
- Okay. Tteokbokki. - It's here.
- Do you want to eat first? - Thank you.
You have 90 cents left now.
We have some money left?
We have 90 cents left.
- I'm so hungry. - Right?
I'm suddenly so hungry.
Sundae.
It looks so tasty.
It's still hot.
(After the cold sauna...)
It tastes so good.
We're eating so well.
- We were hungry. - We were hungry.
- We rode bikes and took a sauna. - Right.
Many people spend their holidays at hotels these days.
Right.
You seem to know a lot about new trends.
- I do. - He knows a lot.
He knows a lot.
We should have ordered more.
We had only 17 dollars.
Can't we order something for 90 cents?
(The 5 of them are sharing 2 portions.)
- 90 cents... - I'm not full yet.
(I want more food.)
Se Chan, do you have instant rice?
- What? - I want some rice.
- Are you serious? - Warm up some rice.
- But we have to eat the meat too. - We can.
Will you be okay?
I eat three times more than ordinary people.
- You'll be surprised. - Do you want some tuna too?
Sure.
Cook some noodles too while you're at it.
(While you're at it...)
- That sounds good. - I want some.
- Me too. - Me too.
We have to eat the meat too.
We can.
We're on vacation.
Stop what you're doing. Do you see the rice bowl?
- Rice bowl? - Get some gochujang.
Shall we make bibimbap?
- That sounds delicious. - Bibimbap and noodles.
- I want bibimbap. - Okay.
Make it with tuna. Is it a small or large can?
- It's a small one. - Is there brown rice?
- Brown rice? - Instant brown rice.
Is there any brown rice?
Cook two servings of instant rice.
Are there any side dishes?
Microwave some rice.
- Chef. - Yes?
Do you have dried yellow corvina?
(Haha is the worst.)
- What? - Dried yellow corvina.
I've never had it.
(Se Chan might explode if they ask for more.)
I'll help you. Shall I mix the rice?
I got it. Just sit and wait.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Did you steal this?
(There's a sticker with a Running Man logo.)
Wait a minute, wait.
Why is there a sticker?
(A penny saved is a penny earned.)
Did the staff put it on?
How could you?
They made me a thief. That's nonsense.
No way. It's not attached to this side.
You wait.
What if everything in the fridge has R stickers?
(We'll watch him carefully from now on.)
That's impossible.
(While they make bibimbap and noodles...)
I'll make some noodles.
(Jong Kook and So Min clean up.)
With kimchi, it's really tasty.
(She wipes the floor.)
Honey.
We raised our children well.
(Father Jong Kook believes in not wasting anything.)
(A play called "Jong Kook, Don't Cry")
(So Min's role model is Shin Saimdang.)
My husband will scold me, so I'll use what was used.
Wipe my mouth as well.
That's not what I meant.
Don't do that. Your health is important.
You might get sick. Medicine and hospital fees will cost more.
Don't get sick. It's a mission.
(Don't get sick. It's a mission.)
(If you fail the mission,)
(you'll be imprisoned in my heart.)
(Her heart flutters.)
- A mission? - I'll scold you if you get sick.
(He gives his all for his love.)
You'll be scolded if you get sick.
(Back in the day when they saved everything)
That's right.
(It's a play that shows our fathers' love.)
Did they become a married couple?
(What's going on?)
- We need to make one more rice. - Okay.
How many did you make? Make about three more.
Aren't you going to eat pork belly meat?
I can eat them all.
Goodness, I don't like taking just one bite.
- How many rice did you make? - I made two.
No, that won't be enough for everyone.
(No one knew how much he ate or about his special recipe.)
(He's tired of chicken breast.)
(Let your precious stomach be free.)
- How many rice is it? - It's two.
- Is that 2? Make 1 more. - Yes.
- What? - How will we eat them all?
I used to make this a lot.
One is regular tuna, and the other is chili tuna.
(Did you eat like this regularly?)
(A lot of sesame oil)
Goodness.
- It looks delicious. - It looks very good.
It'd be good without gochujang.
- This is great. - Okay.
This looks good.
(Shall I eat now?)
Let me have one bite, Jong Kook.
- No. - Just one bite. You have a lot.
You're a pig if you eat all of it.
Bring another spoon, So Min.
- Honey. - Bring a spoon.
(Honey)
- One bite, please. - Bring a spoon.
Dad.
- My baby. - Here you go.
(Honey, have only one bite.)
- Isn't it okay? - It's delicious.
- Did you add gochujang? - No.
I should make this at home. It's delicious.
We ate 17 dollars' worth of tteokbokki...
and 40 dollars' worth of food here.
(We eat well at Se Chan's house.)
Eat. It's okay.
I feel like we're on a real vacation.
Let's go.
Let's eat. It'll get soggy.
- It's ready. - Jong Kook.
You're our eldest son.
- I'm your eldest son? - My son.
(Haha thinks that his father is just an older brother.)
- Our second eldest son. - Mother.
(Se Chan is a troublemaker who returned home last year.)
Our youngest daughter.
(She doesn't look the youngest at all.)
Dad, why do we always steal from empty houses?
("Please Go Home")
- Let's make it our home. - How much is it?
(It's a movie about a family that breaks into other people's houses.)
Isn't it new every day?
People at my school ask me what your occupation is.
Tell them I'm in real estate.
(He attempts to protect his son's pride.)
Our second eldest is bullied around. What should we do?
That's right, Dad. Kids keep hitting me.
If you get hit by others, I'll hit you twice as hard at home.
(Blood-curdling)
You'll hit your son twice as hard?
(He attempts to make his son stronger.)
(The movie ends to protect the second eldest son.)
I thought it was a lot, but it's not now that I've finished it.
- He finished it. - Goodness.
(Clean)
I'm so happy. It really feels like a vacation.
- Now... - Shall we start?
- Escape room? - No.
- Bring some fruit. - Do you have any fruit?
- Do you have any fruit? - That's enough.
(That's enough.)
(The owner of the house explodes.)
(I'm sorry, Se Chan.)
- Let's start the game. - Okay, I'm sorry.
(It's been an hour.)
- I have fruit. - It's too scary.
(They finally start the game.)
Haha, please leave for a while.
- We'll discuss. - I'll stay here.
Let us discuss.
Okay, I'll go inside.
- What? - They're here.
How could he...
- He's here. - be so accurate?
It's unbelievable.
- I never saw him in person. - I know.
(Sirens)
- Goodness. - The police are here.
Are they the police?
- Right. - Seriously?
We guessed everything right.
Je Sung.
(He wears an armor of a comedian.)
(The rising star of 2019 appears.)
Je Sung.
(What's going on?)
(His appearance makes them burst out in laughter.)
What's going on?
(He makes everyone roll on the floor.)
(His armor as a comedian)
(It can't be pierced with anything.)
(Invincible armor)
- Look at him. - Look at his makeup.
He colored his tooth.
- Your tooth is colored. - This is nothing.
- Where did you get the wig? - That's hilarious.
- Was it in the car? - Of course.
(He always carries his comedian armor with him.)
I have a few props in the car.
That's impressive.
- Okay. - I didn't expect it.
- There are so many people. - He looks funnier standing still.
- Come here. - This is embarrassing.
- Je Sung. - Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
- I'm your huge fan. - He's a rising comedian.
Look at the details of his outfit. He has a napkin in here.
It's a napkin. It looks like a handkerchief.
- It does. - I never met the two of you.
- Right. - I had to dress properly.
- I can't change my face so... - You did a good job.
Okay.
2019 Rising Comedian, Hwang Je Sung.
(2019 Rising Comedian, Hwang Je Sung)
(2019 Rising Comedian descends to Running Man.)
(She's so happy.)
- What are these? - You brought a lot.
- It's meat. - Je Sung.
- It's meat. - I didn't expect that.
- We didn't expect this much. - He's so passionate.
- I live nearby. - They said it in passing.
He's amazing.
I came without knowing what we're doing.
- It's about timing. - This is real.
Okay.
(How far will he go?)
Kwang Soo, we'd be in trouble without you here.
(Exhausted)
(2 part-timers are already tired.)
Seriously.
We're almost there.
(They're at the second net.)
Did we come that fast?
- My legs hurt. - I'm getting seasick.
Okay, let's get up. Stay strong.
What should we do? We need to pull it up.
- Pull it up. - Yes, sir.
We need to catch something.
(This is not a replay.)
(He's getting used to it. It might turn into a full-time job.)
It's an extreme job.
Who does three part-time jobs in a day?
How many are we doing?
I knew someone who worked 2 jobs, but 3?
- It's coming. - It's coming.
It's coming. It's a flatfish.
(They only caught 1 flatfish so far.)
- We need to catch something. - It's a flatfish.
What's this?
- It's mackerel. - It's a baby mackerel.
(It doesn't count.)
(Cute)
Look at the baby mackerel.
(Why is it mackerel of all fish?)
It's a mackerel.
When we catch a mackerel,
we catch a big fish later.
What did you say?
After a mackerel, we catch a big flatfish.
Do flatfish come to eat mackerel?
(It's likely that there are many around.)
After a mackerel, we catch a big flatfish?
(It'd be nice to catch some flatfish.)
- It's coming. - It's coming.
(The next fish is coming up.)
It's coming.
(Is what the captain said about flatfish correct?)
- It's a flatfish! - It's coming.
(They catch a large flatfish.)
It's a flatfish!
- It's huge. - It's big.
Look at this.
Its mouth is large.
It's alive, everyone! It's a living flatfish!
- It's not a toy. - It's real.
It's flapping and natural.
It's natural.
It's a wild flatfish.
It's bigger than the other one.
- How much does it weigh? - 2.5kg.
2.5kg?
(Let me hold it.)
This is amazing.
Seok Jin wants to be on the camera.
(Seok Jin wants to be on the camera by holding the fish.)
What? What's wrong?
- Seok Jin. - I hate it when he becomes greedy.
Look at its mouth.
(He's exaggerating for the scene.)
It's upside down. Flip it.
(The fish is upside down.)
(Like this?)
- It's incredible. - I've never seen a fish like this.
It's alive.
(He is still being greedy.)
Go in there.
(They've caught 2 flatfish.)
It's huge.
Seok Jin is so funny.
Out of 72 fish, we've caught 2.
But that fish must weigh a lot.
It should count as more than one.
Please count 1 per 1kg.
You should.
We can't possibly catch 72 fish.
(Another mackerel shows up.)
We're not catching any. All we're catching is mackerel.
But if there's a mackerel,
it means we'll catch another flatfish.
(That's what the captain said.)
(Will they catch another flatfish like Jae Seok says?)
(Come up here, flatfish.)
Here it comes! A flatfish!
(Jae Seok was right.)
- Again? - Here it comes!
(Another flatfish)
(I knew it.)
It's so strong.
(It's full of energy.)
It's a flatfish!
Gosh, that hurts. It bit me.
(He was holding the net,)
(and the fish bit his hand.)
Gosh, that hurts. It bit me.
- Really? - It bit me.
- It did? - Yes.
Gosh, it's so powerful.
- How much would it weigh? - Flatfish can bite you?
Guys, are you having fun?
- Yes! - You are?
- You are? - Kind of.
As you're having so much fun,
we'll count each kilo of flatfish as one fish.
- Okay! - Now, you're talking.
It shouldn't count as just one.
This would weigh about 3kg. It should count as 3 fish.
- We'll weigh them later. - Okay.
It's incredible.
(We might have a chance.)
Look at that. Hold on.
Something just occurred to me.
Kwang Soo, you didn't even have to be penalized.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- I'm sorry. - Don't worry.
I mean...
Now that I think of it,
I shouldn't have challenged Jae Seok.
(That's where it all began.)
(To avoid the penalty roulette, he challenged Jae Seok.)
(Because of that, he had to travel 400km.)
Let me say one thing.
Who put his shoe in the flatfish slot?
It's you, right?
- It's you, right? - Why is that important?
What's important is to catch it.
Why do we have to...
catch flatfish?
Because the flatfish went into the shoe.
(Because the flatfish went into the shoe.)
What?
He's not interested in what you're saying.
He cares about only one thing.
(He is interested in only one thing.)
(Shooting his scenes)
It might get away.
(I'm not done yet.)
- Put it in now. - Put it in.
- Put it in now. - Seok Jin.
Why are you even laughing? Why are you laughing?
(The second flatfish goes into the tank.)
(More flatfish show up.)
This must be a flatfish spot.
It's so big.
- It's incredible. - And it's a wild fish.
(They seem to be catching all the flatfish in Busan.)
There are so many flatfish.
(They've caught 9 flatfish.)
- We're done. - We're done.
(No rockfish or rock cod showed up in the second net either.)
Should I stop it?
Good work.
Thank you.
(They're done with the fishing job.)
Good work, guys.
(They caught 9 flatfish.)
(Despite all the hard work, they caught only 9 fish.)
We didn't catch that many.
We won't be able to finish at this rate.
We still have a lot to do.
(Jae Seok gets up...)
(and walks to the front part of the boat.)
(He drinks water...)
(and sits in the corner carefully.)
Let me see.
(He picks up his bag.)
It never seems to end.
We've been working all day.
(There is a pouch in the bag?)
Here are your mission bags.
- There's a pouch in it. - This is yours.
- There is a pouch inside. - There's a pouch.
You're allowed to open it just once when you think...
- you can't continue working. - just once?
And once it's opened, you can't go back.
(Jae Seok decides to open his pouch...)
(and finds a piece of paper in it.)
(No one is watching, right?)
(The paper is...)
(a ticket to Seoul.)
(Bring Seok Jin's sock, and you can go home.)
(He can go home as soon as he brings Seok Jin's sock.)
(The mission is on.)
(It won't be easy. Will Jae Seok be able to go home?)
Did you drink water?
No. Give me some.
(Seok Jin has no idea.)
(He comes back without being suspected.)
Thank you.
(Now,)
(he has only one target.)
(Seok Jin's sock)
(It's not going to be easy.)
(Seok Jin goes to the bathroom.)
(Hold on. Let me think.)
(It's only Kwang Soo and me.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(Whispering)
You want to go home, right?
(Do you even have to ask?)
Listen carefully.
Seok Jin and I got a pouch each this morning.
- A pouch? - Yes.
The staff told me I could open it when I couldn't take this anymore.
I wanted to finish the job, but it just seems impossible.
It's impossible. We won't be able to go back today.
- Listen. - Okay.
If I bring Seok Jin's sock,
I'm done.
(If I bring Seok Jin's sock, I'm done.)
(Intrigued)
You're interested, right? You want to go home or not?
Please slap me on the forehead.
(Help me.)
Okay.
Just keep that in mind.
(If Kwang Soo helps Jae Seok,)
(Jae Seok will slap him on the forehead so he can go home.)
(They're back at the dock.)
Thank you, Captain.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Good work.
- Good work. - Good work.
- Thank you. - You were the best.
(How much do the flatfish weigh?)
Gosh, I'm covered in sweat.
(Each kilo will count as 1 fish.)
- We'll count each kilo as one fish. - Okay.
(The weight will be deducted from 72.)
(They all worked hard. Will it pay off?)
- What's the weight? - 23kg.
The total weight of the 9 fish is 23kg.
(The target number boils down to 49.)
We'll deduct 23.
That's less than I expected.
It's 49 now.
(They have to do another part-time job.)
(The number is 49 now.)
- Gukje Market... - Are we going to Gukje Market?
- This may not be our last job. - I'm exhausted.
What's the number now?
49.
- 49? - Yes.
- We're only halfway. - Will it really end?
I woke up...
at 4:20am this morning.
When we get home... Can we even go home?
Gosh. What should we do?
We're working too much.
(Exhausted)
How many part-time jobs are we doing today?
What did I do wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
On the boat...
I took all the flatfish out of the net.
The captain did most of the work.
You just held up the fish in front of the cameras.
The viewers don't know.
(The viewers found out today.)
(I worked hard.)
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
(Jae Seok is nervous.)
(Will Kwang Soo and Jae Seok be able to go home early?)
Let's play 1-on-1 games.
First of all...
- I'll be in the room. - Wait in the room.
We're going to play escape room.
I'll do a quiz.
Se Chan and Haha were bragging...
about their knowledge.
- I'll do a puzzle. - What do you mean?
What do you mean?
I'll make a drawing and rip it up.
He has to put the pieces back together in time.
What about this? You call Byul,
and she has to say certain words.
(Byul has to say certain words on the phone.)
Je Sung, you should do one too.
Should I try "Tazzang"?
It's so funny.
- Should I put on funny makeup? - Sounds good.
I'll have my back turned.
When I turn around, Haha shouldn't laugh.
But you can take it easy.
Haha will fail in the last stage anyway.
(I'll use my strength.)
You'll be there.
I'll make him remove my name tag.
(It'll be a name tag elimination.)
(Living Room: Quiz)
(Room 1: Puzzle, Room 2: Tazzang)
(Room 3: Phone, Room 4: Name tag)
Escape room.
Haha's escape room.
I've always wanted to try it.
- The first is Se Chan's room. - My room? Okay.
(Se Chan's Common Sense Quiz Room)
(It's a battle of the century.)
(Discussing Running Man's brain)
(You and your brother can team up.)
(You still can't beat me.)
(It's a super match with the family honor on the line.)
You give a question, and you answer.
And vice versa.
Here you go.
Who will be more of a fool?
Here's what I will do.
I wanted to use this.
I didn't know when.
I'll find a question in here.
Yes, here's my question.
They're very meticulous. They're the brothers of Yang family.
"What to buy today".
"Paper cups and chicken towel".
Wait.
(What's the question?)
No way.
"Chicken towel".
(You still don't know?)
Wait.
(Yang brothers' necessary item in the kitchen)
("Chicken towel")
What should we do with them? What should we do?
(Something seems to be off.)
- Hold on. - So what's the problem here?
What's the problem here?
There's a word that's incorrect.
- Answer in five seconds. - What's the incorrect word?
- 5, 4, 3. - Oh, no.
- Two. - Do you really not know?
- My goodness. - Does it include all?
Why is it wrong? Who wrote it? Did you write it?
- No. - Yang Se...
- I didn't write it either. - It must be your brother.
Will you blame your brother?
Or will you take the blame?
From the Yang family,
one of the brothers is ignorant.
Will you shame your brother?
Leave my family alone!
Or will he shame himself?
My goodness.
- I had no idea. - My goodness.
This is very extreme.
Wait, I can't shame my brother.
Do you know the correct word?
- Of course. - Do you?
What is it?
It's kitchen towel.
So write down that word.
(Write down the word.)
Kitchen towel? He must know.
- Haha. - This is nothing.
We learned it in middle school or in elementary school.
- You know it, right? - Yes.
You need to write the correct answer.
Yes, that's right.
He's right.
What's this?
- You should know it yourself. - What's wrong with you?
You need to write the correct answer first.
- All right. - Let's do it at the same time.
Write it at the same time.
- Gosh. - That's how it is.
This is driving me crazy.
This is so funny.
- It's so funny. - Ji Hyo is laughing.
Give her a piece of paper too.
- I know it. - Ji Hyo.
- Can you write it? - I cook.
- You know kitchen towel. - Of course.
I know how to write it.
They might see it.
They might see it. Lean back. That's right.
- You mean in English? - In English.
(She's surprised.)
(She gets up.)
"In English"?
Wait.
- In English? - Yes.
I didn't know I had to.
It could be confusing.
That's enough, Ji Hyo!
(He takes it away from her.)
(Friendly Jong Kook stops her.)
- Don't do it. - Is it wrong?
Don't do it. Don't do it, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo was cute. "You mean in English?"
Gosh, I didn't know.
(All is new to him.)
Gosh, this one is quite serious.
- Let me see. - I'm so bad at English.
(As it's a super match, the competition is fierce.)
I don't know.
Let's take a look.
We'll take a look at the same time.
1, 2...
(What will be the result of the first round?)
(The correct answer is "kitchen towel".)
- It's wrong. - Is it wrong?
Come on.
(He had no idea that they were this bad.)
- "Kitchen"? - Come on.
- What should we do with you? - Isn't this correct?
Yes.
Did I get "towel" wrong?
Is it with an A?
Don't you know "towel"?
I call it "towol".
"Give me some kitchen towols."
"Towol"?
Both of you were wrong. What's the second question?
No one scored. Both got the first question wrong.
- At least, I kept my pride. - It's neck and neck.
- What's the second one? - Were you surprised?
- I was. - We aren't on the same level.
- I don't know yet. - Let's shake hands.
(Let's shake hands.)
- Learn English from me. - I will learn from you.
You can teach me something else.
Haha is better at English.
Here's the question.
This is common sense that I know.
- Be careful what you ask. - Be careful.
This is something that's easy for those who know.
Those who don't know won't have a clue.
- That's how it is. - Be careful what you ask.
It's a treatment effect based on trust.
What effect is it?
- Does that exist? - A treatment based on trust?
Those who don't know don't know.
To me, it's common sense.
I know what it is. I'll write it down.
- A treatment based on trust? - Yes.
(What is a treatment effect based on trust?)
(I definitely know what it is.)
You'll recognize it when you see it.
It's at the level of middle school students.
I don't think he knows.
It will hurt his pride.
It's 1 of the 2.
(Stuttering)
(I won this round.)
Okay, I got one question.
Write down the question.
How many words?
I'll write 3 or 4.
3 or 4?
It could be that.
I want to keep my pride.
He might lose against me.
- Try to keep your pride. - Okay.
He's filled with a brave spirit.
(Brave and confident)
For example, Jong Kook caught a cold.
- He caught a cold. - You're giving him too much.
- I know. - Should I stop?
It's over once you give him a hint.
Is it convincing yourself that you didn't catch a cold?
(Something lights up in him.)
(Did Haha sense something from the hint?)
Did I tell him too much?
I've heard of it.
You should know this.
- What? - You aren't an easy opponent.
(Haha finally approves of him.)
Do you mean me? Haha.
- You could win. - I knew it.
I approve of you too.
I don't care to know more.
Okay, you aren't easy either.
I'm starting to sweat.
- This game is so fun. - Right.
(He writes without hesitating.)
- I think... - The game is fun.
when I joined Running Man...
(Here. This is my answer.)
- He threw it. - He threw it down.
All right.
(What is a treatment effect based on trust?)
Did he get it right?
He got it right?
(Haha's answer is placebo effect, and it's correct.)
(What do you think?)
I shouldn't have mentioned the cold.
- That was too obvious. - I know.
I was going to write "flash mob".
(Flash mob for the cold)
It wasn't easy.
You choose. Will it be about economy?
(Laughing)
Is this funny?
(Are we that funny?)
How about current issues?
(He agrees on the race.)
I'm confident with current issues.
What do you think?
Were you going to ask about bus fares?
(It sounds like some difficult quiz.)
I want to defeat you with a difficult question.
Will you give me some time?
I hope it will be as amazing as the time you took.
(Is that an encouragement or an attack?)
(Someone from the audience wishes for that.)
This is my first time here.
It's his first time.
- Aren't you nervous? - Yes.
- By the way, - I know a few things.
what brings you here?
I came to sight-see.
- Did you? - Yes.
They're good.
(They're good.)
(His Korean skill is that of a Korean who lives abroad.)
- "They're good"? - They're good.
They're fun.
- You speak Korean well. - Yes.
My grandmother is Korean.
- Where are you from? - Your grandmother?
I'm from Philadelphia.
My grandmother is Korean.
(Philadelphia?)
I don't know the exact spelling of "Philadelphia".
That's a bit too much.
- Right. - One English question is enough.
- Don't give an English question. - Okay.
Okay, it's common sense.
(Let's go with common sense.)
- It's about capital cities. - "Capital cities"?
(Haha is experienced in this category.)
He won't know.
The capital city of India.
(What's the capital city of India?)
(It's a difficult question.)
- The capital city of India. - I don't have to write in English.
Right.
(Try to guess the answer with them.)
I didn't know the capital city of India.
(If this is wrong, I'm in trouble.)
If... If this is wrong, I'm doomed.
- One. - Put it closer.
1, 2, 3.
(New Delhi and Delhi)
That was close.
- It was close. - That was close.
(He only has one question left before he can escape.)
It has nothing to do with Deli Manju, right?
(It has nothing to do with Deli Manju, right?)
I'm not sure. It could be related.
Deli Manju.
Did you really not know?
- I didn't know. - Did you really not know?
Should she know?
He wrote "Delhi".
Connecting "Delhi" and Deli Manju...
Be quiet.
(He's already sensitive as is.)
How about this?
What are you confident about?
I don't know. I have no confidence anymore.
(He gives up on making questions.)
We started off wrong.
Everything went wrong since "chicken towel".
- Are you going insane? - I think I'll lose.
I'll lose.
- Okay. - How about this?
- Se Chan. - Ask him an easy one.
- I'll give you a memory question. - That sounds good.
I prefer memory to common sense.
Write "kitchen towel".
(Write it again.)
(Stop mentioning "kitchen" again.)
- Stop it. - Why?
- Stop it? - Why? It's a memory quiz.
It really is.
- Good job. - Right? That works.
- Stop it. - You're smart.
- That's hilarious. - I think you're a genius.
I can't remember it again.
- You saw it before. - We showed you earlier.
(Write "kitchen towel" in English again.)
(Se Chan is flustered. Haha will win.)
This is driving him nuts.
Okay. "Kitchen towel".
"Klcin".
(It's obviously wrong.)
Se Chan, you almost had it.
From here, just memorize T and H.
(I'll teach you.)
That's not right.
Teach me properly. What are you saying?
(Teach me properly. What are you saying?)
(Se Chan explodes.)
What? Where does the T go and where...
does the H go? Tell me!
This is "kitchen". Okay?
That's right.
(Good work, brother.)
- That was a great match. - I'm okay.
Things got heated up.
- That was so competitive. - Right.
- I have no regrets. - Hey,
you should do this quarterly. Do it again next month.
I can study. Are we going to do English again?
No, I have many more areas.
We can do history.
(Haha solves the trivia questions, and he succeeds.)
Can we finally do it?
When does the part-time job...
(Busan's BIFF Square has many treats and things to see.)
(What kind of a part-time job will they have in the crowded area?)
All right, everybody. You have already completed...
3 out of 5 part-time jobs we had prepared.
There's 49 left.
Busan, the city of culture and arts, is where many people visit daily.
In Busan Gukje Market, you will be...
3 out of 5 part-time jobs we had prepared.
There's 49 left.
Busan, the city of culture and arts, is where many people visit daily.
In Busan Gukje Market, you will be...
drawing caricature portraits of people.
(Caricature Portraits)
(It's a drawing where certain characteristics are exaggerated.)
(People in Busan will be forced to take them.)
Your pay will be based on how many portraits you draw.
However, if they say it doesn't look like them...
or if they get angry, it doesn't count.
They are the two people I know who are the worst at drawing.
(They can't do this job.)
They're worse than infants.
- Listen. - Kwang Soo can draw.
- This doesn't make any sense. - Goodness.
If we draw 1 portrait, is that counted as 1?
- Yes. - It'll take forever to draw 49.
We can't make 49 portraits.
(This won't work out.)
If so,
you can find any part-time jobs you desire.
(You can find any part-time jobs you desire.)
- There's nothing we can do. - What can we do?
I'm speechless.
What are we supposed to do here?
- He's not letting us go home. - He's not.
- We're in Busan... - You already made up your mind.
Am I supposed to complain as well?
(Hold on a second.)
Am I supposed to talk about my misfortunes as well?
I thought about it. Why would I draw?
Why would I draw portraits?
You're the best at drawing out of us three.
But...
There's no other way. We can't find any part-time jobs.
We can't find anything.
- Let's just draw portraits then. - But I can't draw.
- Me neither. - Do we sit here and draw?
Will people let us draw portraits of them?
Seok Jin,
we'll start drawing here,
so you can go around and draw.
Okay, but it'll be weird...
to walk around all of a sudden.
(Loitering)
- Hey, hey. - Kwang Soo is handsome.
I told you.
(Whispering)
Let's steal his sock.
- We can't end this otherwise. - When?
If we steal his sock and leave,
- does he have to do the rest? - Yes.
(That's very nice.)
This is not your punishment.
I just need you...
- to slap my forehead. - Right. You just come with me.
We can't draw 49 portraits.
- It doesn't make sense. - It doesn't.
It doesn't.
(They make another plan since they think this is hopeless.)
- Excuse me. - You scared me.
Are you looking for a part-timer?
I want to do a different job. I can't draw.
We're not, but the pancake place is.
The pancakes? Do you want me to sell them for you?
Sure. Go ahead.
Would you like me to sell them for you?
- Yes. - Each one I sell counts as one.
For each one I sell, right?
Look at these pancakes. How much are they?
- 1.30 dollars. - 1.30 dollars?
- Can we have a sale for a dollar? - Sure.
Is that okay? All right.
All right! Pancakes that are usually 1.30 dollars...
are being sold for a dollar each.
Come here. They're a dollar each.
(Busan's specialty pancakes are on a flash sales.)
Come here.
It's on sale for a dollar each. It's a special sale.
These pancakes are really good.
Let's take a picture.
(You get to take a picture with the part-timer.)
Okay. Enjoy.
- I always watch you on TV. - Thank you. It's a dollar each.
Please get a pancake.
- Here. - I'd like two.
2? She'd like 2.
- Would you like it in a bag? - Yes.
Would you like it in a bag? Sure.
(He'll finish up in no time.)
- It looks great. - Thank you.
Pancakes.
(However...)
They're a dollar each. Have one.
Pancakes. Have some.
Come here. Take one.
Here you go. Thank you.
- Here you go. - It's a dollar each.
Pancakes are on a limited-time sale for a dollar each.
They're usually 1.30 dollars, but they're a dollar.
Pancakes.
Pancakes are on sale for a dollar each.
You can take a picture with me as well. Here you go.
They're a dollar each.
This is so tiring.
How many did I sell?
I'm going to practice first.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok are practicing.)
Let me draw Kwon Ryeol.
I need to practice.
(He doesn't hesitate.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Then...
(He doesn't hesitate.)
What are you doing?
- This is Kwon Ryeol. - What are you doing?
It's him.
(Kwon Ryeol, Jae Seok's cameraman)
It's kind of similar.
- It's similar, right? - Yes.
- Kwon Ryeol. - I can tell that it's him.
I drew a portrait of you before officially starting.
(I drew a portrait of you before officially starting.)
(Laughing)
- What do you think? - Fail.
If we ask the others, they're going to say it's you.
Then I'll approve.
Will this approve as one?
I will.
He's handsome.
I drew a portrait...
of somebody here. Who do you think this is?
(Let's see.)
(She points at him.)
(You, Kwon Ryeol.)
See? Did you see that?
- Did you see that? - Jae Seok.
He drew better than I thought, so I was surprised.
- I... - It's bad, but it's Kwon Ryeol.
It looks like a bad drawing of Kwon Ryeol.
It's you, though.
- It has to be him. - These are your pants too.
- I'll approve this as one. - Okay.
Recruit a random person and draw a portrait of them.
- They might get mad at us. - We don't have any skills.
We are drawing caricatures.
Can somebody be my model? I just need one person.
I need one person with unique features.
- Me. - Can I have you come up?
Just one person. Okay.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Would you like to try? Please come here.
I'm not a great artist.
- Please keep that in mind. - Okay.
I'm asking you for a favor.
(They start drawing.)
Please have a seat.
I'm not a great artist, so please be understanding.
(He apologizes in advance.)
I've never done this before.
Have you done this before?
- No. - No, right?
I'll try my best.
I'm paying attention...
(He's all talk.)
I'm focusing on the shape of your face.
This is a piece of art.
(It looks okay so far.)
Can you make my face narrow?
Do you want it narrow?
(I trust you, Artist Yu.)
What is your name?
Park Sun Ha.
- Sorry? - It's Park Sun Ha.
- Sun Ha? - Yes.
You're supposed to exaggerate when drawing caricatures.
Right?
If I was good at this,
I'd be drawing exactly the way you look,
but my skills...
(What kind of exaggerations is he talking about?)
(While they're busy drawing...)
Hey.
- Did you draw any? - Hey.
I got 10.
- What? 10 what? - I got 10.
I sold... 10...
- I sold 10 pancakes. - Really?
Did you sell pancakes?
You're good.
(It wasn't easy to sell pancakes, so he joins them.)
I'm going to draw too.
Who thinks they're easy to draw?
- Me. - Me.
(He picks somebody who's easy to draw.)
We already have two ladies, so come over here.
(He recruits a person.)
Hey.
It'll take forever to finish.
Goodness.
(Draw if you have time to talk.)
This is not hard. You have a single eyelid.
You have one double eyelid.
(He doesn't hesitate.)
Okay. I'm done.
(Okay. I'm done.)
Hurry.
What are you doing?
- I'm done. - What are you doing?
I'm done.
What are you doing?
(Ta-da)
Please say this looks like you.
- Doesn't this look like you? - Does it?
- Doesn't it? - You think so?
It looks like you.
I'll sign it.
What's that?
(I can't believe him.)
- So Hee. - Yes?
I'm finished, but don't be startled.
- Well... - Is she a grandma?
(Is this a portrait of a grandma?)
You drew a grandma.
(Calm down.)
- So Hee. - Yes?
- Look at it with your heart. - Okay.
Please close your eyes.
Tell me whether you like it or not.
(She closes her eyes and calms herself down.)
(Such an experience is a first for both of them.)
(Among a crowd of people,)
(she was willing to help Jae Seok.)
- This looks... - Pardon?
(She can't speak.)
What do you think?
- I think it looks similar... - Mine looks better.
- Hey. Look. - Hold on.
I took no time at all. Come here.
- This looks like him. - But he looks so depressed.
Don't you like it though?
Yes, I think this looks better than me.
- See? - What?
- Hold on. - My customer is satisfied.
I shouldn't have done this.
This... This is...
I should erase this.
Wait.
Do you have an eraser?
What am I supposed to do?
(Kwang Soo is taking longer than expected.)
- I'm done... - Yes.
- Can you show me? - Doesn't this look like you?
Hey, how long...
Hey.
(Here it is...)
- Hey, why did you draw a grandma? - No, no.
This is supposed to be exaggerated.
- Do you have an eraser? - What?
What is that?
- What's this? You can't do this. - Is this bad?
- I tried my best. - It's okay.
- I'm sorry. - It's all right.
You're much more beautiful than this.
- You don't look like this, - It's okay.
- but I'm bad at drawing. - It's fine.
- Are you giving this to me? - Yes.
(She's going to keep it.)
- Thank you. - If I had more time...
- It's okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
Take care. Thank you.
Look. This is good.
Put it close to your face.
(This is the best picture of him.)
- So Hee. - Yes.
I don't think...
I should have drawn the smile lines. You should erase this, okay?
This is my first drawing.
- Thank you very much. - Sure thing.
Please keep this with you.
- I'll frame it. - You will?
So Hee, thank you. You must be busy.
(There are 35 left.)
You can't draw like that.
I don't think she was happy with it.
This is difficult to do.
Draw me.
(Somebody speaks.)
Would you like me to? Come here. I'll draw you.
(She volunteers even after seeing the previous portraits.)
Please sit down. Come here.
I'm not a great artist.
Would you like me to draw you, kid?
Would you like me to draw you?
- Would you like me to? - Please stay still.
- Would you like me to? - Yes.
Okay, have a seat.
(Kwang Soo recruits a child model.)
What is your name?
- Lee Hae Joon. - Hae Joon?
I don't have too much time,
but I'll try my best.
(Will he be able to recover his reputation?)
My drawings are pretty realistic.
- Please keep that in mind. - Okay.
(Realistic?)
- Focus on the special features. - I'll do that.
- This is for you. - That's good.
I don't know if you'll like this.
(She looks like a criminal.)
I'm sorry, Yu Jin.
You said it'd look cute.
I tried to make it look cute.
This looks really scary.
How does it look?
That scared me.
- What is this? - Yu Jin...
wanted me to make it cute.
- This... - It looks scary.
- What is this? - This looks really scary.
I'm sorry. I wanted to make it look good.
I really like it.
I'm sorry, Yu Jin.
I'm sorry.
This...
(Laughing)
- I'm sorry. - I'm finished.
Do you want to see?
Do you want to see it?
(This is a kid?)
What do you think?
(What am I looking at?)
Do you like it?
What are you doing?
- This is Hae Joon. No. - What are you doing to a child?
- His face looks a bit... - What do you think? Why?
- What's wrong? - What's this?
(This is the worst moment of his 10-year life.)
- What do you think? - I'm not sure.
- Does this look like you? - I'm not sure.
(He's not sure.)
- He's not sure. - Why are you so bad today?
I tried.
Do you like it?
- Yes. - He likes it.
Do you really like it?
- Do you like it? - You can be honest.
- Do you want to take a picture? - What do you think about this?
What do you think about this?
- I like it. - Do you?
- Yes. - Thank you, Hae Joon.
(Thank you so much.)
(Seok Jin completes his portrait again in 10 seconds.)
All right.
Please stand up.
(How will it look this time?)
(Ta-da)
- Doesn't this look nice? - It does.
Right? Doesn't this look nice?
It does. Move your hand for me.
It looks like her, doesn't it?
(Why is she embarrassed?)
- Do you like it? - Yes, I do.
- Do you like it? - Yes.
Did you hear that? She likes it.
- Would you like me to sign it? - Yes.
(They sold 10 pancakes and drew 7 portraits.)
How many caricatures do we have to draw?
You're not even pronouncing it right.
(Meanwhile, Haha escapes So Min's room and enters Je Sung's.)
- It's right. - This is it.
He escaped So Min's room. This is Je Sung's room.
- I'm looking forward to this. - All right.
- Do we go in? - Yes.
- Please come in. - Is he facing the wall?
Hello?
- Can we come in? - Yes, come in.
We're coming in.
- Hello. - You're not ready yet.
(He has to make Haha laugh with a fancy comedy act.)
(There's a chair and just him.)
- You're not ready yet. - What's this?
- Can we come in? - Yes, come in.
- What's this? Is this a bucket? - I thought you'd be busy.
We saw Haha struggling to escape the rooms,
- so this is a one-star level. - Okay.
- It's a massage. - That's good.
The masseur is strict,
so you can't laugh.
(The masseur is strict, so you can't laugh.)
You have to be relaxed. You can't frown...
- or smile. - No expression then?
Your regular facial expression.
- What is he supposed to do? - Please have a seat.
- Is he getting a massage? - Yes.
It's just you.
If it's okay, can you take off your cap?
- He's an expert at scalp massages. - I see.
- Is there a different masseur? - Yes.
Is he coming?
- I'll bring him. - Okay.
- I have to meet the masseur. - Right.
- Let's wait for him. - He's coming.
You should laugh beforehand.
I think he's fully prepared.
- He can't be that funny, right? - I know.
- You can hold it in. - I've seen various types of makeup.
You've seen so many funny things.
- The masseur is here. - He's here. Let's be quiet.
- Do I look? - No, you can't look.
Hold on.
- Set... - I didn't look yet, so can I laugh?
Set, go.
(Haha can't laugh at all. The massage starts now.)
(I won't laugh at all.)
(The masseur approaches him in a solemn atmosphere.)
(The masseur from an unknown country appears.)
(He can handle it so far.)
It's the masseur.
I'll relieve...
your fatigue.
(Laughter is contagious. The audience is in trouble.)
(He's barely holding it in.)
Do you normally look like that?
(Let me hold it in a bit more.)
Fatigue,
come out.
"Fatigue, come out."
Fatigue...
(What will come out?)
Fatigue.
(He turns on his phone.)
(Please come out.)
Once.
(These are great lyrics. He laughs once.)
(It's an African song about being lonely.)
I'll relieve your fatigue.
(Fatigue and laughter, come on out.)
(He attacks with the music and feet washing.)
This is scary.
There is no escape.
Your leg hair is very soft.
All right.
(The second laughter comes out.)
Fatigue.
(The laughter therapy chases away everyone's fatigue.)
Fatigue, come out.
(This massage is driving me crazy.)
Haha.
I will pluck out your long-standing fatigue.
What is he doing?
(The scalp therapy which aims for the 3rd laughter begins.)
(Can you feel your fatigue escaping from the top of your head?)
My goodness.
(Fatigue,)
(come out.)
(I promise to extract laughter from you.)
My goodness.
(Fatigue,)
(come out.)
(Laughing)
(Haha fails to defend himself against the third laughter.)
This is impossible.
- You can't win against this. - The long-standing fatigue.
The long-standing fatigue.
You are out.
This won't do.
His touch, voice,
- and music... - He is so good.
(The penalty is a water slap.)
Let's begin.
(Please come out.)
The song is on repeat.
1, 2, 3.
(Get a water slap and come out.)
I will get you a towel.
Congratulations.
We need to escape.
Thank you for using our service.
- Come out of the bathtub. - Come out.
Come out of the bathtub.
- The next vacation plan is... - Surfing?
- Will you surf next? - Surfing.
Where do you want to surf?
- Me? - Yes.
With Je Sung, this apartment can be Hawaii.
(With Je Sung, this apartment can be Hawaii.)
- What? - He can walk back and forth.
I can be a local.
(His looks and clothes scream Hawaii.)
He can walk back and forth.
- I can be a local. - He can be a local.
It doesn't matter where I go...
as long as there are water and a surfboard.
(A true surfer doesn't worry about the location.)
- The water, surfboard, and wind. - And the sea.
So I choose the bathtub.
(Therefore...)
I will surf there.
(A broke surfer chooses to surf in a bathtub.)
- Let's go. Fill it up. - Let's go.
You have to be cheerful.
- Of course. - Where will we do it?
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
Look at what I have.
Let's ride this.
(This washboard makes a perfect surfboard.)
(This is fun.)
Hold it.
You look like a surfer.
(They pretend to be excited in order to complete the mission.)
My goodness.
Jong Kook, it looks nice.
- There you go. - There you go.
- It works. - It works. It's perfect.
I will ride it.
It has been a while since I rode a shortboard.
All right.
Let's go.
(He goes into the bathtub.)
It's nice.
(Jong Kook enters the bathtub first.)
(Can he really surf here?)
- It works. - Waves.
- It's nice. - Waves.
(Give me the waves.)
Waves. Waves.
(The waves are created manually...)
(with a washbowl.)
It works.
- This is nice. - I know.
Take this.
(This is really fun.)
Let's go.
(They clear the 4th vacation plan, surfing.)
I will count that as surfing.
We have one vacation plan left.
- The rooftop. - Eating meat at the rooftop.
It's time to eat meat, but Je Sung has to leave.
Really?
Yes. It feels like you planned this.
That's not true.
- That's not true, Je Sung. - That's not true.
Give us our 90 cents.
The leftover 90 cents is your appearance fee. Thank you.
- What? - 90 cents.
- 90 cents. - Is my appearance fee 90 cents?
(What? 90 cents?)
It's less than the minimum wage.
- 90 cents. - This is all we have.
- We will pay him on the spot. - 90 cents.
Please insert it in the unicorn.
(We wish we could give you 9,000 dollars.)
I will use it for a good cause.
Okay. Thank you so much for the appearance fee.
- Thank you for your hard work. - I had a lot of fun, Jong Kook.
At this rate...
This won't work.
There is no end in sight. What's the number?
It's 32.
32 caricatures?
I can't draw anymore because I feel really bad.
I almost made a kid cry.
There is no end in sight.
This is driving me crazy.
(Glancing)
(There is a way to end this.)
(When they went net fishing for the third part-time job,)
(Jae Seok opened his pouch and checked the hidden mission.)
(Jae Seok can go home early if he steals Seok Jin's sock.)
(Help me, Kwang Soo.)
(They agreed on a forehead slap for stealing Seok Jin's sock.)
(They quickly formed an alliance.)
(We just need to take one of his socks off.)
(Is there a way to take them off?)
There is no end in sight.
Sit down for a second.
- Why? - I will draw you.
Why would you draw me?
I feel too bad about drawing someone else.
- No, no. - What?
- Sit down for a second. - Why?
We need to draw as many as we can.
I feel too bad about drawing someone else.
A lot of people were upset.
They tried not to show it.
You should be the model.
- I drew his portrait earlier... - What?
- when you weren't here. - We drew each other.
That's why I need to draw you.
Even if you draw me, it's just one more.
We have to do something. We don't have time.
- Let get at least one more done. - No, no.
When I draw you, tell me that you like my work.
If you draw Seok Jin, I will draw you.
Really?
- Okay. - Don't your shoulders hurt?
(Suddenly)
- My shoulders don't hurt. - My shoulders hurt a lot.
- Do your shoulders hurt? - Yes.
My shoulders hurt a lot.
- Why suddenly? - Why?
What? It's because of this bag.
(Seok Jin suddenly talks nonsense about his bag.)
(When they were drawing caricatures for the part-time job)
Come here.
I am really exhausted.
(No one is here, right?)
I was told to open it when I am exhausted. Today...
(He takes out his pouch.)
I don't know when this will end.
(He was told to open it alone when he was exhausted.)
The part-time jobs are never-ending.
What is this?
(What was Seok Jin's mission?)
(Busan to Seoul)
(Switch bags with Jae Seok.)
(Seok Jin's mission was switching bags with Jae Seok.)
(My goodness.)
This is incredible.
I should have opened it sooner.
How will I switch the bags?
I will take out my wallet in advance.
Can I switch only the name tags?
- Yes, you can. - Okay, okay.
I am going to go home.
This is driving me crazy.
(Will he succeed before Jae Seok does?)
This bag is...
What is wrong with you?
- Why would your shoulder hurt? - What?
You didn't carry it all day long.
We need to finish this quickly and go home.
Wait a second. What are you doing?
- What? - Why would you draw me?
Why?
It's not so hard to model for a caricature portrait.
It's strange that you won't do it.
It's strange that your shoulders suddenly hurt.
- They do hurt. - Let me draw you...
so that we will be down to 30.
Sit down. I will draw you.
That's ridiculous.
They told us to hurry.
(Seok Jin secretly takes off his name tag.)
- Okay. - Okay. Sit down.
(Sticking)
(He gets ready to strike with his name tag on his bottom.)
(He succeeds if he switches name tags with Jae Seok.)
(Will he make a successful attack?)
Sit down.
This isn't the right time.
(He backs off.)
Let's move.
- Why? - Let's move.
- Why is he acting this way? - I am embarrassed here.
- Let's move. - What?
What? Don't come near me.
- What is it? - Do I seem strange?
- What? - There is nothing strange about me.
(He is stiff.)
- You seem really strange. - What is that in your hand?
What?
- Let's go. - What is that in your hand?
Nothing. Let's go.
(He decides to wait for his chance.)
- He is hiding something. - Let's go.
- There's nothing. - Why do you keep looking this way?
Let's hurry up and go.
- Let's move. - Let's move.
- Thank you. Take care. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Take care.
Let's go.
- Take his shoes off first. - Now?
(Whispering)
(They discuss when to carry out their plan.)
Is it this way?
(Seok Jin notices them.)
(It's a tinderbox.)
Let's go.
It's this way.
(Seok Jin's mission is switching bags with Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok's mission is getting Seok Jin's sock.)
Hello. Be careful. You don't want to get hurt.
Let's go. Hey.
Gosh, there are so many people.
- Let's go. - Hey,
- this is the moment. - Gosh, there are so many people.
(Hey, this is the moment.)
(It's time to steal his sock.)
(I'm going to steal his sock and go home early.)
(They look for an opportunity...)
(and grab him.)
What?
(Kwang Soo subdues him, and Jae Seok steals.)
What are you doing?
(What are they doing?)
(Jae Seok succeeds in taking off his shoe.)
(If I take off his sock,)
(I can go home.)
(Slipping off)
I did it.
(He takes off a sock.)
(He succeeds in stealing the sock.)
(Seok Jin is in tatters.)
What is going on?
(Running)
Come on!
(Darn it. You little runts.)
Stop right there!
He's coming, Jae Seok!
(There's a chase in Busan out of the blue.)
Follow me.
(We probably lost him now, right?)
- He's right behind us. - Really?
(Give back my sock!)
Hurry up!
(What's gotten into him?)
(Their part-time jobs began from dawn.)
(Whoever gets left behind here...)
(must complete the remaining 32 jobs after a long day of work.)
(It's a matter of getting caught or losing him.)
Stop right there!
(The fate of part-time jobs rests upon this chase.)
(What's the result of this thrilling chase?)
Here he is!
(He suddenly gets slow. He's out of breath.)
Did he take my sock?
(Darn it. My sock!)
My sock?
(The sock-thieves make contact with the van.)
Get in. Hurry. Kwang Soo, hurry.
- Bye. - Kwang Soo, get in. Let's go.
- Go, go, go. - Please drive now.
Hey, you jerks.
(He tries to go after them.)
Where did they go?
(Did you really leave without me?)
- They left. - They left.
- Where did they go? - They went that way.
(Over there. Their van is already out of sight.)
Getting my sock was his mission.
(Trudging)
I thought his mission was drawing a picture.
Those two already set it up. They set this up.
- Kwang Soo, we did it. - We did it.
- We did it. - We did it.
- Thank you. - I really want this to end now.
This is over. Let's go home now.
- I want to go home. - Let's go.
- I want to go home. - Let's go now.
(It will be over after the last forehead slap.)
(Kwang Soo owed Jae Seok two forehead slaps.)
(He was summoned to Busan since dawn.)
(Why am I doing this? I don't even have to face the penalty.)
(After helping them so diligently, he finally got his forehead slap.)
- I don't know where my clothes are. - Jae Seok.
Good job today.
- Let's end it here. Nice and clean. - Okay.
Yes, unchain me, please.
- Let's end everything in Busan. - Yes.
- You're right. - All right. Kwang Soo.
(Get your forehead ready.)
(This slap has been following him around like a shackle.)
- Let's end it here. - Jae Seok, this is awesome.
- Let's go home now. - Please.
Okay.
(He will settle the long-overdue debt now.)
(Slapping)
(The sound of his debt settling)
(The forehead slaps have been settled.)
Let's go. Let's go, Kwang Soo.
(Let's leave with a light heart.)
(He must be feeling so happy.)
We love Busan!
(He's elated.)
We'll come back to Busan.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The sock-thieves leave Busan while feeling carefree.)
- Let's go. - That was so smart.
- Thank you, Je Sung. - Thank you.
- Thank you for the food. - This is so nice.
This is great.
- How is it? - It's good.
Je Sung bought good meat.
(They get to eat thanks to Je Sung.)
- This is so delicious. - You can get off work now.
We'll see you next week.
- We can go home now? - We succeeded.
- Really? - My gosh.
(Meanwhile, at Busan Station)
Jae Seok, great job today.
I'll get going.
Wait.
(They have Seok Jin's sock.)
Hey, Kwon Ryeol.
He'll be here soon. When he comes...
(Right, okay.)
Hold on.
(Please have a safe journey.)
(And Seok Jin who's really left behind all alone...)
- We'll go now. Let's go, Kwang Soo. - Bye.
Good work today.
(He's trying to fill up 32 all by himself.)
Goodness, Jae Seok is unbelievable.
He plotted this with Kwang Soo.
This is so hot. Do you want two?
- Yes. Thank you. - Two? Okay.
(Dropping)
This won't count.
- What should I do? - Please don't count this one.
It's hot.
I'll dock this one from my pay.
Darn it.
This 3-dollar tanghulu is now 2 dollars.
Here. Thank you. Here you go.
- Me too. - Thank you.
All right. Three tanghulus.
Do you want 5? 2? Here's the last 1.
- Congratulations on filling 100. - Yes!
Thank you, everyone.
(Next week)
(Special guests visit Running Man.)
(Lee Ha Na, an actress who swept TV screens)
(Im Soo Hyang, unexpected charms)
(A new character you've never seen on variety shows has come.)
(These scary ladies are ready to join the variety shows.)
(They don't need time to adjust.)
(It's their journey to dominate variety shows.)
(However,)
(a mysterious bank shows up in front of them.)
(And strange things begin to take place.)
(These suspicious ladies are behind everything.)
(A mysterious chase begins all of a sudden. What's the result?)
(Don't Trust Her)