(Jeju Island, the dreamland, is everlastingly exotic.)
- Hello. - Hi, everyone.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello, everyone.
Did you sleep well? Good morning. Hey, Mi Yeon.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hi. - Morning, everyone.
- Hello. - Hi.
It's been a while since we last filmed in Jeju Island,
but it's snowing hard here, and there's a strong gust of wind.
- It's hailing. - Just in case...
(The biting gust of wind pierces from the morning.)
(On top of that, it's hailing hard.)
He's worried that the flights might be canceled.
The producer told me that we were going to start our shoot early...
- because he had another shoot next. - That's right.
- If it's canceled, it'd be bad. - Right.
Seok Jin was feeling nervous and asked him this question quietly.
"Chul Min, can I go poop?"
Seok Jin asked Chul Min that given the current state?
Why would he ask for permission to poop?
- My goodness. - It's because we had to hurry.
You could've just gone without asking.
- Seok Jin. Seriously. - Even kids go without asking.
- You're over 50 years old now. - It's because we have to hurry.
How could you ask someone younger than you for permission?
- Hey. - Would you not poop if he said no?
- The entire staff were waiting. - My goodness.
- No one has done that to poop. - Seriously.
Today's race is a partner race called Rule of Collection.
(Rule of Collection)
You'll receive a black pig gift set for the winning prize.
- Okay. Let's win this. - Black pig.
Jeju Island is famous for that.
You will compete for the black pig gift set and the water bomb.
- Water bomb? - Water bomb? With today's weather?
It's hailing today.
(The water bomb with the biting wind...)
(and the high-end, black pig gift set are at stake for the race.)
First of all, let us present you female guests who have flown...
- all the way here to join the race. - It must've taken a lot of effort.
- All right. - Yes, I agree.
Please come on out.
- Come out, angels. - Please come on out!
I'm so thankful they came here.
(Wait, this song is...)
Lyrics go, "It's the night I want to spend with you".
("Good Time" by Cleo)
(It's the night I want to spend with you)
- This is her song. - With you
Here she comes.
(It's So Min's song.)
It's So Min?
(She sang it in her school days.)
(She dances like she's back in school.)
Why is she circling her hands?
- I see Ji Hyo. - So Min.
Did you see Ji Hyo? She walked out and went like this.
- What's wrong with Ji Hyo? - She's a ghost.
(A shadowy ghost is behind So Min.)
- What's up with her? - So Min!
I didn't know, but we were supposed to come out together.
- Really? - Yes.
- Hurry. - What's going on?
I saw you dancing right away when the song was played.
(I couldn't help it. It's my favorite song.)
Ji Hyo looks like she's going camping today.
I bundled up because it's snowing a lot in Jeju Island.
- You don't dress up for us anymore. - She doesn't care anymore.
She looks like a lumberjack.
You're the one to talk. Look at you. Are you in the army or what?
(She gets infuriated.)
- Fine. I'm in the service. - Are you?
- Yes, I'm in the army. - Go fulfill your military duty.
No, his jacket is the carrot, and his hat is the root of it.
(No, his jacket is the carrot, and his hat is the root of it.)
What? The root of a carrot? Don't you dare call me that!
I was talking about your hat.
- Stop it. - Watch every word, So Min.
- We should bring in another guest. - Here we go.
- We are just getting started. - Okay.
- Can you still smell my cologne? - Yes.
What is happening? It's a quiet song.
(The entrance song is quite calm.)
What?
(Who is the first female guest?)
(A tall, multitalented actress)
- That's Lee Da Hee. - Really?
(Lee Da Hee, a tall, multitalented actress)
(Her build is superior, but her acting is more superior.)
(She showed her superiority on variety shows too.)
- I haven't seen you in ages. - Hey, long time no see.
- Hey. - Do you know each other?
- We've met a long time ago. - Of course.
- How do you know each other? - A long time ago, Da Hee...
was on "Open Your Heart" or a program similar to that.
- Weren't you on variety shows? - Wait, so...
- I haven't met you. - Really? We haven't?
(He's flustered.)
- What's the matter with him? - Why do you pretend you know her?
- He talked like we'd met, - I was just welcoming her.
- but I've never met him. - It sounds like you've been well.
You got taller.
- What's wrong with him? - She said she'd never met you.
I remember skipping ropes with you.
- Skipping ropes? Come on. - We even played the marble game.
- Da Hee has joined us. Who's next? - Great!
(They're expectant.)
- Okay. - What's this song?
Wait, the song sounds a bit...
(She shows up with a trendy song.)
- Who is it? - It's Koo Ha Ra.
- It's Koo Ha Ra. - Koo Ha Ra!
(She's the cute and sexy fairy of the Korean Wave.)
(Unexpectedly, she's an athletic singer with a strong will to win.)
Kwang Soo, it's Koo Ha Ra! It's Ha Ra!
- My gosh. - What's going on with you?
- Hey. - Why? Do you like her?
Do you like her?
(Her return has shaken the fans.)
- Ha Ra. - It's been so long, Ha Ra.
- No way. - It's Ha Ra.
- Long time, no see. - My gosh, it's Koo Ha Ra.
- It's nice to see you all. - How have you been?
It's been years, Ha Ra. I think Se Chan is a big fan.
- I'm a big fan. - Really?
- He's over the moon. - I was so shocked.
- Since when were you her fan? - Ever since she was in Kara.
- Really? - Yes.
- We have amazing guests today. - Seriously.
- I agree. - What's going on today?
- The airport must've been hectic. - It's been years, Ha Ra.
- Let's bring in the next guest. - Okay.
(The entrance song is hip.)
(Did a hip guest join the show?)
- Seor In A! - Seor In A!
(Seor In A, a rising star in the limelight)
- Seor In A is an actress. - Seor In A.
(She is the super rookie of the year who was searched the most online.)
Long time, no see!
(He pretends to know her too.)
Did you say, "Long time, no see"?
- I didn't see you since the awards. - Again?
- Did you see her at the awards? - Yes.
- We have one last guest. - We won't interview her?
- All right. Come on out! - It's Mina.
She's in Gugudan.
- Gugudan! - Long time, no see!
(She's the cutie of Gugudan.)
- Awesome. - Yes, dance for us!
- This is incredible! - We have an idol singer!
- She's much better. - She dances much better.
(Mina, cutie of Gugudan)
She's excellent.
(She is a member of Gugudan and released her own album.)
(Mina, the refreshing singer, is charming the music industry.)
I memorized the multiplication tables a lot in elementary school.
(He makes a pun with the name, Gugudan.)
What's gotten into him today?
- What's wrong? - He's acting so lame.
- I'm a huge fan. I'm serious. - That's enough.
You're my only favorite idol singer.
- I'm serious. - Four guests have gathered here.
- Right. - Welcome, everyone!
(We welcome you with passion.)
- Let's interview them one by one. - Okay.
First up is Lee Da Hee!
(Let's start with Lee Da Hee.)
Da Hee debuted in 2002 as a model.
This is the 17th year of her career.
That's impressive.
That's incredible.
You were recently on "The Law of Jungle".
Wasn't it hard?
- I had fun. - Really?
I want to go again.
She is picking her nose!
(She is flustered.)
What is wrong with him?
She scratched her nose.
She didn't pick her nose.
- Why would Da Hee pick her nose? - For goodness' sake.
Okay. I am sorry.
I am wearing an angora top, and fur keeps getting on my face.
Then did you really pick your nose?
No.
(She is flustered for the 2nd time.)
Did fur go into her nose?
- She picked fur out of her nose. - Really?
Fur went into her nose.
(This is a unique way to treat a guest.)
The thing is,
both Kwang Soo and Da Hee debuted as models.
Have you met her before?
No, this is my first time meeting her.
Didn't you work as a model?
Da Hee, tell us.
I didn't get to work much as a model.
Kwang Soo, you were famous.
- No. - No?
- Not really. - Really?
I joined the fashion show only once.
- I did, too. - Really?
- Me, too. - Really?
Isn't that more of an experience?
(Isn't that more of an experience?)
When did you debut?
Don't be so harsh.
- Don't be so harsh. - It's not like that.
What is up with you today?
I can't believe you.
(Pictures from the days they experienced a modeling career)
What is up with you today?
Kwang Soo is just a tall man.
- He is just a tall man. - Don't say you were a model.
- Stop it. - You weren't much of a model.
I heard that Da Hee can sing.
- Is she a good singer? - She is a good singer.
- Let's hear her sing. - Da Hee.
I heard that you can sing.
When we ask the guests to sing,
- they usually go, "No, no." - That's right.
I don't get many chances to sing.
- This is a good opportunity. - Really?
- That's great. - Please sing a song.
Most guests hate it.
(Breathing out)
Please be quiet. Let's hear her sing.
It's very
Why don't you sing some other time?
(Considerate)
- Your throat is in a bad condition. - No, it's in a good condition.
What was that?
Is it because of the fur?
Could it be because of your angora top?
Why don't you jump to the chorus?
Take us to the highlight.
I can't stop her when she wants to sing.
In 2, 3.
The act of waiting
What should I do?
(What should I do?)
You failed!
- You failed! - Your throat is in a bad condition.
Isn't her participation in the OST more of an experience?
(Isn't her participation in the OST more of an experience?)
Don't say that.
That's no way to treat a guest!
- I am sorry. - Stop it already.
- Do you want to see me angry? - I am sorry.
This isn't the right time.
The next guest is Seor In A.
(The next guest is Seor In A.)
In A tends to throw...
- some profound words... - What are those words?
without thinking.
- Those words have a ripple effect. - What are those words?
Here are some examples.
"Actors are like nails."
- Nails? - Why?
I can't even laugh.
Let's hear her reason.
You grow nails.
You cut nails.
"Actors are like nails."
You can cut the parts you don't like...
and paint them in colors of your choice.
(They are cringing.)
I am sorry, but do you still have MySpace?
Don't say anything.
Seriously.
That's no way to treat a guest!
I got goosebumps.
- That's... - I am sorry, In A.
She must have had sentimental posts.
Exactly how old are you?
How old are you?
I heard you were good at sports.
In A,
- you learned taekwondo, right? - Jiu jitsu?
- Yes. - Did you learn jiu jitsu as well?
I am learning jiu jitsu right now. I learned taekwondo in childhood.
Are you good at kicks?
In A, can you break wooden boards?
- Yes. - Would it be okay?
Kwang Soo, please hold it up.
She will kick it.
- In A. - Yes.
(Kicking)
My goodness.
(It hurts.)
She kicked my hands.
(I can't believe you kicked my hand, too.)
She kicked my hand.
- Are you okay? - She kicked his hand.
Did I really kick your hand?
- It shouldn't be too painful. - It's okay.
She should have kicked the middle.
- Look. - Are you okay?
- Look. - She kicked his hand.
- I think she did. - She kicked his hand all right.
The end broke.
Why did you kick his hand?
- I must have aimed too high. - She obviously kicked his hand.
Kwang Soo is the one at fault.
He should have held up the wooden board higher.
- In A has long legs. - That's right.
- He should have held it up higher. - You are saying it's my fault...
- for getting kicked. - That's right.
- I got kicked. - It's your fault.
In A has long legs. You should have held it up higher.
(I am sorry, Kwang Soo.)
I want to see a jiu jitsu demonstration.
- Can you show us? - An arm bar.
- Then I will have to twist someone. - Really?
Why don't you twist Se Chan?
- Me? - Yes.
I mean...
Let's do it this way.
Think of yourself as a molester.
- That's a good idea. - Yes.
- What should he do? - I love this kind of a set-up.
It suits him.
When I walk,
put your arm around me in a sneaky way.
Okay. That's good.
You can use the trick in real life.
Everyone should learn.
- He looks like a molester. - Go.
(What kind of self-defense technique will the jiu jitsu master show?)
She simply pushed him.
(She twists his arm...)
(and pushes him.)
Anyone can do that.
- It's a simple push. - Hold on.
(It's a simple push.)
Anyone can do that.
This isn't jiu jitsu.
She simply threw a fit.
Try it on me.
- It's jiu jitsu. - She simply threw a fit.
Anyone can do this.
- Is this jiu jitsu? - Listen.
- What was that? - It's a useful tip.
- Didn't she simply throw a fit? - What do you think you are doing?
Let's talk to the next guest.
- The next guest is Mina. - Mina!
- Mina is the best. - It's Mina.
- She is the best. - She is the best.
- In 2016, - I love the way her eyes crinkle.
she debuted as a member of I.O.I.
She now works diligently as a member of Gugudan.
I heard that...
Mina prepared a specialty at home.
Really?
- You did that for Running Man. - That's incredible.
The members told me not to show it.
What did you prepare?
- A voice impression. - A voice impression.
- A voice impression. - Although I practiced hard,
- the members told me not to do it. - Really?
Whom do you imitate?
Well,
- I imitate the rapper, Jolly V. - Jolly V.
(Can she do a voice impression of Jolly V?)
(She covers her mouth and imitates shyly.)
I did this.
It becomes a specialty if you don't cover your mouth.
- You shouldn't cover your mouth. - Really?
- Please try again. - I will give it another try.
(She shows her face.)
That's hilarious.
- Mina, that's the way to do it. - That's hilarious.
- Her mouth looked funny. - For a successful specialty,
you shouldn't cover your mouth.
(Jae Seok's coaching leaves the student satisfied.)
She is cute.
(Does he think it's cute?)
(She does it in a depressing way.)
How do you do it?
Try, "You jerk."
Do a voice impression of Joo Hyun.
For goodness' sake.
Stay out of it, you jerk.
(She is good at this.)
That's really annoying.
"Stay out of it, you jerk."
The next guest is a singer who debuted 10 years ago.
What a surprise!
Koo Ha Ra!
Ha Ra said this...
back in the days.
Do you remember saying this?
"I want to get married at the age of 36."
- 36? - 36?
Do you think differently now?
(What is your stand on it now?)
(Ha Ra wanted to get married at the age of 36.)
(Does she still wish the same?)
I don't want to get married anymore.
(I don't want to get married anymore.)
Those jerks!
(Who hurt her?)
Kwang Soo, stop it.
- Don't make assumptions. - Okay.
- It was all in my imagination. - You must have been hurt.
- It was all in my imagination. - For goodness' sake.
Women always meet a nice man...
- after pieces of trash. - Stop it.
(He makes assumptions.)
- Stop it. - It's like that.
Stop it.
- It's exhausting, right? - Yes.
- I am sorry, Ha Ra. - It's okay.
I think I will have fun today.
(It's thanks to the male members.)
That's right.
I think she will say...
what you said during the flight.
"Those jerks."
(The members of Running Man, those jerks.)
"The members of Running Man, those jerks."
(Let's hope she won't get hurt by the members of Running Man.)
"Those jerks."
I don't know whom those words will direct.
Now, let's choose the partners...
for these six women.
This is nerve-wracking.
The rules are simple.
Each female member will come out...
and say, "I like someone who is..."
If the condition applies to you, step forward.
When you do that, you have to squat walk.
If your hands leave your ears, you are out.
If your hands stay on your ears even if you fall, you are in.
What if your hands leave...
with your ears?
(What if your hands leave with your ears?)
- What? - What happens then?
Your hands leave with your ears.
- Then you are out. - You are out.
I will be careful not to do that.
- We will need strong ears. - You are out...
- if you hold your torn ears. - You are out.
(Let's decide on the partners.)
- Everyone, - Yes.
once you reach this zone,
the woman will make a decision.
- The woman will make a decision. - That's right.
This is nerve-wracking.
Which one...
should we start with?
Who wants to go first?
- Me. - Koo Ha Ra.
(Ha Ra volunteers.)
This is like the final round.
- She's very confident. - Gosh.
- From the start... - It's like finals.
From the start...
It's already beginning.
Say what you look for in your partner.
- Okay. - Okay.
- She's so relaxed. - Yes.
She's a veteran.
She came back very relaxed.
Ready,
start.
I...
(What does Ha Ra look for in her partner?)
(I...)
(What is her dream partner like?)
I want someone in a black outfit.
(Se Chan, Jong Kook, Haha)
(Those in black squat walk forward.)
(Black?)
(I'm wearing black inside.)
I'm not wearing any black.
(Those not in black become restless.)
(I'm not wearing black either.)
(Wait, my undershirt is black.)
That's black. Take your sweater off.
Good.
That's black.
You're late.
- It's over. - Hold on.
(Curious)
- Your hands are off your ears. - Oh, my.
- It's over. - I'm wearing black.
Oh, my.
- I'm wearing black. - It's over.
It's over.
Please turn around on the count of three.
1, 2, 3.
(It's time to see the candidates.)
(Many came.)
- Ha Ra. - Ha Ra.
- Ha Ra. - Please push the ones...
you don't like one by one.
1, 2...
(The candidates are Se Chan, Jong Kook, Haha, and Seok Jin.)
(You can push the ones you don't like out.)
1, 2, 3.
(Sorry, Seok Jin.)
She hit his head first.
- Next. - Well...
- Next. - Kwang Soo, I still have a chance.
(Excited)
(Se Chan, Ha Ra's old fan, was so happy to see her today.)
(Will Se Chan make it to the finals?)
Haha.
- Haha. - Do you need help?
(Haha is eliminated.)
(I'm sorry.)
- Now... - Ha Ra, see what happens.
(Petty)
- See what happens. - Haha.
- See if your cold will go away. - Exactly.
Oh, my.
- Se Chan versus Jong Kook. - Se Chan, you can do this.
Ha Ra.
It's finals.
I've made it to the finals.
(I've made it to finals.)
(Ha Ra, Se Chan's crush for years, is right in front of him.)
(But his opponent is Jong Kook.)
(Whom will Ha Ra choose?)
Okay!
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
I knew it. What was I hoping for?
- Okay. - You made it to second place.
I knew it.
Of course.
- Jong Kook and Ha Ra. - Okay.
Okay.
Next, So Min.
Me? Should I go first?
(It's So Min's turn now.)
(Uninterested)
I feel no excitement at all.
- Say exactly what you want. - Say what you want first.
I want...
someone very generous.
(I want someone very generous.)
- I'm very sensitive these days. - I'm so petty.
- I'm really petty. - I'm so petty...
- that my wife complains about it. - I'm petty.
- I'm so petty. - So Min.
(Forget it.)
- Oh, my. - This is how it works?
- We're all petty. - Can't you say something else?
- I'm petty. - I'm really petty.
I want...
(Second try)
I want someone handsome.
- I'm not handsome. - I'm ugly.
No one is handsome.
So Min.
(They try their best to look ugly.)
Look at Haha.
You guys are so mean.
(I can't believe them.)
- You'll have to wait. - Hey.
(Just give up.)
Are you serious?
- Try again later. - I can't give up.
Come on.
- I want... - Go back.
- I want. - Stop it.
I want someone short and old with a flat bottom and a pouty mouth.
(I want someone short and old, with a flat bottom and a pouty mouth.)
Stop it.
Calm down.
They're so mean.
This is how it works?
Unfortunately, So Min...
failed to find a partner.
It's Da Hee's turn now.
(Da Hee will find a partner.)
She and Kwang Soo will make a great team.
Please say what you look for.
(What is Da Hee's dream partner like?)
I want someone not younger than me.
(Se Chan is younger than Da Hee.)
Hold on. Do you mean everyone except me?
That's right.
- Kwang Soo is your age. - That's okay.
I'll just stay here.
(I'll just stay here.)
Don't take it personally.
You could have just said you wanted anyone but me.
- I mean... - Don't take it personally.
He welcomed all the guests...
- except me. - Is that why?
- He didn't welcome me. - I see.
All right.
Everyone except Se Chan.
Se Chan, you can still...
- try. - I can?
- It doesn't matter. - Of course.
Ready, start.
(It's time to choose.)
(Everyone welcomed Da Hee.)
(How many will be there?)
Da Hee, please turn around. 1, 2, 3.
(Only the one younger than her is here.)
(Cold)
Hold on.
(Why is he here?)
Hold on. This is just too much.
This is too much.
Da Hee. Hold on.
It's not like that.
She looked like Ha Jung Woo in "The Chaser".
(Is there a hammer or a club?)
I'm hurt.
Seriously...
What is this?
You're not the only one who got hurt.
- Da Hee is hurt too. - She is?
You're both hurt.
Don't think we'll go for everyone.
We're hard to please.
We're very picky.
If I don't choose anyone now,
I might end up becoming...
- Seok Jin's partner, right? - Yes.
I don't want that.
(I don't want that.)
- So... - What's going on?
- What are you doing? - Hey.
Seok Jin didn't do anything.
- I don't like you. - What's wrong?
- So... - I don't like you.
- I can't believe her. - Seok Jin didn't do anything.
- I didn't do anything. - It's bad enough now,
but do you think it might get worse?
(Does it show?)
I don't like you.
She's the best.
If...
Da Hee pushes Se Chan out, they won't become a team.
One,
two...
(Da Hee is cornered. Will she choose Se Chan?)
Three.
(Se Chan and Da Hee)
Anyway, Da Hee and...
Se Chan are a team now.
Next, In A.
- In A. - In A.
We're hard to please.
- We're picky. - We are.
- We know what we want. - Let's do this.
I want...
(I want...)
I want someone wearing a cap.
It's everyone.
- Oh, no. - What are you doing?
She's too easy.
She's opening up my heart.
- Should we go? - So Min changed the atmosphere.
- Right? - Completely.
- Ready... - What should we do?
- Should we go? - It's driving me crazy.
- Start. - Should we go?
(They move forward.)
They're moving.
(Kicking)
(Ji Hyo jumps in...)
(and kicks Haha away.)
What's happening?
Are you okay?
She kicked him in the jaw.
- You're eliminated. - Wait.
- What's with her? - You're eliminated.
A gangster wouldn't do that.
In A, turn around.
1, 2, 3.
Peekaboo.
(Only you two?)
Haha had an accident on the way.
Ji Hyo won't leave me alone...
whenever we do couple games.
- You're mine. Don't do anything. - She's driving me crazy.
1, 2, 3. Push someone out.
- Push the one you don't like. - Push the one you don't like.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
(Wait, it means...)
- What's this? - Unbelievable.
- Wait. - What's happening?
- Do you want to try again? - Unbelievable.
Gosh.
(Irritated)
In A, please go back.
- In A... - Kwang Soo thought he'd win.
- It's Mina's turn now. - Mina.
There will be a lot of competition.
Mina is...
Her smile is so pretty, right?
Please say what you look for.
I...
want someone wearing a shirt.
(I want someone wearing a shirt.)
A shirt?
(No one is wearing a shirt.)
- A shirt? - It's you.
Just say you want Jae Seok.
(Just say you want Jae Seok.)
Gosh.
You hurt our pride.
I can't find a shirt.
All I'm wearing is an undershirt.
This is...
It's too obvious whom she wants.
Ready.
(There has been a lot of opposition.)
(But Mina wants only Jae Seok.)
(Mina is only loyal to Jae Seok with a collared shirt.)
(Did Jae Seok come?)
(She's disappointed.)
- What's going on? - He just put it on.
He wasn't wearing a collared shirt before.
- Why is she upset? - She's not.
- Am I that bad? - No.
It may be because she likes you.
- You weren't wearing a shirt. - "Am I that bad?"
- Am I that bad? - Listen.
(How can you react that way?)
(Kwang Soo was rejected when he borrowed a shirt from the staff.)
Listen.
- Listen. - He's discouraged.
Da Hee showed how she felt with her facial expression.
However, Mina...
(Her groaning explained her feelings.)
Please sit down.
- Mina, in 3, 2, 1. - The shirt looks borrowed.
(Will you hold my hand?)
They become a couple.
- Mina and Kwang Soo are together. - Yes.
Come on.
Next is Ji Hyo.
Her partner is obvious.
However, we never know.
All right, Ji Hyo.
I can...
(He's nervous.)
I can make delicious food.
(What is she saying all of a sudden?)
- What do you mean? - What?
Are you awake yet?
You're not awake yet.
- Ji Hyo. - You keep saying that I'm old.
- Come on, Ji Hyo. - You keep saying that I'm old.
This is choosing your partner. You startled me.
Please answer again.
Tell us, Ji Hyo.
I like men who don't wear glasses.
(Haha is the only one without glasses.)
It's Haha.
(Haha goes somewhere.)
You can't borrow other people's items from now on.
(He takes the camera director's glasses.)
Wait.
- You can't borrow things. - You can't.
It's not allowed.
You can't do that.
(That's against the rules.)
You can't borrow from other people.
- You can't. - No.
You can't borrow items from other people.
(He brings a permanent marker.)
Will you draw the glasses?
(He plans to draw him a tattoo.)
- Do it for me. - Really?
We aren't allowed to borrow.
We can't borrow any items.
(He starts to draw.)
It's done.
(I have glasses on, Ji Hyo.)
(He even draws glasses with a permanent marker.)
Then I change my mind.
- To what? - Someone with glasses on.
Someone with glasses on?
(She wants a partner with glasses on.)
(Someone with glasses on?)
- Stop it. - May I change my mind to...
- someone with glasses? - He can't erase them.
If he meets the standard, he's required to come out.
- It's required. - Stop it.
That's enough, Haha.
If you have glasses on, you must come out.
(I took them off. It's all you.)
She's been my partner for weeks.
Ji Hyo!
Why do you find me so attractive?
Why me? I have two children, you punk.
- Stop it. - I have two children, you punk.
(Let me go.)
You punk.
You're full of charms.
Start. You must come out.
(Wait a minute.)
What?
(In A suddenly intercepts him.)
- Take your hands off. - What?
Why won't you?
Wait, what's going on?
What do you want me to do?
- She used a self-defense technique. - Self-defense.
That's self-defense.
That was a self-defense technique.
Did someone steal my partner?
My goodness.
(She pulls his hand away from his ear.)
- He let go of his hands. - He's eliminated.
(Haha is eliminated.)
- You must be happy, Haha. - What happened?
- Do you know what In A did? - Really?
Come back to your place.
Why did you save me suddenly?
(Haha and In A become partners.)
(Couples are formed.)
Everyone has a partner after some difficulties.
Here are the rules for Rule of Collection.
(Race for Rule of Collection officially starts.)
All partners pick a card numbered from 1 to 6.
The team whose total is the highest...
and the lowest win.
The highest and the lowest win.
Everyone except the winning two couples...
(The rest will get a water bomb.)
- Everyone else will get... - Everyone else?
a water bomb.
Only two couples can win.
Only two couples will survive.
The cards of the couple that comes in last will be revealed.
(The cards of the couple that comes in last will be revealed.)
One person of the winning couple finds out who has a certain card.
- He may switch partners. - Switch partners?
(There's a chance to switch partners.)
Can you switch partners?
- That's great. - We get to switch partners?
- My goodness. - That's great.
(What's the meaning behind your smile?)
I'm sorry.
(Wait, I'm sorry.)
Da Hee is finally smiling.
Da Hee looks so happy.
She's so excited.
She smiled very big.
Did you get a shot of her face?
Gosh, she finally smiles.
You must win to get a chance to switch partners.
- We must win? - We must win?
Only if we win.
It's time to select the number that will determine your fate.
The male partners will select the cards first.
Shall we?
This is...
(The total must be the highest or the lowest.)
The female partners may select them.
Is the highest or the lowest better?
That depends on my number.
- Is it the sum? - Yes.
- Let me see it. - It's a good number.
Isn't it good?
I'm not sure about mine.
The total must be the highest or the lowest.
That's right. Ji Hyo.
- I... - Let's show the card each.
(They don't show it to each other.)
- We have a possibility. - We do.
(What will be the fate of these couples?)
- Let's go. - Clumsy.
- Slow cross. - Cross.
I think this is too small.
Your shirt color is different.
(Kwang Soo, your shirt color is different.)
- What? - Something went wrong.
Did she break your heart already?
- He lost the couple shirt. - Right.
Stop teasing me.
- It's because he lost it. - I didn't lose it.
It's when the boyfriend lost the couple shirt?
- Gosh. - That's a good metaphor.
It's obvious with Jong Kook and Ha Ra.
They look like professional game players.
They got together to play games.
They run a business.
- Ha Ra has calmed down a lot. - Really?
- She isn't like before. - Of course not.
This is your first mission with Chance Card on the line.
Let's start Talent Competition.
(Talent Competition)
Talent Competition?
Among six skills that female players feel most confident about,
we'll select three and hold competitions.
The couple with the most stickers wins.
If the skill is what you submitted, you win one R Sticker.
If it's a skill submitted by someone else, you win two stickers.
(You win two R Stickers.)
Okay, it must be someone else's talent.
You'll play three rounds. The team with the most stickers...
gets a chance to switch partners and find out the number you want.
We'll win.
The team that comes in last...
will reveal the number that you have.
My goodness.
(The team that comes in last must reveal their numbers.)
This is difficult.
- We have to show our numbers? - How?
Can it be just one of us?
(Can only one of us show the number?)
- Both of you must show it. - Is that so?
(Let's not do this already.)
- Don't do this. - I won't.
- We haven't started yet. - Gosh.
- Shall we select one? - Yes.
Select one.
(Which category is it?)
"Long jump".
(The first talent competition is long jump.)
- Are you good at long jumps? - It's for Ha Ra.
- Oh, no. - See?
- How about you? - Pardon?
- Are you good at it? - I am.
Is this your talent?
- Yes, it is. - Really?
(She's talented in long jumps.)
- This is ours. - Da Hee says she's good...
- at everything including singing. - Look at her long legs.
- I'm good. - Her legs are long.
That's right. She likes to jump.
Everyone, Da Hee will start first.
Have you done it professionally?
We do one-foot jump often...
- as children. - How old were you?
- I was in kindergarten or so. - Kindergarten?
- Yes. - We're in trouble.
- Kindergarten? - She'll be good.
She'll jump far because her legs are long.
- Please start. - Shall I start now?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Don't step on the line. - I won't.
- I can't do this well. - Good luck.
(She gets nervous.)
It won't be easy with those shoes.
Calm down, and relax.
(Will she show off her talent with her long legs?)
That's good.
(Landing)
- She jumped really far. - Mark right here.
- It's not enough space. - There's her footprint.
No way. How did she jump that far?
I jumped to here.
- I got it. - It's right here.
- It's 43. - It's 2m 43cm.
Who can beat that?
Even men can't jump that far.
All right, Da Hee.
- Are you satisfied? - Yes.
(She can't believe it either.)
- Who wants to go next? - In A will go.
- Come on, In A. - Okay.
Give me your bag.
Let's go.
- Haha. - 2, 3, 4.
- In A, In A, in artist, baby - In A, In A, in artist, baby
(With a chant, they show their teamwork.)
She's good at this.
- In A does it well. - She does.
- Yes. - Start farther back.
(Where are they going?)
Okay, that's good.
- How far are you going? - How far are you going?
I tried that far before, but you get tired on the way.
Let's go, In A.
If In A jumps farther,
she wins two stickers. Da Hee, on the other hand...
You can do it, In A.
This is Da Hee's talent, so she gets another turn.
- You can do it. - I can do it.
Let's go.
(In A gives a try.)
(Will In A break the record?)
(Will In A, full of confidence, be able to break the record?)
- It's right here. - No, no.
- This is the spot. - All right.
- There's a mark here. - Hold on.
- Where is it? - Here it is. This is it.
- This is the footprint. This is it. - My gosh.
- It's 2m 44cm. - It's 45.
- It's 44. - Okay.
- In A! - Yes!
1, 2, 3, 4.
(In A, In A)
(In A, artist, baby)
Great.
This is great. You were so cool.
(Her eyes are fuming.)
Look at Da Hee's face. She looks so intense again.
(Oh, no. I got caught.)
This means that...
(Haha and In A are in 1st place.)
Ha Ra is going to go for it now.
She starred on "Idol Star Athletics Championships".
(The time has come.)
(Ha Ra holds the reputation for the best runner.)
(Ha Ra, the athlete, has returned.)
- Your pants are wide. Are you okay? - Will you be all right?
I was wondering that too.
- I should pull it up. - Pull it all the way up.
If you jump with wide pants, it will make a flapping sound.
The pants are highly resistant.
- I don't know what will happen. - Good luck, Ha Ra.
That's true.
- She starred on the sports show. - It's been a while.
Don't be nervous.
(The third challenger, Ha Ra goes for it.)
(Will she be able to defend her honor of the best athlete?)
(What? What just happened?)
- Come on. - Hey.
That's all right.
- Let's try it one more time. - No, no, no.
- Do it one more time. - Wait, no, no.
- Let me try one more time. - Come on, let her try it again.
- Give her a chance. - Wait, please.
- She should get a second chance. - I couldn't see. I couldn't.
I couldn't see where it was.
- Her nose is getting longer. - Where is it? Is this the line?
- Ha Ra. - Yes?
- You stepped here. - No, no.
- Do you think you can do it? - Jae Seok.
- Tighten your shoelaces. - Can you do it one more time?
- My pants are wide. - Can you do it one more time?
(She makes a point with her pants.)
- Okay. This is your last chance. - Can you do it?
Ha Ra, stick your pants in your socks.
Ha Ra, are your toes okay?
Ha Ra.
Her pants became an old lady's pants.
That's great.
Ha Ra hasn't changed a bit.
Ha Ra hasn't changed at all. I thought she changed.
She's doing her best.
- She's determined now. - All right. And...
Don't let it burden you. It's all right.
Start.
- I see greed in her face. - She moved too far back.
Slowly. It's all right.
Hey, what is this?
Hey, hold on.
She jumped a long distance.
(No way. That's incredible!)
Hey, hold on.
(He's shocked.)
- It's right there. - No, this is the spot.
(Could she have possibly...)
You did so well, but you jumped way behind the starting line.
(What a bummer.)
(She did jump far behind the line like Jong Kook said.)
Where did I jump?
- You jumped from here. - Where?
- Then can you add the distance? - She was scared.
This isn't a place for you to play tricks.
- No way. - My gosh.
That was so close, Ha Ra.
(Thanks to Ha Ra, In A and Haha are still in 1st place.)
- Who's next? - Mina will go.
- Mina! - All right!
(Mina is up next.)
And...
- Get ready. - Excuse me.
Da Hee, why are you looking like that?
- I can't watch? - I felt something creepy.
(Her eyes are brimming with intensity.)
(Da Hee, the scary-eyed woman, is watching.)
We're going to give it a go.
Where is she?
(Peekaboo)
Here she comes. She's going now.
(She's doing a run-up in order to accelerate her speed.)
Mina, run! Mina.
- That's great! - Mina, keep running!
(Screaming)
She jumped far behind the line too.
It's 2m 16cm.
That was close.
Next up is Ji Hyo!
I think Ji Hyo can do this well.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Ha Ra keeps complaining that her pants were too long.
She's complaining.
Stop it.
- That's enough. - She's disappointed. That's all.
- Don't wear wide pants to shoots. - She's disappointed.
- Don't wear such pants for shows. - It's just a shame.
- She was too far behind. - I should change my pants.
When she did her jump, did you know that...
she made the flapping sound of a robe?
- Like a pigeon flapping. - That's right.
I saw several pigeons emerging from her pants.
- I saw pigeons emerging. - People wear them for kendo.
Da Hee, listen to the conversation.
(Focused)
She keeps looking at the mat.
It's not going according to her plan today.
(Da Hee is completely focused on the match.)
- They must not cross the line. - It's not going as she planned.
When I heard this, I was so shocked.
- I got the chills. - What is it?
She was an athlete for long jumping.
- At that time... - When?
- I doubt it. Her limbs are short. - And then what?
- Don't let that bother you. - Hey!
- What? - Don't let him get to you.
(He manages to provoke her.)
Ji Hyo will try now.
- Bring it back - Bring it back
- Why are you singing it? - The title resembles her nickname.
- I see. - Bring it back
You're forcing the pun.
They're making all sorts of puns.
(She displays the look of a real athlete.)
Get ready. Start!
There you go, Ji Hyo.
She will turn 40 soon.
(Oh, my goodness)
(This is unbelievable.)
This is the spot.
(Please)
- 36. - Gosh.
(Ji Hyo is placed 3rd.)
- Currently, In A is... - Yes?
- leading by 1cm. - I see.
Da Hee will go last now.
- It's her last chance. - The last chance.
- Long jumping was her talent. - You can do it, Da Hee.
Start.
(Will Da Hee, the talent owner, be able to reclaim 1st place?)
Please step on the line. Step on the line.
(Please)
Great!
(She makes a powerful jump.)
(It utterly shocks everyone.)
- 8... 85? - My gosh.
(What's the result of her jump that shocked everyone?)
- 8... 85? It's 85! - My gosh.
(Impressed)
(Da Hee sets a new record of 2m 85m.)
This concludes that the first round...
- goes to Da Hee and Se Chan. - Awesome!
You were amazing, Da Hee.
- She's amazing. - She's incredible.
In A, you did well. You were so cool.
Let's put it here.
(Thanks to Da Hee's victory,)
(Se Chan and Da Hee acquire 1 sticker.)
Let me choose the next round.
- Let me pick. - Please.
- "Nostalgic Dance". Whose is it? - Nostalgic Dance.
(Nostalgic Dance)
Nostalgic Dance.
That's So Min's.
(It's So Min's talent.)
- That's right. - Nostalgic Dance.
(Her best talent is doing the nostalgic dances.)
Actually, So Min...
once trained to become an idol singer.
- No, that's not true. - So...
- Faceless Singer. - Right.
- Voiceless Singer. - Singer...
- No, it's Faceless Singer. - Why?
How could a singer be voiceless?
- It's because she can't sing. - I'm a bad singer.
- Hence, the name. - It's Faceless Singer.
- I can't sing. - All right.
- So Min should start us off. - That's right.
- Right. - So Min, it's your time.
- Let's move back. - Break a leg.
Here's the music.
I wish it's a song I know.
Break a leg, So Min.
- This... - Go for it.
I don't know the dance to this song. How could I know this?
("Good Time" by Cleo)
- I can't dance to this. - Do sexy and cute moves.
- It's So Min's time. - You're the best!
(She changes all of a sudden.)
(She does the key dance moves for the song.)
(This 33-year-old woman looks adorable and sexy.)
You're doing great!
(She's summoning Cleo. People of 1999, reply to this.)
You're great.
Let's change. Let's change the song.
(Her unfulfilled dream of an idol singer...)
- This move was so long time ago. - She's actually good.
- I haven't seen that dance in ages. - Exactly.
- She did it. - That was great.
- Great. - She's good at it.
So Min, you're excellent.
(The second song is...)
("Twist King" by Turbo from 1996.)
Look at her. That was sudden.
(She dances as soon as the song is played.)
My goodness. She knows the dance.
- She knows it. That's correct. - Is that it?
- She's doing it right. - So Min.
She's incredible indeed.
So Min is good at dancing.
I can't believe she actually knows it.
(She twists her feet zealously.)
(I'm the master of nostalgic dance!)
That's good. That's enough.
That's it. Let's stop here.
Well done.
- So Min, you did a great job. - That was excellent.
- You did it. - You were amazing!
- She's good. - Everyone.
So Min did such a great job with it.
- She was incredible. - She did well as expected.
She did make the dance look like it's from the old days.
Can they just go for it if they feel confident?
- Sorry? - Can they just go for it?
If you're confident, anyone can go for it.
- Oh, really? - Let's continue.
Please. I hope it's a song I know.
(What's the first song for Nostalgic Dance?)
("Why Do You" by Chul Yi and Mi Ae)
Mina went for it. That's it!
(As soon as the song is played,)
(Mina and In A go for it.)
- Mina knows the dance! - In A, move forward.
- Great. - There you go. Move forward.
(It's a cutthroat battle to take the center spot.)
You're doing great.
That was awesome, In A.
- That was nice. - That was awesome, Mina!
- Way to go, In A! - You're doing great, In A!
Mina!
(In A pulls out a hidden card.)
Mina, please go back.
Mina, wait.
Wait.
- Wait. - You were amazing.
- In A. - Mina, please wait.
- In A has so much energy. - In A wins.
Both were great though.
Next song.
(The next song is...)
All the songs are very old.
- Come in. - This is me.
("Mister" by Kara)
(The original singer joins.)
(Let me try too.)
Kara!
(Ha Ra versus In A versus Mina)
(The "Mister" dance is perfectly reproduced.)
(Ha Ra is owning the stage.)
This is me.
Nice.
Let Ha Ra win.
- This is me. - We have no choice.
- She has to win. - "This is me."
- "This is me." - "I'm Koo Ha Ra."
"This is me."
We have no choice.
- I'm surprised by Mina. - Right.
Her moves are so...
- So energetic. - What did you do?
That's not how you do it.
(Determined)
(The original singer gives strict instructions.)
Nice.
Let's start the game now.
Like I said, the champion...
- The champion has an advantage? - has an advantage.
They can join last.
- Join when you want. - Join at the last minute.
The music will keep playing.
Reflecting everyone's opinions...
- We'll... - Let's eliminate them one by one.
We'll eliminate them one by one.
If it's getting too fierce?
Play the music.
(Music starts.)
Do you know this one? It's Lee Jung Hyun.
- This is mine. - Too bad for Mina.
("Wa" by Lee Jung Hyun)
- Just dance as you want. - Here we go.
She's so good.
Let's go, Mina!
(The 1999-born reinterprets "Wa".)
- You don't know the dance? - It suits the song.
- She doesn't know the song? - Let's go, Mina!
Let's do this!
In A comes onto the stage.
In A.
(Pushing)
Let's go.
(After pushing Mina away, In A starts to techno dance.)
Mina is eliminated.
(She's getting into the zone.)
- That's what we're talking about. - She's so good.
She's so passionate.
- Way to go! - She's so enthusiastic.
Nice.
That's Lee Jung Hyun.
Go, Da Hee! Nice!
- Great! - That's Lee Jung Hyun.
- That's Lee Jung Hyun. - Amazing.
Way to go!
(Powerful)
(She owns the stage with her appearance and dance.)
That's exactly like Lee Jung Hyun!
We can't beat that!
We can't do this.
(She's having her moment.)
- Gosh. - Da Hee did it!
- Da Hee! - It's over.
- Da Hee wins. - No one can beat that.
Da Hee wins.
- No one can beat that. - Da Hee wins.
- Da Hee wins. - No one can beat that.
Let her win.
- You win. - You win.
I thought Lee Jung Hyun really came.
Look at this.
She couldn't even try after preparing this.
Because of Da Hee, she couldn't even try.
Too bad. She should have tried.
It's unbelievable.
Da Hee is...
- threatening the others. - She is.
Da Hee, how did you wait until today?
- Da Hee and Ha Ra... - She's unrivaled.
Next song.
(The next song is...)
It's "Coming-of-Age Ceremony".
(Da Hee and Ha Ra are getting ready.)
This is...
(Crowded)
Something is weird.
(So Min's moves are accurate.)
Look at So Min.
(Stiff)
Something is weird.
- Something is weird. - Da Hee, you're eliminated.
(Someone weirder lies down.)
(I feel tired today.)
What is she doing?
Look at So Min.
- Way to go! - It's a mess.
- What is this? - What is she doing?
That's hilarious.
- Da Hee. - Nice!
- Da Hee. - That's amazing.
You're good.
(Climax)
(I'm...)
(the dancing queen...)
(here.)
Okay. It's over.
- Good job, Ha Ra. - You did great.
Good job, So Min.
- Is it okay to roll on the floor? - That was hilarious.
- These three are not okay. - Good job.
Is it okay to roll on the floor?
I thought Ha Ra collapsed.
I thought it was the red carpet.
I thought...
it was the red carpet. I was so surprised.
Da Hee, you're doing great,
but I don't want to see that facial expression.
"It's my turn."
(Music is the only drug allowed by the law.)
- It was so annoying. - She can't hide it.
Her emotions show on her face.
She can't hide anything.
This is the final round.
Let's see who wins.
In A is so cool.
In A picked a song herself.
She learned how to dance.
- In A is... - She's so good.
She's like a clubber.
- Play the music. - Go, In A!
("Bang Bang Bang" by BIGBANG)
(From head to toe,)
(she's so cool.)
This is amazing.
Let's go!
(Powerful)
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
(She's full of hiphop spirit.)
(She looks professional.)
My face is so red.
(She throws her cap.)
She's doing something.
- She's doing something. - She's doing something.
What was that?
(Freeze)
- Amazing. - What was that?
Oh, my.
What was that?
Was that really necessary?
Was that necessary?
(Respect)
Nothing can beat a freeze.
Can you show us one more time?
I can't believe it.
- She's so strong. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Impressed)
I'm tired.
Can you do it?
- Ha Ra. - She wants to try.
How do you do it?
You don't know? Do you want to learn it now?
- 1, 2, 3... - 1, 2, 3...
- Put your arms down. - Okay.
Go down and put your forehead on the floor.
Get your feet off the floor.
(Ha Ra falls.)
(Falling)
Ha Ra, go back.
Hold on. Da Hee came to me...
and asked...
if "1, 2, 3" was really necessary.
- Is "1, 2, 3" necessary? - Da Hee, come here.
She was wondering.
- Da Hee, try. - No.
- She doesn't think it's necessary. - No.
- She thinks she can do it. - Try it.
- Try. - How are you going to do it?
You don't need the first part.
You just have to support yourself with your arms.
- Right? - Yes.
- She might be able to do it. - Like this...
Will it really be okay if this airs?
Like this...
(She rolls on the floor.)
- Da Hee. - What's with you?
What did she do?
- Mina, can you do it? - Try it.
You can do it.
Put your elbow here.
- Why are they learning it? - Here.
- In A prepared so much. - Let's go.
- Put your forehead on the floor. - It must be hard.
- Let's do this. - You need strength.
(Screaming)
What was that sound?
(She sounds like a pterosaur.)
- What was that sound? - It must be hard.
- What was that? - What did you do?
This is Jurassic Park.
It was a pterosaur.
- Did you make that sound? - Did you?
What was that scream?
Who made that sound?
Mina, what was it?
It's such a mess.
Put your hands down.
- And your leg. - Okay.
Put your forehead down.
Lift your legs.
- Lift your legs. - Lift your legs.
(Thump)
What was that? Did someone fart?
What was that sound?
(She can't control her body.)
- She's annoyed. - She'll be 40 soon.
She'll be 40 soon.
- How do you do it? - In A is amazing.
Did In A win?
- She wins, right? - She's amazing.
This is the final round.
- So Min has... - Right.
- Please play an old song. - another chance.
- This is the last song. - Go.
(The last song is "I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S.)
- So Min. - S.E.S.
- I like S.E.S. - Let's go!
("I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S)
(As soon as the song starts,)
(So Min becomes immersed.)
(Mina joins.)
Mina even knows this dance.
Mina.
She knows every dance.
(The song was released 2 years before she was born.)
S.E.S!
Here comes Da Hee!
(The real one is here.)
(Da Hee looks exactly like Bada.)
Ji Hyo.
(The 2018 version of S.E.S)
- No one can stop Da Hee. - No.
Seriously.
(She's the best entertainer today.)
She is amazing.
They're S.E.S.
That's good enough.
(The fierce dance battle ends.)
Where did she get the hair tie?
Is she some crook?
- Take away her hair tie. - She's a crook.
Did she invite a makeup team?
- Let me say something. - Wait.
Why did this team get a private dressing room?
- That's not it. - Everyone else stays here,
but you enter from back there.
(She's prepared to act like Lee Jung Hyun.)
(She even looks like Ba Da.)
(Where does she get changed?)
- She needs time to do makeup. - What?
- She needs to change. - My goodness.
- Everyone. - She's like a crook.
We have a winner.
They're Da Hee and Se Chan.
(Based on the votes, Se Chan and Da Hee win.)
(They win twice consecutively.)
This is her day.
I'm jealous.
She's like a crook.
Everyone, it's the first time since the segment started.
It's over since we have a winner.
Okay.
(They win with 3 R Stickers.)
(Se Chan and Da Hee win a Chance Card.)
As a result, Seok Jin and So Min come in last.
Please reveal your numbers.
- Do we both reveal it? - Yes, both of you.
(Both must show their numbers.)
People will want my number once they find out.
What is Seok Jin's number?
(Seok Jin's number is 3.)
- Three. - That's tricky.
- It's a tricky number. - Three.
(3 is a tricky number.)
It's a tricky number.
So Min?
- It's 2. - 2.
That's a good number.
- Yes, it is. - Okay.
The highest total as of now is...
12.
(The highest total is 12.)
Does that mean a couple has 6 and 6?
The lowest total is...
The highest total as of now is...
12.
(The highest total is 12.)
Does that mean a couple has 6 and 6?
The lowest total is...
- 5. - That was us.
(Seok Jin and So Min's total is 5.)
- It was us. - Why did you whistle?
We should break that couple.
The winning couple must break them.
For Se Chan and Da Hee who won,
only one of you gets a Chance Card. Play rock-paper-scissors.
I will win.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. - Se Chan.
- Step to the front. - Okay.
(He gets a chance to switch partners.)
Which number would you like to know?
Female player who has number one.
- Female player? - Yes.
Female player that has number one...
is Mina.
(It's Mina.)
(In that case...)
It's Mina.
I have no idea.
- Tell us. - No.
Gosh, it's too general.
Se Chan, would you like to switch partners?
(What will Se Chan choose?)
I will be...
partners with Mina.
(He exchanges with Kwang Soo.)
- I'm sorry. - Who?
It was fun.
- Gosh. - Mina.
- Change partners. - Hello.
- It's nice to meet you. - Who has 6 and 6?
- She looks happier than before. - We were perfect.
Da Hee looks so happy now.
They look good together as well.
They're the perfect height for each other.
- They look the best together. - Really?
- I agree. - Yes.
You two look good as well.
- He looks like her manager. - That's right.
- He looks like a good deacon. - I'm always ready to go.
Shall we move on?
(What will be the result of the switch?)
Meal Card and Chance Card are on the line for the next mission.
Even Meal Cards?
It's called Our Lunch Link.
(Our Lunch Link)
Partners will be linked by the wrists and search for...
the members' name stickers that are hidden in the hotel.
Attach the stickers on the Top and Bottom roulettes.
The selected couple from the Top roulette wins Korean beef steak...
- and a Chance Card. - Korean beef steak?
(Winner from the Top roulette gets Korean beef steak and Chance Card.)
The rest of the couples will get sandwiches.
The selected couple from the Bottom roulette...
gets rice with dried laver and must reveal their numbers.
All couples will start after linking their wrists.
Let's get it. Let's hurry.
- Get it, get it. - Let's go.
Let's go.
- This is great. - It's a nice place.
There's a lot here.
We must win no matter what.
- Jae Seok, we can't separate. - What?
Do you have number six?
(Jae Seok had number 6.)
(The highest total...)
(is 12. That means...)
(That means Ji Hyo's number is 6 as well.)
- Yes, I have number six. - That's amazing.
How can we both have six?
(They must keep it a secret.)
Be quiet so that no one finds out.
How can we search in such a big place?
- Da Hee. - Yes?
Which number does Se Chan have?
- Se Chan's number? - Yes.
- Am I allowed to tell you? - Of course.
You won't be partners with Se Chan again.
Is your number high or low?
- Mine? - Yes.
Shouldn't we know our place since we're a team?
The writer told me that...
- I can believe everyone but you. - What?
What are you talking about?
Da Hee, you must tell each other...
so that we know our place.
Tell me if your number is high or low.
- It's a high number. - Is it high?
Yes, what's your number?
- Mine? - Yes.
My number is six.
- Is it six? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
- You have six? - Yes.
(However, they're the couple with 6's.)
(She's a trickster like Kwang Soo.)
What's your number?
- What is it? - Mine is two.
Is your number six?
Yes, what's your number again?
- To be honest... - Be honest with me.
- You shouldn't lie about it. - Let's show each other.
(They decide to show the number.)
Show me. One.
- In 3, 2, 1. - In 3, 2, 1.
- You didn't take it out. - Come on.
- Don't do it. - Is it six?
Is it six? I'll show you mine.
- In three. - Put it down here.
- Put it down. - Is this necessary?
- Let it go. - Why won't you believe me?
Throw it down.
- In 3, 2, 1. - In 3, 2, 1.
(They hesitate.)
(They're perfect for each other.)
You're a cheater, aren't you?
- No. In 3, 2, 1. - In 3, 2, 1.
(It's a big mess.)
- What? - Okay.
- I got it. Give me one chance. - You're so...
- You're so terrible. - Okay.
- You're terrible. - I won't look. I put it down.
Give it back.
(Was Kwang Soo telling the truth?)
(It's 5.)
(She's angry that he lied to her.)
You said that yours was six.
- It's not. - I thought it was.
I thought it was six.
Aren't we on the same team?
Yes, we are.
You told me that yours was two. What I said was better.
The difference is only one.
Why does the difference matter?
- I bet there's something here. - I agree.
(They look around.)
- Where? - There it is.
(They're the first to find a name sticker.)
- There it is. - Okay.
- Let's go and stick it. - Let's go. What is it?
- It's Jae Seok and Ji Hyo. - There's a lot.
(They find Jae Seok and Ji Hyo's names.)
- Let's go to Room 1509. - Let's stick them there.
Then look for more.
Where is it? Look, Seok Jin.
- Where? - Seok Jin.
Where? This is amazing.
We found more. It's us.
(They find their own names.)
(Stick them on the Top roulette and win Korean beef steak.)
(Other teams find name stickers.)
- We found them. - This is great.
Let's split them just in case.
Okay.
- No one has been here. - Okay.
(They're the first.)
Okay, Jae Seok and Ji Hyo.
Let's stick them right away.
(Let's win steak and the Chance Card.)
- Okay. - We're safe now.
Let's find other people's.
- We're on the Bottom roulette. - They're on the Top roulette.
Gosh, we got unlucky.
It's over.
Is it over?
We'll determine the winner and loser by turning the roulettes.
Let's have Mina turn the Top roulette.
1, 2, 3.
That's great, Mina. Let's go.
- Mina. - Please, Mina.
We have a high chance of winning.
(They have 3 names on the Top roulette.)
- No. - Don't do that.
- Okay. - Keep going.
- Yes! - We won!
(Jong Kook and Ha Ra win.)
We got it.
It's us, Ha Ra.
- We had three. - We got it.
We have four.
We have too many.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo's teams have 4 each.)
Do you know how many weeks I've been eating that?
Drink water.
Who would like to spin the roulette?
Da Hee can do it.
- Do you trust me, Kwang Soo? - Of course.
Trust what? That was random.
In 1, 2, 3.
Give me a fist bump.
(Give me some energy, my partner.)
- She's unlucky now. - Let's go.
(He spreads the unlucky energy.)
Kwang Soo has bad luck. Why did she fist bump him?
She's going to do poorly.
(She spins the roulette with the unlucky energy.)
She's going to get unlucky because of the fist bump.
It won't be us.
But she fist bumped you.
- True. - Please let it be Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok.
(He gets to eat rice and seaweed for 5 weeks in a row.)
You get seaweed for the fifth week.
(He's sick of this simple menu.)
Let's see your numbers.
This shouldn't have happened.
Remember what I said?
What is your number, Jae Seok?
It's six.
- It's six? - See?
- They have the highest numbers. - They have 6 and 6.
- Her number is important. - What is your number, Ji Hyo?
- They have 6 and 6. - My gosh.
- We know now. - Isn't that incredible?
Hey.
If you have 4 or 5, you have to take theirs.
Do rock-paper-scissors, Ha Ra and Jong Kook.
- You have to split. - Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Ha Ra wins.)
- We know the highest. - Yes, right.
- I have to decide. - Don't we know the lowest too?
(Whose number will Ha Ra ask?)
(She's curious.)
(She hears the answer. What would she do?)
I'll eat first.
(I'll think about it as I eat.)
Thank you for the food.
(Everybody but Jae Seok and Ji Hyo enjoys lunch.)
(The steak melts in my mouth.)
This is not just any sandwich. It's like a dish.
- It's really good. - Really?
Yes, the meat is soft.
Excuse me.
Is it good?
Of course. There's so much steak.
It's so good.
- Is the seaweed good? - It is,
but I've been having this for five weeks.
Put your head down, and eat.
- What? - Put your head down, and eat.
That's rude. You want me to put my head down and eat?
Put your head down, and eat.
- Here. - Jae Seok.
Jae Seok.
(What do you think? Doesn't it look good?)
Stop doing that.
It's really good.
(Have some, Jae Seok.)
(Have my finger.)
(He knew it would be like this.)
- Hey. - That was mean.
You put your finger in?
That was so cute.
Please give me a bite.
(Give me a bite.)
(Screaming)
(Ji Hyo joins as well.)
- Jong Kook. - It's so good.
Can I have a piece of the steak?
You have a cold.
- Ha Ra has a cold as well. - He'll catch a cold.
Both Ha Ra and I have a cold,
- but why is she fine and I'm not? - He'll catch a cold.
- I catch colds easily. - Mina.
(She coughs on the steak.)
Da Hee.
I'm a sea elephant.
(He tries to get a bite of Da Hee's sandwich.)
(Isn't it funny? Don't you want to give me a bite?)
(Give a bite to the sea elephant.)
Whose is this?
(He bites into Kwang Soo's sandwich.)
Hey.
There's no meat.
Where's the meat?
(There's no meat in the sandwich?)
(The meat is missing. Who took it?)
What happened to the meat?
Is it gone?
(It was chaotic 1 minute ago.)
(Lifting)
(Da Hee grabbed the meat...)
(and stole it.)
(She covered up her crime because Jae Seok came by.)
What? What happened?
What happened to my meat?
Hey.
(She tries to keep a poker face.)
Did you eat mine?
(She fails.)
No, right? Where's my meat?
Let me see your pocket.
You ate it, right? Open your mouth.
Open your mouth.
- Open your mouth. Where is it? - Hey.
- What happened to the meat? - My meat...
(Give me my meat back.)
No.
(Justice is served.)
(They quarrel several times today.)
(Give me my meat.)
(Give me some too.)
(She kept the meat.)
Gosh, Da Hee.
She wasn't like that before.
Da Hee wasn't like that.
(I like meat more as I get older.)
Ji Hyo.
I got some meat for you.
Put some meat on top.
Look.
(This is sad.)
- Ji Hyo. - Goodness.
- I'm going to cry. - Heungbu...
Heungbu is not a fictional character.
Don't just eat the seaweed. Eat some meat too.
He's so desperate.
- See? - My gosh.
(Grabbing)
(He steals Jae Seok's food in his own way.)
Gosh.
Look at him.
If you're done eating, let's see what Ha Ra will do.
(It's time for Ha Ra to switch her teams.)
It's okay, Ha Ra. I've had the water bomb on me many times.
(It's okay, Ha Ra. I'll honor your decision.)
I...
will change.
She's going to switch.
- Yes. - With whom?
(Whom is she going to switch Jong Kook with?)
Jae Seok.
(She wants to be a couple with Jae Seok.)
She has a high number too.
Ji Hyo and Ha Ra, please switch seats.
Hold on. Are Jong Kook and Ji Hyo a couple then?
Why is it them?
What? Is there something going on?
Do we finally get to see it?
I didn't give her steak earlier.
(We're not in good terms.)
We're not in good terms right now.
(She gets up.)
(Coughing)
Have a seaweed, Jong Kook.
It's okay, Ji Hyo.
I have meat. Have some.
- Have some. - You like meat. You can have it.
No, it's for you.
You like meat.
No, Ji Hyo. Take it.
What's this?
- Are you insane? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - What's this?
I'm celebrating.
What are you doing?
What's that?
- Is he celebrating again? - Why?
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are back together, so it's a happy occasion.)
- Does he want the meat? - That's for me?
(They move to the final location now.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(A college in Jeju Island)
There are...
- so many new things in Jeju Island. - This looks awesome.
Goodness.
(Their eyes open wide.)
- This is awesome. - What's that?
(There are toys everywhere.)
- Look. - Goodness.
Look at the stadium.
(Their average age is 40, but they're still amazed.)
These are all blocks.
(Is there something more?)
- Gosh. - Goodness.
That's me.
These are blocks as well.
- It says "Running Man". - It does.
It's written here.
This is the final mission...
where you get to earn a Chance Card.
- We have to win here. - The winner takes all.
The final mission is called the Pirate Roulette Quiz.
Because it's the pirate?
- Each couple gets 40 knives. - Okay.
Listen to the question, and if you want a chance to answer,
insert the number of knives you want in the Betting Pirate.
If the pirate doesn't pop up, you win the bet.
The couple who bets the most knives gets to answer.
I know this. I'll explain.
But there's something else.
(It's not that simple.)
You have to insert the number of knives...
according to the multiple choice in the Answer Pirate.
You only get to answer if the pirate doesn't pop up.
For example, if the answer is two,
you have to insert two knives into the Answer Pirate.
If we don't win, we lose.
(The couple with the most number of knives wins.)
Before we start the last mission,
I'll tell you the highest and lowest combination of numbers.
The highest number combination...
is 10.
- 10? - What?
(We have the highest numbers.)
We were right.
The lowest number combination...
- is 2. - 2?
- It's not us. - 1 and 1?
- Two? - Does that make sense?
(There's a couple who's lower than Seok Jin and So Min?)
(The male member who had 1...)
(was Se Chan.)
(With the Chance Card,)
(he got to partner up with Mina.)
Mina.
- We don't know each other's. - We don't.
Excuse me.
Mina is acting right now.
(Look at her face.)
- I'm disappointed, Mina. - She's playing dumb.
- You lied when we were eating. - What?
No, you have to see the end result.
Earlier,
Se Chan switched with Kwang Soo for a higher number.
They must be 1 and 1.
- It's them or them. - But...
it's not us.
You're going to reveal who's in first place, right?
Can you not say anything, Kwang Soo?
- Stop saying anything. - It must be them.
- It's them or them. - It's them.
It's them. She's not saying anything.
Da Hee is not saying anything.
No, that's not it.
- What is it? - Just...
I just want to play the game.
- You're the weirdest at the moment. - No.
What are you talking about?
It's them.
(The couple with the lowest numbers is not suspected anymore.)
It's Da Hee. It's in her name.
Let's get started. We have to play first.
- Please give us the question. - All right.
Here's the first question.
In Korean,
what's the word for "continuing to do the same work"?
This is too easy.
One, Gabdori.
Two, Samdori.
Three, Sundori.
Is that it?
Four, Gomdori.
"Gomdori"?
Five, Baedori.
Five! I mean, answer.
(Shouting)
I know.
- That's not what you do. - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Do something about her. - We're not two.
We're not two.
Why is she doing that?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
- Why is she trying so hard to win? - She's suspicious.
Switch. Okay.
- What is wrong with her? - I'm sorry.
(We need to bet first, right?)
Please bet. You can bet after saying, "answer".
- Do you know this? - It's five, Baedori.
Really?
- Answer. - Answer.
How many would you like to bet?
We'll bet seven.
- That's a lot. - Answer.
- It's too... - We'll bet eight.
Eight?
If the pirate pops up, they're done for.
Let's go. In 1, 2, 3.
- Okay. - It's my turn.
You have to insert all the knives.
It's shaking.
Okay. One more. Please.
- Please, In A. - Pop up.
Okay.
You have to insert eight knives.
We'll do that.
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous every time we do this.
- Should we take turns inserting? - Sure.
Pop up. I hope it explodes.
I want it to pop up.
Jae Seok is nasty.
- Kwang Soo... - Okay.
(Kwang Soo succeeds despite Jae Seok's remark.)
- As long as you don't lose... - If we win, we get a chance.
I know. You have to be careful.
No.
This is dangerous. It's risky from now on.
We know the answer.
Okay.
One more. Let's go.
- Pop up. Make this fun. - Pop up.
Da Hee, if you lose here, you're the real star.
You're the best entertainer.
- Da Hee knows the exact answer. - The queen of variety shows.
- The queen of variety shows. - The queen of variety shows.
Here I go!
Okay.
(They win by betting 8 knives.)
- You have to bet two more. - Let's go.
- They're doing it. - Good job.
- Let's go. - Great.
- Please. - You have no choice.
(Please)
(They get one.)
Do the next one.
I think you're good at this.
This is unbelievable.
Please. Please.
Okay.
(Shrieking)
(They lose the bet.)
(Things were going too well.)
(She makes weird noises.)
Before she finished hearing the options, she knew the answer.
Insert the number of knives according to the multiple choice.
(They get to answer after inserting the knives in the Answer Pirate.)
If the pirate pops up, they're done, right?
If the pirate pops up, they're done.
The answer is...
number two.
Number two?
- Samdori. - Right.
- Samdori? - That's not true.
- Insert 2 knives. - Isn't it 5, Baedori?
- She was certain. - Really?
Really?
Isn't it Baedori?
(She bet 2, instead of 5.)
- Pop up. - The queen of variety shows.
(If they win here, they get to answer.)
Okay.
Answer?
- What's the answer? - Maybe they're right.
- They said Samdori. - Samdori?
Two, Samdori...
(It's wrong.)
It's wrong.
(It's not Samdori.)
- I think they're done. - They lost it.
This is awesome.
(They lost even more.)
Let's get a new Betting Pirate.
- We'll get a new one. - A new one?
The betting starts over?
I'm not certain. We'll bet seven.
- How many do we have to do? - Think about this.
Eight?
What's the answer?
(We lost 10 already.)
So what if the pirate doesn't pop up?
Let's go.
(She's uneasy.)
- Please. - This one could be funny too.
Let's do this.
- Let's go. - Please.
- This one could be funny too. - Let's go.
Ha Ra, one more.
The queen of variety shows.
- Ha Ra. - Okay.
- Don't feel pressured. - Jae Seok.
Okay, good.
Good job.
(Jae Seok is unusually bold, and they bet 7.)
- Come on. - Nice.
This is great.
What's the answer?
Which option is it?
- It's 5. - It's 2.
- It's 5, Baedori. - 5, Baedori?
- Please insert the knives. - It's five, Baedori.
Please pop up.
(They have to insert 5 knives.)
I don't know.
Please.
(She's careful.)
Pop up. Pop up.
- There's one left. - It'll pop up.
Please let this be funny.
You have many spaces left.
(Jae Seok is usually unlucky.)
Pop up.
- Pop up. - Gosh.
(They get a chance to answer.)
- Nice. - Five, Baedori.
(It's wrong.)
- Yes. - Yes.
(It's not 5?)
(This is so much fun.)
This is awesome.
This is driving me nuts.
What do we do now?
- Answer. - It's Gabdori or Samdori.
- Answer. - We bet six.
- Okay. - All right.
Okay.
- We'll bet. - You have to bet seven.
We'll bet seven.
- I'll do three this time. - Can they bet?
Do you know the answer?
- Of course. - We can bet.
- Of course. - I don't know.
Oh, dear.
(In A does it again.)
(She's the new unlucky person.)
- Put that down. - Give up your knives, Haha.
I thought she was lucky.
(She seems to be the unlucky one.)
Let's bet.
(This is her new, hidden talent.)
Let's give up.
What's the answer?
We'll go with three, Sundori.
Three, Sundori. Please insert the knives.
- Please don't pop up. - You can't pop up.
It'll be really funny if it does.
Goodness.
(It'll be really funny if it does.)
(Goodness)
This is great. Let's do this.
Let's bet.
Does this make sense?
(Great job, Pirate.)
Nice.
We'll be done in one round.
It's like what I made him do for the TV rating notice.
His can is always empty.
(It's exactly like the reality.)
Is the can yours?
(The pirate is reborn again.)
- How many are you betting? - I'm betting seven.
- This is unbelievable. - We were almost there.
(The pirate keeps on popping up.)
This is unbelievable.
What just happened?
I'm sorry.
Is that even possible?
- We'll bet seven. - Okay.
Let's get it back.
- Ji Hyo. - I'll take three.
Do four. You're lucky.
How did you do that, Kwang Soo?
Do you know before you do it?
- It'll be awesome if it pops up. - He can't know.
I guess it could happen.
Pop up.
They're too...
lucky.
Ji Hyo, can you insert it in a bad spot?
(The pirate is quiet now.)
We'll go. We bet eight.
Eight.
Please.
It has to pop up.
It has to pop up for us.
- Slow down. - It has to pop up.
- Good. - It has to happen.
It has to pop up.
My gosh. You potty pants.
(My gosh.)
(You potty pants.)
Hey.
- That was great. - You're so unlucky.
- You're so unlucky. - What is she doing now?
Why are you doing that all of a sudden?
- She's the female Kwang Soo. - This is great.
That was diarrhea.
That was poop.
Please.
- This is over. - The answer is...
- four, Gomdori. - Gomdori?
Is it really Gomdori?
How many did we lose?
- That was shocking. - Wasn't that around 20?
- They're done. - We're done.
They're all done.
Currently, first place team is...
Se Chan and Mina with 32 knives.
Us?
We didn't bet. They bet eight.
(Here's the last question.)
Here's the last question.
(I'm going to get it right this time.)
During the Joseon Dynasty, if you sent this overnight...
from Namhansanseong Fortress to Seoul, it arrived by daybreak,
so it was called the Daybreak Soup.
This is also the first delivery food in Korea. What is this?
Delivery food?
- From Namhansanseong Fortress? - One, boiled pork.
Two, trotters.
Three, chicken soup.
Four, jjajangmyeon.
Five, hangover soup.
- This is difficult. - What kind of question is this?
Answer.
I'll bet 10.
I'll bet 11.
Jae Seok, do you know?
- We have to bet. - Let's watch.
Why did you bet 10?
It's one, boiled pork.
People eat it when they move, right?
I've delivered food. They don't deliver hangover soup.
- Let's do this. - It's 10.
Let's do it together.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Haha gets one.)
What's wrong with her?
(She escapes from the reality.)
She's so unlucky.
- We'll bet 11. - We are 1st.
In A is so unlucky.
She's unbelievable.
How does that happen?
- Let me switch seats. - She didn't succeed once.
It's because I'm next to Kwang Soo.
Why are you blaming it on me?
It starts over, so you don't have to bet 11.
- It starts over. - We'll bet six. Answer.
- In A, you're unbelievable. - She's so unlucky.
She's the female Kwang Soo.
She has to be on the unlucky special.
It always happens to her.
(Staring)
(Grabbing)
She transferred her energy.
She gave him a touch of bad luck.
Two negatives make a positive.
Bad luck plus bad luck is...
(Bad luck plus bad luck...)
(plus bad luck)
My goodness.
(I can't believe him.)
Then you have bad luck.
(Ha Ra tries to salvage the situation.)
Okay.
Please.
(The unlucky man, Jae Seok, begins to place his bet.)
The answer is one.
(She is sure about the answer.)
(Does Da Hee know the answer?)
Trotter didn't exist back then.
I know how the dish came to be.
Really?
Help me.
(Make sure no one finds out about this.)
My goodness.
(He succeeds in placing 6.)
Who knows the answer?
They inserted six knives.
- We will give it a go. - We will give it a go.
- Seven knives. - That's a lot.
Why aren't we going?
We should wait.
(Se Chan plans to watch the others as he is in 1st place.)
If the pirate pops up at our turn,
another team will win.
We don't need to take that risk.
Da Hee knows the answer to this question.
Da Hee knows the origin of every dish.
- Really? - Yes.
Not every dish.
The pirate will pop up.
Da Hee will make the pirate pop up.
They might fail.
Let's insert the knives together and share the responsibility.
- Okay. - That's a good idea.
(If that's what you want, I can oblige.)
All right.
Let's insert at the count of three.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Da Hee inserts hers, but Kwang Soo doesn't.)
You are so mean. You are an utter jerk, aren't you?
(You are so mean. You are an utter jerk, aren't you?)
(An utter jerk)
(She calls him an utter jerk in a fit of anger.)
An utter jerk!
"You are so mean. You are an utter jerk, aren't you?"
Today,
Da Hee even made a popular phrase.
"You are so mean. You are an utter jerk, aren't you?"
I am sorry. I will insert my knife.
Go.
No, no.
Okay!
(Kwang Soo and Da Hee succeed in betting 7 knives.)
Da Hee knows the origin of every dish.
No, I don't.
Jae Seok, are you going to bet more?
(13 out of 24 slots are filled.)
Jae Seok. Jae Seok. Are you going to bet more?
- That's a good idea. - Are you going to bet more?
- What? - Are you going to bet more?
- He is highly likely to fail. - Are you going to bet more?
Let me tell you this.
If we answer first, we will get the question right.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- Go. - Let's go.
Go.
- Let's go, Jae Seok. - Let's go.
Let's go. You know the answer.
The pirate might pop up.
It's okay. Let's go.
Ha Ra won't pick the wrong slot.
Ha Ra, go.
Ha Ra is sleeping.
I feel like she is inserting it in my stomach.
Hold on. For goodness' sake.
It's okay.
Didn't she sound like a middle-aged woman just now?
Hold on.
(Hold on, Pirate.)
(Ha Ra succeeds.)
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
There aren't a lot of open slots.
(While 9 slots remain,)
(Kwang Hee puts his faith in Da Hee and bets more.)
- We will bet more. - They are cool.
I hope it pops up.
Do you want to insert together?
- Okay. - Do you promise?
Insert the knife on my mark this time.
If they insert the knives together, they will share the responsibility.
That's why I suggested it.
- If we do this, we will win. - We can do this.
Insert it at the count of three.
- Okay. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Victory depends on the last question.)
(Since she claims to know the answer,)
(the tall ones decide to take a leap of faith.)
In 1, 2, 3.
- I can't believe you! - No, no.
(Kwang Soo's hand doesn't move.)
I missed my cue. I missed my cue.
Hey,
how could you miss the cue when I counted to three?
It happened too quickly.
Had you said it slowly, I would've done it correctly.
She is so cute. My goodness.
In 1, 2, 3. Then you insert.
You should have said it slowly.
- You went, "In 1, 2, 3." - You are an utter jerk.
- It happened too quickly. - You are an utter jerk.
Hurry up, and insert the knife. I will watch you.
I didn't pick the bad slot.
- I didn't pick the bad slot. - This is driving me crazy.
(A big shadow watches the utter jerk.)
It will pop up.
(Serious)
Kwang Soo, I will be really angry if you make it pop up.
She will be through with you.
Da Hee knows the answer.
(Kwang Soo meets the biggest crisis.)
(What is his fate?)
(Next week)
(The unlucky ones strike.)
(This is the curse of pirate roulette game.)
(What will become of the fire moth couple?)
(The 2nd Jeju Island Special, Hopscotch Race)
(Jae Seok's team and Seok Jin's team have a face-off.)
(Who will take the attractions of Jeju Island?)
(They are serious.)
(This piece of land is ours.)
(We can't let you have it.)
(They have a scramble to take more land in Jeju Island.)
(Is there a traitor in the team?)
(The sly traitors aim to sell the land,)
(and the loyal strategists aim to defend the land.)
(Who will come out on top in this dirty fight?)
All of us will fall to the pit today.
(The 2nd Jeju Island Special, Hopscotch Race)