- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - The weather is gorgeous.
- Hi. - Ji Hyo is wearing green.
- The weather is gorgeous. - You are right.
- Our outfits suit the weather. - They are wearing colorful clothes.
- Yes, they are. - Only we are wearing dark clothes.
The four of them are like the Teletubbies.
(Guess what I realized.)
- You are right. - It's the Teletubbyland.
- Laa Laa. - You are right.
- Po. - You are right.
- Tinky-Winky. - You know,
this is my first time to see Jong Kook wearing a bright color.
You are Laa Laa.
- He is like the manager of a gym. - You know...
The manager of a gym is going on a picnic.
Seriously.
Isn't it nice that I am wearing a bright color?
(They talk about Jong Kook in a yellow top.)
A bee is attracted to Kwang Soo.
I thought I should go for a bright look.
Don't do that. It's a bee.
What is it?
- What is it? - My goodness!
A bee almost went into my ear.
(My goodness.)
- Was there a bee? - My goodness.
There was nothing on the either one of you.
There was a bee. There was a bee.
- There was a bee. - It went that way.
I heard it.
- Gosh, the two of you are cowards. - I heard it.
(The older members are the most cowardly.)
- His face went red. - I am telling you...
- a bee licked my face. - It doesn't have a tongue!
I am telling you a bee was close to my face.
Don't be ridiculous.
The bee didn't go to Jong Kook.
- What? - He is wearing the same color.
Jong Kook is scarier than a bee.
- He is a wasp. - Jong Kook's words...
- hurt more than a bee sting. - That's right.
- Seriously. - So Min, I see that...
- you didn't miss your flight. - What do you mean?
- After our performance abroad, - She left her passport.
she left her passport at the hotel.
Seok Jin said to her,
"You need to stop being a scatterbrain."
"It makes no sense to leave your passport at the hotel."
But the day before, he left his passport in the car.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
For two days, he didn't realize.
For two days, he didn't realize he had left his passport.
I didn't realize.
You are in no position to patronize her.
When we were having a meal yesterday,
why did you slap Jae Seok?
- What? - When did I slap him?
You slapped him across the face.
(They team up to slander him.)
- I saw it. - You slapped him.
- He didn't do it as a joke. - He slapped hard.
He used the back of his hand.
- You saw it, right? Jae Seok cried. - Jae Seok cried.
What are you talking about?
This is how a rumor starts.
Jae Seok said he cried because Seok Jin's slap was weak.
(Jae Seok said he cried because Seok Jin's slap was weak.)
It broke my heart because I didn't feel a thing.
A fly on my cheek would have felt heavier.
The slap was loud but painless.
You still shouldn't have done it.
The slap is loud but painless.
What was that?
- What is it? - It tickles.
(It suddenly tickles.)
(Seok Jin's slap tickles.)
- What is going on? - Maybe it's an allergic reaction.
- What is going on? - His slap tickles.
The day after Seok Jin hit me, bees swarmed to my cheek.
- He has the Honey Punch. - It was the honey.
Seok Jin also wore a cast the next day.
- My goodness. - Seok Jin, don't hit anyone.
Today, you will have a race in which the ranks are important.
- Okay. - The ranks.
After three different rounds, you will determine the final ranks.
The 1st to 8th ranks will have different benefits...
and the number of Crown Badges...
which gives you an advantage in the final mission.
Let's decide on the ranks.
How will we decide?
- It's a roulette. - Are we using a roulette?
This is good for us.
This is good for us, the youngest members.
The members' names are on the roulette.
The person who gets picked will be in first rank.
Then he or she will decide the rest of the members' ranks.
- All right. - Let my name get picked.
- Let my name get picked. - This is really fair.
It could be anyone.
- Spin it hard. - Let's go. I will spin it hard.
- Let's go. - Please let it be my name.
(The roulette begins to spin.)
(Let's see who will get picked as the 1st rank.)
Come on.
Okay. The timing is perfect.
- It will be me. - It will be me.
(He is desperate.)
- It will be me. - It will be Kwang Soo.
Please don't let it be him.
(The roulette's decision is...)
- No, no! - Yes!
(Kwang Soo gets chosen in a pinch.)
(Here comes the 1st rank.)
- No! - Good job!
No!
This is the worst.
Kwang Soo, the younger members should come together.
(It's our world.)
(Haha, come on.)
- Come here. - Why?
- The younger members. - You are 40 years old!
You are 40 years old.
Lee Kwang Soo is
Our sun
(Let's praise Lee Kwang Soo.)
I love you.
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo.
- My goodness. - Gosh, don't do this.
- Don't do this. - Lee Kwang Soo!
(Falling)
Don't do this.
Gosh, he fell hard.
- Jae Seok did it on purpose. - I think he did it on purpose.
(I am 100-percent sure he did it on purpose.)
Kwang Soo, you are too tall.
- I'm sorry. - Why don't you flick his forehead?
- His forehead? - He flicked your forehead a lot.
- Shall I do that? - Yes.
- He did flick my forehead a lot. - Hold on.
Why would you flick my forehead?
- Can I flick your forehead? - Why?
If you let me do it, I will give you an advantage.
Why don't you just put me in the lowest rank instead?
- Wait. - For goodness' sake!
(What an annoying mouth!)
(He can't flick Jae Seok's forehead.)
Okay. Okay.
Seok Jin is annoyed.
Seok Jin.
What?
Oh, he wants water!
- Move out of my way! It's my task. - Kwang Soo.
- My goodness. - Here is water.
I will take the other one.
(Annoying)
What is wrong with you?
(He is being really annoying.)
Put me in the lowest rank.
What should I do? Should I do it?
He is using a strange tactic.
Do it and see what happens.
Put him in the lowest rank. It won't hurt you.
- Jae Seok. - What is going on?
Think about which standard you will use...
to decide on the ranks. Then it will be fair.
The member you want to go on a blind date with.
Okay.
The member I want to go on a blind date with...
- is Jae Seok without a question. - That's right.
- He will liven up the atmosphere. - That's right.
- And he won't get the girl. - And you look better.
(Those are Kwang Soo's reasons for picking Jae Seok.)
He will make me shine. I will use a different standard.
- You think I make you shine? - Yes.
- That's right. - That's why I'm standing here.
- This is driving me crazy. - That's right.
This is driving me crazy.
(The standard Kwang Soo used to rank everyone remains a secret.)
- I will announce the ranks. - Okay.
Let me come in second.
Please. I will be good to you.
Kwang Soo, remember the younger members.
- Kwang Soo. - Put yourself at ease.
- I... - You can change it up now.
- The younger members. - Let's go.
I will announce the ranks first.
When Jong Kook put his arm on me,
I let him use my shoulder without thinking.
It happens naturally.
I let him use my shoulder.
(Last week, Haha worked as Jong Kook's arm support.)
(Jae Seok succeeded the position without his knowledge.)
(He stuck to Jong Kook like a magnet.)
- I let him use my shoulder. - I see that...
Jong Kook put him on the hook so that he wouldn't run away.
His hand is the hook.
When I put my hand on him, he moved towards me.
- He was like a magnet. - It happens.
It's good as long as you aren't offended.
- I am not offended. - That's right.
It's not like I am going to grow any taller.
- He can put his arm on me. - That's right.
- That's right. - They are like safety bars.
- That's right. - He looks comfortable.
- Let me announce the ranks. - Okay.
(He will announce the ranks.)
(Jong Kook's side is the strongest.)
(Who will be Kwang Soo's right-hand man?)
Jong Kook is the last.
(He is certain.)
(Jong Kook is in the bottom rank.)
He's the lowest.
Jong Kook is in the eighth rank.
(It's a festival.)
I could have worked for you!
No, you are the last. Be glad it's not the 1,000th rank.
This is good.
- The 1st rank is Kwang Soo. - The 2nd rank.
- I will announce the second rank. - Who is it?
- The second rank. - Let's go.
- Come on. - Remember the younger members.
(Who is in the 2nd rank?)
- Haha. - There you go.
My goodness.
(Haha is in the 2nd rank.)
- Why? - He and I have a connection.
- I think I know. - Move down.
- What's this all about? - Please put in the upper ranks.
- Here's how I decided. - Okay.
This is my personal opinion of who dresses well.
(This is the criterion of the ranks.)
- That was my standard. - Then I should be up there.
- Your outfit looks awesome today. - Right.
Then I have a shot.
- You think you have a shot? - You bet I do.
- I should be in the upper ranks. - You think you have a shot?
Is that why I'm placed last?
Whatever the criterion is, you'll be placed last.
(Determine the ranking of your fashion.)
My goodness.
I dress very well.
Here's what I think about Kwang Soo. Putting aside our sense of fashion,
he ranked people based on his grudges.
That's how he ranked us.
He did not rank us based on our outfits.
I always think that I dress very well.
I'm not that happy about this.
Kwang Soo doesn't know anything.
I should be placed first.
- I don't get why Haha is there. - By the way,
- why are you standing there? - Exactly.
What do you mean?
- Can't you see? - Why are you standing there?
- Gosh, all of these are mine. - My goodness, that joker.
Dear me.
You put yellow pickled radishes on your eyes.
(You're ridiculous.)
(The lenses do look like pickled radishes.)
Are you trying to make your head look like a shuttlecock?
- I hate that you don't get this. - This is so annoying.
Actually, Haha's outfit is the coolest.
- Kwang Soo, tell us who's in third. - Yes?
Come on. Try to pay more attention to your outfits.
- Okay? - Here's third place.
- Song Ji Hyo. - That's right.
(Ji Hyo is placed 3rd.)
(As expected, Ji Hyo is in 3rd.)
- Ji Hyo? - I agree with him.
- I should be next. - I...
- It's obvious now. - I'm next.
- I should be in fourth. - Okay.
I'm really torn now. As for the seventh place...
- 7th place? That was sudden. - You'll decide that 1st?
- Is it Jae Seok or Seok Jin? - Right.
- Here's the match. - Hey.
- It's here. Goodness. - It's Jae Seok, of course.
This is a hard one. Seriously. This match is neck and neck.
Kwang Soo.
I have a good sense of fashion, but I don't show it.
I only shop for clothes.
I only shop for clothes. I don't buy anything else.
- Okay. - Pick the fourth place.
I'm not totally satisfied, but...
- Jae Seok is... - Okay.
- in seventh place. - Okay.
(It means Seok Jin is ranked higher than Jae Seok.)
Hey, you. You come here.
- You should go over there. - Seok Jin has won.
- How could Se Chan still be there? - Right?
- He's still there? - That's right.
- My goodness, this is the order. - This is...
- Let's be honest. It's me. - Hey, listen.
- I should be in fourth. - This is the right order.
- This is the right order. - Kwang Soo.
Se Chan does make an effort.
- That's right. I do. - I make an effort too.
- I invest a lot in my clothes. - I did go shopping a lot.
- Right, right. - Come on. I invest in my clothes.
- He does have cool clothes. - Exactly.
- Right, but I make an effort too. - He does have a lot of those.
- Se Chan is in sixth. - No.
(Okay. Se Chan is in 6th.)
(Okay! Se Chan is placed 6th!)
- Okay! - Really? Despite my efforts?
- He makes strange efforts. - Seok Jin is ranked too high.
- This is unbelievable. - This makes no sense.
- Okay, go ahead with fourth place. - I can't believe him.
- Seok Jin's wife used to be... - Right.
- a stylist back in the days. - Right. She was a professional.
- She quit 20 years ago. - 20 years?
(It's been 20 years since she quit.)
- Hey. - Is that why his outfits are...
- from 20 years ago? - He's been staying in the past.
It's been 20 years since...
- she left that field. - She hasn't lost her touch yet.
Come on. You saw my outfits off-camera.
You're torn between So Min and Seok Jin?
- This is crazy. - Come on.
Did you see So Min wearing a beret the other day?
- I did see her beret. - I thought Junjin was here.
Eun Joo wore that hat.
(She thought she put on a cute hat.)
(She's the spitting image of him.)
It went from Jang Hyuk, Junjin,
- That's right. - and to So Min.
(This is the line of celebrities with berets.)
- Jang Hyuk was TJ when he wore it. - That's true.
It had holes too.
- KCM wore that often too. - That's true.
KCM wore that often.
- Let me announce it. - Okay.
(It's a match of retro fashion, Seok Jin versus So Min.)
- 4th place. - 4th place.
(Which one of them will be placed 4th after a heated battle?)
(After thinking hard about it, the 4th place goes to...)
It's Seok Jin by the shape of his mouth.
- It's "Jee". - Look at his mouth.
- He changed just now. - He changed?
How did you know?
(At a crucial moment when the 4th place is about to be announced...)
How did you know? Do you know ventriloquism?
How did you figure it out? Is it that obvious?
I know. I can tell by the shape of your mouth.
- It's the shape of my mouth? - I can tell when I look closely.
The fourth place goes to...
- It's "Jeon" right now. - Okay.
(Chattering away)
(Moving his lips)
- It's "Jee". - It's "Jee" this time.
It's "Jee" right now.
- I'll do it now. - Okay.
- Don't try to read me. - Okay.
"Don't try to read me."
- We can read him though. - The fourth place goes to...
(Which one will win over Kwang Soo's heart?)
- It's So Min. - It's "Jeon".
- Jeon So Min. - Yes!
(He was late.)
- I could tell it was "Jeon". - Yes.
(After a cutthroat battle, Seok Jin is placed 5th.)
- Right? It'd have hurt my pride. - Right.
I look forward to working with you.
- I'm excited to work with you. - This is the result.
(Feeling satisfied)
Everyone must have felt it.
I thought hard and carefully about my decisions.
I believe everyone is satisfied.
(Feeling proud)
(The order from top to bottom: Kwang Soo, Haha, Ji Hyo,)
(So Min, Seok Jin, Se Chan, Jae Seok, and Jong Kook.)
Do we have to stand in order?
(They set out to where their first mission will be held.)
- Stand according to your ranks. - According to our ranks?
- Okay. - In respect to our ranks?
- I forgot about that. - Move.
- Go to the end. - My goodness.
Stand in accordance with how well you dress.
- I can't believe I'm below So Min. - Goodness, seriously. So Min.
- I hate that look on her face. - That's so annoying.
- This is a great start. - All right.
The first mission to arrange the ranks is...
Quiz! Knowledge Is Power.
(Quiz! Knowledge Is Power)
- Okay! - It's a quiz.
- Jae Seok is great at quizzes. - Is it a quiz?
- Well, this is great. - It's a quiz?
Let's go!
(On the other hand, their countenances grow grim.)
Okay. Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
However,
depending on your ranks, the buzzers will differ.
(The buzzers are different for each rank.)
- Really? - The buzzers are different?
- It must be difficult to use them. - What good is having easy buzzers?
It's of no use if you can't answer them.
You will ring each buzzer given to you.
Your ranks will be determined based on how fast you answer them.
(Thank goodness I'm in 1st place.)
However, among the eight of you,
there is an absolute member who knows...
- all the answers to the quizzes. - What?
- No way. - What?
- The member knows all the answers. - Hey!
Who is it?
(One of us is the absolute member who knows all the answers?)
(A member has snuck into this battle of ranks.)
- What? - Who is it?
- This is unbelievable. - Hey.
(They have the same mission but different agendas.)
- It's Kwang Soo. He has the look. - Who is it?
(When there's a spy, it's always Kwang Soo.)
- It's not me. - His reactions are a bit iffy.
- They were a bit off. - It's not me.
- It's not me. I'm serious. - He didn't show any reactions.
I'm telling you the truth.
Here we go again. I'm telling you. It's not me.
- It's not me. I'm serious! - It's you, isn't it?
- Mark my words. It's not me. - My gosh.
- My goodness. - It's really not me.
(He's always suspected first. Is he the absolute member?)
- I think it's Se Chan. - That's not true.
- It's Se Chan. - Mark my words. It's not me.
(He seems particularly nervous today.)
- You look anxious today. - No, I'm not.
It's him.
After your mission, if you apprehend the absolute member...
through a vote,
the absolute member will be placed last and face the penalty.
- Okay. - Let's arrest the spy.
If you fail to apprehend the absolute member,
the absolute member will be placed first.
(The absolute member will be in 1st place.)
- The member can change the ranks. - Again?
(The absolute member can change the ranks.)
We should be careful when trying to arrest the absolute member.
When we look at the difficulty level for the questions,
- we'll know if it's doable or not. - That's right.
- They'd go all red if it's wrong. - Go all red?
We'll start with an O-X quiz...
- to divide upper and lower ranks. - Okay.
- O-X quiz? - Yes, O-X quiz.
- I have a shot at this. - O-X quiz.
After hearing the question, stand behind the flags for your answers.
Here's the first question.
Cobras die when they bite their own tongues.
- What? - This question...
This question was on TV before. Hold on.
(I definitely know this question.)
Cobras die when they bite their own tongues?
(Everyone seems lost with the question.)
- Who? - This question was on TV before.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo set out with big strides.)
(Both of them choose X.)
- Are you choosing, "no"? - Yes.
(Then I'll go over there.)
(It's better to go against Ji Hyo's answer on our show.)
(I'm getting good at solving quizzes nowadays.)
This is a hard question.
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
They have poison in their bodies.
(She trusts Ji Hyo and follows her to X.)
Do they just not bite their tongues...
- although they die in the end? - I think they die.
How can they bite their tongues? They have teeth only on both ends.
- I gave this question on our show. - Do they not bite their tongues?
(Do you remember that, Jae Seok?)
- I gave this question on that show. - Right?
- I came up with this question. - You have 10 seconds.
- Here's a hint. - Right.
When vipers bite their tongues, they faint.
- They only faint? - They don't die, do they?
Hold on. Are cobras venomous?
- They're really venomous. - It's in their teeth.
- It's not in their tongues. - They're venomous.
(Jae Seok and Haha choose O with 3 seconds left.)
Have you decided?
Was it in 2012? Or 2016?
This question came up on one of my former shows.
- I think Haha came up with this. - I came up with this one.
- Really? - You came up with this question?
- It was on Instagram. - I guess we're wrong.
- No, no. The answer is X. - How could they die?
- They're immune to their poison. - That's right.
- That makes no sense. - I'm 100-percent certain.
The answer is...
(Members who answer it correctly will be in upper ranks.)
(And the other four will be in lower ranks.)
(What's the answer that will decide the upper and lower ranks?)
- The answer is "Yes". - That's right.
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Haha, and Se Chan are in upper ranks.)
- Okay! - Come on.
- They die? - Really? They die?
- They can die from that? - Cobras can die from it?
- All of us are smart enough for it. - I'm 100-percent certain.
- This is great. - How could you not know this?
- It's Se Chan. - It's one of them.
- Listen. - It has to be him.
I followed Jae Seok here.
- You know the answer to this? - I'm certain of it.
He looks anxious.
- He seems nervous. - It was on TV.
Actually, on the last episode, Se Chan...
seemed pretty uneducated.
- Yang Chicken is his nickname. - He just got that reputation.
(Se Chan earned a new reputation.)
(On October 7, they found a shocking memo at his house.)
("Chicken" towel)
(And Se Chan also misspelled "towel" in the following quiz.)
That's why the staff could have picked him for the absolute member.
- No, no. There's no way. - By the way, confusing "kitchen"...
- with "chicken" was terrible. - Right.
Can you spell that now?
Of course, I can.
(Will Se Chan remember its spelling after 2 weeks?)
(Acting confidently)
- Can you give us a notebook? - Let's see if he can spell it.
- I can do it. Come on. - Kitchen towel.
- I know it now. - It's been aired.
- Exactly. - Here we go.
Jong Kook...
Stop staring at me. You're making me nervous.
- Leave me alone. - Why would you be nervous?
Write while no one is watching.
Kwang Soo, do you know how to spell it?
- Do you? - I do.
- Try it. - Try it.
- I feel offended. - Kitchen towel.
(Se Chan versus Kwang Soo, Spelling Bee)
(They're more worked up about this than the real mission.)
Seok Jin, you should try it too.
- I know how to spell it. - Try it.
I'm not going to write it wrong on purpose.
(How much knowledge do you have compared to the other members?)
Knowledge?
(Jee Seok Jin, self-claimed intellectual)
Seriously,
let me tell you the truth.
I'm the most knowledgeable one.
I'm number one.
Apart from me, everyone is on the same level.
Should I reveal my answer first?
- Should I? - Sure.
Se Chan must have tried to memorize it.
I did. And it's still written on my fridge.
I'm confident.
"Kitchen towel".
Correct.
- That's the correct answer? - Seok Jin.
Kwang Soo is wrong.
Kwang Soo.
Is it okay to reveal it?
Kwang Soo wrote something else.
(What did he write?)
"Kitchyn tower".
(Wrong)
Tower?
- Tower? - Tower?
"Kitchyn tower".
He wrote, "tower".
Let's see the most educated one's answer.
- Not many can write it. - Seok Jin is wrong too.
I'm the most knowledgeable one.
(He was confident when he said he was better than the others.)
Seok Jin wrote "kitchen" wrong too.
- Is that wrong? - "CK"?
(He wrote "k" instead of "h".)
- Is it wrong? - Why did you write "k"?
"Kitcken".
(He wrote "kitcken" instead of "kitchen".)
- "Kitcken towel". - "Kitcken towel".
- What's the correct answer? - "Kitcken towel".
What's with you?
- You still don't know what's wrong? - I wrote "kitcken".
- This should be "h". - Oh, right.
Stop pretending.
- He left out "towel". - It...
- Write "towel". - slipped my mind.
Seok Jin must be embarrassed.
"Oh, right. It slipped my mind."
It slipped your mind?
(The spelling bee is over.)
All right.
- It was "ch". - Okay.
The lower group will go first.
The upper group can watch.
What's that?
(That's our buzzer?)
They're plastic wraps.
To press the buzzer, you need to break through the wrap.
We have to break through it?
The layers of plastic wraps differ according to your ranks.
1st place gets 1 plastic wrap.
- Kwang Soo... - I can break it right away.
Ranks 2 to 4 get 2 layers.
Ranks 5 to 7 get 3 layers.
Rank 8 gets 4 layers.
- 4 layers? - Did you get 4 layers?
Here's the question.
- It's a multiple-choice question. - Okay.
Which of the following characters' names...
means "nosy"?
- Nosy? - Nosy?
Number one, Jerry.
- As in "Tom and Jerry"? - Jerry.
Number two, Goofy.
Number three, Snoopy.
It's hard.
Number four, Tom.
Number five, Donald Duck.
Number six, Mickey Mouse.
Which of them is nosy?
Isn't it clumsy?
(They have to press the buzzer first.)
(The 3-layer plastic wrap won't break.)
(Neither will the 2-layer plastic wrap.)
We have to break through it.
It's a character?
Answer.
(Kwang Soo's 1-layer plastic wrap breaks right away.)
(Their rankings are low,)
(but their faces deserve high rankings.)
(Let me say my answer.)
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo did it.
- Stop. It's over. - Kwang Soo gets the chance.
- Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo gets the chance. - Will you be okay?
- What's your answer? - It won't break.
Number five, Donald Duck.
(Does it mean "nosy"?)
I was going to say that too.
- It's wrong. - Answer.
(Is it my turn?)
- Answer. - You have to break a new one.
(You have to break plastic wraps again to answer.)
What?
- You have to break a new one. - What?
(Right away)
Again?
(Let me try too.)
Answer.
Number six, Mickey Mouse.
(Wrong)
Number two, Goofy. No?
Answer.
(So Min never gives up.)
Number one, Jerry.
No? It's wrong?
Answer.
Number three, Snoopy.
(Correct)
(Snoopy means "nosy".)
- Isn't he... - Why?
- Why is it Snoopy? - Kwang Soo is in fifth place.
Isn't he clumsy?
If the questions are this hard,
- we might have a chance. - We have a chance.
- You just have to guess. - I didn't know.
We have to remember that.
- Right. - One of us knows all the answers.
(The absolute member knows all the answers.)
(The absolute member is either in the lower group or the upper group.)
They said almost all the options.
- They really had no idea. - The absolute member isn't here.
It's not among us.
It's not among them?
Because...
It's not me.
(Se Chan doesn't fit in the upper group.)
After about two wrong answers,
the absolute member would have wanted to say the correct one.
But they continued.
- It must be among us. - Probably.
Right.
I think it's either Se Chan or Haha.
- Right. - You'll see.
Keep an eye on us.
- Everything points to them. - Okay.
For this round, to press the buzzer,
you have to whistle with candies in your mouth.
I can't whistle.
The number of candies you get...
is in accordance with your rankings.
Here's the question.
What does "Bbaengddae pants" mean in North Korean?
- Bbaengddae? - I know what "bbaengko" is.
- Number one, hiphop pants. - Bbaengddae?
Number two, skinny jeans.
Number three, baggy pants.
Number four, jeans.
Number five, slacks.
Number six, leggings.
(Ji Hyo puts the candies in her mouth.)
(She whistle right away.)
Ji Hyo gets the chance.
Number four, jeans.
(She says the wrong answer.)
Wrong?
(Numbers 4 and 5 are struggling to get the chance.)
- I have no idea. - Number five?
(He spits out a candy.)
Give him one more!
Give me one more.
- Shouldn't he put it back in? - Give me one more.
Give him one more.
Seok Jin has a small mouth.
Ji Hyo gets the chance.
Ji Hyo will say all the options.
Number two, skinny jeans.
(Ji Hyo succeeds easily and says the correct answer.)
- Nice. - It's correct?
It means "skinny jeans"?
I thought so too.
It's me and Seok Jin again.
It's a competition between ranks 7 and 8.
Let's see who ends up at the bottom.
What's that?
- What's that? - Is that a gag?
I can't do that.
- We have to blow it with our noses. - Okay.
(So Min has to blow up 1 bottle with her nose, and Seok Jin, 2.)
(Let me get ready.)
You have a booger on your chin.
(Hold on.)
He has a huge booger on his chin.
Gosh, there's more.
(Something keeps coming out.)
The tissue became so big after he blew his nose.
- What's in it? - Stop it.
- Stop it. - Is it a treasure chest?
It looks like a pouch.
A nose pouch.
How many nicknames do you have now?
Nose Pouch, Nostrils...
You should organize them.
Here's the question.
Ranks 7 and 8 are left.
This word was coined by Shakespeare.
- It means... - What?
"booty of a pirate".
- It's used by hiphop artists. - Right.
- Please say the answer. - I think I know.
- I'm sure many people know. - Really?
Okay. I know this one.
You have to blow up the bottle.
(Seok Jin is worked up.)
- Good. One is done. - Okay.
Swag.
(Correct)
(Seok Jin is in 7th place, and So Min, 8th.)
- So Min. - Okay.
Why did you lose?
(5: Kwang Soo, 6: Ji Hyo, 7: Seok Jin, 8: So Min)
It's the upper group's turn.
Okay.
- Move, lower group. - Okay.
- Move. - Move.
- Move out of the way. - You punks.
We'll be able to find out now.
Is that a gourd?
- What's that? - It's a gourd.
(For this round, they are gourds.)
What are we supposed to do? You get only one?
- It's not bad. - Good.
- I have an advantage. - That looks weak.
Okay.
It's not bad. I could do this.
For this round,
you have to break the gourds with your heads.
If you get this one right, you'll be in first place.
- First place. - Okay.
Let's do this!
Back in elementary school, I even entered a math contest.
A dolphin has an organ...
that detects the direction and location of sounds.
(Haha gives up.)
What's the name of it?
Number one, kiwi.
- Kiwi? - What?
Number two, melon.
Number three, grapes.
Number four, apple.
- It's an organ? - What?
Number five, pineapple.
(Se Chan breaks his gourd even before hearing everything.)
(He doesn't hesitate.)
- What's going on? - It's my turn.
Se Chan knows this?
- He knows this? - What's the answer?
(Se Chan gets the chance right after the question is read.)
Number two, melon?
(He picks number 2, melon.)
(It's a difficult question. Is Se Chan's answer correct?)
Okay!
(Se Chan's answer is correct.)
- He's the culprit. - No.
Hold on. Listen.
He's the culprit.
We caught the absolute member.
- Who are you trying to fool? - Hold on.
Listen.
- It doesn't make sense. - Listen.
He's the absolute member.
- Let's hear what he says. - Listen.
Don't make it so obvious.
- Don't make it so obvious. - You were too hasty.
- A melon... - You were too hasty.
A melon has this.
- What do you mean? - What do you mean?
The stem...
- I mean... - It doesn't make sense.
- No way. - It was a nonsense question.
(Frustrated)
- Gosh. - It's a nonsense question?
- It wasn't. - It's not.
(You're even more suspicious now.)
- It's not? - I hit Seok Jin too.
- I'm sorry. - Did you seriously guess?
- I did. - You did?
They told him, so he just answered back like a parrot.
First place is Se Chan.
Okay, it's not what you think.
It's strange that Se Chan answered correctly.
- It's very strange. - Seriously.
- How could he? - All of them are similar...
- including apples. - Also,
he broke the gourd before anyone with such confidence.
He was in a hurry.
- He was. - He was waiting for it.
I should win.
- Here's the next question. - Let's go.
- The questions are difficult. - Just guess.
- My goal is Jae Seok. - Let's go.
(He wants to defeat Jae Seok.)
(Two big gourds? I'll break them easily.)
(I'll show you how intelligent I am.)
It's a short story by Joo Yo Seop.
(What?)
(Joo Yo Seop?)
Darn it.
In his "Mother and a Guest",
how old is Ok Hee's mother?
- I can answer this. - Ok Hee's mother's age?
Number 1, 20 years old. Number 2, 24 years old.
Number 3, 27 years old. Number 4, 30 years old.
Number 5, 33 years old.
Okay.
(He breaks his gourd.)
Number 3, 27 years old.
(Jae Seok answers with confidence. Is 27 years old the answer?)
(Wrong)
Number 2, 24 years old.
(He breaks two gourds.)
(Number 2, 24 years old)
Did he break them at once?
(Is Jong Kook's answer correct?)
- Number 2, 24 years old. - 24 years old?
- Yes! - Goodness.
("My mother is 24 years old this year.")
26 years old?
- That was strong. - Okay.
(Disappointed)
Give Jong Kook a dog bowl. This is too easy for him.
(Gourds are too easy.)
"Dog bowl"?
- "Dog bowl"? - Give him a metal bowl.
- Isn't it too weak for him? - Okay.
- What do you mean? - Give him a brass pot.
Give him an earthen pot.
Why did you take such a small gourd?
- It's mine. - Second place's gourd is small.
Don't you know the rules?
- It's too small. - What?
That's why you're smaller than me.
(Even your gourd is smaller than mine.)
(What? I'm smaller?)
He got confident.
I don't know about that.
That's why you're smaller than me.
Let's get Jae Seok today.
Here we go again.
Here's the next question. It's a multiple choice.
Okay, I'll guess.
In the story of Buddha's birth...
Okay.
When Buddha was born, this is what he shouted.
- He shouted? - What did he say?
- Did he shout when he was born? - When he was born?
- I've read it in a book. - Did he say something?
- Number one. - Baby sounds?
"Om mani padme hum."
That's right. I know this.
Number two, "Bodhisattva Mahasattva".
Number three, "Namo Amitabhaya".
Number four, "I am my own deity of the skies and earth."
No way.
Number five, "All or nothing".
- What? - "All or nothing"?
Number six, "A big commotion".
By the way...
(The choices are given, but they're hesitant.)
It's difficult to say if it's number one.
(The sound is loud, but it doesn't break.)
(It hurts so much.)
- It didn't break. - Do it again.
It didn't break.
(Haha gives it a try.)
What's the answer?
Number one.
(Haha's answer is number 1.)
- What is it? - What is it?
(Number 1...)
"Om baehon samsasam"?
What? He didn't pronounce it well.
He said something else.
(He created a new phrase.)
I got it.
(He gives it a try.)
- Goodness. - What's the answer?
Number one, "Om mani padme hum."
(He pronounces it correctly.)
(Jae Seok says it correctly. Is it the answer?)
Did I pronounce it wrong?
(The answer is wrong.)
Wait.
(With the remaining choices,)
(he gives it another try.)
- The smaller one is worse. - Smaller ones are harder.
What's the answer?
(What is Haha's answer?)
Hurry up.
Number four, "I am my own deity of the skies and earth."
(He stammers the answer.)
Can you repeat it?
(Is it wrong once again?)
- What's wrong? - Tell him the answer, Se Chan.
I don't know.
Tell him the answer.
- Number four? - "I am my own deity."
(His answer is accurate this time.)
(Will his choice be correct?)
(Haha's answer is correct.)
(Screaming in happiness)
Why are you exaggerating your reaction?
Why not? I defeated Jae Seok.
- Are you that happy? - Yes.
What's wrong with being excited?
- You aren't it, are you? - What's wrong with being excited?
- No. - No, right?
What's wrong with being excited?
It's Se Chan.
Stop it.
Isn't it good to win first place?
Here's the order.
Here's the rank for the first round of Knowledge Is Power.
(Current order)
Now, we'll vote for the absolute member.
Please vote for a member whom you think...
is the absolute member.
(If they succeed, the absolute member is ranked last.)
- I don't know. - Say something, Se Chan.
- Listen. - Why aren't you talking?
- Why aren't you talking? - In terms of hierarchy,
which rank is the best?
- Listen, let me tell you. - Isn't it him?
You answered without listening to all the choices.
It means that you knew the answer.
- Listen. - He's strange too.
(People suspect him all of a sudden.)
You're very strange.
Who are you? What's wrong with you?
This is what detectives do.
Se Chan is the strongest candidate.
Se Chan looks quite tense.
Didn't I tell you during the O-X quiz?
Certainly, Se Chan heard the conversation I had with Haha.
That's probably why he answered that way.
However, it seemed like he acted with an intention.
(Did Se Chan plan to do it?)
(Before the last call, Se Chan changed his answer.)
(He follows Haha and Jae Seok as people suspect him.)
(Was Se Chan acting?)
This is crazy.
Se Chan could have listened to all the choices before answering.
Number two, melon?
(Se Chan answered correctly before all the choices were said.)
(Usually, it's a difficult question for Se Chan to answer.)
It's strange that he guessed right after hearing four choices.
That's true.
- His explanation was... - I already said it, so stop it.
(Jae Seok cuts him off.)
Stay back.
- All right. - He looks tense.
Think about the shape of a melon.
You'll win first place like a fool...
- even if you're the absolute one. - Right.
- "Like a fool"? Goodness. - You're a fool.
Let's vote for the first rank.
Okay. Let me look at their faces first.
This is what's strange.
"Let me look at their faces first". That's strange.
The answer, melon, was obviously strange.
He didn't have to say anything, but he wanted to look at our faces.
- "Let me look at their faces." - Goodness.
You're today's absolute member.
- This is insane. - It's you.
"Let me look at their faces first."
(Is Se Chan the absolute member as everyone predicts?)
I don't know yet.
I'll follow what I felt first.
Let's follow what we felt first.
(Everyone suspects Se Chan.)
Yang Se Chan.
This is difficult.
(Everyone finishes voting.)
- All right. - Do we have the result?
I'll announce the result.
- The result is important. - Okay.
Here's whom Ji Hyo voted.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Me?
(Ji Hyo votes for Kwang Soo.)
Is it Ji Hyo?
It's not him.
- Ji Hyo. - Why me?
- Se Chan's vote. - What on earth?
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Me?
Kwang Soo?
There's a team.
- There's a team. - You're an assistant.
- No way. - You're an assistant.
- I'm not. - You are.
Kwang Soo didn't do anything suspicious.
I didn't do anything suspicious.
- Here's whom Kwang Soo voted. - Let's hear it.
- Kim Jong Kook. - What?
Did he?
(Kwang Soo votes for Jong Kook.)
- What's going on? - Se Chan.
He acted suspiciously enough.
You should have chosen Se Chan.
No one voted for him yet.
The rest of you voted for Se Chan.
- Right. - That's right.
(The remaining 5 members voted for Se Chan.)
Wait, listen to me.
Think about it.
When the question was given, I wanted to win first place.
That's why I answered as quickly as possible.
It's Se Chan, so it's Se Chan.
Don't try to influence others.
It's impossible that Se Chan won first place.
Based on the results, the member with the most votes...
- is Se Chan. - That's right.
(Se Chan gets the most votes.)
For the arrest of the absolute member...
(Did they succeed in arresting the absolute member?)
Did we succeed?
You failed.
(They failed to arrest the absolute member.)
Why did you vote for me? I said I'm not.
(Is Se Chan not the absolute member?)
(Then who could it be?)
Did you really know the answer?
(Everyone is confused.)
The absolute member is...
(The real absolute member)
It's Haha.
(The absolute member is Haha.)
- Really? - This is terrible.
He's terrible. How could he do that?
How is it possible?
(Due to Haha's perfect acting,)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
(they fail to arrest the absolute member.)
Everyone is being interviewed on how they honestly feel.
Haha, you know all the answers to the quiz.
You're the absolute member.
During the quiz mission, don't let others get suspicious of you.
- You must rank at least third. - Really?
You succeed if you don't get arrested.
(He had to avoid getting arrested.)
The other members are being interviewed individually.
Memorize the answers quickly and act like you don't know.
"What do dolphins use to detect sounds and directions?"
"Kiwi, melon, grapes, apples, pineapples".
What do these have to do with it?
"It's a short story by Joo Yo Seop."
"How old is Ok Hee's mother?"
She's only 24?
How old is Ok Hee?
If Ok Hee is six, how old was her mom...
(I've never heard this before.)
But they got married early back in the day.
24, 24, 24.
2, 4. 2, 4.
24. 2, 4.
"In the story of Buddha's birth..."
"when Buddha was born, this is what he shouted."
"Namo Amitabhaya"...
"I am my own deity of the skies and earth."
It doesn't really make sense.
It doesn't match the image of Buddhism.
(To make it natural, he looked confident on purpose.)
(He gave up on a question to avoid suspicion.)
(To fool Jae Seok, he mumbled his answer on purpose.)
(Jae Seok fell for it and said the wrong answer.)
(He won third place by saying the answer he already knew.)
I'm sorry.
Good work.
(Haha successfully completes his mission.)
I wanted to say the correct answer right away.
- Couldn't you do any better? - What did you do?
Why did you say, "melon"?
(Why did I do so well today?)
Why did you have to say, "melon"?
- Se Chan. - I mean...
- Thank you. - When I said, "melon",
I just took a guess.
Why didn't you let me say anything? I kept denying it.
But Jong Kook kept saying, "It's you."
"You made a mistake, so pull yourself together."
I'm a fool? No, you're a fool. You shouldn't live like that.
I kept denying it. I denied it to the end.
- Gosh. - Sorry.
Today's champion is Yang Se Chan!
(They try to comfort him.)
Toss him into the air.
Se Chan even fooled himself.
I mean, I just took a guess.
I had no idea it would be Haha.
Haha is...
in first place now.
- I'm not going to trust him. - He can decide...
- the other members' rankings. - Haha.
- Haha. - Haha.
I won't say much.
Okay.
- I never suspected you. - Okay.
Some people suspected me.
No one did.
As soon as I beat Jae Seok,
someone said, "You're suspicious."
"Why are you so excited?"
You did seem too excited.
Kitcken.
- Go to the back. - Why am I Kitcken?
- Kitcken. - Go.
- Come. - Move.
Come here.
Gosh.
Move.
- Come here. - Why am I in eighth place?
Stay here.
Also,
as soon as Kitcken said that,
someone agreed.
Right.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo, go to the back.)
- Ji Hyo. - I remember it clearly.
I didn't know what to do.
- Listen to him. - Go, Ji Hyo.
- Come to the back. - Hurry up.
- I mean... - Go.
Also, I still remember this.
From far away,
as if to say, "Why are you there,"
- someone looked at me suspiciously. - That's right.
Please go to the back.
(Jae Seok?)
- I think it's you. - You.
Me?
(It's you, Kwang Soo.)
- Me? - Go.
Why me?
- Why? - Go.
You looked at me like this.
- You were a little suspicious. - Just go.
Just go.
Be quiet. Please be quiet, you three.
I think you'll be here soon.
- I have a question for Jae Seok. - Okay.
(Obedient)
How many of the things you have are bigger than mine?
(Well... Let me see.)
(The size dispute begins again.)
Will he choose his pride?
(Pride or ranking?)
(During the briefcase race, they received a controversial hint.)
"It's bigger than Jae Seok's and smaller than Haha's."
What?
(And thus started the dispute regarding their sizes.)
I can definitely beat you.
Haha, the camera.
What are you going to do?
What is this?
(They competed to protect their pride.)
I can't stand it.
Will he choose his pride?
I'd say, none.
(Determined)
(He gives up his pride to get a high ranking.)
I'd say, none.
He's confident.
That's pathetic.
- I'd say, none. - Is this really necessary?
Is this necessary?
(Do you have to do this?)
- Let me ask you one more thing. - Okay.
Are you cute?
- He is. - Yes!
I think so.
Come here.
- Really? - He passed.
- Thank you. - And...
someone took my hand.
I'm so thankful.
- My partner, Jong Kook, come here. - Okay.
- Thank you. - I'm being very fair.
- Just because he's your partner... - This is...
You're being unfair.
- Hold on. I... - Be quiet!
Be quiet!
Be quiet. Keep your mouth shut.
Be quiet.
- Keep your mouth shut. - "Keep your mouth shut"?
Look. Be quiet.
Be quiet.
- Please give me fourth place. - These two...
- But... - To be honest, I...
Right.
Se Chan saved me.
Think about how you got there.
- Se Chan, come here. - Okay!
He did a great job.
Are you a parrot on Haha's shoulder?
He's so cute.
(I'm Haha's spokesperson.)
So Min, switch with the cute guy.
(I can't stand it anymore.)
- Haha. - I can't take it anymore.
Jae Seok talks too much.
It's driving me crazy.
You made the right choice.
- Haha. - I'm done.
So Min didn't suspect me.
Thank you.
Gosh. I can't believe it.
(Jae Seok gets in trouble by talking too much.)
Number 1 gets 8 badges, number 2 gets 7,
and number 8 gets 1.
- Okay. - Unbelievable.
It's shocking that I'm in fifth place after what I did.
(It's shocking that I'm in 5th place.)
(He even gave up his pride.)
He gave up his pride.
He's cute.
"I'd say, none."
I can't believe it.
(It's time to have lunch according to their ranks.)
Gosh, it's ridiculous.
Let's go have lunch.
(Current ranking)
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry,
but I don't have much space here.
- Can you move over a little? - Sorry.
If you sit over there...
Go over there.
- You should squeeze a bit more. - Here?
- We're already three people. - Squeeze.
- Can't we sit 3 and 3? - Gosh.
- Gosh. - We have more space now.
See what happens if I win first place.
Win first place then.
Everyone.
We prepared your favorite food.
Rice, beef radish soup, braised short ribs...
- There's meat. - It's Korean food.
I love beef radish soup.
- Grilled ham... - I love it.
and fried eggs.
- There are only 8 portions. - 8 portions?
But we're eight people.
You'll get your food in the order of your ranking.
You can get as much food as you want.
The last person can eat only the remaining food.
(Only the remaining food?)
Seok Jin will starve again.
Please leave some for me.
- We have to eat. - We have to eat.
Haha, in first place, will go first.
- Okay. - Enjoy your lunch.
Go, you liar.
- You liar. - Go, you liar.
- We'll be fine. - What's that on his chest?
You'll be able to fill up your stomach.
Of course.
I'm not looking forward.
Gosh.
Look how pretentious he is.
- I want to kick him in the bottom. - Hurry up.
- Gosh. - Your lower body looks great.
Your hips look great.
You're very flexible.
You're flexible.
(How much food will Haha get?)
Okay.
I should get enough rice.
(8 portions)
Other people should eat too.
Let me just get this much.
Well... Oh, look at this.
(Beef radish soup)
All right.
The chunks are the best part.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Look at this beef. This would be enough for a meal.
Beef radish soup.
He's taking all the chunks.
- But he can't... - The bowl...
take too much.
(The others are watching him.)
Be reasonable.
Don't take too much.
He's doing that on purpose.
Hey!
- Don't go overboard. - He's taking all the beef.
(Let me get some short ribs now.)
Two pieces?
That wouldn't be enough.
That wouldn't do.
(3 pieces out of 8)
One potato... Okay.
(3 short ribs and 1 potato)
I love short rib patties.
(2 short rib patties)
2 fried eggs. Definitely.
(Full)
Haha is eating too much.
- He's going overboard. - He's too greedy.
My goodness. I love this.
(2.5 grilled hams)
(1 more grilled ham)
It still doesn't look enough.
So Min.
- You can't do that. - So Min.
(Let me go get my food.)
You didn't get any questions right.
So Min, don't go overboard.
So Min, be reasonable.
(So Min is never reasonable.)
I love grilled ham.
(3 grilled hams)
(Beans in soy sauce are my favorite.)
- So Min. - Yes?
Did you leave a lot?
Yes. There's still a lot left.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
(She leaves 6 beans.)
(So Min is done.)
I want fried eggs.
(It's number 3, Jong Kook's turn.)
This...
I love this.
(He likes grilled ham.)
They took so much. Were there 8 in the beginning?
They took so much.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(He cuts it.)
(He divides the rest into 5 pieces.)
It's based on the number of people.
(The three members took a lot.)
I like beans in soy sauce.
(They eat generous portions.)
I need to serve myself a lot.
(I'll take all.)
Hey, hey.
- Don't take too much. - Come on.
Hey!
How can you take all the solids?
If you take all, what's left for us?
Just take one. Good.
(He takes another one.)
Take only one.
Show me your crab leg dance.
(If so...)
Fine, let me go.
(Dancing)
- Jae Seok. - Why do you live like this?
You have no sense of pride.
(Very satisfied)
(Give me one egg.)
Okay, I accept it.
At least, one egg remains.
(He gets one fried egg.)
He's taking it whole. Jae Seok, split it.
Hey.
He'll get to eat though.
(All the protein is gone.)
My goodness.
Jae Seok!
(He takes all the remaining soup.)
- You'll drop it anyway, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
What are you doing?
I trusted him.
I have no choice but to eat two.
- Leave us some kimchi. - Kimchi.
There's nothing to eat.
Yes, Kwang Soo didn't take his soup.
- I'm going in. - He didn't take his soup.
(Ji Hyo goes in before Kwang Soo realizes it.)
(She goes straight to the soup.)
Give me one soup.
Give me one.
(She takes it at the speed of light.)
I forgot my soup.
I served one for myself.
You didn't take it, so it's mine.
I didn't leave it.
- It's mine now. - Wait.
- I forgot to take it. - No way.
Seriously.
What do you mean? I served it myself.
- You didn't take it. - I did take it.
- No, you didn't. - This isn't yours, right?
That's not mine.
Wait, I forgot to take it.
(He served the soup for others.)
I didn't expect much.
There's nothing.
There's absolutely nothing.
(The empty trays welcome him.)
There's only rice.
I'll take all the rice.
(He smears his rice with the sauce.)
(He gets all the remaining sauce.)
(He takes as much of the remaining side dishes as possible.)
I got something at least.
- Can we eat? - Thank you for the food.
Enjoy your food.
What's this?
Do we go through the doors?
What are these?
My goodness.
- What's this? - Gosh.
What is it?
Before you proceed your second mission,
you'll rearrange the rank.
You'll receive benefits based on the rank.
(Rearranging the rank)
- Okay. - Already?
Okay.
Spin the roulette and call the person's friend.
Ask for his rank.
- I see. - Let's try.
Please spin the roulette.
That sounds good.
I'll spin it.
(Call a close friend.)
(Asking helpful questions is important.)
- Please let it be him. - I should be first in rank.
- I want to rank first. - Please.
Let it be me.
It's definitely me.
- It's me. - Here it is.
(Seok Jin is unlucky.)
(Did he really get selected?)
- Is it Seok Jin? - It's me.
- Is it Ji Hyo? - It's me.
It's me.
She's so lucky.
(As always, lucky Ji Hyo is selected.)
- Whom should I call? - Whom should she call?
There are people Ji Hyo is working with on a program.
Shall I call Yoon Ju?
Call Jang Yoon Ju.
(That's a must.)
- "Haha". - "Jae Seok".
It's been a while since she called me by my name.
It's been a while.
(It also benefits Jae Seok and Haha since he's close to her.)
- Ji Hyo. - Yoon Ju.
(She answers the phone.)
- Hello. - I'm at a shoot.
Say hello to her.
Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
This is Haha.
- It's been a long time. - Yoon Ju.
Jae Seok.
- "Jae Seok". - Yoon Ju.
I get to hear your voice through Ji Hyo's call.
You're right, Jae Seok.
- Where are you? - It's been awhile.
I'm at a shoot too.
Is that so? You must be busy then.
I'm free for a little bit.
Is it okay?
Ji Hyo will ask you a question.
You have to decide a rank.
- Rank us based on what you hear. - Be honest.
Be objective and fair.
You have to be really honest, Yoon Ju.
This is what I think.
(What will Ji Hyo's question be?)
(I hope it's a question that's favorable to me.)
Rank Running Man members based on their looks.
(I can rank 1st.)
- "Based on looks"? - Based on looks.
Remember, Yoon Ju.
- Rank us from 1st to 8th. - Be nice.
First in rank is Ji Hyo.
- Yes. - Right.
- I rank first. - I agree.
Who ranks second?
- Hello, Yoon Ju. This is So Min. - Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
(Do you hear me, Yoon Ju?)
- So Min? - So Min ranks second.
Yoon Ju.
- Yoon Ju. - What about me?
- Who ranks third? - The one who ranks third...
Say my name.
My heart flutters when I see Jong Kook.
(It's big news.)
Me? Thank you.
- How? - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Exclude glasses. - I'll do my best!
Judge them without their glasses on.
- Imagine us naked. - Yoon Ju.
Yoon Ju, you have to remember me.
- Yoon Ju. - Remember Se Chan.
I get upset easily.
- Wait. - Don't say anything.
- Next is Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(She ranks Kwang Soo 4th.)
Does Kwang Soo rank fourth?
- Next has to be me. - Which members remain?
Seok Jin.
- Se Chan. - Haha.
There's Haha.
- Think of us without glasses. - Wait.
- Seriously. - Haha is low in rank.
Really?
(Haha is low in rank.)
- Go away. - You're low in rank too.
- Yoon Ju. - Seriously.
I finally get to make my revenge.
I remember what happened on "Infinite Challenge".
She remembers what happened.
- How could you? - On "Infinite Challenge"?
- Say Seok Jin. - Se Chan ranks fifth.
- He ranks fifth. - Okay.
I'm higher than him.
- Come on, Yoon Ju. - Come on.
- Don't do this. - You're unbelievable.
I understand that you're trying to be funny.
I think Seok Jin ranks sixth.
- Sixth? - Goodness.
I don't even feel good.
Yoon Ju has no respect for the two of us.
She takes it so seriously.
- You're right. - Yoon Ju, wait.
- It doesn't matter who wins. - I'll try to understand.
This is about looks.
- Right. - Without glasses...
- With glasses. - Without glasses.
My answer is...
(Who...)
(Who is uglier?)
Jae Seok ranks eighth.
Okay, thank you.
(Jae Seok is the ugliest.)
Listen, Yoon Ju.
- Congratulations. - Come on, Yoon Ju.
He dresses badly, and he's ugly.
- He's the worst kind. - I like you.
- Yoon Ju. - He's the worst.
Come on, Yoon Ju.
You finished ranking all of us.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you, Yoon Ju. - Thank you.
(Current ranking)
Listen. From the fourth rank...
Come to the back.
Yoon Ju judged us accurately.
- Seriously. - I didn't think she'd be serious.
To be honest,
she was trying to be funny from here.
- That's right. - She was serious.
I thought about it.
How dare you, you ugly?
(He steps on his foot.)
You stepped on my foot.
(How dare you step on my foot?)
Goodness.
Get away from me!
- He's ugly and dresses badly. - He dresses badly.
On top of that,
- he agreed that he's not big. - Right.
Isn't that right?
- Listen. - Jae Seok.
Stay out of it.
The second mission is Break the Wall to the Future.
Behind eight styrofoam doors,
there are six mattresses...
and two obstacles.
(Mud and water)
- Goodness. - They're mud and water.
Oh, no.
Break the wall randomly.
You're eliminated if you get an obstacle.
Two members are eliminated in each round.
Mud bath is ranked lower than water.
Goodness, that's right.
However, there's an absolute member who knows which wall stands...
- before the obstacles. - Again?
(There's one absolute member.)
Who is it?
Who is it? Say it.
After the mission is over,
you may arrest them based on voting.
- There must be a mission. - Of course.
Do we have to rank within the top three?
Or you must fall in a mud bath.
That could be true.
We'll have to see.
Based on the rank that Yoon Ju decided,
you'll be given shoes.
These are shoes based on your ranking.
- First rank is aqua shoes. - That's nice.
2nd to 4th in rank are given heels.
5th to 7th in rank are given flippers.
The last in rank...
- is given acupressure slippers. - That's harsh.
Come on. He's already sad to be ugly.
Take your pair of shoes.
- Stand in your place. - What on earth?
(Aqua shoes, heels, flippers, and acupressure slippers)
- I choose number 7. - 7?
- I choose number 7. - I choose number 2.
We will break one of the doors.
In this round, you choose based on 1st come, 1st serve basis.
Isn't this it?
He's going far.
- Get ready. - I'm not it.
Go.
(Which wall will he break?)
- What? - Now...
I picked number seven.
- I'm standing in front of it. - What was that?
- I chose seven. - Get ready...
- Do we run towards this? - One...
We can run towards it, right?
- Can we go to seven? - We can run towards it.
- We have to go to seven. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - One...
(Inching towards 7)
1, 2...
(Number 7 is a safe zone. If they get to it, they move on.)
(They sprint towards 7.)
The soles of my feet are so painful.
I don't even know.
(This is a mess.)
What's this?
(Kwang Soo was standing in front of 7.)
(He goes straight to it.)
(On either side of 7 are Jae Seok and Ji Hyo.)
(Number 4 and 5 are the obstacles.)
- Here. - I'm safe.
- I'm safe. - I'm safe.
- So Min. - Look.
(So Min breaks through the wall with her face...)
(and falls into the water in number 5.)
(That was a powerful dive.)
It's Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook gets showered in mud as he falls into 4.)
It's Jong Kook. He fell!
- I'm safe. - I'm good.
(Some are happy, some are sad.)
What's this?
(He doesn't know where to go.)
- I'm safe. - I'm safe.
- Yes! - I'm safe!
The soles of my feet hurt.
I'm done.
(He was supposed to be invincible.)
I was wrong.
Jong Kook is in 8th place, and So Min is in 7th.
- One of us knows then. - Right.
- One of us? - It has to be.
I'm sure.
I was the last one left.
Really?
(Seok Jin says he wandered around and went to an empty door.)
But she went to number five.
(Hold on.)
I think Seok Jin is suspicious...
because I asked where he was going in the beginning,
and he stood in front of number six.
- He didn't say anything. - He didn't move either.
So Min wanted to switch with him, but he kept on insisting he'd stay.
He would usually ask me to switch, but he didn't say one word.
(There are several testimonies.)
(Seok Jin was standing in front of 6.)
(So Min wanted to switch...)
- It's her. - You're acting weird.
(He pushed So Min towards 5 which was water.)
(What's up with Seok Jin?)
- I'm going to stay here. - No.
(Did he know 5 was water?)
That's right.
- I had a gut feeling. - He always asks to switch.
He does.
That's true. He always asks to switch.
I thought there was a good possibility,
and I didn't want to switch.
Do you always wear your shirt that way?
(What's wrong with his sleeves?)
- No. - You must be sweaty.
- No, no. - You're wiping it off.
- I'm not. - That was unnatural.
It doesn't matter what the situation is.
If I get suspected, I act weirdly.
I'm going to write your name,
but I don't know if it's you. I'm writing your name regardless.
It's not me.
I won't say it's you.
(7th rank: So Min, 8th rank: Jong Kook)
Okay.
Let's get started again.
- What are you standing in front of? - Number four.
I want to do four.
I'm going to do it.
- Who agrees to rock-paper-scissors? - Me.
Why? Isn't it mine if I stood in front of it first?
- It's him. - I agree.
He's acting strangely.
- You're acting strangely. - Why?
- It's so obvious. - Can you let him go first?
It's so obvious.
- Can you let him go first? - You guys are ridiculous.
I'm so natural.
Why are you doubting me? This is driving me nuts.
What did you say?
- "This is driving me nuts." - You're driving us nuts.
Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(They do rock-paper-scissors to be fair.)
Okay, I take four.
- Rock-paper-scissors - This is driving me nuts.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay. - What? Am I in last place?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Goodness.
- Hey. - Seok Jin.
(He has to go to the remaining spot.)
- Are you staying at three? - Yes.
I'll do two.
- This is driving me nuts. - One at a time.
Why don't you just get eliminated?
Then we'll be less suspicious of you.
You guys put me at six.
- Do you want to switch with me? - Sure, let's switch.
(He doesn't hesitate.)
- Really? - See?
- Switch. It doesn't matter. - What if both...
- Are they both safe? - No,
he said he wanted two.
He wanted 4 or 2.
(If Seok Jin survives, he's likely to be the absolute member.)
- Let's switch. Okay. - Really?
I don't care.
Why does Kwang Soo not want to switch?
(He's another target.)
(He would've asked by now.)
- I already made up my mind. - What?
(They're getting suspicious.)
Let's switch.
(He feels Kwang Soo out.)
- I want to stay here. - Here?
- Why? - You like to switch though.
- I know. - I like where I am.
I have a good feeling.
I think it's Kwang Soo.
(Who is the absolute member?)
It must be Kwang Soo and Seok Jin.
- It could be two. - Okay, so...
- Kwang Soo, go first. - Is it one at a time?
- I'm scared. - One,
two,
three.
(He falls on a mattress as predicted.)
- It's Kwang Soo. - I think it's him.
Okay!
Do I go?
I'm going to vote for him.
1, 2, 3.
Let's go!
(He shouts in confidence.)
(Is he the absolute member who knows where the mattresses are?)
Let's go!
(He breaks through the wall.)
(He gets five stars for breaking, jumping, and landing.)
Are you all right?
(He's not the absolute member.)
Okay, it's Kwang Soo.
It wasn't Seok Jin!
(I'm absolutely not the absolute member.)
- It's not me! - Sorry for doubting you.
- I told you it wasn't me! - I'm sorry.
It's not me!
It's not him.
- That was so funny. - He collapsed.
(Sorry for doubting you.)
That was so funny.
- Number three. - Hey, that was so funny.
- 1, 2, 3. - I laughed so much.
- Three. - Oh, gosh.
(Se Chan chose number 3.)
Okay!
(He's safe.)
- Okay! - He passed.
Number four.
(Haha, the former absolute member, chose 4.)
- What a relief. - Are you good?
I was so scared.
(Then...)
(1 of these 2 has the mud.)
- It's one of them. - Goodness.
5 and 6 will go together.
1, 2...
(Will he get unlucky yet again and fall into the mud?)
(Will she continue to be lucky?)
Three. Run.
(Who will fall into the mud?)
(If it's not Jae Seok,)
(it's Ji Hyo.)
(The lucky Ji Hyo falls into the mud.)
What was that?
- What was that? - What did you do?
Ji Hyo is in 6th place, and Seok Jin is in 5th.
(Ji Hyo fell into the mud, and Seok Jin fell into the water.)
3rd and 4th ranks will be decided in this round.
- This is going to be ridiculous. - I know.
What if we do rock-paper-scissors and decide for each other?
- Should we do that? - That's a good idea, right?
- Yes. - The person...
- who wins gets to decide. - For everybody.
- The winner decides for all. - What if I have...
- Put your hands up if you agree. - something...
Put your hands up if you agree.
- Who agrees? - I agree.
- I agree totally. - Are you sure?
- It's not me. - Do you agree? Okay.
It's Kwang Soo. I can see it from here.
I swear it's not me.
(They all doubt him.)
Do you know how you look right now? This is your face.
- "It's not me." - It's not.
- It's not me. This way... - I agree.
Your face!
(Staring)
I swear it's not me! Don't look at me like that.
Don't look at me like that. I swear it's not me.
It's not me.
I'll go where you tell me to. It's not me.
(Is Kwang Soo the absolute member?)
Can I say one thing?
Did he know when he asked to switch?
(Did Jae Seok know when he asked to switch last time?)
He wanted to switch from two.
(That's right. Moments ago...)
- Do you want to switch with me? - Sure, let's switch.
(Jae Seok was standing in front of 2.)
(He switched with Seok Jin and survived.)
(Did he know everything and planned it all?)
He wanted to switch from two.
We were all doubting him.
You're really natural right now.
Why were you like that earlier?
He turns natural once he falls into the water.
He's himself again.
- Okay, let's go. - That's not true.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors and go where we want.
- Okay. - I have no idea.
- It's Jae Seok or Kwang Soo. - I think it's Jae Seok.
(Is the absolute member Jae Seok or Kwang Soo?)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
(The winner gets to decide the position.)
- You and me? - Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok wins. He's a strong candidate for the absolute member.)
- You go second. - Yes.
I go first. I get to stand where I want to.
That's right. Wait.
We should decide too.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo is another candidate, and he goes last.)
- Okay. - I take the last one left.
(He lost.)
You get to go last.
- It's not me. - Fine.
I swear it's not me. Please.
It's not me!
Viewers, it's not me. Please trust me. Please.
- Okay. - It's not me!
I...
- choose 2. - 2?
I choose one.
I choose three.
- Four for me. - Okay.
That person must have a mission.
Right?
That's right. Maybe they have to be the remaining four.
They might just have to be the remaining four.
- That's true. - It's the remaining three.
The person who falls into the water...
is a bad man.
(This is his gut feeling.)
Bad man?
- Hey. - Bad man?
- What do you mean? - What was that?
He wore his cap like a fool too.
- He's the absolute member. - Go.
Let's start with 1. Number 1.
- One, - Is it this one?
two,
three.
(Se Chan is doing well today. Will he move on?)
- Okay! - Is it a mattress?
(He lands on a mattress 3 times in a row.)
Why is he so lucky?
It's not him.
It can't be the person who wins.
I think they have to be the remaining three.
- This is crazy. - Two.
He's going to lose.
(He lands on a mattress 3 times in a row as well.)
It's either 3 or 4.
Yes!
(They're getting very suspicious.)
It's him then.
It was Haha earlier, so it's him.
- 3 and 4. - Hold on.
It's water and mud, right?
- Yes. - I'm going to fly.
Mud is 4th rank, and water is 3rd.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will be the 3rd rank and raise suspicions?)
(Kwang Soo: 3rd rank, Haha: 4th rank)
It's him. He's the culprit.
- Is it him? - It's him.
- It's him. - No!
- It's him. - It's not me.
- It's not me! - He's the culprit, everybody.
I would have gone for six.
Haha is in 4th rank,
and Kwang Soo is in 3rd.
- 3rd rank? - Right on point.
I think it's Kwang Soo.
Okay. This is good.
This is the final round.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors,
and the winner gets to decide. What do you think?
Okay.
- Rock - The winner gets to decide.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
I...
choose one.
Good. I'll go for two.
Let's get started.
- It was my decision. - Watch.
Ready...
One,
two,
three.
(Jae Seok gets the mattress, and Se Chan gets the mud.)
I survived.
This is cold.
(Jae Seok gets the mattress, and Se Chan gets the mud.)
(Se Chan is in 2nd rank for the 2nd mission.)
How did this happen to me?
- It's Jae Seok. - How!
You're acting strangely.
- What? - How did you win?
I know.
This doesn't make any sense. It's strange you won.
I can't...
- This is strange. - I can't believe it either.
It doesn't make any sense Jae Seok won this game.
- It doesn't. - I'm shocked too.
(Current ranking)
It's either one of these.
It's Jae Seok or Kwang Soo.
But...
If Jae Seok won rock-paper-scissors...
and told me where to go,
I'd have the answer, but I won.
He switched too many times though.
I'm confident.
- Who got third place last time? - Haha.
It was Haha.
Who's in third place this time?
- That's it, everybody. - What do you mean?
This time...
It's either Kwang Soo or Jae Seok.
- I'm so confused. - Think it through. It's not me.
I'm not the absolute member.
- Oh, gosh. - Two people...
will vote at a time.
(They start voting.)
(It's time to decide.)
(Whom did they vote as the absolute member?)
What's the result? I'm curious.
Is it close?
- It's very close. - Really?
It's either one of them.
Here are the results.
Kwang Soo has four votes.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Is it a tie?
Jae Seok also has four.
- It's a tie. - Is it a tie?
(They both have 4 votes, and it's a tie.)
- We'll vote again. - Vote again?
(They decide to vote again for the first time.)
Then let's have them two go in the booth.
They're going to vote for each other.
- Can we discuss? - Obviously.
We're going to vote for each other.
- You should go in the booth. - Okay, let's go.
Come here.
- Hey. - Who is it?
- I think it's Kwang Soo. - What?
- I think it's him. - Do you?
- I think it's Jae Seok. - Me too.
(He thinks it's Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok started in 8th rank.)
(He switched with Seok Jin and avoided the obstacle,)
(but people started to doubt him.)
(Kwang Soo behaved strangely at times,)
(but they were more suspicious because Jae Seok never wins.)
(He's known for being unlucky, but he won.)
- I say it's Jae Seok. - Me too.
Me too.
Come out.
- You two can come out. - Are we good?
(The re-voting has concluded.)
All right. Here are the results.
- Kwang Soo... - Please be nice.
Kwang Soo has 2 votes, and Jae Seok has 6.
(Jae Seok: 6 votes, Kwang Soo: 2 votes)
(The members voted that Jae Seok was the absolute member.)
According to the voting results, you were able to...
(According to the voting results, you were able to...)
Arrest the absolute member.
(They were successful.)
(Jae Seok was the second absolute member.)
You know which numbers advance through the game.
You're the absolute member.
This is...
(He was the absolute member who knew which numbers won.)
Jae Seok is in last place.
(They arrest him right before he won.)
Please bring the penalty list.
(There's a penalty that the winner gets to pick.)
Please choose one.
This is your worst day.
- Slapping forehead. - Forehead?
- Kwang Soo can do it. - Me?
There's a chemistry.
- There's a forehead chemistry. - Okay!
- "Forehead chemistry"? - Show us.
I welcome slaps from Kwang Soo.
I'll save this penalty...
and slap his forehead another time.
(He'll save it for another time.)
- Whenever. - This is great.
(I've seen this before.)
I'll slap him later.
(Jae Seok did that for Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo finally got the penalty in Busan.)
Not now. I'm working right now, so I can't hit him.
- Is this allowed? - There's no time.
This is great.
We can't waste our precious time on this.
- I'll do it another time. - Oh, gosh.
I approve.
(Will this yield an enormous butterfly effect?)
(Number of badges)
This is the last mission to decide on the final ranks.
- It's the Dice of Fate. - What is that?
(Final Mission: Dice of Fate)
Dice?
- Can we turn the tables? - Of course.
Okay, there has to be.
Each member has a standard die with numbers 1 through 6,
and you'll be given more pips...
according to the number of badges you have.
(They get more pips according to the number of badges.)
You can place the additional pips...
on any side of the die you want.
- You get to roll the die twice, - It's the numbers game.
and your final ranks will be decided according to the largest sums.
(Their finals ranks will be decided according to the largest sums.)
You can turn the tables around.
We have to decide if we want to spread the pips out or not.
I should put it all on one side.
(You've got one shot in life.)
It's one side.
- I'm going for one side. - For sure.
- Do we take our dice? - This is too little.
Gosh, this is awesome.
(Haha is currently in 1st place.)
This is driving me nuts. If I lose here, I'm going to cry.
- Haha, I have a side with 10. - 10?
(He has 2 sides with 10, and he spreads out the rest.)
What's that for?
First place.
(1st and 2nd places seek for balance and stability.)
I'm thinking about putting everything on one side.
That works.
I'm going to put it on one side.
It's not all or nothing. It's "all".
It's "all".
If you have trypophobia,
you can look away for a moment.
What's that?
He's incredible.
He has many pips.
(They're done distributing the pips.)
If it's 27, I'm going to go nuts.
- I'm going. - Okay.
- Okay, there's no practice. - All right.
I only have one side.
(He has one empty side, and the rest are equally distributed.)
(He rolls the balanced die.)
Dud.
- I hope it's a dud. - Dud.
(The final ranks will depend on the sum of two rolls.)
I have to be safe.
(Will he keep his 1st place with this die?)
- Dud. - Okay, eight!
It's safe.
(He succeeds. He gets 8 on the 1st try.)
(He has many pips, so it works out for him.)
It's safe.
- I'm jealous. - Me too.
Se Chan is next.
I'm the lucky guy.
(Se Chan's 1st attempt)
What's the highest number you have?
There are 2 sides with 10.
(He has 2 high numbers and 2 empty sides.)
Dud. It's a dud!
(4 sides are distributed safely.)
(How is his 1st attempt?)
- It's a dud. - Dud!
(It's a dud!)
(His dream of winning dissipates.)
(He only had two empty sides.)
That burns.
(Yes, we have a chance too.)
What is this?
I had high numbers on either side.
(Haha: 8, Se Chan: 0)
I put 1 pip each on all 5 sides.
The last side has 27.
(The lucky side of Kwang Soo's die has 27 pips.)
(Practicing)
Okay. I am bound to win if I get this side.
(He is bound to win if he gets the side with 27 pips.)
(He throws the die as he has practiced.)
(He throws powerfully for the one last hope in his life.)
(If the die stops here,)
(Kwang Soo can turn the tables.)
I just need to get this side once.
(Let's see if Kwang Soo's tactic is successful.)
(He gets the side with 1 pip.)
(There is no miracle.)
(Haha comes close to getting outrun.)
(It gives hope to the other tiger moths.)
My goodness. I thought he would succeed.
He almost ended the game.
(The current score in Round 1)
Do you have 27 pips on that side?
- Do you have 27 pips on that side? - Yes, I do.
(She copies Kwang Soo, the senior tiger moth.)
I have 27 pips on a single side as well.
- Okay. - Please.
- Please let her get a dud. - A dud.
- A dud. - A dud.
(So Min hurls the die.)
(For a tiger moth, it's all or nothing.)
- My goodness. - I got startled for a second.
(She gets the side with 0 pips.)
(The wings of the tiger moth gets burnt.)
- I knew it. - Okay.
- They went all in. - It keeps you on your toes.
The tiger moths don't disappoint.
- This is driving me crazy. - Move back.
- It's okay. - The tiger moths don't disappoint.
- I still have a chance. - I will get it the next time.
Jump right in.
- Is it my turn? Okay. - Jump right in.
- All right. - Here I go.
Give me a decent number of pips.
Don't go sideways!
(Unless he gets 0 pips, he is sure to join the high rank.)
(Jong Kook gets the side with 0 pips.)
(His despair gives the others hope.)
- Goodness... - How is this possible?
Jong Kook is unlucky today.
Please.
Come on.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
(Rise, my lucky energy.)
Two pips.
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook aren't doing so well today.
(The ace members are suffering.)
I never thought a day like this would come to me.
- Haha is in the first place. - This is incredible.
(We didn't know we could be this unlucky.)
A side with 20 pips and a side with 7 pips.
(All the other sides except for 2 have 0 pips.)
(He has no choice but to make a drastic bet.)
A dud.
(Let's see if Seok Jin will succeed.)
(No way! He gets the side with 20 pips!)
(Seok Jin, the tiger moth, succeeds after going all in.)
(He experiences a miracle in his 50s.)
- No way! - I got the side with 20 pips.
(I can't believe my eyes.)
(Why didn't it work for me?)
You only get one shot in life!
Bring it on.
- That was insane. - Why did you do that, Seok Jin?
We get two throws.
- I got the side with 20 pips. - If...
If I fail here, I won't get to win.
Please. Please let me do this.
(I have to do something...)
(before I admit to my defeat.)
(Jae Seok distributed the stickers on two sides.)
(His die has 2 sides with 13 pips.)
- It's a dud. - A dud.
(The die rolls towards a side with 13 pips.)
(A side with 13 pips can give him a chance to turn the tables.)
It's a dud.
(It's a dud.)
(Goodbye, Jae Seok's chance of turning the tables.)
It's a dud.
(He is an unlucky member through and through.)
Jae Seok.
There is a high chance I will win. It looks like I will win.
(The 1st round ends with the members' joy and despair.)
(Seok Jin: 20, Haha: 8, Ji Hyo: 2, Kwang Soo: 1,)
(the rest: 0.)
Here I go.
(Haha wants to secure his position in the 2nd place.)
All right.
Did you spread the stickers?
(Please let it be a dud.)
(Let's see what Haha gets on his 2nd attempt.)
Okay! I did it!
(He gets the side with 9 pips.)
(He is currently in the 2nd place with a score of 17.)
Okay! I did it! Nine pips.
- 9 pips. - 9 pips.
I did it.
Here I go.
(Se Chan's 2nd attempt)
Please let it be a high number.
Please let it be a high number. There you go!
(He gets the side with 9 pips this time.)
- Nine pips. - Okay.
It's not half bad. Okay!
- Are you ready? - Okay.
(Kwang Soo's 2nd attempt)
- I will get the side with 27 pips. - He might get it.
I bet he will get it.
I bet he will get the side with one pip.
(Come on out, the side with 27 pips.)
(Is the die rolling towards that direction?)
(Hold on.)
I bet he will get the side with one pip.
(Let's see if he will place 1st with a lucky shot.)
(He gets the side with 1 pip again.)
(What are the odds?)
(You are in the lower rank.)
It's over.
I thought he would get it.
Seriously.
(Please let me avoid the lowest rank.)
Please.
(So Min's 2nd attempt)
(She wants to turn the tables this time.)
Three pips.
(The side has 3 pips.)
(The tiger moth gets the side with 3 pips.)
- You still beat Kwang Soo. - No!
You still beat Kwang Soo.
(How much more must I fall?)
The ground is caved.
Is it my turn?
(Ji Hyo is in the 5th place alongside Kwang Soo.)
Please.
(Let's see what Ji Hyo's final score will be.)
A dud. My goodness.
- 9 pips. - 9 pips.
(Ji Hyo is in the 4th place with a score of 11.)
Then I should move the stickers to one side.
(The members on the bottom become busy.)
I should have 11 pips on one side.
Jae Seok is busy.
He is so busy.
It's hard to play this game without many pips.
- Five. - This is bad.
Is it my turn? This is bad. I am going all in.
- What will you do if you fail? - I am going all in.
(Jong Kook puts 19 pips on a single side.)
A lot of sides are empty.
- You aren't usually like this. - I am going all in.
He is going all in.
I have no other choice.
I have to.
(I need to get the side with 19 pips.)
I am going all in.
(He throws the die to make up for the past failure.)
(Can Jong Kook turn the tables?)
- My goodness. - Yes!
(It's a dud again.)
- Dud! - He is in the last place.
(Jong Kook gets 2 duds in a row and ranks last.)
- Jong Kook. - I just need one pip.
Why did you do that? That's so unlike you.
Jae Seok is so busy.
I just need one pip.
It's your last attempt.
Jong Kook.
All right.
(Jong Kook is in the last place alongside Jae Seok.)
- Here I go. - Okay.
(Jae Seok is Jong Kook's rival.)
I bet he will get a dud.
(He distributes the pips so that only one side is empty.)
- How many pips are there? - Seven.
I am in the fifth place.
It's impressive that I moved up that much.
Okay. One more time. Please do me this favor.
- Seok Jin. - If he gets the same side...
Let's get the same side one more time!
(Let's get the side with 20 pips 1 more time!)
(On his 1st attempt, he went all in and took the 1st place.)
(Let's see if he recreates the glorious moment.)
(No way! He gets the side with 20 pips again.)
(Seok Jin is on a roll today.)
(Screaming)
What is going on?
(Is this real?)
(They witness a miracle.)
- It's over. - It's over.
(Screaming)
- It's over. - The world is mine!
The world is mine!
(He feels like his times of struggles are over.)
It's over.
What did we do all day?
(He is dejected.)
How did I get this side twice? This is insane.
(The legendary penalty begins soon.)
In a surprising turn of events,
Jong Kook is in the last place with a score of zero.
The penalty is called the Collective Love and Penalty.
(Collective Love and Penalty)
Starting from the member in the first place,
you will use the tool you are given to throw water at the next member.
(Use the tool you are given to throw water at the next member.)
Then Seok Jin won't get the penalty.
No, I won't.
He will be dry.
Are you in the seventh place? For goodness' sake.
(Why is it Kwang Soo of all people?)
Why is Kwang Soo in the seventh place?
In the interview, I said I'd work hard to beat you.
- Let's go. - That's cute.
Haha, clink the cups.
Cheers.
(Seok Jin holds a small cup.)
(The 2nd place simply gets his face moisturized.)
That's cute.
(Haha throws Ji Hyo a glass of water.)
(She gets moisturized more than Haha.)
(I can feel the water on me.)
It's annoying, right?
Ji Hyo, what you suffered is nothing.
- Okay. - It's annoying, right?
- Okay? - Okay.
Why are you directing your anger at me?
- Okay. It's the collective love. - The collective love.
Check out how much I love you, Se Chan.
- Move out or you'll get hit. - It'll hurt.
(Se Chan, I love you this much.)
Jae Seok, why are you wet?
(Why is Jae Seok already wet?)
(When Ji Hyo threw the water,)
(Jae Seok got hit while watching.)
- Okay. - Okay. I got hit.
- Okay. - I got hit.
- Okay. Did you get hit? - I got hit.
(That's your business.)
(Is that a drenched grasshopper?)
- My goodness. - Okay.
(Here is the side effect of the collective love.)
(You can become very ugly.)
Okay.
So Min, come here.
(Jae Seok throws So Min a washbowl of water.)
- Okay. - Okay.
- Okay. - Hey, I was worried about you.
Hey, I was worried about you.
- 1, 2... - Gosh, that's big.
(So Min has a big bucket for him.)
- Three. - Look at her. She's not strong.
It was heavy even for us.
(Splashing)
(He can't handle her affection towards him.)
Good job. Well done.
- Great. So Min, good job. - Okay.
- He fell back right away. - That was awesome.
Look at Jong Kook. I thought he was a staff member.
(Feeling dejected)
Okay.
- Okay. - Pass on the love to him.
(This is today's highlight.)
- This is fun. - Please crouch down.
- Okay. - Give me a second.
(Wringing)
I have more water in here.
(He squeezes out every ounce of affection from So Min.)
There's a lot.
This one will be strong. There's a lot of water.
One,
two...
(His love fills the huge bucket for the finale.)
- You should splash from afar. - Why are you nervous?
- This feels great. - Great, great.
I'll do it right away.
(Splashing)
(I'll return all the love you have given me so far.)
(His love is as vast as the ocean.)
It was like a bomb.
Wait, Jong Kook.
(Startled)
(Okay. Your turn is over.)
What should I do?
I didn't do anything wrong.
- Jong Kook is mad. - Listen to me. That's not it.
- Jong Kook is mad. - Okay.
I had a feeling that you guys were getting too comfortable.
- That's not it. - Great.
No, no. I'm in seventh. I had no choice.
- He's really mad. - Are you all right?
- Gosh, that's cold. - I had a bit of water left.
(He stays faithful to the end.)
Okay. This is great.
The winner of today's race is...
How many years has it been?
- Jong Kook was placed last. - Seriously.
Seok Jin won the race. I wonder if this has ever happened before.
Hold on. He won the race,
but he only splashed the shot glass. Is that it?
- All right. - Seok Jin, here's your trophy.
Here's the trophy.
(His victory seems insignificant compared to this historical moment.)
Seok Jin, here's the hat.
Congratulations on your winning, Seok Jin!
(We never know when he'll win again.)
This is a great accomplishment.
(Darkness falls on the night of Halloween.)
(The festival of the ghosts has begun.)
(One by one, mysterious ghosts...)
(are assembling.)
(And important guests have come at the news of the festival.)
(Ahn Hyo Seop, Son Na Eun, and Seo Young Hee)
We're wearing this for this game.
(The festival with ghosts who have a lot of grudges begins.)
(They can't ever get enough of laughter.)
(They start fulfilling their wishes on this variety show.)
(However...)
(Someone has opened up a box that wasn't supposed to be open.)
(And this awakens the ghosts' instincts.)
(And the real identities of the ghosts are revealed.)
(There is an uninvited guest among them.)
(What on earth happened here?)
(The Nightmare of Halloween)