Skip to 1:20
- My gosh, that looks good. - Is that so?
We can't eat a lot here.
- We should order two bowls. - Let's do that. Let's share.
- Let's share them. - We can save money too.
I can order. Tell the server that we're ready.
This isn't hard.
- Ordering food isn't that hard. - Excuse me.
- Soba, soba. - Soba?
- The best soba. - The best soba?
- Give us two bowls. - Yes, the best soba.
- 2 bowls, please. - 2 bowls.
(Two bowls?)
Thank you.
I didn't remember "two". I almost said, "this and this".
(This and this, please.)
- What does that mean? - "This and this".
It means, this and this.
- This and this? - Hey, but we are in trouble.
If this goes wrong, we'll end up eating too much.
This is my fourth meal.
(They started eating from Incheon International Airport.)
(He even ate the in-flight meal.)
How many meals will I eat today?
- We're going to get full. - Soba is served.
Here it is.
- It was fast. - My gosh.
(Okinawa soba made with flour and pork broth is flavorful.)
Did we order one with hot soup?
I wanted to eat cold soba.
We can slurp cold soba though.
- This must be the trotter. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Isn't that a perilla leaf?
- Yes, it is. - I wanted to eat cold soba.
Hey, we are supposed to use individual bowls for this.
- What? - My goodness.
We only ordered two bowls.
(They already have 2 bowls. There are 2 more bowls of soba?)
That...
- We only ordered two. - Earlier, how many...
- Is that on the house? - Is it?
- Is that on the house? - What are you talking about?
- Thank you. - Sure.
(They must eat 1 bowl each. What on earth just happened?)
- This is bad. - I'm so flustered.
- Excuse me. Is this steak? - Hey.
Because we repeated, "2 bowls", it's 4 bowls in total.
(When they were ordering earlier,)
(two bowls of soba...)
(were put together with two more bowls.)
(I see. They want to order four bowls in total.)
(Everyone kept saying, "two bowls".)
- One person should order. - Hey.
- Hey, you. - I said it once. He repeated it.
- We have four bowls now. - I mean...
- Come on. This is ludicrous. - Seriously.
I don't like hot soup. I like cold soup.
- Drop it. - You ordered the wrong one.
- The chunk of meat is big too. - It's hard to eat now.
- This is crazy. What will I do? - My gosh.
Four bowls of soba are too much.
- We should've ordered only one. - We should have.
We should have ordered one.
It's good, but...
- It is good. - It tastes like ramyeon.
(It's chewy and delicious though.)
We were supposed to order cold soba.
I asked the owner. Okinawa soba isn't cold.
- There isn't cold soba here. - It's different from Kyoto soba.
What if someone else recommends us soba?
- Then I'll order cold soba. - We can't go to the same place.
You'll have to go to the restaurant the person recommends you.
- This is crazy. - Let's eat cold soba next then.
- No, only in Kyoto... - There isn't cold soba in Okinawa.
- You can find it in Kyoto. - No, there must be.
You were happy that Japan was close. Now, you're all grumpy.
This isn't to my liking.
(I'll be honest.)
- You know? - You don't seem to like it.
- I want to eat something good too. - This is why...
This is why everyone criticizes him.
- You saw, right? He was elated. - I want to really enjoy this too.
- He has mood swings. - I must've reached menopause.
I have mood swings now.
- You finished eating soba. - Okay.
We'll spin the globe now.
- We have to spin it again. - Are we going to do it here?
- Let's do well this time. - So Min, you practiced this.
You have to say, "Start."
- We only have one chance. - Can I practice once?
- You want to practice once? - All right.
Hold this. Hold it.
(As she feels nervous and anxious, she practices first.)
(Cashier at a convenience store)
- That was great. - The cashier is a nice choice.
- Cashier at a convenience store. - Okay.
Okay, everyone. You can go outside, find a convenience store, and ask.
- Let's get out. - We did it.
- Okay. - Let's hurry.
The producer is a bit scatterbrained because he didn't get much sleep.
The bill. We almost forgot the bill.
We definitely said we were practicing.
We said it was a practice, but the producer...
- My gosh, this is great. - Let's go out.
- Okay. - Where did Seok Jin go?
(Seok Jin went to the bathroom.)
He's high-maintenance.
- He really is. - It's too tight here.
We have to eat Japanese rice balls since we are here.
- What? - Rice balls.
Whatever they are, I can't eat anymore today.
If we keep this up, I might...
I might poop on the street.
(Jae Seok gets close to taking care of his business on the street.)
- We ate too much. - That'd be horrible.
Jae Seok, I feel really gassy now.
Exactly. I think I heard you fart a few times, but pretended I didn't.
It was one of those silent farts.
I got the feeling that she was full too. She's in trouble too.
It's just that we didn't talk about this. She keeps farting.
We ate so much. I've never eaten this much in my life.
- Do we need to do more? - It's 7:25pm.
It's hard for us to get on a plane tonight.
- Won't the restaurants close soon? - What?
- Won't they close soon? - In my opinion,
we can try one more place.
If we succeed today but can't find a flight back to Korea,
- we can go back tomorrow morning. - We can return in the morning.
- Seriously. - Should we get going?
Why can't I find a convenience store?
- Usually, there are tons here. - I can't find a single one.
- Okinawa. - What is this?
- That's pizza. - This is an empty street.
Why can't we find a convenience store? Japan has a lot of them.
- Seriously. Not even a single one. - This is quite flustering.
We shouldn't be walking aimlessly. Think about our step counters.
Here's the store. It's like a supermarket.
- Here is the convenience store. - "Food Market".
- This isn't a convenience store. - Let's see if they're doing well.
(That's a market.)
- They are the same. - They are interchangeable.
- They aren't? - We have step counters. Come on.
- Until when must we walk? - What are we doing here?
- Market and convenience stores... - Aren't they the same thing?
(My gosh, you're picky.)
My gosh, I can't find a convenience store here.
- Hold on. Producer Jung. - Why can't we find one?
You can't take us without a plan.
What are you doing to us?
You should ask and find one nearby.
Hold on. Who is this? Someone keeps farting when we're walking.
My gosh, someone keeps farting in front of us.
Hold on a second. Stop right here.
Hey, wait a minute. This is serious.
Hold on. Which one of you keeps farting in front of the group?
- It's not me. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Seriously.
- Who's doing that? - At the immigration checkpoint,
Seok Jin let me go before him. He has never done that for me.
- I wondered why he was generous. - No.
- Seok Jin. - It's because he farted.
You've gotten the wrong idea. It was not me.
- Everyone. - If it smells this bad,
- In front of us... - it means you need to poop soon.
Front of us...
- It will turn into poop soon. - Why do you keep doing that?
Excuse me. I'll be honest. Japanese food doesn't agree with me.
To be honest, it doesn't agree with me.
- I don't care about a food trip. - I am sorry, but...
I want to eat kimchi jjigae.
Seok Jin.
- Why? - Don't keep walking in front of us.
- Fall back to fart. - Fall back to fart.
All of us have upset stomachs.
- Let's mind our manners. - Okay.
- Mind your manners, and fall back. - Let's bring our hands together.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go. - Let's go. Let's keep going.
(Do they think it will help?)
Isn't that a convenience store?
- You are right. It's Lawson. - Is it a convenience store?
(They finally find a convenience store.)
He looks like he would like steak.
(They find an employee they have a good feeling about.)
(They succeed the mission if he recommends steak.)
If there are no flights tonight after we succeed the mission,
- we can take a flight tomorrow. - We can take a flight tomorrow.
(They buy a few items.)
Ask him.
(Kyeong Hwan takes the lead and asks.)
Excuse me.
(Is he speaking the Gyeongsang dialect?)
(Staccato)
(Stuttering)
(He asks the question,)
("Please recommend us a dish and a restaurant.")
(They succeed the mission if he recommends steak.)
(Which dish will the employee recommend?)
Ramen.
(He recommends ramen.)
- Ramen? - Ramen?
(They doubt their ears.)
(Do they need to eat noodles again?)
- Stop it. - Ramen?
- Ramen? - I see.
There is a good restaurant nearby.
(Frustrated)
Thank you.
Which ramen restaurant?
He is kind.
He is drawing us a map.
Thank you.
(They thank the kind employee and head to the ramen restaurant.)
Who knew it'd be ramen?
- Ramen. - We need to eat noodles again.
(At 8pm, they head to the ramen restaurant.)
That must be the ramen restaurant...
- at the corner. - The lights are on.
- There it is. - I am so full.
(They find the ramen restaurant in a quiet alley.)
(How does it taste?)
He makes it on the spot.
(The harmony of rich chicken broth and freshly-cooked noodles)
(The specialty of Okinawa, chicken ramen, is served.)
Thank you.
- It smells good. - It smells good.
It looks delicious.
(Chicken ramen is a noodle dish with chicken broth and pork.)
This one has lighter broth.
Does the seafood ramen taste okay?
Does the seafood ramen taste good?
(No matter how full they are, they always welcome tasty noodles.)
(The dish suits Seok Jin's taste.)
This is...
tastier than soba.
- It's really tasty. - The tasty dish...
makes me want to go out for another round.
(He clears the bowl in an instant.)
Let's call it a night and start tomorrow morning.
Thank you.
It's an incredibly tasty dish.
- It's tasty. - It's tasty.
(It's very tasty.)
The day ended after two meals.
I am so full.
The day ended after a series of meals.
It looks like...
we are 15-minute walk away from the hotel.
- This is a countryside. - Let's take a taxi.
We should take a taxi.
Why don't we ask the taxi driver?
- Ask what? - The mission question.
The menu.
- You want to practice? - Yes. Let's practice.
- Will anyone recommend steak? - Excuse me.
Please recommend us a dish and a restaurant.
Okinawa soba.
- Soba? - It's soba again.
(Okinawa soba)
- Soba. - Soba.
Most people recommend Okinawa soba.
If number one is soba,
- what is number 2? - Number 2?
What would it be?
I guess it's steak.
- Steak. - I guess it's steak.
Steak.
He recommended steak.
We might have better luck tomorrow.
That's it.
(They arrive at the hotel.)
- It's clean. - It's nice.
Thank you.
Your mission is over for the day.
- We will have to stop. - The restaurants are closed.
- The restaurants are closed. - We are exhausted.
We will check the step counters before you go into the hotel.
The step counter.
Mine is strange. The count goes up even when I stand still.
- Okay. - You don't stand still.
When you go to bed, wear the step counter.
Do we need to wear it to bed?
Are we the only ones who have to do this?
- Other teams... - They have to do it, too.
If the count is 20,000 when you wake up, you are sleeping.
- Where should I wear it? - I have no spare clothes.
- Where should I wear it? - I don't know what to do.
- What? - We have no spare clothes.
- Hold on. - Seriously.
Producer.
How am I supposed to wear it when I have no spare clothes?
Wear it on your hair.
Wear it on your hair like a hairpin.
We can't sleep in these clothes.
(They check in at the lobby.)
Are there three beds?
- Are there three beds? - Yes.
Beds. 1, 1, and 1.
(He chimes in.)
(Laughing)
1 bed. 2 rooms.
They might give you six beds.
- 3 beds. 3 beds. - Don't say anything.
- Don't confuse him. - We can draw a picture.
Don't say anything.
- Thank you. Bye. - Thank you.
(White room and men in white)
Steak.
- It's steak. - It's steak.
(There is steak on TV.)
We will eat it tomorrow.
(This trip ends when we eat it.)
Is that an iron griddle?
- That's what we need to eat. - That's what we need to eat.
That's what we need to eat.
I hope we don't get another recommendation for soba.
(He takes off the camera and films the TV.)
I will film it.
The camera needs to film us.
I want to film steak.
- Did I position it right? - Yes, you did.
We are like Andre Kim.
(3 men in white)
We are dressed in white.
It looks oily.
I bet it tastes delicious.
(They fall asleep and dream about steak.)
(They feel like they will be able to take the morning flight.)
- The weather is amazing. - It's refreshing.
The sunlight is nice.
You know,
that's the International Street.
It's the busiest street in Okinawa.
Let's go.
This place makes me really feel like I am in Japan.
This place...
- is Japan through and through. - Seriously.
(International street has souvenir shops, restaurants, etc.)
- I am in a good mood. - Me too.
(Seok Jin is in a good mood.)
Coming to the International Street put me in a good mood.
(Seok Jin's mood is very different from yesterday.)
There is steak everywhere.
- This restaurant serves steak. - There is steak everywhere.
(People in the International Street are bound to recommend steak.)
- It's time to spin the globe. - My goodness.
(The globe that will seal their fate appears.)
Who wants to go?
I will go.
- Celebrate 10,000 counts. - I will celebrate 10,000 counts.
- I will celebrate 10,000 counts. - We will start right away.
- We will start right away. - Yes.
In 1, 2, 3. Start.
The man with 10,000 counts will go.
(Who is the first person to recommend a dish?)
- The step counter... - What is it?
A convenience store employee.
(It's a lucky choice.)
- A convenience store employee. - That's good.
- We are off to a good start. - It's not bad.
Someone whose last name is Suzuki or people who are over 90...
- are difficult choices. - Let's go.
There must be a lot of convenience stores.
I found one. It's a convenience store, right?
(They find a convenience store right away.)
It's a convenience store.
Steak.
- It's a busy street. - Steak.
Steak. Steak.
(There is a steakhouse in front of the convenience store.)
- Let's get it. - Let's get it.
(They enter the convenience store with hope.)
Hi.
(Whom should we ask?)
Who wants to ask?
Let's ask him.
Hi.
(A male employee is bound to prefer steak.)
He is an employee. I will ask him.
Excuse me.
Please recommend us a dish and a restaurant.
(The International Street is full of steakhouses.)
(Let's see if the employee recommends steak.)
Osoba.
Osoba?
(Osoba is soba with an honorific, O.)
It's soba, but he added an honorific, O.
Soba?
Soba. Yes.
(Are you serious?)
(I am serious.)
(Their prayer to get something other than soba goes unanswered.)
Soba.
(She is in a daze.)
You know...
(This can't be real.)
Most people recommend soba.
Please recommend us a restaurant.
Please ask him to recommend us a restaurant.
The best restaurant. The best restaurant.
- The best? - Yes.
I recommend C restaurant.
Please give us the address.
Everyone is so kind...
- to draw us a map. - I know.
This is the restaurant.
Thank you.
- Soba? - Soba.
- Thank you. - There are set menus.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Bye.
We still have soba in our stomachs...
from yesterday.
- This is crazy. - Had you chosen soba,
this mission would have ended yesterday.
That's true.
- We would be in Seoul already. - I told you.
Listen.
At the airport,
- I said we should eat soba. - When did this happen?
- I said we should eat soba, right? - Did you?
(They talked about a dish they wanted to eat at Naha Airport.)
Let's eat this. Okinawa soba.
We need meat.
(We should eat meat.)
- Didn't I mention soba? - Did you?
(He gets angry.)
- I'm not lying. - You...
You said it, but we all mentioned it.
- Seriously. - Right.
Let's go to the restaurant that he recommended.
(Let's go to the best soba restaurant.)
(They ask for directions.)
(It's difficult to find locals who know the restaurant.)
- Do you know this soba restaurant? - A soba restaurant?
- Right. - Yes, I know this restaurant.
- Soba restaurant? - I think she knows.
- She knows. - I think she does.
- Is it delicious? - Yes.
- Is it delicious? - Yes, it is.
- Is it the same as Okinawa soba? - It's quite far.
Yes, it's Okinawa soba.
- I see. - Is it Okinawa soba?
- What else do they have? - Okay.
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal. - Thank you.
(They get on a taxi.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
Excuse us.
- Where's the address? - I have it.
- There we go. - All right.
Anyway, we had soba yesterday.
We also have soba today.
This will be our last soba.
Let's make plans while we eat.
I think it'll be delicious.
I also think that it'll be tasty.
I'm certain of it.
(They ride the taxi for a while.)
I have a bad feeling. It's the mart that we passed yesterday.
- Really? - Yes.
It's the mart that we passed yesterday.
(Looking for a convenience store last night)
(It's yesterday's market which looks quite familiar.)
- Don't say that. - I'm sure.
Don't ever say that.
- Stop talking nonsense. - I'm serious.
- That's nonsense. - We passed by this street.
In Japan...
- Isn't the restaurant on the left? - That's nonsense.
The neighborhoods are...
- We passed by that street. - Hey.
Isn't that the restaurant?
(Is it the same restaurant as yesterday's?)
(It's the Okinawa soba restaurant that they went to yesterday.)
- My goodness. - Gosh.
Is this the place?
Oh, my goodness.
No way.
(There's no way.)
- Is that really it? - Listen.
Did we just arrive at the airport?
I can't believe it.
(Seok Jin didn't like the soba yesterday.)
Is this the right place?
How could this happen?
(Time is the only thing that changed.)
Where are you going? It's this way.
Come this way.
- Are we back? - Are we really back here again?
Come on. It's here.
How is this possible?
We went out to the city.
- How are we back here? - I've seen this before.
(Screaming)
It's like we're in a maze.
I'm only a guest, so I'm leaving.
To be honest,
can't I just leave?
I'm excited.
(Team Between Friends is on three missions in Thailand.)
This is unbelievable.
We didn't have a chance to travel like this.
- Right? - It's great.
- Once we get to Pattaya, - We're heading to Pattaya.
we have a mission.
- It's a drawing competition. - "Drawing Competition".
Jong Kook, there's a problem.
- What is it? - We should...
contact a Thai celebrity beforehand.
We should.
How about the one I mentioned?
- Namcha? - Yes.
(While selecting their missions as soon as they arrived,)
(Shorry said that he knew a Thai celebrity named Namcha.)
(Who is Namcha?)
(She is talented in singing, dancing, and acting.)
(She's a Thai multi-talented entertainer.)
(Does Shorry know such a popular Thai celebrity?)
- You should contact her. - Okay.
Send a message.
Why are you starting your social network site instead?
- I'll send a message from it. - I see.
Don't you know her number?
We're only acquaintances online.
He's her follower.
How are you different from her fans?
The difference is that she's also my follower.
- I see. - So I can send her messages.
- Thanks to YG Entertainment, - Right.
- Byung Jae knows... - It's a member of BLACKPINK.
- Lisa? - Yes, Lisa.
I'll send her a text to see what she's up to.
Do that.
She could be back in Thailand.
I'll contact Nichkhun.
- Nichkhun is a good choice. - Will you call him directly?
Is Seok Cheon around?
He only runs a Thai restaurant.
I see.
What do you think about that, Byung Jae?
Let's forgive him once.
If he does it again...
- I got a response. - Who is it?
- It's from Namcha. - He's your prey.
I wrote, "I'm Shorry. I'm in Thailand. Are you busy?"
She wrote, "Hello." What does "kinda" mean?
It means "a little bit".
She's kind of busy.
When you asked her, she said that she's a bit busy.
- Really? - Is she busy?
She's quite famous in Thailand, so she must be busy.
(Will they succeed in meeting a Thai celebrity?)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Do you want to hear something creepy?
Yes.
At the airport,
I sent a text message to Na Eun.
(Jong Kook sent a message to Na Eun about traveling with them.)
(That'd be amazing if she traveled with us.)
She hadn't called me back, so...
I wasn't thinking about it.
Apparently, she's in Thailand.
(Na Eun is in Thailand.)
(Is Son Na Eun in Thailand?)
- Really? In Thailand? - Yes.
Don't lie. Stop trying to tease me.
Na Eun is really in Thailand.
- Stop lying. - It's true.
- Was she invited? - She's traveling with her family.
- On a family trip? - With her family?
She didn't know that we were coming, right?
Of course.
(Na Eun was Se Chan's partner.)
(Is she in Thailand as well?)
Wait, Jong Kook.
(How is this possible?)
They wouldn't bring me here for a prank, right?
- I'm not that important. - No.
- You're not that important. - Right?
- It's a coincidence. - Right.
- I knew it. - You aren't that important.
Does that mean that it's fate?
(Is this fate?)
- Do you like her? - I'm her fan, and we were partners.
- Were you? - We were partners twice.
- Really? - Yes.
You can have hopes for romance.
- Meeting that person... - That's right.
somewhere abroad.
- It's good to see them in Korea. - Right.
I got a hold of Na Eun.
- Really? - Yes.
- Can we say hello? - Of course.
- Hello? - Na Eun.
- Hello. - Na Eun.
- Is it really Na Eun? - What's going on?
I'm on a family trip in Thailand.
Right. I'm sorry...
for bothering you while you're on a family trip.
(Se Chan listens carefully.)
- It's okay. - Is it?
I'm with Se Chan right now.
Oh, really?
(She speaks more slowly.)
(Oh, really?)
Gosh. Hello, Na Eun. This is Se Chan.
- Hello. - It's been a long time.
Na Eun, Se Chan thinks that...
it's fate that you're both in Thailand.
- Fate? - Yes.
(Isn't it our fate that we're both in Thailand?)
Is that so?
(Isn't it?)
- Na Eun. - Yes?
We're going to a night market in Bangkok later.
- Really? - Would you be free?
(Will you go to the night market with me?)
I like night markets.
(She accepts the invitation.)
(They're excited.)
(The boys get lucky.)
- Yes. - Na Eun.
- See you later, Na Eun. - Bye.
- See you later. - See you.
- Hello, I'm Shorry of Mighty Mouth. - Don't say that.
(What's wrong with you?)
See you later.
- Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
You're amazing. You do everything for us.
You're the best.
It's a twist of fate.
- We work well as a team. - Thank you.
By the way...
(A loud sound)
He keeps farting.
No, I didn't.
(A loud sound)
(Jong Kook, please scold him.)
(He denies it.)
- Hey, you. - Why do you keep farting?
I didn't fart.
- Stop farting. - I didn't. He's lying.
The camera recorded the sound.
I'm not insane. Why would I fart in front of so many cameras?
(Is Byung Jae insane?)
(Where did the sound come from?)
(Another sound)
He farted.
(What's wrong? I didn't fart.)
(It's the first occurrence.)
(Another thud)
(Soon enough, there's the second thud.)
(Here's the ultimate one.)
(He lifts himself up.)
(It's the third time when the sound and movement are suspicious.)
(Why do you keep lying?)
You punk.
He keeps farting in this position.
He keeps farting without stopping.
Are you comfortable with Jong Kook now?
Even I don't fart in front of him.
- I didn't fart. - Does he keep farting?
While he pretends...
to listen to you, he farts off of his seat.
That makes no sense.
This show is for people over 12, and my family is watching.
That's absurd.
You farted.
- Good thing that it didn't smell. - There's an elephant.
- Where? - Where?
- Where's an elephant? - Oh, my.
Over there. To the left.
- To the left. - It's walking.
What's that? It's so huge.
I've never seen an elephant before.
Is this a zoo?
- We're here. - We're here.
- Let's go. - Here we are.
(Asia's largest tropical park)
(This 6,600,000m² park is full of things to see and do.)
I see something.
Jong Kook, look at those birds.
- Birds. - They're alive.
There are birds. We have to pay to take pictures.
- We have to pay. - Really?
- There's a tiger. - Can we take a picture with it?
- It's a tiger. - It's a real tiger.
It's real.
Be quiet.
- Unbelievable. It's a tiger. - It's a tiger.
- I can't believe it. - It's so close.
Is it a pet?
If you annoy him, he might bite you.
It's staring at us. Look away.
Shouldn't we take a picture with it?
Jong Kook. Can you take a picture with the tiger?
- You're the tiger. - You're the tiger.
- Should I take one? - Do it.
Excuse me. Here's the Korean tiger.
One person, please.
This is crazy.
(Scared)
(Jong Kook sits next to the tiger.)
My goodness.
Jong Kook.
(What is he doing?)
Say cheese.
(He meets his relative.)
Okay.
(Nice to meet you, friend.)
(Byung Jae is frightened.)
It felt weird.
(Is Byung Jae going to do it?)
(Getting up)
- It's getting up. - It's getting up.
- It's getting up. - Byung Jae.
(As Byung Jae approaches, the tiger gets up.)
(Frozen)
Could it be the color of your sweater?
(Why did I say I'd do this?)
(Yawning)
(Come take a picture with me.)
(Our eyes met.)
How is this possible?
(The tiger looks more frightening than ever.)
(Byung Jae sits next to it, scared.)
Smile.
(Smile)
- It'll be a nice memory. - Right.
(Roar)
(Let's be friends.)
Amazing.
It was amazing. Good job.
- Should we get some t-shirts? - Let's get some new clothes.
Let's go inside.
(It's cool inside the shopping mall.)
There are many clothes.
There are. Flower-printed shirts.
What do you say to flower-printed shirts?
- What about this? - We could all wear one of these.
- This one. - Hey.
- All four of us. - It'll be nice and cool.
Friends are supposed to do that.
Let's vote.
- Me. Let's wear these shorts. - Let's all wear them.
- Let's all wear them. - These?
- Yes. - We're friends.
(They change into their uniforms.)
(Colorful)
There's an elephant.
Where?
- Isn't that a sculpture? - No. It's moving.
It's real.
(Artist elephants)
(Sunday, male, painter)
Hi.
How sweet.
(Nice to meet you, Sunday.)
- Oh, my. - It feels nice.
- Hi. - He's only three years old?
(Waving)
(Nice to meet you guys.)
- Here. - Oh, my.
(He's stealing the guys' hearts.)
- He's very sweet. - He's so cute.
What are you doing?
(Standing on two feet)
(Let me show you my skills.)
(In love)
He is showing off his skills.
- Right. - I know.
- Good job, Sunday. - Thanks, Sunday.
Here's the mission.
All of you will make a painting...
- on the same subject as Sunday, - All of us?
and the park visitors will take a vote.
The subject is Sunday's favorite, landscape.
- Landscape? Okay. - Are we painting a landscape?
I don't think we'll lose to an elephant.
How well could an elephant paint?
I'm not sure I'll paint better than the elephant.
We have to win.
- Sunday. - We'll beat you.
It's a competition.
Ready.
What if he paints very fast?
Get ready, and...
start.
- Seriously? - What if he is too fast?
(Let me see.)
(Team Between Friends start painting right away.)
(They look very serious.)
(This game is supposed to be fun, but it's getting too tense.)
(How well could an elephant paint?)
(Painting)
(Sunday holds the brush with his trunk.)
(Sketching)
(The audience is fascinated.)
(Meanwhile,)
(the human contestants...)
(Quick strokes)
(He is smudging the canvas with green paint.)
(Byung Jae is an impressionist.)
You're doing very well.
(Shorry actually majored in arts.)
(His painting looks nice,)
(but his movement looks frivolous.)
(With his lips tight,)
(Jong Kooks is making a detailed painting.)
What are you painting?
What is that?
A tree.
I just need some brown.
Use purple if you don't have brown.
(The human contestants use brush strokes.)
(Tapping)
(The elephant relaxedly taps the canvas with his trunk.)
(He reminds you...)
(of the man who used to paint so effortlessly.)
(Bob Ross)
(A landscape painting is a piece of cake.)
The elephant is speeding up.
- He's so fast. - My goodness.
(How can he be so fast?)
I messed up.
(Sunday is finishing up.)
I need some red.
- Red. - I need brown.
We don't have any. Use purple instead.
I messed up.
(Sunday is finished.)
(Time is up.)
Stop.
(The competition is over.)
Already?
- It's already over? - My goodness.
Jong Kook and Shorry did a good job.
Good job, Shorry.
(Shorry's painting has a sense of dimension.)
- No. - It looks very nice.
Mine looks weird.
- But Byung Jae... - Your canvas is...
full at least. It'll stand out.
(What is this?)
Isn't that a planarian?
Why did I paint a mushroom?
- Se Chan's shouldn't be chosen. - Then we'll be doomed.
Gosh.
Mine is bad too.
Gosh, I'm tired.
(How does Sunday's painting look?)
(What is this?)
(Ta-da)
I don't believe it.
It must have been painted by a human being.
- Sir, you painted it, right? - Sunday painted it?
(They can't believe what they see.)
Seriously?
- Unbelievable. - Look at the colors.
- He mixed red with yellow. - The combination of colors...
Look at the combination of colors.
How is this possible?
- It's a piece of art. - How can he do this?
(What are those scribbles?)
Why do ours look so bad?
Why did you paint fruits on the tree?
- The painting looked too empty. - I painted fruits.
It didn't look like a tree, so I painted fruits.
Sunday will choose one painting of yours...
that will compete against his.
He must have a good eye.
I'm getting nervous.
I hope he won't choose mine.
Please don't choose Se Chan's. We have to win.
- Don't come here. - We have to win.
I'm nervous.
Yes, choose that one.
(Whose painting will Sunday choose?)
Not this?
I'm nervous.
Yes, choose that one.
(Jong Kook's?)
- Choose that one. - Not this?
Amazing.
He came... No.
- No! - Don't!
(Se Chan's mushroom)
No!
(No!)
Don't!
Please go away.
No!
(Turning away)
- This is exciting. - He's making us nervous.
He understands variety shows.
We're wearing the same color. Pick mine.
(Everyone is watching Sunday's trunk.)
Come here. Hi.
Come on.
He's coming closer to Shorry.
Come on!
- Yes! - Yes!
He picked Shorry's!
Yes!
- I'm so relieved. - He has a good eye.
Good job.
- Thanks. - Good job. Thanks.
Shorry's painting will compete against Sunday's.
Okay.
(They even signed their paintings.)
(The vote starts.)
(The visitors will vote for the painting for 30 minutes.)
(We'd like to thank everyone who participated in the voting.)
(What is the result?)
It's Sunday, the elephant versus Shorry.
I will announce the result of the voting.
(Which one of them will be the final victor of the match?)
- What is this? - How do we know which one won?
- My gosh, the hearts... - We lost.
- We lost? - Yes, we did. Hold on.
We lost by a landslide.
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. - We lost. We really did.
- We lost, Shorry. - 7, 8, 9, 10.
- There's no point counting. - We lost to an elephant?
I get it, you know. The brushstrokes are too good.
- It looks like a person painted it. - I love the composition here.
(No one would've guessed an elephant drew this painting.)
- Then what happens to us? - Since you failed the mission,
we'll add 1,000 steps to your counters.
Tell us how you want to divide the steps among yourselves.
Shorry, why did you draw the S like this?
I...
You're right. The brushstroke wasn't that good.
- As it so happens, - Right.
- his painting lost out to Sunday's. - Right.
- I think... - I...
I will... I will take...
I will gladly receive those 1,000 steps.
Is that your idea?
- Sure. It's completely my idea. - Is that so?
I will take those steps.
- Should we laugh all together? - It's because...
(Yes, let's smile. I'm lucky that I didn't get 1,000 punches.)
(Meanwhile, Team Love Triangle in Daema Island...)
- Where are we? - Enjoy your meal.
- We can just eat? - My gosh.
I guess he just sliced it.
(They can eat as much as they want.)
- This is so good. - Sir, this tastes divine.
Now, we'll inform your mission in Daema Island.
Your mission is accomplished when you catch the fish you ate.
Per type of fish you fail to catch,
you will earn 1,000 steps.
My gosh, this is too cruel.
- 7? He has to catch 7? - I only ate 2 types of fish.
- What are the other two? - I'm in trouble.
I ate them all.
- Haha. - Seriously.
If we don't pick Ji Hyo, it's impossible to complete our mission.
If we get Haha, it'd be a catastrophe.
- We just have to pick my name. - Yes, we must pick her name.
Bring in the globe now.
- It's because... Look, Haha. - It's either Ji Hyo's or my name.
- We'd be okay with that. - My gosh, you are too harsh.
Picking Ji Hyo's name would be best.
If we get your name and can't catch any, it's 8,000 steps.
For you, it'd be 7,000 steps.
- That's right. It's 7,000. - It's extra 7,000 or 8,000 steps.
When you're ready, say, "Start."
We'll practice.
(He taps it rather late.)
(He taps it after the globe comes to a stop.)
Wasn't that acceptable?
- Isn't that allowed? - This isn't acceptable?
You're too picky.
Remember "apartment in Busan"?
Remember that time? I should give this another try.
- Yes. Apartment in Busan. - Exactly.
Let me practice.
(Haha)
(He picks Haha again.)
You don't need to spin it hard.
I keep choosing Haha. What is happening?
My gosh.
(He picks Haha 5 times and Kwang Soo 1 time.)
- Don't do it. - You shouldn't do that.
Ji Hyo, you should do it. You should pick your name too.
(No one in our team can do this right.)
(Ji Hyo picks her name.)
That's right!
- She picked her name. - Ji Hyo is unbelievable.
(She's our only hope.)
Let's do this. Let's go.
- Don't blame me. - Okay.
- Don't blame me. - Let's do this.
- Let's go. - Don't pick me or Kwang Soo.
She might feel pressured, so even if she picks our names,
- I understand. - let's just laugh.
- Okay. - Laugh like you're happy.
I can smile really happily.
- Ji Hyo will try it. - Okay.
- Start. - Start.
(Feeling nervous)
- This is nerve-wracking. - It's all right.
(If she chooses Haha or Kwang Soo, it's the worst scenario.)
(She must choose herself or Sang Yeob to be successful.)
It's Sang Yeob!
That's all right. It's five.
- This is good. - This isn't bad.
- We were so close though. - Let me tell you the names.
They are filefish, smallscale blackfish, yellowtail amberjack,
striped beakfish, and squid.
(Now that they think of their mission,)
(catching five different types of fish is quite a lot.)
Hold on. Did you say, "Start"?
- She... - She did say so.
- When? - Don't we all have to say that?
- We all have to say that. - We didn't say it together.
- That's the rule. - I almost forgot. Right.
- Why didn't you say it with us? - Let's do this again.
- We must count before we start. - Right.
Let's count before we say, "Start."
- 1, 2, 3. Just like this? - Okay. Start.
- 1, 2, 3. Start. - 1, 2, 3. Start.
(The staff will give them another chance.)
(Please let it be my name this time.)
(They turned down Sang Yeob which is their second best shot.)
(These four members are only aiming for Ji Hyo's name.)
(It's the worst pick. She chooses Haha with 8 species.)
- Haha. - No, no.
- Haha. Let me read yours. - No, Sang Yeob...
- We'll go with Sang Yeob. - You had filefish,
- I'm sorry. - yellowtail amberjack,
chicken grunt, conger eel, conger eel,
- Okay. It's 1 to 1 now. - and squid.
- It's 1 to 1. - 1 to 1.
- 1 to 1. - Don't you agree?
- But still... - Sang Yeob, you should decide.
- In this situation... - We ought to play three times.
Tell us if the score is 1 to 1 or not. Just answer me that.
- Of course, it is. - It's 1 to 1.
Because I didn't say, "Start."
- Then... - We'll accept the result this time.
We'll accept the name we pick this time.
- I'm telling you the truth. - Then...
Why doesn't everyone including the staff say it?
- Say, "Start" when we count. - Okay, let's do it all together...
because we are a family.
I mean if we ask...
the chef to do it, it'd be funny.
- Should we ask him? - Yes, let's do that.
(To be fair, they will ask the Japanese chef to choose.)
My gosh, Haha is a genius.
He's a genius. Seriously.
- His fingers are sensitive too. - That's right.
(The Japanese chef, sushi master, will pick the name.)
If he picks my name, we're good.
(Please pick Ji Hyo's name.)
(He feels nervous for some reason.)
After counting to three, say, "Start."
- 1, 2, 3. Start. - Start.
- Start. - Start.
- Okay. - We'll accept it this time.
- We mean it. - We're serious.
- Seriously. - We'll accept it.
- The chef will say, "Start." - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. Start. - 1, 2, 3. Start.
(Per species they fail to acquire, they'll add 1,000 steps.)
(He must pick Ji Hyo's name for the sake of the counter.)
It's Haha.
(Haha with 8 species to catch is chosen.)
Filefish, yellowtail amberjack, red seabream, smallscale blackfish,
chicken grunt, conger eel, striped beakfish, and squid.
Thank you. Thank you.
(We are doomed.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(It's hard to even memorize those 8 species.)
Hold on. Can we have a meeting? Just give us 20 seconds.
Is there a way we can get out of this?
I can't do this.
Why did you have to eat a lot?
We should've stopped when we had Sang Yeob's name.
Why did you have to risk it?
- What's wrong with you today? - We could've worked together.
Why did you do that?
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(It's time to return to their hotel while feeling bitter.)
(It feels like such a long day today.)
(Trudging)
- Thank you. - That's dangerous.
- Thank you. - No problem.
- My gosh. - Thank you.
- This is the place. - Let's take this.
This must be it.
- This must be the reception. - The ambience looks nice.
How pretty.
- Excuse us. - Excuse us.
- Hello. - Hello.
You speak Korean.
- Come in, please. - Okay.
(How will their lodging look?)
- I'll go in for now, but... - This looks nice.
(It's a cute, cozy, and traditional bed and breakfast in Japan.)
This looks nice.
(It's the best place for them to reflect on their rough day.)
This is lovely.
It's been here for 100 years?
It's been here for 160 years.
- My gosh. - Really?
Then this must be a family business.
(When you climb the stairs with marks of a 160-year-history,)
(there's a room where the members will stay for the night.)
- It's warm. It's warm. - It is so warm in here.
(Impressed)
(Today must have been the toughest for Sang Yeob.)
Hold on.
- Let's change. - Wait.
- I need my bag. - Seriously.
- Sang Yeob, let's get some sleep. - Yes?
Don't do anything fishy during the night.
- Right. - I won't.
(He takes Haha's step counter.)
(Rattling)
- The blankets... - Hey, hey. Bring it back.
Bring it back.
Unbelievable. What's the matter with you?
- Hear me out. - Bring it.
- Give it back. I can't believe you. - That's not what I meant.
- Hey, about what you did... - Did you just slap me?
- It infuriates me. - I was just messing with you.
I was testing if you trusted me or not.
Kwang Soo, you have a problem!
(Thus began the 7th war of the step counter.)
Sang Yeob, hold Haha!
- I'm going to up his number. - Hey!
(Even Sang Yeob joins.)
- I'll hold him. - Hey, Ji Hyo.
I love you!
(He has lost it.)
(This childish war continued for 30 minutes.)
I got it. Okay, I got it.
- Where did he hide it? - Hey.
Let's not attack each other.
So what's our plan?
- Let's make a deal and sleep. - Let's just sleep.
They were very crafty when they were making this game.
2nd and 3rd places aren't important.
We must take the first place.
Ji Hyo is in first.
(What? Look at that.)
What is it?
(1st place is the only way to survive. Let me take your spot!)
(Ji Hyo bumps her head.)
What are you doing?
(He's dejected.)
Are we even a team?
(Are we even a team?)
Is this what family is about?
- My head. - Is this what traveling is about?
Kwang Soo, come on. What's your deal with me?
- What's going on here? - We are a team.
Kwang Soo, what is it that you want?
- Look at his eyes. - Be honest with us.
1st place. To be exempted.
I don't want to face the penalty.
Is that so? Will you be happy if you get those?
I don't care which one of you ends up last...
as long as it's not me.
Will you be happy if we make that happen for you?
- Is that it? - Yes.
- But... - What about you?
- First place. - What about you?
I don't want to be last.
- What's yours, Haha? - What about you, Haha?
Whatever it was, it wasn't this.
(Whom is he trying to fool?)
Then what is it?
How is this a family?
How is this a team?
I won't when we sleep.
- You won't? - This is the end.
Let me be honest.
Including what you did to me and teased me about,
I'll forgive everything.
Stop kidding around.
- We're the ones who should forgive. - It should be us.
I decided to forgive you.
Can you rewind the camera recording?
The show is over for me after today's shoot.
What about you two?
What will you do, Kwang Soo?
Will you keep living like this?
- Sang Yeob. - Yes?
Why would you leave after this shoot?
I'll change my phone number.
I'll change it.
I'll even change the service provider.
I ask you not to shoot dramas for a while.
(Haha asks him a favor.)
Let's promise each other.
Even if we start tomorrow,
let's not bother each other during sleep.
- Right. - From now on to tomorrow morning.
Until we leave tomorrow.
This is really the last time.
The winner of rock-paper-scissors...
gets the loser's step counter for 10 seconds.
I'm sorry.
I feel anxious.
I lost too much just a moment ago.
I have to harass someone before sleeping.
- Okay. - Let's play one last game.
It's the loser.
The loser gives his step counter.
Okay?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo lose.)
This is great.
I played this game because of you.
My target is you too.
I lost so much.
How about this?
You get 10 seconds each.
You get another 10 seconds each.
You can shake the step counter more.
Wouldn't that be great with a table in between?
You're a piece of trash.
Isn't it a good idea?
- It means that we both lose. - That's right.
It'd be great. Think about it.
- It sounds thrilling. - You shake someone else's counter.
Each of you shake the other's step counter.
(He seems convinced.)
Swap the step counters.
Swap them.
- Wait, you swap them for us. - I'll give it to you.
Fine, I won't do it.
(He shakes them immediately.)
- What? - I'll stop.
- Come on, Haha. - I was trying to be funny.
(I've never seen anyone like them.)
I swapped them.
Don't start. Put it down.
Put it down for now.
Should we do this?
I don't know.
(Why are we doing this?)
Get ready.
Listen to him.
- Wait until it's 2:30am. - I think Haha is being too...
Start.
(Does Sang Yeob attack first?)
(My goodness)
You didn't start together.
Let's go.
(Give back my step counter.)
My goodness. They're scary.
10 seconds are up.
- Time is up. - Time is up.
- Stop it. - Stop.
- Stop. - Stop.
- Stop it. - Hey, stop it.
Give it back!
Both of us will lose. Put it down.
- You put it down. - We'll both lose.
- Come on. - Put it down.
You're a piece of trash.
Put it down.
- Stop shaking it. - Let it go.
Let it go.
Stop shaking it.
No.
Just stop shaking it.
- Stop it. - Hey.
- Stop at the count of 3. - 1, 2, 3.
Stop.
I told you to stop.
Stop at the count of three.
- 1, 2, 1, 2, 3. Throw it. - 3.
Please.
- Please. - Oh, no.
- My goodness. - Please stop.
Wait, stop it.
- Stop. - Stand over there.
- Stand over there. - Okay.
This will be pointless.
The game will be pointless.
- Put it down. - Seriously, put it down.
- I put it down. - This is hilarious.
- Put it on the floor. - I laughed so much.
- I laughed so much. - Let's swap.
- Let's swap. - That was hilarious.
Take your hand off. Lift your hand.
- Okay. - Lift hands at the same time.
- 1, 2. I let it go. - That was funny.
1, 2, 3.
My hand is off.
Three. My hand is off.
(The step counter is in his other hand.)
(It's not over yet.)
That's hilarious.
- I won. - You're a piece of trash.
- Hey. - Please stop.
Please stop.
- Stop it. - It's over for you.
I put it down. I did.
- I put it down. - Okay.
- Let it go. 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
I stopped.
Why should we do this?
What's my count?
It's 4,670.
Yours is 5,060.
What are you doing?
Wait.
Stop it.
(Sang Yeob became part of the team.)
How dare you?
- Die! - Wait.
I put yours down.
I really put it down.
I can't stay here anymore.
- Where is it? - I let it go.
- Stop shaking it. - They're hilarious.
- You keep shaking it. - I let it go.
- Okay. - I let it go.
- Stop it. - Okay, I let it go now.
It was nice in the city. There were many restaurants.
There were so many good restaurants, but why are we back here?
It must be a tasty restaurant.
We were so happy on International Street.
- You know what the worst is? - What?
We go back and meet the worker at a convenience store.
- Ramen again? - Again...
we go straight and see ramen again.
Let's order one bowl today.
We ordered a total of four.
Let's be careful of that.
We should be careful.
- Be careful what you say. - Let's order one.
Don't talk too much.
- Let's eat and move to the next. - Let's go.
- Let's hurry. - Shall we?
It's crowded here.
Goodness.
Look how crowded it is.
- The pork cutlet looks good. - It's full of people.
(The restaurant is packed with customers.)
(Do we have to show it again?)
(It's the same as yesterday.)
(It's a soba restaurant that sells Okinawa soba.)
- Excuse me. - Goodness.
You can't shoot because we're full.
The tables are full.
- They're full? - It's full.
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
(Thank you for not letting us in.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Why do you thank her when it's full?
It's full.
- Let's go. - It's such a popular place.
- We can't eat here. - We can't.
Rules are rules.
Let's get a takeout and eat it at a nearby park.
- Listen. - It's too packed.
- However, rules are rules. - Hey.
I didn't know it was such a popular restaurant.
It must be a famous, tasty restaurant.
- It must be delicious. - Customers keep going in.
They keep going in. They're lining up.
- It's only us who don't like it. - Is it delicious?
- It's delicious. - I see.
He says that it's delicious.
Since we don't have time, we'll order a takeout.
- Get one order for takeout. - Yes.
Was there a railroad here in the past?
- I think so. - You're right.
(So Min sits on a steep spot.)
What's this?
Why did you sit at a bad spot?
- Let's just sit and eat. - There's a comfortable spot.
We should sit in one row for the look.
Would we look better?
It looks better than yesterday.
(The soba looks better than yesterday.)
(Today's soba is only soup and noodles.)
(Shall I smell it?)
How is it?
It's okay.
Compared to yesterday,
did we order something else?
What's this?
I think we ordered something else.
- No. - It's the same.
It's with jokbal.
This is what gives that taste.
- That's it. - It's the sauce.
- It's soy sauce jokbal. - Can you not add the meat?
- I have to add it. - We must add everything given.
(We have no choice.)
There's a lot of soy sauce.
- I can smell it. - Gosh.
- It's the same as yesterday. - It is.
It's the same jokbal as yesterday.
Add the noodles.
It's the same as yesterday.
(It's the same soba as yesterday.)
It's known as a tasty restaurant among the locals.
As it's adjusted to the locals' taste,
the smell could be quite strong.
- It's still delicious. - It's delicious.
It's not the soba...
- that we're used to. Right. - We have warm buckwheat soba too.
It's similar to that.
- Go ahead. - I'll take enough.
Eat some meat.
Isn't it Seok Jin's turn now?
- Seok Jin eats much more. - No.
- This reminds me. - What?
- Eat a lot. - We came all the way to Okinawa.
In this park that we don't know...
(They were hoping for steak and sushi.)
(They're eating soba in the middle of a park.)
People will think that we're sharing a bowl.
If we get another recommendation for soba...
It's delicious.
If we stay within 20km, that's...
- the soba restaurant to go to. - If that happens again...
- We'll go back there. - Right.
If the restaurant is full, we'll eat it here again.
(That's the worst part.)
That's scarier than Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
- That'd be terrible. - It's Super Scary Soba.
- We'll go there. - Super Scary Soba.
(Super Scary Soba)
(They must escape this place by carefully spinning the globe.)
Let's spin it.
Spin well so that we get to see various dishes.
- That's what we want too. - Seriously.
- For the viewers, - Right.
we want to show them what kind of food there is in Okinawa.
We went to the same soba restaurant twice.
They'll think that it's a mistake.
- Right. - They'll think it's a rerun.
How about...
- So Min this time? - Me?
We need someone like...
a taxi driver to get out of here.
I'm getting nervous.
Hit it a few times.
- Hit it like that. - It's spinning.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Taxi driver is the best choice.)
I'm getting nervous.
Hit it a few times.
- Hit it like that. - It's spinning.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Taxi driver is the best choice.)
What?
(Someone over 90)
"Someone over 90".
People over 90 must love soba.
(There were many elderly people in the soba restaurant.)
Soba is a traditional food.
You're right.
- People over 90... - There were many in the restaurant.
- The soba restaurant? - The customers...
They'll recommend the same soba restaurant.
(Pull yourself together.)
We could ask where else they usually eat.
Please give us one more chance.
You have to say, "Start".
- Let's go. 1, 2, 3. - Start.
- Start. - Start.
- So Min, pick one. - Pick one.
(This is their last chance to get out of this labyrinth.)
(We have to get away from this area.)
- "Convenience store clerk". - "Convenience store clerk".
(Convenience store clerk)
Hey.
The closest store is the one we've been to.
(The clerk at the only store in the area recommended ramen.)
They recommended ramen,
and after we ate ramen,
someone recommended soba.
- You set us up, right? - Jae Seok.
- It's a trap, right? - Are you sure there's no button?
There's a button, right?
There's no button. It's impossible to control the result.
We have to obey the rules.
- Let's go back to the store. - Again?
Again?
No!
- Seriously... - Please!
- Hey. - No more noodles! I want meat!
- Okinawa is large. - Please.
There are many good restaurants in Okinawa.
- There are sushi, - Our step counters...
- tonkatsu... - We don't care about step counters.
We have to get out of this area.
- I don't want any more soba. - As soon as we woke up,
we came here, excited.
As soon as the restaurant opened.
Convenience store clerks and taxi drivers keep recommending...
soba.
Taxi drivers recommend soba, convenience store clerks ramen.
Soba, ramen, soba, ramen...
We don't have a lot of time. Let's go to the convenience store.
- Let's go. - Convenience stores...
are open 24 hours a day. There might be a new clerk.
That's right. The man who was there last night can't still be there.
- Let's go. - Gosh.
How is this possible?
Anything except soba would work.
Anything except soba.
- And ramen. - And ramen.
Anything except soba and ramen.
I really don't want any more ramen.
Let me tell you.
If I have one more bowl of soba,
I'll be able to make it myself.
I'll be able to make it.
The stock is based on soy sauce.
(He's analyzed the ingredients.)
I want rice, not noodles.
We passed this street last night.
- Did we? - Yes.
We even remember the way.
(Amazed)
Do you know what bothers me the most?
On this sunny day in Okinawa, we're walking around the same place.
This area isn't even beautiful.
I want to go back to International Street.
There are so many good restaurants on that street.
Why would they recommend a place in this area?
That's where you farted last night.
That's right.
(They're back on the fart street.)
Even the wind direction is the same.
(The wind direction is the same.)
The wind blew in this direction.
Even the wind blows in the same direction.
(It's like a Moebius strip.)
Don't fart.
If you fart again, everything will be the same.
Okay. Let's cheer up.
- No. - Let's get excited.
(Let's cheer up. Let's get excited.)
- Stay calm, or you might fart. - Okay.
Let's stay hopeful. We're here.
(They have arrived.)
Hold on. There are so many customers.
It's the only convenience store in this area.
(The store is full.)
If all of us go in, we'll become a nuisance.
- Let's send one person in. - Okay.
- And ask the question. - Buy something,
- and ask this question. - Okay.
See if it's the same man.
I don't think so.
- It looks like a woman. - I can't see.
- It's a woman, right? - It is.
- Okay. - The loser will go in?
It doesn't matter.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
I win.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kyeong Hwan loses.)
Kyeong Hwan, you go in.
Kyeong Hwan...
She looks like the type of person who likes soba.
You should sound like someone who likes meat.
Just speak naturally.
"Excuse me."
- You sound like a woman. - "I..."
Why do you speak like a woman?
- Let me try. - Hold on.
I've been traumatized because of So Min.
(So Min has been saying Jae Seok sounds like a Japanese woman.)
(Jae Seok has been traumatized.)
After all this time in Japan,
I'm traumatized.
I can't speak Japanese anymore.
- "No more soba." Start. - Start.
- No more soba - No more soba
She might hear us and recommend soba.
- Here I come. - I don't think she heard.
(He approaches the clerk.)
Speak naturally. Don't sound too cheesy.
I'll get a bottle of coke.
A bottle of coke.
I'm nervous. I can't hear anything.
And...
Is it really okay to shoot the same thing over and over?
- Okinawa has many delicious dishes. - This is too much.
- Japanese food is so popular. - We're in Okinawa.
We should try the restaurants on International Street.
I'm so shocked.
What are you filming?
(The camera is facing the wrong direction.)
- Oh, right. - What are you filming?
(Why is it facing that way?)
- Have you been filming the staff? - What are you doing?
- Why would you film Chul Min? - Right.
(So Min has been filming the staff all day.)
Just return it.
Gosh.
(I at least filmed something.)
Right.
Does she like steak?
Here.
(Kyeong Hwan is standing close to the clerk.)
(Cheesy)
(He practices the question.)
(He is standing in front of the clerk.)
- He's going to start. - He's starting soon.
My goodness.
- He's going to start. - Please.
I don't even hope for steak anymore.
I just want to avoid noodles.
Tonkatsu, sushi...
- I don't want any more soba. - He's asking her.
(Kyeong Hwan is asking the question.)
He's asking her.
(No noodles, yes steak)
(Please recommend a delicious dish to us.)
(Desperate)
(A dish?)
She's wearing a mask. I can't read her lips.
Oh, my.
(No more noodles, please.)
Please don't say noodles.
(Stress-related stomach pain)
My stomach aches again.
(The staff members burst into laughter.)
- My stomach aches again. What? - It's over?
- Did she say soba? - What happened?
If it's soba again...
Gosh. Please.
If it's soba again, I'll kill you.
I won't forgive you.
If it's the same restaurant again...
Guys, I won't forgive you.
You'll see me angry for the first time.
Stop joking.
I'm going to cry. Please don't do this.
Don't you want to film something else?
(He is asking the cameramen.)
Don't you? Kwon Ryeol.
You want to film something new, right?
We're even wearing the same clothes. Nothing has changed.
She's pointing to a different direction.
- A different direction? - It's a different direction.
(She is pointing the opposite direction from the soba place.)
- It's that way? - It's that way.
(There is still hope.)
(The clerk is making everyone confused.)
(What did she recommend?)
(Ramen)
(Did you say ramen?)
- Okinawa ramen? - Yes.
(Yesterday)
(Different place, same answer)
Excuse me. Do you mean ramen?
Really?
Yes. It's the best.
Ramen...
Is it that way?
(They have to first go in the direction of the soba place.)
Is it there?
I don't want to come to Japan with Seok Jin and Jae Seok again.
- It's not our fault. - Seriously...
You...
He should have spoken naturally. His Japanese sounds too cheesy.
We still don't know.
(How am I going to tell them?)
How should I tell them?
(It's ramen, not soba.)
(It went well.)
My goodness.
His face... He says it's something good.
- He says it's something good. - Okay.
- That's a relief. - It's something good.
(It must not be soba or ramen.)
What's taking him so long?
(It's great.)
How should I tell them?
It's ramen.
(She kindly draws the map of the ramen place.)
- He's coming. - I think it worked.
His face looks okay. Did we guess it right?
- Oh, gosh. - What is it?
- I'm so sweaty. - We have an idea.
- Why did you take so long? - You're sweating.
- Where are we going? - Look. Do you see it?
- Where is it? - If you look here,
- it's a different place. - That's right.
This is...
a very popular ramen place...
in Okinawa.
(This is a very popular ramen place in Okinawa.)
(Did we hear that wrong?)
It's very popular.
She recommended ramen without hesitating.
I asked her a few times.
- "Really"? - Ramen?
- Yes. - Isn't it down there?
My forehead is full of sweat.
I sweated the amount of ramen soup.
- Where is it? - Sorry?
It's a 10-minute walk back this way.
She said it's a tremendous ramen place.
Don't people eat sushi or pork cutlet here?
No?
I think our trip today...
is not a random tour.
It's a soba, ramen tour.
Soba and ramen.
(Even if you like noodles, you'll get sick of soba and ramen.)
Soba and ramen. It's soba next.
Our interpreter looked at the map and said that...
if you go back the way you came, it's past the soba place.
(It's past the soba place they were at earlier.)
- We have to go back there? - Really?
So we can't get away from here. We can't get away from this area.
Are we touring around the soba place?
Are we advertising soba?
Do you know the owner of the restaurant?
I think we're advertising the entire street.
It's that street.
What does that soba mean to us?
I don't know what that street is.
It's a little bit past the soba place.
- At this state... - It's ramen.
(Let's go back the way we came...)
(for ramen.)
Oh, gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- Kyeong Hwan. - Yes.
Thanks for letting us walk back.
- No problem. - This feels new.
It's a ramen place so rather than not knowing the way,
it's better to take the same way. We know the route.
- I want to go home. - I feel sick.
- I want to go home too. - Me too.
I want to eat kimchi stew at home.
We're here. I see it.
- I see it too. - There.
- Where? - It's the soba place.
- It's the soba place. - Oh, dear.
Hey.
If people see us go back and forth,
they'll wonder what we're doing.
(The people at the soba place will wonder.)
This is no joke.
(They plod back down the way.)
- Here he is. - Soba?
Here he is.
He's the owner of the ramen restaurant.
(He's the owner of the restaurant they went to yesterday.)
(The owner recognizes them.)
Sir!
Goodness. Sir.
Hello.
(He served them their first ramen.)
He's the owner of the ramen restaurant.
We can't get away from ramen and soba.
I'm going to work. Do you want to come with me?
We have to go to another ramen place.
He has to watch this on TV to know what situation we're in.
Tell him we've been having ramen and soba for four meals.
Really?
We had soba and ramen yesterday,
then soba and ramen again.
We're going to another ramen place.
His stomach looks full.
- It's full of ramen. - I know. I'm full.
I looked up on the internet, and they are really famous.
He found out that you guys are famous.
(He looked up Running Man last time.)
May I take a picture of you?
(He wants to keep a picture as a memory.)
Can he take a picture of you?
We should move.
(Of course.)
This is so funny. We met him.
It was so nice to see him again.
We keep going around the neighborhood,
so we meet people we know.
(They meet people they know.)
Come here.
We have a friend in Okinawa.
He's our neighbor.
I wish you success in your business.
- See you again. - Thank you.
- How could this happen? - Goodness.
We have a friend here now.
We have a neighbor now.
(They make themselves a friend.)
Once I return to Korea,
I'm going to say my friend owns a ramen place.
My friend owns a ramen place.
We're dominating this street.
(They dominated an alley in Okinawa.)
We're not sheriffs of Okinawa.
Thanks for giving me a great memory, guys.
I was excited about coming to Okinawa.
We didn't even see the ocean. I heard it's really nice.
Everybody, do you see the similar restaurant sign?
Isn't this it?
(They'll swim in the ramen soup instead of the ocean.)
- Here it is. - We're here.
Here it is.
(This is not a replay. This is another good ramen place.)
- Here it is. - It looks famous. It looks good.
It's not full.
(He's disappointed.)
- It's not full. - Did you hear Kyeong Hwan?
"It's not full."
We have to go in now.
(He was expecting it to be full.)
- Whatever. - Everybody is suffering.
We had ramen and the time...
- What time is it? - We just had ramen.
We can try one more time.
We can only try one more time.
- This is our last chance then. - It is.
Let's spin the globe. We have no time.
(The globe they love and hate is back.)
- No more convenience store, please. - I want to get away.
- We have to get away. - But...
we don't have time to find somebody named Suzuki...
- or somebody over 90. - We have no time.
The only way for us to survive is to get a taxi driver.
Who wants to do it?
I'll try it.
I'll spin it.
- You keep doing that. - Fine.
- I'll do it. Start. - Start.
- Start. - Start.
(This is their last chance.)
(They don't have time to find people.)
(They're hoping to get a taxi driver.)
- It's Suzuki. - "Someone called Suzuki".
(They get "someone called Suzuki".)
(It's Suzuki.)
Suzuki?
I asked, and apparently, it's hard to find someone named Suzuki...
in Okinawa.
It's hard to find Suzuki, and you have no time.
Yes, it's too difficult.
You won the chance card yesterday.
- Please help us. - Yes.
(Team Yu-So-Body won a game and got a chance card...)
(which will help them in the mission.)
You can use the chance card to switch to another last name.
(They can use the chance card to switch to another last name.)
A different last name?
What is the most common last name?
We looked it up,
and in Okinawa,
- the most common last name is Higa. - Higa?
Out of 1.5 million people, there are 50,000 people.
- There's 1 in 30 chance. - Higa.
(Wait. It's Higa?)
Well...
She's going.
(She goes to the ramen place to find someone called Higa.)
Excuse me.
Is Mr. Higa here?
(Please)
(An employee approaches them.)
(Will they find someone called Higa this fast?)
I'm not Higa.
(There are none amongst the employees.)
(Of course.)
- There's a Higa? - Higa.
If you ask them, they're going to recommend ramen.
He'll say ramen.
- They have to come out. - Come out.
We have to go to a steak restaurant and ask.
Come out.
(They're banned from approaching any ramen place.)
If you ask here,
they're going to recommend ramen again.
Then...
we don't have time, right?
Let's go with Higa.
(They switch to Higa which is more common than Suzuki.)
Instead of Higa, can we do "somebody with a good impression"?
"Somebody with a good feeling".
(Can't we do that?)
You punk, I'm going to hit you.
(We don't have time. Let's go find somebody called Higa.)
Let's hurry.
It makes me happy whenever I come here.
What do you say again?
- What was it? - This looks the same as before.
It's the same as well.
- Higa... - What was it again?
- "Is Higa here?" - "Is Higa here?"
I'm happy to see so many people.
(At least there are many people here.)
(It's International Street with many tourists,)
(so they might find a Higa.)
We have no time.
- Mr. Higa? - Hey.
(Mr. Higa...)
(She's shooting...)
("Love Letter" on her own.)
(Stop shooting a movie. Let's find them.)
Hey, you can't do that.
You can't yell for Mr. Higa here.
- Hold on. Let's split... - Okay.
and find Mr. or Ms. Higa. We have no time.
- Mr. Higa. - Let's find him or her.
We have to find them. We have no time.
Excuse me.
(Jae Seok finds a target.)
Are you Mr. Higa?
(Please... Are you Mr. Higa?)
- Higa? - I'm Chinese.
(He's confused.)
Sorry.
It's International Street, so there are many foreigners.
Excuse me.
We're Korean.
Are you Korean? I see.
(She looks around.)
Okay, I got this.
I'm going to ask her.
(So Min finds a target.)
Excuse me.
Are you Ms. Higa?
No.
Thank you.
(She starts repeating "Excuse me" and "Thank you".)
Excuse me. Are you Mr. Higa?
(No, we're not.)
(She ends with a thank you again.)
There are none. What do we do?
What should we do?
Are you Ms. Higa?
Ms. Higa?
(She points at her friend.)
(Are you Ms. Higa?)
Are you Ms. Higa?
(Me?)
I found Ms. Higa.
(Where is her friend going?)
(He found Ms. Higa?)
- Yes. - It's Ms. Higa.
- It's Ms. Higa. - We found her.
- We found Ms. Higa. - Ms. Higa?
(She's so happy.)
They found her?
Who?
Her friend pointed at her.
(They ask her for an ID to check her name.)
Here it is. It's Ms. Higa.
Are we right?
(They find a person named Higa.)
It is. Yes!
We found her.
Thank you.
Where were you going?
- Ms. Higa. - Ms. Higa, thank you.
- Ms. Higa. - Let's ask her.
- Who wants to ask her? - I'm getting nervous.
- I'll ask. - Use a nice voice.
I'll ask her the question.
- Excuse me. - You have one chance.
- We can do this. - Please just once.
- Please. - Please, Ms. Higa.
- Please. - Okay.
Excuse me.
What food and restaurant would you like to recommend?
(What does she recommend?)
(For two days, they couldn't get away from noodles.)
(If they get steak, they win and can go home right away.)
(Will she give them the answer they want?)
Black ramen?
(It's garlic and soy sauce ramen.)
(Sighing)
Ramen?
- Ramen? - I like it.
Ramen, Ms. Higa?
- Ramen? - Yes.
I like ramen.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
- I had so much ramen. - Ramen.
- This is hard to believe. - Ramen again?
- What do you recommend next? - Next?
Next?
Okinawa soba.
Soba.
Soba!
- Soba. - Okinawa soba.
Okinawa soba.
- Okinawa soba wasn't the 1st one. - What about 3rd?
- What's the 3rd thing? - Okinawa soba.
Third one.
- Steak? - Steak.
It was the third choice.
It's the third choice.
- It was the third choice. - We wanted steak.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
If we didn't ask for number one, we would have still had soba.
Sushi is not even in top three.
We can't have ramen again. Look, man.
- We just had ramen. - I'm so full.
You should try the ramen.
We can't eat it anymore.
Maybe this is what it is.
Maybe the entire place is a studio.
(Maybe this is the Mobius strip of noodles,)
(and perhaps the people we met were all actors.)
- Did they recruit these people? - Maybe they did.
How can Ms. Higa recommend ramen again?
This doesn't make sense.
We had 2 soba and 3 ramen.
It's 2 soba and 3 ramen.
- 2 soba and 3 ramen. - I'm sick of this.
We had 2 soba and 3 ramen in Okinawa.
How is it possible we only had ramen?
- Let's go. We have no time. - My gosh.
Let's just eat.
I get so happy before asking the question...
and get down after asking.
(They go back again and find another ramen place.)
(The second morning in Daema Island has arrived.)
(They get home-made food before going out to fish.)
It's shiny.
(Their goal is to catch this fish.)
Eat up.
(They look tired after fighting over the step counters last night.)
If we don't catch everything,
- we'll get 8,000 steps added. - Right, if we're not successful.
I thought about this too.
What if I become last place in the losing team...
and exercise some authority?
(The loser can pick whom to receive the punishment with.)
(That's a tempting idea.)
- You're a genius. - I don't want to be scared.
I'm really scared of you right now.
- Me? - Yes.
I'm more scared of you now.
Then let's do it this way.
- What if we shake it as we eat? - Stop.
(Sang Yeob changed a lot over a day.)
- Sang Yeob. - Should I not do it?
Let's eat.
Okay.
You're so cool.
He needs another step counter.
(They go fishing with Sang Yeob who is turning into a monster.)
It's so nice out.
- We're starting again - We're starting again
It's just a step counter.
Running Man is kind of strange.
Once we return home, this is nothing.
- That's true. - The R sticker, ddakji,
and this. This makes no sense.
- I know, right? - What is all this?
I get obsessed whenever I do this.
Goodness.
I thought I was a nice person.
Last night,
I learned that I can hit people.
You shouldn't shoot dramas for a while.
- Stay home on Mondays and Tuesdays. - Make sure you take those days off.
After I was on Running Man last time,
I had more offers for variety shows than dramas.
Really?
Maybe I should ask websites to add...
"entertainer" in my profile.
Maybe I need to ask.
This is the age of creators.
You have to be good at everything.
We'll be doing comedy next week.
(Get yourself ready.)
I have an album coming out next week.
(Running Man raises all-around entertainers.)
You're a genius.
Gosh, you guys are geniuses of variety shows.
(They arrive in a fishing village covered by wet fog.)
There's wet fog.
She's right.
This is amazing.
It's so clean and nice.
The water is so clean.
I can see the bottom.
(Will they be able to catch 8 types of fish here?)
He's an expert...
who will help you today.
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry we're dressed like this.
If he catches some fish,
does it count?
We're a team.
We're a family.
Aren't we a team?
He should get a step counter right now.
He has to have one.
We're a team.
Let us do that.
- Let's fill the boat with fish. - Okay.
If we catch fish that hasn't been discovered before,
do we get any benefit?
What if we catch fish that can talk?
- "Hello". - It can talk?
What if it's like, "That hurts".
"That hurts. Let go."
"You must be from Seoul."
If it can speak Korean,
then you can go home.
Really?
- Let's do this. - We're done then?
What if three people fish,
and one person teach Korean to fish?
I'll do it.
(They go off to the ocean to find talking fish.)
There are waves.
- There are. - It's stronger than I thought.
I know, right?
Oh, dear.
(Shaking)
Oh, gosh.
Don't be startled.
This happens all the time.
Do you know anything about fishing?
Haven't you gone fishing in the ocean?
- Do you usually go fishing? - Of course.
I'm the boatman of Mapo-gu.
All right. This is a good area.
I swear...
that on Haha's camera,
you'll see him puking the whole time.
You can only see the water.
- You'll only see the sky. - I'll look up.
You'll only see the sky.
- Let me show you an example. - Okay.
In Japan, they fish differently than in Korea.
In Korea, we put the anchor down on both sides and fish in the front.
In Japan, they say it's dangerous,
so they put one anchor in the front and fish in the back.
It's different from Korea.
Japan is different from Korea.
What are you doing?
In Korea,
we use both sides,
but in Japan, they only use the back because it's dangerous.
I'm sorry, but are you a parrot?
- I'm an echo. - You are?
(They stop 40 minutes into the boat ride.)
We have no time. Let's get started.
This is the peak time for fishing.
That looked so cool.
(Like Haha, Sang Yeob looks like an expert too.)
I don't know what I'm supposed to feel.
Hold this,
and then this hand supports the bottom.
- Okay. - Like this.
I think this is tangled.
I'll have a look.
(They are three beginners.)
The tide is so strong.
(Let the beginners hook baits in the corner.)
What?
What is it?
(Kwang Soo's fishing rod is doing something funny.)
- Did you catch something? - You did?
Hold on.
I think he got it.
- Kwang Soo! - Really?
Please.
Considering the weight,
the movement, and everything else,
- You caught something. - this must be smallscale blackfish.
Considering the weight,
the movement, and everything else,
- You caught something. - this must be smallscale blackfish.
- I caught it! - You did it!
(Gosh)
(I caught it!)
(He's super excited.)
I caught it!
- He caught it. - Everybody.
- Thank you. - This is insane.
This is what I was expecting.
- Kwang Soo. - I'll show you my skills.
- Kwang Soo. - Goodness.
What did I say?
- He caught it. - Everybody,
the anchors go down on both sides in Korea,
but it goes down the front in Japan.
Despite the difference,
- What's this? - I...
- It's smallscale blackfish. - I caught smallscale blackfish.
Good job, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
- You can hold it. - Kwang Soo.
Everybody, as soon as I started,
within 10 minutes...
- Everybody, - Kwang Soo.
this is a real situation.
Kwang Soo caught smallscale blackfish.
- Yes. - Goodness!
If it can talk, we can return to Korea.
Who are you?
Smallscale blackfish.
- Smallscale blackfish. - It spoke.
You failed.
(You should have done it better.)
Smallscale blackfish.
(The fish can't speak, but they're off to a good start.)
What were you guys going to do without me?
We only need to catch seven more types of fish.
Stop showing off.
- I'm going to catch a bigger one. - You're lucky I'm here.
(What were these people going to do without me?)
I want him to shut his mouth.
Please, just once.
Excuse me. I'll take my shirt off. I'm so mad now.
(Annoyed, Haha takes off his top.)
Haha, you look like you are upset.
I am not. It's not the mission that's important.
(He is a true fisherman.)
I am a fisherman.
I will change into a wetsuit.
(At that moment,)
(Sang Yeob takes Haha's step counter.)
I was greedy when I was in the entertainment business.
Please go ahead.
I will begin once again.
I will begin...
as well.
(He shakes Haha's step counter.)
Okay.
Haha, you are in my way. Please go someplace else.
That young man...
- Okay. - Haha.
- Yes? - I am aiming for 1,000 counts.
No, the number isn't important.
- That's right. - Yes.
Don't you think 5,000 counts would be enough?
- The number isn't important. - That's right.
- Focus on enjoying the sea. - That's right.
Throw your hatred, jealousy, and regret...
into the sea.
I will do that.
That's more than enough.
I want to throw my step counter into the sea.
- My goodness. - Seriously.
Such is life. Such is the sea.
- That's right. - Pour out the pent-up anger...
in your heart.
The sea accepts everything.
(Can you accept this?)
- It's done. - Thank you.
I wish I could tie this to the float.
(The perfect crime makes him smile.)
(30 minutes pass.)
We just need to focus.
(How many counts do I have?)
(Rummaging)
(I know you stole it!)
(Kwang Soo's eyes meet his.)
You stole it, right?
What?
I can't believe how mean Kwang Soo is.
Give it back before I kill you.
- It's not me. - Give it back.
- It really isn't me. - Hurry up and give it back.
Why are you bothering me when I am fishing?
- What are you doing? - Where is it? Give it back.
I don't have it!
Where is it? Give it back. I am serious.
I don't have it, you jerk!
(He is falsely accused.)
(The good brothers exchange words of blessing.)
Gosh, I felt a bite.
I don't have it!
(He feels victimized.)
I don't have it.
I can't believe this clown.
- Why are you fighting? - You jerk!
What do you think you are doing?
Why did you steal my step counter?
- What? - Give it back, you jerk.
I don't have it. I don't.
Come here.
What is this?
(Haha's step counter comes out of Kwang Soo's pocket.)
This is driving me crazy.
It has 2,239 counts.
(Why am I taking a beating?)
It's not me, you jerk!
(It's not me, you jerk!)
It's not me!
(Sang Yeob stole Haha's step counter.)
I am falsely accused!
(How did it come out of Kwang Soo's pocket?)
(While the two fishermen were fighting...)
(Slipping)
(Sang Yeob put the step counter in Kwang Soo's pocket.)
Was it in Kwang Soo's pocket?
(Sang Yeob's dazzling improvement)
Did I do it without even realizing it?
You are less than human.
Was it in Kwang Soo's pocket?
How could you do this to me?
Kwang Soo, did you do it without knowing?
- I didn't know. - That's scary.
- Don't you remember? - Don't you remember?
Do I have a condition? I really didn't do it.
When did you take it off of me?
It's not me. It really isn't me.
(It's a midsummer night's dream.)
(I am happy.)
(I am with Na Eun.)
Namcha! Namcha! Namcha!
(Shorry finds happiness as well.)
I want to stay in Bangkok for one more day.
Jong Kook can leave.
Are you crazy?
We won't see him after today.
(Jong Kook's suffering begins.)
(Their battle against the sea continues.)
(Can they return with a full ship?)
(Also)
(The result is shocking.)
(How will Random Tour end?)
(Coming up)
(4 mysterious people visit Running Man.)
(A new project begins with them.)