(The sun shines brightly at 9am.)
What are we doing today?
Do I have a secret mission?
(The production crew separately meets each member.)
Is there something I must do separately?
You will soon get a message from the headquarters.
- Will I get a message? - Yes.
It will be sent to your phone.
I received it.
(The 8 members receive a mysterious message.)
"Congratulations. You acquired 100 dollars in Running Money..."
"For today's race." Are we receiving money?
"Select a member who will receive 50 out of the said 100 dollars."
"With whom you shared the money won't be revealed."
(Do I need to give half of my Running Money?)
To whom should I give my money?
Do I have to share it? Is it a must?
Is it a rule?
(You must give 50 dollars to someone.)
That's half.
To whom do I want to give half of the money?
(Having more money puts you at an advantage.)
It will be a dogfight.
(Let's see who receives the most amount of money.)
When you have this kind of a mission,
there is someone you must call.
(The psychological warfare begins as they move to the first location.)
I am sure he is busy.
(Who is busy thinking from the start?)
- Haha, I just wrote your name. - Hey.
(He says this as soon as he picks up.)
- What? - It's not like that.
I waited for your call.
I just got in the van.
I did, too.
I thought about you...
as soon as I saw this.
I already sent the money to you.
I am serious. Haha.
Are you telling me the truth?
Yes. If you don't trust me, it can't be helped.
If this is a lie,
I will post something on SNS when the shoot ends.
You remember the celebrity you used to date, right?
(Do you want a big revelation?)
I am sick and tired of this.
- I am serious. - Why did I pick up?
I knew there was a reason why I didn't want to pick up.
If this is a lie, I will feel betrayed.
- Haha. - Yes?
Don't make that threat from now on.
(I can't do anything.)
I can't do anything.
I can't do anything since I know you will really do it.
- To be honest, I haven't sent it. - You haven't, right?
- Let's be honest to each other. - I am sorry.
Kwang Soo, I will send you the money.
(Kwang Soo, I will send you the money.)
Send me 50 dollars. That way, we will have the original amount.
Okay. I will send you the money right away.
- I am almost there. - Okay.
I won't call anyone else.
- Okay, Haha. - Okay. I love you.
I love you. I won't call anyone else.
Okay.
(They hang up.)
He is a jerk.
- Hello. - Kwang Soo.
- Jae Seok. - You were talking on the phone.
Yes, I was.
I got a call from Haha.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
You know what I am going to say, right?
I don't know what to do. I will send you the money.
I am serious. I will send it right away.
Forget it. You are irredeemable.
I will send you the money. I will.
Think about it. We don't know what kind of a game we will play,
but it will be a disaster if we give money to one person...
and let them be on a power trip.
- Jae Seok. - Who shouldn't it be?
- It can't be Jong Kook. - I understand.
- Let's exclude Jong Kook. - Let's exclude Jong Kook.
- I will do that. - Okay.
- All right, Jae Seok. - Okay.
(Everyone wants to keep Jong Kook in check.)
As a star, I will hold an event...
for my fan.
Hello, Jong Kook. It's me, Se Chan.
My lovely Se Chan.
I am your number one celebrity fan, Yang Se Chan.
- That's right. - Yes.
There will be an event from the star.
Jong Kook, your number one celebrity fan...
will send a present today.
I will send 500 dollars.
I don't know if I should accept it.
Please accept it.
I prefer pampering my fans.
- I knew it. - I prefer pampering my fans.
I will believe in the celebrity I like.
- Okay. - Okay.
I awaited your call.
I heard you talked to Kwang Soo on the phone.
He told you, didn't he? When you have a mission like this,
it's customary to give everyone a call.
You weren't going to give Kwang Soo the money, were you?
- Never. - I knew it.
Jae Seok, you will always be the number one...
in my heart.
Since both of us lost our jobs on Saturday,
we should help each other.
We should help each other.
Jae Seok, I love you infinitely.
- Let's keep this short. - Let's not make this childish.
- I will give you 50 dollars. - Okay, Jae Seok.
- Okay. - Thank you, Jae Seok.
- Okay. I am hanging up. - I love you.
Okay. Infinite...
- Challenge! - I love you.
Bye.
(It's a magical cheer that opens the door to one's heart.)
Gosh, that opened the door to my heart.
To whom should I give the money?
- Jae Seok. - Ji Hyo.
- Yes? - I chose you.
- Me? - Yes.
As soon as I received the mission, I thought you should get the money.
You received a lot of calls.
That's not true. Ji Hyo, I received...
one call. However,
I said, "I can't give you 50 dollars."
Then I called you after thinking.
You are giving me a change of heart.
I mean my words. Ji Hyo,
- you are my pick. - You warm up my heart.
- Okay. - I mean my words.
You warm my heart.
I am giving you half of my fortune. Think about that.
- Okay, Ji Hyo. - I will call you Half Ji Hyo...
because you will have half of my fortune.
I will call you Half Ji Hyo, okay?
- Okay, Ji Hyo? - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay, Half Ji Hyo. 50 dollars.
- I will send you the money. - I will send you the money.
- Okay, I will send you the money. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
(It looks like Jae Seok's words moved her.)
Jae Seok called me Half Ji Hyo.
That warmed up my heart.
I am close to tears.
(Let's see what kind of a decision Ji Hyo makes.)
I don't know whom to pick. There is no one.
(Seok Jin is torn because there is no one.)
Shall I call Haha? Or Kwang Soo?
The number you have dialed is temporarily suspended...
(What?)
What is going on?
The number you have dialed is temporarily suspended.
What happened to Kwang Soo's number?
What? That startled me.
(Why can't I call him?)
The number you have dialed is temporarily suspended...
at the customer's request.
Did he just... Did he just block my number?
(He can't believe this.)
Kwang Soo isn't answering.
(He's the most sought-after member during mind games.)
Did he already cut a deal with someone?
Even if he did, he would still answer his phone.
- Hey. - Kwang Soo.
- Yes? - Give me the money.
I'll choose So Min.
(Two reckless members make contact.)
- I just chose you. - Kwang Soo, give me the money.
Will you give me yours then?
Of course.
Don't you think your answer isn't that believable?
I'll decide now. I'll give my money to Kwang Soo.
I'll give mine to So Min who lives in Jeonju.
- I'll give the whole thing. - I'll give mine to Kwang Soo.
Okay, then. We'll understand that So Min will give hers to Kwang Soo.
- Hear that? I made my decision. - Hey, hey.
Who is that? Who's that woman? Put her on the phone.
Why? It's Hyo Im.
Everyone is in this together.
(The staff is part of it too.)
Listen. I thought you'd try to deceive me.
I'm so disappointed to hear her play along.
(He won't fall for it.)
- You know? - My goodness.
Then let's each take a screenshot and exchange it.
- I'll really give it to you then. - Let's exchange screenshots.
Okay, I got it.
- You got that? - Okay.
I'm serious. I'll trust you and hang up now.
- Okay, I'm serious. Okay, okay. - I won't call other people then.
I'll give you the money. I'm going to send it now.
- Sure, sure. - Okay.
Is there a way I can forge the text?
(She concocts a strategy to betray.)
I can delete this. This is awesome. Okay.
(She creates a fake headquarters number and sends a fake text.)
Delete it.
(I choose Lee Kwang Soo.)
There it is.
I made it.
(This is amazing.)
Isn't this incredible?
(Doesn't it look real?)
(I choose Lee Kwang Soo.)
Isn't this amazing?
- You're amazing. - I made this.
He probably already chose someone.
Gosh, I should've made this earlier. I was too late.
- Did you see my text? - Hey.
I took a screenshot and sent it to you. Take a look.
- Okay, okay. - You saw it, right?
Okay. I'll send you mine.
- I sent it to you too. - Send me your screenshot.
- I'll send you the screenshot now. - Okay.
- I definitely sent you mine. - Okay.
(Did Kwang Soo really fall for it?)
I got a text from Kwang Soo.
I should check. I must check if it's real or not.
Hey.
This must be real.
It's hard to forge the "untitled" on top.
(Untitled: Congratulations. You have received 100 dollars.)
(Did Kwang Soo really send So Min 50 dollars?)
(5 minutes ago right after the call with So Min)
- You have your phone, right? - Yes.
Let me see it.
(Kwang Soo wouldn't be that naive. He faked his text too.)
I just sent you the text. Send it to me right now.
(He faked an "untitled" message that So Min didn't think about.)
- I got it. It worked. - I sent it.
(It's the great betrayer's class. He's one step ahead of So Min.)
(So Min is such a fool.)
This must be real.
(The screenshot looks authentic.)
He must've really sent the money.
(She falls for her own trick.)
It'd be great if I had this for everyone.
For each member. I'll have one for Jae Seok and Haha.
(She targets Haha and Jae Seok with the same method.)
That's right. I can just change the name.
This is great. Okay.
(She sends a fake screenshot.)
Gosh.
You know fake news can be dangerous these days, right?
I received fake news just now.
It's a fake tabloid. This is what I got.
(It's So Min's fake text message that isn't believable at all.)
(Jeon So Min)
The world is a scary place.
(How dare she try to pull a fast one on me?)
(He responds to her cute text with another cute text.)
Goodness. Then I should send this to her.
"My gosh."
"My gosh, I'm so touched." Just like this.
(How dare you try to fool me?)
I just received a text message from Haha. He likes it.
He sent me a lot of thumbs-ups and said he's touched.
So Min did this...
(This fool is the only one that fell for her trickery.)
She sent me the screenshot.
(So Min sent me 50 dollars?)
So Min just sent me...
(What a good friend she is.)
(I choose Yu Jae Seok.)
I'll give So Min 50 dollars.
(So Min puts one over on Jae Seok.)
I choose So Min.
(Everyone finishes transferring 50 dollars to someone.)
I got it. I got the text message.
"You're on good terms with others as expected."
"You're a good neighbor."
(Check who sent you half of their money.)
(Should I check how much I got?)
(Neighbor Website)
(If no one gave them money, they'd have only 50 dollars.)
Darn it.
It says I only have 50 dollars now.
(Darn it. It says I only have 50 dollars now.)
(None of them chose Jae Seok.)
(He made all that fuss but to no avail.)
Gosh, this is making me mad.
Kwang Soo and So Min. Gosh, those brats.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
(Add 1 more person to the list.)
None of the members gave me any.
(He wasn't chosen just like Jae Seok.)
I can't understand this.
Who else could they give the money if not to me?
(Think about all the fuss I made.)
I have 150 dollars.
- Okay. - Who sent him the money?
- It says I have 150 dollars. - Okay.
150 dollars?
If it's 150 dollars, that means 2 people sent me money.
(Ji Hyo and Haha chose Jong Kook.)
It says I have 150 dollars.
(Ji Hyo also has 150 dollars.)
(So Min and Seok Jin chose Ji Hyo.)
Jackpot!
I have 100 dollars. That's pretty good.
I didn't have a bad start.
Since Seok Jin isn't as aggressive as others,
I should give some money to a weak member for now...
and get it back later.
(Se Chan gets 50 dollars from Jong Kook.)
Wait, this means someone sent me 50 dollars.
Who could it be? Is it really Jong Kook?
I didn't live a selfish life. At least one person chose me.
(Kwang Soo chose Haha.)
Gosh, this is better than I expected.
(Thank you, whoever you are.)
I have 100 dollars.
Seriously? Only one person sent me money.
(Only the fool, Jae Seok chose her.)
Only one person sent me the money.
(This isn't on pause.)
Other members are talking about from whom they got the money.
You might have to wait a bit.
- They're still talking about it. - Do you want me to punch you?
(This cruel reality is hard for him to bear.)
Rest up for a bit. I have nothing to say.
(Stop filming for a while.)
I have nothing to say. I want to be alone. Stop filming now.
Can you clap for the slate?
(Here you go.)
(The transfer of Running Money ends as it only wounded Kwang Soo.)
- Let's go! - Look at this place.
Listen.
- You know what? - Watch my clip.
- Don't call yourself a human being. - I...
- I... Okay. - Unbelievable.
I'll be honest. I only sent the money because I had to.
- If not, I wouldn't have. - Of course not.
- You bet. - Why would we?
I wasn't going to send anyone the money and give up on it.
- Don't send me fake messages. - Goodness, unbelievable.
Everyone sent fake messages around.
- You know what? I think... - Everyone was all the same.
All right. You'll go inside to meet today's guests.
- Really? Okay, shall we go in? - My gosh.
(Will they find today's guests inside?)
- This looks like a haunted house. - This isn't scary, right?
(The mysterious darkness fills this space.)
- What is this? - Look at the back.
- This place is huge. - It's huge.
(Today's guests will be in here?)
- Hey. - What is it?
- What is it? - What is that? My goodness.
Where?
- Hey. - Hey, what's going on?
- What is this? - What's happening?
(What's happening? We were supposed to meet the guests here.)
(What on earth awaits the members?)
What's going on here?
(It's pitch-dark.)
(A mysterious-looking man shows up.)
(Is this blond man today's guest?)
(As the lights come on, a song suddenly starts playing.)
(Drumming)
(The blonde performance group shows themselves in the spotlight.)
(I should film this since it's quite entertaining.)
(But who are our guests today? Why is there such a concert?)
- What is that? - What's happening?
(Flying)
(A group of people fall from the sky.)
(Are our guests in there?)
(It's a chaos.)
(They are professional dancers. They're not the guests.)
(Who are today's guests that require such a fancy show?)
(Where on earth are the guests?)
(There's another blackout.)
Gosh, what is this?
(And three people show themselves in the darkness.)
- Who are they? Who are they? - My gosh.
(Here are our real guests!)
- Who are they? - What a way to make an entrance.
(Are these the guests for today?)
- These are our guests? - He's holding onto his waist.
- Today's special guests. - Who are they?
(They are the trio of today's special guests.)
This is Kim Roi Ha.
(The first guest is introduced at last.)
(Kim Roi Ha, the best actor for playing the villain)
(His authentic acting of a villain swept the screens in Chungmuro.)
(This legendary actor has made it to our show with his lethal charms.)
(This is so awesome! The legend has come!)
(We wholeheartedly welcome you, Roi Ha!)
Seo Hyo Rim!
(The only female guest is introduced next.)
(Looking lovely)
(Seo Hyo Rim, the prettiest and the best actress for the villainess)
(She crushed her villainess' role with her almond-shaped eyes.)
(An honest, laid-back, and strong woman is joining today.)
(It's Seo Hyo Rim! This is awesome. Their jaws drop open.)
(And the last guest is finally introduced.)
(It's nice to meet you all.)
(Kwak Si Yang, a super rookie among the villains)
(He became a scary villain from a sweet, romantic guy.)
(He displayed unexpected charms through his scary acting.)
(Amazing Trio of Villains: Roi Ha, Hyo Rim, and Si Yang)
(The performance was for the trio.)
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
(We heartily welcome you.)
All right.
Roi Ha, please say hello to the viewers.
Nice to meet you all. Hello, I'm Actor Kim Roi Ha.
I'm your biggest fan.
- You're so charismatic. - By the way,
- this is his first variety show. - That's right.
- Yes, it's my first. - Right?
So this is your first variety show, but you wore a tracksuit to this?
- That's fine. It's Running Man. - That's right.
I wore this so I could run, but I'm the only one wearing this.
- Why was I asked to wear this? - Their outfits...
- are polar opposites. - They are completely different.
They asked me to wear a fancy dress,
- so I wore this. - Why...
did no one tell me to dress up?
What did they tell you?
They told me to dress casually.
- But this is too casual. - You even wore running shoes.
(It looks really casual.)
No one has dressed this casually.
They told him to dress casually, so he listened.
(Is this how variety shows work?)
When they first appeared, Roi Ha seemed to...
feel shy.
He put his hand on his back.
It stopped in the middle.
I thought we had only two guests today.
I thought Roi Ha was a cameraman.
I thought he was filming...
- when I saw him from behind. - You might get in trouble.
- Roi Ha looks a bit angry. - You shouldn't go too far.
You're embarrassing Roi Ha.
Don't go too far.
We appeared in "The Sound of Heart" together.
That's right.
What was Kwang Soo like while shooting that drama?
I'd never seen...
such a tall and nice person before.
- A tall and nice person? - A tall and nice person.
(A tall and nice person?)
A tall and nice person.
- He's really tall. - He's tall and nice.
I'd never met anyone like him before.
In the movies,
- Roi Ha usually plays the villain. - He's usually the villain.
But actors who play villains a lot seem to be weak in real life.
- That's right. - When they're...
- on this show, they're weak. - We've seen that.
- Park Hee Soon, for example. - Exactly.
(Do you remember?)
- He is so weak. - Exactly.
One actor lost to me in arm-wrestling.
Who was it? Kim Hee Won.
- Kim Hee Won. - He was so weak too.
(But they were all funny.)
(Will Roi Ha make us laugh too?)
Kwak Si Yang is here too.
(Another villain actor, Kwak Si Yang)
Si Yang, how are you feeling?
- This is your first appearance. - That's right.
Have you been on many variety shows?
- I... - He got married once.
- That's right. - He got married.
- You got married to Kim So Yeon. - Yes.
You got married.
- He got married? - Yes.
(Surprised)
(Why is he surprised?)
Why did you get married so early?
That's not what we're talking about.
We're talking about "We Got Married".
(We're talking about a show.)
He didn't get married for real.
He got married on the show.
- So he's not married? - No.
He's not married in real life.
Hold on.
Just on the show.
Seok Jin doesn't seem to know that show.
Gosh, Seok Jin.
I thought he got married for real.
Si Yang is here.
You're very tall.
- He is. - I'm 187cm tall.
You're 187cm tall?
Gosh, he's really tall.
Like I always say, that's the right way to become tall.
Don't be like Kwang Soo.
- That's the right way. - Kwang Soo...
- If you're just tall... - Kwang Soo...
really doesn't look good considering his height.
I'm not jealous at all.
They drive me crazy whenever we have tall guests.
It would have been better if his face looked better.
- What? - Kwang Soo has a long waist.
- What? - Kwang Soo has a very long waist.
What are you talking about?
- His waist is 1m long. - My waist is not long.
His waist is 1m long.
I once saw Hyo Rim at a cafe near Namsan.
She was wearing no makeup.
- Really? - You don't remember?
When was it? Oh, right.
You have a worse memory than Seok Jin?
Why do you have such a bad memory?
You remembered that?
I'm hurt that Seok Jin remembered it.
If it had been a guy, he wouldn't have remembered.
He wouldn't have remembered.
- Never. - She left a strong impression.
None of us three were wearing makeup.
- That's right. - It might have been...
someone else.
- She looks very different... - I...
I came here to get you.
- What do you mean? - Today...
- What are you talking about? - You know each other?
Hold on.
You know each other?
Before Kwang Soo debuted,
- I presented an award to him. - An award?
- That's right. The commercial... - His commercial became popular.
For the commercial where I shouted, "Ah Reum",
- I won an award. - Really?
Wasn't it your first drama?
- Yes. - We did a drama together.
And he followed me around, drunk.
(She suddenly criticizes him.)
He did that before he debuted too?
I didn't.
He does that these days too.
What are you talking?
- I didn't do that. - I mean, in the drama.
- I did that in the drama. - In the drama?
- You should be careful. - You should be.
I thought he did that back then too.
You surprised me.
Let me tell you about today's race.
You're going to try to eliminate others and survive.
It's called Out Dot Com Race.
- Out Dot Com Race? - Out Dot Com Race?
Out Dot Com.
Every round, the member with the least money will be the target.
The other members will...
participate in an auction through Out Dot Com.
The highest bidder will...
win the right to eliminate a member.
Having more money gives you an advantage...
because then you can bid more money.
That's right.
Everyone will want to eliminate Kwang Soo.
Of course. I'll try to eliminate him.
- Gosh. - He's our number one target.
We should try to eliminate Kwang Soo.
Please choose a number.
I choose one.
She's getting the highest amount.
- Let's see. The lowest amount. - The lowest amount.
- For Si Yang... - The average amount.
(Everyone has Running Money now.)
Let's start the race after changing into team uniforms.
- Okay! - Okay!
(Current Sums of Money)
(A huge water tank hanging from the ceiling?)
(This mission has the biggest scale ever.)
(Under the huge water tank is...)
(a huge mole game.)
To distribute Running Money and select a target,
let's start Water Tank Quiz.
It's a water tank?
- A water tank? - Are we going into the water?
Two teams will take turns.
One member from the offense...
will act out words.
- In the water tank? - In the water tank?
How are we going to get up there?
- Is that water? - Who is going to do that?
(The water tank is safe and used in performances.)
(You can even dance in it.)
The rest of the team will play the mole game.
They have to guess the words while avoiding the hammers.
The team that gets more words right will win.
The winning team will get 200 dollars.
(The winning team gets 200 dollars.)
- That's a lot. - I'll have to win.
The member with the least money in the losing team...
- will become the target. - Automatically?
Once you become the target, you'll be out.
- You'll be out. - There's no chance.
As Roi Ha and...
Seok Jin are the oldest, they'll be the team leaders.
I want to be on Roi Ha's team.
- Definitely. - Please choose me.
But we don't know if he's good at games.
Should we play rock-paper-scissors?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(The winner can choose a member.)
(Roi Ha wins.)
Roi Ha wins.
- You choose Si Yang? - He's very fast.
Okay.
- Roi Ha. - Jong Kook.
- I choose Jong Kook. - Me?
Why did you choose Si Yang, not Jong Kook?
Will the game require strength?
- You have to think, right? - Of course.
He thinks Jong Kook is strong...
but stupid.
(Slandering)
(Jong Kook only has strength.)
You said we have to think.
(That's not what I meant.)
Don't say that.
- You must be right. - I'm not saying you mean it.
It's just what I think.
You're the target now.
- Okay! Kwang Soo is... - Kwang Soo is...
- saved in my heart. - saved in my heart.
You're saved in my heart.
The team leaders, Seok Jin and Roi Ha, will go up.
Seok Jin.
Team leaders.
- Please go this way. - Not us?
See you, Seok Jin.
(Good luck.)
You can do this!
See you!
Why...
Is it safe?
Yes, it's safe.
Only one person gets the hammer.
You'll play cham, cham, cham,
and the winning team will get a water gun.
Good. Let's win that.
- Let's win that. - Okay.
We can use it against the other team?
We could shoot at their mouths too.
- Si Yang, go. - Me?
- Me? - You can do this.
We choose Hyo Rim.
(We choose Hyo Rim.)
Si Yang, you have to win.
You know how to play cham, cham, cham, right?
- If I lose, I do this, right? - Right.
Should we put them like this?
Let's put them like this.
- Like this. - Like that?
Si Yang isn't going easy on her.
I'm a girl.
It doesn't matter.
Don't go easy on her.
He's strict.
- He's very strict. - Fair and square.
I want to see how good Si Yang is.
Play rock-paper-scissors. Start.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Si Yang gets to attack.)
- Okay. This is important. - Do a good job.
- Hit her. - Do a good job.
Look me in the eye.
Cham, cham, cham
(Si Yang wins.)
(Hitting)
Cham, cham, cham
Hold on.
(Did you see that?)
- Si Yang... - What?
- Si Yang... - What's wrong?
- Come here. - It's a game.
- Hey! - It's a game.
- What did you just do? - What is this?
(Laughing)
Hyo Rim is angry!
Her face is red!
Come here.
Si Yang.
Hyo Rim's face is so red.
(I just followed the rules.)
- Hyo Rim is angry! - Hyo Rim.
As soon as you lose, you should cover your head.
- Let's play one more round. - Hit him right away.
(Angry versus strict)
- I'm scared. - She looks different.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Si Yang gets to attack again.)
(Hyo Rim didn't even get to touch the pot.)
Cham, cham
(Will Hyo Rim be able to protect herself this time?)
(Si Yang wins again.)
(Hitting)
(Si Yang hits her right away.)
- Hold on. What's with you? - What?
- What's wrong? - What's with you?
- What do you expect him to do? - Hey!
- He's supposed to be fast. - What's with you?
What did I do wrong?
I just did what I was supposed to do!
They told me to do it.
- They told him to do it. - I just did my best.
- This is too much. - He's just doing his best.
He didn't hit her hard. He was just fast.
We started fighting.
(Si Yang is so strict.)
- Si Yang wins! - We win!
- You can have the water gun. - Okay!
- Play one more round. - Okay.
We should.
(Meanwhile, by the water tank...)
(Worried)
How are we going to do this?
(I don't want to be the team leader.)
We'll just have to do it.
They should play again.
- They should play again. - Wait.
You seem very upset.
The prize should be one more water gun.
- Seriously. - One more water gun?
- Si Yang. - It was a man against a woman.
Hyo Rim played against him.
Next up is Jong Kook against So Min.
No way, I'm not playing.
- Okay. - I'm not doing it.
- That's great. - You can do it, Jong Kook.
- Okay. - We got it.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - I'm not going to play.
- You aren't making a sacrifice. - Okay.
- Okay. - This is great.
Okay, okay.
- Let's go, Jong Kook. - Okay.
- Hold this. - You can do it.
Attack him right away.
(Whispering)
- Rock - They're too loud.
You're acting like piranhas.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Look at them.
- You must win. - Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min wins.)
You have a chance.
(She has the right of command.)
Cham, cham, cham
(She could defeat Jong Kook.)
(What's with the pot?)
(She tries to attack him with the pot.)
(Why are you giving it to me?)
- What are you doing? - Nice shot.
- What are you doing? - I was in a hurry.
- I was in a hurry. - Hit him with one hand.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jong Kook wins.)
- Okay, cham, cham, cham - I heard the sound.
- Okay. - He got it.
Cham, cham, cham
(He hits her in 1 second.)
She blocked him, but it got a dent.
(The pot is dented after one hit.)
(With a dented pot, the game is over.)
- She blocked, but it got a dent. - Okay.
- Let's go. We won. - Let's go.
- It's ours. - We won.
(They must be doing something fun.)
(You didn't forget about us, did you?)
We'll play the final round with a water gun as a prize.
- Okay, let's bet on water guns. - We'll take all of them.
- Okay. - Put down the water guns.
Both water guns?
Se Chan, you should play with Jae Seok.
- Okay, play with Jae Seok. - Okay.
(They try to coach him again. Will it work?)
In which direction should we put the hammer?
- Using the right hand is easier. - Okay.
Change its position after playing rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
(He tries to dominate the game.)
- Take off your glasses. - Okay.
- Here we go. - You must block well.
- Use one hand diagonally. - Okay.
- That's right. - Do I hit like this?
- You should hit like this instead. - Okay.
(Hitting)
Wait, he's not even playing.
- He was demonstrating. - Fine.
Did you see that? You must attack him right away.
- Here we go. Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
Okay.
(Se Chan has the right of command.)
Cham, cham, cham
- That was great. - Cham, cham, cham
That was great.
- Good job. - That's good.
- We got it. - Why are you so slow?
- You won. - I wanted to hit him once.
- Defend well like Italy. - This is great.
Defend well.
(It's Jae Seok's offense.)
Great, here I go.
(How will Jae Seok attack?)
Stay alert.
- Cham, cham, cham - Okay.
- Nice. - Cham, cham, cham
(Se Chan's super defense)
- Nice, nice. - You did it.
- Good job. - You used your left hand.
- It was your left hand. - It should have been my right.
That was good. It was super defense.
(Current score is 0 to 0.)
We need to score.
(The winner gets 2 water guns.)
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do it.
(He tries to get their attention at an important moment.)
- Hey. - Wait, this is an important game.
- You're not important. - Stop it.
- Give us a minute. - This is important.
Roi Ha can't stand it anymore either.
(Are you listening to me?)
Is that fun?
(Will your game be over?)
Let's play.
- Rock-paper-scissors - That's good.
After you finish saying, "cham, cham, cham",
- only think about grabbing the pot. - Okay.
Just remember this.
- Move the fingers like this. - Okay.
Good luck.
- Here I go. - Do it slowly.
- Cham, cham, cham - What?
(Is it right or left?)
- What are you doing? - What was that?
- That was it. - You were bewitched.
- I was bewitched? - Next.
- Say "cham, cham, cham". - Okay.
- Cham, cham, cham - Okay, that's right.
That's right.
(However,)
(why did he grab the squeaky hammer?)
That's right.
- Okay. - You can't hit him.
- We got it. - Good job.
- Kwang Soo, you can't hit him. - I was so angry.
(You deserve it for cheating.)
- Why did you do that? - I can't do it anymore!
- Be quiet. - You can do it!
- We're having fun. - I can't do it!
We're doing something important.
That's not what's important. Let's go.
- Do it once. - Cham, cham, cham
(Se Chan makes a serious attack.)
(If he wins one more time, he gets 2 water guns.)
- Okay. - Cham, cham, cham
(Se Chan finally wins.)
(The game finally ends.)
- Good job anyway. - It was because of my left hand.
- We'll shoot a lot of water. - Okay.
(Team Roi Ha wins 2 water guns.)
- He's already over there. - That looks amazing.
- You can do it, Roi Ha. - You can do it.
- Aren't you scared? - Are you okay?
- That's not it. - Gosh, good luck.
If all of us answer correctly, it'd be amazing.
- You're right. - Right?
Only one of us gets hit, so let's go up together.
- Okay, bear it. - If you get hit, bear the pain.
- Let's go. - Team Roi Ha's question is...
about animals.
- The category is animals. - Animals are easy.
- Get ready. - The time limit is three minutes.
Get ready.
(The time limit is 3 minutes.)
(The first keyword is snake.)
(Squirming)
(Let's go all at once.)
- It's animals. - 1, 2, 3.
(Only Si Yang goes up.)
What's going on?
Gosh, I can't see.
(Only one of us gets hit, so let's go up together.)
(Si Yang who follows rules believed what they said.)
(He got tricked by others and became a lonely mole.)
(He's the only one who gets attacked.)
(Here I come.)
I can't see.
- It's a snake. - A snake?
Come up now!
(Frilled-neck lizard)
(It's a perfect demonstration.)
What's that? Wait.
I can't see.
(However, they're busy getting hit.)
Don't look.
Go back inside.
- What's going on? - They're over here.
(He doesn't care what's going on.)
What's that?
(He's a lonely, frilled-neck lizard in the jungle.)
- I can't see. - Lizard.
It's a frilled-neck lizard.
Good job.
(Okay, good job.)
(A new animal appears in the water.)
- He's moving. - What's that?
(Guess what I am.)
- 1, 2. - What's that?
- Let's go up and look. - 1, 2, 3.
(The moles go up all at once.)
I know!
(Roi Ha demonstrates elegantly.)
Take a guess.
- A turtle? - Jong Kook.
- Is it a turtle? - Hit with this hammer.
(A loud thud)
What was that?
- What's going on? - What is it?
- Let's see. - What was that just now?
Wait a minute.
- Jong Kook got him. - What's going on?
Come up.
My goodness.
- Let me go. - Do it.
This is not right.
Wait, let me go down.
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
(Thanks to Kwang Soo,)
(So Min guesses ostrich.)
Someone hit me with his hand.
- Gosh, it hurts. - 5, 4.
3, 2.
(Are you watching me?)
I can't see.
(I'm still watching.)
- Okay, time's up. - What's going on?
- Okay. - What's going on?
- This much cheating is nothing. - Of course not.
Let's give it a try.
Thank goodness that we have water guns.
- We have to... - I'll go.
- Ballerina. - They're shooting so much.
(They work very hard.)
(Thanks to Jae Seok and Jong Kook, they answer 10 questions.)
You won with a score of 10 to 7.
(Team Seok Jin wins.)
- However... - However?
(However...)
- However... - They cheated.
Team Seok Jin cheated too much.
There's a campaign called You Get Hit If You Cheat.
- Did that exist? - Yes, it did.
That's why I got hit when I cheated.
(The first candidate was Kwang Soo.)
(Kids, if you cheat,)
(you get hit.)
If one member of the team gets flicked in the head,
- we approve of your win. - Si Yang will flick.
- We decided who will get hit. - Si Yang doesn't hesitate at all.
I do whatever I'm told to do.
1, 2, 3.
- Jong Kook. - We pick Jong Kook.
- I knew it. - Okay.
- Okay. - As you know,
- Jong Kook takes revenge. - Of course.
- You must remember that. - I hold...
a lot of grudges.
He holds grudges.
It's Si Yang's first time doing it, so he might not control himself.
You won't be on this show again, right?
- Will you? - In two months.
Don't come back within two months.
I'll shoot a drama just to see you.
Where does Si Yang hang out most of the time?
- Is it Gangnam or Hongdae? - I stay in my neighborhood.
- Where do you live? - Don't tell him.
- Ichon-dong. - Ichon-dong?
I'll go to Ichon-dong.
Cha Tae Hyun lives there.
Tae Hyun moved to Apgujeong.
- We went there. - Didn't he tell you?
- Did he move? - Didn't he tell you?
Didn't he tell you?
(I shouldn't have said it.)
He's even more upset.
- Why did you say that? - He's more upset.
(He's too direct.)
Why did you say that?
(Tae Hyun, call me when you see this.)
- I'm sorry. - All right.
- Si Yang doesn't know these things. - Let me start.
He doesn't.
(Si Yang hits Jong Kook so hard.)
(We thank our second honorary ambassador for the clip.)
(You Get Hit If You Cheat)
(Si Yang hits Jong Kook so hard.)
Si Yang can't control himself. He doesn't know how to do it.
- What is this? - Okay!
- Si Yang, run! - Okay!
- Did I do something wrong? - You should run.
- Run! - Okay!
- Run! - What's wrong?
Run!
Okay. You get hit if you cheat.
(I'll remember that.)
(Running Man makes sure every cheater gets reprimanded.)
Team Seok Jin wins...
and gets 200 dollars.
Good work.
- Is everyone getting 40 dollars? - Is everyone getting 40 dollars?
No, no. Hey! What are you talking about?
- I should get 100. I went up there. - What are you talking about?
- It was hard for us too. - Guys!
I wish I'd been up there.
- Let's divide it up. - No.
Then...
4 of us will get 50 dollars, and 1 of us will get nothing.
I wrote 50 dollars on 4 of these, and 0 on the last one.
- Let's do that. - Good.
Pick one. Let's start from Hyo Rim.
Show it to us.
- Open it. - Is it zero?
- Open it right now. - Is it zero?
It must be zero.
- Show us. - Is it zero?
Ta-da!
(I get 50 dollars.)
She was acting.
It's 1 in 4 now.
1 in 4.
(3 of them will get 50 dollars, and 1 of them will get nothing.)
(Seok Jin has made his choice.)
If I get nothing, I'm doomed.
My luck...
- Open it right away. - Let's see.
(Seok Jin came up with this idea.)
(He gets nothing.)
(The others get 50 dollars.)
- What happened? - Oh, my.
(He's so unlucky.)
- Oh, my. - How?
(Seok Jin is the one who went into the water tank.)
How can this be possible?
He went up there and everything.
Among the losing members,
two have the least money and have become the targets.
Two?
(2 members become the targets.)
(Lee Kwang Soo and Kim Roi Ha)
- Please start the bidding. - Gosh.
Our first targets are very strong.
Gosh.
I want it so badly.
(Jong Kook wants the right. How much will Jong Kook bid?)
(Careful)
(Exposed)
(He is done bidding.)
Gosh.
(He notices Jae Seok.)
You shouldn't look.
12 dollars for Roi Ha? Then...
I want it so badly.
(Are you talking about me?)
(Peeking)
Gosh.
What is this?
I should raise my bid.
(Everyone has to send their bids.)
Is it too little?
Should I bid more? I have the money anyway.
(Everyone is done bidding.)
(Who will win the right to eliminate Roi Ha and Kwang Soo?)
Let me announce the result.
The right to eliminate Roi Ha...
(First up is Roi Ha.)
goes to someone who bid 70 dollars.
(Someone bid 70 dollars.)
- 70 dollars? - 70 dollars?
It's one person.
It's more than what I had in the first place.
- They must have a lot of money. - I know.
And the right to eliminate Kwang Soo...
was sold for 90 dollars.
(It was sold for even more money.)
- 90 dollars? - Who is it?
- 90 dollars? - Oh, my.
- My bid was nothing. - Someone has a lot of money.
- You're expensive. - I don't feel bad.
90 dollars?
- Kwang Soo is happy. - Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
(Who bought the rights to eliminate the two members?)
(They move to a restaurant.)
By the way, I don't know who they are,
but some people seem to want to spend a lot of money.
- You might... - If someone bid 90 dollars,
- it can't be one of us. - It must be Hyo Rim.
I think it's a guest.
As Si Yang is so rigid...
- That's right. - It's possible.
I bid 30 dollars, and I thought it was a lot.
30 dollars can't do anything.
- I... - Hey!
You bid 18 dollars.
(I saw you bidding.)
So I bid 18 dollars and 10 cents.
If you're scared, stay out of it.
- He's bad at betting. - He's so petty.
- Okay. - On that note,
we'll release some more Running Money.
- Good. We need it. - We need it.
- Give us a chance. - I like it.
The first mission is "Random Five Second Talk".
You'll be given 3 random questions about a member.
- Give 3 answers in 5 seconds. - Okay.
We can just say whatever.
If you succeed, you'll get 30 dollars.
That's a lot.
- That'd help a lot. - That's a lot.
It's a lot of money.
First, we'll ask So Min about Si Yang.
She's been...
She's even sitting next to him.
- What is she doing? - What is she doing?
It's so funny when she covers her mouth.
- Stop it now. - I love it.
I love it.
I'll look at this camera since it's about Si Yang.
(Uncomfortable)
Why would you look at that camera?
For a two shot.
- Gosh. - Here goes the question.
(So Min's Random 5 Second Talk starts.)
What was Si Yang's first impression?
Cute, lovely, and sexy.
Pass.
(You play this kind of game?)
What do you want Si Yang to say to you?
"I love you," "I like you," and "give me a hug."
(What do you want Si Yang to say to you?)
("I love you," "I like you," and "give me a hug"?)
Stop it!
- What are you doing? - What was that?
What was that?
- Why do you laugh like that? - Wake up.
"I love you," "I like you," and "give me a hug"?
I felt so embarrassed after saying that.
- It doesn't make sense. - It should make sense.
Si Yang is still keeping a straight face.
- He's so cold. - He's not even smiling.
- Shouldn't he be happy? - He's not affected at all.
Si Yang is so rigid.
- He's like a robot. - He's like a rock.
- We'll ask Ji Hyo this time. - Okay.
We'll ask her about Haha.
- About Haha. - We're Mapo Siblings.
Here we go.
When does Byul scold Haha?
When he doesn't take care of Dream, when he doesn't take care of Soul,
and when he doesn't do house chores.
- She's so good. - That was perfect.
What kinds of bad things has Haha said about Jong Kook?
(Hesitating)
(Has Haha said bad things about Jong Kook?)
"He's rude," "he's mean," and "he shouldn't live like that!"
("He's rude," "he's mean," and "he shouldn't live like that!")
- Okay. - Good.
(Hitting)
You did well.
I'm...
- I'm hurt. - Why?
- Ji Hyo said the truth. - It was nice.
- Next question. - You have a good memory.
(I'm impressed, Ji Hyo.)
- Next question. - I've heard them a few times.
(Everyone is having fun.)
Roi Ha. Stop looking out the window.
You'll play soon too.
- Focus. - You'll play too.
Here we go.
We'll ask Hyo Rim about Kwang Soo.
- Good. - That's great.
- This is it. - It's going to be fun.
Hold on.
I can't wait.
Here we go. What are Kwang Soo's strengths?
He's a good actor, he's tall, and he's nice.
- Good job. - Good job.
(He's a good actor, he's tall, and he's nice.)
- It was very nice. - It was easy.
- Next question. - Good job.
When do you feel jealous of Kwang Soo?
When he looks at other girls, when his acting is good,
and when he makes more money than I do.
- She's so honest. - When he looks at other girls?
- She's honest. - Why would you feel jealous?
- I want him to look at me. - Of course.
- He's a guy too. - It was nice.
She did well.
- Just look at me. - She did very well.
Kwang Soo.
- He's happy. - Kwang Soo is a guy.
- This is so sudden. - It was...
- He must be surprised. - What is this?
- Hyo Rim did a good job. - I want 30 dollars.
Last question.
What are Kwang Soo's sleeping habits?
(What? Sleeping habits?)
(It's a very personal question.)
He snores, grinds his teeth, and hugs something.
(She lists them so easily.)
(They really are Kwang Soo's sleeping habits.)
- What is this? - I don't know.
- It's true. He hugs something. - Kwang Soo...
- He hugs something. - How did you know that?
- Of course, I know. - How?
We worked together. We shot a drama together.
- How... - But...
- We shot a sitcom together. - Yes.
It was pretty good.
- It was... - Pass.
- It was perfect. - It was.
You get 30 dollars.
(Hyo Rim gets 30 dollars.)
- She has so much money. - She's so rich.
We should stop her.
- She's the richest among us. - She's far ahead of us.
This time, we'll ask Seok Jin...
- questions about Roi Ha. - It's going to be fun.
I hurt his feelings in the beginning.
(They were talking about their ages.)
Between Roi Ha and Seok Jin, who is older?
Aren't you younger than me?
(Arrogant)
I was born in the Year of the Snake.
(Roi Ha is one year older.)
You're older than me.
(You're older than me.)
Why are you so rude?
(Surprised)
- Gosh. - I mean...
- What did he just do? - What did you do?
What did he do?
He should be caned.
(They started off on the wrong foot.)
I'll make it up to you.
I was rude to him.
We'll see some bromance today.
Really.
We haven't seen...
middle-aged men's bromance...
in a while.
- Okay. - Here goes the first question.
Here we go.
What nicknames would you give Roi Ha?
(What nicknames would you give Roi Ha?)
- Sneaky... - The time is up.
(Sneaky)
(Sneaky?)
- What do you mean? - What do you mean?
- What? - What did you say?
- Listen. - Does that even make sense?
Sneaky?
He isn't witty at all.
- Sneaky. - He isn't witty.
- Sneaky sounds cute. - What is sneaky?
(It's bromance between two old men.)
We'll ask a question about Seok Jin...
to Roi Ha.
I think he will be good at this.
- All right. - Just do it.
Let's see.
When are you embarrassed by him?
(Silence)
When no one laughs.
(When no one laughs, Roi Ha is embarrassed.)
- That's right. - That never happens.
He only said, "when no one laughs".
- Roi Ha. - Listen.
I'm doing very well these days.
- Roi Ha. - I like when no one laughs.
I think he meant it. He's really sorry for saying it.
- Just do it, Roi Ha. - It became...
extremely awkward between them.
- What's going on? - I'll take a taxi instead.
- Bromance is over. - This is the worst.
(How will their bromance end?)
Here's your next mission.
It's called Hand and Body Separately.
- This is difficult. - It's hard.
- Don't we have to act cute? - "Act cute"?
Listen to the question given by the staff.
Say the answer...
while showing the wrong answer with your hand.
- It's hard. - I have to score here.
I'll give it a try.
Here comes Jae Seok.
- It requires... - He's a math genius.
separation of the brain from the hand.
Here comes Jae Seok, a math genius.
When I was young, the only private class...
- I took was how to use an abacus. - Really?
You must be good at it.
I can't imagine your being good at math.
- I learned how to use an abacus. - All right.
Start.
- Hand and Body Separately, start - Hand and Body Separately, start
2 minus 1 equals?
(They must say 1 and show a wrong number with their fingers.)
(What?)
What?
(He makes an unknown sound.)
What kind of answer is that?
- I... I was startled. - Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. - Goodness.
- It's because I was startled. - He just made a sound.
No, no.
- Were you startled? Okay. - I was.
- Get ready. - All right.
- Get ready. - I'm not ready yet.
- Hand and Body Separately, start - Hand and Body Separately, start
9 minus 1 equals?
Mouth.
(What kind of number is mouth?)
"Mouth"? What is he saying?
- What do you mean? - He says strange things.
I have no idea.
- Gosh. - I can't help it.
- Come on. - You try it.
Where did you learn how to use an abacus?
Hey, be quiet.
- This is how a math genius falls. - Goodness.
Next is Roi Ha's turn.
Start.
- Hand and Body Separately, start - Hand and Body Separately, start
2 plus 1 equals?
Three.
(He says the correct answer, but what do his fingers show?)
(He thinks about showing the wrong answer.)
(He puts up three fingers.)
What's that, Roi Ha?
Rock and roll!
Rock and roll, peace.
Peace.
Come on.
- Come on, everybody. - Come on.
Yes, come on.
Rock and roll.
He's like an idol singer.
- Yes. - He's an idol singer.
I meant to do something else.
It isn't easy.
- Goodness. - We'll give you another chance.
- Hand and Body Separately, start - Hand and Body Separately, start
2 plus 5 equals?
Eight.
(His hand shows the rock and roll sign.)
(No matter what the answer is, it's always rock and roll.)
- What is he doing with his hand? - Yes.
- Rock and roll. - Peace.
(His rock music spirit comes out.)
He likes rock music a lot.
That's what he likes.
(What opportunity awaits them at the restaurant?)
(They arrive at a naengmyeon restaurant.)
It must be naengmyeon.
It's bossam and naengmyeon.
- This is great. - Yes.
(What? There are squeaky hammers.)
(What kind of squeaky hammer mission awaits them?)
- Are you happy with your seats? - Yes.
(Everyone takes a seat randomly.)
(It's a mission where you hit the person next to you.)
(He gets a chance to hit Jong Kook.)
It's a chance to win money and meal tickets.
(Running Money and meal ticket mission)
It's Funny Scene Quiz.
- "Funny Scene Quiz"? - "Scene Quiz"?
Watch the given scene.
The member to answer correctly gains one point.
If the answer is wrong, you get hit from the person next to you.
(Guess the next line.)
You receive Running Money depending on your points.
The top five members get naengmyeon and grilled meat.
- The top 5? - The top 5.
We need to rank top five.
Today's naengmyeon looks delicious.
The member who earns the least amount of money...
- will be eliminated. - Eliminated?
It'll be amazing to place first.
Here's the first question. Play.
Sir... Sir.
Pardon me, but how do you know our chief?
(What's the following line by Choi Min Sik?)
(It's a famous scene from a movie.)
- I've seen it. - I saw it such a long time ago.
(We'll reveal the answer first.)
Pardon me, but how do you know our chief?
- Your chief lives in Namcheon-dong? - Yes.
You punk, do you know what I did?
Your chief and I ate together yesterday.
We went to a sauna together. We did everything.
(Here's the answer.)
Do we have to say the exact lines?
Yes, but we'll approve of it if it's close enough.
- I know the answer. - It's quite tricky.
"Your chief?"
"He lives in Deungchon-dong, right?"
"Deungchon-dong"?
(Namcheon-dong is correct.)
(Where did Deungchon-dong come from?)
SBS is in Deungchon-dong.
What did you say?
- That's in Seoul. - It's Namcheon-dong.
Deungchon-dong is in Seoul.
Lift up your head.
(She gives a good hit.)
- That was hard. - His neck is gone.
His neck is gone.
(Roi Ha smiles big.)
- Good job. His neck disappeared. - I hit him too hard.
How did it happen?
- I know the answer. - Si Yang.
Si Yang is about to answer.
"Hey, your chief lives in Namcheon-dong, right?"
"I eat with your chief."
"Your chief lives in Namcheon-dong, right?"
(Jong Kook gets up.)
(He's waiting for Si Yang to get it wrong.)
"We went to a sauna together."
"We did everything together."
It's incorrect.
You punk, you deserve a hit.
(Jong Kook spits out water.)
(Si Yang got it wrong, didn't he?)
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook got his forehead slapped.
(It was a big slap.)
(Jong Kook got knocked down by Si Yang's uncontrolled swing.)
(I only did what I was told.)
(He made the wrong choice.)
(He realizes it now.)
He hit his forehead.
It hurts if you keep your cap on.
Poor Si Yang.
You did a good job.
(A loud thud)
- Oh, no. - It wasn't his full strength.
Poor Si Yang.
- It got dented. - I know the answer.
There's one more.
- "Your chief..." - It's wrong.
"He lives in Namcheon-dong, doesn't he?"
"Your chief..."
- The tone is different. - "He lives in Namcheon-dong."
It's wrong. It sounds strange.
"Your chief lives in Namcheon-dong, right?"
- It's strange. - "Your chief lives in..."
- I know the answer. - "Your chief lives in..."
- Kwang Soo. - You're terrible.
"Your chief lives in Namcheon-dong, right?"
What was wrong with it?
Can't you speak with a Busan accent? I know the answer.
Busan is my second home.
How so?
- No one knows that. - Aren't you from Suyuri?
My second home is Busan.
"Hey, your chief lives in Namcheon-dong, right?"
(Whose voice is that?)
Isn't it Shin Moon Sun?
- The answer is Shin Moon Sun. - What are you doing?
This isn't Shin Moon Sun.
"Hey, your chief lives in Namcheon-dong, right?"
- "Yes." - "We drank together yesterday."
"We went to a sauna together."
- "It's a goal." - I know the answer.
(Jae Seok fails.)
- I know the answer. - Let me hit him first.
- It's a bit... - Comedians said these lines a lot.
"Your chief lives in Namcheon-dong?"
"Your chief and I ate together yesterday."
"We went to a sauna together. We did everything."
Okay.
It was missing "yesterday".
(That was great.)
How do you know the exact lines?
- "Yesterday". - "Yesterday".
My goodness.
It's so difficult.
(It's not easy at all.)
Here's the next question. Play.
(From "The Outlaws")
[VIU Ver] SBS E414 Running Man
"The Bid"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Hey, why did you use so much toilet paper?
You don't even pay taxes.
(How will their conversation continue?)
- I know the answer. - I know.
- I know the answer. - I definitely know it.
(I know it.)
Si Yang was quicker.
(Disappointed)
This is easy.
(What will Si Yang's answer be?)
(We'll reveal the answer for the viewers.)
(Here's the answer.)
- Are you alone? - Yes, I'm still single.
Hurry up. Let's count.
"Are you here alone?"
"Yes, I'm single."
(Incorrect)
- It was very close. - That's not it?
(The expression was too different.)
What could it be?
- I know the answer. - What is it?
- What? - It's Kwang Soo's turn.
He said he knows the answer. It's his turn.
- What's the answer? - Was his first line incorrect?
- Yes. - What was the line?
"Did you come alone?"
Come on.
(He uses the incorrect accent.)
(He tries too hard to be funny.)
- Do you want to get hit? - What are you doing?
(You deserve the squeaky hammer.)
- Hold still. - Okay.
(He hits without hesitation.)
- Why isn't he saying anything? - Are you okay?
- What happened? - His head got pushed in.
(His head got pushed in.)
- What happened? - It really got pushed in.
(He pushes up his neck.)
Where's your head?
- Are you okay? - Yes.
- I'm okay. - Are you feeling better?
(They know how to deal with emergency cases.)
- I know the answer. - Is there an accent?
I definitely watch a lot of movies.
"Are you here by yourself?"
And then?
"Yes, I'm single."
That's not it.
- Answer. - Go ahead.
- I gave it to him. - "Are you here by yourself?"
"Yes, I'm still single."
- "I'm still single"? - "I'm still single."
Was this it? Why did I do that?
You must have watched many films.
Actors are different. They look for these things.
I can't even remember my own lines. This is difficult.
That's tough.
I can't remember.
Roi Ha, give it a try.
- Give me a hint. - Roi Ha, rock and roll.
(He appeals to Roi Ha's rock and roll spirit.)
"Rock and roll".
- Next question is a choreography. - Choreography?
I'll show you an image,
and you have to say the lyrics that fit the dance.
- Okay. Good. - The lyrics?
- Lyrics to the dance. Okay. - Here is...
the question.
(What dance and lyrics follow this image?)
- Answer. - "Abracadabra".
(They have to get the next two lines right.)
(I keep going crazy)
(I'm going crazy)
What was it? This is driving me nuts.
- I'm going nuts. - I know this.
I know!
(If you don't know, you shouldn't try.)
(I keep going crazy)
(I used to be nice, but I'm going crazy)
- That's not it. - This is making me crazy.
That surprised me.
- You need to get hit. - I have no idea.
This is going to be in the trailer.
It's tiring going back and forth. Don't move.
Don't move.
(It's a clean shot.)
(Pumping)
Gosh, this...
(How many times was that?)
- Gosh. - What?
How do I... Fine.
- All right. - I know!
"I used to be 'blank', but I keep going crazy like this".
That's the answer.
I know.
(He speaks in a soft voice.)
- Roi Ha. - I look forward to this.
- Roi Ha. - Go.
(Can he get the right answer...?!)
I know.
- Roi Ha. - I look forward to this.
- Roi Ha. - Go.
(He finally gets going.)
(The rock legend has been quietly waiting for the right moment.)
Good job.
(I want to be nice but)
Go again from the beginning. Set, go.
(Swaying)
(He's becoming unsure.)
(He's not too sure.)
"I want to be nice"?
(The rock star's nice exit)
I know. Okay.
(I used to be nice)
(but I keep going crazy like this)
(Will Ji Hyo's answer be correct?)
- She's right. - Because of you
(Ji Hyo is correct.)
- You're right. - "Nice".
(Here's the answer.)
(I used to be nice)
(but I keep going crazy like this)
- That was awesome. - "Nice".
- That was awesome. - This is so hard.
- I'm done. - You're so good.
- I'm not. - Gosh, this is so hard.
Next question is for the older age group.
- Good. - You'll be able to get it.
Here's the next question.
- We know this. - Na Mi and Boom Boom.
Is that not it? Is it Firetruck?
("Like an Indian Doll" by Na Mi and Boom Boom)
(It got burnt by the dark loneliness)
- Okay. - What did he say?
- "Dark loneliness". - I knew too.
- I almost had it. - What was that?
(Jae Seok takes all the old songs.)
(He know every word.)
- He's right. - Goodness.
(He gets it right again.)
I'm so mad.
(Jae Seok gets 1st place, so he wins 100 dollars and a meal ticket.)
Jae Seok won three points.
- Six of you will get meal tickets. - Okay!
(The third target will be revealed shortly.)
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for the meal.
This will take care of the summer.
(As soon as the food comes out, he starts slurping it.)
I really want the naengmyun right now.
- It's so refreshing. - There are dumplings and meat too.
(Meanwhile...)
- Is it good, Jae Seok? - It is.
(Exaggerating)
(Rockers have to be hungry.)
The noodles are so chewy.
Roi Ha really wants some.
Can I have a dumpling?
This is so good. If you show me something...
- An acrostic poem. - Do it with "king-sized dumplings".
- "King-sized dumplings"? - Yes.
- It's simple. King-sized dumplings. - That sounds good.
Roi Ha, if you do one, I'll give you something.
- An acrostic poem. I'll give you. - Start it off for him.
"King".
(King)
- Big Nose. - "Big Nose"?
(He's startled.)
"Sized".
- Do I look easy to you? - Good one.
(Do I look easy to you?)
(Oh, dear.)
Good one.
(He sounds serious.)
- So charismatic. - "Dumplings".
(His facial expression changes.)
Do you want to die?
(Do you want to die, Big Nose?)
- That works. - Nice.
- I'll give you 1 dumpling! - 1 dumpling.
Good job. Take one dumpling.
- Good job. - Here's one dumpling.
He deserves two.
We don't have that many.
(Roi Ha settles in, and they move to the final location.)
Don't we usually run here?
This feels like a race.
Welcome to the headquarters of Out Dot Com.
- Is this the headquarters? - I see.
You win today's race by being the last one remaining.
Here are the rules for Mission Impossible All Out.
(Final match: Mission Impossible All Out)
(Eliminate everybody to win.)
- "All out". - "All out".
You have to remove the name tags of the targets.
A new target is added every 15 minutes.
(The person with the least Running Money becomes a target.)
Only people who bought the right can take off the name tags.
That's right. If you eliminate somebody,
you can take their Running Money.
(Once you eliminate a target, their money becomes yours.)
Also, there are R pawnshops.
(They can recover their asset through it.)
Really?
Once you visit,
there will be opportunities to win more Running Money.
If you win this by yourself,
- it's an honor. - That's right.
The targets for round one...
are Roi Ha and Kwang Soo.
It was 70 and 90 dollars.
The target for round two...
- is Haha. - Oh, me?
(Haha is a new target after the quiz earlier.)
Haha is the target, and his bidding...
will start once you move to your designated locations.
Okay!
(Who will be the last 1 standing?)
- Okay. - Okay, it's Haha.
I'll go for it.
We have to work together.
We can't survive on our own. You have to have money.
That's what I mean. I should have saved up some money.
- Haha, you invested in me. - That's right.
- This is more valuable than money. - I earned you.
We understand each other so well.
(After the 1st mission)
(Kwang Soo suggests that Haha buys his elimination right.)
(Haha only had 100 dollars, but he uses 90 on Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo's value becomes inflated due to the bargain.)
(That's preposterous. What do they have in mind?)
(They act nonchalantly.)
You have to buy me, and I'll buy him.
This is an excellent plan.
You have to use it. If you don't, I'll eliminate you.
Why would I not try?
I know. You have to write 100 dollars though.
- Of course. - I'll be listening...
- and if it's 100 dollars, it's you. - 90 dollars.
- Because... - 90 dollars?
If somebody writes 100 dollars,
- I have to eliminate you. - Okay.
- Do you approve? - Yes.
90 dollars is you.
- Okay. - 90 or 100 dollars.
No, don't do that. Don't be vague. It's 90.
- Okay. - If it's 100, it's not you.
- Okay. - Okay?
- I bid for Roi Ha. - That's right.
(Se Chan bought Roi Ha's elimination right for 70 dollars.)
(He looks weak. I'll try.)
I have to eliminate him first.
But his eyes...
I'm scared.
(Who's after me?)
It's here. I just got it.
The target is Haha. "We will start the bidding."
"The lowest bidding price is 10 dollars."
(Message)
(The target)
(Bidding for Haha starts.)
I'll let this one go. There's no use in winning it.
Around 18 dollars.
- Can I not bid? - No.
(He's frugal.)
10 dollars.
Should I do 50 or 70?
(Hesitating)
(They're all thinking.)
We're talking.
"If you write 90 dollars,"
"let's meet on the footbridge".
(To Kwang Soo)
9, 9, 9, 9, 9.
Write down "nine".
(He sounds like a pigeon.)
(Okay, let's do this.)
(Everybody's done bidding.)
The bid has closed.
(What will Haha's bidding price be?)
Haha...
Haha was auctioned off at 90 dollars.
(Haha was auctioned off at the promised amount.)
Yes, it's 90 dollars.
(Why are things so expensive here?)
90 dollars?
The currents targets are...
Roi Ha, Kwang Soo, and Haha.
- Okay. - The race will begin in...
five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
- Start the race. - Start.
(All Out Race starts.)
(Current Rankings)
Hey, friend.
You saved 100 dollars.
Haha.
Let's give each other a hug.
(After saving each other, they meet on the footbridge.)
We have to trust each other. That's what we need right now.
Let's run. It changes in 15 minutes.
Let's look for people.
They're going around together.
Why is Kwang Soo going around with you?
- I'm the target. - And?
- Why are you... - No, no.
Carry on.
What? Carry on?
Jong Kook, I think Kwang Soo bought Haha's.
Haha bought Kwang Soo's too.
They're going to eliminate everybody else and fight at the end.
- The 2 of them? - Yes, I'm 100 percent sure.
- Each other? - Yes.
It doesn't matter if they know. You have my name tag,
and I have yours. We don't have to be afraid.
As long as we don't betray each other, this won't...
So Min, hurry.
(Meanwhile, some people are at the pawnshop.)
- Hello. - Hello.
How are the prices measured?
It's 10 dollars per cm.
- Length? Does the width not matter? - No.
Don't you have to consider the width too?
- Can I damage it? - You can't.
Give this to me.
- No, this is separate. - No, it's not.
- No, it's separate. - It's one.
- This is a set. - It's not.
I have to sell one each.
- You can't. - That's what pawnshops do.
It depends on the owner's discretion.
(Their opinions clash.)
It's one.
- I'll just measure this then. - This?
- How much is it? - 20 dollars.
- What? - 20 dollars.
- What about 4 dollars? - It's over 20 dollars.
I have no coins.
It's over 20 dollars. Is it still 20?
I'm going to sell everything.
Socks. You buy socks too, right?
- Do you buy people too? - This is 30 dollars.
- Gosh, no. - 30 dollars.
- Hold on. - There's no value.
30 dollars.
- How's this? - No.
This is a stocking now.
(Laughing)
- What now? 50 dollars. - Yes, 50 dollars.
50 dollars.
(He stretches the sock and earns 50 dollars.)
20 dollars for the shoe.
- 30 dollars. - 20 dollars.
30 dollars. Look at you. You're not flexible.
Can I... Well...
Hold on.
Can I sell underclothes too?
(Can I sell underclothes too?)
You can't.
Hey. Oh, gosh.
Who will buy it?
I think it'll be this long.
- I'm okay. - Go away.
Go away! She's insane.
That's too much. Who will buy it?
(It's hot. Please watch out for rude customers.)
As long as we don't betray each other, we'll be fine.
In 15 minutes, there will be a new target.
- He's a target. - Sorry?
He's a target. Why are you leaving him?
- Leaving who? - I...
don't know who bid for me.
- If you didn't win the bid, - Roi Ha.
- Where's Roi Ha? - do you do nothing?
Where's Roi Ha?
(Grabbing)
No, what's this?
Where's Roi Ha?
(He follows quietly and attacks.)
Why are you doing this?
What's this?
(Haha is out in a second.)
Jae Seok...
(Why did Jae Seok get him and not Kwang Soo?)
What happened?
Did he win the bid?
What do I do?
(After the bargain with Haha)
- Hello, Jae Seok. - Yes, what is it?
I'm calling to do something good for you.
- What is it? - If...
you buy Haha...
- at 90 dollars, - Okay.
I will let you know where he is.
Are you sure? If I buy him at 90 dollars,
- will you let me know where he is? - I promise.
(I don't have to do the work.)
- Okay. I got it. - All right.
Is 19 dollars okay?
(Is 19 dollars okay?)
(He handed over Haha and bet a small amount.)
(My bidding amount is 19 dollars.)
(I'll trust Kwang Soo this one time.)
Like Kwang Soo said, I'll do 90 dollars.
(Jae Seok won Haha's elimination right at 90 dollars.)
I sent it.
Hey.
(He clenches his teeth.)
Thanks.
(You're unbelievable.)
He wants to stop the long slavery.
He called and told me.
- You can talk it out. - My 100 dollars...
You were next to me.
How could you...
I wrote it.
I wrote 19 dollars.
I had no choice.
- Once you're eliminated, I'm next. - Hey.
How could you...
Haha.
Don't trust him too much.
(Kwang Soo is not credible.)
(Haha is first to be out. He goes to prison.)
It's been a while since I've gone to prison so early.
What does Jae Seok get out of this?
Just for 10 dollars?
(I only had 10 dollars.)
You have 10 more dollars now.
Is it 10 dollars?
(Haha had 10 dollars?)
- Sorry? - Do I only get 10 dollars?
Yes.
That's so little.
You have 10 more dollars,
- so you have minus 80 now. - Why?
What? You spent 90 dollars to get 10.
(Can't you do the math?)
You have minus 80.
Goodness.
This punk.
- Thank you. - You...
- I will... - No, Jae Seok.
Thank you.
Oh, gosh.
The only way to survive is to get more money.
(He doesn't have a lot of money, so he has to go there.)
I have to make more money.
The shirt...
- If you untie this... - Kwang Soo, aren't you a target?
- You're a target. - Not anymore.
- Why? - He's not a target anymore.
Haha bought him, and Haha is out.
(Haha is out, so Kwang Soo is free again.)
(What's going on?)
What is this?
- It's the pawnshop. - What do we do?
They measure whatever you have...
- and give you money. - The length.
(The longer, the better?)
(I have a 120cm-long belt.)
Kwang Soo, your belt.
You can't. Do belts work?
I don't have a belt today.
(With this belt, Kwang Soo can become a millionaire.)
(I have none.)
Belt.
(My belt is an anaconda.)
- This can't. - You can't.
This doesn't make sense.
- 100 dollars. - This?
What... What's going on?
This?
(He steals the belt.)
What... What's going on?
What is he doing? Hey!
Hold on!
(Catch that thief!)
(His pants go down.)
(Give me my belt back!)
(He runs at full speed...)
(and feels free.)
(As his speed picks up, his pants go down more.)
(Sobbing)
(At 34, he's holding onto his underwear and sprinting.)
(If he doesn't give up and keeps running,)
(his pants fall down.)
(How indecent.)
(I want to go home early.)
(Thief Jae Seok tries to sell the stolen belt.)
Excuse me.
(Please make it fast.)
- It's 100 dollars. - I'll take that.
- How much? 100 dollars? - 100 dollars?
Did you sell it?
Kwang Soo is coming.
(You have to invest like Jae Seok does.)
(He's in a hurry.)
Where's my belt?
- Did he sell it? - He did.
He sold it for 100 dollars.
- He sold it? - It's over.
- Can he buy it back? - Yes.
- For how much? - 130 dollars.
(It's 130 dollars to buy it back.)
(There's a 30-dollar margin.)
Give me my belt back.
- 30 dollars? - He doesn't have that money.
It's the market value.
He doesn't have money.
There's interest.
My stylist got the sponsorship. Give it back.
(My stylist got the sponsorship. Give it back.)
Where's Roi Ha?
(Se Chan, who bought Roi Ha, looks for him.)
Roi Ha.
Where's Roi Ha?
(Where did our rock star hide?)
(He's watching from a corner of the building.)
(Who bought me?)
He's not here. I can't find him.
(There's no time, and his target is nowhere to be seen.)
15 minutes have passed.
- What? It has? - 15 minutes have passed.
- A new target is Yang Se Chan. - Me?
(Am I the new target?)
(Out Dot Com Auction House becomes busy once more.)
Se Chan?
Place your bid.
It's impossible to remove Se Chan's name tag.
Se Chan?
As for Se Chan... Hold on.
How much did you bid on me?
(He sounds her out.)
Me? I bid 10 dollars.
I only have a small sum of money.
- What? - I only have a small sum of money.
I bid 10 dollars.
You won't make the winning bid with 10 dollars.
I only have 10 dollars.
Why are you following me?
I bid 10 dollars.
For goodness' sake.
(She latches onto Se Chan before the bid closes.)
- Wait for me. - Why are you following me?
I think it will be fun to stay with you.
You want to rip my name tag off after the bid closes, right?
I think I will win. I think I am stronger than you.
You underestimated me. Okay.
That's why you want to follow me around.
I am clingy.
I see.
The bid has closed.
Yang Se Chan was sold for 32 dollars.
- Really? - 32 dollars?
Really?
32 dollars?
Hold on.
(I think she made the winning bid.)
This is hilarious.
Hyo Rim, please!
(Se Chan, wait for me.)
Hyo Rim!
(Se Chan uses his strong thighs to outrun Hyo Rim.)
He is really fast.
(It looks like I lost Se Chan.)
I am exhausted.
(I am glad I gave her the slip.)
What?
- Gosh, you startled me. - You startled me.
You startled me, Si Yang.
(He runs into Si Yang who was wandering aimlessly.)
Se Chan.
My goodness.
Where is the pawnshop?
- You need to find it. - Really?
(It's strange because he was at the pawnshop.)
- Who? - So Min.
What is going on?
(He rips Se Chan's name tag.)
(Si Yang rips Se Chan's name tag. What is going on?)
(The person who won the bid with 32 dollars is...)
(Si Yang.)
(That's enough for Se Chan.)
(Okay. It looks like I won the bid.)
(Let's go and get Se Chan.)
Why are you limping?
(He meets Hyo Rim after she loses Se Chan.)
- I was chasing after Se Chan. - Se Chan? Where is he?
- I lost him. - Where is he?
He went to the annex.
(After he gains information, he starts the chase.)
(It's hard to understand why Hyo Rim ran.)
What was that?
(Give me your belongings.)
What is going on?
(Let me sell your things since you're out.)
Why are you taking those? Hold on.
Why are you taking those?
(Isn't Hyo Rim the highest bidder?)
What?
What is going on? Am I out?
What is this?
Aren't you going to tell me anything?
(Since Se Chan is out, Roi Ha is no longer a target.)
Here is Se Chan's name tag.
(Si Yang, the robber, heads straight to the pawnshop.)
30, 30, and 20cm. 80 dollars.
(He acquires 80 dollars.)
80 dollars. Thank you.
Sit down, 32 Dollars.
(Meanwhile, Haha and Se Chan are in prison.)
You were sold at 32 dollars, right?
- Was it 33 dollars? - 32 dollars.
Go and sit over there.
- How much was the winning bid? - 90 dollars.
Sir, I'll sit over there.
For me, the winning bid was 32 dollars.
Come over here.
Eat some sweets.
Jae Seok had no reason to place a bid on me.
What do you mean?
Are you still upset your name tag got ripped?
He had no reason. Would you spend 90 dollars for 10 dollars?
What a weasel.
- That's funny. - He did it for fun.
He did it for 10 dollars.
He must live a boring life at home.
(Meanwhile, the man who leads a boring life at home...)
Hold on. What is this?
What's "Make a call"?
(Make a call.)
(When Haha got eliminated,)
(Jae Seok found a message card on his back.)
(I should hide it and look at it by myself.)
(What is the message card that reads "Make a call"...)
(that was attached to Haha's name tag?)
I can't believe this happened.
(He calls the headquarters of Out Dot Com.)
Out Dot Com Race has an architect and an assistant.
Excuse me?
(An architect and an assistant are among us?)
(An architect and an assistant)
An assistant?
(Si Yang acquires the same piece of information.)
The architect knows how much money...
every member has or bid.
If you find the architect and rip off their name tag,
you win immediately.
(If you eliminate the architect, you win.)
Architect?
(You don't have to eliminate everyone to win.)
The architect has a brother.
(Those who eliminated others received a hint.)
(Hyo Rim, So Min, Roi Ha, Seok Jin,)
(Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo all have a brother.)
Okay.
The architect is in their 30s.
(Si Yang receives a different hint.)
(Among them, those who are in their 30s are...)
(Hyo Rim, So Min, and Ji Hyo.)
(So I win if I eliminate the architect.)
What is going on? Who is the architect?
(What is going on?)
(The architect and the assistant know everything about us.)
For goodness' sake.
(Who could they be?)
(Current Rankings)
(Hyo Rim, Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, Jong Kook, So Min, Seok Jin,)
(Si Yang, Kwang Soo, and Roi Ha)
The new targets have been chosen.
The new targets are Kim Roi Ha,
Lee Kwang Soo, and Kwak Si Yang.
We will start the bidding.
Hold on.
We need to bid on all targets, right?
From now on, I won't aim for all the targets.
(Jae Seok has his eyes on the architect.)
(He bids 40 dollars on Roi Ha, a man who has a brother.)
I bid 62 dollars on Kwang Soo.
62 dollars.
I bid 51 dollars on Si Yang.
I bid 51 dollars on Roi Ha.
(She bids a specific sum of money.)
The bid has closed.
Kim Roi Ha is sold for 51 dollars.
(So Min wins the bid for Roi Ha with 51 dollars.)
Kwak Si Yang is sold for 51 dollars.
(So Min wins the bid for Si Yang with 51 dollars as well.)
I will look for Roi Ha.
I will rip off his name tag.
Lee Kwang Soo is sold for 62 dollars.
I won the bid for Kwang Soo.
(He doesn't know what to do.)
I need to be hidden.
I need to hide for 15 minutes.
(The other targets avoid the mysterious bidders as well.)
For goodness' sake.
I need to find the architect.
Jae Seok.
Okay.
Did you win the bid?
- What? - Did you win the bid?
- Help me. - Why?
I won the bid, but I don't think I will be able to rip his name tag.
- Whose name tag? - Kwang Soo's.
(His stamina doesn't match his passion.)
- It will be hard. - I know it will be hard.
It will be hard to eliminate him.
Look at my shoes.
- I need to buy my shoes back. - Give me 10 dollars if I help you.
Of course.
- 10 dollars from Kwang Soo? - Okay.
- I will give you 10 dollars. - Let's split the profit by 6 to 4.
- That leaves me with nothing. - You can take 60 percent.
I will take 40 percent.
- How much does he have? - 6 to 4.
- How about 7 to 3? - Then I refuse to help.
(Come on.)
7 to 3.
I need to get something out of this.
- Okay. 6 to 4. - 6 to 4.
How much does he have?
- How much does he have? - He has a lot of money.
- Let's take the stairs. - Okay.
(The allied, middle-aged men begin the search.)
(Si Yang is running stealthily.)
Gosh, you startled me.
(I hear you are a target.)
(The tiger in front of the elevator startles him.)
Where are you going?
Me? I am going to the pawnshop.
- You were sold at 51 dollars. - Yes.
I was sold at 51 dollars.
51 Dollars, shall we ride together? Are you going to the pawnshop?
- What? - Let's go together.
My goodness.
- Si Yang. - Yes?
So you were sold at 51 dollars.
I am cheap like that.
Gosh, why is everyone here?
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo make a scary elevator ride.)
Did someone call me?
- Excuse me. - Where are you going?
Excuse me.
- Are you going to come in? - What?
No.
(While the fake highest bidders trap Si Yang,)
(the real highest bidder, So Min, appears.)
What is wrong with you?
(He runs away.)
It's Si Yang.
(Wait right there, 51 Dollars.)
So Min should have said something.
- Why? - Then we would have held him.
(Wait right there.)
(Save me.)
This is exhausting.
(How is he so fast?)
Which way should I go?
(I lost her, right?)
So Min.
Did you win the bid for Roi Ha?
- It seems that way. - He is in the basement.
(Whispering)
- Hurry. - Thank you, Jong Kook.
Let's go.
(Let's go to the basement.)
Roi Ha.
(She finds Roi Ha.)
What are you doing?
- It's not me. - Why are you carrying this?
I am going to sell it.
- You are going to sell it? - Yes.
You are sweating a lot.
Really? It must be because my blood sugar level is low.
- Did you go to the pawnshop? - What?
I did,
but I am still at the bottom.
- I will give this to you. - I'm still poor.
I will give this to you. Sell it.
(She gives him a squeaky hammer to lure him to the pawnshop.)
Thank you.
- Can I sell this? - You never know.
Take it to the pawnshop.
It's so hot.
It's so hot. Roi Ha, try selling it.
(The queen of fraud leaves.)
(It's a strategy to make Roi Ha go to the pawnshop.)
What should I do?
I need to be behind him.
I should go.
(Let me go to the pawnshop to sell this.)
- I should sell a lot. - This isn't easy.
It's so hot.
I should go this way.
(So Min approaches Roi Ha pretending to go somewhere else.)
(She moves in on him.)
(Grabbing)
(Ripping off)
Roi Ha, I'm sorry. He didn't even move.
- He didn't even move. - My gosh.
So Min must've gotten very rich.
Was this a bait for me?
Did I fall for that?
Did you fall for it? Did she fool you?
You didn't get up. That's why I gave this to you.
- My gosh. - It'd be a month later.
If he decides to hide,
- We can't find him in 15 minutes. - it'd be hard.
(Where did you hide, Kwang Soo?)
A new target has been chosen.
The new target is Jee Seok Jin.
(15 minutes have passed.)
We will start the bidding.
(I'm the target now? This is bad.)
(He tries to make a bid for 80 dollars.)
I spent 80 dollars on Seok Jin.
- He's less than 100 dollars. - That's right.
- Seok Jin... - The bid has closed.
Jee Seok Jin is sold for 80 dollars...
- Really? - exclusively.
- What's happening? - That's really expensive.
You'd lose money if you pay 80 dollars for him.
- Right. - You'd just waste your energy.
Jee Seok Jin is sold for 80 dollars to an exclusive bidder.
(Okay! I won the bid for the weakest!)
(Starting now, Kwang Soo and Seok Jin will target each other.)
I won the bid exclusively, right? Okay, I can go out now.
I just need to remove his name tag.
(At times like this, this person pops into his mind first.)
- Hello. - Jae Seok.
Did you make a bid for 80 dollars?
I sent you a text message.
(What is this con artist scheming?)
I read it. Why did you call me?
If you help me eliminate Seok Jin,
I'll give you half on the spot right away.
(He's tempted.)
- Are you serious? - I'll give it to you right away.
- I'm at the rooftop... - Okay.
of the building across from where we received the mission earlier.
- I got it. - Okay, see you, Jae Seok.
(He'll get half.)
(As soon as he hangs up...)
He'll find a way.
- Seok Jin, where are you? - Jae Seok.
Who won the bid? Is that you?
(This trickster is busily making calls.)
You didn't win the bid, right?
- I'll be honest. - Okay.
Kwang Soo made the winning bid.
Kwang Soo said if I helped him eliminate you,
he'd give me half of it.
(What will you offer?)
Hey, if you eliminate Kwang Soo for me...
- Okay. - If you do that...
(Gosh, he will go 5 to 5 with you?)
It's 6 to 4. You'll take the larger amount.
(It's 6 to 4. You'll take the larger amount.)
I'll take the larger amount?
(He started with 4, but ends up with 6.)
You'll take 60 percent. I'll take 40, and you'll take 60.
Are you sure?
Yes. You take 60 percent.
7 to 3.
(Let's negotiate more since we're at it.)
(Gosh, don't you think that's too cruel?)
Seok Jin, it's a life-or-death situation for you.
- I can just go to Kwang Soo. - Okay, fine. Darn it.
- I accept. You take 70 percent. - Okay.
- You take 70 percent. I got it. - Okay, okay.
- Okay. - I'll head over there.
(He's indeed the master of negotiation.)
Okay. This is the only way.
(Clueless of this, he waits for Jae Seok.)
This is my last hope.
- Did you negotiate with Kwang Soo? - Gosh.
- What? I get to take 70 percent. - He didn't offer you 80, right?
- I'd never, Seok Jin. - Okay.
A new target has been chosen.
(15 minutes has passed during negotiations.)
The new target is Yu Jae Seok.
Who?
- Jae Seok. Hey, Jae Seok. - Hold on.
This can't be happening.
- I'll protect you. What? - Someone made a bid.
He made a bid for 130 dollars.
- Who? - Kwang Soo.
130 dollars?
(Kwang Soo was sending the bid to the headquarters.)
I sent this to Jae Seok. I made a mistake of sending it to him.
(He sent Jae Seok the text which was meant for the headquarters.)
Kwang Soo made a bid for 130 dollars.
- What a traitor. - Let's go catch him.
- Let's get him. I can't waste time. - Let's go. Let's not waste time.
(How dare you? We're on our way to get you!)
(I'm doomed. Jae Seok knows where I am.)
Is this it? I see. He must be hiding here.
- This is the place. - It's here. He's behind the door.
Kwang Soo.
- Hey. - Did you buy me or not?
- You? - You didn't, right?
I don't have money.
Hey, you. Why did you send me the text with the bidding price?
Did you make the bid to me?
Did you send it to me instead of to the headquarters by accident?
- What happened was... - Is that it?
(Let's just pounce on my target, Seok Jin.)
Wait.
(I don't know anymore. Give me your name tag!)
Get the name tag now.
(Jae Seok holds Kwang Soo, and Seok Jin tries to remove it.)
(Ripping off)
(By a close call, Seok Jin arrests the con artist, Kwang Soo.)
I got it.
I got it first.
(Both of them are exhausted.)
- Seok Jin was slightly faster. - I was slightly faster.
- Was he faster? - Yes.
(This is all because of that mistake of mine.)
Hey, you. Do you think you can call yourself a human being?
How dare you buy me for 130 dollars?
- Seriously? Hey. - Listen, Jae Seok.
Hey, what is this? "Make a call."
- What? - What is this?
(Seok Jin finds a phone call hint about the architect.)
Hey, we have to make a call. Kwang Soo.
This race isn't everything today.
(Seok Jin finds a phone call hint about the architect.)
There's an architect.
(Seok Jin is listening to the hint about the architect.)
(So Min, Ji Hyo, and Hyo Rim are the possible candidates.)
- The architect's name is real. - Thank you.
(The architect uses her real name? That means...)
(the architect is either So Min or Hyo Rim.)
What's that noise?
A new target has been chosen.
The new target is...
Jee Seok Jin.
(It's me again?)
(Seok Jin is a regular target of the members.)
Listen. Are you doing this on purpose?
- Why is it always me? - Why does it keep happening to him?
(Current Rankings)
(So Min, Hyo Rim, Ji Hyo, Jong Kook,)
(Seok Jin, Jae Seok, and Si Yang.)
The bid has closed.
Jee Seok Jin is sold for 200 dollars exclusively.
(That's the highest bid.)
200 dollars? Jong Kook, did you make the bid?
- No. - Jong Kook. 200 dollars?
No, I didn't. Here's what I think.
It's So Min.
(Did So Min, who's in first place, win the bid with 200 dollars?)
Should I hide in here?
(Seok Jin, the target, is on the run for now.)
(He rushes into the wardrobe department, a perfect hiding spot.)
Come in.
Seok Jin. It's So Min. I think it's So Min.
- Hey. - So Min... She made...
- the bids for you and Jae Seok. - Exactly.
(Is So Min really the winning bidder for Seok Jin?)
- Really? - I saw her bidding.
So Min...
(Grabbing)
I got it!
(Hyo Rim eliminates Seok Jin. What on earth happened here?)
Nice! Nice!
(A while ago, making a bid for Seok Jin)
(Hyo Rim made a bid on Seok Jin for 200 dollars, a high price.)
(She approached Seok Jin, hiding the fact that she won the bid.)
I'm sorry.
(Her plan was a big success. Thank you, Seok Jin.)
(She fooled everyone. Is Suspicious Hyo Rim the architect?)
(Meanwhile, So Min is another possible architect.)
Where is Jae Seok? Did you see Jae Seok?
(Why is she looking for Jae Seok?)
(When it was time to bid for Jae Seok...)
(What should I do with Jae Seok?)
(So Min won the bid on Jae Seok with 156 dollars.)
(I won the bid. Okay, should I go find Jae Seok?)
(So Min was the winning bidder by a close call.)
He's so weak.
I'm so excited. My acting was perfect.
(Which one is the architect?)
A new target has been chosen.
The new target is Seo Hyo Rim.
(Who will win the bid on Hyo Rim who is possibly an architect?)
We will start the bidding.
(Who will win the bid on Hyo Rim, who is possibly an architect?)
(Ji Hyo goes all-in with a bid of 440 dollars.)
The bid has closed.
Seo Hyo Rim is sold for 440 dollars...
- to an exclusive bidder. - Let's go.
I spent 200 dollars on Seok Jin for no reason.
I should've spent 150 dollars.
(Here's comes the winning bidder. Wait for me, Hyo Rim.)
(She's being pursued by Ji Hyo. What will happen to her?)
(Here you are, Hyo Rim.)
You're here.
- Wait. - Hyo Rim.
(If Hyo Rim is the architect and Ji Hyo eliminates her, Ji Hyo wins.)
- Come here. - Ji Hyo.
(Come here, Hyo Rim.)
(She easily gets ahold of Hyo Rim.)
- I have no choice. - No!
No!
(She slowly rips off the name tag.)
(If she's the architect, there must be a mark for the architect.)
(Ripping off)
(She removes her name tag.)
(What's Hyo Rim's identity?)
I'm really sorry.
- Well done. - We should check the hint.
(Hyo Rim isn't the architect.)
(Then the real architect is...)
(Jeon So Min.)
Hello. Hi.
(The architect of the website, Out Dot Com)
Just like the name, Out Dot Com is a website.
Whoever ends up on the site must be eliminated,
and if you're the last, surviving member, you will win the race.
So Min, you're the architect of this website.
- I'm the architect? - Yes.
You must eliminate everyone and become the last one standing.
(This is the architect's mission.)
Wait, but...
(The day has finally come! She's elated.)
50 dollars on Si Yang.
51 dollars on Si Yang.
(As the architect's privilege, she knew everyone's bids.)
50 dollars on Roi Ha.
(She could win the bid by a close call based on the info.)
51 dollars on Roi Ha as well.
(Thanks to her privilege, she could eliminate other members.)
(The architect of the website, Jeon So Min)
A new target has been chosen.
The new target is...
- Kim Jong Kook. - What?
We will start the bidding.
(Jong Kook is the target?)
The new target is Kim Jong Kook.
(Has he become a target too? This capable man is in a crisis.)
I have to get him.
(Here's a lady who is gunning for Jong Kook.)
(She goes all-in with 440 dollars.)
("Ji Hyo spent 440 dollars on him." The architect checks the bid.)
(How much will So Min spend on him?)
The bid has closed.
Kim Jong Kook is sold for...
44...
445 dollars.
Kim Jong Kook is sold for 445 dollars to an exclusive bidder.
Who outbid me by five bucks?
What?
How could they have so much money?
(That's me! I'm the architect.)
(At that time, the target, Jong Kook, shows up.)
Did you get it? Did you win the bid?
I'm happy. I really am,
but I've never eliminated someone.
That's why we have invited...
a strong assistant who will help you today.
(A strong assistant that will help me remove the name tags?)
- Is it a guy? - We'll bring the assistant in.
(Is Jong Kook her assistant that will help So Min, the architect?)
(Right. From earlier...)
(He provided useful information when Roi Ha was the target.)
(Jong Kook helped So Min when she was pursuing Si Yang.)
I have to get him.
(And a while ago, when it was time to bid on Jong Kook,)
(So Min outbid Ji Hyo with 445 dollars.)
(Is this So Min's strategy to protect him, the assistant?)
(Then does it mean Jong Kook has really been So Min's assistant?)
Follow me.
- Why? - Follow me.
Follow me. Run.
- You're going to catch me. - You're going crazy, right?
You think you can catch me, right?
- I'm right in front of you. - This is so upsetting.
(Kwak Si Yang)
(Si Yang launches an attack all of a sudden.)
- Hurry. Hurry, So Min. - What? This guy was alive?
- Hurry, So Min. - Hey.
(He shows up like a comet and attacks Jong Kook.)
Gosh, my arm.
(With Si Yang's crucial help, Jong Kook is out.)
(Jong Kook wasn't the assistant.)
(Then it means the real assistant was...)
(So Min's reliable assistant,)
(Kwak Si Yang)
Hello.
Hello, Si Yang.
(So Min's reliable assistant, Kwak Si Yang)
(In the beginning of the race when he was bidding on Se Chan,)
(he asked So Min about other members' bids.)
(After sharing Ji Hyo's bid on Se Chan with Si Yang,)
(the assistant won the bid on Se Chan by a close call.)
(That's how Si Yang could easily eliminate Se Chan.)
The new target is Kwak Si Yang.
(When he was chosen as the target...)
(So Min, make sure no one wins the bid on me.)
So Min, So Min, So Min.
(Trust me.)
51 dollars on Si Yang.
(After checking Jong Kook's bid on him for 50 dollars,)
(So Min protected him with a bid of 51 dollars.)
(She pretended to have come to eliminate Si Yang.)
(But in reality, So Min helped him get away from Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
Gosh, I made a bid for 50 dollars on him.
- She made a bid for 51 dollars. - Jong Kook.
(Good luck, my assistant. Run far away from here.)
- You didn't eliminate him, right? - Pardon?
You didn't eliminate him, right?
- No, I did. - You did?
- I did. - Go downstairs. To the basement.
- You must go right to go down. - Let's go.
So Min is going to be a rich lady.
(Everyone thought Si Yang was eliminated.)
Si Yang is out now.
Si Yang was being chased earlier.
(Jong Kook who lowered his guard...)
(was eliminated by Si Yang's unexpected ambush.)
(Make a call.)
Jong Kook has superpowers, right?
(The architect and assistant's teamwork stood out in this battle.)
Song Ji Hyo is sold for 20 dollars to an exclusive bidder.
Are you the assistant?
- Stop acting, Jae Seok. - I'm not.
- We found out everything. - Hey.
You're the assistant.
- What are you talking about? - You're the assistant.
Hey, aren't you the assistant?
- You made a bid on me for 60. - Yes.
- That proves you're the assistant. - Forget it.
- No, no. Listen. - Let go.
- No, you listen. - Listen.
- You're the assistant. I'm not it. - I'm... Listen to me.
So Min, you, and I are remaining.
- It's not me. - You're the assistant.
- So it's you. - Listen up, Jae Seok.
(Clueless of Si Yang, Jae Seok thinks Ji Hyo is the assistant.)
If you do this... Fine, go ahead.
"Make a call." I knew it.
What? Hold on.
(There's no mark for the assistant. What happened?)
Gosh.
So Min is coming.
Say hello to her.
- You eliminated her? - You two are a team.
Jae Seok, I'm not the assistant.
- You're not? - No, I'm not.
A new target has been chosen.
- Okay, okay. Watch this. - It's you and So Min.
I'm going to go all-in, Ji Hyo.
- I'm going all-in. - Jae Seok, you're the assistant.
- You're not? - No, I'm not.
If I win the bid, I can eliminate her.
(If he eliminates her, he will win.)
Gosh, she fooled us the whole day. So Min, stop right there.
So Min.
(So Min, stop right there! Jae Seok wins the bid.)
(So Min runs at full speed as well.)
No. No.
(Jae Seok will win if he eliminates the architect.)
So Min!
(Bolting)
(What is this? Things must be urgent.)
- Ji Hyo, I'll rip it off right now. - Jae Seok, hurry.
(Jae Seok is chasing after So Min.)
No, no.
(He's only a few steps away.)
Wait, wait. Hold on a second.
(At times like this, she needs...)
(her assistant, Si Yang.)
(So Min! Where are you?)
What? Why is he here?
(Wasn't he eliminated?)
(I thought he was out.)
(I get it now. He was the assistant.)
- You're the architect. - I can...
- eliminate you too. Hear me out. - Wait.
- Let's stop now. - Hear me out.
(They're face to face with a pillar in the middle.)
- Let's stop this now. - I can also...
(It's a critical moment to eliminate or to be eliminated.)
Listen to me.
(Si Yang shows up.)
- What's this? - Hello.
(Si Yang holds Jae Seok down.)
Let go of me. Hey!
(So Min eliminates Jae Seok right away.)
What was that?
(He's flustered. "Who is on my back?")
Weren't you out?
Good job.
You thought I was out.
(I was completely fooled by the assistant whom I wasn't aware of.)
Good job. You did so well.
- Gosh, I did it. - You showed up at the right time.
(The architect and the assistant win with their perfect teamwork.)
The hidden architect of the Friendly Neighbors,
Out Dot Com Race was So Min.
And the assistant was Si Yang.
- I didn't know there was one. - Well done.
We lost.
I had no idea about the assistant.
- I thought he was out. - You didn't know.
You two will receive today's winning prizes,
- the coffee truck voucher. - Gosh.
- We'll send trucks to your shoot. - This is awesome.
(We'll send the trucks under your names.)
- This is nice. - That's a great prize.
- That's pretty good. - This is awesome.
That's a meaningful prize.
- Roi Ha, share a word with us. - Roi Ha.
Good job today.
Thank you for inviting me today.
Thanks to you, I made great memories. Thank you.
Rock and roll!
(Thank you!)
The victory of today's race goes to So Min and Si Yang.
(We'd like to thank today's guests, Roi Ha, Hyo Rim, and Si Yang...)
(for running with us on a very hot day.)