(Last week)
(Seoul, Gangwon Province, and Hong Kong)
(Team So Min has been locked up in the Noodles of Underworld.)
(No matter how much they wanted to escape it,)
(people keep on recommending them noodles.)
(They failed the first mission to get a steak recommended and eat it.)
(Seoul, Gangwon Province)
(Meanwhile, Team Ji Hyo's mission was to cook a meal for 100 people.)
(They cooked furiously with the perfect teamwork.)
(They served the food furiously too.)
(Team Ji Hyo completed their 1st mission by serving 100 people.)
(Meanwhile, Team Si Young's mission was to gather 4L of sheep milk.)
(They were in a crisis as the sheep didn't behave as they wanted.)
(After endless attempts to win them over, they milked 4L.)
(After many complications, they completed the first mission.)
How many jobs have we done?
We'll be fishing now, right?
(These people get on the car with a heavy heart.)
- My gosh. Hello. - Hi.
(Team Si Young must catch sailfin sandfish which they didn't eat...)
(and complete a mysterious mission.)
Will it take about an hour?
(They set out to the dock in Sokcho to fish.)
No, no.
Si Young, I was really born again today.
(Commenting out of the blue)
I'm serious. I really was.
(He suddenly makes a confession.)
- I mean, I... - Earlier...
Team Leader Si Young, I really tried my best there.
(How does he have the ballots?)
Haha, I was...
(A few hours ago, he had none. How does he have these ballots?)
(Give them back, you brat.)
Where did you get these?
(She suddenly investigates him.)
(As a team leader, she seizes the ballot.)
My gosh, I got goosebumps.
- Where did you get them? - You're so scary.
- Tell me where you got it. - Hold on.
(She furiously interrogates him.)
- Si Young. - Let go of me.
Don't do this. Don't.
- Where... Listen. - That's Se Chan's.
Why? Why? How did you get this?
It's Se Chan's.
But why do you have it?
Did you steal again?
(I thought you were born again.)
Right now,
we finished filming.
Se Chan and I are rooming together.
Se Chan went inside to take a shower.
(The sound of Se Chan's showering fills the silent room.)
(Kwang Soo takes this chance and opens up Se Chan's bag.)
(He takes something out from Se Chan's bag.)
(Are those the ballots?)
(Forget about being reborn again. He stole all of his 4 ballots.)
(I'm sorry, Se Chan. I left you one. I'm being considerate.)
- Even until the end. - I wrote a letter.
Good job.
Well done.
It's the same as taking my money if you take the ballots.
I will hold onto these for now.
Hold on. Don't you think this is strange?
- I just wanted to join the game. - She's just holding onto them.
I will hold onto these.
I'm just keeping them for you. Understood? Okay?
What's going on? What is this?
A long time ago, I saw this in a drama, "Boss".
When two guys pickpocketed people,
the boss took it away just like now.
I will make this decision as a team leader.
- Is that okay with you? - I wanted to see your charisma.
By the way, what you just did was so cool.
You forced my hands to steal someone else's.
Was I like this from the start?
I trusted everyone at first.
I didn't know that you would betray us,
but you betrayed us once before and stole Se Chan's ballots.
Nonetheless, this is helping our team,
so I will forgive you. Under one condition.
I will hold onto these ballots.
- Let's not fight among ourselves. - Right.
Exactly. If we keep fighting, we'll ruin everything.
(Siding with the team leader)
Like sheep...
- We, who spare nothing to give, - We, who spare nothing to give,
- Are the best. - are the best.
All right. Let's go.
We've arrived.
- Si Young. - We arrived at a perfect timing.
When you snatched the ballots, you were really cool.
We're here to catch sailfin sandfish.
(As they can't believe it, their feigned laughter bursts out.)
Let me sum up what your mission is today.
(Their mission was to catch the fish they didn't eat at the restaurant.)
(Luckily, they chose the sailfin sandfish...)
(which are relatively easy to catch as they're in season now.)
In the midst of our trouble...
If you catch the sailfin sandfish and complete the mysterious mission,
you will have completed the second mission.
We have an extra mission.
We'll tell you what the mission is after you come back.
What could it be?
It will be advantageous to remember everything...
that takes place on the boat.
(Is the mission related to what happens while we fish?)
(They set out to try the mission while feeling worried.)
My gosh, what could the additional mission be?
I can catch fish with the fishing rod.
(They set out to catch sailfin sandfish!)
(They must catch the fish and complete a mysterious mission.)
(Will Team Si Young be able to successfully complete the mission?)
Everyone, sit down.
(Acting like an expert)
(What's up with this guy?)
What are you doing?
He's a fisherman.
I'm sure you people from Seoul might not know a lot of things.
- Well, I've never seen... - Okay.
a fisherman put on the patch to prevent seasickness.
(A fisherman is wearing a patch that prevents seasickness?)
This is a mole.
(Fishermen have these moles.)
- That's a mole? - Yes.
(You, city people don't know it.)
(A suspicious fisherman with the patch-looking mole)
It prevents seasickness.
How long have you been working on the boat?
My family has been in this trade for four generations.
(He's in a family of fishermen that goes way back.)
(Although I get seasick, I am a fisherman.)
(Touching)
Hey, don't touch it.
(Giving him a warning sternly)
(My gosh, what's wrong with this guy?)
(Blowing his whistle)
(Where did he get the whistle?)
We're getting things ready.
You can just help us when we ask for your help.
- Have you done net fishing? - Just take a seat for now.
Four generations of my family have done it.
(I told you I'm in a family of fishermen.)
As for the sailfin sandfish you eat,
you should just think that they all come from our boat.
Okay.
(Waving his arm around)
(What is he doing now?)
Do you... Do you know the boat?
- That's my aunt's. - Your aunt's?
I'm letting her pass first.
You let her go first?
(He's the 4th generation of fisherman.)
Stop.
This is the spot.
Did you give them the stopping signal?
I think the engine was turned off before...
- your signal. - No, no. That's not true.
- Is he always like that? - He's a weirdo.
They're reeling it up right away.
- We spread out the nets before. - Right, right.
I hope we go back with a full load of fish.
(They are about to start.)
The current is strong today.
It's hard to catch fish today.
(It's hard to catch the fish due to the strong current.)
(It's hard to even balance themselves on the boat.)
(Frowning)
I think I'm getting nauseous.
(This 4th generation of fishermen shows signs of seasickness.)
- Sir, are you getting seasick? - No, no.
No, no. I have a headache.
I didn't know you had a headache.
Open your eyes, and gaze afar.
(She finds him pathetic.)
(Hey, fisherman. Gaze afar.)
(I thought you were the 4th generation of fishermen.)
My gosh, it's getting salty in my mouth.
(When this fisherman is struggling with seasickness...)
I see the net now.
He's reeling up the net now.
We started now.
(The moment they catch sailfin sandfish, their mission is over.)
(Everyone pulls up the net with a hope of sailfin sandfish.)
(However, they are only reeling up the empty net unlike their hope.)
(I don't see any of the sailfin sandfish.)
- This is it for today, right? - Right.
It's because of the water. The waves are too rapid.
Are there times when you go back empty-handed?
Of course.
On other days, we catch a lot.
They sometimes don't catch anything like today.
Really?
Why does it have to be today?
(The sailfin sandfish has vanished because of the strong waves.)
(If they don't catch any of them, they will fail their mission.)
(Team Si Young is exhausted as they only reel up the empty net.)
Captain, look.
- There's a fish. - Hey, there it is.
(At that moment,)
(something is caught in the net.)
I'm beginning to see the fish.
(If the fish caught in the net is a sailfin sandfish,)
(it will mean they have completed the mission.)
(If it's not, they must wait not knowing for how long.)
(Will it be a sailfin sandfish just like everyone's wish?)
Isn't this a sailfin sandfish?
- Isn't this a sailfin sandfish? - Yes, it is.
(According to the captain, it is a sailfin sandfish!)
We have a sailfin sandfish!
We got the sailfin sandfish as soon as we started.
- We have the sailfin sandfish! - Get that.
Everyone, this is really happening!
- Sir... There are more coming. - That's it.
We are just getting started.
This is the second sailfin sandfish.
Gosh, there's a flood of them now.
There are so many of them.
Gosh, they are all over the net.
I'm so relieved that there are a lot.
(A pile of sailfin sandfish)
It's all sailfin sandfish.
(They complete the mission of catching the sailfin sandfish.)
If we chose another fish, we wouldn't have accomplished it.
(However,)
(the staff said they must complete one extra mission.)
(It's not over yet.)
Everyone, let us explain about the sailfin sandfish.
Okay.
The sailfin sandfish resemble a lot of other fish.
Listen up. This must be the mission. It's the second mission.
Pay attention.
(Let us explain about the sailfin sandfish.)
(The sailfin sandfish resemble a lot of other fish.)
(They look similar to sweetfish and sand lance.)
(During the Japanese Invasion, the king was evacuating...)
(and had a fish named sandfish. After he came back,)
(he had a sweetfish, but he called it a sandfish.)
(There's a sailfin sandfish festival in Cheongho-dong every November.)
(Anyway...)
So this is the mission, right?
(The net doesn't seem to end.)
This isn't a penalty, right? It is a mission, right?
(There are so many fish.)
But we won't have a chance to do this ever again.
- Seriously. - Right.
- It's rewarding though. - Yes, it sure is rewarding.
(One side of the boat is filled up with the sailfin sandfish.)
We're done!
- The boat is full! - My gosh!
- The boat is full. - Gosh.
(They return to the land with a full load of sailfin sandfish.)
Well done.
- Good work. - Good work.
If you complete the mission we explained earlier,
- you will have finished all of it. - Okay.
Bring in the food now.
- We'll really eat this? - What's this?
(The additional mission is finally presented.)
The sailfin sandfish you caught earlier...
are on one of the plates.
- Isn't this too easy? - These are the sailfin sandfish.
- These are sailfin sandfish. - Right.
- It's the ones on a blue plate. - We know that.
What's the name of these fish that look just like sailfin sandfish?
They are sand lance.
- It was that or sweetfish, - Sweetfish.
But you said that sweetfish and sailfin sandfish are different.
Those are not sweetfish.
You said they were different.
(The captain gets involved all of a sudden.)
Those are sand eels.
- These are sand eels? - We have the answer.
Sand eels and sand lances are the same things.
(He kindly confirms it.)
(Nice assist)
(The captain even tells them the answer.)
- It's sandlance. - It's sandlance.
- Right? - Sandlance.
He said, "sandlance", and left.
I told you.
1, 2, 3.
- Sandlance. - Sandlance.
(The answer is "sandlance".)
(Did the captain tell them the correct answer?)
(Or will there be a twist?)
It's correct.
(The name of the fish is "sandlance".)
(They got the question right.)
It ended beautifully.
If we had said the wrong answer, we would have failed.
We would have failed.
- We did a great job. - Right?
(While Team Si Young is celebrating their victory,)
(Team Hong Kong wakes up, worried about their mission.)
- Let me announce a new mission. - What is it?
We have to meet Chow Yun Fat?
(Earlier this morning, the staff barged into Seok Jin's room.)
(Half-asleep, Seok Jin answered, "Chow Yun Fat".)
(Now their second mission is "Taking a picture with Chow Yun Fat".)
How can we meet Chow Yun Fat?
How can we take a picture with him?
- He's a huge star. - Exactly.
But you're lucky.
(It's not impossible.)
Chow Yun Fat is seen at various places in Hong Kong.
- He uses public transportation. - No way.
I've read the articles.
I've seen it on the internet.
Still, it'd be hard to find him.
Many Korean tourists have taken pictures with him...
at restaurants and cafes or on the street.
Really?
It's all over social media.
- Guys. - I don't want to say this, but...
There is a noodle place frequented by Chow Yun Fat.
(A noodle place frequented by Chow Yun Fat?)
Let's go there.
(Excited)
- But... - This is not okay.
- It's noodles again. - This is not okay.
I didn't realize, but it's noodles.
Are we having noodles again, from early morning?
But Chow Yun Fat often goes there. "Chow Yun Fat is here again."
(Chow Yun Fat is said to frequent the restaurant.)
That's the title of the article.
There is a restaurant in Kowloon City.
Chow Yun Fat often eats porridge here.
"He was wearing a black sweatsuit and dark sunglasses."
- Really? - Chow Yun Fat.
- We might be done soon. - That's right.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Will we be able to find him?
It'd be amazing if we meet him.
Definitely.
- If we meet him... - We'd be so lucky.
(Will they be able to meet the legendary Chow Yun Fat?)
(Chow Yun Fat, 63 years old)
(He is a legendary Hong Kong actor famous for his film noirs.)
(He is often seen at a porridge place in Kowloon City.)
(Hotel)
(They move to the restaurant frequented by Chow Yun Fat.)
(Porridge restaurant)
Chow Yun Fat...
By the way, shouldn't we do that?
- Ballots... - Ballots...
We should do it.
We should divide them up.
I have 2, and So Min has 1.
Seok Jin has none.
As long as we don't target each other, it'll be fine.
How many should the winner get, 2 or 1?
- 2. - 2.
What game should we play?
A word game?
- Okay. - Kungkungta.
Let's do it.
(They play a word game to win 2 ballots.)
Can we say a word that's already been said?
Yes.
Let's start with "Chow Yun Fat".
- Chow Yun Fat? - Start.
(Kung, kung, kung)
(It's been a long time since they play a game to the rhythm.)
Chow Yun Fat, kungkungta.
(Chow Yun Fat)
"Foot odor", kungkungta.
"Bird Song", kungkungta.
"Old man", kungkungta.
"King", kungkungta.
(Are they singing a round?)
(King)
"Lim Ha Ryong", kungkungta.
(It suddenly changes.)
(Lim Ha Ryong?)
"Dr. Ryong", kungkungta.
- What's "Dr. Ryong"? - What's "Dr. Ryong"?
- What's that? - I know what it is.
There's a crab restaurant called "Dr. Ryong".
What's "Dr. Ryong"?
You're out.
- It's you and me. - It's hard.
- You and me. - Let's start with "Jeon So Min".
- Start. - Kung, kung, kung
(Which of them will win 2 ballots?)
(Another round)
"Song Ji Hyo", kungkungta.
(I thought it was "Jeon So Min".)
"Fedor", kungkungta.
(Fedor)
(You succeeded?)
"L Brand", kungkungta.
(It's almost the only word you can say.)
What's wrong?
There is L Brand.
- L Brand. - It's over.
- It's over. I have 4 now. - Jae Seok has 4.
(Jae Seok wins 2 more ballots.)
He always attacks his own team member.
He suddenly said, "Song Ji Hyo". That's so sly.
- And he said, "Fedor". - Fedor.
I shouldn't have suggested a word game.
- It's hard. - I'm happy.
Okay.
It's over now.
(Jae Seok has way more ballots than the others.)
Seok Jin is so funny.
(Who will get the remaining 5?)
I used to listen to this a lot.
(Soundtrack of "A Better Tomorrow")
(Where are you, Chow Yun Fat?)
We're on our way to Chow Yun Fat.
(They'd love to meet their childhood idol.)
I really hope we can meet him.
(Singing)
(Their voices sound so feminine.)
(Is that how this song is supposed to be sung?)
(Singing)
(Immersed)
(The song brings back memories.)
If we really meet Chow Yun Fat...
(If we really meet Chow Yun Fat...)
(They wouldn't be able to communicate.)
(They're immersed in memories.)
Shouldn't we buy trench coats for them?
- I really want to meet him. - Chow Yun Fat...
It'd be amazing.
It'd make my heart beat.
Your heart should always beat.
(Jae Seok ruins the mood.)
Hey.
Your heart...
Isn't your heart beating?
- That's not what I mean. - But...
- It's a poetic experssion. - You should say, "burst".
Not "beat".
- If it doesn't beat, you die. - You die.
(Anyway, they're excited.)
I think we're here.
(They arrive at the restaurant.)
Are we going to order the Chow Yun Fat combo?
The Chow Yun Fat combo.
- The combo menu Chow Yun Fat eats. - We should give him a nickname.
- We should give him a nickname. - We should give him a nickname.
- Chow Yunbari. - Jeon Sobari, Yu Jaebari,
- Jee Seokbari, - Jee Seokbari,
- Chow Yunbari. - Chow Yunbari.
- We're the Baribari family. - We're the Baribari family.
We should tell him if we meet him.
- Chow Yunbari. - I already feel so close to him.
Chow Yunbari.
(They want to let him know they're all family now.)
The place looks a bit shabby.
It's this place?
(It's a shabby-looking restaurant.)
(But it's many decades old.)
There are so many customers.
It's early morning, and it's full.
(The restaurant is filled with local people from early morning.)
There's a dog.
(Chow Yun Fat is said to eat here often.)
(Chow Yun Fat...)
(Is he here?)
Chow Yun Fat... When...
(Welcome)
She wants us to come in.
We were just asking a question.
Please ask them when Chow Yun Fat was here last.
When was he here?
(Chow Yun Fat and the owner are good friends.)
(He was here...)
At seven.
At seven this morning?
- This morning? - This morning?
Every day.
(He comes here every day.)
(Every day?)
- Every day? - At seven?
Yes.
He was already here.
He was just here.
(At 7am, while they were sleeping at the hotel,)
(Chow Yun Fat enjoyed his breakfast here.)
One day...
(I've taken a picture with Chow Yun Fat.)
Ask him if Chow Yun Fat likes taking pictures.
He often comes here in the morning, has breakfast,
and takes pictures with the other customers.
- He talks with them too. - He talks?
- We should have been there. - That's incredible.
Let's stay here one more day.
If we had been here at seven...
- We could have... - We might be able to meet him.
- Exactly. - Today...
What did he eat today?
(What did Chow Yun Fat eat this morning?)
(Fish porridge)
He ate the porridge he usually eats...
and stir-fried noodles.
(Stir-fried noodles)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Noodles?)
Oh I see. But because of our personal reasons,
we'll just order the porridge.
Please tell them we don't want the noodles.
(They'll try just the porridge.)
That was so close.
I know.
We could have completed the mission and headed home.
This is what Chow Yun Fat eats?
It's fish porridge, right?
(Generous)
Chow Yun Fat...
- We ordered the Chow Yun Fat combo. - The Chow Yun Fat combo.
The Yunbari combo.
It has some meat in it.
It must be fish.
- It's fish? - It's fish porridge.
Is this what they eat in "A Better Tomorrow"?
That's right.
- It tastes good. - Let me try.
It's a little salty and very flavorful.
It's really flavorful.
This is nice.
It tastes really good.
- It tastes so rich. - It's slightly salty.
It tastes so good.
It's flavorful.
I can see why Chow Yun Fat eats this every morning.
It'd be perfect for breakfast. It's easy on the stomach.
Exactly.
(In the middle of eating,)
(he makes a V sign.)
(Cute)
Because Chow Yun Fat takes pictures with the other customers...
- Move your head. - Gosh.
It's because Chow Yun Fat takes pictures with them.
(I want to be in the picture too.)
(All together)
(Click)
Chow Yun Fat takes pictures with the other customers.
We should do it too.
(The fan is happy.)
(The waitress casually puts something on their table.)
(Noodles?)
(Heaping)
We're really fine but...
(We said we didn't want noodles.)
Well...
(They have to eat noodles again.)
(It's on the house.)
(More noodles)
It's what Chow Yun Fat eats.
It's included in the combo menu.
It's the Chow Yun Fat combo.
The Chow Yun Fat combo.
Jee Seokbari.
- Jeon Sobari. Yu Jaebari. - Jeon Sobari. Yu Jaebari.
We're eating the Chow Yunbari combo.
Chow Yunbari.
(Enjoying)
It tastes so good.
(He can't stop.)
Why aren't you eating the noodles?
No one seems to...
Why is no one eating the noodles?
Sobari, sobari, but you
Since Chow Yun Fat eats them, I'll try some.
(Taking a big bite)
(How do the noodles taste?)
I can't eat any more noodles.
My mouth refuses to take more noodles.
You know what?
If Chow Yun Fat ate breakfast here,
- that means he's not working today. - He's not working.
- Is that so? - That's when he eats breakfast.
He must be around here somewhere.
I heard he walks around the city.
Shall I ask the restaurant owner?
- Where he goes? - Where does he go next?
- Go ahead. - Where does Chow Yun Fat go...
when he leaves here? Does he have lunch?
- There's a milk tea shop. - Right now,
the restaurant owner told...
Chow Yun Fat's friend that we're here.
He asked where Chow Yun Fat is, so wait a little.
- That's amazing. - Really?
Does he know his friend?
He knows Chow Yun Fat's friend?
You might meet him today.
- If we meet him... - My dream would come true.
- I know what you mean. - Seok Jin.
Here's what I found while reading articles.
It's an article about what Chow Yun Fat said.
- However, - What did he say?
- he's very different from Seok Jin. - Why?
In one article,
he said, "You don't wear clothes to show to other people."
(Chow Yun Fat's famous saying)
It's enough if they're comfortable.
It's different from what Seok Jin thinks.
He doesn't think that.
I prefer to look fancy to being comfortable.
He likes white pants.
Being shown to people is important such as white pants.
He said, "Money isn't mine."
"I'm only keeping it for a while."
Seok Jin would say that it's definitely his money.
(Money is mine indeed.)
Seok Jin wants to become successful all of a sudden.
Chow Yun Fat said, "My dream is becoming a happy, normal person."
("My dream is becoming a normal person.")
- He's different. - He's completely different...
from Seok Jin.
Chow Yun Fat is impressive.
- Isn't he amazing? - He really is.
He has famous sayings.
Let's go to the milk tea shop.
- He'll call us. - Okay, milk tea.
I've been craving milk tea since yesterday.
Seok Jin said that Chow Yun Fat drinks milk tea.
- We're lucky today. - I was craving it.
Our second day is better than the first.
- It's great. - I'm happy.
My goodness.
(They head to the second place where he frequents.)
(Milk tea shop)
I want to meet him...
- all of a sudden. - I really want to meet him.
I want to meet him more now that it may be possible.
It'd be interesting to meet him.
I might even scream.
Won't that be embarrassing?
It won't be embarrassing, but Chow Yun Fat would hate it.
- Why would he hate it? - He would hate if you scream.
I like when people scream at me.
It's because it doesn't happen often.
(He attacks with a fact.)
Hey, it happens often.
Who would scream?
Do you know how much I get screamed at home?
- "Why did you put it here?" - Do you mean your wife?
"I told you to put it in your closet."
(He'd do anything if he meets Chow Yun Fat.)
"Why did you put it here?"
Someone is calling.
- Why is Jong Kook calling? - It's Jong Kook.
(They get a sudden call from Jong Kook.)
Hello, Jin, Jin, Jin.
(What's going on?)
(After serving food to 100 people,)
(here's the second mission for Team Ji Hyo.)
Okay.
(Last time was getting a hairstyle that's popular in Osaka.)
(Find a hair salon that includes a celebrity's name.)
(Before going to the hair salon,)
(they must win a speed quiz on the phone with the celebrity.)
"Hair salons in Sokcho".
(He searches hair salons in Sokcho.)
There's Jin Hair Salon.
- Who's Jin? - There's Lee Jin of Fin.K.L.
- There's also Junjin. - You're right.
Doesn't it include Seok Jin? We sometimes call him Jin.
(Can it also be Seok Jin?)
We sometimes call him Jin, Jin, Jin.
Call him Jin, Jin, Jin.
If Seok Jin responds, we'll accept it.
I'll call him Jin, Jin, Jin. Listen.
Seriously?
- I'm curious. - I'll try.
(If the quiz is a success, they head to Jin Hair Salon.)
(How does Jin, Jin, Jin react?)
Hello, Jong Kook.
(He doesn't hesitate at all.)
(He accepts being Jin, Jin, Jin.)
- It worked. - Okay, we got it.
You know a Korean movie with zombies?
- It takes place on a train. - What?
(He accepted his name as Jin, Jin, Jin.)
- I couldn't hear you. - It's a zombie movie.
- It's a movie on the train. - Zombies?
"Train to Busan".
This one is hard. It's a movie about going to...
- North Korea. - Ahn Sung Ki and Seol Kyung Gu.
- What's the movie? Okay. - "Silmido".
What's a recent movie about Queen?
- "Bohemian Rhapsody". - Okay.
Can you talk faster?
- There are ghosts in this movie. - Chun Woo Hee.
It stars Chun Woo Hee.
- "What's important?" - "What's important?" It's a movie.
- "The Wailing". - Yes.
It's a musical movie that takes place in Los Angeles.
- "La La Land". - Okay.
It's a movie starring Ma Dong Seok.
"Are you alone?"
(Will he...)
(succeed?)
It's "The"...
(He's close to remembering it.)
(All he has to say is "Outlaw".)
It's "The"...
(Time is up with one remaining question.)
- That was close. - Come on.
Hey, I couldn't remember it.
- What happened? - Since he failed,
- all of us will vote Seok Jin. - Right.
We'll spend half of our ballots to vote for you.
(Get ready to be penalized.)
- Jong Kook. - What?
My team wants to vote for me too.
They'll vote for me.
(Jin is in a lonely fight.)
- Many people plan to vote for me. - Seok Jin.
You and Kwang Soo are confirmed.
(Kwang Soo stole ballots.)
All right. Thank you anyway.
Send me the number of Jin of BTS.
(Send me Jin's number.)
It's because you failed, Jin, Jin, Jin.
I need to find another Jin.
How about Gook Jin?
Gook Jin?
- Gook Jin. - I'll call him too.
- Awesome. - There are many men named Jin.
Send anyone's number whose name is Jin.
- Send them all. - Ask for Joo Byung Jin too.
Seok Jin, do you have Joo Byung Jin's number?
I do.
(I know Byung Jin.)
I know Joo Byung Jin.
Send me all of their numbers.
- I'll send them all. - Send me all of them.
- Goodness. - Thank you.
- Joo Byung Jin is Jin too. - He is.
You have to call him Jin, Jin, Jin.
- You should call him mister. - Right.
Jin, Jin... Wait.
Mr. Jin, Jin, Jin?
All the senior colleagues...
I can do it. Hand me the phone.
(He calls him nervously.)
Hello?
(Someone answered.)
- Hello? - Wait, I'm making a tee shot.
A tee shot?
- A tee shot? - He's playing golf.
He's at a golf course.
(He kneels unconsciously.)
He's more than 40 years older than me.
He's your senior comedian.
- He's his direct senior. - That's right.
I can't call him Jin, Jin, Jin.
(He feels awkward.)
He'll think it's cute.
- He will. - He will think it's cute.
(His heart is about to burst.)
Good shot.
Thankfully it was a good shot.
(It's such a relief.)
It's a relief.
If he made a mistake, I'd be in trouble.
- It was a good shot. - Hello?
- Hello? - Hello, Se Chan.
Mr. Jin, Jin, Jin.
- Hello. - Mr. Jin, Jin, Jin.
- Byung Jin, yes. - Have you been well?
What do you use to see your face?
- A mirror. - That's correct.
What do you wear around your neck in the cold?
- Scarf. - Thank you, sir.
What do you use when it rains?
- Umbrella. - Thank you, sir.
What instrument plays this rhythm?
- It's not kkwaenggwari. - You play it with a drum.
- You play a drum with? - Janggu.
Thank you. What do you use to fry eggs?
- It has a handle. - A frying pan.
Thank you. What appliance takes photos?
- Camera in Korean. - How do you say it in English?
- Camera. - Thank you.
Sir, thank you. Good shot.
- Good shot. - Byung Jin.
Thank you so much, Byung Jin.
We had to find Jin, Jin, Jin.
It wasn't easy, but we called you anyway.
- I feel honored. - Thank you...
- for participating. - Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
- Yes, have a good day. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye.
(We wish you a hole in one.)
- We got it. - We got it.
- Let's go to Jin Hair Salon. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Go.
- Goodness. - That was funny.
Are we randomly selecting our hairstyle?
- The hairstylist will choose. - We'll write names...
- on the cards. - I wonder who will be picked.
Think of a hairstyle.
- I thought about it. - It will be two people.
Which one will be fun?
Here's a recommendation for Jong Kook.
- Ji Hyo. - The pointy hairstyle?
(What do you think?)
Wouldn't it look cute on Jong Kook? This hairstyle.
Ji Hyo, I'll make your hair like this.
It's Ji Hyo's hair.
[VIU Ver] SBS E431 Running Man
"Year End Special, Losers Bracket Race Part 3"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
This is for Ji Hyo. She's pretty.
This is fun.
- This is it. - It's a neighborhood's hair salon.
- Goodness. - Where are we?
Good shot, good shot.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's neat. - Hello.
- Hello. - Welcome.
Among the four members,
the hairstylist will pick two to change the hair style.
- Okay. - Pick one card.
- Go ahead. - Don't open it yet.
- Don't open it. - Just keep it.
- Pick one more. - Pick one.
- She got them. - All right.
She picked them immediately. Let's open...
the first card. Get ready.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(Who's the first member of honor?)
(Se Chan)
Okay.
Gosh, I'm picked.
- He's always chosen. - No way.
Here's the second one. 1, 2, 3.
(Who's the second member?)
Goodness.
(Byul is picked.)
How did this happen?
Why is it the two of us again?
How did the guest and Se Chan get picked?
What kind of hairstyle should I get?
For Se Chan, there is a really simple one.
What is it?
Strawberry.
- Strawberry. - What?
- The strawberry hair. - The strawberry hair?
Something like this.
It's cute.
(Is this even possible?)
You'd look so cute.
Can you get...
the Miss Korea hairstyle these days too?
The really voluminous one. You can't get it, right?
- The really big one. - I'm sure she can do it.
Like Tina Turner.
- How does that sound? - I'm excited.
I can't believe I'm doing this in Gangwon Province.
(A little later)
- Cute. - So lovely.
What is this?
(Is this a strawberry?)
(It's a mixture of grapes and a strawberry.)
I'm looking forward to this hairstyle.
Back in the day, in addition to this hairstyle,
didn't they wear purple lipstick?
- Right? - Back then,
they wore very dramatic makeup.
They all wore theatrical makeup.
- Kimera too. - Right.
I have such an innocent face, so I'm not sure if it'll work.
(She doesn't even change her expression.)
Who?
Awkward
(Awkward)
It's become awkward
Do something about it
It became so awkward.
(Things you say can make the atmosphere awkward.)
I can't wait.
I like it.
(Although the atmosphere had become awkward...)
This is crazy.
(The crazy hairstyle brings the mood up.)
Today...
Haha will...
(New Miss Korea)
Haha will love it.
- Say something as Miss Korea. - Byul.
I'm serious.
(After preparing food for 100 people,)
(she even got a new hairstyle.)
Thank you, Ms. Byun at Jin Hair Salon.
(Thanks to Byul, Team Ji Hyo completes both missions.)
(Team Hong Kong arrives at SoHo.)
(Crowded)
- We're here. - We're here?
(Chow Yun Fat often visits a milk tea place here.)
I guess this is the city center.
So Min, we've been here before.
Last time, there were no people.
Look at that.
- Look. - What?
(This egg tart place had no customers last time.)
(But there's a long line today.)
The line is so long.
Film that.
Last time, there was no one.
When we went to that egg tart place with Han Na,
there was no line.
(Family Special last May)
(Han Na took them there, saying it was a popular place.)
(There's no line.)
(Empty)
(It was empty last time.)
- There was no line last time. - My goodness.
I can't believe it.
- I can't believe it. - How can it be possible?
No way. How can there be so many people?
Unbelievable.
(I want some egg tarts.)
They're supposed to be very tasty.
(These 3 are especially unlucky abroad.)
Let's meet Chow Yun Fat...
and eat egg tarts.
We should meet him.
(They arrive at the milk tea place frequented by Chow Yun Fat.)
This must be the place.
This.
- There's a picture. - There's a picture.
(There are pictures of Chow Yun Fat on the door.)
(He must be a regular customer here.)
This place really feels local.
(It's popular among both locals and tourists.)
(Chow Yun Fat has been visiting here for 50 years.)
- Chow Yun Fat. - Chow Yun Fat.
There are pictures of him.
- Has he been here today? - Well...
Can you ask them if Chow Yun Fat has been here?
(Has he been here today?)
(The local coordinator is asking the owner.)
Has he been here?
(Has Chow Yun Fat been here today?)
(Today...)
- He hasn't been here this morning. - No?
When was he here last?
It's been a few days.
- A few days? - A few days?
(Too bad.)
- Today... - Who's that?
They must be famous people.
That's Alan Tam.
- Alan Tam. - Alan Tam.
- Alan Tam. - That's Alan Tam.
- Alan Tam? - Yes.
- It's Alan Tam. - It's Alan Tam.
He's a regular here.
How did you get that?
- When did she say that? - She said, "He's a regular."
(She said, "He's a regular.")
(He's a regular.)
- She said that. - Gosh.
She did.
- She said that. - Does she speak Korean?
"He's a regular."
- I heard it too. - "He's a regular."
(You should be our regular customers too.)
(They've visited two places, but they haven't met him yet.)
(But there are many other places Chow Yun Fat often visits.)
I have a feeling he's having tea somewhere right now.
Where should we go now? Where is he?
Where are we headed?
(They end up at...)
As you can see,
Chow Yun Fat's first scene in "A Better Tomorrow" was shot here.
It was shot here?
(The legendary first scene was shot here.)
(The Toothpick Gang)
(Brother, are you ready?)
(You can count on me.)
(And...)
(a passerby)
(Where can we meet Chow Yun Fat?)
(If I knew, I wouldn't be here right now.)
(Looking for Chow Yun Fat)
(Toothpick Gang's Crisis)
I really want to meet Chow Yun Fat.
- Me too. - Even more now.
I want to meet him.
It was a matchstick in the movie.
Well...
- We should divide the ballots. - Right.
What game should we play?
We should play a game to divide the ballots.
Ballots...
How many ballots should the winner get, 1 or 2?
- 2. - 2.
- 2? - 2.
(The winner gets 2 ballots.)
They must be getting married.
The bride looks...
so happy.
I'm jealous. I want to get married too.
I've said I don't have to get married so many times on this show,
- so I won't be able to. - Why?
I've used up all my luck. I can't get married.
(She chose games over her marriage.)
(She was picking a suitcase.)
(I don't have to get married. I want to use all my luck today.)
(Did she have to say that?)
(Everyone tried to stop her, but she used up all her luck.)
(She didn't mind at that time.)
Do you really want to get married?
Seeing those two makes me want to.
Hi.
(They ask the couple for help.)
Let's ask them...
to choose a person who looks happy.
- A person who looks happy. - How does that sound?
- Okay. - The person who looks the happiest.
We want to wish the couple happiness.
Number 1 should get 2,
- and number 2 gets 1. - Number 2 gets 1.
Please ask them to shake hands with the two people they choose.
The two happiest-looking people.
One by one.
(Smiling)
(Innocent smile)
(Fake smile)
(Smiling)
(He smiles with his eyes.)
- They'll choose number 2 first. - Number 2.
The one who looks the second happiest.
(Who should be number 2?)
You two look so happy.
Congratulations.
Happy.
(Number 2 gets 1 ballot.)
(Who will the bride choose?)
(Please come to me.)
(The person who looks pretty happy is...)
(The bride chooses...)
(Jae Seok, not Seok Jin.)
Thank you.
Thank you. Congratulations.
- Now choose number 1. - Number 1.
One by one.
(It's time to choose number 1, who will win 2 ballots.)
(Candidate number 1: the fake smile expert)
(Candidate number 2: the innocent smile master)
(The person the groom chooses will get 2 ballots.)
(Who will the groom choose?)
(This time...)
(Not this time either.)
(Empty)
(They shake hands.)
(So Min wins the 1st place.)
Thank you.
Congratulations.
(Seok Jin's fake smile didn't fool anyone.)
Happy wedding.
Why didn't Seok Jin look happy?
Can you ask them?
Ask them why Seok Jin didn't look happy.
(Whispering)
"I'm sorry to say this,"
"Seok Jin's smile..."
"was pretty too, but the other two smiled so beautifully."
(His smile wasn't as beautiful as the other two's.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(So Min wins 2 ballots.)
- I knew it. - Gosh.
- I look happy. - Seok Jin...
- didn't win any. - Did you interpret correctly?
Did you interpret correctly?
- I have 3. - So Min has 3.
- I have 3. - I have 5.
- There are only 2 left now. - There are 2 left.
- You have none, right? - Gosh.
There are only two left?
I really want to meet Chow Yun Fat.
If we fail to meet him, all this is pointless.
We'll have failed all missions.
Should we search "Chow Yun Fat"?
I'll search the hashtags.
Hashtag, "Chow Yun Fat".
I think we should have met him this morning.
One of the hashtag is "Chow Yun Fat's favorite place".
During lunchtime...
- What is it? - A souffle food truck.
He had lunch at a souffle food truck.
- Is there a picture? - Yes.
(It's the latest news about Chow Yun Fat.)
They open at 1pm.
Souffle food truck. Should I search it?
We should go there right now.
At 1pm?
(Based on the information on social media,)
(they move from the milk tea place to the souffle food truck.)
- It's over there. - Over there?
- Where? This? - This?
- This is... - This is the place?
It looks tasty.
(They arrive at the souffle food truck.)
(Surprised)
(The local people love this souffle food truck.)
(Does he comes and get this sweet and fulffy souffle often?)
What's that?
- Hello. - It looks delicious.
Hi.
Chow Yun Fat?
- Chow Yun Fat. - Chow Yun Fat?
- Chow Yun Fat? - Chow Yun Fat.
(It's a recent photo with Chow Yun Fat.)
(Will they find Chow Yun Fat's whereabouts?)
- There's no photo of his. - He came last month.
Did he drink bubble tea?
Apparently he came last month.
- Last month? - Last month?
- It was last month. - He came last month.
(They fail to find Chow Yun Fat.)
Is it okay to find food without finding him?
Look for Chow Yun Fat.
Who knows if he's around?
What if we meet Chow Yun Fat miraculously?
That would be...
- I will immediately... - the best.
turn on that music.
I would play it right away.
I wish we could meet Chow Yun Fat.
(He wants to meet him once.)
Isn't this Jae Seok?
(Isn't this Jae Seok?)
This souffle looks delicious.
- It's Jae Seok. - Me?
I'm on it too.
- It's Jae Seok. - I thought it was him.
I thought it was me too. I was startled.
He looks exactly like you.
- He looks exactly like you. - You look the same.
Listen up, everyone.
Remember the owner of the porridge restaurant?
We got a call from him.
About 10 minutes away from the porridge restaurant,
there's a herbal medicine shop. He just arrived.
- Just now? - Yes.
(Chow Yun Fat appeared.)
(He's finally here.)
Let's go now.
Let's hurry.
Is it next to the porridge restaurant?
- It's unbelievable. Is it real? - Really?
- He's been staying around there. - An herbal medicine shop?
- It's therapeutic. - He should take care of his health.
That's right.
- Let's go now. - Let's hurry.
Let's go.
(They go from a souffle food truck to Kowloon Market.)
Will we really meet him?
Meeting Chow Yun Fat will be amazing.
A minute ago, he bought some vegetables.
Let's go to the vegetable market.
Okay.
- What's going on? - Did he leave?
Did he leave again?
Where is he?
(Where is he?)
(They're in a hurry to find him.)
Where is he?
(They enter the market where Chow Yun Fat is.)
Did Chow Yun Fat buy vegetables?
- He bought produce. - He bought produce.
Is it this way?
- Where is it? - Over here.
(Is it this vegetable market?)
(Chow Yun Fat is inside this market.)
Is that Chow Yun Fat?
(Did they finally find Chow Yun Fat?)
(Will they meet...)
(Chow Yun Fat?)
Is that Chow Yun Fat?
- Is Chow Yun Fat here? - Chow Yun Fat.
(Chow Yun Fat)
(They ask the owner of the vegetable market his whereabouts.)
(She keeps answering.)
He stopped by and left just now.
- Where did he go? - Where did he go?
(They're in a hurry.)
- Ma'am, where did he go? - Where did he go?
(She speaks in Chinese.)
(What is she saying?)
She thinks that he went home.
(She thinks that he went home.)
(Did Chow Yun Fat go home?)
(She wants to show them something from the corner.)
(He's a regular customer at this place as well.)
We just missed him again.
- We just missed him. - We were so close.
- Let's disperse. - Okay.
- Let's go around once. - Okay.
Let's go separately.
- He might be nearby. - If...
- If you find Chow Yun Fat, - Yes.
- Call each other. - be careful with the camera.
Ask politely for his permission.
Okay, I will.
Shouldn't we check the bus stop?
Or near a subway station?
We have to meet him.
After all we've done,
it'd be great to finally meet Chow Yun Fat.
(He looks for a herbal medicine shop.)
Apparently Chow Yun Fat comes to buy herbal medicine.
(I heard Chow Yun Fat came near an herbal medicine shop.)
(Have you seen Chow Yun Fat?)
(Chow Yun Fat?)
He didn't see him today.
He didn't?
(He didn't see him today.)
I wonder if he stops by here.
(Where are you, Chow Yun Fat?)
(She searches an alleyway across from the market.)
I wish we'd meet him miraculously.
If it's meant to be...
(So Min and Chow Yun Fat)
Even for a little while...
If he appeared at a place like this,
I would be so moved.
(He searches inside the market again.)
(Where is Chow Yun Fat?)
Is he here?
I think he's nearby.
What?
(What?)
(He passes by a restaurant.)
Isn't that Chow Yun Fat?
It is Chow Yun Fat indeed.
He was here too.
(It's another restaurant where he comes.)
Isn't it Chow Yun Fat?
(Does the restaurant owner know his whereabouts?)
(Have you seen Chow Yun Fat?)
He came by a long time ago.
(She can hardly remember.)
(He fails to find Chow Yun Fat.)
He was here. He must come here often.
This is disappointing.
He must be around here somewhere.
(Where is Chow Yun Fat?)
There they are.
(Their search time is over.)
- So Min is coming. - She's coming.
She didn't find him either.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin.
What?
(Did you find him?)
- You didn't find him, right? - Jae Seok.
- Did you take photos? - You didn't find him, right?
(I see failure written on your face.)
I saw you walking from over there.
(I didn't find him.)
All right, everyone.
- You failed to clear the mission. - I know.
Due to your flight, you must go to the airport now.
You know what?
We never cleared a mission while being abroad.
Is it true that he was just at the market?
I know.
(We hope to see you next time.)
(It's the last night of Year End Race.)
(It's time to tally the result.)
It's very cold.
Team Hong Kong must have worked hard.
Did you clear the mission today?
Who?
- Your mission today. - Us?
Let's keep it a secret for now.
Depending on whether you cleared it or not,
the number of members is determined.
Don't be curious, Kwang Soo.
- Why not? - Don't you realize what you did?
- You'll be picked anyway. - Me?
- Of course. - Thank you for your letter.
- Thank you for your letter. - Thank you.
What do you mean?
Blame me only if you're confident.
- What? He's gotten strange. - He's strange.
If your name tag in your jacket, Si Young?
My name tag?
You're right.
- Doesn't she have a name tag? - Shall I help you?
Did you take off each other's name tag in the van?
We did everything.
We did all.
- Did you eliminate name tags? - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What is he doing?
(Laughing)
Wait, Si Young.
(While they're looking for her name tag,)
(he steals her ballots.)
(He takes her ballots.)
(His method gets more daring in the cold.)
(Shaking her head)
(Kwang Soo with skilled hands)
Thank you.
- All right. - Did you stick it on?
Yes.
(Si Young gets betrayed in the open.)
That was incredible.
It's unbelievable.
Seriously.
(Be quiet, it might hurt you.)
Se Chan.
How could you?
Goodness.
(Where are my ballots?)
(Punching)
(Her punch punishes Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo, you're giving me such a hard time.)
My goodness.
This isn't the first time. What's wrong with him?
Stop it, no.
Stop it, no. No.
You will lose.
You said no.
(Come and get me.)
Gosh.
(She's counting her ballot.)
(Grunting)
What's wrong with you, Kwang Soo?
Look at Kwang Soo.
(She finally laughs after counting her ballot.)
Look.
Look at Kwang Soo.
(Disappointed)
(I almost got away with it.)
You're back.
- You're back. - You're back.
Where did you go?
It was cold.
It was hilarious.
You worked hard. Good job.
You finished...
Year End Special, Losers Bracket Race.
Good job, everyone.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Good job.
Thanks to team leader Si Young and special guest Byul,
both teams cleared all the missions.
Really?
- Did you clear all of them? - Goodness.
- That's amazing. - That's amazing.
That's impressive.
She's better than her husband.
For Si Young,
we have a present for her baby who will turn one soon.
We'll give R Ring to Byul.
(Gold R Ring and a ring for one-year birthday)
That's great.
(Is my husband watching this?)
To fit his finger?
(Si Young gets a ring for her son.)
However, Team So Min failed both missions.
(Team So Min failed both missions.)
What will happen now?
They need to take responsibility.
Two members will be penalized.
They will be two with the highest votes.
Did you bring your ballots?
- Yes. - Yes.
Let's check.
How did that happen?
I feel bad for Seok Jin.
- We have... - Two in common.
- We have two ballots. - They're in common.
They played dirty again.
Si Young has 10 ballots.
(They start to vote whom to penalize.)
Stay out if you don't have ballots.
Why do the three of us never have any?
- What do you mean? - My goodness.
(They never have anything.)
I don't understand why.
- Whose name should I write? - Who should I write?
(The members hesitate in the voting booth.)
I only have four ballots.
Who should I write?
It's too cruel to give all the votes to one person.
(Si Young enters the booth.)
Kwang Soo...
worked so hard with me. I can't forget about it.
I don't know what to do.
Those who failed...
Oh, gosh.
I'll announce the results.
(He announces the people chosen for the punishments.)
First of all, this is second place.
- This person received 12 votes. - What?
- 12 votes? - Isn't that all the votes?
Second place, Lee Kwang Soo.
Isn't that almost all the votes?
How come Kwang Soo gets punished every week?
What did you do to deserve it?
Out of 35 votes,
he received 21 votes.
That's almost everybody.
(Who got 1st place?)
You instinctively thought that it's you.
No, it's not me.
People thought I was going to have many votes, so they didn't pick me.
- There's a twist. - They had an overwhelming win...
- There's a twist. - over Kwang Soo.
- Do we have a champion? - There's a twist.
(Who has the most number of votes?)
It's Jee Seok Jin.
- It's Jee Seok Jin. - You're so cool!
(Teasing)
- If he kept his mouth shut... - What's cool?
MVP. You're the MVP.
- He's cool. - This is the best way to lose.
(Seok Jin wants all the attention.)
It's okay.
You wrote my name, right? You too.
(Yes, I did.)
- You did, right? - But...
- I'm going to watch this episode. - we couldn't...
write people from the other teams.
- We had no choice. - We couldn't do much.
I felt bad while writing your name down.
(I'm sorry, Seok Jin.)
Si Young, how was today for you?
Thank you for inviting me.
If I was on a different team,
(For example, a team without Kwang Soo.)
I think I would have been nicer,
so I'm a little sad about that.
(She must have had a hard time.)
And I really hope that...
Kwang Soo recovers.
The illness of the mind.
I'm going to root for him from far away.
I'm going be honest because the voting is over.
Kwang Soo has a problem, but she has one too.
(He makes a revelation.)
- It's serious. - She has no patience.
It's serious.
(They all had a hard time.)
Today's punishment is...
(The punishment for Year End Special is...)
whipped cream bomb.
I'm going to take a revenge.
I'm going to take a revenge. You, So Min... No, Ji Hyo...
Why me?
- Why are you doing that to me? - We were on the same team.
Fine. Let's plan something.
Kwang Soo. Goodness.
We have to do it next week.
Poor Seok Jin.
In one,
- 2, 3. - 2, 3.
(The whipped cream is launched.)
(The white whipped cream splatters on their faces.)
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you for your hard work.
(A week later)
I was so mad.
What did we do to deserve it? We were just working hard.
- Am I guilty for trying too hard? - Are we?
Here's an opportunity for you to take a revenge.
(Here's an opportunity for you to take a revenge.)
(They finally have a chance to get even.)
(They waited for this day!)
In a moment, we'll start Christmas Special Couple Race.
You need to complete a secret mission...
without getting caught.
(They must complete a secret mission during Christmas Special.)
For this race,
one of your identities...
will be revealed during the intro.
(What kind of a mission is it?)
For this race,
one of your identities...
will be revealed during the intro.
(One of their identities will be revealed during the intro.)
What? What do you mean? I don't think I understand.
Do you want us to succeed or not?
We're spies, but you're telling the others?
You're telling them?
Please decide whose identity you'll reveal first.
I choose Seok Jin.
- I choose Kwang Soo. - No, I choose him.
I choose Kwang Soo.
What's this supposed to be?
Do you want us to succeed?
This might be a good thing because if one of us gets revealed,
then people won't think we're a team.
It's doomed to failure.
(It looks like the staff gave up on the Year End Special.)
This is Christmas Special.
If I know you're a spy, I'll be suspicious of Jong Kook.
(The weakest person should be partnered with somebody strong.)
Of course. Or Jae Seok.
- You're good at that kind of thing. - Right.
You're good at framing people. Okay, I'll reveal my identity.
I think that's right. I'll sacrifice myself.
(The winning strategy for the weakest team is...)
I'm volunteering myself.
I know.
- That's how desperate I am. - I know.
(Will their revenge be a success?)
(30 minutes later...)
(This place is filled with the Christmas spirit.)
(Running Man's 2018 Christmas party starts.)
- Merry Christmas! - Merry Christmas!
- And happy new year! - Merry Christmas!
- The cakes look so good. - This is awesome.
Can we eat these? Okay.
Do you know this?
(The light on the tree comes on.)
The old people are fascinated.
What's this?
- Let's eat. - How do we eat this?
What flavor is this?
- Well... - It's Christmas,
- so Jae Seok... - I...
- is being funny with his glasses. - It's been a while.
What's up with your glasses?
- I wore big glasses. - Why?
Are your eye sights worse?
These glasses are perfect for this fashion.
- Is that fashion? - Yes, it is.
- Why are they so thick? - I...
(Why are they so thick if it's fashion?)
I have bad eye sights.
His eyes look this small.
I thought it was Magic Eye.
- His eye sights are so bad. - Wear contact lenses then.
- I have bad eye sights. - Wear contact lenses.
- It's okay if they're thinner. - I know.
- What's on your shirt? - We were supposed to...
- dress for the season. - Right.
Did you design this at home?
- No, this sweater is like that. - Really?
I got here early,
and So Min parked next to me.
I called her name, and her manager rolled down the window.
She was...
(So Min was out.)
The saliva...
She had a black jacket...
- You should have taken a picture. - Yesterday...
I slept late, and she posted something suspicious.
- What did she post? - What did she post on social media?
What did she post?
Was it something special?
Was it "There's 20 percent left"?
She took a screenshot when her phone battery had 20 percent left...
- "My soul is..." - "My heart is..."
No, "There's 20 percent left in my heart too."
(Was she emotional?)
What was that?
That's why she was drooling.
I almost gave her an online gift.
(She had 20 percent left inside and 20 percent of energy left.)
Why are you so emotional?
- What is it? - What is it?
(Peeking)
What is that?
- Who drew that? - I think Dream did.
No, it's not his. He can't draw like that.
(There are portraits of the 8 Running Man members.)
- What's this? - This is pretty high level.
This looks exactly like Jae Seok. This is good.
Jae Seok is on the very left, right?
(Is this Jae Seok?)
(His mouth is protruding, and his hair is parted on the side.)
That looks exactly like Jae Seok.
Who is this ghost?
(Who is this lady ghost?)
Isn't that Ji Hyo?
- Is that me? - It's Ji Hyo.
Are those eyes? Not glasses?
- She's... - She has big eyes.
bleeding from the ears.
(Is that me?)
Is this me? I think it is.
It's you.
- Your mouth... - Is that a mouth?
Hey, Jong Kook has sharp teeth.
He has sharp teeth.
- Look at this. - Is this me?
- Look at your nose. - Why are my eyes so small?
You have a big nose.
(He looks exactly like Seok Jin.)
Why did they draw me like this?
I thought I was Haha.
- Seok Jin. - Haha has the mustache.
- That looks like Haha. - I recognized it right away.
This is Dong Hoon. Is this me then?
This is Kwang Soo.
He has a long face.
Asia Prince.
Why don't I have eyebrows?
So Min...
So Min, why is your forehead so wide?
Ji Hyo, I don't have eyebrows, and my eyes are small.
So Min, your forehead is so small.
Se Chan only has a mouth.
(Today's finale is Se Chan of course.)
They didn't even draw me a nose.
- I don't even have a nose. - Se Chan looks the most alike.
I don't have a nose.
- Why did you get Se Chan's photo? - What's wrong with mine?
Everybody else has drawings. Why does he get a photo?
When Joy and Irene were here,
we had the photo-shopped pictures. Se Chan's are still on the internet.
- They are. - Really?
- Yes. - Those are dark pictures.
That looks like Se Chan.
(The 4 of them have their gums showing.)
What about these drawings?
- Who drew them? - The drawings...
are done by seven-year-old children.
They drew it from their point of view.
- Thank you. - This is good.
This is good for seven-year-olds.
(These are really good!)
(Thank you to Class Blue of Janice Kindergarten!)
These drawings have a significance.
Today is Christmas Special.
It's called Flirting Santa Claus Couple Race.
(Christmas Special: Flirting Santa Claus' Couple Race)
Oh, dear.
- What do I do? - Flirting Santa Claus?
Can we flirt?
(She's excited already.)
- You were a shirt with colors. - I know.
I've never seen him wear something with red and yellow in it.
- It's been a while. - I was going to wear gym clothes.
- Behind the doors are... - Okay.
six male and female guests.
(His heart flutters.)
There will be seven couples in total.
Unfortunately, there will be...
- one male-male couple. - Oh, dear.
(There will be a male-male couple on Christmas.)
You can see who's going to a male-male couple.
(Staring)
See what?
- Why are you staring at me? - Male-male couple.
Kwang Soo looks nice today.
The male-male couple...
It's Christmas.
The children who drew you portraits...
also drew portraits of the guests.
(The children who drew them also drew the faces of the guests.)
Let's guess.
Look at the pictures in front of the doors,
and you can make an initial pick.
You can tell whether they're female or male from the pictures.
Of course.
- Should I open this? - Yes.
Children are good at picking out characteristics.
(How did the children view the first guest?)
- What's this? - It's a male.
He's a singer.
He's holding a microphone.
I'm here.
I like singers.
- He's a male. - He is.
- He has short hair. - Okay.
- He has brown hair. - I think he's a good singer.
He must be.
(He opens the second picture.)
What's this?
A squid?
(It's a male.)
- Abs. - It's a man.
- But... - I think it's a man.
Why is he naked?
- Why is he naked? - What?
- Why is he naked? - How many abs does he have?
Jae Seok, it's a man. He has dark eyebrows.
- The mustache. - He has short hair too.
It's a man anyhow.
(He moves on quickly.)
(The third guest is a woman.)
She's "The Little Mermaid".
(It's a female guest.)
It's a lady.
(It's a female.)
- It's just a drawing... - She's pretty.
She has distinctive features.
This is detailed.
Does she have a bob cut?
She has shiny eyes.
(Who's the third guest?)
This is a woman as well.
Her hair is braided.
- She's cute. - She looks cute.
(It's a female.)
I think she's a singer.
Her hair is yellow.
I think she's an idol star.
By the way,
there's only a small space for the hairline.
People who draw like this...
are narrow-minded.
(The person who drew this must be narrow-minded!)
(Hold on...)
- Really? - Yes, you can tell...
Yes, you can tell from the drawing.
She didn't draw this herself. The children did.
The seven-year-old?
(Oh, right.)
I'm sorry.
He's saying the children are narrow-minded.
- Are you saying that to children? - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
She didn't draw it herself.
(He can't take it back.)
I thought the guests drew themselves.
- I'm sorry. - It was the children.
I'm sorry, children.
I'm sorry.
You have a huge heart.
You are a generous child.
I don't know for sure.
(Who's the person who flustered Jae Seok?)
You are a generous child.
That's nice.
- It's a female. - That looks like Park Na Rae.
- It's Park Na Rae. - It looks like her.
(It's a female.)
It's Na Rae.
That looks like Hong Hyun Hee's nostrils.
- The clothes. - That's Hyun Hee's nose.
Jang Do Yeon?
- There's her too. - Jang Do Yeon.
She has long legs.
No, it might be a man with long hair.
I think it's Na Rae.
I don't know who it is.
Next.
(The last guest's portrait is revealed.)
- What's this? - It's Mona Lisa.
- She's pretty. - She looks pretty.
It's Shin Chan.
(It's a female.)
She's wearing a red dress.
- Her eyes are too small. - I agree.
- I think she's an actress. - This is artistic.
- I want to buy this painting. - They're good.
This one's good.
- That one is good. - It's really good.
Are there two guys then?
- That's what it looks like. - I have no clue.
Yes.
(Shall we flirt today?)
- Do we stand in front of a door? - Do we?
Each of you can stand in front of a door of your choice.
If there's more than one person by a door,
the guest will pick their partner.
I don't want to fight.
The member who gets rejected...
- has to move to the Anxious Bench. - "Anxious Bench"?
- Is there such a thing? - Do we have to do that?
Yes, and...
if there's nobody in front of a door...
or if the guest doesn't like anybody,
they can move to the Single's Bench.
- That's better. - Oh, dear.
Then please stand in front of a door.
All right.
You have to target a niche market. An empty spot.
This is Na Rae.
- I know. - It's Na Rae.
Okay, I'll stand here.
- I think it's Na Rae. - It is.
I don't think it is.
If this is Na Rae, the child did a good job.
It has to be Na Rae.
It's totally her.
Her eyes are too large.
Oh, dear.
I kind of like the short hair.
- Do you like it? - Is that short hair?
That's really short.
I think it's really Na Rae.
(Jong Kook doesn't pick.)
(He just watches.)
Okay, I'll stand here.
(Who does he want to pick?)
- This is strange, - She's cute.
but I'm considering the competitors.
(It's a game of wits.)
- Hey. - He's observing.
I'm considering who my competitors are.
Come.
That's why...
I'm behind Se Chan.
Is that why you came to me?
Jae Seok.
Why? Why?
You have to see who you're up against.
(Flirting Santa Claus' Couple Race is competitive from the beginning.)
If I stand here, I'll end up in a male-male couple.
You never know.
I think you'll lose wherever you go.
- Come. - This is driving me nuts.
(Should I pick Jong Kook or Seok Jin?)
I'm the only one. What if I get rejected?
Who did you pick?
- We both went for number one. - Yes.
Both of you?
Then the second guest...
- has nobody. - There's nobody.
The drawing looks scary.
All right. Let's reveal the first guest.
(Partner Selection)
First guest, come on out.
We didn't have any male guest in a long time.
(Who is it?)
He's holding a microphone.
(Everybody thought he was a singer.)
It's Chi Yeul.
(Cheers in your heart! Hwang Chi Yeul)
(He's a great singer and a dancer.)
(Even when you're tired, he cheers you up.)
Chi Yeul.
- That's why he was holding a mic. - Hello.
- Hello. - Chi Yeul.
(They cheer up just by looking at him.)
Merry Christmas.
It's been a long time.
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
Chi Yeul.
Let me ask you.
Why did you both stand here?
That drawing looks strange.
He's naked, and he's wearing stockings.
(That's very strange.)
I see.
He's really hairy too.
Chi Yeul, do you think that looks like him?
- I understand what this means. - Really?
How do you think it is?
- Are there his characteristics? - Yes.
All right.
You have to pick one person to be your partner.
- You were Ji Hyo's partner once. - Right.
- Right. - He was her partner.
Chi Yeul.
(Chi Yeul, do you remember? We had a good time.)
Ji Hyo.
Chi Yeul, let's do it again.
(Let's be partners again.)
I like you.
Stop lying.
(She makes a false confession to be a couple.)
We haven't done this in a while.
Make an acrostic poem with his name.
That's so hard.
Sure. I think it's a good idea.
So Min.
(This will be a decisive factor for the partner selection.)
The first line.
Hwang Chi Yeul.
- "Hwang Chi Yeul"? - "Hwang Chi Yeul".
- The second line. - Don't be cheap.
- "Don't be cheap". The last line. - That's good.
I'll try my best.
(She'll burn it up.)
(He loves it.)
She'll try her best.
(He likes her more after the acrostic poem.)
(She tried her best. They approve.)
Good job.
Chi Yeul,
please pick one person.
Call their name first and decide if you want to be their partner...
or reject them. Please choose one.
- That's cruel. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Who will Chi Yeul pick?)
- Ji Hyo. - He called out Ji Hyo.
(He calls Ji Hyo first after hesitating.)
Ji Hyo, please come forward.
Ji Hyo? Is she your partner or are you rejecting her?
In 1, 2, 3.
Ji Hyo.
(Does he have good memories of Ji Hyo?)
(Or did he find So Min appealing?)
- 2, 3. - Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo!)
Merry Christmas. I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
(He picks So Min instead of his old partner.)
So Min.
- So Min. - All right. I see.
- No, we were partners last time. - Fine.
- So Min and Chi Yeul. - He rejected her.
He made it sound sad.
- Ji Hyo, go to the Anxious Bench. - Oh, gosh.
Next. Number three.
- Us. - Okay.
Jong Kook and Seok Jin, come here.
Third guest?
I'm really curious.
(You can already see the result.)
(Their partner looks pretty in the drawing.)
(She has distinctive features. Who is this person?)
Oh, dear. Hye Bin.
(The variety show legend, Jeon Hye Bin)
(She's a singer, entertainer, and an actress. She can do it all.)
(She dominated variety shows in the early 21st century...)
(by spinning endlessly.)
- It's Hye Bin. - Right.
- It has been a while. - Hello.
- My goodness. - It has been a while.
It has been a while.
- 24-Hour Spinner. - That's right.
- She spins for 24 hours. - That's right.
That was ages ago.
Stop it.
- 24-Hour Spinner. - 24-Hour Spinner.
- She was on "Match Made in Heaven". - 24-Hour Spinner.
It was the 2000s.
We have an actress,
Jeon Hye Bin!
(The second guest is an actress, Jeon Hye Bin.)
Your outfit matches that of Jong Kook.
- Did they choose me? - Yes.
They chose you.
It has been a while, right?
- It has been a while. - Seriously.
(Seok Jin becomes quiet.)
- She was on "Love Letter". - Was she on "Love Letter"?
You haven't been on a variety show since "Match Made in Heaven".
Seok Jin, say something.
(He looks pitiful.)
- What? - It occurred to Seok Jin.
I am happy to see Hye Bin.
It occurred to Seok Jin.
"She won't choose me."
(That's why he was quiet.)
What?
You only looked at Jong Kook as you asked, "Did they choose me?"
- Seok Jin. - You didn't even look at Seok Jin.
I didn't do that.
He realized he won't get chosen.
- He knows. - He realized that.
You never know.
It's not like that.
Let's see what they can do.
- Do you want to see that? - Yes.
I want to give Seok Jin a chance.
(I want to give Seok Jin a chance.)
(She is the nicest person.)
Seok Jin, show your strength.
She is really nice. She is a saint.
In that case,
(Hye Bin gives him a chance.)
I will show my power.
(He decides to show his power.)
(He is ready to show the power of a middle-aged man.)
- Power? - Against Jong Kook?
Seok Jin will show his power.
(Seok Jin challenges Jong Kook, the embodiment of power.)
Jong Kook, why don't you show us your power?
- Power? - Yes, show us your power.
- What do you want me to do? - Why don't you do push-ups...
with me on your back?
- Superpower. - Show us your superpower.
You are heavy.
- Come on. - Men are heavy.
Men are heavy.
Give it a try.
- He only weighs 63kg. - That's right.
He will be able to do it.
(Hye Bin is expectant.)
Sit on my shoulders.
Okay.
I guess Jong Kook wants to look cool.
(His initial hesitation is gone.)
(Men are like that.)
He even told Jae Seok where to sit,
so that he doesn't fail.
(Jong Kook shows his will to succeed.)
- Okay. - It's a difficult task.
Is this okay?
It's a difficult task.
My goodness.
(After trembling for a while, he does perfect push-ups.)
(This is Jong Kook's power.)
(Jong Kook is amazing.)
(My goodness.)
My goodness.
(He gives it his all.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E431 Running Man
"Christmas Special Race, Flirting Santa Claus"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
He doesn't disappoint.
He is incredible.
Hye Bin, sit on me.
(It's Seok Jin's turn to show his power.)
All right. I will sit on you.
(Seok Jin goes against Jong Kook,)
(who did push-ups with Jae Seok on his back.)
(Will Seok Jin succeed to show his charms?)
(It's not a surprise.)
(He lies flat on the ground.)
He failed.
(Seok Jin completely fails to show his power.)
- My goodness. - Still, he did his best.
- What a shame! - Hye Bin said,
"Still, he did his best."
Why don't you give us an acrostic poem?
- An acrostic poem? - Yes.
(Okay, I will give it a go.)
The first line.
I have known you for a while,
but you changed.
- My goodness. - The second line.
(The second line.)
Hye Bin, it finally happened.
(Hye Bin, it finally happened.)
- The third line. - You lost your shabbiness.
(You lost your shabbiness.)
(Is that a compliment or a criticism?)
What was that?
Is he picking a fight?
Why did you criticize her?
- What was that? - It's okay.
It's okay. I mean...
He is picking a fight.
Seriously.
- He knows he won't get picked, - It just happened that way.
so he is picking a fight with an acrostic poem.
- Please choose right away. - Should I choose here?
Yes. It would be better to do it right away.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin, step forward.
Seok Jin is smiling.
(I can see it.)
(I can see myself at Anxious Bench.)
Say either "I am sorry" or "Get lost."
No, I chose him as my partner.
- Really? - Really?
(Does she want to partner up with Seok Jin?)
(Why does she want to do that with the weakest member?)
Congratulations.
(I am happy, but...)
- Really? - In December,
(What about December?)
- you should help those in need. - Hey.
Be quiet.
- Is this a charity? - No, no.
- It's a charity! - Are you serious?
(Then it makes sense.)
Seok Jin seemed...
lonely at heart.
(The one who is chosen and the one who is left behind)
This makes Jong Kook look weird.
- No way. - Jong Kook.
Okay.
- It's okay. - It's okay.
- She is so nice. - Seriously.
She is a saint.
A saint?
You helped the one in need.
This is a disaster.
This time, number six will be revealed.
- Number six. - All right.
- It's neck-and-neck. - The competition is fierce.
- All right. - I am curious about number six.
- Who could number six be? - I am really curious.
Number six, come on out.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan's pick)
(She seems to be an actress in a red dress.)
(Who is this?)
Seon Hwa!
It has been a while.
(She commanded the music industry and made a comeback as an actress.)
(The talented actress visits Running Man for the first time.)
It's Seon Hwa.
- It has been a while. - Seon Hwa.
- It has been a while. - Seon Hwa, it has been a while.
Seon Hwa.
- Seon Hwa, it has been a while. - Hello.
(We are the candidates.)
- Hello. - Have you been well?
- Are the two of you a couple? - This is incredible.
My goodness.
(Gosh, we are a couple.)
What are you doing?
I am happy to see her.
Seon Hwa, in front of you...
are Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
Is there anything you want to ask of them?
- The thing is, - Do you have a question?
I am fascinated.
When I had the preliminary interview,
I picked the person I want the most...
and the person I want the least.
- You told the writers. - That's right.
Both of them are here.
(One is the 1st place while the other is the last place.)
The person you want the most and the person you want the least.
(One of them will go to Anxious Bench.)
The last place.
I don't want to hurt anyone's feelings.
The person who doesn't get picked is the sixth place in your heart.
The two of you should do something.
Why don't you make an acrostic poem?
I am curious about what you will come up with.
Let's start with Kwang Soo.
The first line.
(The first line.)
Time's up.
(Jae Seok moves on.)
(He is a strict MC.)
Time's up.
Since there are other guests, you can't take too long.
- Yes. You shouldn't take too long. - All right.
Make an acrostic poem.
You did a good job when Irene was here.
(This is how Se Chan did before.)
(The first line: What a picture!)
(The second line)
(Irene, I will make sure you sleep someplace warm.)
(The third line: Rinnai)
(How will the rookie of acrostic poem do today?)
- I will give it a go. - All right.
Make an acrostic poem. The first line.
Seon Hwa, may I like you?
(Seon Hwa, may I like you?)
(He is manly.)
The second line.
Seon Hwa, your face...
(Seon Hwa, your face...)
(Is this a confession of love?)
- The third line. - Looks nice with makeup.
(Looks nice with makeup)
(He suddenly talks about her makeup.)
(I have a chance.)
- Do you think you have a chance? - Yes.
- "I can beat this." - Yes.
- "I can beat this." - I got you started.
Kwang Soo is thinking, "I have a chance."
The first line.
I thought about this for a while.
(I thought about this for a while.)
(It's not bad.)
The second line.
- Seon Hwa. - Yes?
(Seon Hwa.)
(I thought about this for a while. Seon Hwa.)
The third line.
I need to use the restroom.
(I need to use the restroom.)
(He suddenly comes clean about his physiological phenomenon.)
What was that?
- I am sorry. - You did a good job.
- Seon Hwa laughed. - Yes.
It's time to make a decision.
She could push the person she doesn't want.
- Really? - It would really hurt.
- Really? - Push the person you don't want.
- I... - The person you don't want.
The person who will go to Anxious Bench.
It's already packed here.
- In 1, 2, 3. - I have a chance.
(Seon Hwa stands in the middle.)
(In her heart, one is the 1st place while the other is the last place.)
(Who is the last place in her heart?)
(Pushing)
(I have a chance.)
(Go to Anxious Bench.)
She pushed him when he said, "I have a chance."
Stand next to Jong Kook.
I feel bad.
Se Chan.
Seon Hwa and Kwang Soo will go to Couple's Bench.
- Okay. - Haha.
Haha, you picked number four.
Number four,
please come on out.
(Did he pick a blonde idol singer?)
(Is this person really an idol singer?)
My goodness.
- Hello. - Ha Na.
(Park Ha Na specializes in playing antagonists.)
(She is back on Running Man after 3 years.)
My goodness. Hello.
- Ha Na. - Please come this way.
- It has been a while. - Yes.
Park Ha Na.
She visited the show after a long break.
(They are happy to see her.)
I should have gone there.
- I should have gone there. - I should have gone there.
I thought there would be an idol singer.
- She might not want me. - If you don't want him,
you could pass over him.
Ha Na, what is your choice? In 1, 2, 3.
Come on.
- Ha Na. - I am sorry.
(I don't want to be your partner.)
(She refuses to be his partner.)
- He must be embarrassed. - My goodness.
- This is good. - Okay.
(She runs to Single's Bench to avoid Haha.)
She's rather be alone than teaming up with Haha.
- You come here. Join us. - My gosh.
She's very gutsy.
(Haha goes to the Anxious Bench and Ha Na, to the Single's Bench.)
Next up is the fifth partner.
(Jae Seok was the only one who chose the 5th partner.)
- Come on out, Na Rae. - It's Na Rae.
- Na Rae, come on out. - Na Rae.
Na Rae.
Na Rae, come on!
(Will this painting be Na Rae's just like everyone expected?)
- How on earth does it look? - Hey!
- Oh, no. - Hey, is it you, Soo Young?
- I'm sorry. - My gosh.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
My apologies.
(Soo Young from Girls' Generation, Na Rae's lookalike)
(She made the complete transition from the idol singer to an actress.)
(She's an elite of TV shows who can sing, act, and entertain.)
Hey, Soo Young.
- How does the drawing look? - Soo Young.
- I thought it was Na Rae. - I'm sorry.
- That's a great drawing. - I didn't know that.
- But the drawing resembles you. - It does slightly.
- You do look like the drawing. - Do you see the resemblance?
- I do see the resemblance. - That's a great drawing.
As you can see,
Ha Na went to the Single's Bench even if Haha chose her.
- Even though you can choose me, - Okay.
you can also go to the Single's Bench.
Or you and I can go to the Couple's Bench together.
All right. Make your decision, Soo Young.
- Show us. - Actually, she and I...
- go way back. - Is that so?
- What history? - Soo Young, reject him!
- Reject him. - Soo Young and I...
have worked on a TV show for a long time.
(Booing)
- That's pathetic! - Soo Young.
- Your lines suck. - Reject him!
Come on, send him to the Anxious Bench.
- He's feeling arrogant. - He'd be a perfect match here.
- All right. - Give him what he deserves.
Soo Young, make your decision.
Will it be the Single's Bench or the Couple's Bench? 1, 2, 3.
(Will she choose Jae Seok and go to the Couple's Bench?)
(Or will she go to the Single Bench for other partners?)
(Jae Seok as my partner?)
I'm sorry.
Okay!
(Jae Seok is decided to head to the Anxious Bench.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay. This is great.
(They come to fetch the new member.)
- So many of them came out. - Let go!
(She chooses to be an awesome single.)
- Choi Soo Young! - Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas. - Choi Soo Young!
- You're on the Anxious Bench now. - Okay.
- Goodness. - What a great move by Soo Young.
- Haha. - That was great.
- Jae Seok. - I didn't want to be her partner.
(Acting childishly)
(She's speechless.)
I didn't want her as my partner either.
- You're saying that now? - This is great for the both of us.
(It's fun to watch this dirty fight.)
By the way, the second guest hasn't come out yet.
- Oh, that's right. - Right now,
no one chose the second guest.
(Because of this scary drawing, the 2nd guest has been overlooked.)
(One by one, the other guests disappeared through the doors.)
(While everyone is having fun, talking to other people,)
(the guest has been staring at the wall.)
You can come to us. Please come on out.
Who is the guest?
- Is he Park Hwi Soon? - Who is he?
(Who is this guest with weird abs and who aren't fully clothed?)
- It's Sung Hoon. - It's Sung Hoon.
(His acting is as firm as his abs, and he's off-the-wall.)
(I ended up introducing myself pretty late.)
- It's Sung Hoon. - I should've chosen that one.
My gosh, his drawing...
Why did he draw that kind of a drawing?
- Hello. - That was Sung Hoon.
Isn't that his photo from the triathlon?
- I guess it is. - Aren't I right?
- It's for the swimming part. - I see. It's his swimsuit.
- That wasn't a zipper. - How many lines do you have there?
- Zipper? - What's that?
Now, the three guests from the Single's Bench can take...
partners from Couple's Bench too.
- Really? We'll go one by one. - Okay, okay.
- Sure. - Ha Na, you will go first.
Ha Na, you're ups first.
- Me? - Yes.
Ha Na, you can call out the person you want to partner up with.
- Really? - Yes.
- Okay. - She glanced at Kwang Soo.
(Which one should I steal?)
(Glancing)
- Okay. - She glanced at Kwang Soo.
(I'm right, aren't I? She really looked at Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo!
(I don't know anymore.)
(She wants to steal Seon Hwa's partner, Kwang Soo.)
- You're popular. - Did you choose Kwang Soo?
- Is it Kwang Soo? - Did you choose Kwang Soo?
He's tempted. He's tempted.
- That serves you right, Seon Hwa! - My gosh, Kwang Soo. Okay!
- That serves you right! - Okay.
- Ha Na chose you, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- Come this way, Seon Hwa. - This is funny.
- My gosh. - There's nothing we can do.
Seon Hwa, I get that you're dumbfounded, but this is a rule.
- This is ridiculous. - There's nothing I can do.
- It's ridiculous, but it's a rule. - Okay.
- First of all, you must choose... - Lee.
(That case, let's do the poem.)
(He holds an acrostic poem contest with his name, Lee Kwang Soo.)
- I have to listen to her poem. - All right. You don't have to.
- No, I'm going to try. - The first line.
Listen to this weird vibe today.
(Yes, it is a bit off.)
The second line.
Kwang Soo, it's me.
(You promised to be my partner earlier.)
The last one.
Squish my suspicion away.
(What? Squish your suspicion away?)
She doesn't want you to get tempted.
- All right. Her poem was so-so. - Yes.
(The beginning of her poem was great.)
- It was so-so. - I want to do it again.
- It was so-so. - How heartwarming.
Ha Na, it's your turn. The first line.
(Ha Na will try her poem with the keyword, Lee Kwang Soo.)
Look at this man. He's quite decent.
(Look at this man. He's quite decent.)
(I'm decent? What does that mean?)
- Kwang Soo likes it. - He likes it.
- She got his attention. - Look at his smile.
- He's smiling. - Oh, no. Look at Kwang Soo.
- Was that line from a drama? - Right.
- That sounded really pleasant. - It was in a drama.
- It sounded like a line in a drama. - Sure, sure.
The second line.
Kwang Soo, you. I like you.
The last one.
(She's good. Seon Hwa is getting nervous.)
- Soo. - Sweep me off my feet, will you?
(Sweep me off my feet, will you?)
(It was the perfect ending.)
- Okay! - That was great!
(I want to sweep you off your feet right now.)
I'm embarrassed.
- Good. - It was a nice twist.
- Good. - Okay. Great!
(Kwang Soo, come on. Go sweet her off her feet.)
- She's cute. - Good.
(She shows off her charms with a bold ending.)
- It was a nice twist. - All right.
Which one will go to the Single's Bench? You may send her off there.
1, 2, 3.
Grab his hand.
(Reaching out carefully)
(Can you hold my hand, Seon Hwa?)
- Okay. Hold his hand for now. - I'm not out yet?
(What is this? Why is he holding my hand?)
(What do you think? You're heading to the Single's Bench.)
(He escorts her to the Single's Bench like a gentleman.)
Congratulations.
(She joins the Single's Bench after losing her partner.)
- That's mean. - Congratulations, Seon Hwa.
You and Ha Na will partner up. Come this way, please.
Next up is Soo Young.
(Soo Young tries to get a partner.)
(You should have partnered up with me earlier.)
Which member do you want to pair up with?
- I would like to... - Okay.
partner up with a member I was mean to last time I was here.
- Who is it? - It's Jong Kook.
(She deceived her partner to the end.)
(Soo Young won the race as the villainous spy.)
(Jong Kook got the water bomb for trusting Jong Kook.)
Okay. Things happen, you know.
(Acting cool)
(He gets rid of any bad memories with Soo Young.)
- That's all right. - Will you understand her?
- Of course. - You can understand that?
Yes, it was for the show.
- I made him get the water bomb. - Right.
- You remember that, do you? - Up until yesterday, Jong Kook...
badmouthed her behind her back. He criticized her a lot.
- What is this? - I'm serious. I don't mind that.
Anyway, since no one has come forward for them,
- these two will partner up. - Okay!
(Jong Kook and Soo Young will partner up.)
It's your turn, Sung Hoon. Sung Hoon.
- I like Sung Hoon. - Me too.
- Sung Hoon. - I like him too.
Let's partner up.
Is there anyone you'd like to partner up with?
Yes, there is. I had this member in mind from the start.
Who is this member?
(I'm the only female member left. Sung Hoon, it's me, right?)
- Who is it? - It's Haha.
- Really? - What about Ji Hyo?
(Haha, do you want to be my partner?)
- Are you all right? - Are you serious?
- Wait. - What is this?
- Ji Hyo is there. What about her? - My goodness.
Poor Ji Hyo.
- Why does everyone like Haha? - What's his charm?
I love it! I love it!
- Hold on. - Haha is mine!
What's wrong with him?
(Haha and Sung Hoon partner up.)
- It's a male couple. - I like it.
Seon Hwa, you must choose now.
All right. Seon Hwa. One...
- With me? - Han.
(Jae Seok, do the poem.)
(Will you do the poem with my name, Han Seon Hwa?)
(My gosh, this is unbelievable.)
You should. You have to.
- Or you should stay as single. - You should do the poem.
- This is your last chance. - You should do it.
- It's the last one. - We should have a great poem.
- Hold on. - We need a great poem.
Exactly. We should have one.
- You must show us. - My gosh. I...
You should take out your hand from your pocket.
- Gather your hands. - Stand up properly.
Stand up properly.
If you can, you should take off your glasses.
- He's all ready now. - You should start the poem.
- There you go. Okay. - Gosh, look at Jae Seok.
- Go ahead. Han. - Han Seon Hwa.
Seon.
Seon Hwa, what took you so long to join us?
- Hwa. - How angry I am!
(I'm so angry that you joined us now.)
- How angry I am! - Great.
- Great. I knew you could do it. - Was that nice?
- Great. - How angry I am!
- Great. - That was great.
- She and I will partner up. - My gosh.
(Jae Seok and Seon Hwa, Ji Hyo and Se Chan)
(Jong Kook and Soo Young, Haha and Sung Hoon)
(Kwang Soo and Ha Na, Seok Jin and Hye Bin)
(Chi Yeul and So Min)
Today's race will be carried out with seven couples.
It's a Christmas Special Race, Flirting Santa Claus.
A special secret is hidden in today's race.
(It's not just a couple's race. There's a secret in today's race.)
- I knew it. - There's a secret.
In the center of today's secret...
stands Jee Seok Jin.
(Jee Seok Jin is in the center of today's secret?)
- Me? - You did something again.
- Really? - I am?
- Do you not know? - I don't know.
(What's the race about where he's in the center of the secret?)
I don't know anything.
(I didn't do anything!)
(Promise me that you didn't do anything)
(The year-end party begins putting aside Seok Jin's secret.)
(It's the ultimate year-end party.)
(Presents are prepared for members who worked hard for a year.)
(As they open up presents, Seok Jin begins to act suspiciously.)
(Is something going on with Seok Jin?)
(A shocking twist that concerns Seok Jin)
I'm on the fifth floor.
(What is the truth that Seok Jin is hiding?)
(The Easy Brothers are back.)