(Paju, Gyeonggi Province)
(Where is everyone? The field is empty.)
(Where are the members? Why is Kim Yoon Sang there by himself?)
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Why are they playing rock-paper-scissors?)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- No! - I'm last.
You're 1st and 2nd. I'm 3rd.
- Okay. - 4th and 5th.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
(Why is she trying to look cute all of a sudden?)
- Wait, hold on. - No, don't do that.
- That wasn't it. - Why did you do that?
I'm rushing.
(We'll reveal why the ladies are filming a clip.)
Make a storyboard and a clip that represents your team.
All right.
Okay. We're starting, Jae Seok.
(It looks like they're preparing to do something.)
Cue.
(It's time, Jae Seok.)
(Can I just walk over there?)
(They're filming under Haha's command since he's most tech-savvy.)
- Great. It's my turn now. - You should give it a try too.
- It's my turn. - Okay.
- You can just press it. - Okay. Get ready.
Get ready.
- I did it. - That's not it, Jae Seok.
I did it right.
(How can you not even do this simple task?)
(Jae Seok feels small when it comes to new technology.)
- Everyone, cup your faces. - 1, 2.
Hold on.
- Wait. Start. - 1, 2.
(He does his best just in case Haha scolds him again.)
We can apply special effects on this.
(Special effects can conceal their looks.)
- This is nice. - My gosh, what is that?
(Team Jae Seok finishes making their clip.)
("Oldies Use New Technology: Why Is Sang Yeob with Them?")
- We can choose songs from here. - Okay. Let's choose one.
(They are looking for the background music.)
- My goodness. - No, let's not choose that one.
No, let's not do that. Let's not use that song.
Come on. Don't use that song.
We can't use my song.
(Smiling)
Jong Kook, this isn't a photo. You need to move in this clip.
- I have to move? - Yes, you have to move.
- I'll move like this. I will. - You will move? Okay.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(Jong Kook is happy that his song is chosen.)
- Should we jump? - Jump?
- Should we jump a few times then? - Yes.
- Get ready. Start. - Five jumps.
(You're lovely from head to toe)
- Okay. - Okay.
- I think we did it. Is that so? - We did it. It worked perfectly.
("He Was Embarrassed to Pick His Song: He's the Happiest")
- It doesn't look unnatural. Great. - It's natural
It doesn't look unnatural
- We should start with gateball. - All right.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan are in the third team.)
- We should... - Thanks for this new character.
- Seok Jin, this isn't a bad one. - What?
This new character isn't bad.
All right. This is great.
The new generation knows how to work this app.
We're starting, Seok Jin. Get ready.
Start.
(He puts on the performance of his lifetime.)
(This looks great!)
- Why are you so good? - Hey.
It went right in.
("Seok Jin, the Promising Player: 1st Talent in 50 Years")
(Amazing! This is perfect!)
Seok Jin, you did a good job filming this.
- It's perfect. - Awesome. This is perfect.
Start.
(Only the ladies remain.)
(Unlike previous teams, they look lovely.)
(These five ladies show off their cuteness.)
You should bend your head like this.
("They Are Friendly Off-Camera: But Fierce During Missions")
Hey, this is funny.
(It's been a while since they rediscovered their cute sides.)
(They are completely focused on the clip.)
That was fun.
- That was interesting. - We could see people...
- waiting in the back. - We could see ourselves.
- I didn't know we'd be in it. - Right.
- That was fun. - It was, indeed.
Hello, everyone. My name is Kim Yoon Sang. I'm an SBS announcer,
your host for the gala show of Running Man's 36-Strategy Olympics.
I heartily welcome you to the show that many national players joined.
Let me introduce you the players of your heated cheers.
They're an assembly of players with great speed.
However, at the end of their chase,
they've always faced unfortunate endings.
This bobsleigh team will run with all their might as always.
(4 players can write history on the ice.)
(Bobsleigh players challenge the limits of mankind.)
(Screaming)
- Get in. Get in now. - Will you get in first?
Get in the front. Take the front.
- Get in the front. - All right.
Sang Yeob, you're next.
(Here we come.)
- Let's go. - Push.
Hey.
- Hey. - My goodness.
- Move it. - What are we doing?
(The fathers are worried that their kids might watch this.)
Doesn't this make you feel embarrassed?
- This is really embarrassing. - I didn't know about this.
You guys are too mean.
- It's our first meeting. I'm sorry. - By the way,
- Yoon Sang should commentate. - Right.
After introducing us, he's looking at us with pity.
- Can he pretend he doesn't know us? - Unbelievable.
- He's really here to host the show. - My gosh.
- He's like a machine. - He's not approachable at all.
Moving on.
(The machine is speaking his lines.)
- I can't believe him. - Seriously.
- He's unbelievable. - There was a global fad of...
- "Young Mi". - Come out now.
They might not have Ms. Glasses,
but they have the charismatic leader, Ji Hyo.
Here's Team Song, the curling team with the best teamwork.
(Team Kim caused a sensation in Korea and all around the world.)
(Team Song will challenge to defeat the mighty Team Kim.)
- Ji Hyo looks like the player. - Ji Hyo does resemble her.
Ji Hyo looks like her.
(Ji Hyo is the charismatic leader.)
(Ji Hyo is the spitting image of the curling player.)
(Everyone seems busy while trailing behind Ji Hyo.)
Move aside.
(Whom is she talking to?)
(What are you doing?)
- I'm sorry to interrupt. - She's cutting the grass.
Move away.
- Everyone, gather up. - That's not it.
Hey.
All right, girls.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
Ji Hyo does look like her.
- You do look like her. - I know, right?
- Ms. Glasses. - Ji Hyo does look like her.
(Young Mi! We need to get the Luxury Package!)
He's the oldest member among the members of Running Man.
- The oldest member? - He shows the perfect chemistry...
with the youngest member. This gateball team is the friendliest.
- Gateball? - What? Gateball?
(You can discover how fun gateball can be in the twilight years.)
(Gateball, the national sport, is the protector of elders' health.)
My gosh.
Seok Jin.
Seok Jin, try to get the ball in here.
- Seok Jin. - What is this?
(Seok Jin shows up.)
Seok Jin, get the ball in here.
(Mr. Jee shows up.)
My goodness.
(He's still going strong.)
(Everyone is moved by his powerful gait.)
Seok Jin, get the ball in here.
(Seok Jin tries to put on a funny skit.)
Don't try to make it funny. Just do it.
Gateball is a good sport for the elders.
(It's the miracle of Mr. Jee.)
- He did it! - Yes!
I'll live a long life!
- This is amazing. - I will live a long life!
- That was awesome. - I told you he could do it.
They proudly represent Korea and are the pride of Asia.
They are the mascots of 36-Strategy Olympics.
Let me introduce you Soohorang and the human-faced bird.
- Who? - The human-faced bird?
- Soohorang and the bird? - What?
(The whole world loved the mascot of Pyeongchang Olympics, Soohorang.)
(The human-faced bird became the symbol of the opening ceremony.)
- It's the tiger. - It's the tiger.
(Soohorang who might be Jong Kook...)
That's Soohorang!
It's the human-faced bird.
(The bird with Kwang Soo's face enters.)
That's the human-faced bird.
- Wait. - That's Soohorang!
(He looks just like the bird.)
That's the human-faced bird.
- He does look like the bird. - Why is he the tiger?
- He doesn't need any disguise. - Jong Kook.
- That's Jong Kook. - He didn't put on makeup?
He looks like the bird even without makeup.
- The human-faced bird... - You don't need the disguise.
He looks just like the bird.
- He's the human-faced bird. - This is how the bird flies.
This is how it's done.
(Fly, bird with Kwang Soo's face!)
Why does he always do this?
Why does he always ride on my back?
All right!
(Hey, there's a party going on here!)
- Why does he always do this? - This is great.
(Kwang Soo is the last one to be introduced.)
Kwang Soo doesn't look any different.
- My goodness. - Of course, I do.
It's a good look on you.
- Seriously. - Did you fight in the waiting room?
- Why do you ask? - Why are you standing so far apart?
It just happened this way.
The programs they are in compete in the same time slot.
Don't be ridiculous.
That's not the reason.
- "Mom's Diary" and "Live". - They compete for viewer ratings.
When I went to the gym, "Live" was on TV.
I told my manager...
to change the channel for Son Heung Min's live match.
He sent me a video of that.
I filmed a video and sent it to him right away.
Why did you...
- Why did you do that? - What?
He doesn't watch the program I am in.
I don't know why he does that.
This is frustrating.
- For goodness' sake. - He is an embodiment of revenge.
I am an embodiment of revenge.
Everyone,
- this isn't the end. - Are more people coming?
- Are more people coming? - Everyone is here.
Are more people coming?
I will introduce the last team...
that completes...
Running Man's 36-Strategy Olympics.
- Really? - Are there more guests?
The real athletes are here.
They are the Formula One drivers of the ice track.
- Really? - The Avengers on ice...
in the national skeleton team,
- Yun Sung Bin and Kim Ji Soo! - Really?
(Yun Sung Bin and Kim Ji Soo of the national skeleton team?)
(Are you serious?)
Really?
(Yun Sung Bin and Kim Ji Soo)
(They are really here.)
Iron Man!
(Yun Sung Min is a gold medalist from the Pyeongchang Olympics.)
(Kim Ji Soo is top 6 from the Pyeongchang Olympics.)
(Iron Man of ice finally comes to Running Man.)
(They give them a warm welcome.)
Hello.
(He bursts out laughing.)
(Kwang Soo's looks make even Iron Man falter.)
(Kwang Soo is happy that he made Sung Bin laugh.)
Hello.
(Celebrities are fascinated by these real celebrities.)
They really came. They really came.
He even brought his helmet.
(They are all over the place.)
- Where should I go? - Stand here.
Stand in the middle.
- Make yourself comfortable. - Stand in the center.
Do as you please.
The national skeleton team.
- The pride of Korea! - Please introduce yourselves.
I am a skeleton racer who competed in the Pyeongchang Olympics,
Yun Sung Bin.
(A gold medalist, Yun Sung Bin)
- It's your turn. - I am...
also a skeleton racer. My name is Kim Ji Soo.
(Top 6, Kim Ji Soo)
This is incredible.
- Will they join us for today? - It's an honor.
Yoon Sang, what is going on?
- They will join you for today. - Really?
Sang Yeob told me that Yoon Sang makes a lot of mistakes...
- during sports news. - Really?
- He is very good at soccer. - Really?
He got hit by a ball he kicked.
(An actual footage of "SBS News")
(The ball hit his face.)
(My goodness.)
(He smiled as if it was planned.)
- Did you do it on purpose? - It was like a comedy skit.
He will succeed Shim Hyung Rae in slapstick comedy.
You know,
Producer So Hyun told me...
that she started out on the same year as Yoon Sang.
"Jae Seok, Yoon Sang needs to be popular."
(Jae Seok, Yoon Sang needs to be popular.)
Speak for yourself!
Speak for yourself, So Hyun.
She told me that Yoon Sang needs to be popular.
Running Man needs to be more popular.
"Speak for yourself."
You said in an interview...
that you want to visit Running Man.
It's Running Man.
That's why you wanted to visit the show.
It will be funny if he and Jong Kook have a match.
Why would you pit me against an athlete in a national team?
I am a singer.
Don't lie! You are not a singer.
People keep misunderstanding me.
Your occupation changed a long time ago.
- My occupation never changed. - You are an entertainer.
Although I can sing well, people said that...
I have a mosquito's voice.
He is incredible.
Sung Bin, you won a gold medal.
I heard that you were affected by it...
for a while afterwards.
I continuously watched a video of the match.
- A video of your match? - Yes.
We do that, too.
- We revisit the good memories. - To be honest,
- we revisit... - Of course, we do.
the good memories.
I didn't do it to relive the touching moment,
but to analyze my techniques.
Watching the video 2 or 3 times is enough...
to analyze your techniques. How many times did you watch it?
No, you have to watch it continuously...
- to catch the minuscule mistakes. - Really?
He showed it to me and said,
"Don't I look cool?"
(He is lying.)
My goodness.
- That's incredible. - He is just like us.
- He is just like us. - That's right.
Watching a video of the match must fill you with pride.
- It wasn't satisfactory. - Really?
Did Sung Bin say that?
No. He said he looked too cool.
(Ji Soo shakes his head.)
That's a good attitude.
He continues to reflect upon himself.
- Who does he think he is? - Who are you to teach him?
It's not like that.
He fixed Park Ji Sung's form...
and Ryu Hyun Jin's workout routine.
He will do the same for them.
Jong Kook has fixed the forms...
of the world-famous athletes.
(Jong Kook's nagging even help win a gold medal twice.)
He has done that.
They are the national treasures.
Sung Bin, when do you begin...
receiving your monthly pension?
- My monthly pension? - That's right.
(Flustered)
You don't have to answer that.
(He is very interested in pension.)
Pension?
Seok Jin is cool today.
He is older than the two of them combined.
(He is older than the two of them combined.)
(25 plus 25 is still less than 53.)
He is so cool. I'm very impressed.
Really?
- How old are you? - I am 25 years old.
My goodness.
The 2 of them combined are 3 years younger than me.
We will answer your question...
if you tell us when you will begin to receive...
your monthly pension, Seok Jin.
I have 10 years to go.
Take good care of your health.
My understanding is the two of you are friends.
Are they the same age?
You must know each other's strengths and weaknesses.
In your opinion, what is Sung Bin like?
They must be close.
Tell us honestly.
- He is cold-hearted. - Cold-hearted.
He stays focused on his goal.
Describing him as cold-hearted before anything...
- makes him sound cold. - Seriously.
Wouldn't "cool-headed" be a better description?
- He is cool-headed. - "Cool-headed" is better.
"When it comes to competitions, he is cool-headed."
- Make sure you say that. - I made a mistake.
It sounds like you said, "This jerk is cold-hearted."
"He is as hard as nails."
Do you have any other questions?
Da Hee.
Did you bring that helmet as a prize?
No, I need to wear it.
(I see.)
(Cold-hearted)
- My goodness. - He is cold-hearted!
- He is cold-hearted. - He is too cold-hearted.
- He sticks out. - Da Hee.
- He has likes and dislikes. - He sounded like he hated Da Hee.
- You know... - She usually doesn't flush.
(Da Hee is knocked out for the first time in Running Man.)
Did something bad happen to you?
(Kwang Soo slanders him.)
- Maybe he hates Da Hee. - He is realistic.
Other members are beginning...
to attack you.
I am sorry.
(I have a warm heart.)
Feel free to ask them questions.
Do you have anything you want to know?
Do you have a girlfriend?
- Han Na. - Han Na doesn't disappoint.
It's perfectly natural to be curious.
- Good job. - Good job.
- Do you have a girlfriend? - Yes, I do.
Ji Soo has a girlfriend.
How about you, Sung Bin?
It looks like Han Na was turned down.
- No, no. - Thank about it.
"Do you have a girlfriend?" "Yes, I do."
It just sounds like it.
You are right.
Maybe he lied about it...
Don't you need to go to the Korean Folk Village?
I am sorry. I forgot.
- I am sorry. - Look at him.
(Kwang Soo gets lost on his way to an ancestral rite.)
If you could team up with a member as a couple,
- who would you choose? - Choose among female members.
Tell us your opinion.
What is...
Step back.
Gosh, she drives me crazy.
I am curious.
(Even Han Na tries to get their attention.)
I would choose...
(What is Sung Bin's answer?)
someone...
who can help me with games.
- Who do you think will help? - It's Ji Hyo.
I wouldn't know...
- until later. - Okay.
- How about you, Ji Soo? - My choice is...
So Min.
(So Min)
- Why? - Why is she your choice?
She is cute.
You have a girlfriend.
Your girlfriend is watching.
(She can't hear anything.)
You have a girlfriend.
- She will be annoyed. - Seriously.
Why are you stepping forward?
- Why are you stepping forward? - Go back.
For goodness' sake.
You know,
I hate that about So Min.
(Me?)
- She knows it's her. - She knows.
- "Me?" - For goodness' sake.
Sung Bin, how about you?
He gave his answer.
Wake up, will you?
He will decide after he sees how good everyone is.
It's like "A Moment to Remember".
He didn't give anyone's name.
(The question and answer session ends thanks to Seok Jin.)
What are we doing with these guests?
Before we begin the gala show in earnest,
since this is a festival,
the athletes prepared a performance.
- The athletes did? - My goodness.
- Who? - The two of them?
Really? The athletes prepared a performance.
For the first performance to open the event.
Haha, Kwang Soo,
- What? - Ji Hyo, and Se Chan...
will swing dance.
I don't even remember anymore.
- We learned it forever ago! - We aren't prepared for this.
- This is ridiculous. - They didn't even know about this.
- Swing dance? - Seriously?
- Hurry up. - That was so sudden.
I don't remember it at all.
I was a human-faced bird, and now, I have to swing dance?
(It's Running Man's one and only talent.)
- What? - What's going on?
(Excited)
(They don't remember how to swing dance.)
(However, their bodies...)
(remember.)
You remember it.
They remember.
(Swing dance is science.)
(Their bodies automatically react to swing dance.)
Your bodies remember it.
(Including a dancing human-faced bird...)
(and Se Chan)
(Even the guests are satisfied.)
(They dance with their jaws dropped.)
- Look at Kwang Soo's face. - Look at his face.
It looks terrible.
He looks so scary.
- He's smiling. - What is he doing?
What is he doing?
(Panting)
It was a great performance.
It wasn't.
- The ending was strange. - All right.
- It's getting more exciting. - What's going on?
- Was that a good performance? - It's Running Man's girl group.
- "Girl group"? - Who?
(Running Man's girl group?)
So Min, Da Hee, and Han Na are up next.
It's "I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S.
- Aren't you good at dancing? - You're up.
- Who is it? - Let's go.
("I'm Your Girl" cover dance)
Do we start on this side?
(So Min and Da Hee look all right.)
- Han Na doesn't know. - She doesn't know the dance.
Pardon? Isn't this it?
- That's right. - Right?
What's going on?
- Wait a minute. - Han Na seems to know it.
Wait a minute.
- Isn't it the diamond step? - It's good that she dances.
She seems to know how to dance, but what's wrong with her moves?
- What's wrong with her moves? - She moves like an old woman.
An old woman?
Her moves are strange. Can you start the dance again?
- I don't know exactly. - One more time.
Play the music.
- I should watch her. - Do you know it?
- What? - I'll follow Da Hee.
Come to the center, Han Na.
I can't dance in sync with them.
Just dance however you want.
- What is she doing? - What?
Just dance.
Look at So Min.
(It's a culture shock.)
Her grooves are strange.
(Dancing)
Doesn't it go like this?
- It looks like... - Right?
It looks like Zumba dance.
- That's right. - You have strange grooves.
(You danced like this, Han Na.)
That's exactly it.
- Is that it? - She didn't dance like this.
- Being excited is more important... - I agree.
- than accurate movements. - That's so interesting.
Excitement is more important.
(Coming up next)
(Trust no one around you.)
(Mysterious happenings during peaceful Olympic games)
(The culprit is among us.)
(Today's real mission is revealed soon.)
It's a big match.
(It's a big match of strength.)
(Who will be the winner, Sung Bin or Jong Kook?)
Now, the special gala show...
will officially start.
Again?
Here's your first mission.
It's Defeat the National Team.
(Defeat the National Team)
Defeat Sung Bin and Ji Soo?
Each team writes and submits games that they're confident about.
Four of them will be selected.
It'll be a team play.
(Teams will play 4 games.)
Really?
Team Skeleton will submit four games.
One of the members in the winning team...
will receive Luxury Package Sticker immediately.
- Immediately? - Really?
(Luxury Package will be given immediately?)
(The sticker is everyone's wish. Shuddering Sticker is a nightmare.)
(To win Luxury Package by turning the final roulette,)
(it's important to win as many Luxury Stickers as possible.)
(Will Luxury Stickers be given out now?)
We must win no matter what.
However, if Team Skeleton wins,
they'll win a gold medal.
Among the remaining teams,
a member of the team that has the highest score...
will be given a Luxury Sticker.
That sounds nice.
Per team, write the game categories that you're confident about.
Per team?
What should we write?
- Let's write a nonsensical one. - Which one?
How about voice mimicry?
- Pardon? - He did voice mimicry today.
- Right. - We'll win right away.
It's something that we can win.
- We must win this. - Right.
- Okay. - Okay.
- It's needless to say. - Okay.
What can we play so that we win?
- They wrote theirs immediately. - I'm good at most games.
They didn't have to think.
Let's write this.
No, that can't be it.
Come on.
- We wouldn't win. - Arm wrestling.
- We can win. - I don't think so.
- You have strong arms. - They're from the national team.
- Just this once. - Sung Bin...
Sung Bin has huge arms.
- His arms are huge. - Do arm wrestling.
(They submit games that they're familiar with.)
(Jee Seok Jin's Game, Human Magnet)
(He looks around carefully.)
(Which game will the national team submit?)
You'll play once four games are selected.
I saw a video of Sung Bin.
In the village for athletes,
he did Sargent jumps.
- He jumped over 1m. - Did he jump vertically?
Yes.
It's very difficult.
Did he jump 1m?
(Sung Bin jumps up over 1m.)
- Goodness. - It's a vertical jump.
That's amazing.
Did you submit it?
Pardon?
- He did. - We will...
definitely lose.
Did they write Thigh Wrestling?
Didn't you do long jumps, Ji Soo?
Yes, I was in long jump.
- Really? - Goodness.
- We have Da Hee. - Da Hee is good at it.
(We have Da Hee.)
Da Hee is good at long jumps.
(She was good at long jumps on Running Man.)
By the way, So Min.
Stop thanking him for selecting you...
during the shoot.
(Stop thanking him during the shoot.)
When did she thank him?
(During break a few minutes ago)
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- It never happened to me. - Why did you?
- What do you mean? - It's my first time...
this has happened to me.
- When did she thank him? - She did.
We aren't teamed up in couples.
Ji Soo was looking away.
(It's because it was my first time.)
"Thank you for selecting me."
(Ji Soo, thank you for selecting me.)
- Why are you thanking him? - Seriously.
Goodness, So Min. It isn't even funny.
Jae Seok, please select the games.
Shall I? I'll select a game.
- Select well. - Of course.
- What you select is important. - Select well.
- We'll definitely win our game. - Right.
I'll pick one.
- Please. - Let's get it.
(What's the first game?)
(Jae Seok picks High Jump.)
(What's this?)
You did write "High Jump".
(Sung Bin wrote High Jump.)
What? Change it.
What do we do?
They're so coldhearted.
Let's play High Jump.
- That's too harsh. - What do we do?
One member from each team participates.
While standing still, jump over mats...
that keep rising.
The team with the highest record wins.
You earn one point.
Pick a representative from each team.
Se Chan will play.
From our team? Okay.
Jong Kook will play.
(Jong Kook plays.)
Sang Yeob will play.
The one who's lightest should play.
- She can't do it. - How about Han Na?
(It's not even close.)
- Da Hee should play. - Try jumping.
Da Hee.
- Da Hee can do it. - She has long legs.
(She makes it very easily.)
You play, Da Hee.
- It's you. You should play. - It requires thigh strength.
Who will play from this team?
(Sung Bin represents Team Skeleton.)
- You're so cold-hearted. - You're harsh.
- You're so harsh. - Seriously.
- You're cold-hearted. - That's cruel.
Are you trying to win from the start?
It's a game, so we should win.
They're so cold-hearted.
(One representative from each team is selected.)
(Se Chan, Da Hee, Jong Kook,)
(Sang Yeob, and Sung Bin)
Se Chan is up.
Jump on one foot.
Se Chan is good at sports.
- And... - It's not a big deal.
Even I could do it.
- Please be quiet. - Okay.
- I'll concentrate. Be quiet. - He's so serious.
- He said to be quiet. - Be quiet.
Machine sounds may also affect the game,
- so turn off all the cameras. - What?
- Will I be shown? - What's wrong?
Where will I be aired?
- Don't you want to focus? - Where will I be aired?
- Really? - Why would you turn them off?
- Come on. - I should be aired.
All right.
Don't make sounds.
Goodness.
It's Se Chan.
- This is... - Se Chan is good.
He's good at sports.
(He lands easily.)
- It's a success. - See?
- That was light. - It's very basic.
- It's light. - You're amazing.
What's amazing about that?
- His jump was so light. - Right.
It was stable.
- Da Hee is up next. - Here's Da Hee.
Let's go, Da Hee.
Let's go.
Can you step aside? We're shooting.
(Are you an audience member?)
I'm in the shoot.
- I'm shooting. - You are?
- He is? - I'm in the shoot.
(She bursts out laughing.)
What?
What? What's wrong?
- She's laughing. - You're making me feel bad.
Why are you laughing at my face? I'm just standing.
Is she crazy? I didn't make any funny faces.
When you were dancing,
this is what she said.
"Kwang Soo is so ugly."
(She thought Kwang Soo was so ugly.)
Can you take those off?
He's cold.
- These are warm. - They keep him warm.
They're uncomfortable to look at.
(His hair looks funny.)
Really?
(Human-faced bird is sad as he is uncomfortable to look at.)
We'll catch you if you fall. So don't worry.
- Okay. - Da Hee. 1, 2, 3.
(She succeeds easily.)
- Good job! - Nice!
Let's beat them!
(They're pretty good.)
- Jong Kook, give it a try. - This?
- Okay. - It'd be easy for him.
Jong Kook has strong thighs.
(Smooth)
He's Running Man's athlete.
(That's my boy.)
He looked a bit pretentious.
What?
- He looked a bit pretentious. - What?
He was like this.
I just wanted to be quick.
I wanted to be quick.
- Sang Yeob. - Sang Yeob.
- Sang Yeob. - Take it easy.
Don't be nervous.
I'm a bit worried.
- Sang Yeob is clumsy. - I'm worried.
(He succeeds with great power.)
Nice.
Good job.
- It was no problem. - It was nothing.
Sung Bin.
(It's the incredible high jumper's turn.)
You don't even cheer for him.
Let's go!
(Relaxed)
His thighs look heavy.
What was that?
(What just happened?)
- Hold on. - He didn't even bend his legs.
(Flying)
He flew.
He flew, didn't he?
- Seriously... - He didn't bend his legs.
Was it the wind?
Were you making fun of us?
I feel humiliated.
- He flew up like Iron Man. - He just flew up.
It looked so smooth.
(It looks effortless.)
(It's no big deal.)
Was it the wind?
He flew, right?
Five mats will be added.
Five? That's a lot.
Will you be able to do it?
We'll fall this time.
It looks difficult.
It looked so smooth.
Seriously...
They just gave these to me and left.
- Are you a staff? - I don't work here.
(I'm on the show.)
- Is there a memorial service? - What?
(He looks like he is attending a memorial service.)
- What are you talking about? - Are you sure?
I'm a human-faced bird.
(Don't get me wrong. I'm a human-faced bird.)
Go.
- You can do this. - From now on...
By the way, why is your makeup so patchy today?
I have a new stylist.
It's her first day.
- Someone new came. - But...
are you shooting a war scene?
(Are you shooting a war scene?)
Does it look that bad? Does it look bad?
Is it patchy?
- Are you shooting a war scene? - Mind your own business.
- Especially this part. - It's none of your business.
Your lips are blue too.
Your face looks patchy.
- He looks like a student soldier. - I have a new stylist.
Start.
It's so high.
It is high.
It is...
(It's a lot higher.)
It is a bit less than 1m.
(It's 90cm tall.)
You can do this. You have to.
You have to do this.
(You have to do this for Team Gateball.)
I'm nervous.
(Se Chan is nervous.)
(It doesn't look as effortless as last time.)
Amazing.
Se Chan.
Sung Bin seems...
impressed too.
Se Chan looks different.
- I don't think Da Hee can do this. - It'll be too hard.
- Da Hee... - You're a bit nervous, right?
You can do this
- You can do this. - It's so high.
- Be careful. - We'll catch you if you fall.
I'll take my microphone off for a moment.
What are you going to do?
- She took her microphone off. - Her microphone...
(Speak into this.)
Are you fishing?
- I just want to catch... - Are you fishing?
everything Da Hee says.
(Jae Seok becomes a sound director.)
All right.
Start.
You're fishing.
(It's 90cm tall.)
- Start. - Let's go.
(The mats are up to her waist. Will she manage?)
(Jumping)
(She slips.)
It must hurt.
She landed on her knees.
- It made a loud noise. - Good job.
- Good job. - Good job.
Da Hee failed. But she did her best.
- It is hard. - It is.
It was too high.
I'm not sure I can do this.
It'd be funny if he failed.
Let me hold the mats.
I did too much leg exercise yesterday.
(After Da Hee's failure, he feels more nervous.)
Gosh.
You can do it.
(Will Jong Kook be able to overcome this pressure?)
His thighs are so big.
(Jong Kook manages 90cm.)
- It looked so smooth. - Amazing.
(Jong Kook is incredible.)
- The male members are all good. - It looked very smooth.
He's surprisingly agile.
- Sung Bin. - It'd be very funny if he fails.
(They're pretty good at it.)
- If he fails... - If he flies again...
- He'll fly this time too. - He will.
He hasn't bent his legs once.
Exactly.
It's as if he has wings.
- He doesn't even bend his legs. - Can I start?
Can I start?
What was that?
(He flies again.)
- He flew again. - How can he do that?
(How can he fly like that?)
It looked like you were flying.
- Do you have wires attached to you? - What is this?
- There has to be something. - Do you have wires?
Are you hiding something?
(Is there something under your sleeves?)
How can he fly like that?
That's incredible.
(While Jong Kook used his knees,)
(Sung Bin effortlessly flew up.)
It's as if someone pulled him up.
- It looked effortless. - He flew up.
Five more mats will be added.
This won't be easy. We'll fail this time.
- I knew he'd succeed. - We can't do that.
He didn't even bend his legs.
Please put them here.
(The mats are delivered by the human-faced bird again.)
Is it really okay to make the old man work?
(He looks like an old man.)
He's an old man.
- We're sorry. - I'm just 34.
- I'm not old. - He looks old.
We don't need a memorial service.
(You came to the wrong place.)
Can you give me a bowl of yukgaejang?
What are you talking about?
You're mistaken.
(I'm just a human-faced bird.)
That looks so high.
It's up to your belly.
- We can't do that. - Let's try.
- It won't be easy. - It won't be easy for Se Chan.
Let me measure it.
- It's 110cm tall. - 110cm.
(It's 110cm tall.)
Se Chan.
- If you pull it off, - Let's go.
- we'll be so impressed. - You can do this.
- It's 110cm high. - There you go.
If you pull it off, you'll be a hero.
Will he be able to do it?
Even Jong Kook is practicing.
It's impossible.
I won't be able to do it.
Se Chan, you can do this.
- You can do this. - You can do this.
I don't think so.
- You can. - You can.
You can.
Se Chan, you look so sexy right now.
(You look so sexy.)
I mean it.
Han Na seems to have a crush on you.
She's been cheering for you the whole time.
- That's not true. - Let me hear her cheer for me.
Han Na is strong, and you're weak.
(A new couple)
If you pull it off, run to Han Na.
- You can do this! - I can do it.
Let's run to her.
(Se Chan is motivated.)
(The height is 110cm.)
(Will Se Chan get to run to Han Na?)
(Fail)
Se Chan.
Are you okay?
(Embarrassed)
(It didn't work.)
Will he succeed?
(Se Chan fails despite the strong motivation.)
- He hit it so hard. - Are you okay?
- Were you trying to be funny? - No.
Han Na says she's embarrassed by you.
(What are you going to do now?)
This is so humiliating.
He hit right into the mats.
- I was startled. - It's so high that I got scared.
Exactly.
110cm is really high.
Jong Kook, do you want me to cheer for you?
- I'm okay. - Are you sure?
- I don't need it. - Cheer for him.
- Cheer for him! - I can cheer for you.
- I'm really okay. - Jong Kook, you can do this.
(Affectionate)
He can't look her in the eye.
(He is forced to accept it.)
Here we go.
(Se Chan failed at 110cm.)
- You can do this. - Let's go.
Let me start.
(It looks almost impossible for a non-athlete.)
I've never done this before.
(Will he pull it off?)
(He succeeds!)
Jong Kook!
(He did it!)
I've never tried it before, so it's hard to know.
Amazing.
- I knew it. - Jong Kook...
His thighs...
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
It's Sung Bin's turn now.
- Okay. - Ji Soo doesn't even...
cheer for him.
Sung Bin, you can do this.
- He is so good. - He'll fly again.
- Fly up. - He'll fly again.
- Look at that. - He flew up.
(Is this even possible?)
(After looking around,)
(he flies up.)
- He flew up. - Unbelievable.
What was that?
He flew again.
It's impossible.
He's like a cat.
It looks so effortless.
- Isn't it so weird? - It is.
- Someone must be pulling him up. - He stays in the air so long.
He can jump so high.
Five more mats will be added.
(Kwang Soo goes to get the mats.)
Is it really okay to make the old man work?
- Five more... - The old man...
The game hasn't even started, but Kwang Soo is already exhausted.
Five more.
- He's exhausted. - I'm not.
This is impossible. It's up to my chest.
- It's not going to work. - No.
- Let me measure it. - Shouldn't we add about three more?
- Hey, this is... - This is it.
- It's about this high. - This is amazing.
- Let's push them slightly. - My gosh, this is incredible.
It's 120cm.
(The height will be 120cm this time.)
120cm.
It was 110cm before. These added 10 more?
- This is impossible. - So tell me.
- How could we do this? - It's impossible.
- All right. - Sang Yeob.
- Me? - Sang Yeob will start first.
My gosh, this is...
(How can I do this?)
Sang Yeob, if you succeed,
- you should shoot action movies. - We'll start now.
I think I can do this.
- Start. - Really?
I think you can do this too.
- He's getting better. - It'd look so cool.
- Our show can unravel... - Hidden talent.
- potential talents of yours. - That's right.
- You wouldn't do this at home. - Never.
- You'd only do it here. - Only on Running Man.
- You can only find those mats here. - You bet.
Besides, who would bring these mats to your home?
I can bring them to you.
(I can bring these mats to you.)
- Anytime and anywhere. - Kwang Soo.
- Bring them in packs of five. - You got it.
- I'll start. - Sang Yeob.
Be confident.
- He's serious. - Do it.
You can do this.
Take a deep breath.
(He will challenge himself to the extreme height of 120cm.)
I'll go now. One...
I made it to the top.
(His feet got caught in the mats.)
- I made it to the top. - That was so close.
- I made it to the top. - It was so close.
You failed, but you were very close.
- His ankle got in the way. - I was on top of the mats.
(Only two contestants remain for the challenge.)
- It was so close. - It's Jong Kook's turn.
- But that was an accomplishment. - It's 120cm high.
- It goes up to someone's shoulder. - Or someone's chest.
Look. It's as high as my shoulders.
It'd be as high as Jin Young's shoulders.
Right?
- Good luck. - Jong Kook.
- If he succeeds, it'd be amazing. - Exactly.
- This is quite a challenge. - His thighs...
- I'll start now. - Okay.
You can do this, Jong Kook.
I'll get the mats again.
(He seems hesitant to jump.)
(After taking a few deep breaths, he jumps at last.)
(Even Sang Yeob, who was confident, failed to jump over this height.)
(The height made Sung Bin shake his head in disbelief.)
(Will Jong Kook be able to jump on top of the mats?)
(His feet could only touch the mats.)
- Jong Kook, you were so close. - What a bummer.
- I couldn't. I couldn't do it. - Try it one more time.
(As Jong Kook fails, Sung Bin feels relieved.)
I couldn't bend my thighs.
- That was so close. - That was really close.
- Give him 1 more chance. - 1 more chance.
- If you let him try it again... - Give him one more chance.
- No, we cannot. - The mats moved.
- The mats moved. - That was close.
- But he could get his feet on top. - My gosh, he did.
- He got his feet on top at least. - It was so close.
- It's Sung Bin's turn. - My gosh, he could do this.
(If Sung Bin succeeds, Team Skeleton will win.)
- He's shaking his head again. - Right now...
- He's good at acting. - Why are you sighing?
- Don't act like you're in trouble. - I know you'll do well.
- But Sung Bin might fail too. - That's right.
- He might not succeed. - Can I move back a bit?
- Han Na... - I'm sorry, but that'd be cheating.
(I'm sorry, but that'd be cheating.)
- He can't move back, can he? - Yes, he can.
- No, listen. - He can do that.
- Then I would've moved back too. - He can move back.
- I thought that wasn't allowed. - Of course, it's allowed.
- It's allowed. It's acceptable. - Then let me move back and do it.
It's acceptable.
(Sung Bin will try it after overcoming many distractions.)
(He flies up again!)
- This was hard for him. - Yes, it was hard.
- This one was hard for him. - It was difficult for him.
(Without any warm-up exercises, he jumps up 120cm.)
(No way. He jumped up that high?)
(It was a bit challenging, but Sung Bin takes the victory.)
Let's see how high he can jump.
- Let's add 5 more mats. - Add 5 more.
- He can do that? - Right now, it's 120cm.
- He'll try 130cm - You think he can do that?
I'm in awe now.
(1m 30cm will be hard though.)
It comes up as high as my chest now.
If he succeeds, he's superhuman.
- It's 130cm. - It's too high.
- Is it higher than your shoulders? - Yes, it is.
- It's higher than her shoulders. - I can only see her face.
So he's trying to jump this high?
It's higher than Jae Seok's nipples.
(It's higher than Jae Seok's nipples.)
- I must explain thoroughly. - Mats are much higher.
- Mats are much higher. - They are much higher.
The mats are this much higher than Jae Seok's nipples.
- That much? - Yes.
Hey, listen.
Our show airs on a weekend night. How could you say that word?
- I apologize. - I'm sorry.
(I apologize for the inappropriate word use.)
- I'm sorry. - You must refer to them indirectly.
- Use "nubbin" instead. - I'm sorry.
(This is a mess.)
What? "Nubbin"?
(That was the refined term.)
Seriously.
- Sung Bin... - It's an honor to see this.
- This really is an honor. - I'm mesmerized.
- This is incredible. - You've never done this, right?
- Have you tried jumping this high? - I'm not sure.
- It's 130cm. - I think he can succeed.
- He can do this? - But this is too high.
- He can pull this off. He can. - He didn't have to frown so far.
- Tell me if he's about to fall. - We'll catch you.
"Falling". Give me a sign.
- Shouldn't we say, "Catch"? - Don't fall.
(The overwhelming height makes a gold medalist nervous.)
All right. Be quiet now.
The staff must be quiet too.
(If he succeeds this time, he will break the record.)
(Chirping)
- Birds, be quiet. - "Birds, be quiet."
(We came here to root for him.)
Be quiet, you stupid birds!
- He did it? - Hey, you.
(He flies like a bird...)
(and successfully jumps over 130cm.)
(I missed it.)
It was the birds.
- I missed it because of you! - You.
(Kwang Soo's yelling was more disruptive than the chirping.)
- How dare you curse? - I missed it.
Let's give it up for him.
(Sung Bin sets the record of 130cm and takes the win.)
- Good job. - Let's give it up for him.
(No wonder he won a gold medal. It was incredible.)
- The record is 130cm! - 130cm.
(Sung Bin sets the record of 130cm for high jumping.)
- It's hard to jump on it. - It's unbelievable.
- It's hard to climb on top. - How did he do this?
- He's incredible. - Seriously.
With Sung Bin's record of 130cm,
Team Skeleton wins.
- They earned one point. - We lost.
(Team Skeleton wins 1 point.)
- For the next game... - I'll choose.
- Sure. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo will pick. - You must pick the one we wrote.
- We wrote games we're good at too. - Exactly.
(As long as they don't pick Team Skeleton's games, they have a shot.)
(Members wrote games suitable for variety shows instead of sports.)
(He looks at them carefully.)
He looks like an ascetic from a Chinese film.
(Let the card that we wrote present itself.)
(He has finally picked a game.)
- What is it? - What is it?
(Will it be a game that's advantageous to the members?)
(It's running. He chooses the wrong card.)
- It's running. - Running?
Hey, you.
(How are we going to beat them in running?)
- What is this? - Why does it relate to lower body?
- Hold on. - What's wrong with you?
You wrote running, didn't you?
Team Skeleton submitted this game.
- It's a 10m race. - If we only play their games...
But why did Kwang Soo choose?
(He's resentful.)
- My legs aren't good now. - I mean... It's just...
(He becomes the scapegoat.)
Kwang Soo.
(His bad luck can't be cured.)
Everyone will start running at the sound of the whistle.
The runner who crosses the finish line first will win.
The winner will earn one point.
How fast can you run 100m?
I can run 100m in about 10 seconds.
10... 10 seconds?
- 10 seconds for 100m? - 10 seconds?
- About 10 seconds? - About 10 seconds?
- What about you, Sung Bin? - Exactly 11 seconds.
- 11 seconds? - Okay.
We might have a shot for a 10m race.
- 10m race? - Not really because...
- he has a fast start. - That's right.
- But you never know. It's 10m. - I forgot about that.
He's faster in shorter distances.
- He's known for his start. - He's the fastest in the world.
(He's the fastest starter in the world.)
(Sung Bin broke the record with 4.59 seconds for his start.)
("He Writes History at Every Game." "The Fastest Starter".)
(This Iron Man with muscular thighs flies on the ice.)
He's the fastest in the world.
Now that we've played a few games with them, I think...
they are very cunning.
(They only wrote games that they'd be good at.)
They only wrote games they're good at.
- We can't do athletic exercises. - Hold on a second.
When athletes star on variety shows,
- they usually win, of course, - Let's have some fun.
but they'd pick games we could play too.
All right. Ji Soo, why don't you come forward?
(Han Na, Seok Jin, Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Ji Soo will go 1st.)
The whistle. Hey, don't cheat.
(Seok Jin from Team Gateball)
- I'm nervous. - Who's going to give us the sign?
- Ji Soo, we might win, you know. - Yes?
- He might not make it. - Of course.
(Ji Soo from Team Skeleton)
Get ready.
(Get ready.)
All right. Hey, your foot.
(His foot crosses the line.)
- Kwang Soo, move back. - Hey.
(This cunning runner gets caught for the false start.)
Kwang Soo has long legs.
- Look at Han Na. - You never know.
- Jae Seok, look at Han Na. - Han Na, that's not fair.
Let her take a step forward.
- No, no. - I can't?
(Matches must always be fair.)
We don't need to sabotage each other.
- That's right. - We have to defeat them.
(The race comes down to the national team and members of Running Man.)
Did you see that? He's leaning forward.
(Starting position for the win)
You should copy him.
- How do I do that? - Lean forward.
- Who will give us the signal? - All right. We have the whistle.
Get ready.
(I cannot lose even if I'm on a variety show.)
- Wait. - Hold on.
- What was that? - Ji Soo.
Can a national athlete do that?
(Embarrassment surges through him.)
- Wait. - I'm sorry.
Can a national athlete do that?
- Must he do his best? - What's wrong with you?
- You're really going to try hard? - I'm sorry.
- Okay. Fine. I'll do it. - I'm sorry.
Do you have to stand in that order?
Let's switch our places.
- Why isn't Ji Soo in the middle? - Right, let's do that.
Light shoulder bumping is allowed, right?
(He pushes with his shoulder even before the start.)
You're being nasty, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo looks like an arch.
Come here, Kwang Soo. Ji Soo, go to the middle.
(The race is already nasty from the start.)
Get ready.
Wait. What's this from the start?
(Jae Seok tightly holds onto Kwang Soo's clothes.)
- Listen. - We haven't even started.
- Don't do that. - We haven't even started.
- What are you doing? - He makes his cheating so obvious.
He grabbed it to feel secured.
That's right. I grabbed it to feel secured.
- Why would you grab it? - Seriously.
- Let's not cheat. - Don't cheat.
- You always... - Don't cheat.
This is sports.
Why are you scolding me? I didn't do anything.
- Don't cheat. - I just don't like your face.
This is just an outfit. I look normal.
- "Normal"? - Goodness.
If you touch, it's cheating, and you'll be eliminated.
- Okay. - Get ready.
(The game really starts.)
(It's a 10m run.)
(Initial concentration could defeat a national team player.)
(10m run starts.)
(They exclaim in an instant.)
(What's the result of this short yet competitive race?)
(Ji Soo springs out as expected.)
(He finishes the race first.)
They weren't even close.
He's so fast.
(National team members are on a different level.)
- He's very fast. - He's really fast.
He's so fast.
Ji Soo places 1st in 2.36 seconds. Kwang Soo places 2nd.
That was so close.
- Good job, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
I was so close to Ji Soo.
(Ji Soo and Kwang Soo make the cut.)
Next up is Sung Bin.
- Sang Yeob. - Yes?
I can do it.
This is the final round.
You never know.
(Sung Bin and Jong Kook compete.)
(Se Chan from Team Gateball)
(Sang Yeob from Team Bobsleigh)
(Sung Bin from Team Skeleton)
(Jong Kook from Team Soohorang and Human-faced Bird)
(Jin Young from Team Curling)
- Get ready. - Get ready.
(This is the actual, final round.)
Set.
(Set...)
(They expected the whistle.)
(He loses his balance.)
(Gosh, what are you doing?)
Can you give us the count instead?
Come on. I thought it was the start.
(He misses the start signal.)
Let's go. Get ready.
Set.
(Jokes are over. It's time to run.)
(It's impossible to predict the result.)
(Team 2 for 10m run starts.)
(It's Jong Kook versus Sung Bin.)
- What? - You're close.
(It's difficult to determine the winner.)
- What happened? - They were so fast.
(Both of them were fast.)
- What happened? - They went in.
I think Jong Kook won.
- Jong Kook was faster. - He's the fastest runner among us.
(Determining the winner on slow motion)
(Jong Kook finished first.)
First place is...
- Jong Kook, and Sung Bin is second. - Both made it.
Okay.
(Do I have to play hard?)
Goodness.
The whole team passed.
Jong Kook might be the winner.
- It's a fight of pride. - We need a plan.
- Let's make a plan. - Come this way.
Two of you, come here.
(Team Soohorang and Human-faced Bird against Team Skeleton)
We've been running for eight years.
- Let's go. - We ran once a week.
That's true.
There's no cheating.
- No cheating. - No cheating.
Stand in between them.
Kwang Soo, why are you standing next to them?
Why are you standing there?
Kwang Soo can do it.
- Show them, Kwang Soo. - Get ready.
- Wait. Wait a minute. - Be careful.
Get ready.
(Their first step needs to be ahead to win.)
Set.
Get ready.
- Start over. - Gosh.
- Come on. - I'm sorry.
(He always starts before.)
- What are you doing? - I'm sorry.
It's a warning.
- He must be nervous. - Jong Kook is being sensitive.
Athletes don't want to come to the show because of Jong Kook.
What do you mean?
It's hard for me too.
It's hard for me too!
- No... - I worked out until 2:30am!
Wait. It's not hard.
Nobody told you to work out.
He's so funny.
It's not easy.
Get ready.
(The war of stars starts.)
(Running Man versus National Team)
Get ready.
(The war of stars starts.)
(Running Man versus National Team)
Start.
(Sung Bin falls down.)
(It's a neck and neck match between Jong Kook and Ji Soo.)
Who won?
(Jong Kook competes against a national team member.)
- Who won? - Who was it?
(Did Jong Kook win?)
- I think Jong Kook won. - Did he?
Jong Kook.
He won.
(They finished almost at the same time.)
- Sung Bin slipped. - He slipped.
That's right.
(Sung Bin falls behind as he slips from the start.)
He usually doesn't do it,
but Sung Bin held the start position during skeleton.
(He held the start position during skeleton.)
However, this time,
- this is what he did. - That's why he won.
- He was determined. - Did he slip?
He started from the skeleton start position...
in the beginning.
(The ice surface was easier.)
This is exciting.
He slipped.
Do we measure based on the head or the foot?
Wait.
(We must be wise about this.)
Wait a minute.
Let's ask Sung Bin.
It's based on the chest.
- The chest? - The chest.
- Is it the chest? - Yes.
- It's the same as marathon. - Right.
That's good.
Did you run with your chest pushed forward?
Is that why?
- All right. - I had my chest forward.
- The winner is... - I pushed out my chest.
(It was a neck and neck final match.)
Ji Soo places first.
(His head and chest finished first.)
His head and chest came 1st, but Jong Kook's foot came in 1st.
- His foot? - Yes.
(Ji Soo's chest comes in 1st. Jong Kook's foot comes in 1st.)
Look, Jong Kook's right foot came in first.
- If it were short track... - Wait.
Short track counts the foot that comes in first.
If it were short track...
All right.
As the result of the 10m run,
since Kim Ji Soo won first place,
Team Skeleton wins. They earn one point.
That was so close.
Let's hear voice mimicry.
We'll play voice mimicry this time.
- It's a relay. - It's a relay game.
The one who can't do it is eliminated.
- That's great. - Do you understand?
It includes animals and objects.
Get ready.
Ready. Start.
"Goodness, stay out of it."
What was that?
(She mimics Joo Hyun.)
- Wasn't she simply cursing? - No.
(If you mumble while cursing, is it mimicking Joo Hyun?)
Then I'd just curse too.
(So Min succeeds.)
- You did it, right? - Yes.
Da Hee?
(Next is Da Hee's turn.)
"Ye Ri, you wench. Mom!"
("Ye Ri, you wench. Mom!")
(Da Hee succeeds.)
- Good job. - Jin Young?
Jin Young?
(Jin Young is here.)
"Hey, what kind of situation is this?"
"I'm upset right now."
She sounds just like her.
(An Seong Daek's line, "What kind of situation is this?")
(She mimics her perfectly.)
She's good.
She sounds just like her.
Next is Han Na.
(Whom will Han Na mimic?)
(Growling)
(It's a new type of mimicry.)
- A dog. - Was she mimicking a sick person?
It works well for her.
Can you be more enthusiastic?
What should I do?
- Just do anything. - Right.
Even I can do that.
What is she doing?
(What is she doing?)
What's that?
- A horse? - No. It's a train.
It's a train approaching from far away.
(A train is approaching.)
Look at her face.
Train, my foot.
(Train, my foot.)
What?
- Wasn't it okay? - She's being unreasonable.
- It's ridiculous. - Hold on.
Wasn't it convincing?
- Wasn't it? - Have you tried it before?
- No. This is the first time. - It is?
- Yes. - It doesn't count.
- Ji Hyo. - I'll do a really short one.
Okay.
"All right."
- Who is that? - What's that?
The SBS voice actor...
I think I recognize it.
Give her another chance.
- Listen carefully. - All right.
- What is that? - That's just your voice.
(Cold)
- I thought it sounded like him. - Seok Jin.
"Hello, everyone, I'm Hwang Su Gwan."
(Fail)
Hey. It sounded just like him.
(This is how Dr. Hwang Su Gwan sounded in the 90s.)
(This is Seok Jin's impression of him in 2018.)
(What's with the judgment?)
We've heard it so many times.
It sounded just like him.
- It sounded exactly like him. - Everyone.
"Smile because it's Monday."
- "Smile big on Tuesday." - It's him.
"Smile for your life on Thursday."
- "On Saturday..." - That's enough.
"I'm Hwang Su Gwan."
- It sounds just like him. - "I'm Hwang Su Gwan."
- Try something else. - What?
Let me try Yoon Si Nae.
- I'll sing "For No Reason". - Okay.
(For no reason)
(I said it first)
- That's Hwang Su Gwan. - That's Hwang Su Gwan.
"Hello, everyone, I'm Hwang Su Gwan."
Young people don't know who those people are.
You just want to fail me.
Maeng Gu sings Jin Young's song, "Goodbye".
- Okay. - Se Chan is good at impressions.
(Goodbye)
(Struggling)
- All right. - Why are you failing all of us?
- Why is that? - No matter what we do...
Didn't I sound just like Hwang Su Gwan?
- "Hello, everyone." - I'll give you another chance.
- "I'm Hwang Su Gwan." - Do something else.
- I'll mimic a water deer. - A water deer.
- A wild water deer. - Good.
I know how they sound.
(How will Se Chan mimic a water deer?)
Why are you failing us?
(This is how a water deer sounds.)
Hey.
That's right. That's how they sound.
- That's how they sound. - It's so funny.
- It counts. - It counts.
- Please start. - A cuckoo.
- A cuckoo. - A cuckoo? Nice.
(Do you want to hear a cuckoo?)
(It might be hard for an athlete. How will Ji Soo mimic a cuckoo?)
(Cuckoo)
(It sounds just like a cuckoo.)
(We're in trouble.)
- I'm in trouble. - It counts.
- It's an animal. - He's good at it.
It sounded just like a cuckoo.
(Compare it to a real cuckoo.)
(It sounds as if two cuckoos are communicating.)
- Oh no. He's really good. - I have to accept this.
- It sounded just like the bird. - I'm not sure what I can do.
- I'll try Raccoon from "Tazza". - Raccoon?
Raccoon?
(Raccoon from "Tazza"?)
(Raccoon is the scene-stealer with a deep voice.)
- I'll be objective. - It'll be short.
(Sung Bin looks shy. How will he mimic him?)
I just need money.
(I just need money.)
(Was Raccoon just here?)
- That's amazing. - It was okay, right?
I admit it.
- He's really good. - What was that?
(Even his mimicry is top-notch.)
Sang Yeob.
(Even the impression genius feels burdened.)
- Yu Hae Jin in "The Pirates". - Okay. "The Pirates".
(Yu Hae Jin in "The Pirates"?)
(Yu Hae Jin played a talkative and frivolous pirate.)
(Sang Yeob takes out his secret weapon...)
(against the versatile athletes.)
- "The Pirates". - Okay. "The Pirates".
"Have you ever been to a beach?"
"It's spectacular."
(It's spectacular.)
(That was spectacular.)
Unbelievable.
- Nice. - "It's spectacular."
Sang Yeob is on fire.
Let me take a break.
- Take care of your voice. - Okay.
- I'll mimic a car. - Okay.
(Roar)
Two cars.
(Roaring)
(It's a novice-level impression.)
- Three cars. - Stop it.
Isn't that a saw?
- Kwang Soo. - What's that?
"Goal." Why?
(Fail)
- What's wrong? - Why?
- It's weird. - It sounded just like him.
- It's weird. - It's Shin Moon Sun.
- Try again. - It sounded like him.
"Shoot me."
- I know that one. - "Shoot me."
- Is that Shin Moon Sun? - No.
Make up your mind.
- Say, "Shin Moon Sun". - Shin Moon Sun.
- Why? - I thought it was Ahn Sung Ki.
- I thought it was him. - It was Ahn Sung Ki.
Is this a quiz?
- Is this a quiz? - Jong Kook.
- I can't do anything. - Then you're out.
"Will I be the king?"
No.
(You won't be the king.)
Jae Seok has already made up his mind.
You're out. Let's start again. Those eliminated can't participate.
One more round.
(Round 2 starts from So Min.)
(Getting ready)
"Hello, I'm Bae Cheol Soo of 'Bae Cheol Soo's Music Camp'."
(Bae Cheol Soo's Music Camp)
Good job.
- She improved. - She's not good.
She's just brazen.
- You just have to be brazen. - She doesn't care.
- She's so brazen. - She is good.
She's shameless.
Da Hee.
"If you keep doing this, you'll end up having bloody stool."
(If you keep doing this, you'll end up having bloody stool.)
(Fail)
Who's that? It's Baek Yun Shik.
(It's supposed to be Baek Yun Shik.)
Jin Young.
(Barking)
(She doesn't stop even when she is eliminated.)
Step back, please.
- "Hello." - Do you have one?
- Kim Hye Soo in "Tazza". - All right.
(Kim Hye Soo in "Tazza"?)
(Kim Hye Soo was frustrated and infuriated in this scene.)
I can shoot you!
(How will Se Chan's version sound?)
"I can shoot you!"
- Stop. - "I can..."
- "I can really shoot you!" - You're out.
- Why? - You're out.
Let me try Grand Prince Suyang.
Grand Prince Suyang. Good.
(Jong Kook failed at it.)
Played by Lee Jung Jae.
"Will I be the king?"
(Will I be the king?)
It was okay.
(Pass)
How was it different?
- What's the difference? - Do it again.
- What's the difference? - "Will I be the king?"
- Aren't I better? - Please do it again.
"Will I be the king?"
- What? - Hey.
What is this?
- I'm being objective, not biased. - Are you serious?
- "Will I be the king?" - I've heard it many times.
Yes.
- Sang Yeob. - "Will I be the king?"
- Sang Yeob. - I'll mimic Jang Hyuk...
saying Choi Min Soo's last line in "Sandglass".
Okay.
- Jang Hyuk. - Look at my mouth.
"I thought I could have you, Eon Nyeon!"
You've done that too many times now.
- This is not okay. - "I can shoot you!"
- "I can shoot you!" - Isn't ours better?
- Which one's better? - "I can shoot you!"
(While they're fighting...)
"Look at these bullets."
(Random)
"Two bullets from Vladivostok..."
- What are you doing? - What are you doing right now?
- What is this? - It's your fault.
- "2 bullets..." - "2 bullets..."
Stop it.
- "2 bullets"? - What are you doing?
(Please come up with something new.)
- If So Min succeeds, we'll win. - That's right.
- So Min. - If she fails, do another round.
So Min, you can do this!
(I need something new.)
(Laughing)
- Isn't that Kim Je Dong? - Kim Je... You're right.
- How did you know? - Isn't that Kim Je Dong?
(How did you know?)
How did I know?
- Do it again. - How did I know?
Do it again.
- It must have been similar. - How did I know?
- It doesn't sound the same. - Do it again.
Do it again.
(Laughing)
Isn't that just a crazy woman?
It's Kim Je Dong.
(Although it's a bit scary, So Min's impression is accepted.)
- It's Kim Je Dong. - I knew it.
The winner of the mimicry contest...
is Team Curling!
(Thanks to So Min, Team Curling wins.)
She'll tell people that she won a mimicry contest.
She's so brazen.
(In a moment)
(Don't trust anybody.)
(The peaceful games are interrupted by mysterious incidents.)
(The culprit is among us.)
(Today's real mission will be revealed shortly.)
(And...)
(The strength competition)
(Who will be stronger, Sung Bin or Jong Kook?)
- Pick one. - To be fair,
- Ji Soo should pick one. - Pick one.
Ji Soo.
(Seok Jin stops.)
Not Seok Jin.
- Please pick, Ji Soo. - Please.
(What's the 4th game?)
What is it?
- Long jump. - It's long jump?
(They have to compete in long jump against the national team?)
- It's all the same. - This is not fun.
Why did you pick that? Pick again.
- This is all they have. - I know.
Why do you keep picking these?
Is this a competition against the national team?
He used to do long jump.
Please pick one person to represent your team.
Who wrote this?
They wrote four,
- and three got picked. - How's that possible?
By the way, who wrote Jee Seok Jin's Game?
Use common sense.
- Even if it gets aired, - This is too hilarious.
you should pick a fun game that we can play with the players.
What is this?
- Why Jee Seok Jin's Game? - It's so much fun.
- It's so much fun. - That's beside the point.
- I wrote arm wrestling. - That's not good either.
His arms are so thick.
That doesn't mean he's good at arm wrestling.
Why did you write "mimicry" then?
What are we supposed to do?
- Who wrote that? - That's not what I meant.
How far did you go in long jump?
- I went to college for it. - He's a former player.
- He's a former, long jump player. - He has no sense of conscience.
(What conscience?)
- What do you mean? - I need to scold you.
From what I heard, there's another long jump player.
- Who? - Yoon Sang too.
- Really? - How far did you get?
I did it in elementary school.
- What sport was it? - Track. I did long jump.
- Really? - Yes.
They usually don't do it in elementary school.
Can you show us?
- Me? - Yes.
(He's surprised.)
I'll try it.
- I had no idea. - It's suede.
(He enters with suede shoes.)
You can be fast in those shoes.
(That was random.)
You can be really fast in those shoes.
Suede shoes are good.
(He gets ready to jump with suede dress shoes.)
He has to wipe the bottom.
(How good is Yoon Sang in long jump?)
I'm looking forward to this.
He has a good body.
He has good proportions.
You're handsome.
Run-up is the important part.
- All right. - I'll start.
Start.
(The siren is heard.)
(It's been a while since I felt like this.)
(At this moment, he's not an anchor.)
(He's a bird with suede shoes on.)
- Why is he making that face? - I know, right?
(Flying)
(His legs spread apart.)
(He jumped over 3m 50cm.)
Are your pants okay?
(He spread his legs.)
My pants ripped.
(Oh, my goodness)
(His pants couldn't withstand his passion.)
(This is an emergency.)
My bad.
I heard his pants ripping.
Why did you make him do that?
(But he made everybody laugh by getting his pants ripped.)
- Are you all right? - It ripped.
Yoon Sang, do you know what face you made?
When you were jumping...
Hey, stop it.
(The investigation has to continue.)
- Stop it. - It ripped.
(The truth of the ripped pants)
- What are you doing? - I wanted to show that it was real.
(They come up with an emergency solution.)
I hope you're okay with this. Are you all right?
You can join us, Yoon Sang.
- You're a great athlete. - I agree.
Let's start with long jump.
We'll have one person from each team.
Let's pick a variety of people.
Let's mix up those who participated before...
and those who didn't.
- Seok Jin... - Stop it.
- Why do you keep picking him? - What's wrong with you?
- His knees hurt. - Hold on.
If he lands the wrong way, his knees will get injured.
- You both ran, right? - Yes, we did.
- Who did high jump? - Me.
- It's his turn to do long jump. - That's fair.
- It's not. - It's okay.
It's okay.
- Please come here. - Good job.
- Good luck. - All right.
- Please give a round of applause. - Let's go.
(Let's go, my team.)
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
- Please go first. - Okay.
- Seok Jin, use your thighs. - Okay.
Ready, set,
go.
(I'm 53 years old.)
(But at this moment, I'm a youth.)
(He looks like an impala in the run-up. He has a strong will.)
(Groaning)
(Collapsing)
There.
2m 30cm.
It's 2m 30cm.
(They feel bad for him.)
I feel bad for him.
What was that?
- What now? - Goodness.
This is not Running Man.
We have to be thankful that he's at least jumping.
Next.
(Kwang Soo, the human-faced bird, is up next.)
You can do it, Kwang Soo.
Ready.
Go.
- Look at his face. - Go.
(The human-faced bird gets ready to take off.)
(Dashing)
Foul.
(Jae Seok calls a foul.)
(He crossed the line.)
- My goodness. - Foul.
(He jumped far, but it's a foul.)
You crossed the line. Foul.
- What? - It's a foul.
- What do you mean? - You crossed the line.
- I did? - How far was that?
That was 4m 30cm.
That's so far.
- 4m 30cm? - Yes.
Who's next?
- Haha. - Yes.
- I've never seen him do this. - Good luck.
- Look at him. - Set...
- You never know. - You don't.
I think he can get over 3m.
Good job.
(His run-up has swag.)
- That looks cool. - Good job.
- Wait. - Hey.
(Halting)
(He's not ready to jump yet.)
- The start looked good. - You looked so cool though.
- That looked like high jump. - Are you doing high jump?
You looked cool when you turned like that.
- You did. - Turn again.
Haha, that looked cool.
(He changes direction.)
- Turn. - Do it.
- Good job. - It's working.
(The shorty's counterattack)
What was that?
(It wasn't enough.)
- He barely made it. - You barely made it on the mat.
(Dream and So Wool, I'm sorry that I'm too short.)
- What was that? - You barely made it on the mat.
Why did you run sideways?
- I should have used my right leg. - You barely made it.
Da Hee.
Good luck.
Ji Soo is holding her hoodie.
(This looks like...)
(a young lady and a butler.)
(He's obedient.)
He looks like Se Chan when he was Alfredo.
- Alfredo? - Yes.
- He looks like Se Chan. - I agree.
- He's like Se Chan next to Han Na. - True.
- He's like Se Chan next to Na Eun. - I can see that.
Good luck.
- Go. - That's not the line.
You never know.
(The long-legged woman with a burning ambition runs.)
(She runs at full speed.)
Here she comes.
(Leaping)
(I'm the advancing Da Hee.)
She made it.
- It's closer than that. - A little bit.
70cm.
It's around 70cm.
(She's first place with 2m 70cm.)
You never know. This might be the highest.
You never know.
Da Hee is good.
Ji Soo is next.
(Ji Soo from Team Skeleton)
- Ji Soo. - Good luck.
(He looks relaxed as he starts.)
(He gets his thighs warmed up.)
(He ran powerfully toward the world.)
(Let's fly again.)
(He actually flies.)
(What was that?)
- Where was it? - He flew.
(This comes from a national-level athlete's thighs.)
- It's 4m 50cm. - 50cm.
He flew.
- That was good. - He's good.
- He's different. - He was so relaxed.
- He flew. - He did.
This is so not fair.
Let's do arm wrestling.
- This won't count, - Okay.
- but let's do thigh wrestling. - Okay.
If those two face off, who will win?
- I'm curious. - Right?
(Everybody is curious about Jong Kook versus Sung Bin.)
- Who's going to play? - This won't count,
so Team Curling doesn't have to play.
- Se Chan. - Okay.
Sung Bin will play from this team.
- Look at his thighs. - I did long jump.
- It's Jong Kook's turn then. - Okay.
You didn't go,
- so go ahead, Jae Seok. - Me?
- He did the impression. - Okay.
His thighs will be split.
- Please come up, Sung Bin. - Is he facing Jae Seok?
- Look at his thighs. - You never know.
Compared to Jong Kook...
I think his are wider...
than Jong Kook's.
(Everybody is focused on his thighs.)
(He trained with over 200kg of weight to strengthen his thighs.)
(His thighs were made like steel through endurance.)
It looks like he's wearing winter pants.
It looks like cotton pants.
Isn't this too much of a difference?
You never know. You have to play first.
- They do look really different. - You have to try.
- Ready. - I though these were his arms.
(Jae Seok's legs look even skinnier today.)
The camera is on top.
- You never know. - You have to play first.
Set...
(They only have 10 seconds.)
(It's game over once your legs split open or your knees touch.)
Set, go.
Jae Seok.
Oh, dear.
(The reality is cruel.)
Did he play with you?
(The unexpected result came in 2 seconds.)
He was testing you out.
His thighs look strong. They do, right?
Hold on. I think I can do this.
(He is filled with a gallant spirit.)
Really? Try it.
- I'll defend. - He's not weak.
Let me do this.
- Ready, set... - Let's go.
Set...
(It's time for Jae Seok to close Sung Bin's legs.)
(Jae Seok was confident.)
(Will he withstand Sung Bin's attack?)
Start.
He can do it.
He's not using any force.
What is he doing?
(This is an automatic door.)
(He's miserable.)
Jae Seok, you'll hurt yourself.
He's making fun of you.
Let go! Let go!
- Stand up! - Turn the cameras off!
This is a battle between Sung Bin and me!
Is this funny? Stop laughing!
(I'm sorry.)
Sung Bin, open your legs.
(Open sesame.)
Move over. This is embarrassing.
This is so embarrassing.
Move over.
- Oh, dear. - Take him.
Take him out.
Go, Se Chan.
Try, Se Chan.
His thighs are like rocks.
(Se Chan takes the mound after the female members cheer for him.)
I was supposed to face Jae Seok.
- Why would you carry this? - Just in case.
(Spraying)
Where are you spraying it?
- That was so random. - Where are you spraying?
This is what you do.
Why would you spray that?
It helps.
Oh, gosh.
- Why would you spray this? - It'll help.
I faced Jong Kook before.
Try it.
Ready.
Put a fist in between.
(Why is there tension between these two?)
(He has thighs of a national-level athlete.)
(Jong Kook has the best thighs in Running Man.)
(He trains them all year round.)
(He's going to write history again.)
When did you not work out?
Goodness.
- Se Chan's thighs are like rocks. - They are.
(Almost everybody knows.)
(He beats everybody he plays.)
(Se Chan has rock thighs.)
(He's the new icon of power.)
(What's the result of this match?)
- You have to exert force. - Okay.
Set, go.
- He's resisting it. - Set, go.
He's resisting it.
- It'll end quickly. - His knees touched.
(There's a sound.)
- His knees touched. - Se Chan.
Did you just fart?
No, I didn't.
- That was the spray. - I heard the sound.
No, I'm just hungry.
You farted. Admit it and ask them to edit it out.
I farted.
I did. So?
That was a weak fart. Why?
- "Weak fart". - I heard the sound.
- That was a weak fart. - Switch.
This might change.
Set, go.
- Oh, dear. - Hey.
Move your hands.
(Splitting)
(Groaning)
(Are you okay, Se Chan?)
Move. Hey.
- Spray this for him. - Is this fun, Jong Kook?
(Is this fun, Jong Kook?)
It's fun, right? You're playing with kids.
No.
You work out, so you play with people.
Jong Kook and Sung Bin.
All right.
Let's do this.
- This is the real match. - You don't know about this one.
But he's so strong. This won't work.
- We wanted to watch this. - Look at his legs.
Look at these two.
This is worth watching.
(It's finally time.)
He's too strong.
- This won't work. - My gosh.
This is a big match.
- His are much thicker. - They are.
But he has some fat.
- That's true. - He has some fat.
I have no fat at all.
Meat like this tastes badly.
(Meat like this tastes badly.)
I'm serious.
- There's no fat at all. - No.
Legs like these are strong.
Ready.
Pay attention.
- It's 10 seconds. - Right.
I'm nervous for them.
- This is no joke. - Jong Kook never faced him.
- I know, right? - Oh, dear.
- Okay. - Set...
(The real trial of strength begins.)
I'm nervous for them.
- This is no joke. - Jong Kook never faced him.
- I know, right? - Oh, dear.
- Okay. - Set...
(The real trial of strength begins.)
(Sung Bin attacks first.)
Go.
Look at Jong Kook.
He's shaking.
Jong Kook can't do it.
(This is a tight match between their thighs.)
(Shaking)
He's shaking. Sung Bin is shaking too.
Jong Kook can't do it.
(They're both flushed.)
Stop.
(Their strengths are similar, so the game ends.)
(The first match is a tie.)
You just have to attack now.
- How was it? - He's so strong.
He's strong.
- He's so strong. - I've never seen...
Jong Kook's legs open this much.
He's strong.
Hey!
(Hey!)
- You have to relax your muscles. - Stop it.
- Stop it. - Hey!
You have to spray it.
- Why would you spray here? - Kwang Soo.
- Stop it. - You might hurt.
Wait, Kwang Soo.
- My goodness. - Hold on.
(Stop it, Kwang Soo.)
- Are you out of your mind? - You can get hurt.
Ready...
(It's Jong Kook's turn to attack.)
- This is incredible. - Don't get nervous.
- Set... - He's strong.
- I'm curious about the outcome. - Hold on.
(They're more nervous than before.)
Set, go.
(This is the last, thigh wrestling match.)
He can't close his legs.
(They're shocked.)
(He tries his best.)
(Frowning)
(This is a tight match that won't end easily.)
(They're exclaiming...)
(in admiration.)
(Jong Kook's thighs are getting closer a tiny bit.)
Stop.
(Game over)
Goodness.
(Jong Kook's thighs closed slightly near the end.)
Sung Bin won a little bit.
- That's right. - He won by a bit.
Jong Kook.
Sung Bin wins.
(Sung Bin wins in thigh wrestling.)
He's incredible.
- No wonder he got gold. - You were both cool.
- How was it? - That was so sexy.
I only watched him on TV,
- and I finally got to play him. - How was it?
- Make this about me. - I applaud him.
- Right? - I just want to applaud him.
- Thank you. - He's so strong.
Make this interview about me.
(What is he doing?)
What do you mean?
After my match,
this could be the interview.
This?
It was just this.
This can go after the match.
I wasn't going to say this, but you were pitiful.
(I was going to hold back.)
- Stop it. - We'll edit it out for your kid.
My goodness.
(This is what Jae Seok wanted to show.)
(Thigh wrestling)
Set, go.
(I came this far with my thin thighs.)
(History is made in thigh wrestling.)
(I, Yu Jae Seok, did it.)
(I bet you were surprised.)
(I only watched him on TV,)
(and I finally got to play him.)
(I applaud him.)
(Thank you for the interview.)
(Did you see that, son?)
That made Se Chan and me look so bad.
Sung Bin has to thank me though. I made Jong Kook get weaker.
He kept on saying that. He said he made Jong Kook weaker.
Stop it.
- Take good care of the elderly. - Okay.
(I feel bad about myself too.)
These two came after a long time,
- but they have to leave now. - They do?
- It's too bad. - It is.
Next time...
Do you want to see better celebrities next time?
(He's joking.)
I hope to perform well again and be invited to this show.
I'll try my best.
(Sung Bin and Ji Soo, we had so much fun with you.)
After the first mission,
Ji Hyo won the Luxury Sticker.
Sung Bin will hand out...
the suitcase with her name on it.
- Suitcase? - What's that?
This? What is it?
(Congratulations, Ji Hyo.)
I'm so envious of her.
What? It's empty.
(There's nothing.)
- What? - There's nothing.
What?
What? Did someone steal it?
(What? Someone stole it?)
(The Luxury Stickers got robbed?)
Did someone steal it again?
- What's that? - Do we get going?
(There's a mysterious message for the Running Man members.)
- What? - What's this now?
(Scout List)
They won't give it to us so easily.
(What list is this?)
What's this?
(Some people are watching.)
- There are 3 people. - 3 people?
(It's a message from three people.)
(Scout List)
(Scoffing)
Are you surprised?
You must have been excited about receiving the Luxury Stickers.
The stickers are in our hands.
We are the coaches who got rejected when we tried to scout you...
for aerobic exercise club. We are currently among you.
(We are currently among you.)
The coaches are among us.
(Are the 3 coaches among us?)
We came here today...
to eliminate the gold medalist who is hiding among you...
and overcome a blow to our egos.
(Are the 3 coaches aiming for a gold medalist?)
If we find the gold medalist first,
your names will be on the Shuddering Package.
If you find us first,
we will put our names on it.
- Shall we begin the real race? - Shall we begin the real race?
(Laughing)
- There are three coaches, right? - We must catch them.
(The three coaches who are in hiding sent them a video message.)
(Who are the 3 coaches?)
- Those are Kwang Soo's fingers. - Those are your fingers.
(Those are Kwang Soo's fingers.)
- It's Kwang Soo. - No one else has such long fingers.
- You... - Why are you ganging up on me?
- It's you. - For goodness' sake.
It's not me!
It's not me! It's not me!
It's not me! Is it you?
- It's not me. - It's you, right?
Don't be ridiculous.
- Look. - It's not me!
- I caught a coach. - We are done.
- What are you talking about? - We caught the three of them.
Why are you catching people already?
They're Se Chan, Kwang Soo, and Da Hee.
- Da Hee. - I am not a coach.
- We caught them. - I am not a coach.
- They are the coaches. - I swear I am not a coach.
They are the coaches.
(Who are the 3 coaches and the gold medalist?)
(Are there coaches among us?)
(Who are the coaches?)
(You can't trust anyone.)
(Don't let them deceive you.)
(However)
(Did someone take these pictures in secret?)
(People are eliminated.)
(You disappear when you get your picture taken.)
(Do you want to live?)
(Suspicious figures...)
(watch the athletes.)
(There are coaches among us.)
(To survive,)
(they must identify the coaches before sunrise.)
(Coaches in hiding...)
(versus the athletes who must find them)
- Who are they? - You are a coach.
(Who will be the winners of this mysterious match?)
(Don't get your picture taken.)
(Family Package Part 2: Find the Coaches)