My gosh, hello.
- Hello. Let me say hello again. - Hi.
- All right. - Hello.
Hurry, and take the side seat.
I haven't been to a rest area for a while.
Rest areas serve great food, my gosh.
I must eat pork cutlet.
- Me too. - Pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlets are delicious. - Or I want udon.
- I had pork cutlet yesterday. - I want to eat udon.
So Min, it seems you didn't go to a salon today.
Seok Jin, what do you mean? Look at my thick makeup.
- Your makeup is thick? - You have makeup on?
- Yes. - The hat. Did you wash your hair?
Didn't actors in "The Age of Shadows" wear it?
Do people wear this kind of hat these days?
- Jun Jin used to wear this. - Really?
Jin used to wear this kind of hat a lot.
- Kye Sang wore this kind of hat. - That's right.
- Members of g.o.d wore it a lot. - It was when they sang "Road".
- It was when they sang "Road". - Exactly.
No, Jang Hyuk wore it first.
- Do you remember that? - Remember what?
- On Ryu Hyun Jin's wedding day... - I don't remember, Seok Jin.
Why can't you remember?
- Don't interrupt me. Why not? - I don't remember.
- Why are you interrupting me? - I don't remember.
Don't stop me. This is important.
- I don't remember the day. - You remember, Ji Hyo, right?
- You already talked about that. - Come again?
- What do you mean? - He already talked about it.
- When did I talk about it? - You talked about it last week.
- I talked about this? - You mentioned it last week.
- Are you sure? - You two talked about it.
Seok Jin, you talked about it during the opening segment.
I see.
What's happening with him?
Seok Jin is flustered now.
There must be an eraser in his head.
He's developing a new character. Seok Jin, player of the gate ball.
"Gate ball"?
(Play gate ball, and live a long, healthy life.)
Today, to celebrate the new year and in light of our wish for you...
to turn over a new leaf through missions, we prepared our race.
The race is Along with the New.
- "Along with the Gods" is popular. - "Along with the Gods".
- Someone might die today. - Someone...
- No, someone will get superpower. - Is that it?
- Don't talk about death. - Hey, by the way...
- It's not that. - I can't help but look at you.
(He chokes up.)
- Hey. - I end up looking at you.
- Seok Jin, stop it. - Yes, stop.
All is fair when it's about death.
- Don't talk about dying. - Promise me that you won't die.
(Promise me that you won't die.)
- I won't die. - Please, Seok Jin.
- I'm not going to die. - The order...
"I won't die."
Why do you think that I'm going to die?
No, I won't. I'm still healthy.
I don't even take health supplements despite my age.
- That's why you should take some. - Take some supplements.
- Take supplements. - Drop the act. Don't let it worsen.
- When you get old, - Right.
going to clinics should be part of your routine.
Stop it. That's enough.
I'm serious.
Before you start your race today, there is...
- a mission to get Chance Cards. - Really?
We'll proceed with Along with a Spending Spree.
(Mission to gain Chance Cards, Along with a Spending Spree)
You won't get a lunch break today.
Starting now, you'll have your lunch.
Come up with an order after discussing among yourselves.
You need to buy food from the rest area within...
- 20-dollar budget in a relay. - In a relay?
If everyone buys a dish, the mission is successful.
If you accomplish your mission, only one member will be...
- given a special Chance Card. - A Chance Card?
If you fail the mission, one of the members will face a punishment.
From the start?
This sounds like it's about loyalty.
Isn't the probability to fail about 90 percent?
It's about 99.9 percent.
I think Se Chan and Kwang Soo should go last.
- No, I won't betray you. - Se Chan and Kwang Soo should.
- Se Chan does unexpected things. - Yes, he does.
- I do that when it's about money. - That's right.
Se Chan should be consistent with his character.
He should be either loyal or traitorous. He acts differently.
Se Chan would keep changing his sides and get nothing in the end.
I tend to change my side.
- He's involved in both teams. - I'm in both teams.
- We should decide the order. - Yes, let's do that.
Should we play the timing game?
- 1. - 2.
(They will go 7th and 8th.)
- It's them. - You two will go last.
- You will go last. - Both of you will go last.
- What are you doing? - You'll go last.
The rest of us should play the timing game.
- One. - Both of you are out.
(Haha and Jong Kook will go 5th and 6th.)
Go over there.
Move down. Ji Hyo, come here.
- I can win by not doing anything. - This is nice.
- You must do nothing to win. - All right.
The four of us can play the game now.
I guess we are inseparable, right?
- Right? - This is great. I like the order.
- Get ready. - What are we playing?
- The timing game. - I can win if I don't do anything.
- 1. - 2.
Three.
(You fools. I can win this game if I don't do anything.)
(What?)
- Move down. - This is weird.
- Move down. - Move to this side.
- Ji Hyo, sit in the third seat. - You're not motivated at all.
- Come here. - Move down.
This is weird. I should've won since I did nothing.
If you do nothing, you'll become a pushover.
Is there a hat festival today?
- One. - We didn't start yet.
We just started.
- I have to say, "Start". - You said, "Start".
Start when I say the word.
You're quick since you look like Jun Jin.
- She's quick. - She's the fastest.
All right. Start.
One.
Two.
- 1. - 2.
(So Min loses just like Seok Jin.)
- Jin, come here. - Move.
- Jin, come here. - Move down here.
I will get to eat though.
Hey, move down. Get out of here.
- I will get a turn, right? Ji Hyo. - Move down.
Ji Hyo and I should play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok will go 1st.)
- I'll go first. - Gosh.
I have a bad feeling about Jae Seok.
Okay!
- Jae Seok shouldn't go first. - Okay.
Hey, don't you know me? I don't...
- You like to spend money. - I'm quite sensible.
- You can spend up to 3 dollars. - Spend only 2 dollars and 50 cents.
- Only spend three dollars. - Jae Seok.
I will eat moderately.
Is today's special about test-takers?
(Is today's special about test-takers?)
- Seriously? Okay, fine. - Look at him.
- I see how it is. I got it. - Your outfit is horrible.
I see. You pointed at me.
- I got it. - Okay.
- I changed my mind. - What's your color coordination?
I didn't change my outfit because I was lazy.
- Buy your food, and bring it here. - Jae Seok.
Just have ramyeon. That's neat.
I had breakfast before coming here,
so I can't eat a lot.
You can't eat a lot.
- You had breakfast? - I had breakfast.
- I don't overeat. - Jae Seok.
- Let's be reasonable. - Don't you worry.
- People don't want us to overdo it. - Don't worry.
- Hey, viewers hate it the most... - Did I upset him?
- when they can't understand us. - Right. They must understand us.
- That's right. - Okay.
I really had breakfast.
(Will he make a reasonable decision?)
What should I eat?
- Hello. - Hi.
(He passes by the food that gives off tempting smell...)
(and arrives at the food court.)
There are a lot of delicious dishes.
What should I eat?
That...
(Jae Seok is entranced by the menu.)
I really want to eat seafood soft tofu stew.
Then I will have...
(Which dish did he choose after contemplating?)
- A dollar. - After looking at the order,
I won't be able to eat.
- I'm not sure about So Min. - So Min...
I'll just have a bowl of udon.
- That's five dollars. - Please let me have udon.
What's taking him so long? Which dish did he choose?
- He must have ordered a main dish. - Why is he taking so long?
(He starts talking out of the blue.)
Just buy fishcake on a stick. Hey, buy a small dish.
(What?)
(Whom is he talking to?)
- There's no one there. - We are at a rest area.
- Seok Jin, no one's there. - Really?
- Whom are you talking to? - You did that on purpose, right?
No one is there, Seok Jin.
I thought he was talking to the Grim Reaper.
Seok Jin, promise me that you won't die.
- Get a grip. Get yourself together. - That surprised me.
We are at a rest area.
- You startled me. - He talked to the empty space.
- I didn't look at that side. - Whom was he talking to?
- I didn't see... - No one was there.
I didn't look there, but rest areas always serve fishcake on a stick.
- Why don't they have it here? - Sorry?
He's back.
- Jae Seok is back. - He's coming back.
- What did he bring? - He has soup.
What is he bringing?
- That's good. - That's not that bad.
- That's pretty good. - That's great.
- How much was it? - How much?
- Jae Seok. - That looks delicious.
- Right? - Give Ji Hyo the rest of money.
(Jae Seok chooses jjajangmyeon.)
- How much was it? - How much?
- Jae Seok, how much was it? - It must be 4 or 5 dollars.
Ji Hyo, take the money, and go.
- How much was it? - Take it, and go.
- I'll be back. - Don't show it. Pick what you want.
- Okay. - What kind of food do they have?
- Are there a lot? - They serve every kind of food.
You sprinkled chili powder.
You bet.
That looks really good. It's steaming.
No, Jae Seok.
- He's going to slurp. - My gosh.
- Right? My gosh. - Goodness.
You won't be hungry for the whole day, Jae Seok.
When he eats noodles, his slurping sounds really tasty.
The shape of his mouth is cute.
When viewers watch this, some of them will order jjajangmyeon.
I agree. He's enjoying jjajangmyeon more than usual.
To be honest, I had breakfast before coming here.
I'm going to eat some snacks.
I want to eat tteokbokki. It's three dollars.
That's expensive.
(Which dish did she choose?)
If everyone chooses a two-dollar dish,
- Right. - it'd be a happy ending.
Let's buy cheap dishes, so Jae Seok looks selfish.
It's really hot.
- Then... - What did you buy?
- What is that? - What did you buy?
- That's so nice of you. - She's so nice.
Ji Hyo. I bet that only cost a dollar.
(Ji Hyo chooses...)
(garaetteok.)
That's garaetteok.
Ji Hyo, will this be enough for your lunch?
- What's this? - Goodness, Ji Hyo.
What are you doing? That's mine!
- That's mine. - Stop that, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin steals garaetteok.)
- What are you doing? - Hey! Shoot.
She gave me the green light that I can take it.
- Really? - No. Ji Hyo didn't do that.
- You gave me the green light. - When did I do that?
- You took it and split it. - Seriously?
- Seok Jin. - Can he do that?
- I apologize on his behalf. - I bet you'll do the right thing.
I'm off now.
- Be back soon. - I'll be back.
I really want to eat udon.
(So Min only wanted to eat udon.)
What should I do?
(Thinking)
"Udon". I want udon.
Actually, I suffered from the flu and gastritis a few days ago,
so I didn't get to eat anything for a week.
I don't even have eggs at home.
I want to eat pork cutlet and udon, but I can only eat one, right?
(She can only choose one. Which dish did So Min choose?)
When I calculated the prices, it's about 4 dollars and 50 cents.
No. Jae Seok's dish costs over four dollars.
- Let's say it's about 5 dollars. - 5 dollars.
- Then it's 8 dollars already. - This must be 2 dollars.
You need to think about why...
the production crew set the limit at 20 dollars.
The games don't pop out of nowhere.
They are actually played at research center.
Is there a research center?
There are staff members who play eight of us.
Did you know that?
Through simulations...
Then the person who plays me must be hot-headed.
That person...
He comes out of prison...
(He comes out of the prison...)
He comes just for the simulations of the games.
That actor was replaced many times.
- Really? - Yes.
- The actor can be replaced. - It has happened many times.
It's not easy to play me.
What's taking So Min so long?
Is So Min back?
- There she comes. - She is back.
- A hat from "The Age of Shadows". - Kim Tak Goo.
There she comes.
There comes Kim Tak Goo.
- What do you have? - How many dishes did she buy?
- How many dishes did you buy? - I only ordered udon.
She gave me pork cutlet for free.
(Udon...)
(and pork cutlet?)
She asked, "You are Jeon So Min, right?"
"Please take this."
Don't lie.
Are you saying it was given for free?
Yes. I only ordered udon.
The employee said the pork cutlet is a wrong order.
There is no way you got that big pork cutlet for free.
The pork cutlet is the main dish.
- No, it's not. - That doesn't make any sense.
Udon usually isn't served...
- in that dish. - That's an earthen pot.
We are counting on you, Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
- We have a good chance. - That's right.
I didn't get a lot of money.
We can make it work.
I only have small bills, too.
So Min.
You know,
I wanted to share with everyone.
Kim Tak Goo, make sure you eat everything.
I don't even have eggs at home.
(She tries to make the members feel sorry for her.)
You live alone.
I am sure she doesn't want to eat this much.
She did it to be funny.
I should think of it as a joke.
It's a variety show, after all.
I can't believe she did that.
My heart is pounding right now.
Before a fight,
elementary school students' heart pound.
I wouldn't say it happens before a fight.
It happens before a beating.
So Min, eat up. You really wanted those dishes.
Jong Kook, my heart is pounding.
I bet my fortune...
that Jong Kook will make So Min cry in two months.
- It will happen in 2 months. - It won't happen in 2 months.
It will happen today.
So Min's dad will call Jong Kook.
"Jong Kook, I apologize."
(I am sure So Min did it to be funny.)
I can't believe So Min.
I got a dollar and 50 cents.
(Does that mean 3 people spent 18 dollars and 50 cents?)
There are eight of us.
Not everyone will be able to eat.
Please give me jjajangmyeon.
(Jae Seok ordered a 6-dollar jjajangmyeon.)
Please give me garaetteok.
(Ji Hyo, who wasn't hungry, ordered a 2-dollar garaetteok.)
Please give me a pork cutlet and udon set.
(So Min ordered a dish that costs a 10 dollar and 50 cent.)
(Worried)
Seok Jin will be able to eat, right?
(The change is a dollar and 50 cents.)
What will I eat with this money?
(What is Seok Jin's decision?)
Seok Jin!
He is nice.
- Really? - He is nice.
- He bought red bean jelly. - He is really nice.
Did you buy red bean jelly?
The current situation left me with no choice.
Really?
- The current situation? - What does that mean?
- Seok Jin, what happened? - Give me the change.
(My goodness.)
There should be at least 10 dollars left.
Jong Kook, get going.
(She feels like she is chewing sand.)
All right.
(Jong Kook leaves with 60 cents.)
Jong Kook.
For goodness' sake!
I can't believe Jong Kook!
(She throws punches as soon as Jong Kook leaves.)
For goodness' sake!
Kim Jong Kook!
Ji Hyo did this in the past.
- Ji Hyo. - The past is repeating itself.
I will rip Jong Kook's name tag and get eliminated.
Hey! Be quiet!
(So Min is like the delinquent version of Ji Hyo...)
(that was often brought out due to Jong Kook's cool-headedness.)
Ji Hyo, I am so upset.
- Seriously. - I understand.
You have a long way to go.
Have you sworn at Jong Kook?
Of course I have.
- There he comes. - He is back.
I think he bought a soda.
Am I wrong?
- No, he didn't. - He didn't.
Seok Jin, please.
Stop imagining things.
You need to be careful.
Is the person with the soda holding a scythe by any chance?
(Seok Jin, it's time to go.)
Stop it!
(Don't follow a stranger.)
He is back. He is back.
Your steps are light.
Of course they are.
I don't have much in my pockets.
You don't?
Didn't you buy anything?
- Didn't you buy anything? - I did.
You bought gum.
- Really? - How much money do we have left?
Was the change enough to buy gum?
(He gives Haha the change.)
What is this?
(He gets 10 cents.)
- He brought food. - Did he bring food?
For goodness' sake.
- Really? - It's better to eat.
- Is that all? - Thus,
the mission fails since you spent over 20 dollars.
Se Chan and Kwang Soo won't be able to eat.
Why did you set the limit to 20 dollars?
It's not the matter of the limit. How much did you have?
I had 10 cents.
(I see.)
I thought you would have 50 cents.
So Min's dish...
- is the most expensive. - In the entire rest area, right?
It's the most expensive dish in the entire rest area.
It couldn't have been a random choice.
I will take a piece of gum as a dessert.
(It's the gum Jong Kook bought.)
It's dessert.
(Eat up, So Min.)
Everyone got to eat something...
except for you and me.
I drank two bottles of water...
- because my throat went dry. - Me, too.
I finished my bottle of water.
Along with a Spending Spree...
was a failure since you spent more than 20 dollars.
One of you will get Penalty Card.
The person with this card will get a penalty no matter what.
It's a game of chance.
- How will we decide? - There is a container of spoons.
That's how a member will be chosen.
(The container has spoons with the numbers from 1 to 8.)
The worst-case scenario is Jong Kook getting the Penalty Card.
Give me the penalty instead!
Spare Jong Kook.
That would be the worst.
He will visit So Min in her dream.
- Pick a number. - Let's go...
- Let's go with four. - That's the unlucky number.
Let's go with four.
The person who gets four will receive the penalty.
Okay.
Don't look.
It will be incredible if he gets four.
Yes, it will be incredible if he gets four.
(Being the unlucky one, Kwang Soo may choose four.)
4! 4!
- Show us right away. - 4! 4!
- It's three. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo avoids the penalty.)
(That's too bad.)
If no one gets it before it's Jong Kook's turn...
Imagine if I picked four.
(He picks 6 and avoids the penalty.)
- 6! Okay! - Everyone, 4 should go...
(Not knowing what the penalty is makes them nervous.)
So Min.
You are done for if Jong Kook picks four.
Then the real nightmare will begin.
Five!
(He picks 5 and survives.)
My goodness.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
(The container passes by the unluckiest ones.)
Everyone.
Look at this.
The numbers that were picked are 3, 5, and 6.
Four will complete the sequence.
My goodness.
It's the empty spot.
- Four is the empty spot. - It's the empty spot.
- If Jong Kook picks 4... - Jong Kook, pick 4.
My goodness.
The envelope is black, your favorite color.
- This is unbelievable. - Pick four.
- If I pick 4... - Pick 4.
The spirit of variety shows is on your side.
(Jong Kook picks the fourth spoon.)
- So Min. - So Min, pray.
- So Min, pray. - Four.
Show us.
It's four!
(He gets goosebumps.)
(The unthinkable happens.)
(The members and the staff are shocked.)
(Furious Jong Kook warning is issued.)
(What should I do?)
So Min!
This is a disaster!
- Did he really pick four? - How did this happen?
- I got goosebumps. - This is it.
3, 4, 5, 6. You filled the empty spot.
I filled the empty spot.
So Min will feel so uncomfortable today.
So Min's face went pale.
She will feel more uncomfortable when the penalty is revealed.
We will move to the next location for Three People Race.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(What is the ending of this ridiculous drama?)
It's a miraculous day.
The chemistry between the national siblings shine.
That's why I am sitting between them.
(That's why I am sitting between them.)
(Jae Seok is my shield.)
Before we reach the next location,
you will have a mission to win the Chance Card...
since you already took the Penalty Card.
(It's a mission to win a Chance Card.)
It's called Pinocchio's Answer.
- Pinocchio's Answer? - Is it about lying?
Answer the producer's three question...
with lies in three seconds.
One of the members who succeed...
will receive the Chance Card.
You know each other pretty well.
If you think a member is telling the truth,
blow the whistle.
Who wants to go first?
- I will go first. - Seok Jin will go first.
- Get ready. - Okay.
Let's go.
What's your real name?
Jee Seok Jin.
(What?)
You're supposed to lie.
- It's so hard. - You should've said, "Ji Seok Sam".
- You should've said, "Seok Sam". - You're right.
- It's not that easy. - Gosh.
- It's hard. - We're...
- launching a new game right now. - I know.
You should have started it right.
- Let's see how good you are. - This is a launch party.
Let's see how good you are.
You shouldn't launch the game this way.
I'll watch you.
Why did you ruin everything?
No one came to our launch party.
- Watch, and learn from me. - Ready.
Start. What do you do first thing in the morning?
Goodness...
(Goodness)
- Jae Seok. - What's different from Seok Jin?
Can't I say that?
- Say your answer right away. - Can't I?
- Say it right away. - All right.
I didn't know.
I get it.
- Let's try again. Ready. - Okay.
Start. How much do you weigh?
I weigh 102kg.
Who do you talk to on the phone most often?
- See? - Well...
Hey, why can't you say, "Angelina Jolie"?
- That'd be okay, right? - "I weigh 102kg" was weird too.
- He didn't have to say that. - Okay.
I get it. You try.
Okay. I'm good at this kind of game.
- Let's try. - Okay.
Start. Do you like So Min?
No... Yes.
What do you call your girlfriend?
Honey.
See?
(Honey)
- Honey. - You do call her honey.
Why can't you say, "Bear Paw"?
(Coaching)
- What? - What are you saying?
If I play like you...
- What is he saying? - You're bad too.
After doing such a bad job, what are you saying?
Why is it so hard?
- Haha, try. - Gosh.
Ready, start. What comes to your mind when you see Jong Kook?
I want to kill him. Hold on.
You mean it.
I was lying.
It's not a lie.
- I was lying. - He even said it to me once.
- Really? - Hold on.
- He doesn't understand the game. - No.
- I was lying. - He meant it.
He meant it.
Ji Hyo, try.
- Ji Hyo, let's try. - Good luck.
Ready, start.
What is your real name?
Kim Jong Kook.
Who are you most uncomfortable with among the members?
That's true.
- That's true. - Why did you tell the truth?
- Hold on. - Why...
Every time someone says something about me...
- Why did she say, "Jong Kook"? - Why is it true every time?
You said, "Jong Kook", both times.
- What's going on? - Jong Kook just said,
"Why is it true every time someone says something about me?"
It might be a lie.
- But it's true. - It might be a lie.
- Jong Kook should try. - Try.
I'll only tell lies.
- Ready, start. - Okay.
- Your best body part? - Neck.
- Your favorite, Haha or Se Chan? - Se Chan.
You have a girlfriend hidden in the US, right?
- Se Chan... - Yes.
After all the things I've done...
Hold on.
He didn't even hesitate.
- He didn't even hesitate. - No one blew the whistle.
I wanted to blow the whistle,
but everyone else was quiet.
I got hurt.
What have I done for the past year?
I've been taking care of him for the past year.
Haha looks so happy.
- I like it. - I lied.
- I was going to blow the whistle. - Give him the last question.
If he succeeds, he'll win a Chance Card.
I did ask the last question, but let me ask another one.
- Okay. - Ready, start.
- Who is the most beautiful actress? - Ji Hyo.
(This is tricky.)
(It's true.)
It's true.
Why is it true?
It's not true.
Something's bothering me.
- I've seen beautiful actresses. - We're just playing a game,
but why do you say each other's name?
It's because she's in my sight right now.
So is So Min.
Do you think I would want to say her name right now?
(Do you think I would want to say her name right now?)
- Even if it's a lie... - Not today.
Who do you want to give a second chance?
I don't think they were fair to me.
Give Haha another chance.
Ready, start.
How tall are you?
203cm.
Who is your favorite, Jae Seok or Jong Kook?
(Who is your favorite, Jae Seok or Jong Kook?)
Jong Kook.
Hold on.
(Jong Kook gets hurt and hits Haha.)
- Hold on. - Jong Kook.
- It's not like that. - This is how I felt.
- I felt this way too. - Hold on.
That's how I felt.
- It's not like that. - That was funny.
- Jae Seok is older. - That was funny.
You're sitting next to me.
Why don't you let Kwang Soo try again?
- He's good. - Let him try again.
- He's good. - Jong Kook...
(Please ask the same question.)
- Give me a question. - Next.
In your life...
(In your life...)
Who's your favorite, Jae Seok or Jong Kook?
Jong Kook.
(He thought it'd be a different question,)
(but it was the same.)
(He gave the same answer.)
(He blows the whistle.)
(Do you hear the whistle? I really like Jong Kook better.)
Both times...
I can't believe you.
Think of all the things Jong Kook has done for you.
- That question was weird. - You're so ungrateful.
I blew the whistle.
Ask the same question to Se Chan.
This is your last year anyway.
I blew the whistle.
- This is your last year. - I blew the whistle.
(Laughing)
- The sound was so loud. - It was.
It sounded like you crushed a watermelon.
Why would you exaggerate so much?
How many people are you fighting with?
It didn't sound like that.
- Do you want to hear that sound? - He's a fighting cock.
He's a fighting cock.
He really is a fighting cock.
He's picking fights...
A fighting cock?
Kwang Soo said it first.
- I said it quietly. - This is so funny.
- A fighting cock? - He said it first.
- I didn't say it, Kwang Soo did. - I can't believe it.
Do you know what's really scary?
Seok Jin isn't saying anything.
(He isn't saying a word.)
He doesn't want to get in trouble with Jong Kook.
He's being so quiet.
I should protect my pride.
- I should protect my pride. - Gosh.
Seok Jin is so...
You failed to win Chance Cards.
(Where is this bus...)
(headed?)
- Where are we going? - Okay.
What's that?
- Wait. - Oh, my.
- It says, "correction". - It says, "correction".
- Where are we? - What's happening?
What's that?
- We're at a prison. - Hold on.
We're at a prison.
Hold on.
At last, you're taking us to a prison?
What's going on?
(The walls isolate the prisoners from the outside world.)
- For real? - Aren't those prison uniforms?
- Is this "Prison Playbook"? - Are we at a prison?
Is this really a prison?
- Are we going in? - Are we going in?
(Welcome to Running Prison.)
- Seriously? - By the way,
this place suits Jong Kook very well.
(This place suits Jong Kook.)
He deserves to be here.
- What are you saying? - It suits him so well.
- He's finally here. - Think of all your sins.
- That's not true. - Think of all the fights.
He's our fighting cock.
As a part of our project, Along with the New,
we came to this place to become new people.
Why would you bring us to a prison?
Why are we at a prison?
- Before we start the race, - We have to escape?
I'll tell you what crimes you committed in the previous mission.
You'll serve a certain time before you're released as a new person.
Along with the New, Crime and Punishment.
- We have to serve time? - We have to serve time?
We have to serve a sentence?
Let me tell you what crimes you committed.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
You committed disorderly conduct by taking off your clothes.
- That's right. - That's right.
(Does he really have a stylist?)
(Jae Seok suddenly takes off his clothes during the shoot.)
(Jae Seok commits disorderly conduct by taking off his clothes.)
I undressed because I was hot. That's disorderly conduct?
Haha committed defamation by ridiculing Jae Seok's style.
Seok Jin committed theft by eating Ji Hyo's rice cakes.
We were just sharing it.
Jong Kook committed verbal violence...
by telling Seok Jin he'd get Alzheimer's.
- That's right. - He deserves it.
- He deserves to go to prison. - He deserves it.
- I knew it. - My goodness.
He committed physical violence by hitting others' heads too.
You committed two crimes.
So Min spent too much money and caused an internal disturbance.
- So Min? - An internal disturbance.
Se Chan committed defamation...
by making fun of Seok Jin.
- Defamation. - Defamation?
Ji Hyo abetted the other members in spending too much money.
- You abetted the others. - Is that a crime?
Kwang Soo.
I didn't do anything.
- What about Kwang Soo? - Kwang Soo.
I didn't do anything today.
Kwang Soo...
I didn't do anything wrong.
didn't do anything special. He neglected his duties.
What are you talking about?
I can't believe this.
This is ridiculous. What are you talking about?
I made you guys laugh so hard.
You neglected your duties.
What are you talking about?
His crime is so trivial.
It's so insignificant.
Hold on.
I committed violence now.
It hurt my pride.
He didn't do anything.
Your sentence will be determined now.
Your sentence will be determined randomly...
- by drawing cards. - This is important.
It'll determine how long you'll shoot today.
- Really? - Really?
- It ranges from 2 hours... - What?
to 12 hours.
- Can we really go home? - Can we really go home?
- Yes. - We can go home?
If you pick 2 hours, you can leave in 2 hours.
For Jong Kook's penalty,
it'll be the double of what he picks.
(Jong Kook's penalty will be doubled.)
- Is it 24 hours if he picks 12? - Yes.
(I need 24 hours)
(He's angry.)
My goodness.
24 hours
- What are you doing? - I meant...
- 24 hours - What are you doing?
I meant 24 hours...
(What did you say?)
(Do you want to be scolded for 24 hours?)
The person who comes in last...
will get self-bathing penalty on top of...
- Self-bathing? - his original sentence.
(The person who comes in last...)
(will receive an additional self-bathing penalty.)
Pick a card in a random order.
- I pick this one. - I'll take the last one.
- Only show it to your cameraman. - I'll take the last one.
Dong Hwan.
- I have a strong feeling about it. - Do you want to switch?
- Okay. - Is it a secret?
- Let's exchange. - It's a secret.
You may exchange them.
(Why is she smiling?)
Okay.
(Sighing)
It's me.
(What's Jong Kook's sentence?)
(It's 12 hours.)
(His sentence is 24 hours.)
Gosh, I can't do this.
Jong Kook's sentence is a minimum of four hours...
to a maximum of 24 hours.
- By the way... - He looks quite upset.
(He doesn't look happy.)
Did he pick 12 hours?
- Did you? - Who picked two hours?
- After the shoot, - My friends.
what you should do...
is go abroad that's over five hours away.
Take a plane, okay?
You'll change into prisoner attire.
Please follow the prison guard's order.
(They enter Running Prison.)
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- Thank you. - Where should we go?
- Why would we go to prison... - This is upsetting.
- for stealing some rice cake? - Seriously.
(They enter Running Prison at 11am.)
This is a real prison.
It's a real prison.
It feels strange.
- Seriously. - Isn't this a movie set?
It is.
- Seriously. - I don't want to go inside.
(The place where they're forced into...)
- Do we go in? - Is this the dressing room?
Do we really go in?
All I did was eat a pork cutlet set for lunch.
Come this way.
(All members are transferred at 11:10am.)
Goodness.
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Their personal items and clothes are kept in custody.)
- My goodness. - I can't believe we're in prison.
What's happening today?
(What's their first mission?)
- What is this? - There's water.
(There are buckets of water.)
- What's the water for? - What's going on?
Before we officially start,
here's your first mission with a chance to increase or reduce...
your sentence.
It's called Wanting to be Forgiven.
(Wanting to be Forgiven)
Confess something you've done wrong to the members.
Based on your sincerity,
others will decrease the hours from 0 to 10 minutes.
Your sentence will be reduced by the total number of minutes.
We're the judges.
The total is 70 minutes maximum.
(It can be reduced by 0 to 70 minutes.)
- 70 minutes? - It's over an hour.
- 1 hour? - Your sentence could be 23 hours.
Is it a life sentence?
It's 1 night 2 days.
- You have to stay here a few days? - What?
Jong Kook will stay here.
- What? - Be careful what you say.
Why did you make that comment?
- She's irritating him. - So Min is irritating him.
Let's see.
You will be slapped by water to be forgiven.
If you don't get slapped by water, your sentence will increase.
Kwang Soo.
(To whom will he apologize?)
Kwang Soo has a lot to confess.
After he gets married...
(Booing)
Get lost.
- I spit on you. - What's going on?
- I spit on you. - What?
- You're ugly. - He's a petty criminal.
- He's a petty criminal. - Right.
- Your cap looks very cheap. - It's in poop color.
His face looks cheap too.
What if he cries?
(Are we being too harsh?)
I won't play.
I won't.
- He already finished. - Is that it, Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo's turn is over. - It's over.
(His turn is over even before he confesses.)
I will confess...
(He wants to ask forgiveness to...)
I will confess to So Min.
- I haven't told this to anyone. - Okay.
After So Min moved to a new place,
she couldn't install the blinds.
I brought my drill to her house...
and helped her put up the blinds.
Why are you asking for forgiveness?
- However, - Did you steal something?
So Min.
I cracked the ceiling.
I'm renting my place.
I'm sorry, but I'm not good at installing blinds.
It was harder than I thought.
There are many men like that.
- Just admit that you can't do it. - That's right.
- Suddenly, Kwang Soo said... - Don't pretend to know.
that he felt hot.
- He only had on a sleeveless shirt. - Sleeveless?
(Sleeveless shirt is the extreme end of being pretentious.)
My goodness.
What are you talking about?
- Shouldn't he be penalized? - What are you talking about?
I wasn't wearing a sleeveless shirt. It's a misunderstanding.
- Kwang Soo wears it often. - No way.
- He took off his shirt. - What do you mean?
- He stretched his arms. - No way.
She's lying.
Stretch your arms like this...
while showing your hair on the belly.
(He punches him.)
- Be quiet. - Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Don't talk while older men talk. - Okay.
This is what's funny. He promised to install the blinds.
He went somewhere while the drill was being charged.
- Then he went to Myeongdong. - Why?
- I don't know why. - Why did you go to Myeongdong?
I went to eat.
(He answers nonchalantly.)
(Did he go eat by himself?)
I went to eat because I was hungry.
- What about me? - What?
- What about me? - You had no food at home.
What's going on between you two?
(They act like real siblings.)
- That's strange. - He went to eat?
1, 2, 3.
- 10 minutes. - Really?
Is it 65 minutes?
(The total is 65 minutes.)
If his sentence is two hours,
- He gets to leave early. - he gets to leave after an hour.
(I'm sorry, but I don't want to forgive him.)
- I don't want to forgive him. - Wait.
That's right, So Min.
That's a good choice.
- I won't forgive him. - Good job.
(His sentence increases by 65 minutes.)
Let's move to the group cell and start your life in prison.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Current sentence minutes)
(Imprisonment finally starts.)
- It looks scary below. - It's scary.
It's scary below. Don't look down.
I can't walk in the middle.
- It's not scary. - Come on.
Be a man.
(They move to the group cell.)
It's a group cell.
It's a real cell.
(This is...)
(This is a cell for 8 people.)
It's a real cell that I only heard of.
"What the cell leader says is the law."
(What the cell leader says is the law.)
- What's this? - It's the restroom.
This must be the restroom.
- Is it a real restroom? - It's divided.
There are toothbrushes for everyone.
We're really in prison.
(Basic needs are prepared.)
- It's cold in here. - Goodness.
(They can't leave until they serve their sentence.)
We can't leave.
- Really? - We're trapped.
- It feels suffocating already. - It's cold.
Gosh, is there a way to escape?
- There's no way to escape at all. - Seriously.
Why are there beans and a millstone?
(Beans and a millstone?)
(Why are there beans and a millstone in the cell?)
Why is there a millstone?
It's a millstone.
This is the cell where you'll be imprisoned.
There are two ways to reduce your sentence.
- Okay. - What are they?
Clear a mission and exchange the sentence with a member...
whom you suspect has less.
If you make a block of tofu by using the tools,
your sentence will be reduced by half.
(If you make tofu, your sentence will be reduced.)
- A block of tofu? - We have to make tofu?
(They can't believe what they hear.)
- Gosh. - Make a block of tofu?
- Soft tofu? - Is it possible?
We're doing everything.
Did you put them here so that we make tofu?
- How can we? - You make tofu...
There are instructions on how to make tofu.
- You're right. - Gosh.
(They can learn how to make tofu in prison.)
What if it takes 12 hours to make tofu?
- No. - It takes a few hours.
Use whatever ways to make tofu.
Then your sentence is reduced by half.
You may ask someone to bring you tofu as well.
- Ask someone? - To bring it here?
We need a phone to call someone to bring tofu.
It's up to you to find a way.
It's up to us?
We can't attach a message to a pigeon or anything.
Should we yell?
Can you go out from there?
Jung Geol!
(He calls his manager.)
(Do you hear me?)
Jung Geol!
(If you can hear me, bring me some tofu.)
Let's start a riot.
(Let's start a riot.)
(We'll attack them instead.)
Start a riot? That's so much like Jong Kook.
If a member who finished their sentence comes back with tofu,
that will be accepted.
- One of us can bring it? - Yes.
Let's ask one person.
However, he can only bring one block.
- Some of us will leave soon. - Right.
- That's true. - If you have two hours...
- For me... - Save one person if you leave.
The saved member can save someone else.
- Then we can all leave. - After two hours...
- We work as a team? - Would that work?
I don't think so.
- Someone will betray. - We can help each other.
And the cell leader has absolute power.
You must obey the cell leader.
The cell leader can send the members to the solitary cell.
(The cell leader can put members in solitary confinement.)
- That sounds fun. - Do you remember that time?
He went to the solitary cell, but the cell was the paradise.
- Right? - That did happen.
- I was the leader. Do you remember? - Right.
(He was dragged to the solitary cell for infuriating the cell leader,)
(but it turned out to be paradise.)
(However, there are 2 solitary cells today.)
(What kind of secrets are hidden in these solitary cells?)
Whenever the bell rings, you will vote to select the cell leader,
- so it may change. - We are going to vote?
If you vote for me, I'll make...
- a peaceful environment. - Can you swear to that?
I won't betray you.
Ji Hyo never betrays us.
- You know that, right? - Ji Hyo...
- Then I'm sorry, but... - We should team up.
- show us a special talent. - Okay.
Dance for us.
We have no choice here.
- Show us your dance. - Okay.
(Seok Jin dances right away.)
There's no music.
(Ambition exudes from his dance.)
Ji Hyo, you should interrupt him and start dancing.
(Ji Hyo, the 2nd candidate, starts dancing.)
(The first cell leader is me, it's me)
- Ji Hyo, don't forget me. - That's great.
- Okay. - There you go.
One of them will be the cell leader?
Is this how we're going to vote for the cell leader?
- Vote now. - Hey.
- They must be authoritative. - What else can we do?
- In that case... - You guys are too mean.
This isn't how it is in dramas.
- They are powerful. - Stop talking.
- How can cell leaders... - There's no other way.
- What about recent songs? - Which one knows recent songs?
Sing the most recent song you know.
(Sing a recent song among songs you know.)
(Growl)
("Growl" by Exo is the title track of their 1st album in 2013.)
- That's the most recent song? - Growl
(It sounds like a Korean traditional song.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Growl - Growl
(It's a different song. It only shares the same title.)
Growl
- Growl - All right.
(It's when "Growl" meets Korean traditional music.)
Okay. Sing us a more recent song.
You'll win as long as you don't sing "Chunhyangga".
- I have a song in mind. - Go ahead.
(For Ji Hyo, "Hot Issue" has been popular for 8 years.)
(Which song will she sing this time?)
(Are you leaving me?)
- Great. - That's it.
- Ji Hyo, sing a bit more. - You're almost there.
(She sings another line.)
She got it right.
(Babbling)
(She sings it out of nowhere.)
What are you doing?
(After babbling...)
(You can't fool anyone, Ji Hyo.)
- What's wrong with Ji Hyo? - What are you doing?
Is this how you're going to do this?
(Why does she keep doing this?)
At that time, he came to her.
All right.
Should we vote now?
Which one should I vote for?
(6 members cast their votes to decide the first cell leader.)
- I'll announcement it now. - Okay.
- One of you will be chosen. - Okay.
(To whom will the honor of becoming the first cell leader go?)
The first cell leader is...
(1st candidate, Seok Jin, 2nd candidate, Ji Hyo)
Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin, the ambitious one, is elected as the cell leader.)
- Mr. Cell Leader. - Mr. Cell Leader.
- Get away from me. - Mr. Cell Leader.
- Hey, get away from me. - Mr. Cell Leader.
I love you.
- Go away. - Mr. Cell Leader.
(Seok Jin is elected after twists and turns.)
(What kind of environment will he make for the cell?)
(Remaining sentences)
He became the cell leader just like the other time.
Hey, whoever voted for me should sit down.
- Okay. - You should stand over there.
- Se Chan, go stand over there. - That's right.
- Jong Kook, you can sit. - Thank you.
- Kwang Soo, goodness. - The cell leader...
(The prisoner who's on bad terms with him...)
- What are you doing? - Move aside.
(The hated prisoner is forced to turn the millstone.)
- Do your best. - Hey.
- So Min. - Yes?
- Sit. - Okay.
- Stand up. - Okay.
- Whom should you listen to? - Okay.
Whom should you listen to?
- Seok Jin. - Stand up.
But it looks like Jae Seok is the cell leader.
(But it looks like Jae Seok is the cell leader.)
Exactly. You should help Seok Jin out.
- Jae Seok looks like the leader. - You.
- Jae Seok, you should go first it. - My goodness.
- You're getting under my skin. - This is...
- I wasn't trying to do that. - Who is the cell leader here?
We let you become the cell leader.
You "let" me become the leader?
I was the one who helped you get it.
- Haha. - Yes?
- You're off now. - Move.
- Go grind it. - You'd better move.
- Grind it. - Come and grind this.
Do you want to join our gang?
Yes, I'll serve you for the rest of my life.
- Go! - Grind it now.
- Turn the millstone. - How could he change so quickly?
- Is this how you'll play this? - Go work.
- Are you serious? - I told you to grind it.
This is a bit...
- Do as you're told. - Goodness.
(Obey the cell leader.)
- Wait until the next election. - Hey, kid.
- Kid. - I got it. "Kid"?
- Take off your glasses. - By the way...
- Hey, hey. - That little jerk.
I wish you'd be more kind to the cellmates,
- What did you say? - sir.
- Send him to the solitary cell. - You should try...
My goodness.
- I should do that, right? - Yes, it'd be great.
(Why don't you put him in the solitary cell now?)
Hey, I was just...
(Solitary cell)
- Go to the cell. - What?
- You're scaring me, so go now. - The solitary cell.
- Seriously? - Go to the cell.
This is power!
- See if you can get out of here. - My goodness.
You know what? I was curious about the cell anyway.
I was curious about the solitary cell.
(So Jong Kook is dragged to the solitary cell.)
I can't believe he kicked me out to the solitary cell.
I made him the cell leader.
There are two solitary cells.
Choose the one you like, and enter.
(He will choose between the 1st and 2nd solitary cell and enter.)
(The 2 solitary cells give off a creepy vibe.)
(What secrets lie beyond the doors?)
I'll choose the Solitary Cell One.
(Jong Kook chooses the Solitary Cell One.)
Okay.
(The door of the Solitary Cell One opens at last.)
(What is the shocking secret...)
(Jong Kook will face inside the cell?)
- Hey, guys. Get some rest. - Yes, sir.
1, 2, 3.
What's this?
- You already did that much? - Yes.
(The bucket is full of bean extract, ground by the millstone.)
- Hey. - Ji Hyo has a knack for this.
Ji Hyo is good at cooking too.
(Master of tofu)
(When the rest of them were busy settling their ranks...)
I think we can make a block of tofu.
- You think so? - I think we can do it, no?
(Ji Hyo took over the millstone quietly.)
- I think I am good at this. - Let me help.
You are good at this.
We can make tofu with that.
I think we can make about two blocks of tofu.
(Can they make tofu and reduce their sentence?)
- Wait. He's back. - Jong Kook, you're back.
Look at him.
- Did you get splashed? - What happened?
(What goes on in the solitary cell?)
- What is it? What happened? - He's staring at Seok Jin only.
He's only looking at Seok Jin.
What on earth happened?
(He came back wet. What happened in the solitary cell?)
I elected you as cell leader.
Seok Jin.
- What happens in there? - His pants are completely wet.
Hey, Jong Kook.
I only...
sent you there because the cell leader...
I sent you there because I thought it was a paradise.
Did you just put your hand on me?
(He's startled.)
- Get some rest. - Rest up.
(The bell rings.)
- Everyone. - We'll change our cell leader.
- Okay. - Give it back.
All right. You will elect a new cell leader.
Everyone, please help me win the next term.
The second cell leader has been voted.
- It's Jong Kook. - Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin's era is over.)
Face the wall.
(Of course, I should face the wall.)
- "Face the wall". - That's so downgrading.
He sounded so serious. My goodness.
(I'm all right.)
(The cell leader's word is law.)
With the incumbent cell leader, you will complete...
- a mission for a Chance Card. - Okay.
- It's the Voice of the Scene. - "The scene"?
(A Chance Card is at stake.)
You will listen to the intro of a randomly chosen film.
If you guess the film in order, the mission is successful.
- It's about films? - Whoever guesses...
the most films will receive the Chance Card.
(The winning member can acquire a Switch Card.)
(Which 1 of these members will obtain the Switch Card?)
You can come up with the order to guess the films now.
It may be advantageous if you go first...
or go last.
This... Tell you what, Jong Kook.
Listening to the beginning of the film won't be advantageous.
So start with Jae Seok,
- then Kwang Soo. - No, you shouldn't.
- Make them go first. - You should go sixth.
- There are eight of us. - Okay.
- Going fourth is good. It raises... - Okay.
- your chance. - Seok Jin will go first.
(Okay. Seok Jin will go 1st.)
- Jae Seok will go second. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo, you're third. - What about...
You should go fourth.
Going fourth isn't that bad.
(Let me think.)
(What about me?)
I'll go fourth.
So Min wasn't chosen.
- She won't go in the beginning. - The fifth place...
The member in fifth place is likely to guess the correct answer.
- Haha. - Thank you, Jong Kook.
- That's not fair. - It's not fair at all.
You favor Haha the most.
I'll go 5th, and he'll go 6th.
After Se Chan,
Ji Hyo will go.
Isn't it nice?
So Min is last.
So Min...
You won't even give her a chance.
- Right. - It will be the hardest for her.
All right. I'll play the film for the first quiz.
The traffic jam during the morning rush hour has completely subsided.
(It's from the first film.)
This is bad.
I think I know which film it is.
This is...
I bet...
- it's a disaster film. - Five.
It's a disaster film or a film with a monster.
I know the answer.
"The Host".
- "The Host". - "The Host".
"The Host" directed by Bong Joon Ho.
(That's incorrect.)
(That was close.)
That wasn't even close.
I'll give you the next line.
- Play the film. - It won't be my turn anytime soon.
The traffic is smooth on Dongbu and Seobu Expressway.
- It's a traffic report. - Hold on.
Traffic is moderate on Dongbu Expressway and Seobu Expressway.
Is this traffic radio?
- Hold on. - Is this supposed to be a movie?
- This is... - I might have a chance.
- 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. - 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Okay. Whose turn is it now?
It's my turn.
Play the next line.
On Gangbyeon Expressway and Olympic Expressway,
traffic looks good all the way...
from Cheonho Bridge to Banghwa Bridge.
- That was short. - Isn't this just traffic radio?
(What is this movie?)
- "The Tunnel". - I think that's right.
("The Tunnel")
(Is it correct?)
I was thinking of that one too.
- It's wrong? - It's wrong?
(Kwang Soo is wrong.)
I thought it was correct.
- Really? - I was thinking of that one too.
- Ha Jung Woo is in it. - Ha Jung Woo is in it.
I thought it was "The Tunnel".
Here goes the next line.
There's another piece of news.
(I know it.)
Another piece of news?
I don't remember the title.
Ha Jung Woo is in it.
In the radio booth...
I watched that movie.
- 5, 4, - Hold on.
- 3, 2... - That's too fast.
(Surprised)
Don't count down so fast.
- 100, 99, - Hold on.
- 98, 97... - 98, 97...
It's supposed to be two syllables...
No.
- No. - "The Terror Live".
("The Terror Live")
"The Terror Live".
(Correct)
I knew it too.
- I knew it too. - I can't believe I remembered it.
(The movie starts with a traffic announcement.)
(It's a thriller movie starring Ha Jung Woo.)
(Congratulations, Jong Kook.)
- Do you remember it now? - Yes.
- "The Terror Live". - Now, I remember it.
- Here we go. - I'll get it right this time.
- Start. - Ghosts...
(The second question)
I know it.
(Roaring)
No resort in bird sanctuary!
I know this one.
(No resort in bird sanctuary!)
- I know this one. - What is this?
- Gosh. - I know it.
You have to know this.
- Haha. - It's obvious.
- What? - Yes.
- "1987: When the Day Comes". - Gosh.
- What are you talking about? - "1987: When the Day Comes"?
It's still showing at cinemas.
There's no way they'd play it here.
- Kwang Soo. - The next line.
- Play it. - I want to get it right.
The title is...
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
- Withdraw! - Withdraw!
They repeated the same word.
If I tell you the answer,
- can you move me up? - They repeated the same word.
- Okay. - I'm serious.
Can you discuss with others?
5, 4, 3,
- 2, 1. - 2, 1.
"A Violent Prosecutor".
("A Violent Prosecutor")
It's correct.
I was right.
I was right. Move me up two spots.
- Move me up. - Okay.
- It's with Gang Dong Won. - Okay.
I knew it was the one with Gang Dong Won.
(The movie starts with a protest to protect a bird sanctuary.)
(So Min was very impressed by Gang Dong Won's swindler role.)
- Can you move me up? - Which place do you want?
Me?
The one before you.
The one before me? Okay.
Wait. Is that tofu?
- Tofu arrived. - What?
(Tofu arrived?)
(Tofu arrived.)
Tofu arrived.
How did it get here?
- Tofu? How did it get here? - How did it get here?
(How did the tofu get here?)
It's for Jong Kook.
How did it get here?
- It's for Jong Kook. - How did it get here?
What happened?
- Okay. - How did he do it?
- I'm so relieved. - You should eat it.
Did you make it in the solitary cell?
He must have done something.
- He must've carried out a mission. - He must have made it there.
Send me to the solitary cell.
(What happens in the solitary cell?)
There must be something...
in the solitary cell.
(What's the secret of the solitary cells?)
Number eight.
Send me to the solitary cell now.
Can I send someone to the solitary cell?
- Yes. - Send me now.
Guys, there's more than one solitary cell.
You should know that.
- That's up to you. - Right.
- The solitary cell... - You wanted to go.
See you.
Thank you. I'll see you in a while.
- See you. - Go to the solitary cell.
(Haha is looking forward to winning tofu.)
Hello.
I'm a model prisoner.
Please choose between...
the two solitary cells.
(Haha has to choose.)
(Let me see.)
I choose number two.
- Okay. Please go in. - Okay.
(Haha chooses number 2 unlike Jong Kook.)
(What's in solitary cell number 2?)
What's that?
What's that? Wait.
(Pots?)
(Let me sit down.)
You're in the solitary cell with pots.
You'll be splashed with water.
That's it?
(Really?)
What's going on?
Please splash the water. 1, 2, 3.
(Splash)
(Soaked)
(Can I get tofu now?)
You can go back now.
(That's it?)
(All this cell has are pots.)
Gosh.
What is this? Jong Kook took a lot longer.
(What was in the solitary cell Jong Kook went to?)
- I choose number one. - Okay.
(What was in solitary cell number 1?)
(Spend some time alone in the cozy solitary cell.)
(You can take a break from the cold and hunger here.)
I thought I'd be penalized.
(This is nice.)
There's a phone.
(There's a cell phone?)
Can I use it?
(He can talk to someone outside.)
- Hello. - Deok Jin.
- This is Jong Kook. - Hi.
Can you get me some tofu?
Excuse me.
- Do you have tofu? - Yes.
- Please give this to Jong Kook. - Okay.
- Tell him he can take his time. - Okay.
(After secretly asking for tofu...)
Is there some water?
Please give me some water.
(He wets his clothes to deceive others.)
(This way, they won't suspect anything.)
(That's how he had tofu delivered.)
Is this all?
Wait.
(I don't believe it.)
Hold on.
Let me go to cell number one.
Please let me go to a solitary cell.
Let me go.
Let me go to a solitary cell!
Please!
(Haha only got penalized.)
- Haha is back. - Ji Hyo.
Please send me one more time.
What did you do?
Right now.
- No. - No?
- What happened? - Please send me one more time.
Hit me once.
(Kicking)
Go to the solitary cell.
Haha will go to...
- the solitary cell. - What's going on?
- What's there? - Ji Hyo.
(I'll choose cell number 1 this time.)
Cell number one.
- Between the 2 cells... - I choose number 1.
(He chooses number 1 without hesitation.)
(Angry)
Hey!
(Why are the pots here again?)
(The cells switch all the time.)
(Gosh, I'm so unlucky.)
(Splash)
(He's splashed for the 2nd time.)
I'll be right back.
(Angry)
(Haha only got splashed with water.)
Let's continue with the quiz.
- Okay. - Okay.
Before that,
- Se Chan will be released. - Okay!
- Why? - Okay!
- Se Chan will be released. - Yes!
(Every member picked a sentence card.)
(Se Chan's sentence was only 3 hours.)
(It's not bad.)
(His sentence even got reduced by 70 minutes.)
(Se Chan is released...)
(after serving his sentence.)
- Yes! - Has it been two hours?
- Please get me tofu. - Was his sentence two hours?
Please get me tofu.
- Please. - Everyone, worship me!
Se Chan.
- Everyone, - I won't ask for more.
- serve me. - Please.
Please change.
- Is he really getting out? - You can go.
Can I really go?
Can I go home?
Yes!
I could come back with tofu, right?
I should go back to tofu-making.
Worship Se Chan
- Please. - I'll remember you.
- Guys. - Se Chan.
- So Min, you've been so quiet. - Se Chan!
- You... - Have a good life.
Live for yourself. Don't ever come back here.
What are you talking about?
I don't believe you.
Take care of yourself first. Goodness.
Don't come back to this dirty place.
Go live a happy life, punk.
(He leaves prison without lingering feelings.)
(The mission to win Chance Cards starts.)
Who will win the card?
Play the movie.
(Third movie plays.)
(A door opens.)
(Sound of heels clacking on the floor)
(The sound continues. Gosh, it's nice to meet you, ma'am.)
It's nice to meet you, ma'am.
(Jong Kook is 1st, Ji Hyo is 2nd, and Jae Seok is 3rd.)
(I think I recognize the movie.)
(If Jong Kook is wrong, Ji Hyo and Jae Seok get a chance.)
Goodness.
What's your answer?
"The Thieves"?
(He makes a guess.)
(If he's correct, Jong Kook wins.)
"The Thieves".
- That's right. - Is that correct?
("The Thieves" is correct.)
That's what I thought at first. I knew it.
(It's a scene from "The Thieves"...)
(where Jun Ji Hyun and Shin Ha Kyun meet.)
Did Jong Kook win?
I have to switch with someone.
One of you will be released very soon.
Really?
(Jong Kook's life will change if he switches with this member.)
- Is it three hours? - This is your chance.
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
- It's worth it to try. - You can switch with me.
By the way, why are you so quiet, So Min?
- Wait a minute. - What?
- Listen. - Can we leave?
- So Min? - She's so quiet.
- So Min is... - Isn't she so calm?
- She seems disconnected from us. - Right.
- She's so quiet. - She's not saying much at all.
She sympathizes with you because she's being released soon.
So Min.
(He chooses So Min.)
- Jong Kook switched... - No way.
- No. - his sentence with So Min.
(Jong Kook and So Min are enemies.)
(They switch their sentences.)
- All right. - I'm curious.
The two of you will check your sentences after switching.
We'll turn our backs.
(What was So Min's sentence?)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
What's wrong?
(Did you read my sentence?)
- Goodness. - Gosh.
My goodness.
(Her sentence is 10 hours.)
- I can make 20 blocks of tofu. - My sentence is...
Let's see.
(What was Jong Kook's sentence?)
- I can make 20 blocks of tofu. - My sentence is...
(It was 10 minutes.)
(So Min gets 2 hours of sentence.)
She started making tofu.
- Why are you making tofu? - Why?
Why is she making tofu?
- She's suddenly making tofu. - She wouldn't make tofu.
I got goosebumps.
What happened?
- What happened? - What is it?
My goodness.
- What's going on? - What happened?
What happened? Why are you about to cry?
What happened? Is it good or bad?
- What happened? - Ji Hyo.
- Please send me back once more. - I want...
- Please. - I want to go to the solitary cell.
- Do it before I hit you. - Are you the cell leader?
Please send me once more.
- That's a threat. - It's a threat.
- That's a threat. - Yes.
- Don't send him. - Please just once.
- Don't send him. - It's the last time.
I won't ask for it anymore.
(A whistle blows.)
- What? - Jong Kook is released.
(Jong Kook is released.)
(Laughing)
- Really? - His sentence was three hours.
It was him.
- That's why... - Is this possible?
- you made tofu, didn't you? - This is real victory.
(Thanks to So Min, he's the 2nd to be released.)
(Thanks to you, I can smell the fresh air.)
- Goodbye, So Min. - Jong Kook can hit Haha.
- Be happy, Jong Kook. - I will.
Don't we get another chance?
Is the four-hour sentence next?
There's one more mission left.
- One more. - Is that so?
Until...
6pm...
(The one who has the most by 6pm must serve their sentence.)
Unless something changes,
the person who has the longest sentence by 6pm...
will serve the entire sentence. Then they'll get a self-bath.
That will be So Min.
- Don't leave me. - It's So Min.
You have a chance to switch.
We have a chance, right?
(Who will win the last Switch Card?)
- I still have a chance. - If someone brings you tofu...
Why do you keep making tofu?
From the back, she looks like a tofu expert.
(She's almost like a tofu expert.)
She has bits of beans on her. Doesn't she?
(She has a 10-hour sentence.)
Is it colder outside?
It's chilly.
It's cold.
(They get to exercise outside.)
- It's very cold. - It's been a long time.
(Kwang Soo is moved.)
I haven't been out in so long.
There's sunlight.
(They almost forgot about the warm sunlight.)
It's good to be outside.
He's trying to escape.
(He runs fast.)
You could get shot.
(How dare he try to escape?)
(I was only jogging.)
This is great.
(So Min approaches the producer.)
- Wait. - What is it?
Kwang Soo was about to steal it. I'll keep it here for now.
(It's her precious tofu.)
(While the others were playing,)
(she turned the millstone.)
(She kept turning it...)
(and worked hard.)
(So Min completed a block of tofu.)
(Please protect my tofu.)
Among us, who has the least...
amount of sentence?
- I can't tell you. - Really?
I bet it's Kwang Soo.
- It's Kwang Soo. - What?
- I bet it's Kwang Soo. - It's either Kwang Soo or Seok Jin.
I think it's you.
(I doubt it.)
Will Jong Kook bring some tofu?
- I think he left with Se Chan. - Why doesn't he?
He's not bringing back tofu.
(Who will be released next?)
Here's the mission for the last Chance Card.
- It's Red Light, Green Light. - What is it?
(Red Light, Green Light)
The one who will be It...
is our new producer who was a drill instructor in the military.
(He's the new producer.)
- A drill instructor? - Really?
(It's nice to meet you.)
- He used to be a drill instructor. - Hello.
He'll give you an order before saying "Red Light, Green Light".
If he gives an order of two people looking at each other,
you must look at each other to not be eliminated.
Either tap him and come back to the safety line,
or be the last person to survive.
- That's how you win. - I'll win.
You must choose a partner who won't betray.
- Right. - I'll play with Ji Hyo.
- You know that I won't betray. - I want to play with her too.
You know that I won't betray.
- Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo, let's play.
Let's cooperate until the end.
- I don't want to play with him. - I have to survive.
- Me neither. - Do you promise me?
I'll support you.
Here is some tofu
(It's a surprise.)
- Se Chan! - Hey.
(Have you been waiting? I brought tofu to save you.)
(It's tofu. No, it's Se Chan.)
Se Chan!
Here is some fresh tofu
(Fresh tofu will reduce their sentence by half.)
(That's mine.)
- Se Chan. - Se Chan.
(So Min loses her slippers.)
(Give that to me, Se Chan.)
- Here's some tofu. - Se Chan.
- Hey. - Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - Here's some tofu.
(Se Chan plays hard to get with his tofu.)
- Pass it to me. - Se Chan.
- Come here. - It's tofu.
(Follow me if you want it.)
- Here's some tofu. - Se Chan, please.
Give me some tofu.
Se Chan, look at me. I was too excited to see you.
I was excited to see you.
(Her feet are covered with mud.)
It's not because you're excited to see me.
- Your shoes are too big. - Right.
I'm desperate.
(I'm desperate for tofu.)
- Prisoners. - Yes, sir.
I can't hear you. Prisoners!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
- That's not enough. Sit down. - Yes, sir!
- Please, sir. - Se Chan.
One of us will get to leave soon.
Give it to me.
(Give the tofu to me.)
(I want to go out into the world with that tofu.)
Move back.
(He becomes authoritative.)
You're funny. That was hilarious.
Se Chan, it was a funny comment.
- Unbelievable. - I'm serious.
Everyone has their reasons.
- How about this? - What?
Hide the tofu somewhere on the second floor.
- The first to find it gets it. - That's a good idea.
- That's not a bad idea. - Right?
Please fix Kwang Soo's microphone.
(Kwang Soo's microphone falls out.)
- It fell off. - Let's leave him out.
- What? - Leave him out.
What does it have to do with my microphone falling off?
(The battery in the microphone is being changed.)
- How... - Get lost.
Why would I?
- You didn't take care of yourself. - He didn't take care of himself.
Haha is right.
- What do you mean? - You didn't take care of yourself.
- Line up after Jae Seok. - Okay.
Jae Seok, Haha,
- and Ji Hyo. - He didn't take care of himself.
Am I excluded?
(Pushing)
(He takes his anger out on a staff member.)
(Things likes this only happen to Kwang Soo.)
Am I excluded?
(Gosh)
I'll hide it on the second floor.
- Finders keepers. - Okay.
Kwang Soo will be excluded. Seok Jin...
- and So Min are included. - Thank you.
- I'll be fast. - Okay.
(I'll find it and reduce my sentence to half.)
- It starts as soon as I come out. - Okay.
Some people might get released right away with that.
I bet some people will.
(While Se Chan hides the tofu, they play a game.)
Should we start playing a game?
Yes, let's play Red Light, Green Light.
If I find that and make tofu,
my sentences becomes one-fourth?
You have to try your best, Kwang Soo.
I'll risk my life. All right.
- Be my partner, So Min. - Okay, I like that.
- Be my partner, Seok Jin. - Okay.
- We'll both be fine. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Let's get started.
Lie down on the ground.
Red light, green light
(Lie down on the ground.)
(Collapsing)
Seok Jin is out.
I'm sorry.
(He pretended to lie down.)
- Seok Jin is out. - I'm sorry.
- You're out. - Goodness.
Haha went on his belly.
- No, I looked to my side. - He went on his belly.
- He went on his belly. - He did.
Haha is out.
(He's in an awkward position.)
Ji Hyo is on her side!
He never said to lie on your back. You just need to lie down.
- Are we done? - Yes.
- We should have another chance. - Go in when Se Chan comes out.
Next command.
Put your arms around each other's shoulders.
Red light, green light
(Put your arms around each other's shoulders.)
I didn't hear that.
I'm your partner.
(Arguing)
Jae Seok.
(They're still near the start line.)
- Jae Seok. - We have to go forward.
- Jae Seok. - Next instruction.
Make a sexy pose.
Red light, green light
(Make a sexy pose.)
(They try their best to be sexy.)
So Min is not sexy.
(He picks on So Min.)
(How's this? Is this sexy?)
(I approve.)
(4th instruction)
Grab each other by the collar. Red light, green light
(Grab each other by the collar.)
(Grabbing)
We have to go forward.
Get into a push-up position.
Red light, green light
(They move up a lot.)
Green light
So Min is in bare feet.
(So Min is very motivated. She's barefoot again.)
(Kwang Soo is slow.)
Kwang Soo is out.
- You got caught. You're out. - Come.
You're out, Jae Seok.
- Kwang Soo is out. - Come.
Don't be so greedy, Kwang Soo.
Hurry up, Kwang Soo. We have the next instruction.
They're in push-up positions.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Next instruction.
Touch your nose with your tongue. Red light, green light
Hey, how can you do that?
(How can you do that?)
Jae Seok is out. So Min did it.
(Why can't you do this?)
Jae Seok is out.
My gosh.
This is impossible.
- Jae Seok is out. - Jae Seok is out.
Look at this guy.
My tongue doesn't touch my nose. I can't do it.
They told me to do it.
Gosh...
Ready.
(He's done hiding the tofu.)
Set, go.
(He's done hiding the tofu on the 2nd floor.)
(Whoever finds it gets to have it.)
It's on the second floor.
Go wild. It's on the second floor.
I have to find this.
- I have to find this. - Me too.
(If you find the tofu, your sentence gets halved.)
(While they look for the tofu, the game continues outside.)
Where did he hide it?
Where is it?
Make a cute face. Red light, green light
(They act cute.)
Make a heart...
(Ji Hyo touches his back.)
Red light, green light
(They have to run to the start line.)
Oh, dear.
(Falling)
(So Min shows slapstick humor.)
(Ji Hyo sprints back.)
Ji Hyo wins.
You can go look for the tofu.
I have no luck today.
So Min, you have no time.
Go up, and find the tofu.
Go on the second floor.
(Did they find it already?)
My socks are wet.
My shoes are wet too.
Why are you only looking in the cells?
(Seok Jin takes out something.)
(He found the tofu.)
(A few minutes earlier)
(He found the tofu by the 2nd floor railing.)
- Goodness. - Where did it go?
(He hid it inside his clothes.)
(Giggling)
I have it.
You found it?
Where did you find it?
(Where was it?)
- Where did you find it? - You just put it there.
I did.
- You found out. - Your sentence...
is halved.
Okay.
Ji Hyo wins this game.
- Wow. - Good job.
You can switch your sentence with another person.
Before that...
- It's the cell leader. - Who?
Jae Seok is released.
(Jae Seok is released this time.)
- Jae Seok. - I knew it would be him.
(He picked 4 hours,)
(the 3rd shortest sentence.)
There's another person who is soon-to-be released.
- There's another person? - Yes.
(I want to switch with that person.)
Let's go. Friends.
Change your clothes.
(I'm going back into society.)
Friends, I...
It's Jong Kook. Run.
(Have some tofu.)
Jong Kook!
It's Jong Kook. He has tofu.
- Jong Kook! - Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook. - Please.
I beg you. Please.
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Please.
- My sentence is so long. - Let's go.
- Jong Kook. - I have 10 to 11 hours.
- Jong Kook. - What did you do?
The tofu is here.
- Where's my tofu? Who did this? - He has tofu.
Somebody took it.
- Go to Jong Kook. - Somebody took my tofu.
(She checked her tofu a few minutes earlier.)
(Why is there a white towel instead of tofu?)
(So Min's missing tofu case)
(I know. It was you, right?)
- I don't even know where it is. - Jae Seok.
It's you, right? It's Jae Seok.
(Suspect 1 is Jae Seok who just got released.)
It's not me.
Think about those who didn't leave to look for the tofu.
- Give it back. - It's not me.
(Suspect 2 is Kwang Soo who was left here alone.)
- Give it back. - Find it for her.
It's not me. This is not fair.
Who took my tofu?
I was playing the game, and they put a towel in here.
- How many years do you have? - Kwang Soo.
Is it the same as before?
It is. Only an hour has passed.
Here.
(Take this tofu, So Min.)
(Jong Kook, you're giving this to me?)
- He's being nice. - I switched...
with her.
- Jong Kook. - He switched with you.
You're acting so warm.
- Thank you, Jong Kook. - It's nothing.
I worked so hard to make that tofu.
I know. Good job.
But that tall jerk...
(That tall jerk took it.)
It's not me, punk.
Hey, don't fight.
- What's going on? - What was that?
I hope they kiss.
My tofu, gosh.
It's not me.
Who is it?
You'll get punished. I hope three generations of your family fail.
- Goodness. - What?
(That wasn't nice.)
Don't say that.
You went too far.
(Kwang Soo overreacts to what she did.)
(When So Min left to find Se Chan's tofu...)
(He moves slowly.)
(He takes the tofu.)
Lee Kwang Soo.
I'm done. It's complete.
It's been over 30 minutes.
I can't believe he's doing this.
Kwang Soo,
you submitted a tofu,
- so your sentence is halved. - Yes!
(He switched the tofu with a towel.)
(We'll see about this.)
- It's not me. - All right.
At this time,
Ji Hyo has a chance to switch with another person.
The person who is going to be released soon...
- has 15 minutes left. - It's almost time.
- It's Kwang Soo. - It's not me.
- Don't pick me. - It's him.
The person with the longest sentence...
has seven hours.
- Oh, dear. Are you all right? - Who is it?
It's So Min.
- Is that after being halved? - It is her.
- No. - It's not.
If she gets halved, she only has around five hours.
It's not her.
There's another person with seven hours. It's the longest.
- Seven hours? - We don't have any more games left.
You have to make a good decision, Ji Hyo.
You have to make a good decision.
If you pick seven hours, that's the end.
Hold on, Ji Hyo.
- Can you let me investigate? - Sure.
- Everybody. - Who are you?
- I am... - You got released. You're done.
- Get lost. - Go away.
Get away from my house. You're irrelevant.
Can I borrow your coat?
(Jae Seok tries again with a detective look.)
- These people... - Go away, you beggar.
You came as a beggar.
(Yelling)
You look like a beggar.
- I think so too. - It's true.
- Did it? - It kind of did.
- A little bit. - Just a bit.
Ji Hyo, you have to decide.
What's the shortest sentence left?
15 minutes. It's 10 minutes now.
It's not So Min. She's not a suspect.
The most important thing is that somebody took her tofu.
I think it's Kwang Soo.
- He ate it. - I'm 100-percent sure.
Consider the circumstance.
- He was smacking his lips. - I didn't eat anything.
Look at my mouth. Check it.
- Check my mouth. - Hold on. There's a piece stuck.
(She opens his mouth wide.)
(Let me see where my tofu is.)
- Hold on. - I didn't eat it.
- There's a piece of tofu. - That's from earlier.
- I didn't eat it. - It's definitely him.
You still have the tofu from earlier?
Think about it, Ji Hyo.
You don't need to hesitate.
Let me tell the truth.
I have seven hours left. Pick me if you want.
(Is he confessing?)
(Is this Kwang Soo's timer?)
Pick me if you want. I have nothing to lose.
- Pick him. - Hey.
- I have seven hours left. - Think about it.
- She just smiled. - Ji Hyo.
(Hold on. What does that smile mean?)
(This morning when they were selecting their sentences)
(The person who picked 10 hours, the 2nd longest sentence...)
(was Ji Hyo.)
(She has 7 hours left. She laughs at Kwang Soo's lie.)
- I have seven hours left. - Ji Hyo.
This is the decisive hint.
Pick him. I'm sure.
You don't have seven hours, right?
- I have seven hours left. - No.
- Hold on. - I'm sure.
- What is your decision, Ji Hyo? - Hold on.
- Wait. - Do it.
- Is it you? - Don't feel pressured.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes.
(She switches with Kwang Soo.)
As long as I'm not in last place. It's okay.
You're not in last place.
Ji Hyo, we'll show you the time left.
Kwang Soo, we'll give you yours too.
- In three, you'll show everybody. - How much did you have left?
- We'll show everybody? - In 1, 2, 3.
(1 hour and 3 minutes)
Kwang Soo said he had seven hours.
1 hour.
(He does have 7 hours and 10 minutes now.)
- 1 hour. - Kwang Soo.
You had seven hours?
(Thanks, Kwang Soo.)
That's why you smiled.
(Kwang Soo comes in last place for stealing and lying.)
I knew it. You thief.
- You had seven hours. - You ate it, right?
- It was you, right? - I didn't eat it. I submitted it.
- Hey. - It was finished. I submitted it.
- See? I told you. - I know.
You have seven hours?
I have seven hours.
What a thief.
Still, I was close.
Three generations of your family will fail.
Shut your mouth.
I'll marry you then.
(Our family can fail then!)
- What? - What was that?
- Was that a proposal? - Was it?
I just got nauseous.
(I'm against this marriage.)
(It's not that bad.)
I'm just saying.
(Jail time is over after the unexpected proposal.)
The rest of you can be released.
- Can we go? - Are they all leaving?
Kwang Soo,
make tofu for seven hours.
By himself?
You'll be left alone with your cameraman...
and do self-bathing. You'll be released then.
I did most of the work.
So Min used all of it, so I submitted it.
- You submitted it? - Yes.
Then Kwang Soo, have a great rest of the time.
- We'll visit. - We will.
Take care.
- Go back, Kwang Soo. - Can they buy me tofu?
They can.
- I have plans today. - What plans?
(I can't come.)
Where do you have to be?
- I'm sorry. - With whom?
- And I have no money. - What do you mean?
I'll transfer you the money. Get me some tofu.
I didn't bring my wallet.
If you buy me tofu, I won't forget your kindness.
I won't forget it.
- I don't trust you. - Do you think anybody will?
It doesn't benefit us in any way.
- Let's leave. - Shall we go?
Kwang Soo, please return to the same cell.
- I don't want to go. - Take care.
Please help me. I'm sorry. I won't steal again.
- Give me one chance. - Make a tofu.
- Give me another chance. - Hope that they buy you tofu.
Please buy me 1. Just 1.
They are all leaving!
(The thief, Kwang Soo, gets imprisoned again.)
How am I supposed to make this?
(His only friend for 7 hours is the millstone.)
How do I make this? Do I have to self-bathe too?
(The self-bathing system is ready.)
My goodness. When will I finish?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
What did I do? What did I...
- Why do you keep committing crimes? - No, that's not why.
(His cameraman is mad at him.)
I shouldn't have said I had seven hours left.
This is driving me nuts.
(Spinning)
When will I grind all this?
(He keeps on spinning it, but the soybeans don't go away.)
(What did I do so wrong?)
To make this...
Jae Seok!
(He comes back.)
(Kwang Soo, I got you tofu.)
- Kwang Soo. - Jae Seok.
You punk.
- Jae Seok. - You are still here.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
- I felt this for the first time. - Kwang Soo.
I felt like this for the first time.
You punk.
- You can't commit crimes. - I'm sorry.
- Your parents are watching you! - I'm sorry.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes.
I knew you'd come.
- I never doubted it. - You punk...
(They're absorbed in their act.)
- Thank you, Jae Seok. - Here.
- You're fine. - Thank you.
- It's all good. - Give it to me.
This is enough.
Thank you. I committed a big crime.
Give me a spoon.
I repented for everything.
(You don't have to feed me.)
- My gosh. - I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Sorry?
I'm going to eat this on my way home.
(Thanks for the spoon.)
(Give me the tofu.)
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
- Really? - Jong Kook got this earlier.
- I wanted to eat it on my way. - Why would you do that?
Buy one on your way home! Give this to me!
- Jae Seok. - If you give it to him,
he has 3 hours and 10 minutes left.
(His sentence will be shortened to 3 hours and 10 minutes.)
This is...
enough.
- Are you giving it to him? - Yes.
Thank you. Thank you, Jae Seok.
Kwang Soo, you have 3 hours and 10 minutes left.
Thank you.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Be good. - Okay.
- Don't betray people. - Okay.
- I won't steal. - Don't, okay?
- Don't steal people's stuff. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- I'll be good. - It's cold.
I'll finish my sentence and get back.
That's right. Finish the three hours.
- All right? - Yes.
- Thank you! - No worries.
- I'll repay my debt of gratitude. - Okay.
- All right, Kwang Soo. - Please take care!
- Okay. - Thank you.
You don't know how to make it, right?
Isn't this how you do it?
I'm done. I have to boil this.
Haha!
(He once again pretends like he's born again.)
You're not like that, right?
I was a fool.
I wanted to get out.
(I have changed.)
I'm sorry.
- I'll take care of your parents. - What?
My dad and my mom? Why?
Don't worry. I'm a loyal person.
Are you empty... Are you empty-handed?
Haha. Hold on.
(I'll see you back in society.)
Haha!
What did you do?
Be good.
(Thanks to Haha, his sentence is reduced to 1 hour and 30 minutes.)
Seok Jin! My gosh.
My mom keeps on asking why I'm not coming home.
- Feeling! - Intuition!
- Cross! - Cross!
- Good job. - Ji Hyo!
- Thank you. - Do your best.
Thank you. Okay.
So this...
(He's almost done. He focuses on making tofu.)
The stove...
Does this become that?
This becomes that when I boil it?
(That doesn't look like tofu.)
This is tofu?
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo)
(Her warmth makes him regret about his mistakes and betrayal.)
Kwang Soo.
How could you lie to me so shamelessly?
- I'm sorry. - I'm not that gullible,
- I regret it. - but you tricked me.
(I reflected on myself.)
Please give me another chance. I'm sorry.
Cry.
Cry. Let me see you cry.
If I see a drop of tear, I'll give it to you.
Goodness.
(She provokes him.)
Kwang Soo, you are released.
(His sentence has expired.)
(Come back, you punk.)
Hey, come back.
- What did you say? - Kwang Soo.
Take your tofu, and get lost.
Take it, and get lost. I don't need it.
- Don't throw it at me. - It's for you.
I got released.
- I brought it for you. - I don't want it.
This is for making stew. I can't eat it.
Everybody gave me regular ones. Only you got me this.
(If he didn't get out, she would have made him eat it.)
(Congratulations on your release.)
Kwang Soo, take a self-bath,
and go home.
For the rest of my life, I'll serve others...
and live cleanly. Thank you.
There's a button. You can press it.
I'm talking right now.
I'm talking.
I'm sorry.
It's difficult to come here the 1st time, but not the 2nd time.
- I'm sorry. - Okay?
(A water bomb for one person stands in a lonesome way.)
(One man exits the prison to receive the penalty.)
(Goodbye, prison. A bath is bound to change me.)
It's a do-it-yourself penalty.
You need to speak louder because there is no microphone.
There is no microphone.
(There are only 1 producer and 1 cameraman on the set.)
It's a do-it-yourself penalty.
Don't you think this is too cruel?
- I need to press it myself? - Yes, the button is next to you.
(The water comes out when he presses the button.)
I am sorry, viewers.
I will pay penance and start a new life.
If you lie or steal,
you will receive a penalty.
I am sorry.
(I am sorry, viewers.)
(Shall we begin?)
(He does his own work.)
I am sorry!
(He feels like his sins are washed away.)
I won't do it again.
(Screaming)
No one is here.
Where do I need to go?
Kwang Soo.
Please clap for the slate.
(Don't make fun of me!)
(Waddling)
I will clap.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Running Man in Jeju)
(The first story)
(The queen of variety shows, Gu Ha Ra)
(The woman with many charms, Seor In A)
(The girl with fruit-like charms, Mi Na of Gugudan)
(The master of variety shows, Lee Da Hee)
(In Jeju Island,)
(they dream of romance.)
(Like you are shot)
(The crazy one...)
(next to the crazy one)
(All of them are crazy.)
She is Lee Jung Hyun!
(Even So Min is shocked...)
(by the craziness.)
Why is she going that far?
Let's insert it at the count of three.
In 1, 2, 3.
You are so mean. You are an utter jerk, aren't you?
(You are an utter jerk, aren't you?)
(Craziness at Jeju Special)