- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Move out of my way.
- I'm sitting at the end. - Welcome.
(Kwang Soo refuses Se Chan's push.)
You sit next to Jong Kook.
- Sit next to Jong Kook. - No.
- Go next to Jong Kook. - Sit here.
Okay, that's done. I feel so relieved.
(Why is Kwang Soo refusing?)
(Punching)
(He felt the power of Jong Kook's squeaky hammer.)
(He's determined not to sit next to Jong Kook during games.)
(Is my hearing okay?)
- I feel so relieved. - You two became close friends.
- I was startled during my shower. - Why?
I was washing my hair.
(He screamed while washing his hair.)
Some of my hair was missing. My head hurt so much.
- Are you bruised from last week? - Yes.
- That's being coldhearted. - Right.
- Hello, everyone. - Hello.
Why are you so late?
- I arrived first and waited. - Why did you come so late?
I had to spit my gum out.
- Come and have a seat. - Hello, everyone.
- Hello. - Why are you so late?
- Pardon? - We're wearing the same cap.
(We're wearing the same cap.)
Goodness.
- Stop it. - My goodness.
(The brothers have reunited.)
We're wearing the same cap.
You're copying me these days. You're also wearing layers like me.
Jae Seok wasn't wearing this cap when I saw him a moment ago.
(Let me put on the same one.)
(Is he copying Haha's style?)
This is frustrating.
Will you be on "High School Rapper" as well?
What does "High School Rapper" have to do with wearing this cap?
I'm your role model from now on.
(Stop messing around.)
Is Ji Hyo working on a movie?
- Ji Hyo? - Are you working on a drama too?
Is she working on a movie and a drama?
Both at the same time?
- I got many offers all at once. - That's impressive.
- Worst times will start now. - That's amazing.
(Worst times will start now.)
What will happen to us if she starts working on both of them?
It's her first time working on both. What shall we do?
When Ji Hyo works on a movie or a drama, she becomes sensitive.
- She does. - It'll be like a gift set.
- In that case... - Which role are you playing?
- It depends on your role. - I know.
She plays the wife of Ma Dong Seok.
- Ma Dong Seok's wife. - We're dead meat.
- Be careful. I'll tell on you. - Don't tell on us.
Ma Dong Seok's arm is bigger than your thigh.
- Be quiet. What about yours? - I think so.
- Your thighs are small too. - They're bigger than yours.
Stop it. It's because my legs are American-style.
- "American-style"? - My legs are American-style.
What do you mean? How are they American-style?
Then why are they so thin?
- No Americans have legs like those. - Listen.
- In retirement homes? - No.
They're like thighs of American basketball players.
All you need are wheels on your chair.
(Instead of being western, he's old.)
(That's so harsh.)
How dare you?
(He's subdued easily.)
- You punk. - How can you say that?
- You'd better be careful. - You're being too harsh on him.
- You're worse than him. - I saw a photo.
- It looked exactly like you. - Be quiet.
It was a sandpiper. Sandpipers have legs like yours.
(Sandpipers have a wide torso with thin, long legs.)
My legs are long. I have long legs.
Kwang Soo appeared in "The Accidental Detective".
- That's right. - He wore a wig.
- Pardon? - Didn't he extend his hair?
It was recent. It isn't a wig.
- He was imitating an animal. - What?
- Afghan Hound. - What did you say?
Why would I imitate a dog?
- You guys had similar hair. - No.
Yours looked like Han Ki Beom's.
(Detective Han Ki Beom)
- What? It's a different style. - It looked like Han Ki Beom's.
- It was very long. - This is what I hope for.
I hope that you play basketball.
No, I'm not good at it.
- You'll succeed after 10 years. - He's right.
- Starting now? - Of course.
- You're only 40. You can do it. - That's what dreams are.
- Play the center at 40? - That's possible.
He can do it.
Soccer sounds good too. It's better than being on TV.
What?
(You're better at sports than being on TV.)
- Seriously. - I have a main job.
(He's flustered.)
Is being on TV your main job?
- As a main job, it isn't enough. - What do you mean?
(As a main job, it isn't enough.)
I always envied you for being on TV as a hobby.
It isn't my hobby. Goodness.
So Min is dominating all the commercials.
You should treat all of us.
So Min is moving soon.
- No, not yet. - Is it next year?
Yes, I'll move once the contract is over next year.
Are you moving to a 2 or 3-bedroom apartment?
- If I can take out more loans, - Move to a two-bedroom place.
I'll move to a bigger place.
That's great. It's great news.
- It's good that she moved out. - Actually,
a TV that she got as a present is too big for her apartment.
That's true.
It's because the TV is too big.
The TV is too close, but there's no room to move back.
She has to watch TV through a mirror.
She has to watch it sideways.
(I'll work hard to buy a bigger house for my TV.)
Today, we have something to recharge you for...
- being penalized continuously. - Really?
Today's race is called Invigorating Race.
(Today's race is called Invigorating Race.)
(This is a surprise.)
The staff finally started to care about our health.
It has been a long time.
- What is it? - It's eel.
- Eel? - Is there eel?
(The menu is presented.)
- It's food that restores energy. - There's even sturgeon sashimi.
"Sturgeon sashimi"?
(Unlike its name, sturgeon sashimi melts in the mouth.)
- What's nine-seafood stew? - "Sturgeon sashimi"?
- There must be nine of something. - That must be it.
(9-seafood stew includes 9 types of healthy food.)
I never heard of cold, raw Korean beef soup.
This sushi is really delicious. It's made with seasoned raw beef.
(Seasoned raw beef sushi)
- What's pink samgyetang? - Pink samgyetang?
- What is it? - What's pink samgyetang?
(Pink samgyetang tastes and looks good.)
- Octopus naengmyeon sounds good. - It sounds delicious.
(Octopus naengmyeon is made with octopus in spicy sauce.)
Lobster pizza.
(Lobster pizza is made with a whole lobster.)
I want some grilled eel.
(It's a high-protein meal.)
Any place sounds good today.
This is amazing.
Among seven tasty restaurants located in and near Seoul,
you may choose a dish that you'd like to eat.
(They get to choose a dish that they want to eat.)
Within the five-hour time limit...
(However, there's a 5-hour time limit.)
- There can't be a time limit. - Come on.
- Seriously. - My gosh, this is about food.
Within the five-hour time limit,
if the accumulated number of meals by the members...
reaches 20, it will count as a success.
- 20 meals? - What? The accumulated number?
- 8 of us can finish 20 meals. - We can definitely reach 20 meals.
We can finish 20 meals in 5 hours.
Besides, there's no traffic today since it's a holiday.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
(Be quiet. Be quiet.)
(Seriously?)
Why would you say that?
- Why would you? - I was just saying...
Be quiet.
Why did you talk? Why?
The director is talking right now. Why are you talking over him?
- I mean... - It's like we're in a class.
Why are we in a class?
The class is in session now.
- You shouldn't be talking. - I said, I didn't want to sit here.
I had no idea Jae Seok was going to sit there.
- Exactly. - By the way, be honest.
Which one of us bullies you more?
You're asking me to choose which parent I like more.
(You're asking me to choose which parent I like more.)
Jong Kook bullies you.
I'm just speaking the truth.
It's physical bullying against emotional bullying.
That's true.
However,
in the case which you fail to reach the target number...
- We'll accomplish this. - We can finish 20 meals.
We have prepared a cool penalty to remove your fatigue from the heat.
You must complete Running Man's...
water bomb festival to celebrate summer before getting off work.
(Everyone must carry out this cool, but humiliating penalty.)
My goodness. Today's weather is not that hot today.
You should've asked us to bring extra underwear then.
- I didn't bring an extra one. - It will rain in the evening,
but even if it rains, you will still carry it out.
Besides, don't already assume that we'll get the penalty.
We can accomplish the mission.
It's just that we always end up getting the penalty.
- I immediately thought I'd get it. - It's impossible not to think so.
We'll start with that assumption.
We'll explain the rules when we arrive at the first restaurant.
You can freely choose a restaurant and set out.
Since we have five hours, we should go to a clustered area.
Why don't we start with that?
(He targets Jongno-gu which is close from Bomun-dong.)
- Start with restaurants nearby. - Number 4, 5, and 6.
Number Five. We're very close to Jongno.
- Let's hit Jongno first. - I think that'd be better.
- Let's start with this restaurant. - Number five.
- Let's eat lobster pizza first. - That's right.
- Let's go. - Go.
- We'll travel by car. - Okay.
My gosh, she doesn't usually serve me breakfast,
but my wife cooked me breakfast today.
(They set out to finish 20 meals.)
Why did she cook me breakfast today?
- We have to keep eating today. - That sounds delicious.
(Lobster pizza)
Eels and pizza can taste greasy at times.
- We might not finish our next meal. - That's why...
we made the right decision to start with pizza.
- We'll eat the pizza. - After eating something greasy,
- we'll want spicy food. - Exactly.
We ought to try sturgeon sashimi.
- Let's try what we hadn't tasted. - I've never tried that.
Seok Jin...
is as shameless as a sturgeon.
- He must be brazen. - My goodness.
- "My goodness." - My gosh.
- I should've scolded him at 20. - Seok Jin...
(Giggling)
Hey, we're at Daehangno.
- Hey, we're at Daehangno. - Are we going to Daehangno?
- My gosh. Really? - Goodness, this area...
I have a lot of memories in this neighborhood.
- I haven't been here in a while. - I love it here.
- I went to Marronnier Park a lot. - That park is on the right.
Exactly.
- Have you ever seen me there? - Me?
I used to drink soju a lot there with a bowl of jjamppong.
- They delivered to the park then. - That's right.
- At that time, artists... - We didn't have money back then.
I had two bags of snacks with a friend who drank a lot.
- I was in a play for kids. - Really?
- A play for kids? - Yes.
Kwang Soo, you were in a play for kids?
- But weren't you too tall for that? - What was your role?
I was the scarecrow in The Wizard of Oz.
(It's the perfect role for Kwang Soo.)
- You were, weren't you? I knew it. - Seriously?
- He made the perfect scarecrow. - That's right.
A bird pooped on me right here.
- Where? - I was standing at the crosswalk.
- Really? - I was in a crowd, but I got it.
- My gosh. - Weren't you lucky that day?
- No, I was totally unlucky. - The day the bird poop fell on you.
I had the worst luck.
I've never felt that So Min was lucky.
- She doesn't get lucky at all. - I'm never lucky.
Jae Seok, she was lucky that she got to join Running Man.
(Impressed)
- That was pretty cool. - You said a great punchline.
- "You said a great punchline." - No, my punch is pretty amazing.
(My punch is pretty amazing.)
He said his punch was amazing.
- Let's just skip this. - That's right.
(An absence of a word "line" makes the sentence sound scary.)
- Your punch is strong? - Not punchline.
We're here.
We have arrived. This is the place.
Everyone, we have arrived at the first restaurant.
Before you enter, let me inform you the additional rules of the race.
- I knew it. - There are additional rules?
(I'll tell you the additional rules of the race.)
Not everyone can taste the invigorating dishes today.
(Not everyone can taste the invigorating dishes today.)
- I saw this coming. - You can't do that.
(We saw this coming.)
It's Food Trouble: One Bite Race.
- You can't do this to us. - "One Bite Race"?
Every time you arrive at a restaurant,
you will select a member to represent all of you.
- 1 member? - Just 1 member?
The selected member will choose whether three members will...
taste the food or six random members will taste the food.
- 6 random members? - 6 random members?
How will those six random members be chosen?
You might not be included in those six random members.
- Three members including myself? - It's either playing it safe...
- So two more additional members? - or taking a risk.
I believe that I should be chosen...
as the representative for this restaurant.
- Come on. What? - I believe...
(He throws his hat in the ring.)
- That's nonsense. - What?
- You had breakfast. - Why not?
- Shouldn't I be chosen for this? - No.
- Then I... - How will we decide?
Depending on the decision,
the mission will determine who will get to eat the food.
Members who get to taste the food will receive a meal badge.
After the race,
only one member with the least badges...
will face the penalty if you accomplish the mission.
However, if you fail to accomplish the mission,
everyone except the member with the most badges will face it.
- Someone who eats a lot should go. - Exactly.
- Someone like me. - Someone like me.
- I can eat the most. - Me too.
- I can eat five servings. - I'm always the last one eating.
- Don't you agree? - I can eat a lot too.
- If you select me, - Listen.
I'll go with six random members.
- We don't need to pick 3 members. - Right. We can get 6 meals.
(Smirking)
We don't need to pick three members?
- No, we don't. - You'll choose that.
- I don't think we need to. - I can see it...
in your eyes that you'll choose three members.
- I see number 3 in your eyes. - The number 3 is written here.
- Can you see it or not? - You're holding three fingers too.
No, no. This is not it.
(He can't conceal his instincts to betray as it's his nature.)
- You already chose three members. - I don't think so.
- You already chose three members. - I'm not thinking that.
How are we going to choose the representative?
You can freely decide it among yourselves.
- Let's pick a representative. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - In that case,
Team England and Team Switzerland are sitting together.
A member from each team will play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. - Let's split it into two teams.
We'll play first among us?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha and Ji Hyo win the 1st round.)
(Haha is the representative of Team Luxury Package.)
Okay. I'm the representative.
I'm the representative.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin, Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo win the 1st round.)
(Feeling disappointed)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok win the 2nd round.)
- Who won? - Seok Jin and I remain.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok is Team Shuddering Package's representative.)
I'm the representative.
My gosh, you're copying me again.
- My gosh, it's so annoying. - Jae Seok, stop copying him.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll play rock. - Okay.
(There's tension during the final match of rock-paper-scissors.)
(Which member will become the representative for lobster pizza?)
(Haha is elected to become the representative.)
Okay.
Six of us should eat this.
- 6 of us should eat it. - We should start with 6 members.
Should I get out of here first?
- Haha. - Hey, hey.
- Haha. - We should start with six members.
- Haha, I'm hungry. - Do it well.
- Hey, hey. - Haha, we should start...
- Hey, hey. - We should have a good start.
(Haha, are you going to abandon us?)
- I believe in your luck. - Haha.
(Shouting)
- Don't forget about the mission. - Okay.
- We must finish six meals. - Look me in the eye.
Accomplishing the mission matters.
(It's the success of the mission versus the guarantee to eat.)
(What is Haha's decision?)
(My goodness)
(The mix of a plump lobster and pizza makes his jaw drop.)
(The freshly-baked lobster pizza makes his heart pound heavily.)
Hold on a second. I should video call them.
Jong Kook, show this to the members.
Show this to them?
- Let me show you how it looks. - Okay.
(They're amazed.)
(The sight of the plump lobster is shown through the phone.)
- Oh, my goodness. - They put the whole lobster on it.
They put the whole lobster on it.
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
(Where are you going?)
(How dare you violate the rule?)
- He hasn't decided yet. - Where are you going?
Scream if you want to eat this.
(Screaming)
Come on.
The member who can scream the longest.
(Screaming)
(He screams for 1 second.)
Let's eat!
- Jae Seok didn't shout. - Hey.
Jae Seok only pretended to shout.
(Jae Seok's silent shouting is exposed too.)
- What's wrong with Jae Seok? - Jae Seok didn't shout.
Jae Seok only mouthed it.
Jae Seok can't eat it.
(Let me have the lobster pizza with you.)
Okay, okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
(It's time to make his decision after the shouting.)
Haha, the first dish is the lobster pizza.
Three members including yourself can taste this dish.
Or six random members can taste it. Which one will you choose?
I want everyone to have this if it's possible.
I think Ji Hyo and So Min will love this.
Should I set a good example?
(Haha makes his decision as the representative.)
- You're all here. - My gosh, this place looks awesome.
- The six of us should eat this. - You don't need to think about it.
- Exactly. - Haha, seriously.
Take a seat.
- Please sit down. - My gosh.
- I wanted everyone to eat it. - Precisely.
You don't need to think about it.
All right. Haha is the representative.
Between three members including himself...
and six random members...
(It's the team versus the guarantee to eat. Which did he choose?)
Haha chose three members including himself to eat the dish.
(Haha chose 3 members including himself to eat the dish.)
- Okay. - What?
(What? You chose 3 members to eat this dish?)
Show us your decision with your fingers.
(He was torn during the moment of decision.)
(Three people)
Three people.
(With swag, he chose 3 people including himself.)
(I want to eat and live well.)
Haha, I am disappointed in you.
This is bad. I think we will fail the mission.
- You are less than human. - Don't say that.
I swear this is what happened.
They asked, "What's your decision?"
I went, "What should I do?" "You chose three people."
They practically decided for me. I am serious.
(What is he saying?)
- Watch this episode later. - Stop lying.
- Your acting skills improved a lot. - I am serious.
I swear.
- Haha, I believe you. - Forget it.
You believe me, right?
Among the three people,
the two people who aren't the representatives...
will be chosen by a mission.
Will there be a mission?
They will be chosen by a mission.
- In any case, I get to eat, right? - That's right.
The competition will be fierce.
The mission that determines who gets to eat is...
Food ASMR Quiz.
(Food ASMR Quiz)
(Food ASMR Quiz?)
- What is that? - You will hear the sound...
of a cooking process...
- and guess what the dish is. - That sounds fun.
The two people who get the answer right the quickest win.
- Okay. - We have to answer quickly.
- I am good at this. - Me, too. I really like food.
I am the ASMR expert.
Play the sound of the first dish.
(Is it a scraping sound?)
Answer!
- You only get one chance. - I know that.
You only get one chance.
(What does So Min think the dish is?)
A fried egg.
(A fried egg?)
That's it. All right.
- You blew your chance. - Okay, okay.
Okay. One person got eliminated.
Play.
(They play the sound again.)
(After the beeping sound,)
That the induction cooktop.
(they hear the sizzling sound.)
- The induction cooktop. - The buttons were pressed.
I have the answer.
(Jong Kook raises his hand.)
Spring onion pancake.
- That's it. - Okay, okay.
- 2 people got eliminated. - 2 people got eliminated.
I am almost there. I just need to be patient.
(So Min and Jong Kook are eliminated.)
Something is being deep-fried.
It's the sound of oil.
Something is being sliced.
I get it now.
- I got it. Tonkatsu. - He will get eliminated.
(Tonkatsu?)
He got eliminated.
(I can't believe it's not tonkatsu getting deep-fried and sliced.)
I just need three more people to be eliminated.
Maybe it would be better to wait until the end.
(Is it a scraping sound?)
Answer!
Bibimbap.
- Bibimbap. - I had the same thought.
(Isn't it a sound that comes from mixing bibimbap?)
(Bibimbap!)
(Incorrect)
- He got eliminated. - Three people remain.
(Let's see who gets the answer first.)
(It's a boiling sound.)
It's a boiling sound.
Answer.
(Combining the earlier sounds and the boiling sound...)
Tuna kimchi stew.
That can't be the answer.
(Tuna kimchi stew is correct.)
This is how I knew.
We first heard the sound of a can opening.
I waited patiently.
I got goosebumps.
We will show you the answer video. He is spot on.
- Look at that. - That was the sound.
Kimchi was stir-fried.
- Right. You stir-fry kimchi... - The sound...
in tuna oil.
I thought it was the sound of something getting deep-fried.
(The sound of scraping tuna out of a can)
This part gave me the answer.
I thought it was the sound of tonkatsu getting sliced.
This part was confusing.
(The sound of slicing an onion)
- That looks delicious. - Okay.
(Se Chan becomes the first person.)
- Nice. - There is a spot.
- There is a spot. - There is a spot.
One more person will be picked.
- Let's go. - I can do this.
This is the last question. Play.
(Is it the sound of cracking eggs?)
- Eggs were added. - Beat the eggs.
It's not the sound of eggs.
I think about three eggs were added.
It's the third egg.
Answer.
(Jong Kook guesses.)
- Rolled omelet. - No way.
It would be too easy, right?
Okay. He got eliminated.
Okay. Let's be patient.
- I thought it was rolled omelet. - Me, too.
I think they were trying to confuse us.
(Maybe it's not the sound of eggs.)
(It seems like the sound of beating eggs.)
The eggs are being beaten.
- The eggs are being beaten. - That's right.
Answer.
(Kwang Soo looks confident. What's his answer?)
Gimbap.
- What? - Gimbap.
(That's ridiculous.)
That makes no sense.
Your ears are rotten.
You add eggs to gimbap.
- Get your ears checked out. - It's not like that.
That was a ridiculous answer.
You add eggs to gimbap.
Since this dish uses a lot of eggs, it could be steamed egg.
You might think that, but that's not the answer.
- It's not steamed egg. - That would be too easy.
(What's the answer to this question?)
(It is steamed egg.)
(It can't be steamed egg.)
So many eggs are being used.
This person's arm must hurt.
(Steamed egg is the answer.)
This person is beating eggs for so long.
Is this person making meringue?
Is this person making castella?
No, no. The sound stopped.
Answer.
Perhaps, I overthought it. It's steamed egg.
No way.
- That's it! - Are you serious?
(Steamed egg is correct.)
We overthought it.
- We overthought it. - Are you serious?
- It was on my mind for a while. - That's right.
Since Jae Seok said, "It's not steamed egg,"
no one thought to try the answer.
Steamed egg was on my mind.
- That's it. - Steamed egg is an easy answer.
Steamed egg.
There were no other cooking processes.
(Se Chan, Haha, and Jae Seok get to eat lobster pizza.)
(The meaty lobster sits on the pizza and waits for the 3 people.)
- It must be tasty. - We should show it...
to the viewers.
(Please take a look.)
(They can already taste the lobster meat on their tongues.)
- It looks so tasty. - The lobster is meaty.
- The lobster is meaty. - Let's put it on the pizza.
My goodness.
(The sight of lobster meat on the pizza...)
(annoys other people.)
Let's roll it up like gimbap.
(He rolls up the lobster meat with pizza.)
(Biting)
Thank you.
(My goodness.)
(Eating)
I love that the crust is thin.
I will be sure to eat the next dish.
May I drink coke?
If you want to drink it, act cute.
I won't drink it then.
My goodness.
Se Chan!
(Se Chan, please give me a bite.)
Se Chan, So Min wants coke.
That's not the kind of cute act I want to see.
Se Chan, So Min is sad. So Min wants coke.
(She shakes her shoulders.)
(She is the fairy of coke.)
When I become the representative,
I promise I will eliminate So Min.
(I promise I will eliminate So Min.)
I can't stand this.
- Seok Jin. - Come on.
- Let me smell it. - May I eat the mussel?
The mussel is...
(Maybe there is some meat.)
Do you want to hear the ASMR sound?
(Do you want to hear the ASMR sound?)
What?
(That's ASMR.)
(Sucking)
Answer. It's a bidet.
(It's a bidet.)
(It looks tasty, right?)
(There must be some meat left.)
You are hungry, right?
Why don't we play a game...
and give a bite to one person?
- I would love that. - Okay.
I am like Lim Yo Hwan when I come to these games.
(Lim Yo Hwan, the professional gamer)
When I played a drinking game at a group date,
I never got drunk because I was so good at games.
That means...
people gave you water, not alcohol.
(That means people gave you water, not alcohol.)
They worried that you would be an annoying drunk.
Ji Hyo is the luckiest.
- All right. - My goodness.
- That's incredible. - Yes!
Go ahead.
Why don't the rest of you play a game for the last slice?
- I would love that. - Yes!
- Another game! - Let's play a different game.
- How about 3-6-9 Game? - 3-6-9 Game.
Let's play a new version of 3-6-9 Game.
- What is that? - You go, "3, 6, 9, 3, 6, 9."
1, 2.
4, 5.
(Each person says a syllable.)
You clap twice for 6 since it has 2 syllables in Korean.
You clap twice.
Let's stand up because it's confusing.
We need to focus.
- The pizza... - It's tasty.
Let's eat pizza.
- 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
- 1. - 1.
Two.
- 4. - 5.
Five.
- You are wrong. - You are wrong.
(So Min gets eliminated.)
(So Min gets eliminated because she said the number late.)
(I want pizza.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
You should have said it faster.
- Let's begin. 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
- 1. - 1.
Two.
- 4. - 5.
- Okay. - Out.
(Jong Kook is eliminated after saying both syllables.)
- You have to say one syllable. - I don't know this game.
- Start. - Okay.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo have been waiting for this moment.)
Start.
(Say one syllable each time, and the lobster pizza will be yours.)
- 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
One.
Yes!
(Seok Jin confidently says both syllables.)
(Why did I do that?)
(Seok Jin, thank you for your mistake.)
Seok Jin.
- "One"! - I was doing so well.
Gosh, I was too worked up.
(The winner, Kwang Soo, wins a piece of pizza.)
I feel too bad. Can't they compete for a glass of coke?
- Coke? - Yes, the rest of them.
- Let's play 3, 6, 9 again. - Let's stand up.
- So Min is so bad. - I want to win.
- 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
Five.
- Five. - Sit down.
(Jong Kook is the weakest when it comes to drinking games.)
Jong Kook.
I'm so bad at games.
- 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
- 1. - 1.
Two.
- 4. - 5.
Five.
(Clap)
Seven.
You should have clapped your hands.
(He was supposed to clap his hands.)
Why did you say, "seven"?
I was going to...
- Exchange it for a sip of coke. - Kwang Soo finally gets to eat.
Exchange it for a sip of coke.
That looks amazing.
It tastes fantastic.
Leave a bite for me.
They'll start craving coke.
You have to eat it with coke.
Okay. Let me take a bite first.
- Eat it with coke. - It tastes amazing.
Don't eat everything. Please.
(Don't eat everything. Please.)
Please! That jerk.
(That jerk.)
(So Min is so desperate that she calls Kwang Soo a jerk.)
Let's do better next time.
What should we eat next?
Let's go have naengmyeon.
We should have some noodles.
Beef sushi.
- It sounds so nice. - Let's have beef sushi.
- Should we? - Let's go for beef sushi.
- Okay. - Let's get going.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(For the 2nd round, they go for beef sushi.)
I used to come to Daehangno a lot...
back in high school and college.
I lived near here.
But I couldn't enter many places,
and I just remembered why.
- I didn't have money. - Right.
- That's sad. - Right.
I used to have a dollar and 50 cents in my pocket.
- You? - Yes.
Couldn't you buy a house with that money back in the day?
(Couldn't you buy a house with that money back in the day?)
Didn't you carry around shells?
Didn't you carry around the Sangpyeongtongbo coins?
(I think I've seen him in black-and-white textbooks.)
I remember hanging out in Daehangno.
You guys didn't hang out in Jongno District, did you?
Are you from the same generation as Kim Du Han?
- Hey. - Have you seen him fight?
- Sirasoni... - Back in the day...
- Have you seen him? - Have you?
- He'd knock anyone out. - Really?
- He was amazing. - What about Sirasoni?
I've seen Sirasoni too. He flew, landed, and started eating.
Is he older than you?
- What? - Is he older than you?
He was born a few months before me.
(Seok Jin plays along.)
- Is he? - We're two months apart.
Did you get your nickname, Big Nose, then?
- Of course. - Big Nose of Jongno District.
He'd sweep the streets of Jongno District with his nose.
He crawled?
The streets of Jongno District used to be so clean...
when he was there.
I was the vacuum cleaner of Jongno District.
- He swept the streets. - That's right.
(The cleaner with a big nose has faded into the mists of history.)
Look at Changgyeonggung on the right.
- I... - You got beaten up there?
Back in high school...
(You got beaten up there?)
- He got robbed. - He got robbed.
- He got beaten up. - Goodness.
- He got robbed? - I really...
like palaces.
Maybe I lived in a palace in my previous life.
You must have been a servant.
- You must have been a eunuch. - A eunuch.
- A eunuch. - He probably was a eunuch.
- It suits you. - You guys...
"Your Majesty."
- Gosh. - It suits you.
Gosh, you fruit flies.
Doesn't a eunuch taste the king's poop?
- Right. - Right.
(Doesn't a eunuch taste the king's poop?)
- To check the king's health. - That's right.
That's a eunuch's job.
His hands were unlucky back then too.
(His hands were unlucky back then too.)
- Because he ate poop? - He had to touch poop.
"It has a golden color today, Your Majesty."
- Gosh. - You were a eunuch.
You guys are driving me crazy.
(It's a miracle that he got to try the lobster pizza.)
You're going to have cold, raw Korean beef soup and beef sushi.
- That sounds amazing. - Okay.
- You have to pick a representative. - Okay.
Let's pick one.
- Should we play a game? - Okay.
Each of you will text someone, "I want to hear your voice."
The one who gets a call first will be the representative.
(After texting, the one who gets a call first wins.)
Okay. Let's all send it at the same time.
You can't text your family member.
It's cheating if you text a family member.
I'll text Jang Do Yeon.
- Jang Do Yeon? - Yes.
- I'll text Kim Jin Ho. - Kim Jin Ho.
I'll text Nam Chang Hee.
(Nam Chang Hee, Shorry, Tae Hang Ho, Lee Jong Hyuk)
(Kim Jin Ho, Jang Do Yeon, Lee Sang Yeob)
It has to be fair for everyone.
- Get your phones ready. - Get ready.
- 1, 2, 3. - Ready.
(They send a message at the same time.)
- Done. - Jong Hyuk. Jong Hyuk!
- Let's go, Sang Yeob! - Jong Hyuk!
- Please. - Sang Yeob.
I got a call!
(I got a call!)
(Seok Jin gets a call from Jong Hyuk.)
My phone is ringing.
(Is this it?)
Jong Hyuk.
- What is it? - I wanted to hear your voice.
- He's so nice. - He is.
- Really? - I love you.
- Are you shooting? - How did you know?
(How did you know?)
Gosh.
My doppelganger although it doesn't make sense.
Jong Hyuk, thank you.
- Buy me a meal. - I will.
Okay.
- I texted Chang Hee again. - What did you write?
"I don't want to hear your voice anymore."
(Seok Jin can decide how many will get to eat.)
I want my image to change from today.
- I should choose six people... - You should.
You should.
- I'll choose six people. - That makes sense.
If Seok Jin chooses three people, things will get weird.
- What do you mean? - Stop making things weird.
Change your image.
I don't understand. Why would things get weird?
Please cut this part out.
- Because... - Whom are you talking to?
- I'm talking to the director. - What are you talking about?
Please cut this part out for Seok Jin's sake.
Seriously...
If you choose three people here, you'll look like a psycho.
What?
(You'll look like a psycho.)
I'll look like a psycho? I can't believe him.
He's ridiculous. He's getting on my nerves.
I'm starting to want to choose three people.
- Let me tell you again. - Let's do this.
- Please cut out this part too. - Please cut it.
I want to hear him out. What is it?
- If you choose three people... - I'll look like a psycho?
No.
Your career will be jeopardized.
(Your career will be jeopardized.)
For your own sake...
- Does he have to retire? - I mean...
Say something that makes sense.
Do you think I'm stupid? Stop trying to brainwash me.
- Try to convince me. - Does he have to retire?
He doesn't understand. Please talk to him.
Seok Jin will be too scared not to choose six people now.
It'll start to bother him as time goes by.
- Right. - "Will my career be jeopardized?"
Things will seriously get weird.
- Fine, I'll do it right. - Okay.
We're here.
- I know this place. - You do?
- It's this place? - Will I get to eat?
(Beef sushi)
Gosh.
(Cold, raw Korean beef soup)
(It's decision-making time.)
3 people including you or 6 randomly chosen people?
(He has to make a choice.)
I need to see the big picture.
Who am I? I'm the oldest member.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(What will the oldest member who sees the big picture choose?)
Gosh, look at that.
(The other 7 members arrive.)
Look at that.
- What's that? - Is it real food?
- So this is what we'll eat. - It looks delicious.
- It's Korean beef. - Please, Seok Jin.
Dear our captain
- Go, Seok Jin - Go, Seok Jin
- Go, Seok Jin - You've made your decision, right?
- We don't have to butter him up. - We don't.
- That's why I've been quiet. - Have you made your decision?
- Yes. - Seok Jin...
chose between three people including him...
and six randomly chosen people.
(3 people versus 6 people)
(What did Seok Jin choose?)
He chose six randomly chosen people.
(6 randomly chosen people)
(This is the oldest member's big picture.)
Really?
(He was torn between the two choices.)
- I choose 6 people. - 6 randomly chosen people?
- You might not get to eat. - I'll probably get to eat too.
I doubt that I won't get to eat.
(A ray of sunshine among all the betrayals and lies)
I really...
- told myself, - Seok Jin...
"I'm the oldest member."
(I'm the oldest member.)
I wanted to let you guys eat.
Jae Seok.
(Praise Seok Jin!)
- Seok Jin - Seok Jin
Let me correct something you said.
I really appreciate your choice.
- It's really admirable. - Yes.
But I'm the leader of Running Man.
What?
You're just the oldest member.
I think it's because you told him...
his career would be jeopardized.
(That was probably why.)
- It was because of Jae Seok. - You're right.
He's very scared.
I didn't know that he was a coward.
(Seok Jin couldn't simply ignore Jae Seok's warning.)
Cowards recognize each other.
Anyway,
remember what I said before we got off the bus.
I sacrificed myself for the greater good.
Seok Jin made a big decision.
He acts like our big brother.
This mission determines six members who will get to eat.
- It's called Strange Buzzer Quiz. - "Strange Buzzer"?
Listen to questions related to food.
The first member to ring the buzzer indicated by the staff answers.
You receive a meal badge in the order of answering questions.
The first buzzer is lemon.
Eat half of a lemon whole.
If you answer the question accurately in five seconds, you win.
- I just imagined the taste. - Lemon is difficult.
It's already sour.
What's the origin of dried laver that we often eat?
One, the last name of the person who first grew dried laver.
Two, the shape of long laver that grows deep in the sea.
Three, its smoke-like movement under the sea.
Four, the last name of the king who enjoyed eating dried laver.
Answer.
Go ahead.
Read the question, and answer it accurately.
- "Read the question"? - That's right.
He lost.
Start.
Poor Kwang Soo.
(He must answer in 5 seconds.)
Read the question.
- Two. - Goodness.
He won't make it.
- Three. - Goodness.
- He looks so ugly. - Four.
(Looking at him makes my mouth water.)
(He exceeds the time limit.)
It makes my mouth water.
Do we have to read the question?
Read the question, and say the answer.
I can't do it.
- It's impossible. - One.
- Goodness. - Two.
That's so dirty.
(He mumbles.)
(They're two ugly brothers.)
Answer!
(Se Chan gives it a try since he's used to eating lemon.)
- How can we do it? - What's this?
(Screaming)
(Everyone is getting invigorated.)
It's impossible. Anyone who can do it deserves respect.
"What's the origin of dried laver that we often eat?"
"Three, its smoke-like movement under the sea."
(Haha barely finished saying it. Is his answer correct?)
(Number 3 is wrong.)
- Answer. - That's wrong.
(He fails.)
(What's this?)
(What's her answer among the 3 remaining choices?)
"Four, the last name of the king who enjoyed eating dried laver."
(Number 4 is also wrong.)
Answer.
(The second time should be better. He spits it out.)
- Goodness. - That's dirty.
(It's more painful for those who are watching.)
(He embarrasses himself more.)
- What is it? - Answer!
(It's a waterfall of vitamin C.)
(He burps.)
- He's making dinosaur sounds. - Answer.
(While everyone is being energized...)
"What's the origin of dried laver that we often eat?"
"One, the last name of the person who first grew dried laver."
(Se Chan's answer is number 1.)
That's not it.
(Number one is not it.)
(Se Chan answers correctly.)
(Se Chan's vitamin C party is finally over.)
It's so sour.
I can't even focus.
Kim Yeo Ik successfully grew dried laver in 1640.
- We'll give Se Chan a meal badge. - Yes!
Se Chan got it.
He got it.
(It's the second question.)
(Jae Seok wins a meal ticket and a meal badge.)
Next question's buzzer is water.
- Water will be easy enough. - If you know the answer,
call out and put a cup on your head.
The member to pour the water closest to the red line answers.
You say when to stop.
This is why we needed an extra pair of underwear.
- Get wet before answering. - Goodness.
We have four spots left. Please try hard.
I haven't gotten a meal badge yet.
You should be included.
- I should, right? - Yes.
I made a sacrifice.
Do you understand?
Here's your question.
Which of the following...
- is a good food pairing? - I know all about this.
One, tomato and sugar.
Two, beef and butter.
Three, bread and orange juice.
- No. - Four, abalone and chicken.
Answer!
- What's the answer? - I definitely know it.
- You know it? - Here I go.
(He must say stop once the water reaches the line.)
(He's completely focused.)
(Haha goes for the red line without any hesitation.)
(The water went over the line.)
Stop.
(He says stop after getting wet.)
(He gets ugly for the 2nd time.)
"Stop."
This is so difficult.
(He becomes a piece of wet laver.)
Answer.
That must feel cool.
I definitely know the answer.
I do too.
(She's completely focused.)
(Everyone holds their breaths and watches her.)
(The water flows over the line again.)
Isn't it full yet?
No way.
- Answer. - Answer.
(While people get wet, Kwang Soo raises his hand.)
- It's Kwang Soo. - Don't even pour it.
Where's the cup?
(The cup keeps avoiding the water.)
Where's the cup? Hold on.
Pour it carefully.
- Where is it? - Kwang Soo.
(The cup keeps moving away.)
- What's going on? - Pour it carefully.
Pour it toward the side.
Toward the front.
- What's going on? - Kwang Soo.
(He fails as he runs out of water.)
You only got this much. You're so silly.
- Answer. - You're frustrating, Kwang Soo.
- Who's next? - He's frustrating.
Hold the cup for her.
(He holds it carefully.)
You can't look.
Wait.
- Get ready. - Don't act foolishly.
What?
(She says it out of the blue.)
What did I do?
What did I do wrong?
- What do you mean? - What did I do?
- "Act foolishly"? - What do you mean?
- You're being harsh. - That's right.
Don't blame Kwang Soo.
I was holding it still.
(As Kwang Soo acts foolishly, So Min starts to pour.)
Start.
(She pours carefully.)
- Where is it? - That's cold.
It's cold.
So Min.
(She pours it all over Kwang Soo's arm.)
(They're the funniest pair.)
Hurry up.
- Stop. - What are you doing?
Where is it?
(She pours it on Kwang Soo's armpit without filling half the cup.)
(His seat is soaked.)
What happened?
Why didn't it get filled?
(It's unfair how Kwang Soo got wet.)
(He really starts to act foolishly.)
(He pours the rest of the water into his cup.)
(He fills it up to the red line by taking someone else's water.)
You're a cheater.
- Give it back. - What?
- What are you doing? - What's wrong?
He filled up the cup and is going to put it in the kettle.
- We'll change his kettle. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo's foolish act fails.)
- Answer. - Here you go.
I'll do it for you.
(He feels bad for getting him soaked.)
(Apologetic Jae Seok makes a deal with Kwang Soo.)
- Answer. - It's Kwang Soo's turn.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo's time for teamwork)
I'll get it.
I think I know now.
(He pretends to be careful.)
(What happened?)
(Water comes out only a little.)
(The kettle is too light.)
(He runs out of water.)
(The water isn't enough.)
(Come on.)
I took away too much water from your kettle.
Will you keep doing this?
- Will you keep doing this? - I took away too much.
- Answer. - Let's continue.
- Isn't that it? - No.
Stop.
Did I get it? That's amazing.
I followed my senses.
- Four, abalone and chicken. - That's right.
That should be the answer.
(Haha answers correctly.)
Listen, everyone.
- People are taking the meal badges. - Wasn't I amazing?
How did I get it?
Everyone, I'm not included yet.
Do you remember what I said?
- There are 3 spots left. - 3 spots? That's right.
- Please work hard, everyone. - Okay.
There are still three spots.
I made the decision because I trust you.
Please clap for the main member today.
(Clap for the main member today.)
- Do you understand? - That's great.
Please do what I say.
Next buzzer is...
pulling sideburns.
- This is hard too. - The person next to you pulls.
- Endure it for 5 seconds. - 5 seconds?
- Please go easy on me. - Okay.
If you do it while I shout out the answer,
I'll tear it apart.
That's too harsh.
- Don't tear them. - I can't stand it.
I have to eat.
Why did you change your seat?
(What's going on?)
I couldn't participate easily as I was sitting at the edge.
- You said that you'll tear it. - I got closer.
Goodness.
- Jong Kook is being more active. - Right.
We don't have many chances left.
- I'll be more active. - Let's start.
In "The Smurfs",
the word "smurf" originates from a word that was mispronounced by...
cartoonist Peyo while eating lunch. He couldn't remember the right word.
What's the word? One, salt.
Two, soy sauce.
Three, sugar.
Four, sesame seeds.
Answer.
Pull his sideburns.
- Do I pull them? - Endure it for five seconds.
Isn't it either side?
Which side should it be?
It doesn't matter which side.
- Just pull his sideburns. - What?
His hairstyle will be flattop.
- I'm good at standing pain. - Ready.
(I'll stand the pain and say the answer.)
Start.
(He screams right away.)
- Answer! - Answer.
The person next to you will pull your sideburns.
For five seconds? I'm really good at standing pain.
(Do as you like.)
- Hey! - What?
You're supposed to pull my sideburns!
I'm really good at standing pain.
- Hey! - What?
- My sideburns... - My hands are too big.
- He... - My hands are just too big.
grabbed the hair on the side of my head.
- Stop him. - I have big hands.
Did you see that?
Let me just try. I'll let go when you tell me to.
I'll do that.
- Gosh. Okay. - It won't hurt that much.
Does it hurt?
- I can do this, right? - Hold on.
Hey, ask the others!
Is this not okay?
Is this not allowed?
That's not my sideburns.
That's not okay.
- It's not? - Don't go overboard.
Don't go overboard.
- I'll stop. - It's just too much.
I won't do it if it's too much.
Ready.
Start.
1, 2, 3,
- I don't feel anything. - 4, 5.
That was nothing.
You really didn't feel anything?
(Are you really okay?)
- Your hair got pulled out. - I didn't feel anything.
(Even though your hair got pulled out?)
You really didn't feel anything?
- Your hair got pulled out. - I didn't feel anything.
- What's your answer? - Number four, "sesame".
- "Sesame". - I was going to say that.
Number four, "sesame".
- It's wrong. - Answer!
Ji Hyo.
Soy sauce...
Start.
- It must hurt. - 1, 2, 3,
4, 5.
It must have hurt a lot.
Are you crazy?
I'm sorry. It's just a game.
It must have hurt a lot, but she put up with it.
What?
It hurt.
(Ji Hyo gets to answer.)
Just take a guess.
Answer.
Two, soy sauce.
(Wrong)
Say, "Answer!"
Answer!
Okay.
- Okay. You know... - I know.
You remember my promise, right?
- Of course. - You know how we got here, right?
Of course.
I'll pretend it hurts. Just pull it slightly.
But you're not supposed to show that it hurts.
- Start. - Start.
(Gosh)
Hey!
Start.
(Gosh)
(He is the symbol of sacrifice.)
Answer!
You should have put up with it.
(You should have put up with it.)
He should've put up with it.
- Pull his sideburns. - Me?
- The other side. - He should've put up with it.
Ready.
(Pinching)
- What are you doing? - I can't pick up his sideburns.
Are you going to pull my skin off?
- Your sideburns... - I won't feel anything anyway.
- He doesn't seem to feel pain. - I don't.
Start.
- It doesn't hurt, seriously. - 1, 2,
- three, - It doesn't hurt?
- It's really okay? - four,
- I'm totally fine. - five.
- Your skin is red. - I didn't feel anything.
- It's so red. - Your answer?
It's either of the two.
Number one.
- "Salt". - Number one, "salt".
Okay.
It's "salt"?
I thought it was "sesame".
There are two seats left.
- There are two seats left. - I have to get in.
- You remember, right? - Stop it.
- There are only 2 seats left. - There are 2 seats left.
There are only two seats left.
Let's give a big hand to today's star, Seok Jin.
We're playing this game thanks to him.
We can do this, right?
(There are only two seats left.)
Here goes the question.
Which of the four is classified as food waste?
I definitely know it.
I'm sure I know it.
I actually separate the garbage.
Number one, "onion skins".
Number two, "egg shells".
Number three, "tangerine peels".
Number four, "corn husks".
Answer!
Sideburns.
- Seok Jin. - I'm confused.
You know this.
- I know this. - Ready.
Start.
1, 2, 3...
(It hurts just by watching.)
4, 5.
Gosh.
How did she stand it?
- Ji Hyo is amazing. - It must have hurt a lot.
Which is classified as food waste?
Number three, "tangerine peels".
- Number three, "tangerine peels". - That's wrong.
(Ji Hyo passes.)
I'm good at housekeeping.
Really?
It's not "corn husks"?
- I didn't know. - Tangerine peels are food waste.
(But now...)
Guys, there's only one spot left.
What should we do?
(Without realizing...)
Guys.
- Our dream will come true? - Our last spot.
He's today's star.
- Guys. - We're really thankful.
We left the last spot for you.
I can't believe that I'm left with these two. Guys.
Okay?
This is crazy.
There are three people left.
Let me ask you something. Who's been to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?
(Me)
Who's been to Australia?
Who is going to the UK?
It turned out this way.
Okay. If I can't even beat these two...
Okay.
I can do this.
- You can sit in the middle. - Okay.
Pull my sideburns.
It's finals.
He just swore.
I think you could hear it.
- What did he say? - What did he say?
While shooting...
(Seok Jin swore.)
(Why did you swear?)
Seok Jin!
- Seriously? - I didn't.
- I didn't. - How could you do that?
Don't swear.
- Don't swear. - What did we do wrong?
I was just...
so frustrated by the situation.
Think about it.
I gave six people a chance.
They said they'd let me eat.
I can't believe I ended up here.
- You're today's star. - I can't help but laugh.
You're today's star, so you have to remain.
The person next to you will pull your sideburns.
Which of these four is considered to be a bad combination?
- I don't know this. - I know.
A bad combination?
Number one, "makgeolli and green onion pancakes".
- It's too... - Number two, "naengmyeon and meat".
Number three, "sweet potatoes and kimchi".
Number four, "pork belly and soju".
- Answer! - Answer! I know this one.
Five seconds. Ready.
(Please fail.)
Start.
(Seok Jin uses all the strength he has.)
2, 3, 4,
- five. - Done.
How did you stand it?
It hurts so much every week.
(It hurts because you're young.)
Every week...
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
Naengmyeon.
- "Pork belly and soju". - No!
- It's correct. - No!
- It's better with beer. - No way!
It can't be right.
(It's the last chance.)
- "Pork belly and soju". - No!
No!
- Okay! - No!
(No!)
(Kwang Soo is the last person to win a meal badge.)
It's a bad combination.
- The rest of you... - Okay!
Okay!
- Why me? - How can you do this to me?
- Guys. - Thank you.
- Don't you have something to say? - Okay.
- Thank you. - Say something to me.
When you get penalized...
Thank you.
Say something to me.
So Min is so bad at games.
(The 6 people get meal badges.)
Gosh, the food is here.
(Cold, raw Korean beef soup and Korean beef sushi)
This is the best.
It looks fantastic.
It looks amazing. I've never tried it.
It tastes really good.
Gosh.
- Are we supposed to add noodles? - Yes.
It tastes amazing.
It's delicious.
(The Korean beef will replenish their energy.)
The world is full of betrayals.
There's no point in being nice to others.
- This is how the world works. - That's right.
- It tastes great. - It does.
It feels like the summer is over. It's so nice and refreshing.
(Cold, raw Korean beef soup makes you forget the heat.)
I can't believe that I didn't get to eat.
- All right. - I really don't understand.
- Gosh. - I'm not 1 of the 6 people?
How did Kwang Soo get the last question right?
- At the first try. - Do we really have no chance?
- I shouldn't have trusted you guys. - Sir.
- Do we have no chance? - I'll let you...
draw a Chance Card.
- Okay. - There will be more Chance Cards.
- There will be more? Okay. - Okay.
I'll let either Seok Jin or So Min draw one.
- Should I do it? - You do it.
(To win a Chance Card...)
She's going under the table.
So Min, please.
- I really want to eat. - Two are duds.
There's 1 Everybody Eats, and 1...
What's the last one?
You get to eat.
- This one? - Yes.
(As long as she doesn't pick a dud, they can taste the food.)
Okay. Do it.
- I really want to eat. - Two are duds.
There's 1 Everybody Eats, and 1...
What's the last one?
You get to eat.
- This one? - Yes.
(As long as she doesn't pick a dud, they can taste the food.)
Okay. Do it.
If it's a dud, I'll jump out the window.
- This is good. - It's a dud.
Why? Is it a dud?
(Why?)
(Is it a dud?)
- Hey, come on. - Goodness.
What did you just do? I'll pick one.
I'll show you the rest. This one was a dud,
- Two Bites, - What's going on?
and Everybody Eats.
See? You should have picked that.
I've been with these people a lot.
They'll somehow pick a dud.
(Teasing)
- Why? - They just can't do it.
It's my first time trying this. It's really good.
- It's good. - This is so good.
- Just one of us. - This is too bad.
I ate so much earlier. I'm full, so I can't eat too much.
- Gosh, this punk. - What do you mean?
You're so annoying.
- Hey. - Fine, you can curse.
- Go ahead. - Hey, think about it.
I'm the one who prepared this meal.
"I'm the one who prepared this meal."
I'm so upset.
I'm the one who prepared this meal.
Does it make sense that I can't eat at all?
We can't do anything about that.
We all had to solve quizzes to eat.
It was a difficult process for us too.
(Only 6 members got to eat. Now, they're going for sturgeon sashimi.)
I have no meal badge.
Who doesn't have any badges?
You two.
(Seok Jin and So Min)
- It's just us two? - Yes.
(I shouldn't have asked.)
- Haha and I have two badges. - Fine.
- Okay. - Am I being bullied?
Fine, I get it. I'll pay back what I suffered.
Sir, you don't have too much time for a payback.
We just need to go to two places, and we're done.
Yes, that's right.
- We're all full right now. - That's right.
- Did you say, "we're all full"? - To be honest...
(What?)
Hey, I'm so hungry right now.
- We didn't eat. - She and I...
You two can get hit with the water bomb.
- In general. - I agree.
Fine.
(He's going to be drinking a lot of water.)
Do you want to play a game?
- That was fun. - Which one?
Do you want to play 3, 6, 9?
- Okay. - All right.
This is how we're choosing a representative.
If you become a representative again,
- you can pick new people. - Okay.
Let's start with Seok Jin and end with Jae Seok.
- Like this? - Let's start.
- 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
- 1. - 1.
(Clapping)
- You're out. - One.
(She was supposed to say, "two".)
- That was predicted. - Okay.
- You're the first one to go. - It's Ji Hyo.
- That never happened. - She's out.
- Ji Hyo. - She has the minus touch.
- That wasn't totally unexpected. - Right.
It's too bad. Actually, let me take that back.
- Give me another chance. - We can't.
I just taught it to her.
- Let's get started again. - Start.
- 3, 6, 9 - 3, 6, 9
- 1. - 1.
(Clap?)
- Don't do it. - Fine.
- I wanted to join. - What's wrong with you?
- You weren't supposed to clap. - I wanted to join.
It was "two".
- Fine. - Why did you clap?
This is the order, right?
- 5. - 5.
(After Ji Hyo stops playing, they continue.)
Seven.
(He takes a while.)
- Seven. - Jong Kook.
- No. - I got confused because of her.
She confused me. I forgot she's not playing.
- 15. - 15.
15.
One.
(It's 16.)
He's so confident.
It's hard after 10.
- Hold on. - Kwang Soo is the winner.
(After many rounds, Kwang Soo becomes the representative.)
Kwang Soo is going to want to save himself...
and see the rest of us get wet.
- I know it's true... - He'll choose three people.
- I agree. - If you pick three people...
and you don't get a badge,
you'll get wet if you're not in first place.
- That's right. - You'll get people's criticism too.
(You'll get both.)
- No, I'll hit him. - Right. He'll hit you.
(Look at these people.)
- If it's water and criticism... - Be quiet.
Let's focus now.
- Should we think silently? - I like that idea.
- If it's going to be this way... - Be quiet.
Quiet.
I pick three people.
You can pick when we get off.
- Calm down. - They have sturgeons here.
- Look. - This is it?
- Is this a farm? - Yes, they have them here.
- That's right. - Be careful.
- This is a farm. - These are sturgeons.
There they are.
It's a sturgeon!
- Where? It's a sturgeon. - It's a sturgeon.
Didn't Seok Jin say that they're small?
- They're huge. - Some of them are big.
- They're big. - How do we catch them? Look.
They're huge.
He'll show you how to catch it.
- Really? - Hello.
- You catch it by yourself? - Yes.
(He uses a basic net.)
- Sir. - Do you make sashimi right away?
He catches a big one?
(He enters the farm with just a net.)
- It's too big, sir. - You're right. It's really big.
(He moves the net carefully.)
Is he going under it?
(He successfully catches the sturgeon.)
(Look at how strong it is.)
It's so big.
(How many members will get to eat?)
It's really strong.
Let me be realistic.
(He has to pick 3 or 6 people.)
There's plenty of chance to get first place.
(Kwang Soo gets to see it first.)
This is how it looks like. There's caviar too.
(There's sturgeon sashimi, liver, skin, and caviar.)
The third menu is sturgeon sashimi.
Between three people, including yourself, eating...
or six random people eating, which do you choose?
- Can it be just one person? - No.
For your information, looking at the remaining time,
if you pick three people, you'll lose the mission.
(There is 1.5 hours left.)
(If he picks 3 people, he gets to eat and get a badge.)
If I pick three people, I'll lose?
Based on the remaining time, that's likely.
(If he picks 3 people, he gets to eat and get a badge.)
- I'll have two badges, right? - Yes.
(Why do I have to face this ordeal?)
(Let me think rationally.)
(He peeks at the sashimi.)
(Kwang Soo is in deep thought. What is his decision?)
(Quivering)
I think he picked six random people. I'm slightly hopeful.
Kwang Soo, is it three people?
I think he picked six people.
I think so too.
He won't. He won't pick six people.
Between picking three people including himself...
or six random people...
- If he picked three people... - That would be a surprise.
That means he doesn't think.
That's like a treason.
That's right. That's betraying the whole team.
- That means the day is over. - He picked three people.
Kwang Soo...
(What did Kwang Soo choose?)
Kwang Soo picked six random people.
(That was unexpected.)
- Really? - Why?
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Why did you do that? - I...
If I had none, I would have picked three people right away.
But I have this.
(He thought it'd be beneficial for him to win the mission.)
- I pick six people. - Okay.
I mentioned this earlier, but he won't ruin it for us.
This mission will decide which six people get to eat.
- It's the Apartment Game. - "Apartment"?
(Apartment Game)
- What is it? - This?
(Do you stack something?)
You'll be in teams of four people, and each team will take turns.
I'll say a random number, and you have to stack your fists.
The bottom hand goes to the top, and you stack them...
starting from one.
If your turn lands on the number I called, you're out.
Okay. You're out?
(If your turn is the number that's called, you're out.)
- This is all luck. - However,
you're not just stacking. You'll slap the hand that's on top.
(You have to slap the hand on top and place your hand above it.)
If you can't withstand the pain and make noise,
- you're out. - We can't make noise?
(They didn't know about this one.)
Where Jong Kook's hand is...
We're on this side.
- No. - I picked the wrong seat.
- No, we have to choose teams. - We get to pick.
I don't want to be on Jong Kook's or Kwang Soo's team.
Kwang Soo has big hands.
We have to avoid Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
Haha first.
(There are 4 yellow spoons, and 4 red spoons.)
- It's yellow. - He's weak.
- It's yellow. - She's weak.
I have to be on that team.
Yellow.
(So Min picks yellow as well.)
- What? Yes. - What?
- If he's yellow, it's over. - As long as it's not Jong Kook.
(Team Yellow has the weak people. There's only 1 space left.)
(I want to be on this team too.)
It's red.
(Kwang Soo picks Team Red.)
(That was expected.)
Obviously.
(Everybody wants to be on Team Yellow.)
This...
(What did Jae Seok pick?)
Gosh.
(Jae Seok is also on Team Red.)
Okay. It's my turn.
(Let me take that last spot in Team Yellow.)
(Team Red is already dirty.)
(Team Yellow is the weak team with one space left.)
(Where will Se Chan go?)
(Goodness)
(Se Chan is also on Team Red.)
This is the best.
(The weakest and the strongest are left.)
Please.
- Seok Jin! - Seok Jin!
- At the same time? - 1, 2, 3.
(There's 1 space left in each team.)
- Please. - Please.
(This is the only time Seok Jin is popular. Which team is lucky?)
(Team Red gets Seok Jin.)
(Yes, we have him.)
(Team Red is so happy.)
What? Do we get Jong Kook?
(There's a predator...)
(amongst the weak ones.)
- This is good. - That was no joke.
(The teams have been decided.)
I should have gone to the other team.
- That was nerve-wrecking. - We're good.
I'm going to endure the pain.
- Let me apologize ahead of time. - I'll clench my teeth and endure.
If you make any kind of noise, you're out, right?
If you make any kind of noise, you are...
- 1 of 2 people who can't eat. - That's right.
One person is out.
- They can't eat. - Yes, they're out.
Start.
- Apartment - Apartment
I'm crossing the bridge on a starry night
(They sing until the director calls out a number.)
(Let's eat some sturgeon sashimi.)
And passing by a windy reed field
(They have to stack both hands.)
(My sturgeon sashimi)
15 floors.
- Okay, this is good. - This is good.
You can bring your hand to the top and say, "First floor".
(Kwang Soo is on the bottom, and Seok Jin is on top.)
(Kwang Soo slaps Seok Jin's hand, and Seok Jin can't make any noises.)
(Kwang Soo jumps and slaps.)
That wasn't as bad as I thought.
(What?)
You made a sound.
(That means you're out.)
No.
He's out.
(He didn't understand the rules. He was loud, and he's out.)
He didn't understand the game.
(Isn't it okay as long as it didn't hurt?)
(You're not supposed to make any noise.)
No way.
(Nice, Seok Jin.)
Did you see that?
"That wasn't as bad as I thought."
(Seok Jin can't eat.)
That was unbelievable.
(Seok Jin gets to keep starving. Who will join him from Team Yellow?)
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Apartment - Apartment
(Team Yellow starts.)
(The person who gets eliminated doesn't get to eat the sashimi.)
(They have their arms around each other and sing.)
(So Min is so weak.)
So Min doesn't want to do it.
She doesn't want to do it.
(She didn't eat at all. She doesn't want to do it.)
(When the director calls out a number, they have to stack.)
(Creaking)
- 13 floors. - 13 floors.
Why do you look so unenthusiastic?
- It's so obvious. - Stop pretending.
- I'm sorry. I stacked wrong. - 13 floors?
I stacked my hands wrong.
I'm dead.
(Haha gets to slap So Min's hands.)
First floor.
(He slaps with full power.)
She didn't make noise.
You shouldn't say the floor numbers.
Do we have to...
- call out the floor? - It doesn't matter.
The one getting hit can't make a noise.
Two?
(It's Jong Kook's turn against the coward, Haha.)
He's using his right hand.
(If Haha makes any noise, he doesn't get to eat.)
(Why did So Min make noise?)
What?
(Haha didn't say anything, but So Min started crying.)
- She made noise. - So Min is out.
It wasn't your turn.
- It wasn't your turn, right? - Already?
Why you? What's wrong?
I got slapped.
- My hand hurts too. - Why?
I didn't get slapped directly, but it hurts.
That was so useless.
(So Min and Seok Jin can't eat.)
I've never had sturgeon sashimi before.
There's soup too.
You can have it as shabu shabu.
There's caviar.
This is good.
Can I have the sauce?
(Seok Jin won the bonus game, and he gets to eat.)
This is really good as shabu shabu.
(This is the best.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Let me see. Let me see your hand.
Let me try the shabu shabu.
I will make shabu shabu.
(Let me parboil your hand.)
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
So Min must be hungry.
(She didn't get to eat at all.)
So Min, I can't give you a badge,
but I'll give you a chance to eat the sashimi.
Can't you give me a badge?
I can't.
I can let you eat.
I do want to give her a chance.
Okay.
Can I have a bite?
Can you make an acrostic poem with "sturgeon sashimi"?
- Sturgeon sashimi? That's hard. - If the staff members...
laugh, you win.
That's so hard.
- Sturgeon sashimi. - So Min.
- Do a cute version like Twice. - That's right.
(Do you remember?)
(Twice's cute acrostic poems were a big hit a month ago.)
(This is how you act cute.)
(The staff fell for them too.)
- Do the cute version. - They'll laugh.
Our staff...
- "S". Start over. - "S".
So Min loves you.
(So Min loves you.)
(They're not laughing yet.)
- "G". - "G".
Gosh.
(She tries to act cute.)
Nobody is laughing.
(There's no expression on his face.)
I'm speechless.
(They're not laughing at all.)
"S".
Start smiling!
(That wasn't good.)
How can I make you laugh when you're trying not to?
It worked because it was Twice.
They were trying to be open-minded.
First of all...
(If you're going to be this way,)
(how's this?)
They are pretty.
(She tries to make them laugh with a cute dance.)
(She's doing that again.)
(He is ignoring her.)
Don't I look like Twice?
(She tries her best.)
They're heartless.
(The members don't laugh either.)
When Twice was here,
they were drooling while watching Twice.
(They were drooling while watching Twice.)
(They were all smiles.)
You're too strict towards So Min. You're too cold.
- That's tough. - They're so cold.
So Min.
(Poor So Min.)
(Will Jae Seok give her a bite?)
Eat the next one.
(Give up on this one.)
- There's another chance. - He was...
so mean. You were eating too.
Eat the next one.
That's a way.
Where are we going to next?
You can pick.
We're here right now.
(It's time to pick the next restaurant.)
- Should we go this way? - Go down.
(There's eel or nine-seafood stew.)
- We have to try nine-seafood stew. - It sounds interesting.
I've never had it before. Nine-seafood stew.
All right. That's the next menu.
(Nine-seafood stew is the next menu.)
Let's pick the next representative with the spoons.
(Ji Hyo, So Min, Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok are left.)
(The person who picks a red spoon is the representative.)
- I saw the yellow. - Me too.
(I saw So Min's yellow spoon.)
Why didn't you say anything?
I couldn't say anything.
So Min, your spoon is yellow.
(She tries to switch.)
- Goodness. - You were hiding it, but we saw it.
(I hope I picked red this time.)
- Ji Hyo first. - Ji Hyo first.
- Do I go first? - Yes.
(She picks a red spoon.)
(How typical.)
- You saw it. - I'll take them back.
Ji Hyo, let's go for six people.
I knew it would be her. She's good.
There was no point in changing it.
Nine-seafood stew is the last item.
- I really want to try it. - It's today's highlight.
This is the main item.
Will I...
get to eat it or surrender?
(She tries to joke.)
It's raining today.
- It'll be cold. - If you get wet, it will be.
If there are two people in last place,
they'll compete to pick one loser.
(There'll be a match to pick one loser.)
So Min has a chance then.
What if the loser picks one person to take the penalty with?
All of a sudden?
I don't like that idea.
Everything is a competition.
- Do you have none? - I have none.
I'm the only one without a badge.
- And you didn't eat at all? - No.
It's rare for either Kwang Soo or I to...
- get penalties two weeks in a row. - That's right.
It doesn't happen.
- She's incredible. - She is.
She's a legend.
I'm so depressed. It's raining too.
(What is wrong with me?)
It's raining
- So I thought of you - So I thought of you
- And the music plays - When were you born?
- I think of - There are many songs about rain.
I think of you
(She expresses her depressed feelings with songs.)
Old songs have good lyrics.
- "Letter" is good too. - Right, "Letter".
- Is this - Is this
We're in harmony.
- The end - The end
- Is that harmony? - Really?
You just can't sing, so you're singing in different keys.
- We weren't totally off. - No, we were not.
- That worked a little bit. - Who's singing the melody?
- I'll do it. - You will?
Sing in harmony. 1, 2, start.
(So Min is the main vocalist.)
(Let's sing in harmony.)
- Is this - Is this
(It's terrifying.)
(It's a frightening harmony.)
- You're pretty good. - Right?
- He's pretty good. - Right.
- He's not sloppy. - No.
I'm solid.
- You're solid. - I'm good, right?
(They sing a cappella this time.)
(I'd rather not watch.)
(Beatboxing)
This isn't bad.
When the night
Has come
His voice...
sounds like Cherry Boy's.
(He's an old singer.)
(Cherry Boy?)
That's so funny.
Jeery Boy.
- "Jeery Boy". - Jeery Boy.
(Seok Jin is Jeery Boy.)
(Jeery Boy?)
Nice one.
My songs are not hot.
- I'm Jeery Boy. - Jeery Boy.
It's a bit bland.
It's clear.
It's Jeery.
- Jeery Boy. - It's clear soup.
We're missing a word in front.
Pee Jeery Boy.
("Pee" is the missing word.)
(Pee Jeery Boy?)
Jeery Boy.
(He becomes a dirty boy.)
- Pee Jeery Boy. - Pee Jeery Boy.
Remove the first word.
Jeery Boy is better.
It's like a stage name.
That was hilarious.
(After the Jeery Boy fiasco)
- I think we are here. - I know.
(He doesn't wake up.)
(He is sleeping.)
He is sleeping.
(Shall we pull a prank on him?)
(Okay, I have an idea.)
(Cheering)
(He wakes up in a surprised state.)
- That's amazing. - I can't believe it.
Will the rule apply from now on?
You agree with the decision, right?
- Yes. - It's just unexpected.
Then a come-from-behind victory will be possible.
- That's right. - Let's stop talking about it.
- Okay. - Don't change your mind.
- Okay. - Don't change the rule.
- We can turn the tables. - It's more than possible.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Seok Jin...
Is it possible to turn the tables?
(Slurring)
(They can't hold in their laughter.)
(Why are they laughing?)
- What? - Your pronunciation.
What's wrong with your pronunciation?
Seok Jin, do you even know how to turn the tables?
Why would you continue on with the shoot without me?
(Why would you continue on with the shoot without me?)
Seriously.
You fell asleep.
(Tell me how to turn the tables.)
This is the best.
(Ji Hyo gets to make the final decision.)
(This is nine-seafood stew.)
It smells delicious.
(The dish contains ingredients from the land, sea, and air.)
(Nine-seafood stew is the epitome of invigorating food...)
(that contains ogol chicken, octopus, abalone, and more.)
It looks amazing.
Since this is the last decision,
I will choose six people.
(She chooses 6 people without hesitation...)
(to get 20 servings.)
The mission to determine the six people who get to eat is...
the backwards long jump.
You will stand at the end of the mat and jump backwards.
The six people who jump the farthest...
will get to eat.
All right.
Okay.
(Ji Hyo's record isn't very good.)
What was that?
(Hopping)
(Seok Jin places last.)
Thus, the bottom two are Ji Hyo and Seok Jin.
(Everyone except for Ji Hyo and Seok Jin get to eat.)
What is that?
(The sight makes their mouths water.)
Oh, my goodness.
It's sad that I can't eat it.
- It's sad that I can't eat it. - I get to eat it.
- It's invigorating food. - I get to eat it.
- Seok Jin doesn't get to eat it. - I get to eat it.
- Seok Jin doesn't get to eat it. - Jae Seok, let's eat.
Okay.
- Thank you for the food. - I chose six people...
- for the members. - Thank you so much.
(How does nine-seafood stew taste?)
It contains a whole chicken.
- A whole chicken. - This is...
I will eat a drumstick.
(It's tender and chewy.)
My goodness.
Look at that conch.
It's invigorating food.
Isn't there...
- a Chance Card? - A Chance Card.
Would you please let...
one of us eat?
We should give some food to Ji Hyo.
- Why? - Why?
- She sacrificed herself for us. - I chose...
six people so that the members could eat.
I chose six people earlier as well.
That was forever ago.
(That was forever ago.)
- All right. - That was forever ago.
He keeps talking about the past.
Just know that I am waiting to take my revenge.
I am waiting to take my revenge.
Will you let them play Pirate Roulette Game...
for a chance to eat?
- Sure. - I am for it.
It's not too much to ask of us.
- If you make the pirate pop up... - Then you don't get to eat.
(Then you don't get to eat.)
(Let's see who gets to taste the nine-seafood stew.)
Okay.
(Seok Jin's first try is a success.)
(Should I insert it here or there?)
(She hesitates for a while...)
(and succeeds to insert a sword.)
Okay, I will choose the slot you didn't choose.
That's the slot Ji Hyo didn't choose.
(That's the slot Ji Hyo didn't choose.)
(Popping up)
(Seok Jin loses.)
Did it end already?
- Ji Hyo avoided the slot. - Move.
- You avoided the slot. - Move.
- My goodness. - Move.
Seok Jin is really unlucky.
I think he will receive the penalty.
I think so.
This will be the end of my bad luck.
(This is tasty.)
May I give you a 3-line poem about 9-seafood stew?
Go ahead.
- The 1st line. - The 1st line.
I refuse to beg for food.
Fine.
(I refuse to beg for food.)
(Fine.)
Fine.
- You refuse to beg for food. - I am not done yet.
The second line.
I await my chance for a revenge.
The third line.
Bang, bang, bang, I shoot.
(Bang, bang, bang, I shoot.)
("Bang, bang, bang, I shoot"?)
I find it funny.
I find it funny. "Bang, bang, bang, I shoot."
It's so ridiculous...
that it's funny.
I like ridiculous jokes.
- The octopus is tasty. - The octopus is really tasty.
Try the octopus.
This is driving me crazy. Why did it pop up?
Would you give me...
a little bit of the soup?
(Can't they hear me?)
It's invigorating food.
- Really? - Yes.
The soup is...
Please give me a little bit of the soup.
The soup won't taste this way without these ingredients.
- How does the soup taste so good? - Seriously.
It's so tasty.
These jerks are too much.
(These jerks are too much.)
(Seok Jin explodes.)
Hold on. What was that?
Don't be like that.
- Don't get angry. - You won't give me a bite.
(Don't you have the common courtesy before nine-seafood stew?)
Thank you.
- It was delicious. - We had a good meal.
We are eating a lot of invigorating food today.
- Did you enjoy the food? - Yes.
Here is the result.
You succeeded the mission by eating 22 servings...
in five hours.
(The mission is a success.)
- Yes! - Yes!
The member with the smallest number of meal badges...
will receive the penalty.
Currently, Seok Jin and So Min are tied...
with one meal badge each.
We will now have a death match...
to choose the person who will receive the penalty.
(The death match begins now.)
Stop the retracting tape measure to get the shorter length.
If it retracts all the way, you lose.
This is fun.
- This is so much fun. - Haha likes these games.
This is nerve-wracking.
(Let's see who avoids the penalty.)
- I will go first. - Seok Jin will go first.
This is the real round.
- All right. - I am so nervous.
Get ready. You only have one chance.
- What should I do? - Get ready.
All right.
(How much can Seok Jin shorten the tape?)
(He stops it.)
All right.
- It's 50cm. - It's 53cm.
It's 53.5cm to be precise.
- It's long. - Make it shorter than that.
So Min, you can relax.
I can't predict who will win.
- You can relax. - I am nervous.
Get ready.
Seok Jin's record is 53.5cm.
(Seok Jin's record is 53.5cm.)
(Can So Min make the tape shorter than 53.5cm?)
(Coming soon)
(The 2018 FIFA World Cup Russia)
- Goal! - Goal!
(The beginning of the legend)
Hurrah for Korea!
(The legends of the Korean soccer...)
(who made us laugh and cry will come.)
("All The Butlers" and the World Cup Legends will air shortly.)
Seok Jin's record is 53.5cm.
(Seok Jin's record is 53.5cm.)
(Can So Min make the tape shorter than 53.5cm?)
Let's go.
The tape is long.
(It doesn't look much different from Seok Jin's.)
No, no.
It's 50cm.
(So Min's record is 50cm.)
- It's 50cm. - 50cm.
(I can't believe it.)
- It's 50cm. - It's 50cm.
- Seok Jin gets the penalty. - Yes.
The result was divided by 3cm.
It was a neck-and-neck match.
You are good.
(I can't believe you beat me.)
(She is bad at games, but Seok Jin is worse.)
You are good.
Thus, Seok Jin will receive the penalty.
(Seok Jin moves for a water bomb attack.)
Okay.
Seok Jin will now receive the penalty.
- It's raining. - Yes, it is.
- It's a good day to get a penalty. - That's right.
A water-related penalty on a rainy day.
You can hit above his face.
(Throwing)
That's it.
(Popping)
- The above? - Yes.
(Smile because this is a water bomb festival.)
There you go.
(It's a happy day.)
That was a nice shot.
(He straightens his shoulders...)
(and aims for his target perfectly.)
(Popping)
This is fun.
(Never cry)
Hold on.
(Hitting)
My goodness.
Why is my aim so good today?
It just happened that way.
It can't be helped.
Who did that?
Come here.
(Wait until I catch you.)
(Seok Jin explodes for the 2nd time.)
My goodness.
(No matter what anyone says,)
- My goodness. - Seok Jin.
(today is Seok Jin's lucky day.)
All right.
(One peaceful day)
(A group of thieves showed up.)
(The people were starving.)
(They were waiting for someone who would rescue them.)
(These women joined to save the miserable people.)
(Son Dam Bi, a sniper after their hearts)
(Gyeong Ree, charming master of smiles)
(Seo Eun Su, a golden thief)
(Lee Gook Ju, hunter looking for laughter)
(However,)
(the boss of the thieves and the king are hidden among them?)
(The boss must steal without getting caught by the king.)
(The king must sweep the group of thieves for the people.)
(Everything will go to waste the moment the identities are revealed.)
(Who will win at this mind game where they deceive each other?)
(Ms. Son, the poor civilian...)
(Mr. Thief, this is crazy)
(Don't Trust Them)