- Hello. - Hello.
What is this place? I have never been here before.
- It must be new. - Prehistoric Park.
It's a prehistoric person who is barbecuing a pig.
Seok Jin used to live here.
Seok Jin, say hello to them.
(Seok Jin, welcome home.)
Seok Jin, why did you wear clothes?
You used to wear animal hides.
- I used to wear animal hides. - That's right.
(The breakfast of a prehistoric celebrity)
Jae Seok, I don't know you anymore.
- What do you mean? - I don't know you anymore.
You are so frustrating.
- You are suspicious. - Jong Kook was strange,
- but Jae Seok was stranger. - He is strange.
To be honest, you are more suspicious than Kwang Soo now.
- You drive me crazy. - You know what I am like.
When people suspect me, I get into the character.
- But he... - Stop doing that.
Stop doing that.
- Stop doing that. - He loves attention too much.
When he gets a solo shot,
he absorbs attention like a sponge.
(I can do anything for a solo shot.)
He zooms into himself.
It's called the Solo Shot Syndrome.
- When he gets a solo shot... - Isn't it incurable?
- Isn't it incurable? - It's incurable.
- Solo Shot Syndrome. - When he gets a solo shot,
- he feels like he needs to act. - That's right.
Thus, the majority of the posts on the website is...
- about me. - That's right.
I get a lot of malicious comments.
(He gets a lot of malicious comments.)
They say criticism lengthens life. You are practically immortal.
(He becomes immortal from too much criticism.)
- You are immortal. - He is immortal.
Not even Emperor Qin Shi Huang could achieve that feat.
- In the past, you got no comments. - "Stop talking." What?
- You got no comments. - I got, "Cheer up."
"Cheer up."
- "Good luck." - You cheered up too much.
That's right. I cheered up too much.
- He should have stopped himself. - It's an interest in me.
- It is. - I like the malicious comments.
What are we doing today?
- A video? - Is there a video?
(Is there a video that introduces today's race?)
- Is there a video? - Will we get a silhouette?
- Kwang Soo. - Where is this place?
(A mysterious place)
- What is this? - When was this taken?
- It's mysterious. - Who is that?
(A mysterious man)
(Who is this middle-aged man?)
- Isn't he Seok Jin? - Who is he?
- He has defined features. - Is he Lee Duk Hwa?
Is he Kim Byung Man?
He is Kim Byung Ok!
- He is Kim Byung Ok. - My goodness.
(A charismatic middle-aged man, Kim Byung Ok)
(Byung Ok, it's nice to meet you.)
- It's your dad. - Seriously.
- It's your dad. - I know.
(What is Byung Ok doing here?)
My lovely sons and daughters,
how have you been?
(My lovely sons and daughters, how have you been?)
- What? - He must be our dad.
- He is our dad. - Father.
I thought So Min resembled him a lot.
Because I had to roam the world for business,
I couldn't look after you.
That's right.
Seok Jin, you were a loser with a runny nose.
- That sounds like him. - Jae Seok,
you were the mischievous one.
Jong Kook, you were like the eldest since you didn't care about the age.
- He doesn't care about the age. - He doesn't care about the age.
- He doesn't care about the age. - That sounds like him.
Ji Hyo, you were always in a daze.
Haha, you worried a lot because you didn't grow taller.
Se Chan, you liked to make people laugh.
Kwang Soo, you made me worry because you lacked in every way.
(He remembers that Kwang Soo lacked in every way.)
- What? - So Min, you resembled me a lot.
- That's right. - She does resemble him.
I am very proud...
that everyone grew up well.
- Mother struggled a lot. - He is our dad.
- We are a family today. - He is our dad.
There is a reason why I made you gather around today.
What is that?
When I was little, my late mother always made me...
a certain dish in autumn.
- Mom passed away. - His mom passed away.
Mom!
(Why is he acting that way?)
Our grandma passed away.
- Our grandma. - Our grandma?
- He is talking about our grandma. - He suddenly went, "Mom!"
- Mom, I am sorry. Mom, I love you! - Our grandma.
Stay healthy.
(His mom is alive and well.)
When I was little, my late mother always made me...
a certain dish in autumn.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't remember what the dish is.
Do we need to find it for him?
Please find the food I am looking for...
by this evening.
(Please find the food I am looking for by this evening.)
Food?
What is it?
If you find it for me,
I will leave all of my fortune to you.
(Is this an opportunity to receive all of this fortune?)
If you don't find it,
you will receive a big punishment.
(You will receive a big punishment.)
What kind of a dad is he?
- I think he is nice. - It's ridiculous.
- Seriously. - What kind of a dad...
forces his children to be devoted?
It's not like he was interested in us before.
I will leave this game.
He is a rebel.
Dad doesn't seem to be much older than Seok Jin.
He had me when he was five.
(They look like brothers.)
- He had Seok Jin at a young age. - That's right.
You are five years apart from Dad.
That's right.
- They are like Haha and me. - Seok Jin was adopted.
Today, you will find the food of your dad's life.
The race is titled Go, Determined Gourmet.
Go, Determined Gourmet.
(Go, Determined Gourmet)
Every time you complete a mission, you will receive a hint.
You can check your answer at the restaurant...
that sells the dish.
The time limit is six hours.
If you bring the food before the sun sets,
you will inherit the fortune.
If you fail, you will receive a big punishment.
- Okay. - Okay.
The mission to receive the first hint is...
One-mind Family Portrait.
(One-mind Family Portrait)
One-mind?
Gosh, what is this?
It's a mission that requires unanimity.
You succeed...
if all the members take a photo with an identical item.
If you fail, the minority that chose a different item...
will receive a penalty from the majority.
What is this?
We are Running Man.
- We are Running Man. - Now,
please run to the hut.
- Don't walk, but run. Running Man! - Running Man!
(Each one of them takes a hut.)
My goodness.
It's impossible for eight people to choose the same thing.
The same item?
(The question is revealed after they enter the hut...)
What's the question?
(so that they don't plan ahead.)
"Pick a wig and put it on."
(Pick a wig and put it on.)
(It's a success if everyone picks the same wig.)
This is driving me crazy.
We need to pick the same wig, right?
(They may succeed if they read the members' minds.)
This is a mission about having the one mind, right?
This is... This is...
It has to be this wig. This wig suits Running Man.
(It suits a variety show.)
This wig suits Running Man.
This wig suits Running Man. There's nothing better.
Kwang Soo and I wore it.
I made up my mind as soon as you took out the wigs.
It's my favorite item.
(It's my favorite item.)
I wear it often. It's a bald wig.
Comedians would go with this one.
(I need to wear it for more screen time.)
I wore something similar last week. I feel like something is missing...
without a bald wig.
Okay. I think everyone will choose this wig.
(The male members choose the same wig.)
This is the one.
Hold on a second.
I think Ji Hyo will choose the pink wig.
(What if they want to look pretty?)
I think So Min will choose a red wig.
Given other members' preferences,
it's likely that they will choose a funny sig.
These two are funny.
(Is it Young Gu's wig or the bald one?)
I saw Ji Hyo wearing this wig a lot.
(What should I do? Ji Hyo seems to like Young Gu's wig.)
So Min dressed up as Chucky a while ago. Should I go with this?
(Will Ji Hyo choose an unexpected wig?)
(If Ji Hyo and So Min choose the right one, it'll end.)
We wore this wig a lot on Running Man.
Should I put on this one?
(Will they be able to choose the same wig as the other members?)
I'll count to five.
5, 4...
Everyone might choose the same wig.
- Three. - We all might get the right wig.
- 2, 1. - This one stood out right away!
Come on out. One. Come on out.
(What's the wig that they all chose?)
- That's right! - Hey!
- That's right. - Yes, this is the one.
- This is the wig. - This is it.
- That's right. - Yes!
- That's it. - Hey!
(All the male members chose the same wig.)
(Now, it all depends on So Min and Ji Hyo.)
Hey, we all chose the same one!
(Which wig did So Min choose?)
I knew it!
(7 members including So Min chose the same wig.)
(Now, only Ji Hyo's choice remains. Will they succeed on the first try?)
(No way. Ji Hyo is the only one who chose a red wig.)
(Due to Ji Hyo, the 1st round is a failure.)
- Hey, it's this wig. - My goodness.
- You wanted to look pretty. - You wanted to be the pretty one.
(Our looks are important too.)
- No, no. Seriously. Listen. - Come on, this one was obvious.
- Hey, this is the wig. - No, watch my clips later.
I was thinking of putting that on even until the last moment.
- My goodness. - I can't believe this.
- Seriously. - This is our show's signature wig.
- This is our signature wig. - Come on.
- Goodness. - She's unbelievable.
- Listen. In there... - Ji Hyo.
- Why did you choose that one? - I was torn between that and this.
- I'm serious. I held it to the end. - It could've ended right away.
By the way, when everyone was walking out,
everyone's forehead was shining.
- I'm telling you. - It was shining.
- When I was coming out in this wig, - By the way...
- I almost cried. I'm serious. - Everyone chose this.
I choked up for a second.
It was the most touching moment after the World Cup.
Seriously.
But as for Jong Kook,
- he looks scary with just this wig. - Hey.
- I look like Predator. - Why does he look so scary?
(He wanted to be funny, but he looks like he's about to invade Earth.)
- Goodness, we were so close. - Right.
- I bet the staff was surprised too. - Hey, by the way...
(Are those markers?)
(The marker makeup is the penalty for failing the mission.)
(Seok Jin, the makeup artist, starts off the makeup.)
(A few strokes of the marker...)
This is Se Chan's makeup.
I'll just do this.
- Gosh. - But the makeup looks nice on you.
You know what?
Ji Hyo humbly accepts the makeup, right?
- She has no choice. - She's the only one.
- Seriously. - Hey.
- I was holding it until the end. - I can't do it.
- We'll start the second round. - Okay.
- Please go back to your own hut. - So this is how the game is played.
- Okay. - I got it. I know how to play it.
We'll succeed this time.
We must be able to put ourselves in each other's shoes.
Think about the whole group, not just the individual.
Gosh, that was so close.
(Which choice will be unanimous this time?)
(There are various funny glasses.)
(They must choose the same pair among three to succeed.)
This time, we'll definitely succeed.
(He grabs a pair without thinking about it.)
It's definitely this one.
(On Running Man, it's the glasses with the big nose.)
We'll succeed this time.
Two of our members have big noses.
Seok Jin and Jae Seok.
We always joked about it.
It's...
this pair of glasses with the big nose.
(It's the pair of glasses with the big nose.)
I look just like Jae Seok.
This is my signature pair of glasses.
The glasses with the big nose.
I'm 100 percent sure we'll get this one.
But I'm not sure.
Seok Jin is getting greedy with close-up shots.
He might think about this from the staff's point of view.
He might wear this one.
(Bingo!)
(How come his behavior is always so predictable?)
(The close-up shot is all mine!)
Let me see which one looks the best on me.
(All he thinks about is the close-up shot. Which one will he choose?)
All right. Here we go.
- 5, 4, - Use our telepathy!
- 3, 2, 1. - Whoever gets it wrong is done for.
- We don't have to think about this. - It's so obvious.
(It has to be the pair of glasses with the big nose.)
- That's right. This has to be it. - It's the big nose.
- This is it. Great. - We don't even need to think.
(Except for Seok Jin, all 7 of them chose the same one.)
(Now, Seok Jin has to choose the same pair.)
That's it.
(A shot with dizzy eyes)
Exactly.
- Why did he choose that one? - What is that? Darn it.
Come on, Seok Jin.
- You know what? - He wants to get a close-up.
This is what I said in my hut. I'll tell you what I said.
I said everyone would definitely go for this pair...
except for Seok Jin who wants to get a close-up.
- Seok Jin. - This is unbelievable.
- Don't try to stand out. - How could you choose that one?
I always wear that one. Do you think I want to put that on?
- Exactly. I knew it. - I always wear that one.
- This is wrong. Seriously. - Look.
Hand them over. Seok Jin should get his penalty.
(A marker therapy to cure his syndrome begins.)
I should draw on his nose like this.
Hey, only one of you should do it.
- You look great. - Hey, you look so cool.
- Really? - You look like Tongki.
- Are you serious? - You look great.
You look like a hero character.
- Okay, okay. - Really?
(Close-up Shot Hero, Mr. Seok Jin)
- Let's get it right this time. - Let's do this right.
- Let's take this seriously. - Be serious.
Don't think about yourself, but the whole group.
I'm serious.
I didn't predict this. See? Look at him.
- Look at him. - He was in "Snowpiercer".
- "Snowpiercer". - Right.
- Right. He looks just like her. - It's his lost sister.
Go look for your sister.
- Let's focus. - This is so frustrating.
- Now, I want to stand out too. - All right.
I bet you're starting to want those close-up shots.
You want those shots little by little.
Seok Jin is enjoying this.
He's liking this.
Gosh, name tags?
(Are those name tags of the members?)
(Why are there name tags out of the blue?)
"Among the members of Running Man,"
"choose the name tag of the ugliest member."
(The ugliest member?)
(A while ago, Yoon Ju lined up members based on their looks.)
(According to Yoon Ju's standard, Jae Seok was ranked last.)
(Given this result from a recent episode...)
I'm 100 percent sure. I'm completely sure.
It has to be him.
He's the ugliest.
I'm torn between this guy and Jae Seok.
(But the problem is Se Chan, the dark-horse candidate.)
Goodness, this is tough.
(Which one should they choose from this rivalry?)
This is driving me crazy.
You're asking which of my parents I like more.
(An infinite loop of thoughts)
Se Chan... After he joined, things have gotten confusing.
I'll go with him.
It's impossible for me not to choose him.
(He picks the original ugly member.)
But it has to be Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok.
Gosh, it makes...
It makes no sense that I'm choosing my own name.
The ugliest member?
(Will he save his team or his self-respect?)
First of all...
(When the ugly ones were full of worries...)
Without all the accessories!
(A crucial phrase, "without all the accessories")
Hey, glasses aren't accessories.
Removing all the accessories?
Let me make a decision based on just the looks.
(Everyone is inclined to choose Jae Seok. What's their decision?)
Come on out.
- This is crazy. - It was so tough.
- Why is this so hard? - Hey, you know who it is, right?
- I was having an inner conflict. - Why was it so hard?
- It was so tough. - It was really hard.
It was really hard,
but without all the accessories,
- it was easy. - How could you do that?
- I said my glasses stay. - That's nonsense.
- I said my glasses stay. - That's nonsense. Hey.
(Jae Seok chose Seok Jin.)
- I thought long and hard about it. - Don't you know?
I gave it a lot of thought.
- I thought you knew. - Se Chan and Seok Jin.
- I thought a lot about this. - 1, 2, 3.
- I'm sure we all chose Jae Seok. - She chose Se Chan.
- She chose Se Chan. - Come on.
- Hold on. - You chose Se Chan?
- Without glasses and popularity, - It's a mess.
- it has to be Jae Seok. - Yes, you're right.
- It was either Se Chan or Jae Seok. - Right, it was neck and neck.
- I... - Female staff members said...
- he was handsome. I remembered it. - Right, they like him.
- Yes, he's handsome. - But...
- I never heard that Jae Seok was. - Me neither. Not even once.
(But I've never heard that Jae Seok was handsome.)
- I heard them say that he was cool. - The thing about me is...
- I know it. - I heard them say you were cool.
- Among F4, - What do you know?
- I'm not the one. - I do agree you are popular.
- Who are the F4? - F4...
- Who are the F4? - Do you not know?
- Who are they? - Lee Kwang Soo, Jee Seok Jin,
Yang Se Chan, and me.
(A quartet of members with Grade F looks)
You're Gu Jun Pyo.
It's like getting an F for a class.
- You're the leader of the gang. - No.
- He's the leader. - The leader of the ugly members.
- He's the leader. - Why am I the leader? It's you.
- You, F4. - He's disappointed.
- Seriously. - Give us the markers.
They need to get makeup done.
- The markers. - Ji Hyo will get another one?
- Let me draw your lips bigger. - No, it's the last ounce of pride.
- I'm furious. - We have to finish this up.
- What is it? - You look cool.
It says, "ugly".
- That jerk. My goodness. - Hey.
- It's not makeup. It's a tattoo. - I'm so angry.
- It says, "ugly". - "Ugly".
Goodness, I'm so mad.
- Jae Seok, - You should accept who you are.
you're the ugliest.
- Objectively speaking... - Accept it.
- I'm furious. - I can't believe this.
Let's hurry up.
- Don't try to stand out. - Let's get this over with.
That was close.
(For this round, their unanimous decision is about...)
(the name tags again?)
- It's this again? - Among the members,
choose the most...
good-looking member.
(That's really hard too!)
It's too hard.
(It's harder than the college entrance exam.)
It's harder than the college entrance exam.
(He sighs as he is tormented by the thoughts.)
You don't want me to pick anyone.
You don't want to choose anyone. Isn't that it?
(There's a good-looking member?)
(Kwang Soo thinks long and hard about it.)
(He flashes the Prince of Asia's smile out of nowhere.)
To be honest, personally, it's me.
It's just my opinion.
(It's me.)
But...
(Hesitant)
So many people are jealous of me.
I'm serious.
That's why they won't choose me.
Gosh, I don't look great today.
I'm not in my best shape. I was sick yesterday.
I'm me,
so I'll choose myself.
(He is not only muscular but also narcissistic.)
Think, So Min.
Imagine the world has come to an end.
These are the only men left on earth.
The world has come to an end, and you have to choose a man.
(She is playing a truth game.)
Imagine you're getting married.
Jong Kook's face is actually very cute.
His eyes when he smiles, right?
When he smiles with his eyes, he looks like a nice person.
But...
it'd be hard to be his wife.
I can't stop thinking about that.
This question...
They want us to fail.
I was choosing between me and another person.
Stay out of it.
Seriously.
You look like a cuttlefish.
You look like a webfoot octopus.
Gosh.
- You're stir-fried anchovies. - Stir-fried anchovies.
Seriously.
- One, - All of us?
- 2... - 2,
- Three. - Let's be honest.
- I chose Jong Kook. - It's definitely Jong Kook.
It's definitely Jong Kook.
Gosh. I can't believe you.
So Min.
Do you seriously think Haha is good-looking?
I was choosing between him and Jong Kook.
No.
(So Min, that's enough.)
I didn't expect you to choose me.
Gosh.
Even if she wanted to choose me,
she would never choose me. I knew it.
There must be reasons why Haha is married.
It must be his looks.
- Calm down. - Was I being petty?
(They fail to give unanimous answers.)
- What a shame. - You can't blame me.
(Can we finish today?)
- Three. - It was hard.
Look.
(They continue to give different answers.)
Gosh.
I...
I at least gave you both lenses.
(They fail the next question too.)
The worst.
(The worst makeup)
This is too much. It's not okay.
It's about time we succeeded.
- Let's do this, okay? - Okay!
- Let's succeed. - We have to succeed this time.
- Let's succeed this time. - You know this.
(What is the next question?)
What is it?
(Choose the name that comes to your mind...)
(when you hear the word, "betrayer".)
I don't even have to think.
It's...
Lee Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo is the biggest betrayer.)
(The staff must want us to succeed.)
You gave us a very easy question.
I can go out even now.
It's obvious.
(They don't even see any other names.)
It's too easy.
Let's go!
(5 people have chosen Kwang Soo right away.)
I don't even have to think.
It's obvious.
I don't even have to say anything.
The problem is if Kwang Soo will choose his name.
Gosh.
You just have to choose your own name!
Choose your name if you're a man!
This is driving me crazy.
(The man in question...)
(is thinking hard.)
3, 2, 1.
Come out!
(Team or pride?)
One. Come out!
- I won't forgive you. - Seriously...
It's so easy.
- It's a gift from the staff. - The staff wants us to stop.
It's a gift.
- Shouldn't he come out? - Seriously.
- Kwang Soo. - Why isn't he out yet?
- Just a second. Let me check. - Shouldn't Kwang Soo come out?
Why would he even think?
He won't come out!
(The door opens.)
Pick up your name right now!
(Yelling)
I can't make up my mind.
- Put this down! - Why?
- Put this down! - What's wrong?
Pick up your name!
- You don't need all these. - What?
Bring your name.
- Leave your name on the table. - Come out!
- I'm choosing between the two. - Go out!
Go out!
There he comes.
Let's hang Kwang Soo up here.
Hey. You didn't have to think.
- Just admit it. - Why would you think?
- This is a gift from the staff. - We should just accept it.
- That's their intention. - One.
- Gosh. - Two.
- Three. - Yes!
(They unanimously chose Kwang Soo.)
Yes!
Kwang Soo, you might have a different idea,
but we have to finish this game.
Congratulations.
- Here is the first hint. - Okay.
(The first hint after an hour and 20 minutes.)
(What food is their father looking for?)
It's our grandma's...
(This ingredient must have lived in the water.)
"This ingredient must have lived in the water."
It must be fish.
It might be seaweed as well.
(Fish? Seafood?)
- "Lived in the water". - "Lived in the water".
(If you combine the video and the hint...)
When I was little, every autumn,
my mother would make this dish for me.
(This ingredient is in season in the autumn and lives in the water?)
- In the autumn... - Jumbo shrimp.
Jumbo shrimp.
It could be jumbo shrimp.
- It's in season now. - That's right.
There's a jumbo shrimp festival. Are we on the west coast?
- We're on Oido﻿. That's right. - It's definitely jumbo shrimp then.
- Jumbo shrimp. - Let's go for jumbo shrimp.
Okay.
(Is "jumbo shrimp" the correct answer?)
(They move to a jumbo shrimp restaurant.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Jumbo shrimp. - I hope we're right.
(If they're right, they can go home.)
I'm following because it's good food.
But I can't eat it because of my cholesterol level.
- What? - That's right.
But you can eat the tails.
- Is that right? - The head has the most.
I could eat the tails then.
- We could have ramyeon too. - I could eat the tails then.
Jumbo shrimp ramyeon?
- Jumbo shrimp ramyeon. - Okay.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's go, everybody!
Let's check it out.
You're full of energy.
I slept a lot.
- You slept a lot? - Did you sleep for four hours?
If you sleep a lot, you sleep well the next day too.
Don't you wake up around 5am?
(Se Chan is provoking Seok Jin.)
It's not like that.
Don't you go to the mineral spring early in the morning?
He plays badminton too.
He walks around while clapping his hands.
- I massage my back against a tree. - Against a tree.
- I do the front-and-back claps. - The front-and-back claps.
I really hope it's jumbo shrimp that our grandma liked.
We're here.
It'll be so tasty.
- There really is jumbo shrimp. - Look at that shrimp.
Guys, look at this.
(If "jumbo shrimp" is right, they can go home.)
Look at this.
(They're at a jumbo shrimp restaurant.)
Look at this. It's live shrimp.
(Their grandma used to make this dish every autumn.)
(The ingredient lives in the water. Is it jumbo shrimp?)
Along with the name of the ingredient,
please say the name of the dish.
You have to get both correct.
The ingredient is jumbo shrimp, right?
Definitely.
But is it grilled or steamed?
- It must be grilled. - Grilled.
Jumbo shrimp has to be grilled.
In the autumn, you have to grill the jumbo shrimp.
That's right.
You cover the grill with salt...
- That's exactly right. - and put the shrimp on it.
(Grilled jumbo shrimp is the best autumn dish.)
- Right, right. - Hey.
But grilled jumbo shrimp is too hard.
It's softer when steamed.
(When steamed, you can enjoy the soft flesh of jumbo shrimp.)
On the count of three, please say the name of the dish.
- Okay. - Grilled jumbo shrimp.
- Grilled jumbo shrimp. - Grilled jumbo shrimp.
(They're leaning towards grilled jumbo shrimp.)
- Grilled jumbo shrimp. - I don't know.
It has to be grilled.
(Dad, did you eat grilled jumbo shrimp every autumn?)
Grilled jumbo shrimp.
It's grilled jumbo shrimp.
We have to make up our minds.
- Grilled jumbo shrimp. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
- Grilled jumbo shrimp. - Sashimi!
(What is their answer?)
What's with you? Gosh.
(Seok Jin shouts, "sashimi", alone.)
What's with you?
He has close-up syndrome.
(There he goes again.)
I don't understand him.
- What's with you? - We all said it at the same time.
His voice is too loud.
He definitely has close-up syndrome.
- He said it too loud. - Yes.
He knew that he'd be the only one who'd say it.
He was aware of it.
You're so smart.
(He admits it right away.)
(Seok Jin loves close-ups.)
Let's go for sashimi.
No.
- It's grilled. - Let's start with grilled.
Grilled.
- Jumbo shrimp has to be grilled. - Let's go for it.
- Let's do it. - Okay.
Grilled.
1, 2, 3.
- Grilled jumbo shrimp! - Grilled jumbo shrimp!
(Is "grilled jumbo shrimp" correct?)
(Wrong)
It's sashimi!
(Is "jumbo shrimp" wrong?)
- Is it gizzard shad then? - Why is it wrong?
All right. You're at a restaurant,
so you have to eat grilled jumbo shrimp before you can leave.
- That's good. - We can eat?
(They have to eat before leaving.)
What kind of rule is that?
(That's a great rule.)
I think our grandma loved lobster.
Should we go for lobster?
We'll keep saying wrong answers.
But we don't have much time.
(There's not much time left.)
We have to say the correct answer within the given time.
Eating will take some time.
- We're doomed. - He's so smart.
(They'll be penalized if they don't succeed before sunset.)
By carrying out a mission, you can win an additional hint.
The mission is called...
Dried Persimmon Hat.
(Dried Persimmon Hat)
We have to eat the hat?
(They have to bite the dried persimmon hanging from the hat.)
- We've done this before. - Kwang Soo and I...
- That's right. - We did this to meet UIe.
(This game makes you look as ugly as you can.)
All of you will take turns.
You're given 3 minutes. If you succeed 8 times,
you'll get a "high" hint and eight portions of food.
If you succeed 5 times, you'll get a "medium" hint and 6 portions.
If you succeed 3 times, you'll get a "low" hint and 4 portions.
If you succeed 0 times, you'll get the "lowest" hint...
and only a single serving of food.
One portion of jumbo shrimp is nothing.
There will be about three pieces.
By the way, is the ingredient jumbo shrimp?
Do you think they'll tell us, you fool?
Do you think they'll tell us?
Gosh, she's so stupid.
(Seok Jin thinks Ji Hyo is stupid.)
Our viewers are saying, "You're the stupid one."
(We can almost see the board.)
(Who's calling who stupid? Seok Jin is the stupid one.)
- "You're the stupid one." - What's wrong with asking?
It was a good question.
(He must be upset about not eating jumbo shrimp sashimi.)
- Oh, that game. - It's very hard.
- I've never tried it. - It's really hard.
Kwang Soo was so funny when he played it.
You'll take turns.
If you think you'll fail, you have to pass the chance.
You can start by saying, "start".
1, 2, 3.
- Start! - Start!
(They're given 3 minutes.)
(It's coming.)
(The hilarious Kwang Soo is coming.)
I can't see anything.
- It doesn't matter. - I can't see the persimmon.
Hey.
(Class is permanent.)
This is Kwang Soo's specialty.
- You're almost there. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo. You look like a fish.
(He's good at looking funny, but not at biting the persimmon.)
Pass.
A little more.
Kwang Soo, why can't you do it?
- He almost got it. - Hey.
- Pass it. - Kwang Soo.
(Time passes by, and he can't catch the dried persimmon.)
Kwang Soo, stop it.
(Slapping)
Pass it.
(Stop sticking out your tongue, and pass it.)
I almost got it.
- Stop it. - I almost got it.
(Haha gives it a try.)
- Goodness, Haha. - It's too heavy.
- Haha. - I got it.
- Haha. - Now.
- Haha. - Bite it.
Just bite it.
(It touches his tongue.)
It may get on his tongue.
(However, he must bite it to succeed.)
- Yes, bite it. - Haha.
He got it.
(He bites it.)
- It's possible. - Next is So Min.
You can't eat it like that.
(She's obviously a beginner.)
That won't work. Yes, lower your head.
Lower your head.
You must be determined to do it.
So Min.
Lower your head forward.
- Goodness. - She looks like Ahn Young Mi.
Look, they look similar, right?
She looks like Ahn Young Mi. Don't they look the same?
- It's her when she was younger. - Noh Joo Hyun...
and Ahn Young Mi.
So Min.
- Bite it. - Come on.
Do it like a frog.
(She uses a frog tactic.)
You got it.
- You can do it. - Hop like a frog.
- Hop, hop. - You got it.
You got it.
- You almost got it. - So Min.
(She bites it.)
- She got it. - All right.
- What's the time? - There's a method.
(Expert Jae Seok sighed while watching frustrating beginners.)
(He shows his method.)
That's not a method.
You're the ugliest.
He looks so ugly.
- Come on, Jae Seok. - Do it more.
- Use your protruding mouth. - It's over.
Use your protruding mouth, Jae Seok.
You can't miss out on the shrimp.
- Goodness. - Look at his mouth.
(He pulls out his lips and his tongue.)
- That's good. - It's now.
- It's now. - That's good.
(Licking)
That's good.
(They cheer at his method that makes him look ugly.)
- Didn't I eat it? - Stop it.
Bite it. Hurry up.
That's right.
- That's right. - You got it.
Okay.
(A total of 3 people made it.)
Next is Jong Kook.
- I got it. - Darn it.
It looks easy.
- He looks like a shark. - The persimmon's moving by itself.
(I won't eat you if you give me a dried persimmon.)
Jong Kook.
(He looks like a tiger.)
Just bite it.
He got it.
(He hunts down a dried persimmon.)
(A total of 4 succeed.)
That was fast.
- Did you make it? 40 seconds. - I got it.
- It's delicious. - Hurry up, Seok Jin.
He's alone on camera.
- Wake up, Seok Jin. - It's his shot.
He's taking all the attention from the cameras.
He's alone on camera. He's enjoying it.
He's doing well.
You can do it if you focus, Seok Jin.
It's because you aren't focusing.
(Focusing)
- That's right. - That's it.
(Seok Jin succeeds.)
- Great. - Okay.
(After five people succeed, Ji Hyo gives it a try.)
- That's right. - Ji Hyo.
- Bite it when it comes down. - Ji Hyo.
- 15 seconds, Ji Hyo. - That's right.
- You almost got it. - Ji Hyo.
- Here it is. Bite it. - Hurry.
- Ace. - Bite it.
Bite it. That's right.
(It won't work. Pass it.)
- Pass it to Se Chan. - Pass.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
- 10, 9, 8. - That's right.
(He turns into Maeng Gu.)
He looks like Maeng Gu.
Are you acting?
My goodness.
- Are you being funny? - He's being funny.
That's out of the blue.
He's acting.
(Limited time of 3 minutes is up.)
There wasn't enough time.
- Why were you acting? - There wasn't enough time.
- I almost had it. - Five of you made it.
You'll get a medium hint and six servings of shrimp.
- That's amazing. - That's a lot.
- We did quite well. - Okay.
That's a lot.
You gained six servings.
Please pick two members who won't eat.
Let's play Race of Wits.
The three of us?
- We'll play Race of Wits. - All of us?
All of us.
Here comes the first to be eliminated. Start.
One.
- Two. - I'm going to sell him.
Three.
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 7.
(Jong Kook is eliminated.)
He's so bad at Race of Wits.
(Let's see.)
(Shall I stand...)
(Shall I stand up?)
- I'm usually tactless. - He doesn't like being tactful.
One is eliminated.
- One is eliminated. - We need one more.
I'll win no matter what.
- Start. - One.
(Round 2 starts.)
Two.
Three.
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 6.
(Haha and Se Chan are selected.)
Goodness.
(The rest get to eat jumbo shrimp.)
This is great.
I'll eat.
- One of us can eat, right? - Yes.
Let's do it.
(Haha and Se Chan compete to eat jumbo shrimp.)
- What are you confident about? - A quiz?
Okay, let's do a quiz.
- Go ahead. - Let's do a quiz.
(I'll defeat you with a quiz.)
Goodness.
(Haha and Se Chan are competitive in quizzes.)
(They fought hard to avoid being the worst quiz taker.)
(Due to his bad English skills, Se Chan lost.)
The one who answers Jae Seok's question wins.
I really don't want to lose this one.
I'm curious. It's nerve-racking.
- This is most entertaining. - A competition between them...
- Capital cities? - A question about capital cities?
That sounds good. Here's a question about capital cities.
(Will Se Chan be okay with Haha's suggestion?)
How about in South America?
- South America? - How about Southeast Asia?
- Southeast Asia? - I'm an expert.
I prefer South America.
- Southeast Asia is fine. - Is that okay?
- That's fine. - All right.
Capital city of Singapore.
Wait.
- Singapore? - I know this.
This is crazy.
(He's full of confidence.)
- This is difficult. - I know this.
- Se Chan knows the answer. - This is crazy.
What's the capital city of Singapore? You have five seconds.
(They must write the capital city of Singapore.)
This is frustrating. I know the answer.
If this is correct, I'm a genius.
The capital city of Singapore is quite easy.
- Haha. - Did he write it?
- Yes. - He's almost done.
- What's the capital city? - This is wrong.
- Wait. - Let's take a look.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Haha shows his answer first.)
- One of us can eat. - Yes.
(You need a correct answer to eat.)
(Haha isn't confident. What is his answer?)
- Kuala Lumpur is in Malaysia. - That's Malaysia.
That's in Malaysia. Here's mine.
(The capital city of Singapore)
Changi?
(Changi is the capital city of Singapore?)
(It's a creative answer.)
Do you mean Song Chang Eui?
You mean Nam Chang Eui? What's that?
- Who? - Changi.
Is that the capital city?
He's talking about the international airport.
That's Changi International Airport.
- Isn't that the capital city? - That's the name of the airport.
We have Incheon Airport. Is that our capital city?
We have Gimpo Airport. Is Gimpo our capital city?
What's the capital city of Singapore?
The capital city is Singapore, right?
Really?
The capital city of Singapore is Singapore.
That's why he asked this question.
- The city is a country. - It's an interesting question.
We don't have time to waste.
- Let's hurry. - We have to find it.
All right, what's the capital city of Mongolia?
(What's the capital city of Mongolia?)
- I know this. Goodness. - We've been there.
We've been there.
- Goodness. - We went there.
- I really know it. - We went there.
(Running Man had missions in Mongolia and Russia.)
(Ulaanbaatar is the capital city.)
The two of them didn't go to Mongolia.
They went to Russia.
I'll give you the first syllable.
(He gives a hint.)
"Ul".
(It's "Ul".)
(Haha writes it down as soon as he hears it.)
- Isn't it "Ul"? - That's right.
He got it.
(He has no idea.)
Listen, we don't have much time.
- When will you finish? - Can we do it while eating?
When will you finish?
(They're taking too long.)
We must go in six hours.
We have to finish.
- 1, 2, 3. - I really don't want to lose.
- Ulaanbaatar. - Ulaanbaatar.
(Haha answers correctly.)
(What did you say?)
Ulaan what?
"Ulaando..."?
"Ulaandobuntu".
"Ulaandobuntu"?
(That's very creative.)
Why didn't you write "Orlando Bloom"?
- "Ulaandobuntu"? - Orlando Bloom.
This is what I wrote.
The answer is Ulaanbaatar.
That's correct.
What is "Ulaandobuntu"?
(It's not made by their father.)
(Grilled jumbo shrimp is a specialty in autumn.)
(They eat quickly and move to their next mission.)
Come here, Creative Yang.
"Creative Yang"?
- Can I get one? - Yes.
- I gave you mine last time. - Right.
It's funny that he got Changi from the airport's name.
I'll eat something delicious next time.
Jumbo shrimp tastes so sweet when it's in season.
(The grilled jumbo shrimp tastes amazing.)
(He slurps the flesh.)
(His reaction is so sincere.)
It tastes so good.
Try it with some lemon juice.
That's it.
- It tastes so good. - With lemon juice?
The gourmet won the food.
One of the pieces tasted really good.
It's so good.
(It tastes good with some lemon?)
Like this?
(He puts a lemon slice on his shrimp.)
You can eat it this way too.
Seriously.
(He seems to be aiming for a close-up.)
Shrimp tastes so good in season.
(He pretends to be okay.)
To get a close-up,
- he wrapped it in a lemon slice. - He wrapped it in a lemon slice.
He's full of energy today.
It tastes so good with some lemon.
(We appreciate your efforts.)
Can we eat the Enoki mushrooms too?
- They taste good. - They taste good.
(They even eat the mushrooms.)
It's a shame.
I want some more.
We'd love to eat some more.
(Haha gets to the bottom of his plate.)
For breakfast?
It's a shame.
What is this?
(He found something on his plate?)
Should we try one more time with jumbo shrimp?
(Under the mushrooms...)
(was a mission note.)
(I thought it was a normal dish. What is this?)
Did you find anything under your food?
What's that?
(He receives a secret mission to call a number.)
(Surprised)
What's that?
- What is this? - There was a hint?
(Only Haha received the mission.)
- I don't have anything. - No one else?
- No. - No.
- What is it? - It's nothing.
Did you see it?
- Share it with us. - We're a team.
He's hiding something.
Share it with us.
We're siblings. We don't have to compete.
We're a team.
I didn't get anything,
but I did see Haha's note.
(They search Kwang Soo's body.)
Do you think I'm hiding something in my hair?
(Why would you check my hair?)
- Why did you check my hair? - Just in case.
You're getting worse and worse.
You're crossing the line.
- Just to be sure. - You might be hiding something.
- It's just to be sure. - I just wanted to check.
You might be hiding something in your hair.
In my hair?
- My gosh. - We don't have much time,
so please decide where we should go next.
- Blue crab. - Blue crab.
(Their next answer is blue crab?)
(The reason why they chose blue crab is...)
(They received a medium hint after the persimmon hat mission.)
Let's see the hint.
"As a kid, I was afraid of touching this ingredient."
"But my mom didn't seem to be."
(It's something scary to touch?)
(It's in season in the autumn,)
(lives in the water,)
(and is scary to touch.)
(To combine all the hints so far...)
Isn't it blue crab?
- Autumn blue crab? - Or gizzard shad.
Gizzard shad is scary to touch too.
- I still can't touch fish. - Right.
- It's too slippery. - That's right.
Blue crabs are scary to touch because of their claws.
(After finding out that the ingredient is scary to touch,)
(they become divided between blue crab and gizzard shad.)
(Is either of the answers correct?)
(We think it's blue crab.)
(After a discussion, they agree on blue crab.)
(Blue crab tastes amazing in the autumn.)
(They decide on blue crab.)
- Okay. Blue crab. - 1, 2, 3.
- Blue crab. - Blue crab.
Let's go to a blue crab restaurant.
- I like it. - I still want more.
It tasted so good.
(Is "blue crab" the correct answer?)
I have to use the bathroom.
(Haha stays behind, saying he needs to use the bathroom.)
(He goes to the staircase with his phone in his hand...)
(instead of going to the bathroom.)
(He tries calling the number written on the note...)
(without others knowing.)
(Someone answers the phone.)
Hello.
(Haha hears someone's voice.)
Is this Haha?
(Haha hears something shocking.)
(What did Haha hear?)
Did you receive a mission?
Haha, are you a spy?
No. I just went to the bathroom.
I swear.
What was written on that note?
Share it with us.
We're trying to fulfil our father's request.
That's right. We're a family.
- Why would you... - You're right.
I...
The thing is, we might not be...
- all siblings. - Really?
(They might not all be siblings?)
- So I... - We might not all be siblings?
- Or... - We might not all be siblings?
- Is someone adopted? - Let's just go.
We might not all be siblings.
(Is Haha saying the truth?)
That person might be aware.
(Time left)
It has such a nice view.
(They arrive at a sashimi place with an amazing view.)
I love the view.
We're at the second restaurant now.
Which food did you choose?
- Blue crab. - Blue crab.
But it can be cooked in many different ways.
It could be blue crab stew or steamed blue crab.
Wouldn't it be steamed blue crab?
(Steamed blue crab has deep flavors from the autumn sea.)
(Is this Father's soul food?)
Blue crab stew.
- It must be stew. - It must be stew.
(Or is it spicy blue crab stew...)
(made with Grandma's secret sauce?)
In this weather, stew might be better.
- It's stew weather. - Stew would be better.
- Also, - I think it's stew.
we just ate grilled jumbo shrimp.
It has to be stew this time.
Let's go for stew.
Guys, listen.
In the crab shell...
With all the guts...
(Haha attacks.)
Blend it with some sesame oil,
add some kimchi, and eat it.
It seems to me that...
everyone is talking about what they want to eat.
Should we vote?
- Let's do that. - Let's do that.
- Steamed blue crab. - Steamed blue crab.
- Me. - Raise your hand.
- 4 voted for steamed blue crab. - It's 4.
Should I vote for steamed blue crab?
- Who wants stew? - Stew.
Three. What about you?
You're the only one left.
(Jong Kook is the only one left.)
- Steamed blue crab. - I vote for steamed blue crab.
- Okay. - Gosh.
(With Jong Kook's vote, steamed blue crab wins.)
I mean...
- It's steamed blue crab. - Haha just said,
"Steamed blue crab." That's why you said it.
- My goodness. - Steamed blue crab is better.
Please say your answer on the count of three.
One...
1, 2, 3.
- Steamed blue crab. - I want stew,
but steamed blue crab.
Let's say it again.
1, 2, 3.
- Steamed blue crab. - Steamed blue crab.
Gosh, your hands smell like shrimp.
My goodness.
Steamed blue crab.
(Is it the correct answer?)
- It's wrong. - See?
We'll get to eat it then.
It must be stew.
- It's definitely stew. - No.
Haha made us change our minds.
- Is he really our family? - That's right.
- Hey. - Okay. Think what you want.
You can think what you want.
He could be a spy.
That's right.
(What is Haha's secret?)
- Haha could be the spy. - Someone among us is a spy.
(He is punished.)
There's a hint he can't tell us?
We're obviously not siblings...
because we look so different.
Some of us are too ugly while others look okay.
My goodness.
- Hey. - You're driving me crazy.
Let me announce something.
I'll always sit next to Jae Seok. No one can come here.
(Next to Jae Seok, you suddenly look handsome.)
You want to look handsome.
Do you know what makes me really upset?
When he said that, no one said anything.
It makes me so upset.
- You can win another hint. - Yes.
This mission is...
Blowing a Ping-pong Ball.
(Blowing a Ping-pong Ball)
Blow a ping-pong ball...
over bottles turned upside down.
If you get the ball in the cup, you succeed.
If the ball falls, the next player takes over.
Is it even possible?
How are we going to do it?
- Let's win a high hint with this. - Yes.
We need a hint.
Without it, we can't succeed.
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook plays first.)
- To the right... - We don't have much time.
Let me start.
(Will Jong Kook succeed?)
(To win a high hint, all of them have to succeed.)
(Blowing)
(The ball rolls over the bottles quickly.)
(Bouncing)
(The ball bounces off the brim of the cup.)
Did it bounce off the cup?
The cup must have been too close.
Let's move the cup.
(The cup is moved.)
(It's farther away from the bottles now.)
Start!
Just give one strong puff.
(Puff)
(The ball rolls on.)
- There you go. - That's it.
It should have been stronger.
(The ball falls where the cup used to be.)
Should the cup be moved?
- It doesn't matter. - It has to move all the time.
Like this. Okay.
(So Min is the third player.)
(The cup is moved again.)
(Blowing)
(Rolling)
(The ball bounces off the cup.)
The cup was moved.
But it depends on how strong you blow.
- Let me try. - That was close.
- I should practice. - I've never tried it.
Just give one strong puff.
Get closer to the ball.
You can do it.
Start!
(Will Ji Hyo succeed?)
(The ball rolls over the bottles quickly.)
(It just has to land now.)
(It's in.)
(Ji Hyo is the first person to succeed.)
(Is there anything she's not good at?)
- That's how you do it. - Ji Hyo is the best.
She's an ace.
- Who's next? - I'll go.
I'll go.
(That jerk.)
(It's an important moment to win a hint.)
- Is this spot okay? - Okay.
His mouth is crooked.
(He attacks him verbally.)
(He tries to mess with him.)
(Goodness)
- Isn't this... - What are you doing?
a psychological warfare?
(Is he a spy?)
Stop it.
- This is what you did. - My mouth is crooked?
(He's not a team player.)
- Why did you do that? - Come on.
- It's fine as long as he can speak. - Goodness.
Jae Seok, accept the truth.
Blow it straight.
Start.
(It's a real start this time.)
- Start. - Wait.
Okay, wait.
(He blows with his crooked mouth.)
(It rolls straight.)
(It hits the cup and falls off.)
Isn't this a success? Talk to them.
(Isn't this a success? Talk to them.)
(Shameless)
Isn't it?
It went in and out.
Look at the replay.
It went in and out. Take a look.
Jae Seok.
- You're depending on me a lot. - Talk to them.
It felt great.
Right? Talk to them.
"You talk to them."
(Will he negotiate?)
- You should say it. - Jae Seok.
The cup was knocked down.
- Otherwise, the ball would be in. - Listen.
It's common sense.
If the force went from top to bottom...
I love him when he's on my side.
- That's good. - As the force went this way,
- it got knocked down. - We know that.
Isn't that correct?
- It's correct. - Scientifically speaking?
- Isn't it right? - Am I right or wrong?
It's common sense.
Think about it. I'll convince them.
- The cup was knocked down. - Give it to me.
The cup was knocked down.
It's the staff's mistake.
If the ball hit the inside,
I'll accept it.
- It hit the inside. - It did.
It definitely did.
(They analyze the video.)
(The ball hits the inside and bounces off.)
It's considered a success.
- See? We got it. - It hit the inside.
That's right.
(Other members are moved by Jong Kook.)
(We'll show you too.)
- That's good. - Nice.
Okay.
- You got it. - Okay.
- Okay. - Our members do well.
Currently, you won a low hint, and four people get to eat.
At least five of us should eat.
If you succeed one more time,
- Can six of us eat? - Yes and win a medium hint.
Okay.
- Seok Jin. - Try it.
(The last player is Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin is good at this.
I'm nervous.
(A medium hint is on the line.)
Start.
(Will Seok Jin succeed?)
(He blows it carefully.)
(Will it go straight into the cup?)
If you succeed one more time,
you win a medium hint, and six of you can eat.
(Bouncing)
(It goes in.)
(Seok Jin wins.)
(He becomes a hero.)
- You're our big man. - This is my world.
That was amazing.
(He's the hope of the middle-aged.)
He seemed confident.
If I had failed, you guys would've felt disheartened.
Of course.
(They gain a medium hint and a meal for six.)
(Who will be the unlucky 2 who can't eat?)
Pick two members who can't eat.
Let's play Race of Wits.
(They select one unlucky person with Race of Wits.)
- Start, 1. - 2.
Three.
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 6.
Okay.
It's the three of them.
(Either Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, or Seok Jin will be eliminated.)
Okay, we're safe.
- We're okay. - Good job.
I was ready.
(I'm the hero.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Ji Hyo loses.)
Okay.
- Okay, you're out. - Ji Hyo can't eat?
- I'm out. - You're out.
- You lost. - She's the last.
- I accept it. - Pick one more person.
- It's six servings. - Right.
One more person can't eat.
- Pick one more. - Okay.
(How will they decide?)
- How about... - Don't play Race of Wits.
- Let's play it. - Stop it.
Let's stand up. Everyone, sit down.
My goodness.
Everyone, sit down comfortably.
You don't have to sit in one line.
- Ji Hyo will call when to start. - I will.
Okay.
I'm always number one.
I'm number two.
Someone will get caught in the middle.
Get ready.
[VIU Ver] SBS E425 Running Man
"Go, Determined Gourmet"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Get ready.
- Ji Hyo will call when to start. - I will.
Okay.
I'm always number one.
I'm number two.
Someone will get caught in the middle.
Get ready.
- Start. - One.
- 3. - 4.
(It's chaotic.)
(Goodness)
- 5. - 6.
You said six.
Three.
- Gosh, 5. - 6.
(His sound became number 5.)
I also said six.
- Did he? - I said six.
- You didn't. - Did you say six?
- Five. - I think you said...
- Five. - No.
(Seok Jin loses.)
She got me on my nerves.
- It's over. - Seok Jin and Ji Hyo can't eat.
Okay.
You're terrible.
(I knew today was going too well for me.)
(It's time for six members to eat steamed blue crabs.)
It looks delicious.
- Look at the meat. - Listen.
Look at the meat oozing out.
(It's packed with meat.)
(Tasty)
(They fill their mouths with in-season blue crabs.)
That looks delicious.
How could this be?
It was me who made two more people eat.
- What is it? - That looks amazing.
(Blue crab is delicious.)
It's delicious.
Look at this.
(They're busy eating.)
I want some too.
(It's full of crab meat.)
(Give it to me.)
- Look at the steam rising. - Wait a minute.
(They start to fight for the crab.)
I didn't even get a spoon of it.
(Look at Seok Jin.)
(He goes after the blue crab thief.)
(Pressing)
I want to eat it.
(Why are they fighting above him?)
Jong Kook is still eating.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook. Wait. - I'm sorry.
Go and sit down.
- I blocked him. - Okay.
I'll eat.
(It's so delicious that Jong Kook doesn't get upset.)
Take a look while eating.
- Here's your hint. - Okay.
We also have a hint.
You get a medium hint thanks to Seok Jin.
That's right. You should be grateful.
This hint is quite important.
Let's look carefully.
(Will they guess the answer with this hint?)
"There were bones."
(Third hint is "There were bones.")
- Something that was alive? - It lived underwater.
Something alive?
"It was scary to touch it when I was young."
"But my mom touched it with ease."
(It's scary to touch.)
(And there were bones?)
It must have bones.
- If there are bones... - It must be gizzard shad.
- Gizzard shad? - It's gizzard shad.
- It's definitely gizzard shad. - We eat its bones too.
That's right.
(They make their guesses.)
(Looking around)
We should go and eat gizzard shad.
(Let's see.)
What are you looking for?
- What? - What are you looking for?
I was wondering if there was anything.
Let's see.
(I almost forgot.)
- There's something else. - There's nothing.
Look on your plate.
(Where's the secret mission this time?)
- I completely forgot. - It must be somewhere.
(The secret mission...)
(goes to Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo finds a hint on his plate.)
(He hides it secretly as soon as he sees it.)
(He makes a call like Haha did.)
Hello?
Is it Kwang Soo?
(Is this the secret that Haha received?)
(He pretends not to know.)
I choose you.
That must be it.
(As secrets pile up, time keeps passing.)
What was the hint again?
- "There were bones." - "There were bones."
It's gizzard shad.
If it's in autumn and has bones, it's gizzard shad.
- That's it. - It lives underwater.
- Grilled gizzard shad. - Grilled gizzard shad.
It's grilled gizzard shad.
- Gizzard shad is grilled. - There's also sashimi.
It has bones in it too.
- That's true. - You eat it straight.
Right,
but gizzard shad is grilled.
- They say grilled gizzard shad... - It's gizzard shad.
- is delicious. - Right.
Let's go. In 1, 2, 3.
- Grilled gizzard shad. - Grilled gizzard shad.
(They decide on grilled gizzard shad.)
Grilled gizzard shad?
(Everyone is certain of grilled gizzard shad.)
(Is it the father's food for soul?)
Grilled gizzard shad?
- It's incorrect. - That's not nice.
It's not grilled gizzard shad?
- What is it then? - It has bones?
Here's a mission to get additional hints. It's Magic Bowling.
(Magic Bowling is a mission to earn additional hints.)
You line up 10 markers and roll a marble.
It could either be a strike or spare as long as you knock them all out.
Four teams have to succeed, so let's pair up well.
(If 4 teams succeed, they earn the best hint and all get to eat.)
(Gizzard shad wasn't right, so this is their only option.)
- So Min. - Me?
So Min and Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Let's go.
- Next team. - So Min.
- So Min. - Yes.
- Seok Jin and So Min. - Are you going first?
Okay. Do we stand here?
- It's So Min. - Looking good.
Why was this placed here?
Good! No, it's good.
(She knocks down 3 out of 10 markers.)
- Good. - That was good.
(She hits the end.)
(They're not in a bad position to get a spare.)
Seok Jin can finish it.
- Seok Jin. - Good job.
Please finish it off.
- I need more at the back. - I'm counting on you.
- You start back here. - It doesn't matter.
- You can do it. - You just have to hit here.
- Just throw it. - Good luck.
- It looks good. - Good luck.
(Will Seok Jin get a spare?)
- Start. - Focus.
- Start. - Start.
(Just one?)
Okay! I did it, right?
Start.
(He hit the marker on the outside.)
(The blue marker fell toward the middle and made the rest fall.)
(That was a spare.)
You approve, right?
- It fell and pushed the others. - It fell.
Okay. Yes!
Referee.
He's an ace member.
Go. Ji Hyo?
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are the second pair.)
(Ji Hyo goes first.)
- Good! - Good.
- That wasn't bad. - One.
That wasn't bad.
(Ace member Ji Hyo only knocks down 1.)
(That's too bad.)
Good job.
It's better to stand far away, right?
Kwang Soo, you have to do this.
- I'll go. - Where's the start line?
(Gulping)
(Did he just inhale the marble?)
(His ready position is unusual.)
- Aim for the right one. - Can you hold my arms?
Okay.
Hold on.
Why is he doing that?
He looks cool.
He's going to launch.
- This looks really good. - He looks like a pufferfish.
He's a pufferfish.
He looks like a hero.
This looks like "Transformers".
You'll be a hero if you do this.
(You'll be a hero if you do this.)
(Take aim...)
Okay!
- Okay! - Yes!
- Great job. - That was a strike.
That was perfect.
- Okay. - That was excellent.
- We did it. - Did he do it?
- That was perfect. - I'm serious.
- Great job. - I knew it.
- Great job. - Wait a minute. We have an issue.
The cameraman said...
the markers fell before the marble touched it.
- That's not right. - Really?
- Let's see it. - Rewind the tape.
- Rewind it. - Hold on.
- It's because... - Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook! - Excuse me.
Jong Kook!
- Tell them. - How's that possible?
There's action and reaction. How can the markers fall first?
I know. Rewind the tape.
No, I was mistaken.
Right.
(He waves his hand.)
- All right! - All right!
- Okay. - Okay.
All right.
- I understand. - He can be mistaken.
- Good. - Start.
(Se Chan and Jae Seok are the third pair.)
(Falling)
- Goodness. - What was that?
You're incredible.
(Strike first...)
(and then bowl.)
How did you do that?
- We didn't even push it. - Psychokinesis.
- It's windy. - It was the wind.
- Fail. - Leave it.
That was a fail.
- It's a fail. - It is.
- Our turn. - Last pair.
- Last one. I'm going to start. - Start.
This won't be easy.
(They have to succeed to get a medium hint and let 6 people eat.)
Go.
(What will the result be?)
There you go.
- All right! - I did it.
(It's a strike.)
(He put a spin on the marble.)
(It made a sharp turn and got a strike.)
(This is the class of the ace member.)
- That was perfect. - Do I not get a turn?
I don't get a turn, right?
That was it, right? That was precise.
That was faultless.
(All but Jae Seok and Se Chan get to eat the gizzard shad.)
You are supposed to eat it like this.
- How do you eat this? - You eat the bones too.
- Try this. - It's good.
It's good.
- There you go. - So Min knows how to eat it.
Use your hands.
- Eat the head first. - That's right.
You eat the head too?
(The head is very savory.)
While you eat,
we'll give you the hint.
This is the medium hint.
You'll get the answer once you see this.
Is that right?
(They can hopefully get the answer with this hint.)
What is it?
(Fourth hint)
"Seok Jin reminds me of this."
(Fourth hint: Seok Jin reminds me of this.)
(Seok Jin reminds me of this.)
(It lives in the water, and he's scared to touch it.)
(You can chew on the bones, and it's related to Seok Jin.)
What does Seok Jin remind you of?
- Pollack! - That's right.
- Why? - His nose is big.
Anchovy.
Pollacks swim in the water and once you dry it,
you eat it.
You eat the whole thing, right?
Is it a pollack?
(He's not certain.)
What is it?
Jamwon-dong loach.
- A loach? - A loach.
(A loach?)
(Last fall during Healing Race)
(Seok Jin's nickname became "loach".)
(He dodges around and avoids punishments.)
Jamwon-dong loach. I mentioned it.
- A long time ago? - I mentioned it.
- Right. - Loach soup.
It's a loach soup.
You eat the bones too.
- Right. - That's right.
It's scary to touch because it looks like a snake.
- That's right. - He said he can't touch it.
(Is loach soup the right answer?)
- Let's get loach soup. - Let's go.
Loach soup!
Where do we go?
- It's nearby. - There must be one nearby.
There must be one. There has to be a place.
Loach soup is eaten in the fall weather.
There it is.
- It's here. - There's one.
Let's go. We just have to get it.
Let's go.
- Okay. - Hello.
Hello.
(They had jumbo shrimps, blue crabs, and gizzard shad.)
I looked it up,
and loach soup is eaten in the fall as nutritious food.
(Loach soup is eaten to replenish energy in the fall.)
In 1, 2, 3.
- Loach soup. - Loach soup.
(Was this the food their father was looking for?)
(It lives in the water,)
(and he was scared to touch it.)
(It also reminded him of Seok Jin.)
(Is loach soup correct?)
Correct.
(Loach soup is correct.)
Yes!
(Their father wanted to find the loach soup.)
We did it the hard way.
- It's here. - Let's go.
All right.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Take care. - It's one serving.
- Thank you. - Take care.
(Museum in Oido)
- Let's get it! - Go.
- Do you have the loach soup? - Yes.
Bring the loach soup.
- Bring it. - Loach soup.
Bring it.
Do we have to weep when we see Father?
Don't we have to bow?
Do we? It's been a while.
(They're meeting him for the first time,)
(but they missed him.)
(Finally...)
- Oh, dear. - Father.
- Dad. - Father.
(The family reunites after decades.)
- Father. - Dad.
- Father. - Father!
(They wanted to call him "father" in person.)
- Great work. - Father.
You work too hard, Father.
- She's... - So Min,
- it's your dad. - Oh, my.
Father, you two look the same.
- We found it. - Okay, let me see.
- We found it. - We don't know if it's right.
- What is it? - It's loach soup.
- Is that what it is? - Yes.
When I was young...
(His mother made it for him every fall when he was young.)
(He never forgot the taste of it.)
Please take a look.
- Is this it? - It's loach soup. It's warm.
(Memories of his youth and of his mom...)
(are contained in this bowl of loach soup.)
- Father... - Thank you.
I appreciate it very much. Great work.
Do you have some inheritance?
(He makes an inappropriate comment.)
(He switches the subject all of a sudden.)
Goodness.
Why are you so materialistic?
I thought you were leaving us your inheritance.
I already told you.
(He's creepy.)
(Seok Jin must have forgotten...)
(who he used to be.)
- I told you I would, so I will. - I know.
- You should know. - Are you kidding me?
My apologies.
He's scary.
(Isn't our father a businessman?)
Is our father a gangster?
(He's not into killing people, right?)
- What are you saying? - Father.
He doesn't watch his mouth.
I don't know what his occupation is.
I don't know what it is.
- Come here. - Fine.
Hey.
Great job.
As I promised...
(Anyhow...)
I'll leave you...
- my entire asset. - Thank you.
However,
I left it...
(The asset is on the 3rd floor!)
- On the 3rd floor. - 3rd floor?
Third floor?
When I say "start",
- you go. - Okay.
Get ready...
(The asset is divided in the order of arrival.)
(The person who arrives first...)
(can get the most amount.)
(Which of the 8 siblings will get the most amount of money?)
- Go. - Okay, let's go.
Go.
(There's no family when it comes to money.)
(I'm going to take more.)
(While the others fight, Jong Kook gets ahead.)
Look carefully.
- I can't catch up. - Where is it?
(They sprint for the money.)
(At that moment!)
(Haha takes a different route.)
(He hides while the other 7 siblings are in a mess.)
Should we try again?
(While they were eating jumbo shrimps,)
(Haha found something on the bottom of his plate.)
(Looking around)
(He called the number...)
(on the plate.)
(He heard the voice...)
(and was shocked.)
(It wasn't just Haha.)
(He puts something away.)
(Kwang Soo was stunned as well.)
I'm okay.
- Go. Go. - Are you all right?
(Is that why? Kwang Soo is not running.)
(Jong Kook arrives first.)
What's this?
(As their father said, his entire asset is on 3rd floor.)
(Wig, glasses, letter,)
(and a picture frame that's flipped over)
(Is this his entire asset?)
What is it?
(He reads the letter first.)
- What is it? - "Hello, my sons and daughters."
"I've been doing business abroad, so I didn't care of you all."
"The oldest son of the nine siblings is missing."
"He's Byung Ok".
(It's 9 siblings, not 8?)
- I'm getting goosebumps. - What?
(We weren't 8 siblings?)
Byung Ok is the oldest sibling.
"The oldest son of the nine siblings is missing."
- I'm getting goosebumps. - What?
Byung Ok is the oldest sibling.
Hold on.
Byung Ok is the oldest sibling?
(We had a big brother?)
Look carefully.
(So he's not their father.)
(Is he their brother Byung Ok?)
Hello?
(He sent the secret message.)
Is this Haha?
(He's the one who called them.)
I'm actually...
your older brother Byung Ok.
(He was their brother!)
You're our brother?
- Let me see. - Byung Ok is the oldest sibling?
"1st picnic with the 9 siblings".
(They had a brother!)
Byung Ok is our brother.
- He's not our father. - Really?
(This is not the end.)
(The wig and glasses next to the photo...)
(were what he used to look like their father.)
(They were completely fooled.)
(Why did their brother...)
(do this?)
(For what?)
(He lied to his siblings and plotted this.)
- So then? - He's not our father.
He's our oldest brother.
He pretended to be our father.
Hold on. Where is he?
Where is Byung Ok?
(He lied to his siblings and won over Haha and Kwang Soo.)
I'm actually your older brother Byung Ok.
You're our brother, not our father?
Yes, we were 9 siblings, not 8.
(What was he trying to achieve?)
I know a way you can take all the asset.
Don't tell the others.
Just follow me.
Do you understand?
(The older brother knew!)
All right.
I thought you were our father.
(Haha and Kwang Soo joined the scheme.)
Okay.
(They were blinded by greed.)
If you find it first,
you get more money. Those who find it first.
(He pretended to be their father and left with the loach soup.)
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo followed him quietly.)
(So did Haha.)
Father, where do I go?
(Is there another traitor?)
(He also won over Ji Hyo...)
(out of the 8 siblings!)
(She found the message under the gizzard shad!)
(She hides it...)
(before the others see it.)
(Even Ji Hyo betrayed the others to take all the asset!)
- You're scary people. - Is this happening again?
What's going on?
We got the same message, right?
I think we did.
But where's Haha?
Haha, Ji Hyo,
and Kwang Soo are gone.
They probably know by now.
The oldest brother snatched your father's food,
and he's trying to take all the asset.
If they find the hidden materials and successfully parcel the food,
Team Big Brother wins, and they take the money.
If you rip their name tags before that,
you can remove their names from the family register.
If you succeed, you will get to share the asset,
and Team Big Brother will get the punishment.
- You can start chasing them. - Okay!
Follow them.
We just have to rip their name tags, right?
It's been a while. I'll do this properly.
Let's hurry. Let's just go.
(They arrive at the park that has the box, tape, and an invoice.)
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Go.
Run.
Where do we start?
This place looks like a plain.
- Where do we go? - I think we should...
- look into each room. - What?
There's nothing here.
(They start searching right away.)
Look here too!
(Let's find this fast!)
Where...
Where are they going?
(He has a huge scheme, but he doesn't have any energy.)
Where is this?
Where's Kwang Soo?
- I'm here. - Hey.
Where do I go?
- We have to look. - Where...
You have to look, Byung Ok!
(Toddling)
You have to look.
Stop walking around.
You have to find the box.
The invoice too.
It's here somewhere?
(He's tired. Where is this?)
(They have to find a box, tape, and an invoice.)
- What do we do? - Tape.
Where is this?
- I found the box. - Did you?
(At that moment! They find the box.)
Did you?
(They find 1 out of 3 items before Team Siblings arrives.)
- The box. - Did you find it?
- Let's go. Tape. - What?
Tape.
(They only have 2 items left. Tape and invoice!)
(She finds tape!)
Byung Ok.
Hey, we just have to find the invoice.
The invoice?
That's all we have to find?
Hey, hey.
- We're here. - Let's go. Come on.
Those guys...
Let's go.
- Run. - Go, go. Move.
Where are these punks?
(We'll teach you what you pay for being a traitor.)
- Kwang Soo! - Run.
Ji Hyo!
(We'll rip your name tags and take the asset.)
They're here.
(They're here!)
- Are they? - They're already here.
Byung Ok!
- Kwang Soo. - Where?
- There they are. - What?
Let's go. I spotted them right away.
There they are.
(Those who are trying to rip name tags)
Jae Seok.
(He hides behind the mud hut.)
It was him, right?
(Team Siblings is closing in.)
Where did they go?
I'm a spy.
(He tries to trick them.)
I'm serious.
I swear.
Hey! So Min.
(He runs away while Se Chan is off-guard.)
What's that box?
(It's difficult to catch people in this vast meadow.)
Haha.
Haha!
(He runs away.)
(Or not!)
(Tiger is the king of the meadow.)
(Haha was running in the meadow fearlessly.)
(He's out.)
- Who else is there? - Kwang Soo.
(Remaining Team Big Brother: Byung Ok, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo)
That was so scary.
(He's frightened.)
Oh, dear. Goodness.
(Is he human or a tiger?)
Then let's...
What's this?
- Here. - No, what are you doing?
- Catch Ji Hyo. - Byung Ok!
- Take this. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo is out as well.)
Get Byung Ok.
(Byung Ok is running at full speed.)
He can't get away.
No! Hey.
Tape.
(He runs as fast as he can.)
(He was going to take all the asset, but he's out.)
It's over.
Jae Seok.
- Come here. - Hey.
- Come here. - Jae Seok.
- Hey. - Jae Seok.
Does this make sense?
- How can you do this to us? - Well...
- Of course I can. Why not? - No...
- How? - Still,
I'm sorry.
- But... - Give me the tape.
Hey!
Get him.
He went this way.
Kwang Soo.
(He has to trust Kwang Soo now.)
Get Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo?
Is he the only one left?
Hold on. Where did he go?
(Where did Kwang Soo go?)
I just have to find the invoice.
(He's struggling by himself to find the invoice.)
(There's a white paper in the woods.)
(He found the invoice!)
I found it.
(He acquired all items.)
(He just has to bring the loach soup to the parcel office!)
Where is he?
Where are you, Kwang Soo?
Oh, gosh.
Where did he go?
Why is the path so winding?
(Let's hide and rest.)
Get down. Get down.
(Don't let them find you.)
Get down.
Where did he go?
(Where is the traitor?)
(Jae Seok comes near Kwang Soo's hiding place.)
Kwang Soo is the last one.
(Jae Seok's voice is near.)
(Jae Seok's heavy breath approaches.)
(Before he gets nearer,)
(I must run away.)
There he is!
- There he is! - Catch him!
(Does he have enough energy to lose the determined Jae Seok...)
(after finding the invoice?)
Why is the path so winding?
My goodness.
(The members close in on him from all sides.)
(The only way out is another uphill path.)
(Kwang Soo is dying.)
(Kwang Soo moves further away from the camera.)
Don't go that way!
Kwang Soo!
(I can't go further. I am sorry, Kwang Soo.)
- Don't go that way. - Go back.
I will run until I reach the end of the earth.
Bye, viewers.
Where did he go?
(He loses Kwang Soo.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
- Did you catch Kwang Soo? - We lost him.
Gosh, Kwang Soo ran until the end.
(I can't believe he left without the cameraman.)
He would do that.
There is no path.
(They don't see Kwang Soo anywhere.)
Will he take the mountain path?
(Kwang Soo and the cameraman manage to reunite.)
I just need to find it.
(After losing Team Siblings,)
(he took a long way around.)
(He just needs to go to the parcel office.)
Father.
(Is he suddenly acting?)
It's your favorite dish,
loach soup.
I will be sure...
to send it to you...
while it's still warm.
(He just needs to go to the parcel office...)
(to inherit the asset and become a good son.)
- We should go in and look. - Where?
(Team Siblings spread out to find Kwang Soo.)
For goodness' sake. Where is Kwang Soo?
(This is the opportunity.)
We need to catch him before he goes to the parcel office.
That's right.
(Without getting caught,)
(he arrives near the parcel office.)
(He is close to inheriting the entire asset.)
Where is he?
(They have no idea Kwang Soo is so close.)
He must be in the woods.
(Where is Kwang Soo?)
So Min is coming.
(To avoid So Min,)
(he decides to go around.)
(I bet no one is on this side.)
Now!
What? What?
(Jae Seok and a cameraman suddenly appear.)
(A cameraman yells, "Now!")
(With the help of a cameraman,)
(Jae Seok gets Kwang Soo.)
What? What?
(Kwang Soo didn't expect a sudden attack.)
- What? - Now!
Okay!
(This cameraman looks familiar for some reason.)
(He isn't a cameraman, but Se Chan.)
- Okay. - We got Kwang Soo.
(Let's see how this happened.)
I should hide.
The color of my outfit stands out too much.
(He decided to be discreet.)
(By taking off his top...)
Stay here.
(and holding a camera,)
(Se Chan became a cameraman.)
Go forward.
(He told Jae Seok where to stand...)
(and when to attack.)
Kwang Soo!
Now!
(Se Chan outsmarted Kwang Soo!)
Good job, Se Chan.
(I can't believe I got caught.)
I was so close to the parcel office.
This is the parcel office.
You shouldn't have been so greedy.
Don't live that way.
(His dream of inheriting the asset gets ruined.)
The final winner of the delicacy of autumn,
Go, Determined Gourmet is...
Team Siblings.
Yes!
- Seriously. - We did a good job.
It feels good to defeat the evil.
Since Team Siblings won, the members will get...
- an equal share of the asset. - What are we getting?
What is the asset?
The asset your father left behind...
is the fruit of autumn, dried persimmon.
- Is that the asset? - I like it.
- I like dried persimmon. It's good. - I like it as well,
but it's too humble to be the asset.
It's too fresh to be the asset.
Dried persimmon is the father's second favorite food.
- Dried persimmon is delicious. - Seriously.
(Loach soup and dried persimmon are Father's favorite food.)
Byung Ok, you worked hard.
Get the penalty before you go.
(That's what you get for working hard.)
- Okay. - Does he need to get the penalty?
- Of course. - The thing is...
I am willing to receive the penalty,
but I am a lot older than the members.
You should get the penalty in my stead.
We can't do that.
We are a team and rules are rules.
Let's go eat dried persimmons.
- Let's enjoy the asset. - Let's eat dried persimmons.
- Take care. - Bye, Byung Ok.
- Enjoy the penalty. - Good luck.
- Bye, Byung Ok. - Enjoy the penalty.
Ji Hyo hasn't had a penalty in a long time.
We failed.
The sunset is beautiful.
It's the whipped cream bomb.
(The penalty is the whipped cream bomb.)
Byung Ok isn't exempt, is he?
(There are 4 people and 2 bombs. No one is exempt.)
Really?
In that case...
- Decide... - How will we decide?
among yourselves.
Let's decide fairly.
Okay.
(What is he doing?)
Hold on. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- The sunset is beautiful. - What?
I was looking at the sunset.
He made us laugh with his back.
- Can't I look at the sunset? - I am jealous of him.
You can look, but...
He made us laugh with his back.
(It's not that I don't want to receive the penalty.)
My goodness.
He was moved.
Let's play a game.
- Really? - Yes.
Let's decide fairly.
Let's play Game of Wits. One!
- Two! - The two of you are it!
One!
(Gosh, he got us.)
The two of you went down at the same time.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo get chosen.)
(They get the penalty instead of the asset.)
It's a good day to receive the penalty.
In 1, 2, 3.
What happened to Kwang Soo?
(Kwang Soo?)
(I am sorry, Kwang Soo.)
You look cool.
Stay that way for a second.
(Upon a closer look...)
You look like Groot.
(I am Lee Kwang Soo. I am Groot.)
See you next week.
(I am Lee Kwang Soo.)
Look at the sunset.
(The legend within the family gets wrapped up.)
(How well do you know Running Man?)
(It's a sudden question.)
(Which member knows the Running Man members the best?)
(It's either Jong Kook or Seok Jin.)
(- It's Jeon So Min. - It's Haha.)
(You don't know anything about me.)
(The answers they blurt out change everything.)
(The members get dragged to a mysterious place.)
(Unknown missions await them.)
(No one can leave.)
(However,)
(a miracle...)
(that is hard to believe...)
(occurs.)
(This has never happened before.)
(Do we go home?)
(No!)
(Irene, Joy,)
(Kang Han Na,)
(and Seol In Ah)
(The familiar partners are back.)
(The cheerful partners...)
(adjust to the variety show with a bang.)
(Also)
(I know Jae Seok's weakness.)
(Is there a story about the national MC we don't know?)
(What's the secret of the national MC?)
(Intimate Strangers)