(Recap)
(Lee Da Hee, a tall rookie of the variety shows)
(Koo Ha Ra, the athletic idol singer)
(Seor In A, super rookie of 2018)
That's Seor In A.
(Mina of Gugudan, the bubbly one)
(These 4 beautiful ladies flew to Jeju Island to join the race.)
(Or could they be the best TV personalities for variety shows?)
(Are they idol singers?)
(No, they are the crazy ladies.)
(These queens of variety shows came to take over Running Man.)
(A partner race, Rule of Collection)
(Each partner chooses a number from 1 to 6.)
(The pairs with the highest and lowest sums of numbers win.)
(The remaining pairs will face the water bomb.)
(The water bomb is at stake on the last mission, Pirate Roulette Quiz.)
(The reckless members choose Betting Pirate with the hope of winning.)
(The unfortunate members make it hard for the pirate to rest.)
(Let's insert it on the count of three for our partnership's sake.)
You're the worst. You're such a jerk.
(Kwang Soo has become a jerk. What will happen to him now?)
- Please pop. Please. - "You're such a jerk."
(The last question will determine the winning pair.)
Do you want to do it together this time?
- Okay. - Are you sure?
I'm sure it will pop.
You have to insert it this time.
If you do it at the same time, we won't know which one caused it.
I know. That's the point. All right.
- If we get this one, we will win. - We can win then.
All right. Stick it in on the count of three.
- All right. 1, 2, 3. - She's counting.
- I can't believe you! - No, no.
(Kwang Soo's hand still doesn't move.)
I missed my cue. I missed my cue.
- Hey, "1, 2, 3." - I just missed my window.
- How could you miss this? - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I really am. You counted out of nowhere.
You didn't give me a heads-up.
Had you counted before to let me know, I would've done it.
Jong Kook, she's so cute.
- My gosh, she's the cutest. - One more time.
- 1, 2, 3. Then you insert it. - No, I mean...
You could've said, "1, 2, 3, 2, 2, 3."
- You went, "1, 2, 3." - You really are a jerk.
- It just caught me off guard. - You are such a jerk.
I can't believe you. Anyway, just insert it then. I'll watch.
Mine didn't pop.
(Pressured)
- This is driving me crazy. - I bet it will pop.
(She's watching him intently.)
I bet it's going to pop.
I'm sure of it.
(He's serious.)
Kwang Soo, if yours pop this time,
I think I'm going to be really angry.
You won't be friends with Da Hee anymore.
Da Hee knows the answer.
(Kwang Soo has nowhere to turn.)
This is crazy.
(What will happen to Kwang Soo?)
Okay!
(He succeeds.)
- We did it. - You have three left.
You have the opposite feelings.
(Will I escape the curse of bad luck starting today?)
- Let's take a seat. - You're not challenging it, right?
All right. Then you will have the chance to answer the question first.
- Okay. - Good luck.
The answer is number one, boiled pork.
(Confident Da Hee chooses number 1, boiled pork.)
- Boiled pork. - It's because...
Da Hee knows how trotters...
- originated. - They didn't exist back then.
And I was slightly confused with chicken soup.
Since it's soup, I thought it'd be boiled down.
- So to get it delivered... - Why do you two stand like that?
Wait, no. It's not what you think.
- Are you models, posing for shots? - No.
- It's not what you think. - You always stand behind her.
- Why do you do that? - I want her to be on camera.
Both of them are cunning.
Insert it for number one, boiled pork.
- Okay. - Number one, boiled pork.
Okay!
(They make a bet on an answer.)
Number one, boiled pork.
(Is number 1, boiled pork the right answer?)
(It's wrong.)
I can't believe this. No way.
- I told you so. - Hey, I told you...
- boiled pork wasn't it. - My gosh, seriously.
- Kwang Soo should've answered it. - This was...
(This isn't what we were expecting.)
Ha Ra will get it right.
(Ha Ra and Jae Seok will try.)
Number five, hangover soup.
Everyone, you think it's not the answer because it's soup.
You're wrong.
The soup would've spilled.
(5, hangover soup)
- I'll insert 5. Jae Seok. - 5.
- You should choose. - No, no.
You should insert three.
(Popping)
See?
Let's change. Hurry!
- We should go. Six? - This is crazy.
- Five. - What am I going to do?
- Let's do 3. - 3?
I'm not sure if we'll have a chance.
How could it pop at our first try?
(So Min places her bet in the midst of the commotion.)
- I thought it was correct. - I can't believe this.
(And she fails.)
(It's the disappointing end of a reckless player.)
She tried.
- I'm going all in with six. - Did she just try that?
I'm going all in with six.
We need one for the Answer Pirate.
Three.
Chicken soup.
No. Should I try one?
Yes, try it.
- Besides, - Go for it.
- there's only three options. - Go for it.
(They pick number 3, chicken soup.)
(This lady who staked everything she had...)
(is the super rookie among the unlucky ones.)
It has to pop.
(She couldn't say anything as she failed 3 times in a row.)
I guess her name didn't mean what I thought it meant.
(Will she be able to redeem herself this time?)
- I mean, seriously. - Hey!
(As expected, she is still the unlucky one.)
- Come here! - I mean, seriously.
Hey! Darn you. Come here!
What's wrong with you? What are you?
We should perform an exorcism. Prepare for an exorcism.
We have to do an exorcism on her. She's giving me the chills.
- Yes, do it. - We have to perform one.
- Who are you? - In A.
- You're not In A, are you? - This is unbelievable.
You're not her, right?
We have 10, right?
But what's the answer?
What if we have the wrong answer?
It doesn't matter. We must go for it.
Look at those love birds.
(What's Korea's first delivery food?)
1, 2, 3.
- If they succeed with nine... - My goodness.
(What happened?)
We won!
- What just happened? - Yes!
(Se Chan and Mina, who did nothing, win the game.)
The victory goes to Se Chan's team.
- Yes! - It's their win. The answer is...
- What's the answer? - It's number five, hangover soup.
- We were going to go for that. - Hey.
We should've thought it as rice soup.
(People cooked the soup during the night, and it arrived at dawn.)
- They won't change. - No, they probably won't.
- It's over then. - Hey, this was...
- All right. - The stage.
Let me reveal the final sums.
- The highest sum, 10 points, - Good for you, Kwang Soo.
Goes to Kwang Soo and Da Hee.
- And... - "And"?
Jae Seok and Ha Ra have 10 points too.
- Come on. - Except for these three pairs,
the rest will face the water bomb.
(They'll face the penalty.)
- We did it! We did it! - It's over.
(They set out to get the penalty in the snowing weather.)
Let's go.
(Jong Kook, So Min, and In A are exempted from the penalty.)
The three of you will get the water bomb now.
One,
- two, - It'll be warm!
- 3! - 3!
(Is this a warm shower?)
(It's fun to watch others get the water bomb.)
(His hair looks like seaweed.)
- I feel so bad. - Good job.
- Well done. - Great work, everyone.
(The race in Jeju Island begins now!)
(Part 2 of Jeju Island Special, Roads of Jeju's Famous Locations)
(Find the tastiest, coolest, and the most entertaining activities.)
(The chaotic race in Jeju Island begins now.)
This is just for you.
- Hello. Hi. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Good morning. - Hello.
- Welcome. - Morning, everyone.
It's warm.
- Haha is all dressed up today. - Right.
- He got excited about this trip. - His outfit tells me...
- "Head, shoulder, knees, and feet". - He has a problem.
- "Swag". - He dressed up like G-Dragon,
but he's not even close.
(Try to copy me if you can.)
Now that I see him in person, Haha is no match for him.
- He also talks like G-Dragon too. - Right.
"Okay."
- Haha, don't go overboard. - I think this is removable.
It's not that it's removable. He's afraid he might lose it,
- so he tied it there. - Hey, that's enough.
- Don't mental institutions do this? - Stop it.
- Don't they? - Cool it.
- I think they do this there. - I saw that too.
- Do you go to soccer classes then? - Hey.
It's better to get this over with now.
Are you here to take coaching classes or what?
I'm not lying when I saw this, but lately, Yu Seok, the cameraman,
dresses better than you.
(The cameraman is a better dresser.)
Look. He's wearing the navy jacket.
- Wear something like that. - He has a lot of clothes. I see.
Look at the navy jacket. That looks nice.
- That's a nice color. - His clothes are colorful.
Today, it's a relaxing tour where you can enjoy the nature.
This race in Jeju Island is called Bingo to the Flowery Road.
- He said it's a relaxing tour. - This is nice.
- "Flowery Road"? - "Bingo to the Flowery Road"?
(Flowery road? Relaxing?)
- This will be a 4-on-4 team match. - 4-on-4?
You select and carry out a mission in a square.
If you succeed, you win a square on the bingo board...
and get an opportunity to win a Chance Card.
Okay.
The first team to complete a line wins.
The winning team takes the best accommodation,
the luxury suite.
- The suite! - The suite!
(The winning team gets to rest in the luxury suite.)
(Let's go to the suite.)
I have never been to one.
The losing team sleeps on an ice rink.
- An ice rink? - An ice rink?
(Do the losers have to sleep on an ice rink?)
- An ice rink? - Yes.
- The losing team sleeps on it. - That's the worst.
(The losing team gets to be cozy in the tents on an ice rink.)
Your face might become paralyzed.
People who sleep on the ice rink might not wake up the next day.
Sleeping on an ice rink is too much.
Those who sleep on the ice rink will be...
3 members from the losing team and 1 member from the winning team.
- Why? - Why?
(3 members from the losing team and 1 member from the winning team)
Why would you choose one member from the winning team?
The winning team saves one member from the losing team,
and the losing team selects one member from the winning team.
There are so many twists and turns.
That means Jae Seok will sleep on the ice rink...
whether he wins or loses.
- You are the same. - That's not true.
- You are the same. - Speak for yourself.
We have two people who are most likely to be selected.
- What are you talking about? - One of them will be selected.
The only way I can save myself...
is by winning with Jae Seok in my team.
That's right. That's the only way.
I can already picture who will sleep...
on the ice rink.
Please bring in the bingo board.
What is that? There are a lot of options.
There are a lot of options.
(Various places in Jeju Island are included.)
(Eliminating the name tag of the target)
(The missions of Bingo to the Flowery Road...)
(lets them enjoy all aspects of the beautiful island.)
"The first tangerine tree". "Korean peninsula in Jeju Island".
- I know what it is. - It's beautiful.
(The first tangerine tree of Jeju Island dates back to 1911.)
(The shape of the Korean peninsula is a treasure of the Olle Trail...)
(that is located in Namwon Keuneong Promenade.)
What's the oldest building in Jeju Island?
(Gwandeogjeong breathes with the history since 1448.)
(The biggest Camellia Hill in Asia)
I should eat the meat noodles with 60 years of traditions.
I told you that I want to eat it on my way here.
- We should eat black cattle. - Black cattle.
(Black cattle is a natural monument that was given to the king.)
(The oldest meat noodles restaurant serves a delicious dish.)
There is "eliminating the name tag of the target".
(Eliminating the name tag of the target)
My goodness.
(It's not fitting for a healing trip.)
(Confident)
Before the race, you will be divided into two teams.
In the count of three,
all members must either sit or stand.
When 4 members sit down and 4 members stand up,
the two teams will be divided.
The team members are important.
(The team members are important for victory.)
Let's go.
We either sit or stand.
(Odd numbers sit and even numbers stand at first.)
- What should I do? - Up and down! In 1, 2...
(You become a team with the members who choose the same position.)
My goodness.
(5 members are standing, and 3 members are sitting.)
The teams haven't been decided yet.
- Kwang Soo stood up a bit late. - No, I didn't.
- Sit or stand at three. - Okay.
Here we go.
Up and down! In 1, 2...
(Are the teams decided this time?)
It's 4 versus 4.
Up and down! In 1, 2...
We can win with these members.
(Haha, Jong Kook, Jae Seok, and So Min are standing.)
I am a bit surprised.
Victory is ours.
(Let's see.)
Hold on. Hold on.
- Give me a chance. - Let's do it once again.
It won't be fun with these teams.
- It won't be fun. - We will be destroyed.
- Let's try it one more time. - We will be destroyed.
- This won't work. - Let's try it one more time.
- This won't work. - This won't work.
- Victory is ours. - Let's sleep in the suite.
- Let's sleep in the suite. - This is great.
Seriously.
- We are set. - This is great.
Okay. We will sleep on the ice rink.
- It won't be fun. - This won't work.
We are the varsity team, and they are the junior varsity team.
(We are the varsity team, and they are the junior varsity team.)
- What are you talking about? - For goodness' sake.
Junior varsity team, my foot!
Just you wait.
- This is new. - "Just you wait"?
Are these the teams?
We have everything.
We have strength, intellect,
and flippant charms. We have everything.
We are set.
We don't have anything.
Your team doesn't have stamina.
- Stamina? - They have no stamina.
- They have no stamina. - This is the worst.
- We are the weakest team. - What should I do?
We are the weakest team.
There usually were Team Jae Seok and Team Jong Kook.
You will have to come up with new names today.
Team Senior and Team Junior.
Jae Seok debuted before Seok Jin.
That's right.
Team Junior Jee.
Team Senior Yu and Team Junior Jee.
If you don't do well today, you will get a scolding.
A scolding? Hey.
It's natural for a junior to get a scolding from the senior.
- Jae Seok is your senior. - He is a senior comedian.
I will get you one day, you punk.
Hold me back.
- What? - Hold me back.
I know you won't do anything to begin with.
We will go with Team Senior Yu,
- and Team Junior Jee. - So it's Team Junior.
After Team Senior Yu and Team Junior Jee change,
- the race will begin. - Is this really happening?
Is this really happening?
It's okay. We will win. Let's win.
Let's show them what we can do.
I don't belong in this team.
I have a different color.
- Stop it. - Hey.
- I don't belong in this team. - You represent this team.
- You lowered the team's quality. - We are like oil and water.
- We don't belong together. - You represent this team.
You lowered the team's quality.
I don't belong in this team.
(Team Senior Yu and Team Junior Jee)
Jae Seok, let's go.
- Are we taking the car? - We have the fighting spirits.
Please take this before you go.
Okay.
(Why is there a roulette?)
- What is this? - Before you go,
you see "eliminating the name tag of the target", right?
(Eliminating the name tag of the target)
For this, you eliminate the name tag...
of the chosen member in the opposing team.
(Eliminate the name tag of the chosen member.)
You will choose the member before you go.
So that the other team doesn't see the result,
- spin the roulette at your spot. - Let's avoid Jong Kook.
Let's avoid Jong Kook.
It will be easy to dominate the race.
- Our team... - Let's spin the roulette.
It doesn't matter which member we get.
I hope we get Seok Jin.
Seok Jin will be the best choice.
- Say, "Start." - Start.
It's only right that you spin the roulette.
My goodness.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
- This is fun. - It's game over.
- This is great. - This is fun.
Let's stick together today.
- We have to do this. - We have to win.
It will be too boring if we lose.
We have to win.
We will win today.
I am sorry. I will be serious today.
I am sorry. I won't be funny today.
- I am sorry. - Don't expect us to joke around.
- We will win today. - Dear viewers,
don't laugh for an hour.
Watch the show with seriousness.
Watch the race...
as if you are watching the Olympic Games. We are serious.
We will be fine as long as you do well.
This is Pyeongchang Olympics.
We can spin the roulette now, right?
- Pick a member. - Spin the roulette.
- Say, "Start." - It's a practice round.
Spin it for practice.
- Spin it for practice. - It's a practice round.
It's nothing.
- Okay! So Min! - So Min! We did it.
(They give a ceremony after seeing they picked So Min.)
- For goodness' sake. - All right.
The four of you must shout, "Start."
- We did that. - No, you didn't.
We did that.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Spin the roulette.
In 2, 3.
- Why would you spin it? - It's a practice round.
It's a practice round.
So Min!
(They get So Min again.)
No.
(They make the ceremony look more natural.)
Let's go.
Come on.
- Say, "Start." - Let's go.
- Start. - Start.
- Here I go. - Let's spin it together.
In 1, 2, 3.
(After Ji Hyo shouts, "Start," they spin the roulette for real.)
(Please let it be So Min again.)
(They get Jong Kook.)
We have to shout, "Start," together.
- You picked Jong Kook. - No, no.
- Come on. - One person should spin it.
Actually, my finger wasn't on the roulette.
- Who said, "Start"? - You picked Jong Kook.
Kwang Soo, you should have kept your unlucky finger off of it.
Where should we go first?
- Camellia will be pretty. - Let's go to Camellia Hill.
- I want to go there. - We will go to Camellia Hill.
- I love camellia. - Camellia Hill.
- Let's go and eat black cattle. - Black cattle?
- How about black cattle? - I want to eat meat noodles.
Aren't we eating black cattle?
- Did you think we would raise them? - We'd be eating it?
- We are only here for two days. - Hold on.
I get that you are annoyed,
- but don't snap at me. - Think about it.
We are in this together.
I don't belong in this team.
You belong in this team more than I do.
- I don't belong here. - We won't raise the black cattle.
If they were red, I am yellow. I don't belong in this team.
- Hey. - For goodness' sake.
- You are taking forever. - Seriously.
We are going to eat meat noodles.
What's taking you so long? Hurry up.
- We are set. - We just don't have the teamwork.
Gosh, they are so annoying.
- Let's eat black cattle. - Let's do that.
Did the roulette point at my name?
Go, and do it.
- Stop the car. - Do it.
Hurry up, and run.
Run.
- That's right. - Haha.
What's wrong?
- Start driving. - What is he doing?
- Go. - Hey.
I'm sorry.
(Will Haha think that he's the target?)
Was it me?
- Is it me? - I don't think it's you.
It's not you.
Okay.
It was enough to look suspicious.
(Dark treasure of Jeju Island and arboretum)
Let's get to the black cattle ranch first.
- We're leaving. - Okay.
What's our strategy?
After eating,
if we see the other team, we'll tear off his name tag.
- Okay. - Finish at the mandarin trees.
- That's one bingo. - Is that bingo?
Listen.
- The center is the most important. - The center?
"Eliminating the name tag of the target".
Why did we get Jong Kook?
How could our target be Jong Kook?
It was as if it were planned.
Teams were arranged if it were planned.
- Gosh. - How is it possible?
- We should definitely win. - I agree.
- We usually imagine the worst team. - Right.
This is the worst team that I've never imagined.
(It's the worst team ever.)
Is it the worst?
Who makes it the worst team?
Don't ask.
(You know the answer.)
(Are you talking about me?)
- Who do you think it is? - Pardon?
Who makes this team the worst?
I'll show you what I have.
Get ready, everyone.
This is great. It's perfect to drive in Jeju Island.
- It's the best. - When there are no cameras...
(She looks around carefully.)
This is great.
It feels...
like...
(She hesitates.)
It's my first time being on a team with people...
who aren't weaker than me.
Se Chan and Kwang Soo...
are around my age.
- That's true. - I feel comfortable with them.
I think Seok Jin is...
He's quite weak.
- I don't have to be careful... - He's weak.
Around Seok Jin.
Seok Jin is weak.
It's my first time being around my seniors.
Seok Jin doesn't count.
So Min, have you been to Jeju Island often?
- Jeju Island? - Yes.
I used to live here.
- When? - It was when I was six.
- Really? - I lived for about a year.
- Really? - It was due to my dad's work.
- Did your father work here? - Yes.
Did he work in Jeju Island?
During his stay here,
while he peed in the ocean in Jeju Island,
- he caught an octopus. - Really?
- How did he? - As he peed,
the water turned warm.
An octopus came up from underneath the rocks.
Your stories...
including about your father are strange.
- They're unbelievable. - They're strange.
- I agree. - You tell unbelievable stories.
It was my first time eating octopus that was freshly caught.
- Really? - It was an octopus that...
- your father caught with his urine. - Yes.
It was surprised by the warmth.
- So Min. - Yes?
Do you have memories in Jeju Island?
Let me think.
Have you come here with a boyfriend?
I have.
- Have you? - Yes.
Jeju Island.
Did you come here alone with him?
Just us two.
You sound nostalgic.
- "Just us two." - "Just us two."
- The woman... - However
that I loved the most got married.
That's great news.
(Jae Seok makes him feel worse.)
- I think... - Seriously?
It's great for her.
How dare you say that?
- Get out! - What's wrong?
- How could you? - What is it?
Don't ruin my beautiful memory.
- Gosh. - You probably gave her a hard time.
My goodness.
(Here they go again.)
But listen.
Just don't say anything.
Don't say anything after saying but.
- Stop it. - I'm getting...
- upset little by little. - The water looks great.
- Let's just win today. - Goodness.
This is great.
- It's great. - Isn't it?
We're here.
(While they argue, they arrive at Camellia Hill.)
- Camellias bloom in the winter. - It's so windy.
- A song is called "Camellia Lady". - "Camellia Lady".
- Countless numbers of - "Camellia Lady".
- Nights - Nights
I'm thankful Jong Kook is a singer.
If not, his voice sounds so weak.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Jong Kook is a singer.
- What do you mean? - Seriously.
- Jae Seok. - What did I say?
- He's trying to pick a fight. - It's just my opinion.
- Mr. Yu. - What is it?
We're having a good time today.
Wasn't that an attack?
What do you mean? I was only speaking my mind.
- What's wrong with that? - Gosh.
Don't make it uncomfortable, and get out of the car.
He's strange.
- Let's get out first. - Do I take this with me?
(They don't stop arguing.)
- It's so windy. - Where do we go?
- The wind is warm. - It's warm.
It's warm today.
- There's sunlight. - The weather is...
- great today. - There's sunlight.
- I know. - Where are the camellias?
- Let's go. - Where are they?
(The best Camellia Hill in Asia)
This is amazing.
I didn't know there was a place like this.
- There are many new places here. - It's not cold.
- Are camellia flowers red or white? - They're red.
(With various camellia flowers from the world, it changes with seasons.)
(At this beautiful arboretum...)
What's that?
- It's Tray Karaoke. - It's Tray Karaoke.
- It is. - It's Tray Karaoke.
Gosh, it's Tray Karaoke.
Tray Karaoke?
(She's excited alone.)
Look at these camellia flowers.
- They're pretty. - They're pretty, So Min.
- Are these camellia flowers? - I see.
- I can't find where you are. - Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook makes So Min's heart flutter.)
Indeed.
I see you very clearly, So Min.
I see you clearly.
- Move. Don't hurt the flowers. - Hey.
So Min is a camellia.
- I'm a camellia. - She was.
Goodness.
- You're at the first destination. - It's so beautiful here.
I was worried being in the car with Jong Kook,
but we didn't argue so much.
- That's not it. - The way he drives is so different.
He wanted to pick a fight...
- No, his driving... - during the ride.
Made me want to fight.
- When we're in a big group... - They were close to arguing.
Jae Seok knows how to agitate people.
Sorry?
That jerk.
- Jae Seok is... - Let's sit down.
What do we do?
Your mission is called...
Camellia Flower Tray Karaoke.
(Camellia Flower Tray Karaoke)
You get five chances.
Sing "Camellia Lady" without making any mistakes.
(You must sing "Camellia Lady" without any mistakes to succeed.)
Then, you clear the mission.
If you make a mistake, the tray falls on you.
I know.
(This is a song by Lee Mi Ja, a famous Korean singer.)
Aren't you familiar with "Camellia Lady"?
You'll sing verse two.
Verse two?
- Wait a minute. - That's too harsh.
(Does anyone know the second verse?)
- You're really terrible. - Is this...
I hardly know the lyrics.
The three Chance Cards are...
listen to the whole song, listen to one measure, and changing seats.
You get two chances to use them.
Let's start right away.
You'll pick seats after listening.
Goodness.
Play the song.
(The main song plays.)
(Try to memorize the lyrics with them.)
The story engraved on.
Camellia petals.
With the secret story.
In her heart.
Camellia Lady.
(She murmurs to herself.)
Is.
Waiting.
When will her love come back
I don't know this song.
(This part is sung by the whole group.)
- I'm in trouble. - To the lonely camellia flower?
- "Camellia Lady is waiting". - My part is...
(It's difficult.)
- I'm in trouble. - You may not discuss.
- Pick a number. - Goodness.
I need number three.
"Camellia Lady is waiting".
- "Camellia Lady waits"? - "Waiting".
- "Waiting". - You may not discuss.
We can't discuss?
You may not discuss.
- I need to pick number three. - What?
The story engraved on.
You may not discuss.
I'm number four.
(Jae Seok picks his original seat.)
- What's your number? - Number one.
That's a relief.
(Haha and So Min pick their original seats.)
(Everyone picks their original seats.)
Wait, do it again.
- We didn't cheat. - We didn't.
- No way. - We didn't cheat.
- We didn't cheat. - We didn't do anything.
No way.
- We swear. - We didn't do anything.
- I got goosebumps. - This is unbelievable.
- We got the same result. - I can't remember anyway.
- We only have four. - I don't...
I don't know the melody.
Let's play for now.
(They sit in their original seats.)
If you discuss, you'll have to pick another number.
(It's their first attempt.)
Gosh.
(How will it turn out?)
Please play the sound.
Music starts.
(It's their first try.)
(The story engraved on camellia petals)
The story.
What is he doing?
(The tray comes down.)
Haha, how could you?
- The story - What?
What was that melody?
- I don't know the song. - What are your lyrics?
- It hurt. - "The story engraved on".
The story engraved on.
Camellias.
Isn't it "The story engraved on camellia petals"?
- I think so. - Isn't it camellia petals?
- With - With the secret story.
In her heart.
Camellia Lady.
- You're terrible at singing. - Is.
- Waiting - So Min.
Can you sing with emotions?
- Camellia Lady - Camellia Lady.
What was the last line?
(What was my part?)
- What? - It went...
(Are you serious?)
It went, "Wherever" or something like that.
"Or something like that"?
- What did you hear? - Seriously,
you should have at least heard a phrase.
- Seriously... - Hold on.
Are there teams within this team?
- It's not like that. - It's not like that.
- We're all in this. - We all aim to succeed.
- So Min, come here. - Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. - Hey.
Choose the right team.
- Choose the right team. - He should know at least a little.
- So Min, are you sure? - Seriously...
- You should've heard something. - You should have.
The thing is,
I was flustered. I was listening to the beginning part.
Do you want to sleep on the ice rink tonight?
Sing the beginning part then.
- What? Hold on. - Sing the beginning part.
- What is he saying? - Sing the beginning part.
If it's correct, I'll let it slide.
I'm sorry.
(I sincerely apologize.)
- I'm sorry. - You should have apologized.
- The thing is... - Stop giving excuses.
You can either hear the whole song, hear one line, or switch places.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
You can use only two Chance Cards.
Why are you picking one yourself?
- Did you pick one? - It'll be the whole song.
(He's confident in his choice.)
- You're unlucky. - Hey!
Why did you do it?
(They have only 2 chances, )
(and Jae Seok picked "switching places".)
- I shouldn't have done it. - Why did you do it on your own?
My team...
No. You already picked one.
I can't believe you.
- But I... - He didn't even hear his line.
We're Team Senior Yu.
Our team was named after me.
That's just the team's name, nothing more.
- Aren't you going to say something? - We named the team after you,
- so pull yourself together. - Jae Seok.
- Pull yourself together, will you? - Gosh.
- Are you serious? - Why did you do it on your own?
My goodness.
- Let's try. - Gosh.
- "The story"... - "On camellia petals"...
- "Engraved on camellia petals". - "Engraved on camellia petals".
- Love engraved on camellia petals - The story engraved on.
It's "the story".
It sounded like, "the story".
It doesn't suit the melody.
(The story engraved)
You sound so sly.
He's great.
- Sly? - He's amazing.
- You sound so sly. - Sly?
- You sound sly. - I sounded sly?
I'm short.
- I'm short. - You're short.
- Jong Kook is sly. - Sly?
I'm embarrassing.
Exactly.
- How did you know? - Let's draw a number.
(Let's switch places.)
- What was it? - The story.
- We're in trouble. - I'm number one.
- The story - Stop discussing.
- MR. - The story on.
- That must be it. - "Engraved on".
- "The story on"... - Play.
- The story on - Play the music.
(They can't even agree on the first line.)
(Will their second try be successful?)
(Second try)
(The story engraved on camellia petals)
The story.
On camellia petals.
- It's "engraved on". - It's "engraved on".
(Jong Kook told you.)
- It's "engraved on". - He deserves a beating.
You deserve a beating.
Come here.
Get up.
We're Team Senior Yu.
- We're Team Senior Yu. - I didn't know my part.
When you've done something wrong, you should be criticized.
You should learn to take criticism.
Draw a Chance Card.
Draw one. Let Jong Kook do it.
Look.
(Let Jong Kook do it this time.)
(If he draws something bad, he'll feel bad.)
Look. I'll show you.
(I'll show you all.)
(Will it go as Jae Seok planned?)
Look. It's the whole song, see?
Go away.
Why can't you do this? Do you see this?
Apologize.
- Why? - Kiss his hand.
Kiss his hand.
Gosh.
- Hey. - Focus.
Focus. Let's hear the whole song again.
Okay.
- Gosh. - Good job.
Listen to others' parts too. I don't know my part.
All right. Play the music.
(As their last chance, they hear the whole song again.)
(The story engraved on camellia petals)
(It's "engraved on".)
(With the secret story in her heart)
(Listening carefully)
It's "in her heart".
(Camellia Lady is waiting)
"Camellia Lady is"...
(Nodding)
(Camellia Lady is waiting)
(When will her love come back)
What did she sing?
(To the lonely camellia flower?)
All right. It's "To the lonely camellia flower".
- I didn't hear my part. - Let's start right away.
- "When will"... - "To the lonely"...
- "To the lonely"... - What should I do?
- To the lonely... - Play...
- the music. - What was my part? The story...
The story...
(Third try)
- The story - "Engraved on"...
"Camellia petals".
The story on camellia petals.
It's "engraved on".
(He's wrong again.)
(Engraved!)
"Engraved", you idiot!
Let me engrave your body.
I can't believe you guys.
- How many times did I tell you? - Jae Seok!
Guys, say something.
How could you do this?
What are you doing?
- It's "engraved"... - What are you?
(Let me teach you a lesson.)
What are you doing?
- Hold on. - Let me take care of it.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe it.
- That's enough. - Is he a spy?
- Please ignore this one. - Are you a spy?
- Apologize to everyone. - What?
- What? - Apologize.
Apologize.
- I can't let it slide. - Hands on your belly.
- Okay. - Hands on your belly.
- Hands on your belly. - Hands on your belly.
- I'm sorry. - There you go.
- Good. - Do you remember my part?
The story.
- It's "engraved on". - Okay.
Let's try singing the whole thing.
Stop pointing your spoon at me.
- I've had enough. - I'm sorry.
If you sing it wrong again, I'll engrave your body.
(Haha is practicing diligently.)
I don't know my part. When will her.
When will her love.
It was your part before.
- He didn't hear it. - I didn't hear that part.
- Why? - I was busy listening to mine.
I don't remember what I heard in the beginning.
What?
- Tell her something. - How could I remember it?
- Can't you say anything? - When will her love...
(I remember it now.)
(When will her love come back)
- Good. - Let's start.
- Okay. - What was the last line?
The last line.
(To the lonely camellia flower?)
The lonely camellia flower blooms.
- What? - "To the lonely camellia flower".
- Isn't that a different song? - "To the lonely camellia flower".
All three of them got up.
To the lonely camellia flower?
Fine. Stay in your seats.
- We're here. - Okay.
- I've never seen black cattle. - Neither have I.
We're in Jeju Island. Is this Olle Trail?
- Are we on Olle Trail? - I think so.
No, this is not Olle Trail.
It's somewhere else.
Just agree with him.
- I'm sorry. - I really don't like him.
- I'm sorry. - Gosh.
You're number three.
- Hey. - What's that?
- What is this? - Is this all poop?
- It's all poop. - Really?
It's all poop.
No. Oh, it is.
It is.
It's all poop?
It's poop.
I've never seen anything like this before.
(Are you surprised?)
The road is covered with poop.
- There's so much. - It's all poop.
Gosh.
(It's a poop trail.)
(Come here.)
(They're struggling to get poop on each other.)
(They take hold of the team leader.)
(He steps on it.)
Seok Jin stepped on poop.
(Look at Seok Jin. He stepped on poop.)
Don't sweat over this.
Focus on winning.
- I'll be lucky today. - Seok Jin stepped on poop.
(I'll be lucky.)
- It's all poop. - Look at that.
(Look at the cows.)
- But they're brown. - One of them is black.
- Where? - They're mixed.
There are so many of them.
There are calves too.
The black cattle you see over there are...
- the treasure of Jeju Island. - Black cattle.
(Jeju's treasure, black cattle)
They were Jeju Island's specialty in the Joseon dynasty period.
20 of them were offered to the king...
every year.
(Black cattle are rare and taste good.)
If you complete the black cattle mission,
you'll win a Chance Card and a meal.
(They can win a meal.)
Will we get to eat black cattle?
Really?
- Okay. - Black cattle.
We have to win it.
This mission is...
Cow Quiz.
(Cow Quiz)
If you get more than two questions right, you succeed.
It's a quiz related to cows.
- Cow Quiz? - It's a quiz?
(They have to get two or more questions right.)
- It's a quiz? - I'm bad at quizzes.
- I'm really bad at quizzes. - It doesn't matter.
- Don't say that in front of Ji Hyo. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
- That's rude. - She doesn't understand questions.
- You're nothing compared to her. - I apologize.
(You and Ji Hyo belong to different classes.)
- You're not even close to her. - Kwang Soo.
- Stop talking. - Are you making fun of her?
- Don't take the title away from me. - She's worse than me.
(Everyone in the team is bad at solving quizzes.)
(Can they win the Chance Card and Meal Card for black cattle?)
- All right. First question. - Okay.
You know the story "Minister Hwang Hui and the Farmer", right?
- I don't know much about history. - What is that?
(He's perplexed.)
(Minister Hwang Hui? I don't know much about history.)
It was right after when Joseon had been established as a country.
Hwang Hui at a young age was walking down the street.
He met an old man, heading to the field with a brown and a black bull.
Hwang Hui asked which one did a better job plowing the field.
The man whispered to his ear,
"This bull plows the field much better."
Hwang Hui asked why the old man had whispered to him.
He answered, "They have ears too."
"If they hear they're not good, they won't be happy either."
From this encounter, Hwang Hui had an epiphany.
Then he carefully chose his words and became a wise prime minister.
(Wait. This is similar to that.)
The man covered their ears like he was playing the game, Of Course.
(Was it similar to the game, Of Course on "X-Man"?)
- No, it's not. - It's not?
Kwang Soo, don't associate it with weird stuff.
I mean, he covered the ears. Didn't he? Isn't it the same?
- I know this. I got goose bumps. - Are you serious?
- Here's the question. - I really know this story.
- In the story I told you, - I have a bad feeling about this.
The farmer said 1 of the 2 bulls did a better job.
- Which bull was that? - Is it a multiple-choice question?
Number One, the black bull.
Number Two, the brown bull.
(Ji Hyo is confused.)
- It's 1 of those 2 choices? - Yes.
- That's it? - It's 1 of those 2.
- He picked 1 of the 2? - Kwang Soo, look.
Kwang Soo, look. We are here to see the black cattle.
- Black cattle. - So it must be the black bull.
Or should we expect a twist?
Minister Hwang Hui...
- "Hwang" means brown. - Hey.
- Is it the same character though? - His name does have "Hwang" in it.
- Are you sure it's the same one? - Yes, it is the same one.
- Does "Hwang" mean brown? - Does he use the same character?
(He does use the same Chinese character, but how is it relevant?)
(What's Ji Hyo's answer?)
I think it's the black one.
- I was going to pick the opposite. - Is it the black one?
- Should we do rock-paper-scissors? - Sure.
- This is just among us. - Let's do whatever we want.
- Or we won't make a decision. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo win.)
- I really hope you win. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll pick Number 1. You'll pick 2. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
- Okay. - Which one will it be?
- I sort of remember this. - What's your answer?
(I think I know.)
The brown bull. Number Two, brown bull.
(Kwang Soo keeps saying he remembers the story and is confident.)
(Their opinions differ. Is his memory reliable?)
- I told you! See? I told you. - My gosh. You got it right.
(Kwang Soo's answer is correct.)
- I knew it. - I kind of remember this.
- My goodness, Kwang Soo. - It's because...
I was three when I heard it.
- When I went to bed, my mother... - The Chinese character...
- When I went to bed, - Did that help?
My mom read me this story at the bedside.
(She read me "Minister Hwang Hui and the Farmer".)
We managed to read the crew's thought. That's all.
- Exactly. - Since there are black cattle.
- Things are going well for us. - Hey.
- That's what we did. - Let me be really objective.
"We" didn't manage to do that. "I" got this right.
- No, that's not true. - I disagree.
- Kwang Soo. - I was going to pick the brown one.
I won the rock-paper-scissors.
- We all contributed to this win. - Then I picked the right one.
- We all got the right answer. - Let's not do this.
- Aren't you in the same team? - I...
- The three of us... - They'll go to the ice rink.
- I'll go to the suite. - Dream on, Kwang Soo.
(They will end up on the ice rink, and I'll be in the suite.)
We are not in the same team.
- Okay. He did a good job after all. - Let's do this.
- Right. You did an excellent job. - Let's compliment him.
- Why don't we pat him on the back? - Well done.
- I'm serious. - Well done.
Great job.
(His hand dives into the poop while being patted.)
He touched the poop.
(This is unbelievable. He dips his hand in the poop.)
- Come on, Kwang Soo. Unbelievable. - That's disgusting.
- That's nasty. - Go away. Stay away from us.
(No way.)
That's nasty.
(He's having fun.)
This is real poop.
This is real.
- Wipe it there. - That's disgusting.
We must get this right.
- The staff members are flustered. - They are flustered now.
Give us a harder one.
- I was going to do that. - Sure. Take your shot at it.
- Here's the second question. - Okay.
You'll all take turns and answer it.
(For this one, everyone must answer it.)
Name a celebrity whose surname is So within 5 seconds.
(That's not a common surname.)
We will start with Kwang Soo. Get ready. Start.
- One. - So Yu Jin.
- Two. - So Ji Sub.
- 3, 4, - So... So Chan Whee.
(If Ji Hyo can answer, they'll get the Chance and Meal Cards.)
(Can she think of one more celebrity whose surname is So?)
Time is up!
- So Dingfang. - Who is that?
There's a Chinese actor named So Dingfang.
(He should've said that earlier.)
Then why did you say So Ji Sub earlier?
(You should've gone with So Dingfang then.)
(If he knew another one, why did he say So Ji Sub?)
Then why did you say So Ji Sub earlier?
- You shouldn't have used that one. - You...
(He turns on Kwang Soo for his action.)
It was you.
- Why did you say that? - You said that name.
(He slaps Seok Jin with the dirty hand.)
- It was you who said his name. - You shouldn't have named him.
(Kwang Soo's massage with his dirty hand enrages Seok Jin.)
Stop it.
(Because of So Dingfang, their unsanitary fight begins.)
This just turned into a fight of poop.
(What are they doing?)
Seriously.
(Get this poop powder!)
(I hate you guys.)
(We're staying away because you guys are disgusting.)
All right. This is a quiz about a pun.
I'm good at those.
It's Pictionary.
- We'll solve it together, right? - Yes.
Look at this drawing.
- Is that a pumpkin? - Guess the title of the drawing.
(Guess the title of the drawing within 1 minute.)
- Look at this. - The time limit is one minute.
This is a cow.
(The cow is looking at the burning flame.)
- "My gosh, it's burning nicely." - Hey, keep quiet. Come on.
- "A big loss for a small gain"? - Could it be a name of a celebrity?
Or is it beef bulgogi?
- Cow and the fire. - Cow...
- Beef bulgogi. - Fluorine.
- The cow is looking at the fire. - Right.
The fact that it's looking at the fire is important.
"Fire" by BTS?
- Could it be BTS? - No, I don't think so.
Then tell us how many characters are in the title.
- There are three. This is the hint. - Okay.
- He said there are 3. - 3 characters?
The cow is crossing its legs.
Beef tripe.
(They don't have a clue, but time is ticking away.)
A fable...
- How could we get this right? - Hold on.
- You set us up to fail. - Wait.
We can tell you the answer, right?
That's right. Tell us the answer.
- 5, 4, - This isn't right. It's too hard.
- 3, 2, 1. - This is too hard. Seriously.
The answer is...
(What's the title of the drawing in which a cow is looking at a fire?)
It's "Firefighter".
I don't get the last character.
- The cow is neglecting it. - It's neglecting the fire.
My gosh. Are you serious?
You failed to finish your mission.
- But the thing is... - It's securing the fire.
If it's "Gall Bladder",
- shouldn't it hold its stomach? - No, it's "Firefighter".
(It means the cow has to pee.)
- No, it's "Firefighter". - "Firefighter".
I'm sorry.
- How could you mix those two? - My apologies.
I can't believe he's in my team.
He's the worst among us.
- I'll give up. - He's the worst among us.
I will just go to the ice rink.
Kwang Soo, please be nice even though I'm bad at this.
All right. You failed to accomplish your mission.
(Do you think you can win the stickers like this?)
- When will her love - You'll start now.
- Hey, hey. - We were so close.
We were so close even though Jae Seok messed up.
- He made the same mistake twice. - Fine. I got it.
Why don't you get rid of me then?
I am planning on it. How did you figure that out?
(Stop fighting, and try finishing it.)
All right. Here we go.
- Play the song, please. - What's my first line?
- "The story"... - "The story"...
- "engraved on"... - "engraved on"...
(They only have 2 chances left. They must go past the first verse.)
The story engraved.
On camellia petals.
With a secret.
(He gets it wrong.)
- What just happened? - Hey, that hurts.
(The trays come down during the second line.)
- What just happened? What is it? - I can't believe you.
- It's correct up to "with". - What did you say?
- It's correct up to "with". - With...
- See? - What are you going to do?
- You nagged me, but you messed up. - Look.
If you didn't mess up before,
I would've fixed the lyrics and got them right this time.
Is it my fault?
Is this my fault?
(They get violent.)
It's hard to be with this team.
So Min, is it my fault?
- Listen. - It's better to lose.
- I think... - It's because...
Is this our last chance?
(This is exhausting.)
Here's your last chance.
Let's give each other a chance.
- "With the secret story" - Let's do it.
- Come here. - These are the lyrics.
"With the secret story."
- With the secret story - With the secret story.
- In her heart - In her heart, that's right.
- Camellia Lady is - Camellia Lady is.
Raise the tone.
- Waiting - Waiting.
When will her love.
- When will her love come - That's wrong.
- When will her - When will her love come back?
When will her... I can't do it.
The melody is wrong.
- We'll start after we get it. - Hey.
What are the lyrics?
When will her love.
- Come back - Come back.
- "When will her love"... - "Come back".
- "Come back". - Is Jong Kook giving a lesson?
What?
We have to hurry up.
Goodness.
Let's sing the last measure together.
- To the lonely - To the lonely.
- Camellia Lady - Camellia flower?
- It's not "lady". - Isn't it?
Camellia Lady.
Camellia.
(The last measure is the problem.)
(They get serious.)
To the lonely.
- Camellia flower? - Camellia flower?
"To the lonely camellia flower?"
- I'm worried. - Let's do it.
This is your last chance.
(If they fail, they won't win any Bingo Sticker.)
Camellia Lady.
Wait, with the secret story...
- This is the melody. - "With the secret story".
- Play music. - "The story engraved on".
Play music.
- "Camellia petals". - "Camellia petals".
"The story engraved on".
The story engraved on.
Camellia petals.
With the secret story.
In her heart.
(Jong Kook sings correctly.)
Camellia Lady is.
(Jong Kook guides him.)
Waiting.
That's right.
Camellia Lady.
(Haha sings the third measure successfully.)
(Next is So Min.)
(She seemed unsure during the last practice.)
(Will So Min sing the correct lyrics?)
When will her love.
Come back.
(She sings correctly.)
(They clear the mission if they sing the last measure correctly.)
(Will they make it without any mistake?)
- Camellia flower? - Camellia flower?
(This must be correct.)
(They clear the mission miraculously.)
(We can't believe that we did it.)
We got it.
- Goodness. - It was difficult.
It was really difficult.
- It was difficult. - It was hard.
Still...
- We did it. - Of course.
We barely made it.
(Camellia Hill is cleared.)
There's a piece of paper.
- Meat noodles. - We'll pick...
- meat noodles. - Okay.
(Let's go eat meat noodles.)
Before you go,
you need to pick a Chance Card.
(It's time to pick another Chance Card.)
We have no choice, right?
(We have to pick a good one.)
There are...
Steal Card, Cancel Card,
Exchange Card, and Dud. It's a total of four.
- I'll pick if you don't want to. - How about this?
- Let's pick. - I'll pick if you don't want to.
(Jong Kook picks a Chance Card.)
We picked one.
- That's great. It's Steal Card. - Steal Card.
(Team Senior Yu picks a Steal Card.)
(Let's steal Team Junior Jee's land.)
Do we get to steal it?
That's right.
Where did they go?
They went to see black cattle.
This one? That's good.
We can pick the same, right?
Take off the sticker...
and put it on the black cattle.
Why?
(Why would we take ours off?)
The other team picked a Steal Card. You stole from each other.
- Goodness. - Did they steal too?
(They ended up switching their land.)
We should have picked a Cancel Card.
(Team Junior Jee picks a Steal Card.)
(They steal Camellia Hills from Team Senior Yu.)
(The teams switch places.)
Let's go while showing off.
- Let's go to mandarin trees. - Let's go.
- Go to mandarin tress. - Let's go to mandarin trees.
Let's go.
We work quite well as a team.
We can say that if we win.
Let's win.
However, if we lose,
we can't ever be on the same team.
What about just once more?
- If we lose... - Just once more.
Let's surprise everyone today...
instead of betraying each other.
There's no reason to betray each other.
(They promise not to betray each other.)
Wait, Haha sent me a text message.
(Did he send Team Senior Yu's secret information?)
What did he say?
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Goodness. - What is it?
(Was the text message related to Kwang Soo?)
Who is it from?
Kwang Soo sent a message to Haha.
I sent it a long time ago.
It was a long time ago.
"Haha, please pick me."
"My team is hopeless."
"I'll do anything for you. I'll help you win."
I sent that before the game.
- Let's check the time. - Before the game.
(Kwang Soo tried to be a spy.)
- Kwang Soo. - It was a long time ago.
It was during my childhood.
My goodness.
(It was 10 minutes ago.)
I think everyone got a text message.
- Let me check. - "Please pick me."
"My team is hopeless."
"I'll do anything for you."
- Is it from Kwang Soo? - "I'll help you win."
He also sent me a message...
a while ago.
I'll forward it to Seok Jin and Se Chan.
That's a good idea.
(He tells on Kwang Soo.)
- Before we left... - Well,
it could be before we left.
Do you think I'd do the same?
- Gosh, Kwang Soo. - Would I do the same?
That was harsh, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Stop thinking about betraying.
- It's already late. - You should think about winning.
I agree.
I'll be honest. I wasn't going to say it.
I had a big dream.
What dream?
- Winning alone? - By sending the message,
I wanted to use it against them.
Come on, Kwang Soo.
Okay, goodness.
He totally fooled us.
- Kwang Soo. - Seriously.
You're a piece of trash.
- You're a piece of trash. - Kwang Soo.
You're creeping me out.
I wanted to use it.
- Drop the subject. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
Can't you understand it?
Okay, Kwang Soo.
(Seok Jin does something on his phone.)
- This is frustrating. - I tried to use it against them.
Wait, Seok Jin.
Did you send a text message?
No.
- No, how could I? - What?
- Seok Jin. - I didn't.
Ji Hyo, verify it with Jae Seok.
(They call Jae Seok to verify.)
- You can't do that as our leader. - You're frustrating.
Ji Hyo.
Did Seok Jin send you a text message?
Yes, he did.
(He answers without hesitating.)
- Seok Jin! - Seok Jin.
What if I didn't notice?
(He's another cheater.)
- What's wrong with everyone? - No.
- This is wrong. - What if I didn't notice?
This is wrong, Seok Jin.
What did Seok Jin say in his message?
He said that he's an X-man...
and will destroy the team.
(Jae Seok repeats exactly what Seok Jin wrote him.)
Stop it. Goodness.
- Hey. - Forget it, Seok Jin.
It's our strategy.
What's wrong with him?
This is driving me crazy.
- We got it. - My plan worked perfectly.
- I knew it. - They'll be...
- completely fooled by us. - They'll be fooled.
They'll fall for it.
- I knew it. - Seok Jin.
The other team is...
- in my hands. - Right.
- I knew it. We have... - They're in my hands.
Control over them.
- This is ridiculous. - Okay.
We'll win today.
(They head for the mandarin tree mission.)
Is it in the middle of a city?
Is there a mandarin farm in the city?
Look to the front.
(Look at that.)
- It suddenly appeared. - It's great.
It suddenly appeared.
- There's a view of nature. - What's that?
It's a house with a stone fence.
Is there a mandarin farm here?
This is it.
The tree in the back...
was planted in 1911. It's the first mandarin tree in Jeju Island.
- In 1911? - It was in 1911.
- What? Was it in 1911? - "To express gratitude..."
"for King cherry trees sent from Korea,."
"Japan sent 14 mandarin trees."
"The first one was planted in Jeju Island."
(It's the first Jeju mandarin tree.)
- It's... - The tree is older than Seok Jin.
- Right. - It's much older than him.
Do mandarins grow?
- It's very old. - Do mandarins still grow?
- Yes. - Do they still grow?
There they are.
- There's one. - They're on the tree.
- There are two. - Really?
They're really there.
They must be expensive.
Here's your next mission.
(What's their mission?)
It's called Find This Person in Jeju Island.
(Find This Person in Jeju Island)
Find a person who's native to Jeju Island without a mandarin tree...
neither at his home nor at his relatives'.
- Then you clear the mission. - Relatives?
- I see. - What do you mean relatives?
Up to cousins.
- They must live in an apartment. - Right.
(Mandarins are a specialty in Jeju Island.)
(Does every other person in Jeju Island own a mandarin tree?)
(I have mandarin trees in the yard. We grow mandarins too.)
(There are only mandarin trees. We have mandarin trees at home.)
I heard that...
mandarin trees are very common.
- They're everywhere? - Everyone has a tree at home.
But there are so many apartment buildings.
(Will they be able to find someone who has no mandarin trees?)
Just find one person.
- You don't have much time. Hurry. - Let's go.
It might not take so long.
If we're lucky, we might find someone soon.
Here.
(He drives the car for the staff.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Are you from Jeju Island? - Yes.
Do you have mandarin trees at home?
(Do you have mandarin trees at home?)
Yes, I do.
- I see. Thank you. - Yes, I do.
(He has mandarin trees.)
- Thank you. - Mandarins taste good.
They do.
- Most own mandarin trees, right? - Yes.
Do you know anyone...
who doesn't have mandarin trees?
- There aren't many. - See?
We're looking for someone...
whose relatives don't have mandarin trees either.
There won't be many.
- 80 percent will have them. - 80 percent?
We'll have to find the 20 percent.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(It might be harder than we thought.)
- My goodness. - How are we going to find them?
I see no people.
- There are no people. - It's Monday.
(The street is empty.)
Everyone must be working.
I can't believe this. Cheonjiyeon Waterfall is near here.
- Where? - Cheonjiyeon Waterfall...
Won't there be a lot of people from Jeju Island there?
Isn't it too far?
Look at that sign.
- Where? - Over there.
It's behind that tree.
Hey, it doesn't mean that the waterfall is near here.
The sign is just to say...
it's in that direction.
It might be 50km away.
I'm sorry, but we're a team.
- She just didn't make sense. - Listen to...
your team members.
I'll find someone.
- Hello, sir. - Ask him.
(Polite)
- Are you from Jeju Island? - Yes. I live over there.
Are you from here?
Do you have mandarin trees?
(Step 2)
I don't.
What about...
Does any of your relatives...
have mandarin trees?
Your cousins.
(They found someone who is from here and doesn't have mandarin trees.)
(Do his relatives have mandarin trees?)
My in-laws do.
(My relatives do.)
(I see.)
His in-laws...
- His relatives do. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- His in-laws do. - Thank you.
I wish your family happiness.
It's hard.
Their relatives have mandarin trees.
Someone might be allergic to mandarins.
If we find that person, we'll succeed.
That's right.
- If the whole family is allergic... - Exactly.
There's a supermarket.
Does any of your relatives have mandarin trees?
Yes.
- My aunt does. - Your aunt.
Do you have mandarin trees?
Why? I do.
- We're asking around. - I hope...
your trees will grow well.
Thank you.
(Culture shock)
- Here. - Please.
Hello.
Are you from Jeju Island?
- Are you from Jeju Island? - Yes.
Do you have mandarin trees?
- No. - Okay.
- The final question. - The final question.
Does any of your relatives have mandarin trees?
- Your cousins. - Your cousins.
(What's his answer?)
No.
We found him.
(They finally found someone.)
- We found him. - Thank you.
We found him.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Happy New Year.
Let's buy one of these.
- Mission complete. - Okay.
(They found someone after 30 minutes.)
Thank you.
(They finally completed the mission.)
- We succeeded. - There were no more people to ask.
- The mandarin tree. - Okay.
We can complete the whole mission soon.
- We'll be done soon. - We have only one more.
Let's go there.
(They only have to visit the shape of Korean Peninsula.)
- We have to win a Chance Card. - That's right.
It's important.
Who wants to draw it?
Chance Cards...
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
(Se Chan wins.)
Okay.
- Se Chan... - Pick one.
He's unlucky.
- Just avoid the dud. - Just avoid the dud.
(What does his reaction mean?)
Oh, my.
(Dud)
How can this be possible?
(He picked the dud.)
(We won't say anything.)
How can this be possible?
I have nothing to say.
(Why did you win rock-paper-scissors?)
- I think... - I mean...
we're meant to sleep in the ice rink.
- How can I pick the dud? - Come here.
Come here.
I can't believe it.
The other team...
completed the meat noodle mission.
We have to go there then.
And...
- the other team... - No way.
Picked an Exchange Card.
Black cattle and Camellia Hill got switched again.
(Then it means...)
They must want to eliminate the name tag.
It seems so.
Then we could try to do that too.
That's right.
We can win that way.
- That's right. - Let's avoid it.
- Exchange Card or... - We'll go there...
- and there. - There.
We'll go to the oldest building in Jeju Island.
Let's go.
We'll pick a Chance Card here and...
- They want to remove the name tag. - It's hard.
(How will their strategy pay off?)
Everyone seems to be enjoying.
It looks so tasty.
Four bowls will be served.
I can't wait to taste it.
It's coming.
(Steaming)
- It's... - It's steaming.
(Thick pork broth)
- It's... - Thank you.
(It's been boiled for many hours.)
The broth looks so thick.
It looks so tasty.
(60 years of history)
It looks amazing.
- Let's try. - It looks so...
It has 60 years of history.
(Slurping)
(Enjoying)
- How does it taste? - Good.
(Slurping)
It tastes good.
(She slurps the noodles.)
It tastes very good.
(The tasty noodles...)
(fill her mouth.)
It was worth our efforts.
(The family is finally at peace.)
The broth is so thick.
(It tastes even better with meat and kimchi.)
It tastes great.
Things are going so well.
(Our team is the best.)
My heart is warming up.
Really.
Let's go.
- We have to... - We have to eliminate...
We have to eliminate the name tag.
I think we'll succeed.
We have to go where they're going.
Call Kwang Soo and ask.
(He's calling Kwang Soo.)
- Hello? - Kwang Soo.
- Yes? - Why did you call me?
Where are you going?
- Where are we going? - Yes.
We haven't decided yet. We just finished eating.
Where are you going?
- We should meet... - Yes.
And settle things. Let's meet.
Where are you going?
Where are you going, Kwang Soo?
We're going to see the shape of Korean Peninsula.
(In fact, they're going to the oldest building in Jeju Island.)
Not the oldest building in Jeju Island?
(Sharp)
- What? - The oldest building.
(Well...)
Are you sure you're not going there?
We have to meet once anyway.
Let's meet.
Well... Let's meet.
(Let's meet.)
- The way he speaks. - The way you speak.
- I think we'll meet anyway. - Okay.
Let's do this.
Let's meet at the oldest building in Jeju Island.
Bring the oldest guy, Seok Jin.
Hey. Who is your target?
(Suddenly)
What?
- What are you doing? - Who is your target?
All of you would be easy targets for us.
But we picked the easiest opponent.
(They picked the easiest opponent.)
- It must be you. - Is it me?
(Surprised)
- Is it me? - It must be you.
Yes, it's you.
- Bingo. - Is it really me?
Bingo.
Let's meet first.
(Let's meet.)
Let's do this.
- Okay. - Gosh.
Gosh, I wonder who their target is.
Gosh, I'm so curious.
It's about time one of them betrayed the others.
If someone tells us who their target is...
Should we promise that we'll spare that person?
(They approach Seok Jin.)
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
Just listen.
(He turns off the speaker.)
- Okay. - Seok Jin.
- Isn't it on speaker? - I turned it off.
- Just listen. - Okay.
- If you... - Yes?
Text me who your target is,
we'll spare you...
if we win.
It's a promise.
Okay? Text me the name.
Okay.
Why would you say that while we're shooting?
You could have texted me.
What did he say?
- What? - What did he say?
He said they weren't shooting. He talked about something else.
Seok Jin. What are you doing right now?
Gosh.
I'm getting irritated.
- What's with you? - He talked about something else.
- Let's ignore Seok Jin from now on. - Gosh.
Gosh.
I don't know anymore.
Just know that you're already at a disadvantage.
- Have you heard from Seok Jin yet? - No.
I think he's thinking.
Why isn't he telling us?
We're here.
(They arrive at the oldest building in Jeju Island.)
This must be the oldest...
This building has been designated as treasure number 322.
Built in 1448, it's the oldest building in Jeju Island.
- We're here. - It's called Gwandeogjeong.
Gwandeogjeong.
It's right in the center of the city,
so people often use this place as a meeting point.
- A meeting point. - The next mission is called...
Meet a Celebrity.
(Meet a Celebrity)
Meet a celebrity who's in Jeju Island right now...
- and take a picture with them. - What?
My friend, Jin Ho, is here right now.
Kim Jin Ho from SG Wannabe.
- Really? - He's in Jeju Island right now.
- He's here? - Yes.
- I was going to... - Tell him to come.
I don't know if he's nearby. I wonder where he is.
- But if we... - Lee Jung.
But if we rip a name tag, we're done.
(We just need to rip a name tag.)
Right?
(Both teams will get a bingo.)
(Eliminating the name tag of the target)
We have to eliminate their name tag.
- We have to. There's no other way. - I agree.
- We have to guess again. - Of course.
What? It's me.
(What? It's me.)
It's me. He said it's me.
- What? - He texted me. It's me.
- Really? - Yes.
He said it's So Min. Look.
Look.
- "I'll pick you." - Really?
"It's So Min." That's what it said.
Really? It's really you?
(What is Seok Jin's strategy?)
I'm going to send it.
- Seok Jin, I... - I'm going to say it's So Min.
(Watch me.)
(They're going to pretend like they're attacking So Min.)
Let's run at So Min.
Jong Kook will try to block us, right?
Let's rip his name tag then.
- He said it's me. - We can't trust him though.
Pretend like it's me...
and protect me.
I'm sorry, but this is my team.
- I'll make the calls. - Fine.
(Stay out of this.)
- Why are you doing this? - Each person...
Each person should... Hold on.
- Don't you know this is my team? - Hold on.
All of a sudden?
- It's not all of a sudden. - Look.
- This is my team. - Look at this guy.
I formed the foundation for the team and all of a sudden?
I get this team is named after you,
but you should be satisfied with the team name.
- Let's get away. - Hey.
If we have one less person, it's a disadvantage.
That's right.
That's the only way for us to win.
See?
I want my team to win.
Here.
(He did something honorable, and he's full of confidence.)
I'll say it's Jong Kook then.
It's weird if we don't mention his name.
That means you're only trying to save yourself.
How?
How does it matter?
- How does that matter? - Let's all say it's Jong Kook.
I'm trying to trick them.
- It's odd if we don't mention him. - Se Chan.
We're in this situation, so let's all send it.
You're a weasel.
You consider me that way? Fine.
(Look who's accusing me.)
- So Min. - Yes.
What if I get blown away?
- Hey. - What is wrong with her?
(Why does she want to get punished?)
Why are you trying this?
Jong Kook held the club.
- You have layers on, so it's okay. - Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Does that hurt?
(You have layers on so it's okay.)
- Does that hurt? - Jong Kook.
- Hey, don't do that. - Jae Seok.
- Try it. - Lie down.
- Lie down. - Let me try.
Lie down for me.
You hit his lower back.
- I'm sorry. - You hit his lower back.
(She hits the wrong spot.)
You hit his lower back.
(This is ridiculous.)
- I'm sorry. - You hit his lower back.
Was that your butt?
Why is your butt so low?
(His butt is too low.)
You hit my tailbone.
(Team Senior Yu is having fun.)
- We're here. - I said it's So Min.
We're here. Is this the oldest building?
(It's finally time to go head-to-head.)
- Let's go. - Aren't they here already?
- Are they here? - There.
- They're here. - No.
No, they're not here.
- Isn't that Jae Seok? - No, it's not him.
I thought it was here.
- They're here. - It's them.
- It won't work. - We have to block it.
They're here.
- What do we do? - Hey.
Jong Kook, go to the back. Hold on.
(Team Junior Jee walks into the tiger's den.)
(Jong Kook hides in the back to make a surprise attack.)
Hide.
(So Min hides as well because she might be the target.)
- They're here. - They're inside.
(They're determined.)
(Everybody will think we'll lose.)
(They're plotting an ending that's against everyone's expectation.)
(Let's turn this around.)
- Where are they? - Let's go, Se Chan.
Where are you going?
- Jong Kook. - Hey.
Jong Kook.
Come back.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan betray them first.)
Jong Kook.
- Get away. - Run away, Jong Kook.
(Get away, Jong Kook.)
Why should he run away?
- Be careful, Jong Kook. - Wait.
It's Jong Kook.
Run away, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, they set you up.
- What are they doing? - I don't know.
(They're confused.)
Get away, Jong Kook.
(Why are they telling me to get away?)
(Where did he go?)
- What's going on? - What's all this?
Come here, Seok Jin.
(Team Senior Yu is confused about this strategy.)
- You're going to rip my name tag. - What?
- You're going to rip mine. - Why would we rip yours?
It's not you. Why would we rip yours?
Who is it?
It's not me.
(Jong Kook is watching everything.)
- I swear I'm not lying. - Seok Jin.
(What? They made eye contacts.)
It's Jong Kook.
(They find Jong Kook alone and unite again.)
(Why are they coming here?)
He's here.
(Eliminate his name tag.)
Hey, rip his name tag.
Rip his name tag.
Seok Jin.
(This is strange.)
Is it me?
- Jong Kook. - It might be you.
- No, hold on to So Min. - It's not her.
(Team Senior Yu is confused by the other team's strategy.)
- Hold on. Kwang Soo. - There he is.
(This is our chance.)
Jong Kook.
(They get a head start thanks to the unplanned strategy.)
(Team Junior Jee surrounds the opponents with great force.)
- Jong Kook. - No, hold on to So Min.
- It's not me? - It's not you.
- Hold on. - Be careful.
(Team Senior Yu protects So Min, )
(and Jong Kook is all alone.)
(If they all attack Jong Kook, they can turn this around.)
Let's run at So Min. Jong Kook will try to block us, right?
Let's rip his name tag then.
- I'll do it. - Wait.
I'll do it.
(Seok Jin steps up as the team leader.)
- You're going to rip mine. - Why would we rip yours?
(If he's not the target, he won't be eliminated.)
(Seok Jin steps up and distracts them.)
Don't come.
- Go. Let's go. - Don't come.
(Seok Jin gets in between Jong Kook and Haha.)
(This is their chance.)
- Don't come. - We told you.
Go. Let's go.
(Will Seok Jin's plan succeed?)
(What?)
(Ripping)
- Go. Let's go. - Don't come.
(What?)
(What's going on?)
(What happened?)
What just happened?
(Why did Seok Jin get eliminated?)
(That means...)
(This morning, they were choosing the target.)
(Team Senior Yu's target was Seok Jin.)
This is interesting.
(It was me?)
What were you doing?
- That's not how you do this. - Why did you do that?
This is so not fun. What was that?
This isn't fun at all.
- What are you doing? - What did you do?
What just happened?
Why did he come?
- Why did you do that? - Why did you do that for?
Did you overestimate yourself? Why did you do that?
I thought it wasn't me.
- I didn't think it was me at all. - Why not?
I just thought it wasn't me.
Why did he hit the empty can last week?
Why do you keep ruining the plan?
Then,
should we give you a chance?
(They lost, but this is not the end.)
(They can switch one team member.)
The winning team can save one person from the losing team.
- Then, should we give you a chance? - Yes.
Let's go to the torturing equipment.
(Dashing)
(This is their last chance to avoid sleeping at the ice rink.)
We'll time you from now on.
(I'll twist his legs.)
- You can take turns. - I'll do one person at a time.
- You can take turns. - It's one person at a time.
We knew this would happen,
so we prepared for this.
- Let's time this. - Okay.
It's how long you can resist, right?
- Cross your legs. - Okay.
- Like this? I'll resist. - Yes.
You can't ask for a time out.
Get set, go.
(Groaning)
(He's done.)
It's over.
(He feels the electricity.)
Two seconds.
That was two seconds. That was long.
I'm in first place right now.
This will take forever,
so let's go to a different one.
Should we move on?
Let's see how many hits they can take.
In a row? Okay.
(He clenches his teeth.)
I'm ready.
- Would you be okay? - Yes.
Here's one.
(Shaking)
- He lasted. - He did.
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm okay.
- Here's two. - He's resisting.
- Yes. - Here's two.
(It's painful.)
Wait. What's wrong? Why are you sitting?
Jae Seok.
- What? - You're so funny.
Who are you to hit him?
- Jae Seok, - I mean...
we're not going to use this to make our decision.
(We're not going to use this to make our decision.)
- What? - Let's edit this out.
- Okay. - You're going to edit this out?
That was too violent.
We need to decide who will survive and who will sleep at the ice rink.
Let's go to the hotel and finish off.
He must be disappointed.
Hold on.
We'll do it too.
We won't pick the person who doesn't scream.
- I'm serious. - Let's decide when we get there.
Let's decide when we get there. Don't do it here.
It's you for sure.
(You're sleeping outside.)
- It's you. - Fine.
- We'll sleep together. - Let's do this.
Let's do this. This is good.
- We'll sleep together. - Good.
- Okay. - You'll sleep outside,
and you'll freeze.
- Good plan. - Good.
(Darkness falls in the outdoor ice rink.)
This is entirely outdoors.
(There are three small tents on the ice rink.)
It's so small.
This is just the ground.
(There are sleeping bags for a comfortable rest.)
I heard it's getting cold tonight.
It's really cold.
Team Senior Yu is the winner,
so you'll be sleeping in luxurious suite rooms.
(The winners will get a comfortable rest...)
(in the elegant, luxurious suite rooms.)
(Welcome, Team Senior Yu.)
The losing team...
- will sleep on the ice rink. - We're sleeping here?
This isn't good.
You can't sleep here.
(How are you supposed to sleep here?)
Before that, there will be a change of fates...
between the flowery road and the icy road.
This is important.
(One person from each team will switch where they sleep.)
This isn't possible.
First of all, the winning team...
will choose one person they'd like to save...
from the losing team.
(Which lucky person will sleep in the suite room?)
It's Team Junior Jee,
so Seok Jin has to be there.
We want Seok Jin to stay here,
and Kwang Soo has no reason to be here.
- I agree. - We gave you a chance.
(We saw you in Gwandeogjeong Pavilion.)
- We gave you a chance and you lied. - You lied.
You two can choose A, B, or C.
- I want the middle. - I want B.
I want the middle.
Get out. Both of you, get out.
- It's either one of them. - Let's see who sleeps in C.
- Feeling! Intuition! Cross! - Feeling! Intuition! Cross!
We'll be in A and B. Come to C.
I was going to...
exclude Ji Hyo.
(She almost didn't get saved, )
(but what made Jae Seok change his mind?)
(On their way to Gwandeogjeong Pavilion)
(Their destination was being kept a secret to avoid the other team.)
(Jong Kook guessed right.)
Are you going to the oldest building in Jeju Island?
(How did Jong Kook guess right?)
Ji Hyo said...
they're going to the oldest building.
(Come to the oldest building.)
(Ji Hyo was the one who provided the information.)
Come here, Ji Hyo.
You can sleep in the hotel.
(She betrayed her team, so she gets to sleep in the suite room.)
- Let's decide. - Yes.
We have to decide.
- Everybody, let's do this. - What?
The five of you can go to your hotel rooms,
- and you'll get a call. - They'll call us? That's cruel.
Should we go then?
(The person to get the call will come back down.)
- You know, I... - This is cruel.
Jae Seok is getting a call.
You got a call from Kwang Soo.
- Hello? - Come to C.
(The decision has been made.)
- We haven't started. - What?
- It's not yet? - We haven't started yet.
- We didn't start. - It's not yet.
(They know who it is even before they start.)
This is nerve-wracking.
This is nerve-wracking. I really don't want to go.
(Please don't let it be me.)
Think about it. We won,
so why does it feel like we lost?
What? Why am I getting a call?
(She gets a call from Seok Jin.)
Yes, Seok Jin.
Magnet human.
(He's worried.)
(Pausing)
I'm sorry for calling you.
Can you give the phone to Jong Kook?
Hold on.
Me?
(That's right. Jong Kook was rude to Seok Jin.)
Yes. Hello?
(Yes. Hello?)
Yes.
Jong Kook.
- Yes. - I haven't heard that tone.
Can you keep being polite?
- Seok Jin. - Yes.
I only did that because this is TV.
- Jong Kook. - Yes, Kwang Soo.
(He's so warm.)
We'll talk casually to you then.
Sure, go ahead.
(This is a different situation.)
You can talk casually.
Jong Kook.
- You have to be polite. - You can't do that.
Really? I'm sorry.
That was Se Chan.
- I'm sorry. - He called you by your name.
I'm sorry.
(I'm speechless.)
Was that Se Chan?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
(You have to respect him still.)
We took a vote, and it was a unanimous decision.
(They got a unanimous vote for the person sleeping on the rink?)
He got voted.
(Somebody got voted.)
Should I pass it on?
(If it's not Jong Kook, is it 1 of the other 3?)
Yes.
Okay.
I'll pass it on. Hold on.
(He's uneasy.)
What?
(Is it really me?)
Go.
- Hold on. - Sorry.
(Do I get to stay?)
I got a special order.
Where?
- Really? - I got a special order.
I'm sorry.
- Really? - Yes.
- What? Am I safe? - Really?
Jae Seok.
Follow me.
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook, please say it's not me.)
- What? - Jong Kook.
(Come here, So Min.)
What?
Jong Kook.
(Haha is left alone, and he's dazed.)
Hold on.
- I'll take this. - He's getting a call.
He's getting a call, so let's leave.
I didn't know I'd be saved.
Hello?
- Haha. - Hello?
Where are you?
I got left alone.
Haha, why aren't you coming down?
We'll make it clear. In 1, 2, 3.
- Haha. - Haha.
(We'll make it clear. In 1, 2, 3.)
(Haha)
You must be having fun. You're laughing.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Haha. - Haha.
(They discussed about allocating tent C.)
(Haha caused the discord in their team.)
(They all agree to invite Haha who caused the discord.)
Let's get going.
(No, the ice rink.)
This feels like a dream. It feels like I'm dreaming.
(His 30 minutes in the suite room is up.)
Haha, who do you want to sleep with?
My gosh.
This is too cozy.
Is this the outside?
- Hurry up. Go in. - Haha.
- It's shaking in the wind. - How do we...
This is insane.
Everybody, good night.
We'll go now.
I'm so mad!
- Everybody, - In the morning...
have a sweet dream.
Sleep tight.
Good night.
(They stayed warm together and fell asleep.)