(Last week)
(Kang Han Na and Seol In A return.)
(Joy and Irene come back stronger.)
(The couple battle starts as soon as they arrive.)
(It's a fierce battle where they steal each other's partners.)
(There hasn't been a matchmaking game like this before.)
(Some were happy...)
(and some were wounded.)
(Everyone found a pair.)
(Current partner status)
With familiar partners,
you'll play Finding Thief Race.
"Finding Thief"?
(Familiar Partner, Finding Thief Race)
There's a thief hiding.
Among you, there are two male...
and two female thieves.
Two each?
Gosh, Han Na. Look at her act.
(She's a thief.)
What do you mean?
She got startled.
- All of a sudden. - That's strange.
That's very strange.
It's Finding Thief Race.
- A thief? - Wait a minute.
(What was that awkward tone?)
- She acted surprised. - No!
She's suspicious.
She's very suspicious.
Something smells fishy.
There's no reason why Irene would choose me.
- We need to make deductions. - Gosh, Han Na.
We haven't chosen the thieves yet.
(The director tells them the truth.)
(The thieves haven't been picked?)
Oh, not yet?
- See! - We haven't picked them.
I'm so sorry, Irene.
(They get suspicious so easily.)
You should've told us sooner!
(Amidst all this, he is calm.)
- Really? We're choosing now? - What?
I'm so sorry.
Seok Jin!
Enough with the acting from the start!
Seok Jin acts like he's the one.
- What are you doing? - Seriously.
- Don't act guilty. - Honestly,
I love it when you doubt me.
- Stop it. - I love it.
Continue doing that for me.
(This 50-year-old yearns for attention.)
He wants us to do that.
(Whether you're a thief or not,)
(there's only one way to win.)
If your final partner is a thief, you get penalized.
If your final partner is a citizen, you receive a reward.
Okay.
From now,
let's randomly pick the thieves.
- Randomly? - I see.
I should observe their expressions.
We need to look at their faces.
Among the 6 cards, there are 4 citizen cards...
and two thief cards.
- I can't be a thief. - 4 citizens and 2 thieves.
- I'll go first. - It's so stressful to be a thief.
I'll take the last one.
- Me too. - Goodness.
I don't like...
- being a thief. - Right?
- You're anxious all day. - It's stressful.
It's such a hassle to be a thief.
(But deep down, he has his fingers crossed.)
(Sadly, Seok Jin is a citizen.)
(I see... I'm a thief...)
(The men finish choosing.)
I checked mine.
Irene, good luck.
(It's the ladies' turn.)
Observe your partners.
(I'm watching you.)
(Everyone finishes choosing.)
I saw mine.
Citizens, we can do it.
Okay, thief.
I got you, thief.
(They already start doubting.)
He's definitely a thief.
- He's a thief. - What do you mean?
- What do you mean? - Are you a citizen then?
He is a citizen.
How do you know already?
We're both citizens.
If you turn out to be a thief, I'll be greatly disappointed.
Trust me.
- It's so easy to seduce Kwang Soo. - Right.
- I won't hurt you anymore. - She's doing it again.
Change into your uniforms,
- and let's move. - Okay.
(After they finish choosing,)
(all the thieves and citizens change their uniforms.)
Jae Seok, you're all-blue.
(He's wearing a blue top and blue pants.)
Isn't that a bit too much?
It's the chroma key effect.
- I didn't plan this. - Chroma key.
If it's funny, that'll suffice.
That's great.
(He's a funny chroma key.)
(He does look funny.)
(While they're eyeing one another in doubt,)
(an important rule is thrown at them.)
To the winning couple,
we'll disclose their partners' identities.
(This is for every mission.)
- Goodness. - Really?
That's huge.
- Wow. - Okay.
For the losing couple,
we will disclose to all of you...
whether one of them is a thief or not.
(If one of them is a thief, everybody will know.)
(That means, the thieves will try their best not to come last place.)
Seok Jin, stop acting.
What are you doing?
- Why are you stretching? - What's wrong with you?
- I need to run. - Stretching won't help.
All right, we will play a game beforehand with a quite useful...
- chance card at stake. - A game?
This chance card...
will make the winning team gain victory by default.
- By default? - For the losing team,
it will act as a revival card.
(The card can be used for victory or revival.)
The game...
is called Say Three Syllables.
Ji Hyo's good at this.
I'll say the first syllable,
and a couple will finish it.
If it's a celebrity name and I say,
- Kim. - Jong.
- Kook. - Right.
I see.
- Do you get it? - Yes.
Should we run first?
(Joy asks a question.)
Where to?
We have to run first, right?
- No. - Ji Hyo...
I told you. Joy is weird.
- She doesn't know. - She's lost.
Joy, wake up.
(Apart from her identity, she's just weird.)
If I say, "Hong", what should you say?
If you win three consecutive times, you pass.
Three consecutive times?
First category is...
celebrities.
Nam.
Ji.
Hyun.
Noh.
- Sa. - Yeon.
Do.
- Ji. - Won.
(They get all three correct.)
- Okay! - Yes!
Okay!
They said, "Do Ji Won".
How did they think of that?
That was good.
(It was a hard one.)
(They reacted very quickly.)
- That was... - Next category is...
- food. - Food?
- Hold on. - It's not bad.
Here we go. Gam.
- Ja. - Tang.
- Kim. - So.
Bap.
(Haha gives up.)
- What's kimsobap? - What?
(Is there such a food name?)
- What is that? - What was that?
You could have said kimchi jjim.
You fail.
- What's kimso? - I don't know.
- Kimsobap? - This is hard.
Try to explain yourself.
She's a thief.
I was thinking of another dish.
This category is animals.
- Wa. - Pi.
What?
(It's Jong Kook and In A's turn.)
(Jong Kook gets it wrong.)
- Wait. - Wapiti.
- I mean... - Hold on.
- You pointed at me. - You fail.
- You failed. - He pointed at me.
- This is his fault. - He pointed at me.
Amidst all this, So Min...
- told me an interesting story. - What?
- What? - What did she say?
"What if four-letter Chinese idioms come out?"
We're only doing three syllables.
(During the game)
(What if four-letter Chinese idioms come out?)
(We are only doing three syllables.)
(She can't differentiate between 3 and 4.)
Who goes first?
You do.
For this team, it doesn't matter who goes first.
The category is objects.
We'll start. Flower.
- Bou. - Quet.
- Instant. - Noodles.
Extract.
(Instant noodles extract?)
(Do you get the extract by squeezing the noodles?)
- Instant noodles? - What was that?
What is instant noodles extract?
- What is that? - Sorry.
Did we fail?
Of course.
The category is food.
Delicious.
- Side. - Dishes.
(Delicious side dishes?)
Delicious side dishes?
(Was that what they meant?)
- Delicious side dishes? - You should've said...
yam extract.
Why do you like extracts so much?
- Stop it. - Yam extracts are great.
- Extracts are food. - You like them too much.
- Yam extract. - Last round.
- Who's turn is it? - Who wants to go?
- She does. - Me.
- What's the category? - I imagined it for a second.
I imagined if you two...
were a couple.
Really? How did it look?
You cannot be lazy at all.
Right.
I'm serious.
- He's right. - You shouldn't sleep.
- I have to be diligent. - Yes.
- You have to take care of her. - I see.
- Take care of her? - Yes.
- I'm like a slave. - Yes.
A slave?
Let's start.
The category is animals.
Please give easy ones.
- Okay. - All right.
We'll start. Tal.
- Pi. - Dae.
- Ba. - By.
- Calf. - E.
- Le. - Phant.
- Those were too easy. - No.
Those were way too easy.
(Hold on.)
- Weren't they too easy? - Come on.
That's too much.
Even my kid could do it.
- What was that? - I'll be more diligent!
- You gave us the hard ones. - I've succeeded!
(Kwang Soo's team and Se Chan's team rise to the finals.)
- This is the finals. - Okay.
This category...
is not limited. It just needs to make sense.
- I'll start. - Kwang Soo.
- Hold on. - There's an insect.
Why?
(Gibbering)
(She swings her arms about.)
- What was that? - I wasn't pranking her.
- I'm serious. - What have you done?
I'm serious.
- What have you done? - There was an insect.
I'm not lying.
- Let me see. - Are you all right, Joy?
I'm sorry. There was an earwig.
- Joy. - Yes?
You were very natural.
(Put your arms in the air and swing them left and right)
Joy's reaction is worth remembering.
(If it comes out as an emoticon, it's worth buying.)
- We'll really start. - Okay.
Joy will go first.
- We'll start. - You'll go first.
Joy's turn. Kang.
- San. - Ae.
Jun.
- Ji. - Hyun.
S.
- Ky. - Lark.
(Correct)
(They get 3 consecutive questions right.)
- If we win again, it'll be a tie. - Right.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Who'll go first? You have to decide.
Irene.
- You go first. - Right.
- Should I? - No, I'll go first.
Sure, go ahead.
(The answer already exists.)
I bet she picked him because she doesn't feel pressured.
I can see it in her facial expression.
She never once looked at you.
That's not true.
It's unusual for team members to stand like this.
- She's cold-hearted. - They usually face each other.
I'll just take a peek at her.
(I can approach her first.)
(This slave...)
(has his eyes locked on her.)
(That was romantic.)
That was a romantic response.
That's great.
We'll start.
- All right. - Irene first.
Irene will go first. You.
- Little. - Punk.
(You little punk?)
(Incorrect)
(The lovely vibe and the chance card have both disappeared.)
- "You little punk" works. - Goodness.
From how I see it,
Irene didn't care about what Se Chan would say.
It's all up to him to make it work.
Goodness.
You're quite high-maintenance.
The chance card will be given...
- to Kwang Soo's team. - Yes!
(The chance card will be useful.)
We did it.
(We're off to a good start.)
We're off to a good start.
This first mission offers a chance to check the identity of thieves...
as well as a chance to change partners.
It is the Barefoot Tango.
(Finding Thief Race first mission, The Barefoot Tango)
- What's that? - A barefoot tango?
The woman gets on the man's feet...
in a tango posture and they start walking.
The team that moves the rose from the flour pile...
to the vase with their mouth first wins.
It's going to be an intense race.
However, if the woman's foot touches the ground,
the other teams will punish them with water guns.
(Flour and water guns. How dirty will the game be?)
(Barefoot Tango Tournament Chart)
(Flour roses in the center of the race)
- You can do it! - You're too close.
I'll be ready when you touch the ground.
There will be music playing. The race starts with the whistle.
Okay.
Jae Seok likes dancing.
He's getting ready.
We shouldn't start late, though.
Jae Seok likes dancing.
We'll play the music.
- "Havana"! - It's "Havana".
I love "Havana".
(A melody full of sentiment)
Look at Joy!
(Along with Joy's groove)
(Glazed eyes)
Kwang Soo's expression is too much.
Hey, So Min.
They look good together!
(Wriggling)
(What's with Kwang Soo?)
(I can't lose.)
Hey, So Min.
(Wriggle wriggle)
So Min is a bit weird, right?
(There isn't a hint of "Havana" in So Min's dance.)
(Flap flap)
(When will the race start?)
(Whistle blows.)
Let's go!
1, 2. 1, 2.
Wait a minute.
(Awkward)
- How are they so fast? - They're so fast.
1, 2. 1, 2. 1, 2.
We'll spray you if your feet touch the ground.
- Not here! We have to go around. - Okay.
Jae Seok.
Her feet are on the ground.
Get back up, Joy! Get back up!
(Get back up, Joy, get back up!)
Her feet touched the ground!
Let's fire!
Why? Why?
1, 2. 1, 2. 1, 2.
Stick it in, hurry.
She used her hands!
- Joy, you cheated. - You can only use your mouth.
I didn't know!
Use your mouth. Use your mouth!
You have to use your mouth!
I tried so hard!
So Min, you did well.
Go, So Min!
Nice, So Min.
This isn't easy.
What do we do now?
- They won by default. - Nice, So Min.
Water gun sprayers, come here!
We'll begin the second round.
The music will play.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo against Jong Kook and In A)
("I'm so sexy" by Yu Jae Seok and JYP)
(Wriggle wriggle)
Let's go.
(The famous dancer revs up her engine!)
- I'm so sexy! - Sexy!
(I'm so sexy.)
(The dancer shows up.)
(The club gets wilder!)
Nice.
(One more time?)
- Don't do it! - I'm so sexy!
Why did you spray me?
(Failing on both ends)
(Corny dad wave)
(Strangely pitiful)
- Let's go. - Come on.
Let's go.
- 1, 2. - Look at him.
- He's carrying her. - Look.
- He's just carrying her. - Jong Kook is carrying her.
- Hurry and go. - Why is she so heavy?
I said, hurry and go!
Hurry and go!
We don't know who will win yet.
(Mouthful of rose)
Seok Jin, just move forward!
Don't get caught up with useless things!
(We'll get going, then.)
(Jong Kook and In A proceed...)
There's so much flour.
I'm not kidding. She's so heavy.
(Seok Jin blames Ji Hyo 100 times for every step he takes.)
You're saying it's Ji Hyo's fault?
(Meanwhile, this team is about to finish.)
Are you mocking us, In A?
(The rose goes in.)
- Hey. - Okay!
Nice.
(Jong Kook and In A proceed to semifinals.)
- Seok Jin... - She's actually so heavy!
Music, start.
Play music for a couple dance.
Play music for couples to dance.
Let's go, let's go.
("Red Flavor" by Red Velvet)
(Irene dances to "Red Flavor".)
(Se Chan dances towards her.)
It's a couple dance, but Irene dances by herself.
(Irene, look at me.)
(Instead of dance moves, it's a hopeless couple dance.)
Lucky her.
(We can't lose to them!)
(Flailing)
Han Na's dancing. She's dancing!
Look at Kang Han Na.
(Happy)
(Please don't use your good body like that.)
What kind of dance is that?
(The signal starts the race when they were busy dancing.)
(Fumbling)
She's falling.
Don't wear socks. It's easier to do it barefoot.
Take your socks off.
1, 2. 1, 2.
- Bite it. - I can't.
- Hurry up. - I can't.
- Pick it up. - The other side!
My back is going to break.
Come on.
Nice job. Let's go now.
1, 2. 1, 2.
- Han Na, what are you doing? - What are you doing?
- Han Na, what are you doing? - Han Na!
Are you okay?
Nice.
(Se Chan and Irene proceed to semifinals.)
- Okay! - Okay!
(Barefoot Tango Tournament Chart)
(Kwang Soo and Joy have a chance card.)
(They go against Se Chan and Irene.)
I hope the music is good.
You're being picky about the music?
I'm a little excited.
- Do you know why you're excited? - Why?
- It's not because of the music. - Right.
It's all because of Irene.
That's right.
We'll start the music.
(It's our song!)
It's "Peek-A-Boo".
(Wild dance moves)
(Red Velvet magic that turns the field into a stage)
The two guys should leave!
(Awkward couple dancing on the side)
(Decalcomania couple shimmy)
The two guys should leave!
(Enraged middle-aged fan)
(We can't do that.)
(The more jealousy, the more passion.)
(Whistle blows.)
1, 2. 1, 2.
Se Chan, you can do it.
Nice, nice.
Hurry up!
- Your feet might touch. - Kwang Soo!
Joy's feet touched the ground.
- Her feet touched the ground. - No, that is...
(I bit it first.)
(Is he Bigfoot?)
(Kwang Soo follows behind.)
He's catching up.
Smoke is coming out of Kwang Soo.
There's smoke coming out.
How can there be smoke?
(Like Thomas the Tank Engine)
We're almost there.
(Kwang Soo's team arrives first through the power of flour engine.)
(They just need to stick the flower in the vase.)
- Come on. - There you go!
You can do it!
It went in.
(Kwang Soo, who came first to secure a good spot, succeeds.)
It went in! Kwang Soo won.
(Kwang Soo and Joy proceed to finals!)
There must be a thief...
since they're working so hard.
(I did work really hard. Not that I'm a thief.)
He needs some water.
- Open your mouth. - Give us some water.
(Spraying)
(Easy flour rinsing with water scaling)
(Look at him.)
- It's scaling. - There, you're clean now.
You're clean now.
(He's actually clean.)
- Show your gratitude. - Thank you.
We scaled your teeth.
Thank you so much. Thanks.
(Kwang Soo tried hard to win. What is his identity?)
(Semifinals, Jong Kook and In A, Jae Seok and So Min)
(Jong Kook and In A get a head start.)
(Perfect couple freeze)
It went in.
(Jong Kook and In A proceed to finals!)
Nice.
(Tango Finals)
(Jong Kook and In A, Kwang Soo and Joy)
We'll start the finals.
We have to look for the thief here.
There's definitely a thief there.
- Among us? - Yes.
I don't understand why.
- Let's win. - We have to.
(Who will win the amazing benefit?)
("Fire" by BTS)
Kwang Soo, you know this dance, right?
- You know this, right? - You know this!
(He's getting ready.)
(Shoot!)
(I'm the hottest man in this town.)
(Squeaky)
(What... What are those joints?)
(His body crumples like he's on fire.)
(Then his joints get lit on fire!)
How do you know this?
(She's no match for Kwang Soo.)
(The dance battle is more heated than ever for the finals!)
(Maximum expectations)
(Muscular tiger versus attack of the giraffe)
Let's go.
Ready, set, go.
- They're so fast, look. - Wow, they're really fast.
They're so fast.
1, 2. 1, 2.
- They're fast. - Oh, sorry!
No, no, no!
(Long Kwang Soo swoops in again.)
Excuse me! You can't just...
I can't tell who will win.
(Honk honk)
He's starting his engine!
He looks like a white dragon.
(He charges forward.)
No! No.
(With the flour engine, he arrives at the finishing line first.)
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo hit her with his head!
He cheated!
- He hit her! - They won, they won.
(Kwang Soo stuck it in.)
- It's over. Kwang Soo! - Kwang Soo wins!
(Kwang Soo and Joy win The Barefoot Tango mission.)
- Are you okay? - He cheated.
Are you okay?
The couple that placed last in Barefoot Tango...
is Seok Jin and Ji Hyo.
- They must reveal themselves. - I'll announce...
if any one of them is a thief.
One of them must be a thief for Seok Jin's performance.
In Seok Jin and Ji Hyo couple,
(Between the two of them...)
there is a thief.
See?
(One of them is a thief.)
I told you.
(Is one of them a thief?)
Look.
(Seok Jin is a citizen.)
(That means...)
(Ji Hyo is a thief.)
(During the random pick,)
(she picked a thief card.)
(Ji Hyo is 1 of the 2 female thieves.)
It must be Seok Jin.
- I think so. - Aren't you a thief?
(She keeps a poker face.)
(He's very flustered.)
You're a thief, aren't you?
- Are you a thief? - You're a thief.
- Are you a thief? - He's arguing with Ji Hyo.
They're fighting.
- I'm not it. - You are a thief.
- I'm human. - I am. You're a thief.
I'm human.
(Ji Hyo is good at acting.)
He says that he's human.
Are you human, Seok Jin?
- I'm human. - Seriously, Seok Jin?
I'm human.
Are you human? Stop joking.
What do you mean? Thieves are human too.
I'm human. She keeps saying that I'm a thief.
You know who the thief is, right?
- What do you mean? - Okay, I got it.
The winning couple will go to the room of truth.
- Find out each other's identity. - Gosh.
You'll decide whether to switch partners.
Okay.
One of them must be a thief if they switch.
(If they switch, one of them is likely a thief.)
You aren't a thief, right?
- I'm a citizen. - Right.
(They find out their status.)
(They enter the room of truth.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(What is their identity?)
They'll stay as a couple if they're both thieves.
Wouldn't they stay as a couple either way?
They'll stay together for now.
- To fool the citizens? - Yes.
When other couples switch,
one of them will be picked.
This is difficult.
- It's difficult. - It isn't easy.
Here's the identity of your partner.
We'll start with Joy.
(Joy and Kwang Soo find out about each other's identity.)
If they're both thieves and don't switch partners,
- they're smart. - It'll get complicated.
It has more factors to consider than I thought.
We have to see how they look.
Then we'll decide.
- Here they come. - They're coming out.
(Their time is up in the room of truth.)
(They finally come out of the room.)
(Cold)
- They argued. - They argued.
They don't look happy.
Stop acting.
Both of them are acting.
Are they both thieves?
Joy looks upset.
What if they decided to look upset?
Their citizen identity can't be obvious.
They're afraid others will switch with their partner.
(It's time to announce their decision.)
The winning couple made a decision.
Kwang Soo and Joy decided to...
stay as a couple.
(They stay as a couple.)
(Will they stay as a couple?)
It's the case that we talked about.
- Is it possible? - It is.
(Is it more likely that they're both citizens?)
(The first room of truth ends.)
- Gosh. - Gosh, wake up.
You're a thief.
Stop being a thief.
Goodness.
What's wrong with you, thief? You're a thief.
I'm not either.
You're a thief.
(She's interested in the thieves' fight.)
I'm sure that Joy and Kwang Soo are thieves.
Why?
(So Min proposes the idea that Joy and Kwang Soo are thieves.)
I heard Joy say it in passing.
When there weren't cameras, she told Kwang Soo,
"What do we do?"
(So Min makes a report.)
We can be citizens.
- "What do we do?" - We can be...
- I heard her. - That's incredible.
What's incredible?
If they're citizens,
they don't have to come out looking upset.
- What is it? - Someone could see them.
- I'm hungry. - Do you smell the food?
- It's jjajangmyeon. - It's definitely jjajangmyeon.
Yes, it's driving me crazy.
I'm about to go crazy.
- It smells like jjajangmyeon. - Jjajangmyeon and pickled radish.
It's driving me crazy.
(For lunch, warm jjajangmyeon is ready.)
I'm hungry.
(There's also tangsuyuk.)
Next mission is one round each for male and female.
It's a food mission.
It's the total amount of time that the couple finishes eating.
The couple that eats the fastest...
- wins. - Can you eat fast?
Do we have to do that?
The couple to finish last will lose.
- You can't do it? - I can do it.
The first round is A Curious Taste of Black.
(A round for male members, A Curious Taste of Black)
(We like the name.)
(He gets excited.)
(Once you bite)
(He controls his excitement.)
I was just being excited.
You should have fun during your free time.
I'm sorry, but I don't have time to have fun right now.
Jae Seok is busy these days.
I have no time to have fun at home.
- I know that. - At home,
I'm very busy.
- Do you take care of your child? - Yes, I'm busy as a bee.
When my wife calls, I go to her.
When my child calls me, I go to him.
- When the baby cries? - Then I go to her.
You take care of the baby when she cries.
- He's so kind. - You must be busy.
(There's one person who stays silent.)
- I see. - I'm very busy, but...
I envy you.
- Really? - I envy you.
(He's envious of Jae Seok for being busy with his family.)
Jong Kook.
(I want to stop working out alone.)
I seriously told him.
If he wants to, he must make an effort.
That's true.
It's true.
The first round is for men.
(Men's round starts now.)
Female members will have their eyes covered...
and stand behind their partners and feed them jjajangmyeon.
As three teams play, we'll count how long it takes to finish a bowl.
We'll total the time.
- You like noodles. - I love noodles.
You know how much I like noodles, right?
Okay.
I'm not good at it.
- I eat a lot. Don't worry. - Really?
I like eating.
Don't do anything strange just because you're a thief.
Ji Hyo, we need to switch partners.
Give me a big mouthful.
(Teamwork is key.)
Can we mix them first?
It's warm. Look at the steam.
- You're right. - Look at that.
(Oily and steamy)
This is the delicious kind.
The noodles look great.
- Get ready. - Where's your mouth?
- Get ready. - It's here. Wait a minute.
Does it not fit his neck?
(What about this couple?)
(What?)
What's wrong?
(She covers Seok Jin's eyes.)
- Gosh. - You need to cover your eyes.
My eyes?
(It's me who should cover my eyes.)
- You cover your own eyes. - Hey.
Why are you covering mine?
Ji Hyo should cover hers.
- What are you doing? - This thief is so...
- Hey, thief. - What's wrong with you?
- I thought... - When she covered his eyes,
he let her. He didn't budge.
He was looking for his chopsticks.
Goodness. My eyes...
(They're a couple with great teamwork.)
They work so well together.
Why did you cover my eyes?
Practice with the chopsticks.
Men will eat.
Why did you break the chopsticks like this?
(She complains.)
Can you give us another pair?
(He loses 10 points on his slavery skills.)
I've been watching Irene.
She's never satisfied with what Se Chan does.
She keeps complaining under her breath.
(It's hard to keep up with her.)
Get ready.
- Here we go. - Here we go.
- Let's show them. - Here we go.
We're Song Ji Seok Jin.
- Get ready. - Song Ji Seok Jin.
Start.
All right, go.
(They eat a lot as soon as they start.)
Go.
I thought Se Chan was eating by himself.
(They work well together.)
I thought he was cheating.
So Min and Jae Seok work well together.
(When So Min gives him a big bite,)
(Jae Seok takes it all in one go.)
(Song Ji Seok Jin had trouble from the start.)
(She feeds him quickly, but he can't keep up.)
She wants to switch her partner so badly.
Hey, hey.
- Eat. - She doesn't stop moving.
She keeps going.
Irene is very good.
This isn't easy.
Jae Seok's team is the quickest.
- Really? - No way.
- No way. - Seok Jin's team is the dirtiest.
Swallow it without chewing.
Irene has her eyes covered.
She seems kinder than ever before.
(She seems kinder than ever before.)
(She complains less with her eyes covered.)
She's doing well.
(The blindfold makes Irene kind.)
She's very warm.
- Eat. - I think he finished eating.
- He finished eating. - You have some left.
- Jae Seok. - I can't see.
- Hold the bowl. - I can't get the noodles.
That's it.
Se Chan is almost done.
(The two couples spurt at the last minute.)
- We're done. - I think we're done.
Jae Seok finished.
(Jae Seok and So Min clear the mission.)
- Jae Seok. - Good job.
- Jae Seok. - The noodles are all on the table.
He has to finish the food dropped on the table.
(Did we spill a lot?)
(Grabbing)
(She feeds him with her hand.)
Ji Hyo.
(He tastes her hand.)
That's incredible.
Is that necessary?
(Her ambition is impressive.)
- Seriously. - That must be easy.
Ji Hyo, come to my house and feed my children for me.
(He refers to Dream and So Wool.)
- They don't eat. - Eat!
Open your mouth!
Seok Jin is done.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo have completed the mission.)
Seok Jin is like a vacuum cleaner.
Lastly...
Why are you so slow?
Continue!
Se Chan is slower than I expected.
He is. What's wrong?
Are you done?
- Se Chan is done. - He's done.
Poor Seok Jin.
Okay. So Min.
- Jae Seok. - Good work.
Why are you so slow?
It was hard.
(Se Chan says it was hard.)
(He's being suspicious.)
(He confidently said he loves food.)
(In the beginning, he was very fast.)
(But in the end, he finished last.)
- Are you a thief? - No.
(Suspicious)
(Se Chan is suspicious.)
- He must be a thief. - No.
(Did he lose on purpose to stay with his partner?)
Good.
Seriously.
Irene, trust me.
Please put on your blindfolds.
Ready.
Let's do this, Han Na!
The last time I ate jjajangmyeon...
was on a show.
This is the first time since then.
Hold on.
- I can't believe you. - What happened?
She kept wiping my face,
but it's a mole.
(She kept wiping my face, but it's a mole.)
(Irene tried to wipe off a mole.)
She tried to wipe off a mole.
(Irene offered help for the first time.)
(You have some sauce on your face.)
(But in reality...)
Is that a mole?
(She got it wrong.)
I can't believe her. It's a mole.
What's wrong with you?
- I thought it was the sauce. - It's a mole.
Irene at least doesn't make you confused.
- It shows who she likes... - She's straightforward.
and doesn't like.
- In A, here. - Put on your blindfolds.
- Hold the chopsticks. - Ready.
I'm nervous.
- Me too. - Ready.
- Let's show them, Joy. - Let's show them.
- Ready. - Try to pick them up.
It's okay to do that.
Start.
With some sauce, it's easy to eat.
Gosh, look at Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is definitely the fastest.)
Kwang Soo is so fast.
Gosh.
- But he's eating on his own. - He's eating on his own.
This is not okay.
You can't do that.
(He doesn't even need his partner.)
You can't do that. Haha is fast too.
We don't know yet.
- He's so fast. - He's really fast.
(He is like a vacuum cleaner.)
Jong Kook is catching up too.
But...
(He finishes half the bowl in one bite.)
- Jong Kook. - Where is his mouth?
(1st place, 3rd place, 2nd place)
Haha is unexpectedly fast.
- Haha. - High up...
- What's going on? - High up...
It's unbelievable.
Look at Haha.
(Han Na moves her hand like a machine,)
(and Haha slurps down the noodles like a vacuum cleaner.)
- Haha is almost done. - Unbelievable.
It even looks neat.
Haha is almost done.
He's almost done.
(Haha is finishing up the sauce.)
He's done. Finished!
Haha is finished.
Are we finished?
Did we finish first?
He's done.
- Finished! - Haha is finished.
(Their speed and teamwork deserve an applause.)
Did we finish first?
- You were really fast. - Your left hand.
Joy, you can't use your left hand.
Are we done?
(As soon as she hears Haha's team is finished,)
(Joy starts using her left hand.)
(They're desperate to catch up.)
Hey, that's...
Kwang Soo. What are you doing?
(They make you wonder why they're so desperate.)
What are they doing?
Let me chew it first.
Has he eaten anything?
You're done.
- Jong Kook is done. - Jong Kook is done.
Are we done?
(Jong Kook finishes the bowl in a few minutes.)
Jong Kook ate it so neatly.
(Jong Kook's determination deserves respect.)
Why are you so slow?
- Kwang Soo is very slow. - He's not finished yet.
He'll finish last.
- He's done. - You're finished.
(Kwang Soo and Joy finally finish the bowl.)
Joy needs...
I think Haha is in first place.
- Definitely. - He's in first place.
- It's women's round now. - What are they eating?
In the second round, you're going to eat tangsuyuk.
(The female members are going to eat tangsuyuk.)
I love tangsuyuk.
When the female member breaks plastic wrap with her face,
her partner will feed her tangsuyuk. Repeat it five times...
and whistle. The time the female member takes...
will be combined with the time her partner took in the first round.
Okay.
Here we go.
So Min is very good.
Bite off the plastic wrap.
Let's beat Joy.
So Min, just keep going.
Don't miss the funny part.
There was a funny part.
(What funny part?)
Se Chan said, "Let's do this!"
Irene said, "You startled me."
Don't miss it.
(You saw it?)
(A few minutes earlier)
- Let's do this! - You startled me.
(You startled me.)
(It was a funny moment.)
(You saw it?)
Irene...
I don't know anymore.
Just split up. You're making everyone uncomfortable.
- I want to change my partner. - They're a good team.
I love this combination.
Here we go.
Ready.
And...
(They have to break through the plastic wrap to eat.)
(The tangsuyuk mission starts.)
Get in there.
(Joy breaks 1.)
Joy.
Break the next one.
(Okay.)
(Breaking)
(Kwang Soo and Joy have finished 2.)
They're fast.
Get in there. Use your forehead.
Break through.
Keep going. There you go.
(Irene finally breaks 1.)
Eat it.
Good.
So Min, use your forehead.
Use your forehead.
(What is So Min doing?)
So Min.
There you go. Eat now.
- Eat it. - Chew it.
- Hurry up. - So Min.
- You whistle after eating five? - Yes.
Joy, you have a big mouth, but you eat very slowly.
(Joy pauses and chews the food.)
Get in there.
There you go.
Keep going.
Break through!
Break it!
Way to go, Irene!
Keep going!
Break through.
Break it. Okay.
(Irene breaks the 2nd plastic wrap with her whole body.)
Eat it. Chew it.
So Min, come on.
(So Min is battling with the plastic wrap.)
Keep going.
Break it!
So Min, break it!
(Biting)
So Min.
Isn't that Voldemort?
(She looks just like Voldemort.)
(She looks like the worst villain.)
So Min. There you go.
There you go.
(Voldemort has finished 2.)
So Min.
So Min, you're amazing.
So Min is incredible.
(Let me break the plastic wrap now.)
So Min, break it!
Can you eat?
(Joy has finished 3.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Eat the tangsuyuk first.
Eat it.
Keep going.
Irene is competitive. I love it!
Irene, what are you doing?
She has some tangsuyuk in her mouth.
(Irene is challenged by Joy.)
(Breaking)
Okay.
(Irene has finished 3.)
(Joy, take your time.)
Eat it.
(No. I should get moving too.)
(The family battle starts.)
Joy.
I'm sorry.
I can't break it.
Put it down.
- Joy has only 1 left. - Joy has only 1 left.
Joy has finished four.
Get in there!
Good!
(Irene is catching up.)
(But Joy breaks her 5th plastic wrap.)
Joy.
Joy has such a big mouth.
- There you go. - She's good.
- Now you have to eat fast. - It's important.
So Min. Keep going.
You look like a mess right now.
So Min, eat this.
(She has some food left in her mouth.)
Keep going.
(She continues with the food in her mouth.)
So Min. There you go.
You're so good. Why didn't you do better before?
It's okay.
(She spills some juices.)
It's okay to spill some juices.
One more to go.
Keep going!
- You're so good. - Break it. Keep going!
Break it!
Break it, So Min!
(So Min is amazing.)
So Min, come on.
- You're almost there. - You're almost there.
You're almost there.
Isn't that tangsuyuk?
So Min, break it.
Break it.
So Min, keep going.
You're almost there. Break it.
She's the best.
- There you go. - You're almost there.
(She has finally broken 5.)
There you go. So Min.
This will go down in history.
(Your struggle today will go down in history.)
(Congratulations on entering the Comedy Hall of Fame.)
(She has given up her looks for the mission.)
(We support actress and comedian Jeon So Min's endeavors.)
This will go down in history.
(She adds a page to the history of comedy.)
(They applaud her to show their respect.)
- There you go. - Irene is going to whistle.
(Irene is going to try to whistle.)
- Whistle. - Now they have to whistle.
Whistle.
She whistled.
(Irene completes the tangsuyuk mission.)
It's Joy's turn.
Joy.
(Joy completes the tangsuyuk mission.)
So Min.
Whistle.
Isn't she that girl?
The one with Se Chan...
You mean the mixture of me and So Min?
She looks like that mixture.
The mixture of me and So Min.
Where have you been since the opening?
(We missed you.)
So Min, eat.
- So Min. - It's her, isn't it?
(Thank you for having me again.)
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
(She has added a page to the history of funny faces.)
She's whistled.
(Good job, So Min.)
- She's amazing. - So Min.
You finished last, but you were the best.
- It was so funny. - I'm so touched.
(After many funny moments, the game is over.)
Here we go.
- Ji Hyo. - Let's do this.
I have to change my partner.
I have to change my partner. Let's do this.
If you do your best, you'll look pretty.
- It's okay. - Han Na, let's go.
- So Min is weird, - I'm nervous.
- but you're weird too. - No. Hold on.
- What should I do? - You can do this.
Ready.
(Start)
Look at Han Na.
(Both Han Na and In A break 1 right away.)
Way to go!
Look at Han Na.
(She takes a big bite.)
- Han Na's eyes completely changed. - That's good.
- The look in her eyes changed. - She's doing well.
- Go. - Eat it.
She's fast.
She's doing well.
- In A is doing well. - Here you go.
In A is doing well.
Ji Hyo.
(He's impressed by In A and Han Na.)
Wait a minute.
Hurry.
(This is difficult.)
That's good. Here you go.
(She barely manages to break 1.)
Eat slowly.
(The others are so fast.)
Look.
Hurry up.
That's good.
(She struggles.)
Eat slowly.
They're so ambitious.
Go through it.
All you have to do is whistle.
(Han Na takes another wrapped frame.)
That's good.
(This looks familiar.)
- You look so funny. - It's Hwang Bi Hong.
That was hilarious.
(Hwang Bi Hong appears unexpectedly.)
What's going on with Han Na?
That was Hwang Bi Hong.
It's what I wore for Halloween.
- Han Na. - Hurry.
Come on.
We don't have time to laugh.
(She goes through 3 frames.)
- She can't get through it. - In A.
(While Hwang Bi Hong passes,)
In A.
(someone else appears.)
- In A. - In A.
- She got it. - In A.
She got through it.
In A's face startled me.
I thought it was a stranger.
Don't say that.
It's okay.
- Jong Kook, that's worse. - What?
What's wrong, In A?
You look pretty.
- Just do your best. - Her face looked really compressed.
Just do your best.
It's okay as long as you work hard.
Okay, that's good.
(When In A goes through one, Han Na does too.)
- Chew well. - That's good.
All right, that's good.
(The one who whistles first will win.)
She ate five of them.
Time out.
She'll whistle now.
Hurry up.
She did it.
(Han Na clears the mission first.)
- That's impressive. - She didn't take one minute.
Didn't I do well?
She did it. Okay.
(The only person left is...)
You did a good job.
Good job.
In A did well. She works hard.
Goodness.
She's not an ace.
(He's frustrated.)
(She can't argue with him.)
- What's going on? - How can you say that?
Seok Jin.
Why would you hurt her feelings?
- Listen. - She should play...
- She's good at certain things. - She should play her part.
She should be better than that.
She can't be good at everything.
Of course not.
(Whistling)
- Okay. - I did it.
Okay.
(What are the couples' final records?)
We're the winner.
I'll announce the winner first.
- Isn't it Haha and Han Na? - Right.
Right?
They were both quick.
It's worth hoping for.
Hard work will pay off.
The winner is...
(The winning team gets a chance to switch partners.)
Haha and Han Na.
(Haha and Han Na place first.)
I knew it.
They were so fast.
Both of them were fast.
They were outstanding.
He finished jjajangmyeon in 44 seconds.
She took 1 minute 55 seconds to pierce the plastic wrap frames.
Both of them were the fastest.
Did you finish in 44 seconds?
That's incredible.
I'll announce the loser.
The loser is...
(He announces the loser.)
- It's Seok Jin and Ji Hyo. - Why?
What's the point of knowing about them?
Why?
(They're overly relieved.)
(We didn't place last.)
It'd been great if it had been Kwang Soo.
The losing team,
Seok Jin and Ji Hyo.
- One of them is a thief. - I know.
- What's the point? - It's one of them.
- Is that all? - It's one of them.
Is this all?
One of us is a thief.
(It's not me.)
She's a thief.
What's this?
It's pointless.
(Are both of them thieves?)
This couple is...
very relieved.
They were so surprised.
I can't figure out if they're faking it or not.
- I'm curious about that. - Me too.
I'm curious.
They're thieves.
I think they're both citizens.
They're worried about someone taking away the partner.
That's why they control their expression...
and stay suspicious.
(Is Jong Kook's guess correct?)
I'll announce the identity of your partner.
We'll start with Joy.
Joy is a citizen.
(Joy is a citizen indeed.)
Kwang Soo.
He's a citizen.
(Kwang Soo is also a citizen.)
(As Jong Kook guessed, they're both citizens.)
Will you switch partners?
Or stay being a couple?
What should we do? We'll stay.
- We'll stay as a couple. - Will you?
We should be careful.
Let's say that people find out we're both citizens.
If a couple with a thief...
wins,
they'll try to switch partners with us.
We're both citizens.
We have to pretend like we're both thieves.
(Let's pretend to be thieves.)
- They're out. - They argued.
They argued.
They look upset.
Are both of them thieves?
That's why they control expression and stay suspicious.
- I see. - A thief could separate them.
The winning couple.
Haha and Han Na will go to the room of truth.
You'll find out each other's identity...
and decide whether to change partners or not.
If they change partners,
it's likely that they'll switch with them.
(If either Haha or Han Na is a thief...)
This is exciting.
- That's possible. - Right.
That's possible.
- Okay. - Okay.
(What will Haha and Han Na decide?)
(What is their identity?)
Both of them can be thieves, or it's one of them.
- Aren't you a thief? - I am not.
- You're not? - I'm not.
Me neither.
(Seok Jin is completely honest.)
You're a thief.
She's driving me crazy.
My goodness.
Ji Hyo is an actress.
Her acting is classic.
Wait.
(He looks so awkward.)
- Was that a line? - Was it?
Did you just say a line?
"Her acting is classic"?
- Did you write it at home? - "Her acting is classic"?
He did.
- She acts so well. - Goodness.
- They're coming out. - Let's read their faces.
(Haha and Han Na come out.)
(They checked each other's identity.)
(Han Na looks upset.)
(Are they acting, or are they shocked by the result?)
What's your decision?
What happened?
Here's the winning couple's decision.
Haha and Han Na.
(Did they decide to stay as a couple or change partners?)
They'll switch partners with Kwang Soo and Joy.
- See? - One of them is a thief.
(They switch with Kwang Soo and Joy.)
(The citizen couple is separated.)
It's incredible.
This must be a tactic.
One of them is definitely a thief.
It's definite.
I had to change partners.
- Is that so? - I'm serious.
Watch how I behave today and see if I act like a thief.
- Kwang Soo. - I won't.
- Seriously. - You were like a thief.
- It's her. - He was like a thief.
Han Na's acting improved.
- No way. - It's true.
That's why she worked hard.
I knew that Haha was good at pretending.
- I almost got in trouble. - I didn't know he was this good.
It can't be either of you.
(Their suspicion gets worse.)
As you continue suspecting,
let's move to the final round.
(Let's move to the final round.)
Is it already the final round?
(Is it almost over?)
(What if my partner is a thief?)
Is this the last round?
- No. - When can we change partners?
Do we not get another chance?
You have more opportunities...
- than you imagine. - Really? Okay.
- Let's move to the final round. - Okay.
(Current partner status)
(Joy and Han Na switch partners.)
Are you a thief?
Why would I be a thief?
Aren't you a thief?
- Aren't you a thief? - I'm not.
I really am not.
I promise.
- I swear. Yes. - Is it Han Na?
I'm really not a thief.
- Really? - I'm not.
Don't trust Haha. He's not trustworthy.
My goodness.
Here we go.
Here's the last mission and a chance to find out...
your partner's identity and change your partner.
It's Familiar Pirate Roulette Quiz.
- "Familiar Pirate Roulette"? - "Familiar Pirate Roulette"?
What's Familiar Pirate Roulette Quiz?
There's a box on top of each table.
Inside the boxes are...
pirate roulettes of 24 slots, 16 slots,
and 8 slots randomly.
The number of knives given depends on...
the difficulty level of the question.
Is this...
The team to answer correctly...
will pick another team.
They find out if any of them is a thief.
(The winning couple can find out the identity of a couple.)
- Really? - That's amazing.
The winning couple will stick knives into the other couple's roulette.
If the pirate pops out,
it's possible to switch partners with that couple.
It has to pop out, right?
Is the one with eight slots the best?
- I'm a citizen. - Right.
- You aren't a thief, right? - I'm not.
We should get a big one.
Right.
If you answer incorrectly,
the person next to you hits you with a squeaky hammer.
How about we decide...
by playing rock-paper-scissors?
Where you stand is important.
- Why? Everyone found their spot. - Why not?
We should decide with rock-paper-scissors.
Why don't we play Race of Wits?
Let's play Race of Wits.
Don't say anything if it's not Race of Wits.
- Let's play Race of Wits. - What's wrong with him?
Since when did you like that game?
Pardon?
What's its charm?
Here's what I think.
I played Race of Wits with a small number of people.
It's so much more fun to play it with a big group.
(It gets addicting with more people.)
Race of Wits is fun with over 10 people.
Let's play it.
Just pick the winner.
- Decide the winner? - Yes.
- Decide the winner. - That sounds good.
I'll tell you when to start.
I'll say one.
Start.
- 1. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 5.
(In Round 1...)
- Come on. - Jae Seok and Jong Kook are out.
Okay, okay.
I like the tension so much.
Why did I get eliminated first? Goodness.
- Start. - One.
- Two. - For goodness' sake.
Three.
(Watching Race of Wits fills me with satisfaction.)
- How nice. - She is good at this.
- It's time to go. - Four.
(Even an elimination doesn't make anyone grimace.)
All right!
Han Na!
Even those who get eliminated remain happy.
Race of Wits is fun, right?
- It's really fun. - Race of Wits is fun, right?
- It's better than I expected. - It's fun, right?
- It's exciting. - It's fun with a lot of people.
It would be amazing if it becomes an Olympic event.
An Olympic event?
Jae Seok would be in the national team.
- That much is given. - It would be hilarious.
He would practice every day at the athletes' village.
Thank you so much for playing Race of Wits for me.
- It was fun. - I love Race of Wits.
I love Race of Wits.
(Korea will win the event in the Olympics someday.)
I love Race of Wits, but the end is disappointing.
I know.
It ends with rock-paper-scissors.
It makes me go, "Why didn't we play rock-paper-scissors from the start?"
- That's right. - It's not disappointing.
Rock-paper-scissors.
It happens.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha wins.)
Okay!
Hold on. This doesn't mean we won.
- We are deciding where to stand. - Right?
- You get to decide where to stand. - That's right.
- You get to decide where to sit. - You get to decide where to sit.
All right. Here is what we will do.
We must choose the right box. Where we sit is insignificant.
- Let's pick the third one. - The one in the middle?
Yes.
Do you think this one will be nice? Okay.
- We will sit here. - Okay.
To our left will be...
- Se Chan. - Okay.
To our right will be Seok Jin.
- How about the rest? - You can sit anywhere.
- In that case... - Where should we sit?
You can sit over there.
(Jong Kook's seat is...)
Where should we sit? At the end?
Okay.
(Kwang Soo automatically stands up.)
Change my seat.
- Change my seat. - What?
What? What?
All right.
I will sit here.
- The seats have been chosen. - Yes.
Please open the box in front of you and check the pirate roulette.
It's better to have less slots to change your partner, right?
That's right.
In 1, 2, 3.
No way!
- No way. - Okay.
- Okay. - This is incredible.
- Look at ours. - Okay.
The ones with more slots are better.
(Kwang Soo wants to escape from Han Na.)
My goodness.
What is up with your facial expression?
This is good.
(It's a big pirate roulette.)
It's good news!
I can't believe Kwang Soo picked that pirate roulette.
I mean...
(They feel bad for Kwang Soo.)
I can't believe it went to him.
Seriously.
(I hoped for a small one.)
(The number of slots...)
(in each couple's pirate roulette)
Here comes the 1st question with 3 knives.
- 3 knives. - 3 knives.
- That's good. - Haha's pirate will pop out.
This is the first question.
An alcoholic beverage that lessens the effects of a hangover...
is "Hair of the blank" in English.
What goes in the blank?
"Hair of the blank"? Gosh, I saw this somewhere.
Number one, bird.
Number two, horse.
Number three, dog.
Number four, water.
I got it.
(I got it.)
Number one, bird.
- Bird? - It could refer to a woodpecker.
(It seems like he heard something about a woodpecker.)
(He is certain.)
(Is it correct?)
(Incorrect)
Hold on. Hold on, hold on.
- Let's go. - I mean...
- Seok Jin is to my left. - We will go this way.
(Jong Kook gets to hit Kwang Soo.)
Does Haha get to decide?
We won.
Take off your hat.
Hold on. You have white hair.
It's flour!
- I see. - I have flour all over my hair.
I felt bad for a second.
- It's flour. - Okay.
I will hit lightly since this is the first round.
(Thud)
(It makes him bow his head.)
My goodness, that startled me.
- The sound wasn't very loud. - I thought it would burst.
You should get his neck back up.
- That was incredible. - Here.
(The squeaky hammer is intact, but his neck is stuck.)
- Okay. - It could have been disastrous.
- Okay. - I got it.
(Now is my chance.)
Hair of the dog.
- Number 3, dog. - Number 3.
All right!
(It's a colloquial expression that means "Like cures like".)
- There you go. - I didn't think it was the answer.
Come on out and ask about a couple of your choice.
- Which couple? - Haha's.
- Haha's? - Yes.
Okay. Okay.
Haha and Joy.
(Is there a thief in Haha and Joy couple?)
In Haha and Joy couple,
(What is Haha's identity?)
there is...
There is...
In Haha and Joy couple,
(What is Haha's identity?)
there is...
- No thief. - Okay, okay.
Okay.
(Joy is a citizen,)
(so that means Haha is a citizen as well.)
- Okay, okay. - Okay.
They now know which couple has a thief.
- Now... - Haha and Joy are safe.
- Okay. - Let's insert our swords there.
We will insert our swords in Haha and Joy's pirate roulette.
(These citizens have the smallest pirate roulette.)
In case the pirate pops out,
they will need to pick the safest couple.
If you want to switch a partner...
We keep our partners if it doesn't pop out, right?
All right.
(The pirate doesn't pop out after the first sword.)
It would be so easy for the pirate to pop out.
- Right? - You have one more sword to go.
(Not knowing who is a thief, Joy is nervous.)
All right.
- It didn't pop out. - My goodness.
It didn't pop out.
We don't know if there is a thief in Jae Seok and So Min couple.
- We don't know. - We don't know.
Then why did you insert the swords in a smallest pirate roulette?
Why didn't you pick a big one?
Maybe they asked a question and found out...
- that couple doesn't have a thief. - I see.
You are smart.
For goodness' sake.
(Does that mean Han Na is a thief?)
There is a big chance Han Na is a thief.
- What are you talking about? - There is a big chance.
Hold on.
Here comes the second question.
A caldera lake is a crater lake that forms...
in a volcanic crater...
and has a diameter of 3km or longer.
- That's right. - What does "Caldera" mean...
in Spanish?
Caldera.
Number one, cup.
Number two, cauldron.
- Cauldron? - Number three, basket.
Number, plate.
I got it!
Number two, cauldron.
What?
- It's incorrect. - Number two, cauldron?
(Does "Caldera" mean "Cauldron" in Spanish?)
It's incorrect. It can't be "Cauldron".
(Correct)
Is it correct?
("Caldera" means "Cauldron" in Spanish.)
- He is good these days. - That was incredible.
Joy, please ask about us.
- Kwang Soo. - Joy.
Ask about us and you'll find out about your partner.
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
If we want to work this to our advantage,
there is no need to check Seok Jin and Ji Hyo couple.
In that case...
(How about Jae Seok and So Min couple?)
Gosh, is it Jae Seok?
(Did they pick our pirate roulette because there is a thief?)
I can't read Irene's face!
What is going on? What is she thinking?
It's hard to figure her out.
(They pass over Se Chan and Irene couple.)
Hold on.
(Which couple has two citizens?)
What are you thinking?
Let's ask about Jong Kook's couple.
Jong Kook's couple.
With whom was Joy in the beginning?
She was with Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo?
In Jong Kook and In A couple,
(Is there a thief...)
there is...
(in Jong Kook and In A couple?)
A thief.
(There is a thief!)
Really?
(How is there a thief in Jong Kook and In A couple?)
(You can't trust anyone in the world.)
You can insert three swords in a pirate roulette of your choice.
Which couple's pirate roulette will you choose?
This is driving me crazy.
(Staring)
- Kwang Soo. - Haha.
- Insert the swords in ours. - How about this one?
- Look at Kwang Soo. - I am begging you.
Insert the swords into ours. We have a big pirate roulette.
- It won't pop out. - It's too big.
Do you really think it will pop out?
The chance is 1 out of 23.
What have I done wrong?
- Let's go with theirs. - Okay.
(They pick the safest one.)
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
Please, please.
It's the best one. It's the safest one.
If the pirate pops out, we switch partners.
That's right.
(I really hope the pirate pops out so that I can get a new partner.)
(Please pop out.)
It didn't pop out.
My goodness.
(The second sword doesn't move the pirate either.)
It won't pop out.
(22 slots and 1 sword remain.)
(Joy, I believe in you.)
(I want to be reunited with you.)
I bet it will pop out.
Gosh, it didn't pop out.
Kwang Soo wanted it to pop out.
Seriously.
- Kwang Soo, you are safe with me. - He wants a different partner.
The circumstances tell me you are a thief!
(There is no doubt about it.)
For goodness' sake.
(Is Han Na a thief?)
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
The next question comes with four knives.
- Okay. - They will make a pirate pop out...
of a small one.
It's bound to happen.
Come on!
Among the examples,
which one isn't a pure Korean word?
Which one isn't a pure Korean word?
Number one, you.
Number two, wife.
Number three, honey.
Number four, darling.
I got it!
Okay.
Number one, you.
- Number one, you. - It's correct.
(Is "You" not a pure Korean word?)
(It's correct.)
("You" uses Chinese characters.)
Yes!
- Does "You" use Chinese characters? - Yes.
It uses Chinese characters...
- for "Suitable" and "Body". - I didn't know.
Hold on. Han Na has no intention...
to get a question right.
Shouldn't you take a measure?
- That's ridiculous. - She doesn't do anything.
"I see. Honey."
"Wife."
(She simply repeats after the examples.)
(She turns on the parrot mode.)
(Honey)
(Darling)
(She has zero interest in the question.)
(For goodness' sake.)
She simply talks to herself.
It's fascinating.
"Honey" is like an exclamation.
Honey!
(Does she not answer the questions because she is a thief?)
We should ask.
That's right.
In Haha and Joy couple,
- is there a thief? - Is there a thief?
There is no thief.
I told you.
(It's time to insert the swords.)
- Whose roulette will it be? - We will choose...
the one with the highest chance,
- Haha and Joy's pirate roulette. - It's the best bet.
The pirate will pop out for sure.
If it doesn't, I must choose their roulette next.
We will insert the swords. Please focus.
I will be really surprised if it doesn't pop out.
I hope it pops out.
(It's Seok Jin's chance to lose Ji Hyo, a thief.)
(The first sword)
It didn't pop out.
Could it be that...
(Please pop out...)
(so that I can escape from Ji Hyo, a thief.)
It didn't pop out.
Maybe it won't pop out.
(The second sword doesn't do anything either.)
- This is unbelievable. - Hey!
- If it doesn't pop out... - If it doesn't pop out...
It needs to pop out. It has to pop out.
This is unbelievable.
How many swords do you have left? 2? 4?
(In any case, Ji Hyo will be a citizen's partner...)
(since both Seok Jin and Haha are citizens.)
(The pirate pops out.)
- All right. - This is bad.
- This is bad. - You did it.
I need a different partner.
I really need a different partner.
Either Haha...
or Joy...
is with a thief no matter what.
Perhaps both of them are thieves.
Joy.
You are a thief, right?
(Seok Jin is obsessed with attention.)
I am a citizen.
You are lying.
(He confesses he is a citizen in the most suspicious way.)
I know what you are because I asked.
Are you a citizen?
- Really? - Really.
(Haha gets fooled by Ji Hyo's acting skills.)
Now,
it's better to find a couple with two citizens.
- That's right. - That's right.
Then you can switch with that couple.
(In that case...)
What?
You can put yourself at ease!
I am so scared and stressed out.
Why would you be stressed out?
Why do you think I am calm?
- Why wouldn't you be calm? - I mean...
(Kwang Soo is determined to get a different partner.)
I can't believe you.
This question also comes...
- with 4 swords. - 4 swords.
A person has 12 pairs of ribs.
What's the name of the 10th ribs?
I know this one!
Number one, true ribs.
- That sounds delicious. - Number two,
floating ribs.
Number three, false ribs.
Number four, young ribs.
- I got it! - I got it!
(They yell out at the same time.)
Se Chan was faster.
Please give me a chance.
- Se Chan was faster. - Please.
They yelled out at the same time.
- Rock-paper-scissors? - Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors and Kwang Soo wins.)
- Okay! - You know,
- Han Na didn't move an inch. - Come on out.
We need to answer the question.
Han Na is disinterested.
She likes things as they are.
- Which answer do you have in mind? - What's the answer?
Number three, false ribs.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
Number four, young ribs.
Number three... No.
Number three.
What is wrong with you?
(My pick was number three.)
- I think... - What is wrong with you?
- Those are the 10th ribs. - There are other citizens.
There are other citizens too!
(Why are you doing this to me?)
There are citizens other than me!
Han Na is good.
- I mean... - Listen.
- I want to be with you. - Why?
You don't say a word to me. So why?
It's not like you ask me a question.
- Kwang Soo. - My goodness.
(It wakes him up.)
In the end,
- good days will come. - That's right.
I got it!
- She said it first. - In A.
Number three, gasm ribs?
I got it!
The answer is false ribs!
He needs to get hit.
Jae Seok, you need to hit Jong Kook.
- Why? - Will Jae Seok hit me?
(Do I get to hit Jong Kook?)
- Stay where you are. - Why?
- I was on my way to hit you. - I like meeting people halfway.
(The hitter is more nervous.)
- Oh, is that so? - Okay.
Running Man will continue to air.
(He makes it clear.)
Go ahead and hit me.
Would you sit down?
Why? I like to get hit standing up.
(He refuses to sit down.)
Since he doesn't want to sit down, you can stand on a chair.
- Okay. - Fine.
(Seok Jin gets him a chair.)
- Stand on a chair. Okay. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Is this okay? - It's good.
(Smacking)
Okay.
(Jong Kook is annoyed.)
(He explodes with anger.)
Don't be angry.
- Don't be angry. - Okay.
(Jae Seok hit a sleeping tiger.)
Shout out, "I got it."
I got it!
- I got it! - I got it!
Number three, false ribs.
F, A, L, S, E.
Ribs. Number three.
- Yes! - We had the correct answer.
My goodness.
Which couple should we ask about?
Kwang Soo, why don't we ask...
about Jong Kook's couple?
Let's ask about Jae Seok's couple.
But So Min is...
You are having a long discussion with Han Na.
There is a couple I want to ask about,
but she is insistent.
Let Han Na pick the question.
I will let you pick the question.
I will let you insert the swords as you please.
- Okay. - Pick a couple you are sure about.
In Jong Kook and In A couple, is there a thief?
In Jong Kook and In A couple,
there is a thief.
Really?
(The unexpected answer throws them off.)
- What is it? - What is it?
What happened?
It could have been disastrous.
(Thank goodness.)
- What? - I thought they were citizens.
Don't talk to me.
(She sticks out her tongue.)
What?
Hold on.
She stuck out her tongue at me.
Why?
- Why? - When did she do that?
He told me not to talk to him.
(That's why she stuck out her tongue.)
- I communicated with my tongue. - That's right.
Han Na is right.
I understand her.
- She stuck out her tongue. - Then...
Insert the swords where you want.
Make the choices...
and pave your own path.
(I will let you go.)
I still don't think you should change your partner.
(She is still a bit obsessive.)
(What does she want me to do?)
How frustrating.
(He must be confused.)
I think you should go with a big pirate roulette.
You must think I am an utter fool.
It's not like that.
It would be better for your future...
to avoid changing your partner.
Seok Jin and Joy.
Why did you pick us?
- Kwang Soo. - Why did you pick us?
What did you ask?
It's just that I know Joy is a citizen.
He knows Joy is a citizen.
(Kwang Soo makes a wise decision to be reunited with Joy.)
It won't be an easy task since you have four swords.
(There are 8 slots and 4 swords.)
(50 percent is a good chance.)
Hurry up and do it.
(I must become a couple with Joy once more.)
- I am confident. - It won't pop out.
It doesn't pop out in this kind of a situation.
I know.
- That's what makes him unlucky. - Come on.
Joy is desperate, too.
(Pop out.)
It will pop out.
I am sure it will pop out.
(The second sword is a failure.)
- You inserted it. - It doesn't pop out...
in a situation like this one.
If it doesn't pop out, it will be like a festival.
Seriously. I will dance right away.
I will throw Kwang Soo in the air to celebrate.
(The third sword is a failure.)
Didn't you say you are confident?
Kwang Soo must be nervous.
Get ready to throw Kwang Soo in the air.
Get ready. Get ready.
- Get ready. - Look at Han Na.
(She is ready to throw him in the air.)
Han Na, get ready.
- Okay. - I am ready.
- Get ready. - Kwang Soo, I am ready.
Let's throw Kwang Soo in the air.
This is the last sword.
It will be amazing.
(5 slots and 1 sword remain.)
No.
(Will Kwang Soo get thrown in the air?)
(Will the pirate pop out?)
(The pirate remains the same.)
(The couples remain the same.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(It's a festival for everyone but Kwang Soo.)
All right.
That was great.
- That was great. - All right.
Cheer up. This is good for your future.
(Kwang Soo lost a 50-percent chance.)
Get up now. Don't be like this.
It's so interesting. How could he fail?
- You can win five knives. - Let's do this.
You can win five knives.
(You can win 5 knives by solving this question.)
Let's do this.
(We have to get it right.)
- It's a short-answer question. - A short-answer question?
Okay. It might actually be better.
Here we go.
What does this newly-coined word mean?
I know many new words.
Se Chan and Haha are good at these things.
(We know many new words.)
Let's do this. Let's get it.
"Jamanchu".
(Jamanchu)
What?
(What does the newly-coined word, "jamanchu", mean?)
(I've never heard it before.)
"Jamanchu".
Let me answer!
(So Min seems confident. Will she get it right?)
"Confident but ugly man".
(Confident but ugly man)
Come here.
(So Min comes up with a meaning based on the people around her.)
(When you say the wrong answer, you get hit with a hammer.)
- Jamanchu? - Jamanchu?
- I think I've heard it somewhere. - Jamanchu.
Let me answer!
(Will Jong Kook say the correct answer?)
"A memory that only you cherish"?
Memory?
(It sounds so old.)
Is it correct?
No?
- Hold on. - Hit me.
(When you say the wrong answer, you get hit.)
Hit me.
- Hit me right now. - What are you doing?
(Jae Seok steps backwards.)
- What are you doing? - Let's get it over with.
- Get me a stool. - What stool?
Get me a stool.
(Here you go.)
Gosh. Get me a stool.
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok work well together.)
- Gosh. - Why do you never trust me?
- Thank you. - No problem.
- I thought you'd like this angle. - Look to the front.
(Fine. Hit me once.)
(Twice)
- Hold on. - I'm sorry.
(Why did you hit me twice?)
- You hit me twice. - Hold on.
(I didn't mean to.)
- Why did you hit me twice? - I was going to hit you once.
- Exactly. - I'm sorry.
- Let go of me. - I was so annoyed.
Let go of me.
- I was so annoyed. - Stay still.
(Jong Kook gets back at Jae Seok.)
(After hitting Jong Kook lightly twice,)
(Jae Seok gets hit hard once.)
Let me answer!
It's too hard.
It's really hard.
Let me give you a hint.
It is related to dating.
Also, people who have always been single often say this.
Jamanchu.
People who have always been single?
(People who have always been single often say this.)
- People who have been single... - Jamanchu.
When was your last relationship?
(You must understand singles well.)
- Do you have any idea? - Why do you suddenly...
You're so cruel.
Do I have any idea?
You...
Let me answer!
(It's related to dating.)
(Does he remember it now?)
(What will this dating expert say?)
I think you say it when you order more food.
- When you order more food? - When you order more food?
When you order more food?
- When you order more food? - "Jjajangmyeon..."
"10 dollars' worth of jjajangmyeon, please."
"Jjajangmyeon and dumplings, please."
(That must be it.)
"Jjajangmyeon and dumplings, please." Isn't it correct?
(Do they date at Chinese restaurants these days?)
"Jjajangmyeon and dumplings, please."
It's taking too long.
As it's a bit hard,
- we'll give you a crucial hint. - Okay.
- It's very crucial. - Good.
It'd be the opposite of a blind date.
(It's a crucial hint.)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(We're sure this time!)
Isn't it "casual relationship preferred"?
Oh, my.
(Jong Kook sounds confident. Is it correct?)
- "Casual relationship preferred". - "Casual relationship preferred".
- It must be correct. - It must be correct.
(Jong Kook and In A's answer is correct.)
- Right? - The opposite of a blind date...
That's right.
"Casual relationship preferred". That makes sense.
It was correct.
That's why I asked you.
This is why you still don't have a girlfriend.
Hey.
(It's what everyone has wanted to point out.)
Did you hear what she said?
"When was your last relationship?"
She asked me if I knew the answer.
Because it was about singles.
(Stop preferring casual relationships now.)
- Those two? - Jae Seok and So Min.
Okay.
(Jong Kook and In A choose Jae Seok and So Min.)
- Ask them. - Okay.
(Jae Seok gulps.)
We want to know about Jae Seok's team.
(Are Jae Seok and So Min both citizens?)
(Or is either of them a thief?)
There is one or more thieves...
in Jae Seok and So Min's team.
(There is one or more thieves.)
Too bad. Hold on.
(There is one or more thieves?)
(It's unexpected.)
Hold on. Let me think.
(They start to think hard.)
(Which team should we switch partners with?)
Strategically, we have to switch with citizens.
A team where both are citizens.
Exactly. Definitely.
(Regardless of your own identities,)
(it's safe to choose Seok Jin and Joy because they're citizens.)
- Okay. - Okay.
We choose...
Seok Jin and Joy.
(Jong Kook and In A choose Seok Jin and Joy.)
Do we look that easy?
Why?
The pirate will definitely pop out this time.
- It will. - It will.
Three knives are already in.
Okay.
- It will pop out. - We have to...
switch partners.
There you go.
- One. - It'll definitely pop out.
- It will pop out. - Two.
If it doesn't, that'd be strange.
In A.
It hasn't popped out yet.
(It's not popping out.)
(Despite the high chance, it still hasn't popped out.)
I can't believe it.
Why isn't it popping out?
There you go.
It has popped out.
Switch partners.
(Seok Jin and In A become partners.)
Gosh.
(Jong Kook and Joy become partners.)
Okay.
(Jae Seok and So Min win 7 knives.)
How did you know?
I knew the answer.
Let's ask about Jong Kook's team.
Jong Kook?
Jong Kook and Joy.
There is one or more thieves...
in Jong Kook and Joy's team.
(There is one or more thieves.)
We were right.
(There is a thief in Jong Kook and Joy's team?)
Gosh, I'm so surprised.
I'm so surprised.
Gosh.
(As Joy is a citizen, it must mean...)
(Jong Kook is the first male thief.)
(After deciding partners, thieves were decided.)
I'm in trouble.
(I'm a thief?)
I'm so surprised.
Really?
Han Na or In A...
(Which team should we choose?)
But we know Han Na's identity.
Then...
- Irene and Se Chan... - It might be...
It might be better.
Irene and Se Chan.
We choose Irene and Se Chan.
(They switch partners with Se Chan and Irene.)
- Okay. - Every team is dangerous.
- Every team is dangerous. - It gave me goosebumps.
We're so surprised.
- We can't tell you who it is. - It's so unexpected.
Which team are you choosing?
- You guys. - Us?
Yes.
We want to be safe.
I'm so surprised.
(They have 7 knives, and there are 16 slots.)
Gosh.
They have seven knives.
We have seven knives.
The chance is high then.
(It's almost a 50-percent chance. It has to pop out.)
- I'm so surprised. - We're doomed.
(They succeed after 4 tries.)
- It has popped out. - It has popped out.
- So we're changing partners. - It's okay, right?
- Are we switching partners? - Yes.
(They seem a little suspicious too.)
Me and Irene...
Are you switching partners?
(Jong Kook asked about Jae Seok and So Min's identities.)
I'm starting to see it.
It's driving me crazy.
Gosh.
(They don't know each other's identity.)
I was so surprised.
(They feel unsure.)
What happened?
You're a thief, right?
Tell me.
I can't tell you until you tell me.
- Are you a thief? - No.
But Jong Kook is.
Really?
That's right.
Here's the last question.
- You can win seven knives. - Okay.
Seven.
(You can win 7 knives by solving this difficult question.)
It's an English question.
- English? - Gosh.
(We're allergic to English.)
Please.
(I feel confident.)
Which word should go in the blank?
You are the "blank" of my eye.
Okay. Let me answer.
- There are options. - There are?
He should get hit, though.
(Jong Kook is wrong.)
- What? - He should.
I mean...
Come here.
(Fine. Hit me.)
- Hit me. - Hold on.
(It's happened before.)
Hold on.
Give me a second.
- Hit me. - Hey.
Hit me.
There's a stool.
- I made a mistake last time. - Okay.
- I'll hit you just once this time. - Okay.
- I got too worked up earlier. - Okay.
(Jae Seok jumps before hitting.)
Is jumping allowed?
Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Okay. I'll see you later.)
Let me answer.
Number four, "tear".
(Kwang Soo always says whatever word he knows.)
Come here.
Apparently, jumping is allowed.
But I have nothing to do with Jae Seok.
Jumping is allowed.
- I mean... - They say jumping is allowed.
I didn't do anything wrong.
They say jumping is allowed.
It's allowed.
- Jumping is allowed. - I didn't...
- I didn't do anything wrong. - Don't worry.
I have to jump anyway because you're too tall.
(Jumping)
(Let's jump together.)
Hold on.
You said jumping is allowed.
- You said jumping is allowed. - But you can't.
- Why not? - You can't jump.
"Why not?"
- You can't. - Why can't I jump?
Sit down.
1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook punishes Kwang Soo for cheating.)
(Kwang Soo's neck is pressed down.)
Okay.
(His neck is straightened.)
(They never leave his neck alone.)
Thank you.
Number one, "apple".
Number two, "peach".
Number three, "pear".
Number four, "melon".
Number...
- I know. - I know.
I know.
Number four, "melon".
(Wrong)
- I know. - I know.
- I raised my arm first. - I know!
(Among the tiger moths, Kwang Soo is the most passionate.)
(Determined)
I know. I know.
I know.
(He clenches his teeth.)
I said, I know.
I raised my hand first.
Let me. Let me.
- Let me. - Okay.
Number one, "apple".
(He must get this right...)
(in order to run away from Han Na.)
(Will his answer be able to save him?)
Yes!
(I got it right!)
(Goodbye, Han Na.)
This time, you can choose the couple.
I'll stick it...
- wherever I want. - Why are you suddenly...
- talking to me? - Then...
Why are you doing this after being so quiet?
I mean...
(What is her identity?)
Han Na.
You can ask the question.
- And you'll stick the sword? - Yes.
Okay.
(Kwang Soo will ask, and Han Na will stick the sword in.)
(A couple has Kwang Soo's attention.)
(He is curious about Se Chan's team.)
Se Chan and So Min.
(If neither one of them is a thief,)
(he plans to switch teams with one of them.)
In Se Chan's team, there is...
(Is there a thief?)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Is either Se Chan or So Min a thief?)
(It's time to stick the swords in.)
If Han Na sticks the swords in but it doesn't work,
Han Na and Kwang Soo will...
(By the way)
Whom do you think I'll stab?
(She is scary.)
- Hold on. - Whom will it be?
(I will follow what the barrel man wants.)
Hold on, hold on. Why would you stick it in there?
(He is flustered.)
(She sticks it in Haha and Ji Hyo's team where there is a thief.)
- She did it. - It's all done.
- That's it. - It's over.
Why would you put it in there?
Great.
- Why? - It needs to pop out.
Kwang Soo! Hurry! You need to stop her.
It popped out!
I asked about Se Chan and So Min, so why would you do this?
Is Haha stupid? Why is he happy when Han Na is a thief?
Han Na is a thief.
(What is this situation?)
This is awesome.
Maybe they're not it.
- What? - They're not the thieves.
(The two must not be thieves.)
- It's not them? - That was the last game, right?
- Are you the thief? - No, I'm not.
(Why do I feel duped?)
- Why did you stand still? - No, that's not it.
- That's not it. - Why did you?
(He had to stop her.)
(Han Na shakes hands with Haha.)
Good job.
It's what I wanted.
- Good job. - Okay.
Good job.
(Was this all planned out?)
(After the 2nd round, their identities were revealed.)
(Both of them were citizens.)
(If the thieves knew about them, they would be targeted.)
(They decided to switch teams in order to be safe.)
(They planned to switch with Kwang Soo and Joy...)
(who were highly likely to be citizens.)
I'll also make it seem like you're a thief.
All right. And then...
- Let's act when we get out. - All right.
(This couple had schemed a big picture.)
(Everything worked out the way they planned it.)
(If she's also a citizen, who is the other thief?)
We have finished all the games.
I will now tell you the results.
- We'll start with Joy. - All right.
(They'll find out her identity.)
Turn around.
1, 2, 3.
She was a citizen.
(Yes, I succeeded.)
- Kim Jong Kook. - I did it.
- You're a thief. - He must be.
(If he's a thief, he wins.)
(Exclaiming)
(Why, deities, have you forsaken me by giving me a thief?)
It was all for you.
(I'm sorry, Joy.)
- You were a thief? - You were?
Joy will be penalized.
Jong Kook will receive a reward.
Next couple, please.
We'll check Haha and Han Na.
I'm curious about Han Na.
We thought Han Na was a thief.
She is.
- Citizen. - Citizen.
- He wasn't a thief. - Han Na's a thief.
- Then it's Han Na? - It's Han Na.
(We're both citizens. We duped you.)
(Through their fearless switching of teams and scheming, they've won.)
(While these two are celebrating,)
(Kwang Soo is lost for words.)
Why did you do it?
(Does that mean I voluntarily abandoned a citizen?)
Wait.
Han Na is very smart.
No, that's not it. I didn't have plans...
to switch because I thought Kwang Soo was a citizen.
- No, that's not it. - I switched grudgingly.
I thought you were a thief.
Kwang Soo will be penalized.
Ji Hyo will receive a reward.
Next couple.
Is it us?
I think Se Chan is a thief.
(One of them is a thief.)
Are you a thief? Be honest with me.
No, I'm not. Irene, take a good look.
(While slaving for her, no one knew their identities.)
Look.
(Se Chan went to So Min at the end. What is his identity?)
- He's a citizen. - I was telling the truth.
(He's a citizen.)
(So Min is also a citizen, and they both receive rewards.)
(If Se Chan is a citizen,)
(that means Jae Seok is a thief.)
Goodness.
- Jae Seok is a thief. - No way.
It's him.
We'll rip both of theirs at once.
One of them is a thief.
(Jae Seok's fate is in Irene's hands.)
I can't believe this.
- Turn around, please. - Okay.
(If Irene is a thief, Jae Seok gets penalized.)
I'm really curious about yours.
I have to watch this as a viewer myself.
(Everyone's identities will be revealed at this moment.)
All right. One.
(Between In A and Irene, who is the thief?)
Two.
Three.
(Irene is a citizen.)
- Jae Seok! - I'm sorry.
Irene, I'm sorry.
- Irene. - Three.
(In A was a thief.)
You!
This is shocking.
- You trusted me. - Irene.
(This is a hair-raising twist.)
I'm sorry.
- Irene. - Who got it right?
Jae Seok.
You fooled me perfectly.
(Final Results)
Here is the penalty.
- I'm curious. - I heard it's intense.
It's whipped cream.
They prepared a lot of it.
Goodness.
(Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Irene, and Joy will be penalized.)
There are four of you.
But only two?
But only two canons.
Okay!
(Yes, I have one last chance!)
I can do it.
(Two of them can go free.)
- Irene. - So...
- here is your last chance. - Okay!
- It's the barrel man. - Okay!
(They will play the Pirate Roulette.)
If he pops up, you'll get penalized.
(You'll be chosen immediately.)
- All right. - Go first.
(They start with Irene.)
If it pops up, you get the penalty.
(Will Irene's first attempt be a safe one?)
(She's safe.)
You lose if it pops up, right?
- Okay. - Let's do one-by-one.
- Joy's next. - Right.
Pop out.
(Will she be safe just like Irene was?)
(Flying)
(The barrel man says hi.)
(Collapsing)
(Joy is chosen for the penalty.)
Joy...
(They're halfway there.)
- Joy! - Yes! Yes!
(Only 1 more spot remains.)
Joy, who made the barrel man pop out,
and another person of her pick...
- will be penalized. - Okay.
(I don't need to say it.)
And another person of her pick...
(Wait. Is that me?)
Don't you need to count down?
(There's no need. I choose you.)
- Goodness. - You have to say 1, 2, 3.
Joy and Kwang Soo will be the ones getting the penalty.
(They were once separated due to betrayal...)
(but are beautifully reunited once again.)
- All right. - Smile.
(Teasing)
I'm feeling great today.
(The schemers always have the last laugh.)
Are you ready?
- One... - Here we go.
Two...
Three.
(From the start until the end, they are meant to be.)
(They do say couples look alike.)
Goodness.
(It looks like Groot...)
(and his girlfriend.)
Goodness.
Joy, you look pretty.
- You look great. - You look great too, Joy.
Who are they?
Joy, take a photo.
Yes, do that.
1, 2, 3.
(It was nice to team up, but I hope we never meet again.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(They are headed somewhere.)
(Some people are searching for something.)
(After that thing was touched, everything started.)
It was here a while ago.
(Objects keep disappearing.)
(Some of the ladies are suspicious.)
(Ever since they appeared, things became strange.)
(They are not the cute ladies we once knew.)
(They strive to reveal the girls' secret.)
(What strange secret did they bring?)
(Big Nosed Seok Jin)
("Everyone Has a Secret")