Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hello. - Gloves? It's not that even cold.
- Seok Jin, this is fashion. - What fashion?
- Are you that cold, Jae Seok? - I can't believe you.
This is fashion.
Hey, it's really sunny out today.
Who is that over there? Is he a beggar?
- My goodness, that's too much. - What's up with your pants?
- Haha wasn't that bad in the past. - Exactly.
- There was an article once. - What did it say?
(After that article, his outfits have been too much.)
- It was 1 year or 2 years ago. - It was with G-Dragon.
He and G-Dragon were named for the fashion article.
I'm the only one who can match his style.
- He said he was going to sue you. - Listen.
(Stop talking nonsense, Haha.)
No, that's not true. This is what G-Dragon told me one day.
"Haha, where did you buy this?"
Because it was revolting?
- It was. "Where did you get that?" - Revolting?
- What is that? What is it? - What is it?
Are you learning how to be a DJ?
- You posted that on your account. - What is that?
I went to visit one of my friends who is a DJ.
- I tried it, and it was so fun. - And?
I'm learning it as a hobby.
At first, I thought that he finally bought his hearing aid.
(At first, I thought that he finally bought his hearing aid.)
- He had something on his ears. - Hearing aids aren't that big.
(Seok Jin's hearing aid is big to match his big nose.)
- A hearing aid. - I thought...
Hey, no hearing aid can be that big.
- He was getting his hearing tested. - He wouldn't hear things well.
All right. Since it's the kimchi-making season,
- you must find its best partner. - Kimchi?
It's the Kimchi Special. Today, you'll do a race called...
Who Is Kimchi's Partner?
What do you mean by kimchi's partner?
- It's pork belly. - Are we getting kimchi?
You're right. Like kimchi and tofu.
- Right. It could be tofu. - Right.
- You'll form teams first. - There is.
- What's going on now? - What is that?
- Gosh, there's rice. - Rice.
- Sweet potatoes go well with that. - There are sweet potatoes.
- No, it's ramyeon! - I see.
Kimchi and ramyeon make the perfect pair.
Jae Seok will choose ramyeon.
- Sweet potatoes are steaming! - Gosh, those are hot!
- Goodness, the sweet potatoes. - Sweet potatoes look appetizing.
- They got tasty ones too. - This looks really good.
- Kimchi is great with suyuk too. - Goodness.
- It looks so delicious. - Ramyeon...
- Rice is great with kimchi. - With freshly made kimchi.
You'll pick a dish that you believe it to be the best partner.
Each dish can have up to two members.
(Taking the seat)
Seok Jin.
(Will Seok Jin and So Min choose the sweet potatoes?)
- Seok Jin. - You should move then.
- Choose something else. - I will...
I'll go with ramyeon. Ramyeon and kimchi are the best.
- It's hot. - You need kimchi for ramyeon.
End of discussion.
- This is hard to decide. - It's hot.
I'll go with suyuk.
(He chooses the suyuk which is high in protein.)
- I'll choose suyuk. - Look at this. It's steaming.
- Kimchi and suyuk are the best. - Take a seat.
- Hold on. - What?
- It has to be rice, you know. - Haha, come here.
Rice and freshly made kimchi...
- are the best pairing. - Everything goes well with kimchi.
But I kind of want to get some ramyeon too. This is crazy.
- I'll go with ramyeon. - I choose ramyeon.
- Hold on. - Why?
No one wants to join Seok Jin.
- I choose ramyeon. - I choose ramyeon.
- I'll go with sweet potatoes then. - Sweet potatoes?
Sweet potatoes.
Why are you sitting here?
I have to choose this. I ought to choose sweet potatoes.
I choose sweet potatoes.
(Ramyeon: Jae Seok, Se Chan, Sweet Potato: Seok Jin, Kwang Soo)
(Suyuk: Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Rice: Haha, So Min)
Stand with your teams.
We have invited your soulmates who will join you on the journey...
of searching the best partner for kimchi.
- "Soulmates". - "Soulmates".
"Soulmates"? Who are they?
(Wait, this song is...)
TWICE!
(No way. They are really here?)
Really?
- All of them? It's the whole group! - All of them are here.
- The whole group is here! - Unbelievable!
(TWICE in its entirety)
(They're a girl group that specializes in breaking records.)
(The world-class girl group, the million-dollar baby, TWICE)
(The most sought-after idol group has joined Running Man.)
(He can't stop smiling.)
TWICE! TWICE!
(They are cute and adorable soulmates of Running Man.)
(Hey, guys. We're here!)
We love you, TWICE!
(We didn't know what you'd like, but we still prepared this.)
(Choose 1 of the 2)
(Say yes no matter what!)
(When TWICE does their part,)
(the members respond.)
(TWICE is our partner!)
(They're overly excited to see TWICE.)
TWICE!
- Hello. - You're so pretty.
- I'm such a fan. - Hello.
Hey, hello. Goodness.
Can you introduce yourselves to the viewers first?
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3.
- 1 in a million. Hello. - 1 in a million. Hello.
- We're TWICE. - TWICE!
TWICE, TWICE, TWICE, TWICE!
- Our brother group, family group, - That's right.
- and sister group. - Sister group.
- They're like our family. - You can use any nicknames.
By the way, it's quite chilly today.
- It's so cold. - Today...
Jeongyeon, it's really cold today.
- I'm freezing. - Right, right.
All right. First of all, we have TWICE with us.
TWICE introduced themselves just now.
(Why is he giving his coat to her?)
- What? - You look cold.
(Throwing away)
Gosh, he's trying to get a nice story out of this.
(There he goes again, trying to get a close-up.)
- He's coming back again. - What are you doing?
Hey, you should wear this, at least.
(Talking to Nayeon)
What are you doing? They seem cold. They look cold.
(His coat can't come near TWICE.)
"You should wear this, at least."
- What are you doing? - They're freezing.
TWICE has to be on TV in their own outfits!
- They seemed especially cold. - What are you talking about?
- You're unbelievable. - They're healthier than you.
One wrong move can destroy you.
Fine.
- Jeongyeon is cold. - Listen up.
TWICE visited us on the orientation trip in the beginning of the year.
- That's right. It was so short. - Right.
You did the acrostic poems and danced for us.
- It was brief, but sensational. - Yes, indeed.
- That's when she did her cute act. - Exactly.
(Kim)
(I want to eat kimchi fried rice.)
(I want to eat it with Jong Kook.)
(Goo goo gaa gaa)
(That was the final blow.)
(She dominated the field with her cute act.)
- It was crazy. - It created quite a sensation.
That's right. Did you prepare another acrostic poem today?
- Yes, Nayeon prepared one. - Yes.
- Does Nayeon have one? - Yes, she has one.
- Yes, she has one. - Momo has one too.
- Momo. - Momo, do you want to go first?
- Okay. - What's the keyword?
- I'll do one with Jee Seok Jin. - Gosh, with Jee Seok Jin?
(She'll do an acrostic poem with Jee Seok Jin?)
- Seok Jin! There's your close-up. - Gosh.
(This is what you've been after.)
Hurry. Hurry up and go. This is the close-up you love.
- Get a shot with her. - Hey. They can get it from here.
My goodness.
This is Seok Jin's close-up.
All right. Do the acrostic poem.
I didn't think she'd choose Seok Jin.
The fact that she chose Seok Jin itself is unusual.
We'll start with Jee.
- "Jee". - She's so nice.
Jee Seok Jin.
- "Jee Seok Jin". - "Jee Seok Jin".
- "Seok". - Seok Jin's nose is...
"Seok Jin's nose is..." Go ahead.
Truly...
a big nose.
(In person, his nose is huge.)
- That was cute. - "Truly a big nose".
"Truly a big nose".
(She made his big nose cute.)
That was great.
The last part was great.
It sounded plain, but she twisted the last part.
"Seok Jin's nose is..."
- "Truly a big nose". - "Truly a big nose".
(According to Momo, Seok Jin has a big nose.)
That's great.
Well done.
All right. Let's hear Nayeon's.
With whose name will you do yours?
- I'll do it with Ji Hyo's name. - Ji Hyo.
- Gosh. - It's Ji Hyo.
Do one with her name. Go ahead.
My fingers hurt.
Her fingers hurt?
(She launches her cute act when no one is expecting it.)
(Slurring)
- She started right away. - Right off the bat.
- I wasn't even prepared for that. - Your fingers hurt.
- I wasn't ready at all. - My goodness.
- She started already. - I didn't see that one coming.
- I can't get excited yet. - We'll go to the next one.
Kwang Soo, come here right now.
- Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo. - Go.
- She asked for you. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
(I came here right away upon Nayeon's calling.)
(Both of them are feeling shy.)
Go ahead.
(She's the expert in acrostic poem. How will she finish?)
(My fingers hurt. Kwang Soo, come here right now.)
Please blow on them.
(Please blow on them.)
(Slurring)
She's so cute.
(Punching)
(How dare you, you punk!)
(The fans take the initiatives to cut this part out.)
Stop it!
- Why would you do that? Why? - Stop it!
- How dare you? - Don't do it.
- Stop it. - Your breath stinks!
(I'll protect your fingers no matter what.)
- She's great. - That was so original.
- The first line was original. - Right.
- I didn't see that one coming. - My goodness.
- It was beyond our imagination. - Goodness, her fingers.
This one is about Dahyun.
These days, you have a new nickname, Mr. Tofu.
(Another interesting fact is Dahyun's nickname.)
- My nickname is Tofu. - Okay.
They combined it with a title for men.
- That's why you're Mr. Tofu. - They call me Mr. Tofu.
That's why. I see.
I see how you got your nickname.
You mispronounced it. You said, "plate" instead.
(You mispronounced it. You said, "plate" instead.)
- It's Mr. Tofu. - Mr. Tofu.
- Be careful with the pronunciation. - Come on.
- It's not "plate". - Why is she a plate?
It's Mr. Tofu.
All right. Mr. Tofu.
Just like last time,
- she'll show us impressive dance. - Right.
Dance for us since you're here.
Without further ado,
we'll ask her to dance for us.
- Dahyun, please show us your dance! - Okay.
But what kind of music will you play?
Music? Which song is it?
Can you dance to this?
There she is again. Look at her face.
(Of course, I can.)
There she is again.
- She changed right away. - Gosh.
(What... What is this?)
(Dancing)
- Mr. Tofu. Mr. Tofu. - You have to do it now.
(Here comes Mr. Tofu. Step aside.)
(Staggering)
- Gosh, he is Mr. Tofu indeed. - Look at her swag.
(It's the swag of a middle-aged man.)
Gosh, look at her dance.
Seriously, her dance.
(Why must we suffer embarrassment for her dance?)
- Gosh, she's adorable. - She doesn't like the sun.
- Do you not like the sun? - Why are you blocking it?
(Last night, she had a nice after-work dinner.)
- She's cold now. She's freezing. - She's cold.
(I hate the rising sun in the midst of the morning air.)
- She's shivering. - What is that?
(Mr. Tofu's swag embraces the joys and sorrows of an office worker.)
(Mr. Tofu would like to cheer for all of middle-aged men out there.)
(Her dance of a middle-aged man is also a big success.)
She walked like a middle-aged man.
She came out like one from the start.
- Seriously. - Right now...
I want to give her the long johns as a present.
Thank you.
All right. That was Mr. Tofu.
Continuing from Dahyun's dance,
Momo will dance too.
- She was really good that day. - What's this?
- Wasn't she great that day? - She was phenomenal.
- They went to the final that day. - Her sexy dance moves were great.
All right. Momo. Are you ready?
- I'll play the music. - Okay
- What is this song? - She was in the final too.
She's so cool.
(When the song plays, she shyly walks out.)
(There's a sudden change.)
(As a warm-up, she splits the beats.)
(Shall I get started now?)
- How does she do this? - Seriously.
(Groovy and sexy)
- Gosh. - She's flexible.
How could she be so flexible?
(Momo is the best dancer. Dance like Momo to be popular.)
(Gosh! Way to go, Momo!)
(Her girl-crushing bounce...)
(makes her performance explode.)
She's so cool.
(She's so cool whenever she dances.)
You were crazy.
(She shows off her charms today just like last time.)
- She's such a great dancer. - That was amazing.
- She's so good. - She's amazing.
(What do you lack, TWICE?)
- You were great. - That was so cool.
- You were indeed great. - You were so cool.
- Jeongyeon, it's warm now, right? - Seriously. She's so cool.
- It's really warm. - It's so warm.
(To continue with this heated momentum...)
Right now, the members...
have chosen a partner for kimchi.
TWICE must choose from...
ramyeon, sweet potatoes, suyuk, and rice,
the best food pairing for kimchi.
Each team can hold up to four people.
Only one team will have five people in it.
A team with five people will have an advantage for a mission.
Please choose wisely.
I have ramyeon. Come on!
- Come to ramyeon. - Come to suyuk!
- Ramyeon goes well with kimchi. - It's ramyeon and kimchi.
Girls, it's suyuk.
- Kimchi goes with suyuk. - Of course!
- It's meat. - Rice.
- Hey, you. - You can't eat this without kimchi.
Rice and kimchi are the best.
Think about the freshly made kimchi.
- All right. 1, 2, 3. - This is the best pairing.
- Come here. It's rice. - Come here.
- There you go! - Gosh!
This is it!
- I can't believe my luck. - What's going on?
- I can't believe this. - Gosh.
- Come here. Rice? - Hey, it's suyuk!
- It's suyuk! - It's meat!
- Suyuk, suyuk! - We chose suyuk!
- Right? Suyuk is the best! - That's right.
- You need meat! - Suyuk is the best indeed.
- Come on. - You need ramyeon for kimchi.
- Ramyeon. - Ramyeon.
(Passing by)
- Jae Seok. - No one chose ramyeon?
Choose sweet potatoes!
(No one chooses sweet potatoes too.)
Sweet potatoes!
What's going on?
Ramyeon?
- Jae Seok. - No one chose ramyeon?
(These two teams are low on members.)
- Okay! - Yes!
(Nayeon and Momo save Team Ramyeon.)
- What is this? - Look at them.
- No one picked sweet potatoes! - Hey, come here!
- No one went to sweet potatoes. - How could this be possible?
- No one? - How could this happen?
No one chose sweet potatoes?
- Why don't you eat sweet potatoes? - Not even one chose our food.
- Right now, - How is this possible?
there are six people in Team Rice.
- No, what am I going to do? - Send two of them...
to Team Sweet Potato.
- What am I going to do? - No, this is so sad.
(It must be done.)
Don't say it like it's a bad thing.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
They are so loyal to each other.
- All right. The losers? - The losers will go there.
- The losers will go. - Ready or not,
- rock-paper-scissors - rock-paper-scissors
(Jeongyeon and Tzuyu won. Chaeyoung and Mina lost.)
(Jeongyeon and Tzuyu will stay in Team Rice.)
- Okay! - My goodness.
(We're off to Team Sweet Potato.)
- Hey. - Hey, this is a great team.
- That's a great team. - I'm fine. I'm okay.
(Meanwhile, Mr. Tofu from Team Suyuk...)
(Looking around)
- Mr. Tofu? - TWICE can choose.
- They can change their teams? - Mr. Tofu.
- I'd like to change my team. - Think carefully.
- Join our team. - Choose Team Rice.
We have a spot for one more member.
- Join us, Dahyun. - Choose Team Rice.
Sweet potatoes are nicely cooked.
We can have one more.
(Which team will Dahyun choose and become its 5th member?)
- I'll go with Team Sweet Potato. - Don't even look at them.
- Team Sweet Potato! - Yes!
(Dahyun chooses the sweet potatoes like a true middle-aged man.)
Our team has won at the end.
We have five members.
- All the teams have been formed. - Okay.
(Only Team Sweet Potato has 5 members.)
(They finished teaming up.)
It's the Kimchi Special with TWICE.
The race is called Who Is Kimchi's Partner?
We asked teenagers to people in their 50s...
which food complements kimchi the most through a survey.
The team who guesses the food in first place wins the race.
You can buy hints about...
the food in first place with cabbage leaves you earn from missions.
The team that guesses the food in first place won't face a penalty.
The rest of three teams who have lost the race will...
- season 100 heads of Napa cabbages. - 100 heads?
What? What's that?
We have to season 100 heads of Napa cabbages.
We'll have to do 100?
Anyway, this will be fun.
- You think this will be fun? - Yes.
They're so positive.
(Which team will avoid getting this frightening kimchi penalty?)
(The first mission after changing outfits)
- Why are there stairs? - What's that?
Stand with your teams.
- What happened? - My hand warmer exploded again.
- It exploded again? - Yes.
It exploded again in the car earlier.
Your hand warmer exploded?
Hey, get me some wet wipes.
Dahyun's hand warmer...
Seok Jin and his good stories.
He got another close-up with his forced story.
- He's aiming for one more close-up. - He's forcing it.
- You're forcing it again. - Seok Jin, why...
(I'm getting my shot, right?)
- Seok Jin with his good stories. - Another close-up.
Thank you.
(Thank you, anyway.)
Here's the first mission for you to get your hints.
It's called Invest Napa Cabbages, Line up.
(Invest Napa Cabbages, Line up)
Each team will receive 50 cabbage leaves.
You'll bet your cabbage leaves every round.
The winning team will win additional leaves as many as their bets.
(The winning team wins additional leaves as many as their bets.)
- Gosh, should we be adventurous? - Should we give that a try?
- Should we go all in? - Shall we?
When the final mission is over,
you can go to the Hint Shop and buy the hints you want...
with cabbage leaves you earned.
All right. For the missions of each round,
you will hear what it is first and choose the order to try the mission.
If everyone in your team passes in order, it's a success.
(Pass the mission in the assigned order.)
- We have five. It's harder for us. - Our team is at a disadvantage.
Since other teams have four members,
you have to choose four players...
- for each game. - Only four.
- You guys play. - Seok Jin should stay out.
Kwang Soo will stay out.
(Disapproving)
- Seok Jin. - Kwang Soo will stay out.
Kwang Soo will stay out. Let's do this.
Either Kwang Soo or Seok Jin should stay out.
(What will happen to Team Sweet Potato?)
The first round is Low Bar Rollover.
(First Round: Low Bar Rollover)
The bar will get lower and lower. Roll over it once...
one by one.
Roll over the bar?
We have to roll over the bar?
(Success)
Please decide the order and make a bet.
Which of you is the most athletic?
That doesn't really matter.
As long as the head doesn't touch the ground...
- This... - It's not going to be easy.
Nayeon should do the forward roll.
You and I should do the backward roll.
Should we do that?
Ji Hyo...
(Team Suyuk's strategy)
Ji Hyo has a long upper body, so she should go first.
(Harsh)
(I can't believe him.)
I think you can do it.
- You should go first. - What if I fail?
No.
- You go 3rd. - I'll go 3rd. You go 2nd.
- How many should we bet? - 12?
- 12? - 15.
- 15. - 15.
We can do it.
We can roll backwards.
Your head might touch...
15.
- What do you say? - Good.
Guys, let's bet just one.
Just one?
I think we'll fail.
- I think so too. - It's better than losing a lot.
- We'll bet big later. - Exactly.
(Line-ups and Bets)
Line up. Decide which team will go first.
- Go, So Min. - You can do this!
So Min, give that to me.
Okay.
I've never done this before.
If you fail, your team is out.
- How do I do it? - You have only one chance.
- Do I roll on my stomach? - You have only one chance.
- Yes. - Show us who you are.
Let's go!
(How will So Min's first try go?)
Try to remember how you did it when you were little.
Good.
If you fail, you're out.
(In the 1st round, the bar is 100cm high, so it's pretty easy.)
(She's rolling.)
Keep going.
There you go.
- Keep going. - Hey.
Good.
Hold on.
Is this okay?
Is this a success?
- Does it count? - Is it okay?
She just fell.
- Does this count? - You have to land on your feet.
Stop pretending it doesn't hurt.
Shouldn't we land on our feet?
Stop pretending.
We should land on our feet.
She fell with a thud.
I was too heavy.
(Although her bottom hurts, So Min succeeds.)
Go, Team Ramyeon!
(Next up is Nayeon from Team Ramyeon.)
I don't think I can do it.
(Floundering)
- Is it too hard? - You have to jump.
- Hold on. She's a mess. - Nayeon.
- She's a mess. - Nayeon.
Jump and roll over on your stomach.
You can't give her a lesson here.
What are you talking about?
- It's a lesson. - It's not a lesson.
- She has to start right away. - Jump up.
Just start.
(Will Nayeon succeed?)
- Let's go. - I'm scared.
There you go. Jump up and roll over.
Bend over.
There you go. You can do this.
Roll over.
There you go.
(Nayeon's legs are wandering.)
(Will she land successfully?)
- Jump! - That's definitely a success.
- That's how you do it. - Good job, Nayeon.
(She lands perfectly.)
Good job, Nayeon.
- That's how you do it. - It was nothing.
- Right? - Who is next?
It's our turn.
It's our turn now.
(Slow)
Seok Jin...
Are you the first player?
That's not okay.
The principal...
- came to our sports day. - Please give a speech.
(Is Seok Jin as good as So Min and Nayeon?)
I can't believe it. Seok Jin is the first player.
- Here we go. - If you fail, your team is out.
How could I fail?
(Offended)
(He sounds confident.)
(Even if my team has given up on me,)
(this would be easy.)
(He rolls over...)
(and falls.)
Isn't that a fail?
(Heavy)
(He falls on his bottom as it's the heaviest part.)
(Is he okay?)
Fail.
- Isn't that a fail? - It's a success.
He's rolled over.
- Success! - I've rolled over.
Okay!
Sana!
We should hold the bar.
(She grabs the bar...)
(and jumps up right away.)
She's so light.
She's so flexible.
Good job.
(She even lands perfectly.)
- How did she do that? - She's so flexible.
She's flexible.
She's so light.
(All 4 teams have passed the 1st round.)
The bar will be lowered now. Please lower it.
(In the 2nd round, the bar is lowered to 80cm high.)
It's too low.
Is that how much they lower it?
We'll follow the same order in the second round.
Go, Team Rice!
Team Rice!
- Tzuyu. - Let's go, Tzuyu!
(She feels a sense of duty.)
- You can do this! - You have to land on your feet.
If you don't, you're out.
Tzuyu, if you don't land on your feet, you're out.
You can do this.
Let's go, Tzuyu.
- There you go. - She's folded.
- She's folded her body. - There you go.
Bend over.
Roll over now.
There you go.
If you don't land on your feet...
- Good! - Success.
It's a success.
- There you go. - Your legs.
Good!
Let's do this, Dahyun!
Just land on your feet.
Your feet. There you go.
- Okay! - Good job.
It's Ji Hyo's turn!
There you go. Your legs.
- Good! - Yes!
- It'll be lowered to 60cm. - Good job.
(In the 3rd round, the bar is 60cm high.)
- Is that how low it's going to be? - It's impossible.
- Team Rice will go first. - Team Rice!
Let's do this, Jeongyeon!
Jeongyeon has been my partner all three times so far.
Even her sister, Seung Yeon, was my partner.
So what?
Stop talking about something irrelevant.
- We're a family. - It doesn't matter!
Just focus on raising your kids.
(Focus on your real family.)
(Gosh, they always get in my way.)
Here we go.
- Do it like this. - We're very close.
Like this?
- Is that harder? - It'd be hard to lift your legs.
It must be hard.
- Right. - It's not going to work.
Watch your head.
- Jeongyeon. - But...
her head will definitely touch the ground.
Watch your head.
Jeongyeon.
(With her head not touching, she has to land on her feet.)
(Her head isn't touching the ground.)
(All she has to do now is land on her feet.)
Fail.
(She rolls over well...)
(but lands on her bottom.)
- That was close. - Is this even possible?
It's impossible.
(Good job, my family member.)
You have to stay close to the bar.
Can you do it?
- It's Jae Seok's turn. - Who is next?
- Who is next? - It's your turn.
Is it my turn?
(Next up is Jae Seok from Team Ramyeon.)
- Let me... - Please hold the bar.
Nayeon, please hold the bar.
It's not going to be easy.
(Now that he's holding the bar, he realizes.)
- Is that even possible? - Are you doing a backward roll?
I'm doing a backward roll.
- Are you doing a backward roll? - I'm doing a backward roll.
He has to lift his legs.
- Roll over. - Land on your feet.
- There you go. - Nice.
(Even with a forward roll, everyone has been struggling.)
He's doing a backward roll.
(Jae Seok has decided to do a backward roll, which is harder.)
I don't think he can do it.
Is that even possible?
- Are you doing a backward roll? - I'm doing a backward roll.
Without a run-up?
There you go.
(Will he succeed?)
Yes!
(Perfect)
(Powerful)
- Without a run-up? - There you go.
(After a quick roll, he lands perfectly.)
(Jae Seok nails the 60cm-high bar.)
Yes!
- Good! - He's so strong.
(Jae Seok's success threatens the other teams.)
Do you want to try? You can do it, right?
- Kwang Soo will try. - What a man.
- Yes! - He's a man.
The fourth round will be hard.
Do your best.
Who is up next? Team Sweet Potato?
- Kwang Soo! - Yes.
(Next up is Kwang Soo from Team Sweet Potato.)
Kwang Soo is too tall.
But he's strong too.
He's good at chin-ups.
You can do it, right?
(We trust you.)
Ready.
(He'll try a backward roll on the 60cm-high bar.)
You can do it!
(If he fails, his team will be out.)
(His legs are turned over.)
(He might succeed.)
Hold on.
(Wait)
Fail.
(He did roll over, but...)
(His private part got injured.)
(He can't control his body.)
(Kwang Soo's sacrifice deserves respect.)
- Fail. - Is it a fail?
- Are you okay? - It's a fail.
(Team Sweet Potato is out.)
My goodness.
It must have hurt a lot.
(You guys carry on. Let me take a break.)
Next.
It's like the finals.
It's her turn, right?
(Next up is Jihyo from Team Suyuk.)
Stay close to the bar.
Jihyo...
Also, roll quickly.
Tuck your head in.
Stay close to the bar.
(If Jihyo fails, Team Suyuk will be out.)
That's how you do it.
(Jihyo is going to try to roll over the 60cm-high bar.)
(Rolling)
(After a quick roll, she lands perfectly.)
- Good job. - That was amazing.
You did an amazing job.
You did the best job so far.
Jihyo.
- You did the best job. - You did the best job.
I'll do a forward roll.
A forward roll is better.
Jihyo.
Team Rice is out.
Team Sweet Potato and Team Rice are out.
It's Team Ramyeon versus Team Suyuk.
(The bar is lowered to 50cm.)
It's the finals.
If we lose, the damage will be big.
(It's Jong Kook versus Se Chan.)
The bar is so low. How are they going to roll over it?
I hope both of them will fail.
The head would touch the ground.
We have to...
Can you do a forward roll?
(Se Chan from Team Ramyeon will try first.)
- Give it a try. - You can't practice.
(Jong Kook keeps him in check.)
- Can't I practice? - No.
(The competition is fierce even from the start.)
Gosh, do you want to defeat me that badly?
He won't go easy.
We put a lot at stake this time.
Nayeon.
(She's so curious that she wants to try it.)
(Let's try it.)
(She falls down.)
(Her head lands successfully.)
Nayeon.
(It's harder than I thought.)
Are you okay, Nayeon?
Hey, you can get stuck.
Come on, ramyeon.
- Let's go, Se Chan. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - I'm certain that he can't do it.
You can do it.
He can't do it.
Don't lean on your stomach. It should be lower.
Be quick.
Turn quickly.
Se Chan, do it.
Be quick.
(If he fails, Team Ramyeon is eliminated.)
(He's very nervous.)
You must turn quickly.
(The bar height is very low. Will Se Chan succeed?)
(He falls off.)
(He lands on his face.)
(Se Chan fails.)
Hey.
(It's a very sad yet funny way to fail.)
My goodness.
(People pretend not to see it.)
(It's sad but funny.)
- Are you okay, Se Chan? - Are you okay?
- Tell everyone to leave. - Are you okay?
- I'm okay. - My goodness.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
(We'll pretend we didn't see it.)
This is frustrating.
(It's so embarrassing.)
I'm so embarrassed.
Se Chan usually does it better.
Let's go.
(Team Ramyeon fails.)
- My goodness. - Next team, go.
- Is it our turn now? - Yes.
Is it our turn?
(Let's try the hanging bar.)
- This is... - Jong Kook is next.
He's been working out for over 20 years for today.
- For today. - This is short.
(His 20 years of weightlifting will be put to test.)
(I've been training my back muscles. Are you ready?)
Jong Kook's sense of pride is on the line.
- Seriously. - He'll win.
This will be amazing.
- Jong Kook will look good doing it. - What will happen?
Here I go.
(He's nervous.)
(He tries flipping over backwards over a bar of 50cm in height.)
(He does it with ease.)
(He turns once without using any force.)
(Team Suyuk clears the hanging bar mission.)
Good job.
- You should have gone last. - I know.
He did it.
(They're amazed by Jong Kook's physical skills.)
- Let's move on. - He did it.
- Take 30. - Okay.
We won 30.
- I should have gone last. - Thank you.
This is great.
Our team is amazing.
I thought it'd take longer, but it didn't.
All right.
(Shall I try it?)
You have to do it like this.
- All the way. - It requires abs and arm strength.
What's the point of me doing it?
(He gives up right away.)
When he grabbed the bar, he realized that it's impossible.
Gosh, Jae Seok.
Just give it a try.
- Give it a try. - Okay.
- Give it a try. - I will.
I bet all of my money that he can't do it.
- Really? - I'll let you treat me like...
a younger brother if you succeed.
- Do you promise? Really? - Of course.
If Jae Seok makes it, you'll always be considered younger than him.
Seok Jin promised.
- Jae Seok can do it. - No, he can't.
- He can't do it. - It's possible.
(Hierarchy between Seok Jin and Jae Seok depends on this bet.)
(Will Jae Seok make it?)
(Thankfully he fails.)
(Jae Seok is nice enough to keep Seok Jin's sense of pride.)
I got stuck.
(Round 1 is finished.)
How is that possible?
Can we play games that we can do?
Round Two is called Wrap, Yes or Yes.
I'm confident.
I'm good at eating it.
Having a big mouth is an advantage.
I have a very big mouth.
Do you?
(She opens her mouth wide.)
- Nayeon is amazing. - That's cheating.
Women have bigger mouths.
Listen, our team members seem promising.
(TWICE members show off the size of their mouths.)
- The wrap can go in. - It's big enough.
- It's possible. - Isn't it big?
(It's best to assign members with big mouths last.)
- Momo should go first and second. - First and second.
- You're third. - You're fourth.
Here you go.
(Tzuyu is assigned last.)
Is Tzuyu last?
Is Tzuyu going last?
Everyone, we'll show you Tunnel Number One at Mount Nam.
Tzuyu.
(Her mouth is big enough for a wrap to go through.)
- Not a lot will go in. - We're not listening.
Jihyo has a big mouth too.
Mine is Tunnel Number Two at Mount Nam.
- Tunnel Number Two? - Show us your mouth, Jihyo.
(Her mouth is big enough as well.)
Jihyo has a big mouth too.
Is this the order?
Is Mina going last?
No, she's just sitting here.
(Let TWICE join the game.)
- Let TWICE play the game. - Let them play.
Seok Jin or Kwang Soo can stay out.
Either Seok Jin or Kwang Soo should stay out.
TWICE should play.
- Seriously. - The audience wants Mina to play.
- Should we make her play? - Mina should join.
Why are the others playing?
People left many comments about you.
Shall we have Mina play?
Don't push Mina away.
(He plays with words.)
Okay, Mina, you should play.
- That's right. She should play. - Go, Mina.
- Shall I stay out? - You shouldn't.
- How about this? - Don't make Mina stay out.
- Come here, Dahyun. - Step up, Dahyun.
Are you taking out Dahyun?
You're insane.
- Show us Dahyun. - Show us Dahyun.
It's our strategy.
(We're taking out members with small mouths.)
The other team gets to strategize.
Have a seat and play, Dahyun.
(Dahyun joins the game again.)
Wait.
- What should we do? - Hurry up.
Seok Jin should stay out.
- Dahyun, you have to eat. - Okay.
- I'll stay out. - Okay.
(Everyone is quiet.)
No one is protesting.
Whom were you talking to?
When he said, "I'll stay out", it only echoed.
"I'll stay out", "I'll stay out".
No one is protesting.
- This is good. It's quiet now. - This is great.
(Their peaceful agreement is made.)
- Let's go. - Let's play.
Now everyone is quiet.
Now the world is at peace.
Here comes the first wrap.
(They try the wrap at level 1.)
This is great.
The first one is cute.
That looks delicious. We can definitely eat it.
Start with So Min.
You're doing a good job.
- Sana. - Sana.
(Everyone including Sana, Momo, and Mina succeed.)
You look pretty.
- Isn't it spicy? - Sana.
(It's just like finger food.)
Second players, come out.
Chili and garlic are added.
- Jeongyeon looks good. - There it goes.
Nayeon, you look like your jaw is dislocated.
That's right.
- Nayeon, she's so confident. - Look at Nayeon.
Nayeon looks confident.
- Third players, come out. - Okay.
(Wrap at level 3)
- Let's go, team. - Let's go.
Start.
(Haha from Team Rice starts.)
- It's impossible. - It won't be possible.
It's much bigger than I thought.
Garlic is falling out.
(A clove of garlic falls out.)
He's out.
- He's eliminated. - It can't fall out.
Here goes Jihyo.
She can't closer her mouth.
Jihyo's mouth is small.
She got it. She did it.
She did it. That was perfect.
(She succeeds perfectly.)
Okay, go, Jae Seok.
- Put it in. - He has a big mouth.
(He fails as garlic falls out.)
Who's next?
(Dahyun opens her mouth wide.)
- Face the camera. - Dahyun.
(Her wrap disappears.)
She made it.
(Only Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are left.)
Fourth players, come out.
The last level will be difficult.
I bet it'll be huge.
(A gigantic wrap at level 4 arrives.)
- It's too big. Look at that. - There it is.
(What does level 4 look like?)
Level four is difficult.
It's too big.
This is...
(The one who puts everything inside his mouth wins.)
How is it possible to put it in?
The throat will hurt.
- Tear everything and put it in. - In the large one?
Yes.
- Is this more advantageous? - Yes.
This is possible, right?
Even I can do it.
We haven't put meat in yet.
(They haven't put in pork belly meat yet.)
We can't put it in.
This isn't possible to eat.
It's too big.
(His wrap is large too.)
Let's just do it.
- It's too big. - It's impossible.
I don't think you can eat it.
(He warms up his jaw.)
Let's go. You can do it.
(He's very nervous.)
Go, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook attempts to eat wrap at level 4.)
This is...
It'll be difficult.
Jong Kook can't even open his eyes.
(The gigantic wrap goes in little by little.)
- Even Jong Kook can't do it. - It's going in.
No, stop it, Jong Kook.
- Stop it, Jong Kook. - Stop it.
It's about to tear open his cheeks.
- Look at his cheeks. - He's being competitive.
You don't need to go that far.
- Save Jong Kook. - Are you okay?
- He fails. - Jong Kook tried to do it...
with his mentality, but it's impossible.
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
Wait.
(If he wins, Team Sweet Potato wins.)
Even if his mouth is big, it will be hard.
He's putting on lip balm.
His mouth might tear.
His mouth became red.
Here goes Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo starts.)
That's good. Go, let's go.
It isn't easy. It's spilling.
Is his mouth that big?
- No way. - That's not possible.
(How does it go in?)
(He succeeds if he closes his mouth.)
This is what I do for a hobby.
I can't watch anymore.
(He puts in every little piece.)
You got it.
(He puts everything inside.)
He can't be human.
(Team Sweet Potato wins the wrap game.)
He did it!
(I admit my defeat.)
Team Sweet Potato wins the second round.
Amazing!
(Team Sweet Potato wins Round 2.)
Team Sweet Potato...
bet 20 cabbage leaves, so they win 20 more.
(Team Sweet Potato wins 20 cabbage leaves.)
Good job, Kwang Soo.
Here we go.
The third game is Pig Ssireum.
(Pig Ssireum)
1 player from each team will compete, so 4 in total.
You have to push the others so that their fingers come unlaced...
or they get out of the area.
When someone is out, the next player takes over within five seconds.
The team whose member lasts longest wins.
(The team that lasts longest wins.)
How many should we bet?
I'm not sure.
This is hard.
- They might target you. - That's right.
We should bet just a little.
Let's pass this game too.
Let's go for the next game.
- Let's give it our all. - How many do we have left?
(We might not be able to win many cabbage leaves.)
We have...
Should we steal some?
(Jeongyeon suggests that they steal some cabbage leaves.)
(Let's do that.)
Okay.
(Team Rice's strategy is to make small bets and steal others'.)
Watch how we do it.
The first players.
Go to your positions.
(Line-ups and Bets)
- Guys. - Go, So Min!
Team up and eliminate Jae Seok first.
- Let's do that. - Hold on.
(Are you serious?)
- Let's team up. - Let's do that!
(They're ready for a joint attack.)
Sana!
Go, So Min!
(Shouting)
How many?
Seven.
(Haha secretly checks what Jeongyeon has brought.)
I think I can steal some.
(A moment ago)
Jeongyeon, go behind the wall.
(Team Rice sends Jeongyeon behind the wall...)
(and distracts the others with loud cheers.)
(Meanwhile, Jeongyeon approaches Team Sweet Potato...)
(and steals a handful of cabbage leaves.)
(Okay, everything is going well.)
(We have so many cabbage leaves now.)
Ready.
Sana!
(Let's start our joint attack.)
I mean... Guys.
- Let's go. - Think about it.
Especially you.
We don't have many cabbage leaves.
Jae Seok, hang in there.
- Turn your back. - Hang in there!
We don't have many cabbage leaves. You can't do this to me.
(Jae Seok is surrounded.)
(Sana kicks him.)
Jae Seok is out.
No! Jae Seok!
Jae Seok is out. Who's next?
Momo, go in.
Momo, go all the way in.
(The alliance breaks.)
Help me!
Momo.
(Sana kicks So Min too.)
(So Min from Team Rice is eliminated.)
So Min is out.
Your legs. There you go!
Momo, step back.
(So Min out, Haha in.)
Momo, watch your back.
(Sana kicks Momo too.)
(Sana has eliminated 3 people in a row.)
- Out! - Sana is the best!
Go, Sana!
- Sana is amazing! - She's incredible!
(Who should I eliminate next?)
(Momo out, Se Chan in)
- Let's attack Se Chan first. - No.
(Pushing)
Let's go.
(As soon as he sits down,)
(Mina pushes him out.)
(Go get some rest.)
Mina!
- Mina did an amazing job. - Mina!
- Mina, Nayeon is behind you! - Mina!
Mina is amazing!
- Mina did an amazing job. - Mina!
- Mina, Nayeon is behind you! - Mina!
(Kicking)
(Did you just kick me?)
Nayeon, be careful!
(Nayeon is eliminated right away.)
Sana is amazing!
- Team Ramyeon is out. - My team...
- What's wrong with my team? - Out!
(Should we eliminate Haha?)
(Mina pushes Haha.)
Haha. Who is next?
So Min. It's inside.
Gosh, it's so funny.
Are we the only ones left?
No.
(No way.)
(Jeongyeon versus Mina versus Sana)
Mina won't fall.
- With her legs apart... - She won't fall.
(What? Mina won't fall?)
(Sana will make her fall.)
(Between these strong contestants, who is going to win?)
(Sana pushes Mina.)
(Mina is out.)
Sana will survive to the end.
(Sana is incredible.)
Sana is unbelievable.
Jeongyeon is out.
(Sana eliminates Jeongyeon as well.)
(By eliminating Tzuyu,)
(she eliminates the whole Team Rice.)
Is Sana the first player?
- She is. - She is?
(Sana is exhausted.)
Go, Chaeyoung!
(Chaeyoung attacks Sana while she is exhausted.)
Push her down!
Sana!
No! Chaeyoung!
(Strong defense versus strong offense)
(With her legs, Sana resists against Chaeyoung's attack.)
(But her foot gets out.)
(Sana is finally eliminated.)
Sana...
Sana, you're amazing!
I'm scared.
Chaeyoung.
(Chaeyoung eliminates Jihyo from Team Suyuk.)
- It's dangerous. - Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hyo, with 8 years' experience, eliminates Chaeyoung right away.)
- Both of you should go in. - Go in.
Kwang Soo, go in.
Dahyun, go for Jong Kook.
Attack Jong Kook!
(Have you ever been attacked by toes?)
Good.
Dahyun is out.
(Dahyun from Team Sweet Potato is out.)
Good.
(Dahyun is out?)
(I want you out too.)
(No way.)
(It's time for test signals.)
(Screaming)
(Suffering)
Done.
(What's going on?)
(So many things happened.)
It's so funny.
Good job, Ji Hyo.
(Although we can't show you everything, Team Suyuk wins.)
With your cabbage leaves,
you can buy a hint and make a guess.
You can see each age group's choice directly.
We can see it?
I want to know what people in their 30s chose.
Number-one choice of people in their 30s?
Number-one choice of people in their 30s.
There you go.
(Team Suyuk buys a hint for the 1st choice of people in their 30s.)
44 percent?
- Really? - I had no idea.
That's unexpected.
(44 percent of the people in their 30s chose ramyeon.)
- Jeongyeon did it. - What should we choose?
- What should we choose? - I choose people in their 20s.
Let's do that.
(Team Rice buys a hint for the 1st choice of people in their 20s.)
(What did people in their 20s choose as kimchi's partner?)
(It's ramyeon again.)
44 percent chose it.
(44 percent of people in their 20s and 30s...)
(chose ramyeon as kimchi's true partner.)
Can we win more cabbage leaves in the next round?
Yes.
We can win more. Let's go for 50.
We should go for 50. We can win more.
How many do we have left?
- 8. - 8?
(They count their cabbage leaves.)
Hold on.
- Some are missing. - Some are missing.
We won 20 in the beginning...
- and then... - Why do we have less?
(Some of the cabbage leaves are missing.)
(Team Sweet Potato finally realizes their cabbage leaves are missing.)
Why do we have less? How many are we supposed to have?
We're supposed to have 49.
- But we have less than that. - What happened?
We're supposed to have 52.
- We're supposed to have 52. - We have less.
(It's a perfect crime.)
Someone must have stolen them.
(Now I get it.)
That's right.
I told you to keep an eye on them.
Seriously?
Okay.
I've chosen my path for today.
Now I understand how it works.
(So this is how you play?)
(Why didn't you tell me before?)
Now I understand how this game works.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's do it. - Let's do it.
It's going to be so fun today.
Let's do it.
(Round 1 is over. What game is waiting for them next?)
(Round 2, Tanhyeon SBS sports field)
(It looks like a shot put area. What game are they going to play?)
Stand in teams.
Kwang Soo, can you clap your hands once?
Okay.
Come back in.
(They suddenly attack him.)
Ha Seok Ju, come back in!
(It's so fun to tease Kwang Soo.)
Why is he so full of energy today?
Your hair is too long on the back.
TWICE should do it.
Jeongyeon is going to do it.
1, 2, 3.
Nice!
(Kwang Soo is missing.)
(Even before Round 2, Kwang Soo is exhausted.)
- Come back in. - You know how they are.
(How should I get back at them?)
You can win more hints in this game.
It's called Flying Wig Shot Put.
(Flying Wig Shot Put)
At the starting line, you will...
throw your wig off your head.
The area your wig lands in will determine how many points you win.
The team can win as many cabbage leaves as the points combined.
There are four types of wigs.
Bald, short,
curly, and long.
The bald one is the best...
- because it's heavy. - That's right.
We'll play a simple game, and the winner will distribute the wigs.
Since we have as many as 17 people today,
let's play Race of Wits.
Jae Seok's Race of Wits has started.
He looks so happy.
- What's with your hands? - Why do you like it so much?
I've never played it with 17 people.
- Okay. - It's never been bigger.
- He looks so happy. - My hands are shaking.
Ready.
I'm going to say, "one".
I'm definitely saying, "one".
Ready, start.
- 1. - 1.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo and So Min are out.)
- They're out. - They're out.
So Min and Ji Hyo are out.
Step aside.
It's dangerous to say, "one", in the beginning.
(I survived.)
With the reckless ones out, it's my turn now.
1, 1...
Ready, start.
One.
Two.
- 3. - 4.
Five.
Six.
- 7. - 7.
Both of them said seven.
I said it first.
- He said it first. - I said it first.
Really?
- Then eight. - He said it first.
(I'll go with 8.)
That doesn't work.
What?
- What was that? - Isn't he eliminated?
Mister.
Get out, mister.
My bad.
He's ridiculous.
That's hilarious.
(They can't get used to Haha's tricks.)
- Mister. - What is he doing?
- What was that? - Come on.
Let's go again. Start.
One.
(Jeongyeon calls out 1 as soon as it starts.)
- 2. - 3.
- 4. - 5.
Six.
- 7. - 7.
(Dahyun and Tzuyu are out.)
They're out.
- Tzuyu and Dahyun? - You were so close.
Please go over there.
Okay.
Let's go again.
(All members of Team Ramyeon survived so far.)
This is good.
We have to start over again.
Only Jeongyeon is left.
(She's from Team Rice.)
(Jeongyeon is the only survivor from Team Rice.)
(She must compete against many opponents.)
Jeongyeon is good at calling out number one.
(Jeongyeon is good at calling out number one.)
(Jeongyeon survived twice in a row with number 1.)
- It's okay, Jeongyeon. - She's good with number one.
You'll be our hero...
if you win.
- Start. - One.
(She calls out number 1 again.)
- 2. - 2.
(Kwang Soo and Nayeon are out.)
Kwang Soo is eliminated.
Good job, Nayeon.
One.
(She always goes for number 1.)
- Start. - One.
- 3. - 3.
(She never loses with number 1.)
Jeongyeon is the best.
(She's working hard.)
Say one no matter what.
(Only 4 members remain.)
- Say one no matter what. - By the way,
are you three working separately from other TWICE members?
Isn't the one on the right your manager?
(Isn't the one on the right your manager?)
Are you their manager?
- They work as a unit. - Really?
- We're a unit. - The four of you are fun today.
We like to work together.
- Get ready. - Say one no matter what.
Start.
(Will Jeongyeon survive again by calling out number 1?)
- 1. - 1.
(Jeongyeon and Se Chan are out at the same time.)
(Mina and Chaeyoung win without realizing it.)
That was clean.
(She fails with number 1.)
It's our first time not playing rock-paper-scissors...
while playing Race of Wits.
It was Jeongyeon.
- That was close. - She went far.
Good job.
- Look at the wigs. - Isn't this the best?
Really?
- This is the heaviest. - This one?
The heaviest is the best.
- This is... - It's influenced the most by wind.
Isn't that the best?
(That's why...)
Wait, we have to think.
(Kwang Soo gives them the worst wig.)
- Think carefully. - Think again.
- You're being impatient. - What do you mean?
Don't ruin the show like this.
What did you say?
Wear this and make kimchi.
(Do you think I'm a fool?)
Put this on and make kimchi later.
Put it on now.
(Wigs are distributed.)
(Practice and discussing strategies)
50 would be enough.
- Won't it be hard to score 50? - Yes.
We're at 15, so are we going for 50?
That's right.
Can we score 15?
It'll reach 20.
(Laughing)
(Running)
(He runs and shoots.)
(Thud)
(He runs quickly, but the wig doesn't travel far.)
What is he doing?
- He ran far, but it landed here. - It didn't travel far.
(He tries again from farther back.)
(Running forward)
(Swing)
That was good, Kwang Soo.
You should run from that far.
Poor Kwang Soo.
Start.
- You're amazing. - Let's go.
Each member from Team Sweet Potato...
will play.
It's Dahyun's turn.
The first player is Dahyun.
It's fine as long as it isn't negative.
Throw it farther than here.
10, 15, and 20.
(Run quickly and gain momentum.)
(The first player of Team Sweet Potato)
(Where will Dahyun's wig land?)
(It falls in front of her feet.)
What?
(She's eliminated in an elegant way.)
- Okay. - Wait.
What happened?
- She hasn't started yet. - Start?
- She hasn't started. - She already started.
- It's because... - She already started.
Seriously.
(Twisting his arm is the answer.)
It was her first time.
(Why is he so energetic today?)
It's easy.
Do you want to be hit by younger members?
- Pardon? - Want to be hit by younger members?
Call everyone including Cho Sae Ho and Nam Chang Hie.
(Do you mean them?)
- It's your first time. - I know.
I'll start.
(Dahyun earns 0 points.)
Let's go, Se Chan. Say "start" beforehand.
That's right.
Let's do it.
He's so cute.
Start.
(He turns his pelvis to throw the wig. What is his score?)
It's 15.
That was close.
- It's 15. - 15.
(That was close.)
- It's closer to 15, right? - 15?
- Is it 15? It is. - It's 15.
- Isn't it closer to 15? - It's 15.
- Wait a minute. - It's five.
- It's 15. - It's 15.
- It's definitely 5. - It's 15.
It's 15.
- Jae Seok definitely said... - It's 15.
"That was close."
- He definitely said it was close. - It's 15.
It's five.
- It's 15. - No way.
It's 15.
Isn't it?
(Jae Seok moves it stealthily.)
- He said that it was close. - It's definitely five.
Can the judge decide?
Jae Seok cheated.
- No. - It'll be considered five points.
Good job.
- At least we earned five points. - This is good.
Is it our turn?
Go, So Min.
Split the hair in the middle.
The wig looks good on you.
She has a middle split.
You should do your hair like that every day.
(How dare you say that?)
- It looks great on her. - Start.
(She reduces the air resistance by splitting the hair.)
(Will So Min's strategy work?)
(Stumbling)
(This wasn't the plan.)
(She loses her balance after tripping.)
(She steps on the starting line.)
She stepped on the line.
(As she stepped on the line, she loses her chance.)
She started.
- She stepped on the line. - She stepped on it.
- She's out. - No.
- She missed her chance. - She tripped,
- but is she out? - She hopped on one leg.
- Wasn't it very cute? - It was.
(So Min earns 0 points.)
Next is Team Suyuk.
- Start. - You can do it.
Sana.
We never know.
- Sana has many hidden skills. - It'll be 20.
(Sana has hidden skills. What is her score?)
- It's negative 10. - Negative 10.
It's negative 10.
(Her hidden skills...)
(will remain hidden.)
- She didn't say "start". - She didn't.
- Sana. - She did.
No, she didn't.
She did right before she started.
- She didn't, or did you? - Did you say it or not?
You didn't, did you?
I want to say that I didn't.
(I want to say that I didn't.)
- Did you say it? - She wants to say that she didn't.
She did say it.
- It's okay. - Is it negative 10?
You did well.
I got negative 10 points.
(Sana's honest score is negative 10 points.)
You look cute.
(The members of TWICE show off their looks.)
Start.
(She easily scores 5 points.)
At least it's not negative.
(Nayeon from Team Ramyeon starts.)
- Start. - Okay.
(She gets sloppy and scores negative 10 points.)
- Start. - Start.
Okay.
That's right.
Start.
(She throws it elegantly.)
It's 20 points.
You got 20 points.
Start.
Wait.
Okay.
Good job, Momo.
Start.
- Throw it harder. - Harder.
It's 10 points.
See? You did well.
Start.
It's negative 10.
(Her bow scores negative 10 points.)
This is fun.
- Let's just... - That's good.
leave it at that.
The last turn goes to Team Suyuk.
- Okay. - It's Jong Kook.
Here he goes.
- Is it Jong Kook? - Here he comes.
He looks like a superhero.
Start.
(Team Suyuk's score depends on Jong Kook's head.)
That wig is difficult.
- Are you starting? - Here I go.
(He needs to score at least 15 points to win.)
Start.
Okay.
(Will Jong Kook earn over 15 points?)
Okay, I got it.
(His wig falls between 15 and negative 10.)
- That's sneaky. - What do you mean?
(It's definitely 15 points.)
- Come over here. - it's clearly 15 points.
- There's 50 percent chance. - It's clearly 15.
It's clearly 15 points.
(Mr. Judge, it's 15 points.)
Isn't it 15 points?
It's 15 points.
(It's 15 points, Mr. Judge.)
- There's a big difference. - It's 15 points.
You should be objective.
- It's clearly... - Please be objective.
It's longer on this side.
Okay.
(In my opinion, it's definitely 15 points.)
Look at this man.
(I'll give you 150 points next time.)
It's Team Ramyeon's last turn.
(Jae Seok plays.)
Win 50 points.
Please win 50 points.
This is...
(He warms up to get the winner's hint.)
- You can do it. - Show us, Jae Seok.
(I'll show you.)
That's right.
He's really good.
He's enjoying it.
- Jae Seok is enjoying it. - What is he doing?
- What is he doing? - What's wrong with him?
Why is he so annoying today?
What's wrong with you today? What did you eat yesterday?
He's the ugliest today. How does he look like that?
Did he eat a lot of sweets today?
(Enjoy life.)
(No more fooling around.)
(Team Ramyeon's last try!)
- Start! - Good. Let's focus.
(He was getting the feel of it when he was fooling around.)
If you can reach 50, that's great.
Good. Go!
(Can Jae Seok create miracle?)
Good job!
(Between negative 20 and 15?)
- 15! - Wait!
- Don't touch it. - Don't touch it.
- 15. - This has to be 15.
Isn't it 15?
- Don't touch it. - It's 15.
- This is 15. - Take a look at this.
- This is 15. - It's 15.
- This is so 15. - Don't touch it.
- Don't touch it! - It's so 15.
This doesn't make any sense.
- Don't touch it. - Don't touch it.
- I know. It doesn't make sense. - Look at it this way.
This doesn't make sense.
(Sweating)
What? It's there. Look at this.
(He accepts it as 15!)
This guy. I almost took you the wrong way.
(He apologizes for earlier.)
He's not mad anymore.
- All right! - All right!
Good.
Get ready.
(Team Rice's last try)
What's that?
Who is this?
It looks like Haha's hair.
(Throwing)
Good luck.
(The short Native Indian is showy.)
It looks great on him.
- You're so handsome. - It's totally your hair.
There has to be somebody who looks like this.
You look like your mother when she was a young woman.
(That's right.)
(She had long straight hair, and her heart fluttered with joy.)
You look like your mother when she was a young woman.
That's right. When her heart fluttered with joy.
That's who you are.
(He's identical to his mother.)
- Start. - Start!
(This is penniless Team Rice's final try!)
(He flew.)
(He threw himself in the air. What is the result?)
Disqualified!
(It's outside the lines, so it's disqualified.)
Disqualified.
(He flounders in the air and gets disqualified.)
Wait, what did I do? What's wrong?
Last person.
(Team Sweet Potato's last try)
(Is it finally my turn?)
Kwang Soo, walk back to the shade.
I watched earlier, and it was good.
I think he'll get tired while he runs up.
(I realized when I was practicing!)
(If you run up from a distance, it travels farther!)
(Do as you practiced!)
More. Go farther.
(He stands farther away than when he practiced.)
- Run up to it. Use your speed. - Good luck.
Good luck.
(Use your speed!)
Start!
(Booing)
(People boo at him at a crucial moment.)
You're ugly.
(Booing)
It's no joke.
(I have to overcome this.)
It looks like your real hair.
(Team Sweet Potato's last person to go is Kwang Soo!)
(He swung his head powerfully!)
It looks like your real hair.
(Team Sweet Potato's last person to go is Kwang Soo!)
(He swung his head powerfully!)
(The momentum was in his favor!)
(Can he get a high score?)
- Okay. - It's...
(What?)
(What did I run up for?)
- Negative five. - All right!
- This is ridiculous. - That was useless.
(The finale is anticlimactic.)
(He wastes his energy on running and scores negative 5 points.)
(Final Cabbage Leaves Count)
(It's time to purchase the 2nd hint. Which hint will they look at?)
- It's kind of... - Behind you, Kwang Soo.
(Team Sweet Potato buys number 1 hint from the teenagers.)
What is it?
(Ramyeon is in 1st place!)
- See? - Hide it.
(It's ramyeon for sure.)
(Team Ramyeon buys number 2 hint from the 20s.)
- This is possible. - See? I told you.
- This is unexpected. - I knew it.
That was unexpected.
- I knew it. - You can't deny it.
- I knew it. - That was unexpected.
Should we buy a hint from the 40s or 50s?
40s?
Okay. We should go for the middle.
(What food does people in their 40s think goes well with kimchi?)
(Rice is in 1st place!)
People in their 40s.
- That was totally unexpected. - Goodness.
That was so unexpected.
There's a twist.
I know.
This is the final mission...
where you can protect or steal first place.
Here are the rules for Finding Kimchi's Partner.
- Okay. - Okay.
If you think the dish on your team's menu is not in first place,
you can rip the name tags of people in first place and switch.
(If you rip the name tags of 1st place team, you can switch.)
Suyuk? Ramyeon?
They won't try to rip our name tags.
- What? - We're done.
- We're done. - There's an exception.
There's an exception.
Each team will get stickers...
containing the dish and Bomb Stickers.
If you rip the name tag of a person with the Menu Sticker,
you can switch the dish,
but if you rip the name tag of someone with the Bomb Sticker,
the team that ripped the name tag is eliminated.
- That's mean. - The entire team?
If you rip the name tag of someone with no sticker,
then only the person who ripped the name tag is eliminated.
I remember Tzuyu got eliminated last time because of a mistake.
She was eliminated early last time.
(Everybody knew Jae Seok was a trap.)
(Tzuyu was unstoppable.)
(She finished the game in 5 minutes.)
We only have to look out for Tzuyu.
However, if you think your dish is the first place menu,
you can find the platforms hidden in this building...
and say your answer to win the race.
(If you say your answer on the platform, you win the race!)
Is that it?
The platform. It must be somewhere.
- Do we have to find it? - Yes.
If it's the right answer, your team wins the race.
If it's the wrong answer, the entire team is eliminated.
- The entire team? - Yes.
We have to be careful.
The best hints...
are hidden in this building.
These are the different types of hints.
First, there's a hint about the first place dish.
Second, there's a hint about the location of the platform.
- Okay. - There's one each.
Plus, there's a hint about each team's Bomb Sticker.
(There are 3 hints.)
There are many hints.
Each team will head to their headquarters.
- Come on. - Leader!
- Let's go. - We're in trouble.
I think ramyeon is in first place.
- I agree. - So we...
We have to protect it.
I'm a little confused because I think it can be suyuk.
- Suyuk? - I think it might be better.
(They saw a hint on suyuk and start thinking.)
Is suyuk better?
When you first make kimchi, you eat it with suyuk.
- I agree. - It's never ramyeon.
Rice is all right.
- It has to be suyuk. - Then we have to keep that in mind.
If it's not ramyeon, we have to switch with the team that has suyuk.
With Jong Kook's team.
I don't know how this will turn out.
Do we have to let them rip our name tags?
We heard what Team Ramyeon was thinking.
They think suyuk is in two 1st-place hints.
- That's what they were saying. - Really?
- That's what Nayeon was saying too. - Right?
"People in their 30s and 40s would choose suyuk."
They said this among themselves.
What if it's really suyuk?
I don't think so because we saw two hints,
and people in their 30s chose ramyeon.
People in their 40s chose rice.
Rice was so unexpected.
That surprised me too.
They thought rice goes well with kimchi.
What do we do?
(Rice might be the 1st place.)
I'm certain people in their teens and 20s chose ramyeon.
I overheard, and I think people in their 50s chose ramyeon too.
- Is that right? - Yes.
Ramyeon has the highest probability then.
It is. Their team is in danger.
We're at an advantage. Nobody is interested in us.
- That's right. - I agree.
It's kind of sad though.
Even if people see us, they won't be on full alert.
We just have to search for hints like crazy.
Hints.
I'm certain about one thing only. It's not sweet potato.
I'm certain.
It's neither sweet potato nor rice.
- I think it's ramyeon too. - That's what everybody thinks.
Let's go for ramyeon first.
- We have to look for more hints. - Okay.
How do we distribute these?
People will think a male member has the Menu Sticker.
In order to protect it.
Who should take the Menu Sticker?
Somebody who will survive until the end.
That's you.
But I might get eliminated first too.
Right, people might go after you.
- What about the Bomb Sticker? - The Bomb Sticker...
should go to somebody who'll get eliminated easily...
(It should be somebody who's a good target for other teams.)
Or somebody who'll attack others well.
You can attack as much as you want.
I have to take the Bomb Sticker and eliminate others like crazy.
Let's give you the Bomb Sticker for now.
Give it to him, Jihyo.
Then I'll lead them...
into ripping my name tag.
I have to be a good actor.
This is difficult.
You should all pretend like you have the Bomb Sticker.
The person who has the Menu Sticker...
should still act like they have the Bomb Sticker.
(She understands.)
Okay, you take the Bomb Sticker, and you take the Menu Sticker.
(The teams decide on who takes the stickers.)
This is for the best.
- Let's do this. - Let's go.
- Go. - Let's go, ramyeon!
- Let's go, sweet potato! - Let's go, sweet potato!
Race starts in five seconds.
- Are we starting all of a sudden? - Five,
- I'm scared. - four,
- I want to do well. - three,
two,
one.
- I'm going this way. - Race starts.
- Okay. - Good luck.
Let's go this way.
That space?
Is that what we're doing?
- I just want to say "ramyeon" now. - Ramyeon!
Ramyeon...
We have to get ramyeon.
I think it's ramyeon.
Everybody is after us.
I agree as well.
Right? You think so too, right?
We have to find the hints.
(Team Ramyeon has to find a hint on suyuk and be on full alert.)
Shouldn't we find some hints?
I don't think we should rip name tags from the beginning.
We have to see the hints...
about the Bomb Stickers.
- Will there be... - There's one.
(There's a hint!)
Where?
- See? I told you. - This.
You're the best.
- Here. - There you go.
Suyuk is in 4th place for people in 50s.
- Fourth place? - See? I knew it.
It's certainly not suyuk.
- A box? - A box...
It's in...
So Min is looking actively.
(You have to find as many hints as possible!)
(She finds a hint!)
This is awesome.
- Tzuyu... - This is awesome.
(Tzuyu does a good job unlike last time!)
"Sweet potato is in fourth place for people in 30s."
- This is not it. - It's not.
What? Is this all?
Let's hurry.
What? That wasn't helpful.
- I knew that much. - I know.
That was awful.
Sweet potato...
Nobody is after us.
I feel relaxed.
It can't be sweet potato.
The five of us are a family.
It's gray.
- What are they doing there? - Suyuk.
Let's go towards them.
It's Team Suyuk.
(They walk confidently.)
It's Team Suyuk!
Is that Team Sweet Potato?
- Let's go that way. - It's Team Suyuk!
Girls, we will...
- Jong Kook. - Where are you going?
Why are they running away?
Why are they following us?
Why do they keep coming?
(Team Sweet Potato is the outlaw of this territory.)
This is driving me nuts.
Jong Kook, so many people are after suyuk.
- Suyuk? - Yes.
Why are you hiding?
- Sana. - Yes?
Are you worried about your backside?
- You must be hiding something. - Stop looking.
Is it Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?
We can't start ripping name tags yet.
- I know. - I know we can't.
We can't rip name tags yet.
It's not time yet. We have to find the hints and be certain.
(Team Suyuk leaves to find hints.)
- Let's go downstairs. - Should we?
- Downstairs? - We don't have the main item,
so we're going around too comfortably.
(They have nothing to lose, so they're relaxed.)
- Do we go this way? - Hold on.
Usually...
(Team Suyuk goes downstairs to avoid Team Sweet Potato.)
Usually, you can find some around here.
(They need a hint about Team Rice.)
There are no hints.
(Where are the hints?)
I found one.
(He finds their second hint.)
(He looks around.)
(He opens up the hint carefully.)
Then...
If ramyeon is in 2nd place, 1st place is something else.
(Ramyeon, 2nd place for 50s)
(Suyuk, 4th place for 50s)
(Team Suyuk's Hints)
Then it's either sweet potato or rice.
- I think it's rice. - Then...
we think...
- rice is more likely. - I think it's rice.
Rice...
(There's a higher probability that rice is 1st place!)
We have to find one first...
to know what it looks like.
(They meet with Team Ramyeon.)
Okay, Team Sweet Potato!
(They don't know who has the Bomb Sticker.)
Don't you have the Bomb Sticker?
Okay, Nayeon.
(They all act as if they have the Bomb Sticker.)
Gosh, this...
Rip it. Go ahead.
(You can rip it if you want.)
You know Team Ramyeon is...
everybody's enemy, right?
We hope we are everybody's enemy.
- Really? - Yes.
You don't think it's ramyeon?
You know we saw the last one too, right?
We have something else in mind.
There's a twist.
You don't think it's sweet potato, right?
No, we don't.
(Don't worry! It's not sweet potato.)
Sweet potato has nothing to do with our target.
It might be a waste of time to be after us only.
You should look for some hints first.
We need to look for some hints.
Okay, see you later then.
(They don't have hints about each other,)
(so they part ways.)
(They feel each other out and leave.)
- Why are you laughing? - What? That looked sassy.
Se Chan's name tag is crooked.
- Right? Se Chan's name tag was. - It was obviously crooked.
(Se Chan's name tag is crooked?)
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo was looking carefully at Se Chan's name tag.)
(He saw that Se Chan's name tag was too obviously crooked.)
That scared me.
Kwang Soo...
He's so detailed.
(Se Chan has a sticker. Is it Bomb or Menu Sticker?)
I put it on a bit crooked.
This is brutal.
(Team Rice is looking for hints as planned.)
They're coming.
Is it Team Rice?
- Team Rice. - Is it Team Rice?
They're not very popular either.
It's Team Rice.
We're Team Rice,
- so you're not interested in us. - We're Team Rice.
- We have no reason to attack you. - Who are you after?
We're after Team Ramyeon.
- Same here. - You too?
Should we mix...
half of Team Sweet Potato and Team Rice?
- Should we? - Should we mix them?
That's fine.
Have you had rice with sweet potato?
- That's right. - I have.
It's so good.
You add rice and sweet potato...
- in the rice cooker. - Right.
It goes well with kimchi.
Should we try it out for 20 minutes?
- Good. - Should we?
- We can share the hints too. - Of course.
When we get back again...
and if somebody is gone, I'll feel really bad about it.
- Let's not do that. - Let's promise each other.
Why would we do that to each other?
We have no reasons to rip each other's name tag.
That's true.
We'll both die if we keep doing this.
This is a new type of collaboration.
I agree.
A collaboration like this...
It's a fantastic collaboration.
Sweet potato and rice.
(This is the 2019 spring and summer kimchi trend.)
We should go that way together.
Should we go?
This is a fun collaboration.
(They'll meet back in 20 minutes because they trust each other.)
Let's keep looking for 20 minutes.
We have to find who has the Bomb Sticker.
We don't know which teams will become Team Ramyeon or Suyuk,
so we have to remove them first.
(Peeking)
Should we go upstairs?
(His betrayal instinct is coming to life.)
He was going to rip my name tag.
He was trying to rip mine.
Should I tell on you to Haha?
- Kwang Soo. - No, I won't rip yours.
- You were trying to rip mine. - I wasn't.
Gosh...
See?
- Tzuyu, - What are you talking about?
- he's trying to rip mine. - I'm not.
Tzuyu.
I have to call Haha.
(I am Team Sweet Potato, so I have nothing to lose.)
(If So Min has the Menu Sticker, that's great.)
Why?
Why? Don't do this.
I just need one hint.
Let's look for more hints.
You never know.
(It's fine as long as she doesn't have the Bomb Sticker.)
I don't have anything.
Rip it.
Okay.
- Rip it. - All right.
Go ahead.
Rip...
- Rip mine. - What?
- Okay. - Rip it.
(Will he really rip it?)
- Rip it. - This is driving me nuts.
(He hesitates.)
(I don't think Kwang Soo has the Bomb Sticker.)
Let's look for some hints.
(Should I just rip his?)
You can rip mine.
- Really? - Yes.
Really?
I'm going to rip it.
- Should I? - Hold on.
Let's look for more hints...
(She ripped it!)
(Bomb)
No way!
(Kwang Soo had the Bomb Sticker!)
(No way!)
What do I do?
(She didn't know he had it.)
(They gave the Bomb Sticker to the person who attacks well.)
(Kwang Soo had Team Sweet Potato's Bomb Sticker.)
- So Min. - I'm so mad.
(She should have realized when he was teasing her.)
What do I do?
That came out of nowhere.
That was insane. There are no hints.
I didn't know you had the Bomb Sticker.
You didn't know,
and you just ripped my name tag?
It serves you right.
What now?
You stole our cabbage leaves, so it serves you right.
(Team Rice is eliminated. Team Sweet Potato takes their menu.)
Let's look for hints.
(The other half of the team doesn't know this.)
It'll be really funny if we meet back later...
and are missing one person each.
We might all get eliminated while walking down the hall like this.
Team Rice is eliminated.
- What? - What?
(Team Rice is eliminated.)
- Really? - Why?
- Goodness. - All of a sudden?
- All of a sudden? Why? - Why?
Wait...
What?
It's ramyeon.
It's ramyeon for sure.
Let's go.
- No, no. - No, no.
No, no. They got absorbed. Somebody eliminated them.
Somebody eliminated them.
Is it Team Ramyeon? Will you tell us who it was?
(Who took Team Rice that we were after?)
Won't you tell us?
- Really? - Why?
Somebody got the Bomb.
- Somebody ripped it. - Is it Tzuyu?
Was it Tzuyu?
Somebody got the Bomb.
Goodness.
(They were just getting started.)
Please go to jail.
(There's no mercy. They have to go to jail.)
- Really? - Tzuyu.
Tzuyu...
Sorry for not keeping our promise. We were supposed to meet again.
I know. What now?
(The collaboration is forced to dissolve in 10 minutes.)
- There are not enough hints. - I know.
I thought they said there are many hints.
(Where are the hints?)
I found one.
(She finally found one!)
(What is the hint about?)
- Momo. - Momo.
- This is incredible. - This is incredible.
What is it?
(Suyuk, 4th place for people in their 50s)
I think it will be either ramyeon or suyuk.
- Suyuk. - Suyuk could be more popular.
(They didn't think suyuk would rank so low.)
That means it's ramyeon.
- What? - It's ramyeon.
- It's ramyeon. - "It's ramyeon."
- It's ramyeon. - Shall we go with ramyeon?
I think it's right.
- Okay. Let's go. - Let's go.
(They just need to find the headquarter.)
It could be at the store.
You are right.
Could it be that you just want to go to the store?
At a place like that...
(What is that?)
- There it is. - Where?
- Okay. - How did you find that?
(She finds a hint that was hidden in the corner.)
How did you find that? Good job.
(What does Mina's hint say?)
Someone in yellow has a Menu Sticker and has an "N" in his or her name.
This is an important hint.
It's not Momo.
It's not Jae Seok.
It's either Nayeon or Se Chan.
(It's either Nayeon or Se Chan.)
There is a good chance it's Se Chan...
because he looked very nervous.
Hold on.
(Is Se Chan's name tag crooked...)
(because it contains the Menu Sticker?)
Right? Se Chan's name tag must be hiding something.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's remove Se Chan's name tag.
(Let's remove Se Chan's name tag and get ramyeon.)
Shall we take this way to go to the first floor?
- Let's do that. - Yes. This way is...
They are here.
- Oh. - Oh.
- Oh. - They are here.
They are here.
All right. Did you find some hints?
We found many hints.
- Is that so? - Yes.
We searched for a while.
(They could remove Se Chan's name tag any minute.)
- We searched for a while. - My goodness.
(However,)
(they can't make a rash decision.)
Your hair grew a lot.
(It's a 50-50 chance.)
(They need a definite hint.)
Hold on. It's a showdown.
What are they doing? Are they trying to go that way?
I think they are fighting.
We looked for Team Sweet Potato for a while.
Really? Did you look for us?
What? Jae Seok!
(Something is strange about Team Sweet Potato.)
(Team Sweet Potato has rice.)
They took rice.
- We took out Team Rice. - I see.
Whose name tag did So Min remove?
(Who has the Bomb Sticker?)
We needed something other than sweet potato.
(Team Suyuk was aiming to get rice.)
Oh, that's how it went.
We need to go.
(They make a move upon finding out that Team Sweet Potato has rice.)
- What? - We need to go.
(There is a reason why Team Suyuk doesn't hesitate.)
There is a hint.
Someone in orange has a Bomb Sticker and has an "O" in his or her name.
You are good at finding hints.
Someone in orange has a Bomb Sticker and is a member of Running Man.
It's him. It's him.
- It's Kwang Soo. - He has a Bomb Sticker.
(They can remove everyone's name tag except for Kwang Soo's.)
Will you remove someone's name tag?
(Team Sweet Potato and Team Rice are still having a showdown.)
Se Chan has the Menu Sticker.
I will remove Se Chan's name tag.
(Team Sweet Potato has their eyes on Team Ramyeon.)
Here comes Jong Kook.
It's Jong Kook.
(Team Suyuk aims for Team Sweet Potato.)
Gosh, rice is...
Rice is probably the first place.
Please settle the situation.
- Get rid of these sweet potatoes. - Seriously.
- Here comes Jong Kook. - I don't think...
he is here for sweet potato and rice.
(He wouldn't go for us.)
(I most certainly would.)
Come here, Nayeon.
(Why is he glaring at us?)
Come here.
There is no need to get involved in that fight. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
- All right. - Let's rip off some name tags.
Team Ramyeon ran away.
Why are you crowding us?
- Let's do it. We need rice. - Let's do it.
- Okay. Let's rip off the name tags. - Let's go.
We got them.
Who has the Bomb Sticker?
- They are coming! - What?
What is it?
What are they doing?
(Team Suyuk's hunt begins.)
- Hey! - What is going on?
(He runs past Kwang Soo, a member with a Bomb Sticker,)
(and goes straight to Dahyun.)
Dahyun!
(Ji Hyo runs towards Mina.)
(They are ready to take everyone out except for Kwang Soo.)
(Mina is out.)
- Did she remove it? - Yes.
(There is a reason why Dahyun is running so desperately.)
- It's for the best. - Okay.
We must avoid eliminating someone with a Bomb Sticker.
(Team Sweet Potato's Menu Sticker)
Go ahead...
and eliminate everyone else.
Dahyun!
No, no!
(Before she gets help,)
(Jong Kook removes her name tag.)
What?
(The teams' menus get switched.)
- The menus get switched. - Yes.
This team has two menus.
Which one will you choose?
We made a decision before we came here.
- Which one will it be? - Rice.
- Rice? - Yes.
(Of course it's rice.)
Is that what you wanted?
- Rice. - You will switch suyuk with rice.
- Yes. - We like suyuk better.
Doesn't suyuk have a higher chance?
Rice? Why are you doing this?
- We want rice. - Is rice important?
- Really? - Give us rice.
It feels like a meaningless move.
(Team Ramyeon)
(Team Rice)
(Team Suyuk and Sweet Potato)
I have no clue.
This will end once we find a hint on the headquarter.
We really need a hint on the headquarter.
Let's look for it.
(Now that they have rice, they need to go to the headquarter.)
(Which team will find the headquarter first?)
There it is! There it is!
- Where? - There it is!
There is a hint. What is it?
Okay.
(They really want a hint on the location of the headquarter.)
Nayeon, you are really good at this.
- Let's go inside just in case. - Okay.
Let's open it here.
That was amazing.
You are really good at this.
What is it?
(The hint is...)
- No way. - No way.
The headquarter is on the first basement floor...
of Annex Building.
- You did a good job. - You did a good job.
- This is the best. - Let's hurry up and go.
Let's hurry up and go.
(They need to go and shout, "Ramyeon".)
Turn left.
Let's check. It should be at the end.
It should be at the end. Come here.
It should be at the end.
Gosh, they are on a stakeout.
(What should we do?)
It's too dangerous.
(I am sure Jong Kook will eliminate Team Ramyeon as well.)
Hold on. Hey, hey.
It would be the best to get a car ride.
(He is witty.)
Let's get a car.
Are you serious?
Nayeon and you should go without us.
You know what I mean, right?
- Shall we call a taxi? - Can we ask people in that car?
- A car came in. - Let's ask.
Jae Seok is something else.
How did he think of this?
Seriously. I need to learn from him.
Sir.
(He carefully approaches the car.)
If I may ask, where is this car headed?
This is the president's car.
(President?)
Is this the president's car?
When is he coming out?
- In 3 minutes. - In 3 minutes?
- It's the president's car. - Can't we wait and ride with him?
We can't do that to the president.
- We can't do that to the president. - Really?
The car belongs to the president of SBS.
Nayeon's confidence tells me she has a Bomb Sticker.
The fact that Nayeon has no fear whatsoever tells me...
- she has the Bomb Sticker. - Really?
I think Se Chan has the Menu Sticker.
- His eyes tell me so. - I think she is right.
- His eyes tell me so. - That's right.
I think Nayeon has the Bomb Sticker.
Where are they?
Team Ramyeon was stalling over there.
I think they saw us.
Why won't anyone come?
(They are still trying to hitchhike.)
Maybe people think we are shooing them away.
This way. This way.
- This way. This way. - Please come this way.
This way. Sir.
(A van slows down.)
- Sir. - You should go and ask.
Sir, are you busy by any chance?
In that case, would you help us get to that place?
It won't take long.
- Over there? - Yes.
Okay. Come.
Okay. Nayeon, come here. Hurry up.
Nayeon, hurry up and get in.
Go that way.
Hurry up and get in.
Thank you, sir.
(Nayeon and Se Chan take a car to the headquarter.)
- Let's go. - Let's spread out.
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok and Momo will divert attention.)
This is like a spy movie.
- Hide the camera. - Hide it.
Shall we wait here?
- Here? - Team Orange is over there.
(They stake out at an alley Team Ramyeon frequents.)
I have the perfect scenario.
Team Ramyeon...
fights against us and makes it to the headquarter.
Then they shout out, "Ramyeon",
but the crew goes, "It's incorrect."
Then the answer would be rice.
Then we can take over and shout, "Rice".
It will be convenient, right?
(They focus on the stakeout.)
If they come, they will see us.
(Team Ramyeon, come on.)
(Team Ramyeon is moving secretly in a van.)
You should go to the back.
- Hold on. - Team Suyuk is there.
(Team Rice is before their eyes.)
Hold on.
I am so nervous.
(They try to enter the building from the opposite side.)
If this plan fails, it will be over.
If they get caught,
- it will be over. - I know.
- Are you getting off? - Yes, we are.
Thank you. Hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
(While Jong Kook looks the other way,)
(they succeed to get off the van.)
Thank you.
(If Jong Kook turns his head,)
(their plan will fail.)
(Team Ramyeon succeeds to enter the building.)
(They must stand on the platform and shout out the answer.)
(If ramyeon is the 1st place, Team Ramyeon wins.)
(If it isn't, the entire team is out.)
Let's go.
(Victory is near.)
Now! Get them!
(However,)
(Team Sweet Potato and Team Suyuk suddenly come out.)
(When Team Ramyeon was hitchhiking, inside the building,)
(Team Sweet Potato and Team Suyuk found hints on the headquarter.)
(They will wait until Team Ramyeon's arrival and ambush them then.)
(Se Chan has the Menu Sticker. Let's eliminate Se Chan.)
(Team Sweet Potato and Team Suyuk are sure Se Chan is their target.)
(With any hesitation, they removed...)
(Se Chan's name tag.)
- No. - I got his name tag.
He removed my name tag. He removed mine.
He just eliminated me. He got my name tag.
- What is he then? - He's the bomb.
(They were certain Se Chan had the Menu Sticker.)
- He removed my name tag. - He's the bomb.
(Se Chan isn't the one with the Menu Sticker?)
He's the bomb.
(Then who are the bomb and menu of Team Ramyeon?)
(Se Chan had the Bomb Sticker while Nayeon had the Menu Sticker.)
You just eliminated the bomb.
What happens now?
(All of their menus will be passed onto Team Ramyeon.)
- He was the bomb? - Seok Jin. Goodness, Seok Jin.
(I can't believe Se Chan was the bomb.)
I did not see that coming.
Is this it? Hold on.
Let's go.
I'll start now.
- Wait, is it rice? - My goodness.
Why did we get suyuk? It's confusing us.
Where is it? Is it in the basement?
- I'm going to... - Is it suyuk?
- Nayeon. - count now.
Is it ramyeon or suyuk?
Choose 1 of the 2. You can pick anything.
- If you're out, you're out. - Should we go with suyuk?
(Contemplating)
(In no time, Jihyo is right next to Nayeon.)
(If her name tag is removed, they'll lose everything, and it's over.)
The first place is ramyeon!
(Rushing)
(She blurted out her answer in a hurry.)
(Is ramyeon in 1st place?)
(1st place was ramyeon!)
- We were right! - Yes!
- We were right! - It was ramyeon!
- Jae Seok! - Yes!
- Ramyeon won! - Amazing!
Ramyeon won!
It was Kimchi Special with TWICE.
The winning team is...
Team Ramyeon.
(Team Ramyeon wins the Kimchi Special.)
According to conducting a survey on a total of 500 people,
ramyeon won first place with 42.8 percent of the votes.
- That's quite high. - Gosh.
Therefore, Team Suyuk, Team Rice, and Team Sweet Potato,
will carry out seasoning 100 heads of Napa cabbages.
(100 heads of Napa cabbages? Is this really happening?)
(There's no giving up on it.)
(They really want to give up on these Napa cabbages.)
(Don't think about going home yet.)
- I will give you a chance... - Really?
to transfer all of 100 Napa cabbages to 1 team.
(It's their last chance to avert the penalty.)
(Only one team will face the penalty.)
Only 1 team will season 100 heads of Napa cabbages?
- Girls, let's go for this. - Let's do this.
He's the Mr. Cabbage for today's Kimchi Special.
- What's that? - He has the cabbage on his head.
That's cabbage on his head.
(Notice that he's not the pirate.)
He's cute.
A member from each team will stick in the sword.
The team that makes him pop out will season 100 Napa cabbages.
We'll go first.
- Sure. - Okay.
- We'll go second then. - It's all the same, anyway.
Actually, the bomb was Jeongyeon.
But the real bomb, So Min, will go first.
- Please no. - I'm giving you a chance.
(So Min had the worst luck today.)
So Min, if he pops out now,
- you'll be... - It will be treasonous.
Pop out! Pop out!
(Will So Min's bad luck continue?)
(If he pops out now, they'll season 100 Napa cabbages.)
(She's saved.)
(Team Rice passes for now.)
It didn't pop out.
- Sana. - Sana.
- I don't think I can do this. - Get the green one.
Do you want to go first?
(Sana doesn't seem confident.)
You must push it in completely.
I'm scared.
(If it pops out, they'll face the penalty. What's the result?)
(How lucky. He didn't pop out.)
(Team Suyuk passes too.)
Good job.
(Well done, Sana.)
- Should I try? - Do you want to?
(Chaeyoung from Team Sweet Potato sets out.)
Check if you pushed it in.
- Why don't you push it again? - That's all right.
- Okay, okay. It went in. - This is it?
- That's it. - It went in.
(Don't provoke the cabbage man.)
It's in.
Okay, okay.
(Team Sweet Potato safely passes too.)
(After going around once,)
(Mr. Cabbage is still intact.)
- Jeongyeon. - I might make it pop out.
- Come on. - It might come out.
- That's all right. It won't. - Good luck.
- Where should I push this in? - No.
Anywhere.
(You'll be fine.)
- Please save our team. - No.
- Not yet. - I think this will pop out.
(Feeling anxious)
(Just like she said, Mr. Cabbage really popped out.)
(Team Rice will face the penalty of seasoning 100 Napa cabbages.)
(We have to finish seasoning 100 heads of Napa cabbages, right?)
- We're doomed. - You must do all of them.
This is over now. Do they have to finish all of them?
Goodness.
Jeongyeon, you're incredible.
All you did today was stealing.
(She only stole the cabbage leaves.)
What are we going to do?
Get lost! You annoying jerks.
(He has lost his senses.)
- Let's make kimchi. - Let's finish quickly and go home.
- I wonder what happened at the end. - Yes, I'm curious. What happened?
(They still put a lot of effort into it.)
I should put a lot of paste in it.
Yes, spread a lot.
Make sure you spread it between the leaves and stuff the inside.
At this rate, who will...
Hey, do you want to do an acrostic poem?
- Pardon? - Yes, how about kimchi? Rice.
- I'll do one with rice. - Go ahead.
It's chilly. Do you want to go clubbing?
Continue.
(Humming)
- Isn't that an old song? - I guess it is.
Can you do one with kimchi?
A poem with kimchi?
I have one, Haha.
- Kim. - Kim Jong Kook.
- Go on. - Are you kidding me?
(Kim Jong Kook. Are you kidding me?)
Jong Kook isn't here, right? Is he?
(I was kidding, Jong Kook.)
- Are you kidding me? - Please edit this part out.
(In no time, they're almost done making 100 heads of kimchi.)
Put them in the containers, and your penalty is over.
(Put them in the containers, and your penalty is over.)
I'll be honest. From now on,
I don't think I can eat rice.
Then you should have multi-grain rice from now on.
(Haha will only have multi-grain rice from now on.)
You finished your penalty.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(See you again, our soulmates, TWICE!)
(2018 Year End Special)
What did I tell you?
(They will try the missions they failed once again.)
(We'll be back!)
(It will be a difficult journey.)
I should've gone there. Darn it.
(They face the return of harder missions.)
(Their destinations...)
(and their missions...)
(have become more challenging.)
(Their mission is beyond their imagination.)
(Before they accomplish their mission,)
(they cannot return.)
(And...)
(schemes and betrayals engulf the members.)
(Are they having an internal dispute?)
(They face the hardest mission of all. What will happen to them?)
Come on, Mr. Producer!
(Year End Special, Once Again Even If You Hate It)