Gosh, it smells like gingko nuts.
(You can feel the end of fall approaching this morning in Seoul.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hello, good morning.)
(Why is Jae Seok alone?)
You are making me nervous. Why are we starting off separately?
(Why are we starting off separately?)
What is going on?
Why did you ask me to come to the beauty shop?
Hello.
(Each member has an opening alone.)
Good morning.
This is a mission for you.
Why didn't you wait for me to say hello to the viewers?
Hello, viewers. Good morning.
Please move back a little.
Should I move back a little? Okay.
This is the first mission.
The first mission?
(It's out of the blue.)
(What's the first mission everyone got at the same time?)
What is this?
"Which member knows the most about the Running Man members?"
(Which member knows the most about the Running Man members?)
"Everyone must give the same answer in order to succeed."
One member who knows us the most.
Yes.
We have worked together...
for over eight years.
We know each other pretty well.
(Spending 8 years together,)
(the members came to know each other like a family.)
(Is there one person who knows the others the most?)
(Can they give a unanimous answer?)
I personally think...
I know a lot about the members.
However, it's a secret.
The fact I know a lot about the members...
is a well-kept secret.
Actually, I know too much.
As for Jong Kook,
I know every girl he has dated.
Oh, it's a secret.
Can you edit this part out?
He dated a celebrity. Please edit this out.
Recently, Se Chan has seen someone.
Please edit this out.
As for So Min, she goes around talking about her private life.
(Haha is the king of editing.)
I know so much. In any case...
(Who is Haha's choice?)
My choice is Jae Seok.
Jae Seok has been on the show...
the longest.
He is close to all the members.
He has known Seok Jin...
for over 30 years.
They were friends since their days of obscurity.
He and I have been in two major programs.
Because of that,
we spent a lot of time together.
He has also worked with Jong Kook since "Family Outing"...
and "X-Man".
For many years,
he has been a diligent leader.
That's why I think it's Jae Seok.
It has to be Jae Seok.
Who else would it be?
The member who knows the least is Seok Jin for sure.
I would be confident with my answer if that's the question.
Seok Jin knows nothing about us.
Seok Jin is only interested in himself.
Jae Seok knows not only the Running Man members,
but also everyone. I heard he has more than 10 TVs.
That's how he watches so many programs.
He knows everything.
- Yu Jae Seok. - Yu Jae Seok.
My answer is Jae Seok.
(7 members beside Jae Seok chose Jae Seok.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok receives the question.)
What is this?
"Everyone must give the same answer in order to succeed."
(Which member will Jae Seok choose?)
(Their answers will be unanimous...)
I know.
(if Jae Seok picks himself.)
Yu Jae Seok.
(He picks himself without hesitation.)
(Everyone picks Yu Jae Seok.)
All eight members have picked...
- Yu Jae Seok. - Really?
- The first mission is a success. - Okay. Come on.
That was easy.
I know them the best.
All eight members chose Yu Jae Seok.
- The first mission is... - Really?
a success.
- Did everyone choose Jae Seok? - Yes.
Did no one choose me?
I am glad we succeeded, but...
- I didn't get a single vote? - No.
I know a lot about them.
What are we doing today?
What are the rules?
We will have How Well Do You Know Running Man Race.
(How Well Do You Know Running Man Race)
Jae Seok, you were chosen by all eight members.
Among the eight missions the production crew prepared,
pick one mission and go to the member...
who would be the best at it.
If the member completes the mission, you receive one success.
If all seven members succeed, you can go home right away.
(It's an incredible offer.)
If anyone fails, all members...
will be dragged away and locked in the final location.
My goodness. My goodness.
(Dragged away and locked?)
(The final location has the members' name tags.)
(When a member succeeds a mission, his or her name tag lights up.)
(If they fail to light up all the name tags,)
(they must succeed the final mission and escape in a set time.)
(A big penalty awaits should they fail.)
If I fail, everyone will be dragged away?
I hope I am last.
I don't do well under pressure.
I don't want to participate in a mission today.
I don't want to be pressured.
You might think it's easy, but it's hard.
We succeeded one mission, right?
Yes, you did.
- Do I pick a mission? - Yes.
(It's time for Jae Seok to pick the second mission.)
Gosh, this is...
(Their success depends on how well Jae Seok distributes the missions.)
This one.
(What is the second mission?)
Ddakji Game.
(Flip over a ddakji at once to succeed.)
"Flip over a ddakji at once to succeed." This is my mission.
(He is really disappointed.)
This is my mission.
Gosh.
(This is a mission for Jae Seok, the king of ddakjis.)
I would be the best for this mission.
This is really disappointing.
Who can flip over a ddakji at once?
(Let's see who is good at it.)
Me.
(No matter how hard I think, it's me.)
I am the best.
(He is proud.)
I am the best. Everyone else is the same.
The person who can flip over a ddakji at once...
is either Jong Kook or Seok Jin.
(Jong Kook or Seok Jin)
We are two thirds there.
(Ddakji Game is all about strength.)
(Will it be the powerful Jong Kook?)
(He only had ddakji when he was young.)
(Will it be the veteran, Seok Jin?)
(Who will be chosen as a player for Ddakji Game?)
(Thinking)
I will pick Seok Jin.
Seok Jin's place is close from here.
Seok Jin has often played Ddakji Game.
In terms of experience, he is the best candidate.
He has played it for a long time.
- Shall we go? - Let's go right away.
(The second player is Seok Jin.)
Let's go.
(Seok Jin's place in Jamwon-dong.)
A mission like this one is pretty doable.
It's not too hard.
(It looks like we will succeed today.)
(If Seok Jin does as well as he did back then...)
(Seok Jin, please succeed.)
Heading to Seok Jin now.
(Was it the right call to choose Seok Jin?)
(He arrives at where Seok Jin is now.)
I'm getting off now.
(Where is Seok Jin, the ddakji player?)
Where is he?
(There's no Seok Jin. No one is there.)
He went to the restroom all of a sudden.
What did you say?
(Dumbfounded)
Why would he go to the restroom now? We're filming.
(Seok Jin was waiting for Jae Seok to make a decision.)
Today's weather is kind of cold.
(It's chilly, but Jae Seok isn't there.)
- I'm going to use the restroom. - Okay.
(Seok Jin left his spot to empty out some things.)
Why would he go to the restroom now? We're filming.
- Seok Jin, have you lost your mind? - What?
Are you here to work or not?
I wanted to use the restroom before you came.
You killed all the suspense. How can you go to the restroom now?
Why did you come when I went to the restroom out of all times?
- I've been waiting for you. - Listen.
- You know? - You killed the mood. Why go there?
(Something is off even from the first player.)
- I didn't kill the suspense. - I mean...
There's tension in the air.
- Always be ready for the tension. - Hey, even if...
- All right. - Okay.
For a part of today's mission,
the mission you'll try out is...
the Ddakji Game.
Gosh, I'm the best at it. My second name is Jee Ddakji.
- What did you say? - It's Jee Ddakji.
"Jee Ddakji"?
- No, it's more like Jee Booger. - Hey.
- Hey, no. I'm good at that. - You have a booger there.
The clip that I won the Ddakji Game is playing at the corner.
- I won the game. It's playing. - Where is that clip?
- What are you talking about? - It's playing at this corner. Here.
- They dug out a corner for me. - Where in the corner?
They dug it out and are showing the time when I won.
- What are you talking about? - I remember that.
(Don't you remember? Me, the King of Ddakji, Jee Ddakji)
(Please do well just like that day.)
Okay. You must flip this ddakji with this one.
You have to flip it at once.
If you don't, it's over.
(If he fails, everyone will head to the final destination.)
(All right. Let me warm up.)
(Struggling)
Pull this out.
You only get 1 chance. Only 1 chance.
- What if I fail? - What do you think?
- If you fail, it's over. - It's over then.
- You'll be locked up right away. - Really?
We have to complete the mission to get off work.
Only if we complete the mission?
(He can do this, right?)
Can't I have a practice round? Can I practice?
I'll let you practice.
(He can practice before he tries.)
(My instinct that he'd be good was correct, right?)
There's no re-do. You only get one chance.
- I can do it here. - Go.
Hit the center of it.
- Your vision is important. - Great.
- Look at the center. - I'll spot it until the end.
Look right in the center.
- Will you try now? - You only get one chance.
Start.
(He'll try right away.)
- Quiet. - If you fail, it's over.
This is really important.
(Let me get back my skill as the King of Ddakji.)
(He only gets one chance. He must succeed by all means.)
(If he fails, everyone will be dragged to the final destination.)
Make sure you hit the center.
Hit it hard.
Please.
(I can overcome this pressure.)
(Will Seok Jin be able to flip the ddakji?)
- Okay! - Okay!
(It's flipped!)
(I'm Jee Ddakji.)
We did it.
Did you see that? It turned twice.
- We did it. - That's how powerful I am.
- My goodness. - Didn't I tell you? I'm Jee Ddakji.
- All right. You... - Goodness.
- completed the mission. - Yes!
- I picked the right person. - We're having a great start.
Gosh, this was great.
- Seok Jin completed the mission. - This isn't easy, you know.
(As Seok Jin accomplishes his mission,)
(his name tag is lit up.)
Here's the next mission.
(They completed 2 missions so far. It's time for their 3rd one.)
(Since the beginning is important, he must choose a good one.)
Choose the opposite of what you want first.
Shouldn't we go with that one?
- What's that? - Hey.
(What's the third mission Jae Seok chose?)
"Witty Pictionary".
It's Witty Pictionary.
(Figure out the answer with a picture.)
Hold on. If that's the mission...
(Who's good at clever jokes?)
From a picture? If it's witty,
Haha is good at it.
(A lion falls into the soup. What's the name of it?)
(The answer is animal kingdom.)
(Will they go to Haha who's good at figuring out clever puns?)
- Or Kwang Soo? - Should we go to Kwang Soo?
- He's better than you'd expect. - He's pretty good.
(Kwang Soo enjoys drawing which will be an advantage.)
(Besides, his pictures are already like clever jokes.)
(Which one will Jae Seok choose? Kwang Soo or Haha?)
Kwang Soo.
- We'll get going now. - Kwang Soo.
- Where is he? Let's go. - Kwang Soo.
Let's go.
- Okay, let's go. - Okay. Let's go.
I'm good at figuring out those puns.
- You are? - Yes.
- No, you're not. - I'm good at it.
You're terrible at it.
- Let me give you a problem. - Gosh, bring it.
- I got this from the internet. - I'll get it right for certain.
Lately, I've been on the streets, giving people quizzes.
Just tell me. I'll get them all right.
(Wait for it. I'll get you a hard one.)
"What does it make when a bear stands on his head?"
- When a bear stands on his head? - Yes.
It's a door.
(He answers it correctly right away.)
- How did you figure it out? - Goodness.
Gosh, that's easy.
You're frustrating.
"What does a king say when he doesn't want to go to a palace?"
He mutters.
How did you figure it out? That was correct.
- That's a piece of cake. - You know that one.
Of course. I'm clever, you know.
(Hopefully, Kwang Soo can be as clever as Jae Seok.)
- Goodness, he must be here. - We're here.
Yes, we arrived.
- I think he's over there. - Where?
He's over there. He's in front of us.
(There's Kwang Soo, our player for Witty Pictionary.)
(My members are here.)
They are here.
(Feeling happy to see them)
I see the R Sticker on the van.
(He rushes to them as he's grateful for their trust.)
(They chose Kwang Soo for the third mission without any hesitation.)
Hello.
What's going on? Jae Seok.
Goodness.
(As soon as he sees Kwang Soo, troubling thoughts flood in.)
(Gosh, I'm not sure if he can pull this off.)
- Hello. - Let's go to the park first.
(With a heavy heart, they head to carry out the 3rd mission.)
- I flipped the ddakji at once. - This is a lot of pressure.
- It's for All-Success Mission. - Okay.
The mission Kwang Soo will try is...
Witty Pictionary.
Witty Pictionary?
- You have to... - With the given picture,
you must guess a term, associated to the photo.
- You only get 1 chance. - Just 1 chance.
Other members cannot give you an answer.
I'll take this seriously. When it comes to this kind of...
You know, Kwang Soo...
might not be knowledgeable, but he is...
- pretty good at... - I'll take this seriously.
How could you say that right before my important moment?
- You should encourage me. - Kwang Soo is...
A friend of mine told me.
You were once placed last in your whole grade.
Who told you that?
- I wasn't last in my grade. - Is it not true?
- Is that true? - I wasn't last in my grade.
I was the third from the back.
(I was 3rd from the back.)
At that time, I was going through a rebellious stage.
As if that's true.
Who told you that?
I wasn't last in my grade.
- I'm serious. I swear I wasn't. - Two students were behind you.
- Two students were behind you. - Yes.
I'm very close with 1 of the 2 students.
- Really? - Yes.
- Are you serious? - Yes. It's like...
he used to be my cutthroat competition.
We have put everything behind us and are like family now.
Why are you laughing?
Don't think...
only those in the higher places have a fierce competition going on.
- We're competitive in our own way. - We're competitive in our own way.
- The competition is fierce too. - That's right.
- Right, right. - It hurts our pride if we lose.
It depends on which one sleeps an extra hour or not.
- That changes the rankings. - It was...
- just like that with me too. - Of course.
- All right. - So you have to get this right.
I'll get it right by all means.
He's witty, after all.
- Here it goes. - Okay.
Kwang Soo, believe in your IQ.
(The picture for the quiz is presented.)
(What does the picture mean?)
Who drew this?
- This is a terrible drawing. - What an awful drawing.
(Burning, sizzling)
This is too easy.
- Did you figure this out? - Are you serious?
- You know the answer? - Don't you get it?
- "Burning and sizzling". - "Burning".
What's burning here?
- What's this? - The answer is on the drawing.
It's right in the drawing.
Is he bald?
- That's irrelevant. - Tell me the answer you have.
Go over there and tell him.
(Certain of himself, Jae Seok tells the answer.)
If it's wrong, what an embarrassment he'll face.
(He showed off that he was good at figuring out clever jokes.)
(Jae Seok is full of wits.)
(He's certain of his answer.)
Isn't that correct?
- Is it correct? - Is it?
- Aren't I right? - Is it correct?
- Aren't I right? - Is it wrong?
(Did Jae Seok already know the answer?)
- It's wrong. - It's wrong?
- What did you tell him? - What was your answer?
- Gosh, what was that? - Tell us. What was it?
- I thought you knew. - My goodness.
- I thought you were better than us. - Dear me.
He was bragging.
I thought it was "to be in a jam."
How does that even make sense?
- He's stuck here. - No, that's not right.
- Hey! - He's in a jam.
- Where did you get "jam" from? - Right here.
- He's in a jam! - Do you think it'd be that easy?
Really? That wasn't right?
- Goodness. "To be in a jam?" - Okay, okay.
- Go ahead, Kwang Soo. - My friend with lower marks...
really liked talking about that.
- That's all he ever talked about. - That's enough.
- Cut it out. - I'm embarrassed.
Gosh, how embarrassing.
It's been a while since my face turned red.
(He focuses on the drawing again.)
It's on his back. It's his back.
Is that his back or his bottom?
(Something on his back is burning.)
- Is that a pain-relief patch? - That's not it.
Is that a coal briquette?
(Is that a pain-relief patch or a coal briquette?)
(The thing around his head seems to be burning.)
(Pain-relief patch...)
That's it.
It's that thing.
- It must be that. - I have the answer.
- That's right. - Pasta.
(Kwang Soo is certain that the answer is pasta.)
(He only gets one chance. Is "pasta" the answer?)
(If he's wrong, everyone will be dragged to the final destination.)
(Pasta)
- That's correct. - There you go!
- There you go! - That's right!
- That's right. - Exactly.
(The pain-relief patch is burning. PASTA is an abbreviation of that.)
(As he completes the 3rd mission, his name tag lights up.)
- There you go. - No wonder.
No wonder I kept...
- smelling the pasta. - Exactly.
- I smelled it the moment I got it. - It had a savory smell.
- Pasta was the answer. - Gosh, that's the pasta.
- It was pasta. - That's right.
Gosh, what a drawing.
- Okay. - He's good at this.
- We completed two of our missions. - Okay.
This is our third success.
- All right. - Next mission.
(Pick the 4th mission.)
This one.
(Jae Seok picks one without hesitation. What is it?)
"Spin the Prince"?
"Lift Jae Seok in your arms..."
"and spin him 5 times within 30 seconds."
(Spin Prince Jae Seok 5 times with power and speed.)
(Mission complete)
- Like this? - This has to be Jong Kook.
We have no other choice than Jong Kook.
- Definitely. - "Lift Jae Seok in your arms..."
(This mission is for Jong Kook, the symbol of strength.)
Jong Kook will have to do it.
Definitely.
It has to be either Jong Kook or Kwang Soo.
- We'll choose Jong Kook. - We'll go for Jong Kook.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go!
(The fourth player, Jong Kook)
(To Jong Kook's place in Nonhyeon-dong)
Let's go. Shouldn't we give him a call?
(Let's go to Jong Kook's place.)
Gosh. They're always late.
Gosh. Seriously!
Why are you so late?
- What are you wearing? - This is in fashion these days.
- What's that? - You do this when it's not cold.
- I didn't know. - You wear it like this.
It's in fashion. You didn't know?
Jong Kook is getting more and more annoying.
(Jong Kook is getting more and more annoying.)
(Annoying fashionista)
All the others asked us to come to a park.
Why did you ask us to come to your place?
We have a very sunny playground here.
Look. What do you think?
- It's pretty nice. - Right?
Will he succeed?
If he fails, it's over.
Did these two succeed?
- Yes. - Really?
- I flipped the ddakji at once, - I did a nonsense question.
- He got a nonsense question right. - Really?
Okay.
All-Success Mission.
Jong Kook's mission is...
Spin the Prince.
- Who is the prince? - Me.
(I'm the prince.)
I'm the prince.
(Shameless)
I don't understand why you named it Spin the Prince.
Why would you?
- What's wrong? - I don't want to do it.
I'm not doing it.
What about Spin the Grasshopper or...
Exactly.
- Spin the Grasshopper? - Spin the Grasshopper.
- Do you think you can do it? - Let me spin him once.
Just in case.
- Wait a minute. - Like this?
What does it have to do with a prince?
Try.
(Spinning)
(The prince looks hilarious.)
- Like this. - Good.
- Good. - There you go.
That's not how you do it.
There you go.
(Jae Seok is hit hard.)
(The pain is indescribable.)
Are you okay?
(The prince is in pain.)
Gosh.
Jae Seok won't be able to have...
a third child.
It's okay.
(He has to give up on having more children.)
- Gosh. - It's okay.
What?
- My goodness. - Guys.
(Seok Jin notices something.)
We're probably going to fail. Devils are getting ready over there.
(Are they the devils who are going to take us away?)
(If you fail, we'll take you to the final destination.)
Let's be careful.
They're taking us to prison.
Let's do this.
Start! Let me start.
- Start. - Quickly.
- Good. 1. - 1.
(1 spin within 3 seconds)
(Jong Kook seems to have no problem.)
Keep going.
- He's doing it. - He's doing it.
(He can actually do it.)
- Good. - Good.
- No! - No!
(The prince slips down.)
Lift me up.
- Grab him somewhere. - Lift me up.
- We're in trouble. - Lift me up!
- Where are you? - Lift me up.
There you go.
Three.
(Jong Kook overcomes the crisis.)
(He spins Jae Seok for the 3rd time.)
It hurts!
Hang in there.
- You're almost done. - Hang in there!
Just one more spin.
(There is not much time left.)
Just one more spin!
- One more! - Please!
(They have half a spin to go. Will they finish in 4 seconds?)
- Stop! - Success!
- Done! - Are we done?
Success!
(Jong Kook did it!)
(They've completed the Spin the Prince mission.)
Okay!
(Is this a dream?)
Go away, devils!
(Embarrassed)
(With the 4th mission complete, Jong Kook's light turns on.)
- It must have really hurt. - Right?
I grabbed his skin.
- Hey. - Are you okay?
I...
I heard some noise. Are you okay?
Hey.
Jong Kook...
- This is so funny. - grabbed my skin.
Are you okay?
- How do you feel? - I was in a hurry.
He grabbed my skin.
(Jong Kook grabbed Jae Seok wherever he could.)
- He grabbed his skin. - This is so funny.
Our teamwork is great.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Success. - Success.
- Good job. - That was close.
Please pick the next mission.
How many times have we succeeded so far?
We have four more to go.
(What's the fifth mission?)
What is it?
(Is the mission so hard that it shocks you?)
So Min!
So Min. She's an actress.
I choose So Min.
So Min.
- Will she be able to do it? - Is she good?
(The fifth player is So Min.)
- We're halfway through now. - I know.
Things usually don't go this well.
- It feels weird, right? - Yes, it does.
Why are they so late?
Where are they?
Let's go.
This must be the place. Let's hurry.
(So Min is waiting inside.)
They're here.
(They're finally here.)
Guys, why are you so late?
- So Min. - Hi.
You had your hair curled?
- Why are you so late? - Hey, don't laugh.
- Bring out your emotions. - Why?
I'm in a good mood. Hi.
(Why shouldn't she smile?)
Don't you see the devils? They're getting ready.
- You have to do a good job. - What's going on?
What is it?
(The devils are ready to take them to prison.)
All-Success Mission.
So Min's mission is...
(It has to be So Min!)
So Min.
(As soon as they saw the mission, they all picked So Min.)
So Min's mission is...
(What's the mission they all chose So Min for?)
A Single Teardrop.
(A Single Teardrop)
You have 30 seconds...
to shed a teardrop to complete the mission.
You have only one chance.
Start!
(So suddenly?)
Already?
- Start! - Already?
Start.
(She starts to focus.)
(Everything depends on So Min now.)
Please!
- Done. - She's done.
(So Min manages to shed a teardrop.)
She did it.
I can't believe it.
It popped out like computer graphics.
She squeezed it out. She squeezed it.
- You're amazing. - Success.
(Is this really happening?)
Success.
(The fifth mission, A Single Teardrop, is complete.)
- How could you do it so fast? - I forced it.
Did you make your eyes hurt or did you bring up emotions?
I just... This is what I thought.
"If I fail, they'll beat me up."
(If I fail, they'll beat me up.)
- Really? - Really?
- Are you talking about me? - Jong Kook played a big part.
(The Jong Kook effect)
It's good that I was here.
(The devils are disappointed.)
(With So Min completing her mission,)
(5 out of 8 lights are on.)
Succeed three more times, and we'll be done.
We can go home.
Next mission.
You can't tell us to come back. When it's over, it's over.
- We'll go home. - I won't turn back once.
- Let's do this. - We'll go home.
- What is it? - "Person Quiz".
"By looking at the pictures of the eyes, nose, and lips,"
"guess which celebrity it is."
(Person Quiz)
Who should do it? Haha?
- Definitely not Ji Hyo. - Haha.
Haha is good at guessing. Se Chan would be okay too.
- Se Chan... - He's good at guessing too.
Haha...
doesn't know many young celebrities.
That's right.
(Haha is getting old.)
- He doesn't. - You're right.
- Se Chan would do better. - Se Chan...
- He knows a lot of celebrities. - He monitors many shows.
He meets celebrities in real life too.
He...
(What are you saying?)
- He's like a semi-celebrity. - Exactly. Se Chan.
- Let's go. - Let's go for Se Chan.
- I think he's near here. - We finished too quickly.
I'm getting worried. The weather is getting worse.
I think I'll be the last person.
I don't want them to put all the blame on me.
There he is.
Gosh.
Guys!
- It's raining. - It's raining.
As soon as we met you, it started raining.
Let's hurry up.
- What have you been doing so far? - It's simple. We've all succeeded.
- Really? - We've all succeeded.
What's the mission? Is it the same for everyone?
It's different for everyone.
- All-Success Mission. - Yes.
Se Chan's Mission is...
- Person Quiz. - Person Quiz?
You're good at these things.
- You know many celebrities. - I do.
He watches a lot of TV.
By looking at the pictures of the eyes, nose, and lips,
guess which celebrity it is to succeed.
- I think you'll get it right. - You have 15 seconds.
(15 seconds)
- 15 seconds? - You have...
- only one chance. - 15 seconds?
- 15 seconds? - The others had 30 seconds.
I need at least 30 seconds.
It's too short.
(He has 15 seconds and only 1 chance.)
Se Chan, come here.
- It's starting to rain a lot. - Here we go.
- One, - Let's do this.
two...
(The eyes, nose, and lips will be revealed.)
Three.
I have no clue.
- It's a woman. - It's...
(I think I know.)
Se Chan.
Isn't it...
You know many celebrities. You watch a lot of TV.
(Whose eyes, nose, and lips are they?)
I know the answer.
I'm very observant.
(He finally realizes who it is.)
(What is Se Chan's answer?)
- Who is it? - Jennie.
(Se Chan's answer is Jennie.)
(If Jennie is the answer, they clear 6 missions consecutively.)
(If it's wrong, everyone will be locked up.)
(What's the result?)
It's correct.
(The answer is Jennie.)
(Se Chan clears the mission.)
- I know many celebrities. - That was amazing.
I would have not known.
- I had no idea. - You're amazing.
All of us might clear a mission.
(They cleared 6 missions so far.)
That was great.
Didn't I tell you that questions were well assigned?
Okay, let's go.
- Here you go. - How did he guess that?
(What's the next mission?)
"Common sense".
(It's a common sense question.)
(Seventh mission is a common sense quiz.)
(Only two members remain, Haha and Ji Hyo.)
It's a competition between Messi and Ronaldo.
(Will it be Ji Hyo or Haha, who both have bad common sense?)
- Haha is better than Ji Hyo. - What?
(Isn't Haha better than Ji Hyo?)
- Let's be honest. - Ji Hyo can't do it.
She's terrible with common sense.
(They're at their greatest risk.)
This is incredible.
- Haha should do it. - It should be Haha.
- Next is Haha. - It should be Haha.
- He's just in the front there. - Let's walk up to him.
- Can we walk there? - Yes, he's right there.
Really? Let's walk.
- Haha. - It's Haha.
We expect a lot from you.
Haha.
This is an important moment.
You must feel pressured.
- All we need is you to succeed. - I agree that you were successful.
All we need is you to succeed.
(Swish)
(All we need is you to succeed.)
You should have come earlier.
(You should have come earlier.)
I'm the best with ddakji.
Goodness, do you even know me?
- I knew it was you. - Jae Seok.
We spent so much time together.
- What about our time? - I know. Stop it.
We tried so many things together.
- I went there first. - Stop it.
- Is that so? - Stop it.
I'm so disappointed.
- Listen, Haha. - Why?
This one is your chance.
Don't be disappointed.
- Do this one, Haha. - What is it?
All-Success Mission.
Haha's mission is a common sense quiz.
(A common sense quiz)
Aren't you glad?
Gosh, you fool.
(He has nothing to say.)
I'm relieved.
You should've picked him who went to college.
We didn't know about it. It was randomly picked.
It's actually making me feel good.
- Doesn't it? - It's common sense.
You're better than Ji Hyo.
You got a unanimous vote.
What's the question?
Here's the question.
Which has the most number of teeth?
Number 1, shark. Number 2, crocodile.
Number 3, human. Number 4, snail.
- A snail? - My goodness.
(He has one chance to answer.)
(If he answers wrong, everyone goes to the final destination.)
This isn't common sense.
Snail as a choice could be a trap.
That's very strange.
Isn't it a trap?
It's confusing why snail is a choice.
It's definitely neither a crocodile nor a human.
Sharks have teeth in the front and the back.
I saw them.
So it's either a shark or a snail?
Yes, it's either a shark or a snail.
Why is snail one of the choices?
Why is there a snail?
What's the answer?
(The snail seems confusing.)
(Which will Haha choose, a shark or a snail?)
This is driving me insane.
(He's going nuts.)
Hurry up. We don't have time.
- Believe in yourself. - Five.
- Four. - Wait.
- Three. - Otherwise, we'll be eliminated.
- I have no idea. - 2, 1.
Number one, shark.
(Haha picks number one, shark.)
(It's over if the answer is shark.)
(Is shark the right answer?)
It's wrong.
(It's incorrect.)
(They fail their seventh mission.)
Is snail the answer?
A shark has 300 teeth on average.
A snail has 10,000...
- to 25,000 teeth. - That's right.
Wait a minute.
(Dark shadows appear.)
- Come on. - Are they taking us already?
(We were so close.)
We were so close. What a waste, Haha.
Gosh, we were so close.
Where are they taking us?
Isn't anyone coming?
Why isn't anyone coming? I waited for a long time.
(She's waiting without understanding the situation.)
(Moving awkwardly)
What's going on? You startled me.
Who is it?
(Ji Hyo is taken to the final destination.)
Where are we going? Wait.
Who failed? Goodness.
I heard the penalty will be terrible.
They said that it's a terrible penalty.
Apparently, it's much worse than what we've experienced.
They said that it's insane.
- We must be here. - We stopped. He's parking.
- Where are we? - Do we get out?
(The vehicle stops somewhere.)
- What's going on? - What is it?
- We're here. Wait. - Are we leaving?
- Is someone taking you? - Wait a minute.
- Where are we? - Who is it?
- Wait. - I'm scared.
- What's going on? - They're taking us to a basement.
Where are you taking us?
(Why are they taking them to a basement?)
I'm scared.
(Ji Hyo also joins them.)
- What's going on? - Who is it?
- What? - Ji Hyo.
She's here. It's Ji Hyo.
- Se Chan, where are you? - It's me. Come here.
Please take off your blindfolds.
(They arrive at the final destination.)
- What's going on? - What is it?
What's this?
Please take off your blindfolds.
(What's this place?)
(What will we do here?)
What's that?
(A dartboard?)
(They're plastic dividers shaped into a pyramid.)
- That must be the jail cell. - It is.
(There are name tag boxes.)
What's this?
- Lights are off on mine. - There are name tags.
They must be the members who didn't succeed.
(Lights are off on Haha and Ji Hyo's name tag.)
What's going on?
You only have one chance per mission.
You escape if you light up all the name tags.
If you fail, everyone will be penalized.
- All of us? - Everyone?
(Everyone will be penalized.)
Only 6 of us are lit because we cleared 6 missions.
Save me, please.
- We have to escape. - Which one is Ji Hyo's?
It's right here.
It's this one.
This one is Ji Hyo's.
These must be where shoes go in, aren't they?
- Are they? - We throw our shoes.
We need to put in five shoes.
- Put a shoe in each? - In each of them?
- How is it possible? - There's a dartboard.
Is there a dartboard?
It's a dartboard?
- It says "On". - "On" is written.
- What is it? - We have to hit "On".
Hit the bull's-eye?
- Goodness. - It will be difficult.
(If anyone hits "On", Haha's name tag will light up.)
- It doesn't seem easy. - You're right.
- There's a clock. - What do you mean?
What do you mean?
- Is the time running? - What's this?
(The given time is...)
- No way. - Let's hurry.
- The time is running. - The clock is running.
If you don't clear the mission within 10 minutes,
you will be penalized.
- Can we practice? - You can practice.
- Shall we do a simulation? - Let's hurry.
We only need to light two name tags.
Shall I throw it?
(It's important to distribute appropriate time for practice.)
You have to throw the dart inside the line.
- Inside the line? - Wait a minute.
You don't even know how to play darts.
- Gosh. - I spent my life playing darts.
- You went to a dart cafe twice. - Let's go.
- Go. - You can do it.
We only need one person to hit it.
(Bouncing off)
My goodness.
It didn't stick.
- Is that a fail? - She failed.
- It doesn't stick. - Why didn't mine stick?
(She throws it easily.)
(It sticks near the target.)
That was so close.
It was so close.
She's good at everything.
- We don't have time. - She did well the first time.
Throw it harder than you think.
(What?)
(He chooses his own target.)
What have you done?
What is he doing?
(It's harder to hit that spot.)
- What have you done? - Where's your target?
- It could have been dangerous. - What did you do?
He threw a dart toward the camera.
- He's worse than Ji Hyo. - Kwang Soo.
That was incredible.
That was so incredible.
I'm not good at playing darts.
Unless you throw it hard, it won't stick.
- Ji Hyo didn't throw it hard. - It won't stick.
Don't step beyond the line.
- Hold him back. Go straight. - Okay.
- Pull his leg. - That's right.
- That's not how you play darts. - That's right.
(He takes a better aim with long arms and legs.)
- Go closer. - That's good.
Can you grab his hand?
You can go closer.
- Throw it. - It's "The Creation of Adam".
Go.
Throw it.
You got it.
- Throw it. - Throw it.
- Goodness. - That was close.
(It didn't stick.)
- That was close. - Is something wrong with the board?
This isn't working.
- It's difficult. - It's difficult.
The darts won't stick.
We don't have time.
- Let's get our shoes ready. - Shoes.
- We don't have time. - Let's throw the shoes.
- Next are the shoes. - We'll throw our shoes.
Get over here now.
- Hurry up. - Here we go.
- Line up. - Hurry up.
- Hurry up. - The top part is going to be hard.
That top section would be the hardest.
- We should all go for that section. - You know I'm good at this, right?
You'll definitely succeed.
(After bouncing off the second section,)
(it goes back in.)
- That's a good one. - Nice!
How should we do the top part?
Let me try.
(Will Ji Hyo get the hang of the shoe game too?)
(It hits the first section...)
(and then bounces off.)
That was close.
(She might succeed in the real game.)
That was so close.
- She did well. - That was close.
Good!
Good job, So Min.
(Even if you aim for the first section,)
(it's hard to succeed.)
- Gosh. - You're so bad.
Why were you being so ambitious?
I was aiming for the bottom part.
- Can you hold my hand? - Okay.
Everyone hold his hand.
- Can I lean forward? - Are we doing this again?
You can go even further.
- A little further. - You have to lean forward.
- A bit further. - Even further.
- Further. - There you go.
Can you throw your shoe?
It looks promising.
(I trust my body to the other members.)
- A bit further. - Even further.
Can you throw your shoe?
(I'm flying.)
(The heroine had the hero behind her back...)
(to hold her hands.)
(Behind me is...)
Who is pulling my hair?
(They pull Kwang Soo's hair with love.)
We'll hold your hair.
We'll hold it.
(From head to toe, he gives his body to the members.)
Straighten your leg.
(Throwing)
There you go!
(It lands in the fifth section easily.)
That wasn't what we were going for!
(We were going for the first section!)
Everyone can do this.
Who can't do this?
- Gosh. - It might bounce off.
- It's not that easy. - It might bounce off.
- It might bounce off. - The top section is the hardest.
(The top section is definitely the hardest.)
- It's too hard. - Let's hurry up.
We're running out of time.
- We have limited time. - Let's hurry up.
- We should hurry up. - Let's do the shoe game first.
- The shoe game. - We'll start the shoe game.
Hurry up!
If we fail once, it's over.
- Start! - Start!
- We have to hurry up. - Hurry up!
Line up.
(They have to hurry up and focus at the same time.)
Okay!
Move on.
Line up.
(Is he going for the first section?)
- Okay! - Okay!
Good.
(Just like during practice, his shoe goes into the second section.)
Good!
- It's amazing. - It's unbelievable.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
Fail.
(It bounces off the wall.)
- It almost went in. - It bounces off.
It's hard.
Start!
(Seok Jin has been the dark horse lately.)
(Everything he wishes for comes true.)
(As soon as he shouts, "Start",)
(it brings success.)
(Jee's magic takes over the world.)
Start!
(Will his magic work this time too?)
Which one do you want? The farthest one?
That's the most difficult one.
(On its way to the third section, the shoe bounces off.)
(Will it end up in the first section?)
(Jee's magic comes to an end.)
It bounced out.
- Focus. - What's with you?
- Just ask to let it go. - Okay, So Min.
Let's go for the closet first.
I'll go for a close one.
- The middle... - We don't have much time, do we?
- Hurry up. - Start.
(So Min casually throws her shoes.)
- Okay! - Two more to go.
If you fail, it'll be a shame.
(The 1st and 5th sections are left.)
Hurry.
(The 6th player, Haha, throws his shoe.)
- Okay! - Yes!
(Haha's shoe lands in the first section.)
(It's hard to believe.)
- Unbelievable. - It's Kwang Soo's turn.
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- We can do this. - Kwang Soo.
(We just have to repeat what we did during practice.)
- Keep going. - We can do this.
- Even further. - We've done this.
(The tip of Kwang Soo's foot...)
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
(Everyone's fate relies on Kwang Soo's foot.)
You can do this.
Stay calm.
- Focus. - Focus.
(We need to become one...)
(to turn on Ji Hyo's light.)
We can do this. We've done this before.
(We work together...)
Kwang Soo.
(We work together to succeed.)
(It bounces off Se Chan's shoe.)
(It's in!)
It's in.
(Kwang Soo didn't do this alone.)
(He did it with his team.)
He made it. It's in.
We succeeded.
We saved Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo's light is on.
- We need to save Haha now. - Save me.
We have to win in darts too.
- It's connected to my light. - Darts.
It's hard. We have to hurry up.
This is unbelievable.
(They have to succeed in 3 minutes to escape from the place.)
- You did an amazing job. - I spent three years playing darts.
- Really? - In Donam-dong...
- We don't have much time. - That's enough.
Your arm shouldn't go back.
- It didn't go back. - Hurry up.
1, 2, 3. Start!
(How good is he?)
What's with you?
Why didn't it go in? I threw it hard.
It bounced off.
There's something wrong with the board.
Gosh, it's hard.
- It's hard. - We need to hurry up.
Let me start.
(He looks stable.)
(The dart makes a perfect arc.)
It hit the board.
It hit "ON".
(That was close.)
(It did hit "ON"...)
(and fell.)
It hit the board.
It hit "ON".
- It hit "ON". - Normally,
you shouldn't throw it like a baseball.
- But we have to do it here. - Okay.
- Like this? - Like this.
- Should we throw it hard? - Yes.
Very hard?
It perfectly hit "ON", right?
(Darts seems to be a lot harder.)
(Time is running out.)
(Se Chan gets ready to throw the dart like a baseball.)
It works if you throw it hard.
(The dart went into the board.)
(The 4th player, Haha, gets ready.)
I can't do that.
We don't have much time!
(There are 2 minutes and 4 players left.)
It should make an arc.
(The 5th player, So Min, fails.)
Please save me.
(The ace, Ji Hyo, is ready.)
(Will she make a miracle happen?)
(Even Ji Hyo fails.)
We have to save Haha.
It's not just Haha, we have to save the whole team.
(There are only two players left.)
(High strength)
(Low accuracy)
(Jae Seok)
(High accuracy)
(Low strength)
(Kwang Soo)
(If their strengths can be combined, they'll be able to succeed.)
(Will they fail to escape?)
We have to save Haha.
(Their fate relies on these two guys' hands.)
It's not just Haha, we have to save the whole team.
There you go!
What?
(He hit the target right in the center.)
(What just happened?)
Unbelievable.
- You did it. - Good job.
(With Jae Seok hitting the mark, the time stops.)
You did it.
- What did I just do? - He did it.
- It gave me goosebumps. - Haha's light is on.
Haha's light is one.
We did it!
(Haha's light is on.)
- We succeeded. How did you do it? - We did it.
How is this possible?
- What just happened? - Did we really make it?
- He just casually threw it. - What did I do?
I can't believe it.
You've completed the mission.
It feels weird.
You managed to turn on all of the eight lights...
- within the given time. - I can't believe it.
You can now get out of this building...
and go home.
We can go home?
(They can go home.)
- We can go home? - We can go home?
- Are we really done? - We can go home?
- Is it okay? - Yes.
- We can really go home? - We can go home?
We finished shooting before the stock market closes.
(The stock market closes at 3:30pm.)
This has never happened before.
- We're done? - We can go home.
- Ji Hyo. - We're really done?
- Can we really go home? - Bye.
- Thank you for today. - This is a new record.
I should go to the gym.
(After some unexpected rest, they meet for the next shooting.)
- Hi. - Hi.
(A university campus in Paju)
It's suddenly so cold today,
but it's very sunny.
- It's perfect. - It's very sunny.
Jong Kook is finally wearing pants!
Oh, my.
Winter is here.
- Today... - It's already winter.
we're shooting in Paju.
- You almost made me cry. - Why?
You're wearing pants a bit earlier than the past years.
(You're wearing pants a bit earlier than the past years.)
You don't normally wear them until November.
It's about two weeks earlier this year.
(Is he really okay?)
At night, it's a lot colder here than in Seoul.
I'm disappointed.
You started wearing pants around mid-December.
(Everyone gets old.)
It makes me sad.
Did Jong Kook get weaker?
Get over it, Jong Kook.
"Get over it"?
- Okay. - Okay, okay.
- Aren't you cold? - I'm not.
- Aren't you cold? - I'm warm.
Does your youngest child take after you?
(Does your youngest child take after you?)
I'm not sure yet.
- I want to know. - I'm not sure yet.
- She's still a baby. - She's still a baby.
Her face becomes more defined after 2 to 3 weeks.
You must be anxious every day.
(You must be anxious every day.)
I'm very anxious these days.
(We hope that she doesn't take after him.)
- I'm anxious. - She should take after her mom.
- She should take after her mom. - That's right.
I'm praying a lot these days.
Usually, the eldest takes after the father.
- Really? - Yes.
- Aren't you relieved? - She's the youngest.
She'll be okay since she's the youngest.
- Is that so? - Yes.
The nose of my child...
didn't look like mine when he was young.
(He talks about his son Hyun Woo.)
- Then? - When he turned 12,
- his nose got bigger. - Really?
- It became... - Did it get bigger?
- When he was 12? - It grew like a mushroom.
That's not good.
- It got... - Did it get wider?
His nose got wider.
- His nose became wider. - Hyun Woo is handsome.
He is handsome.
- Hyun Woo is very handsome. - He's also tall.
- He was amazing. - Sons take after their mother.
Daughters take after their father.
- That's right. - She can get braces.
For today, could you take it off?
(Could you take off the black cloth?)
There's something underneath.
- What is it? - What is it?
(What is that?)
(Mysterious objects stand on the side.)
- Both of them? - Take them off.
We'll take them off.
(What is it?)
- What's that? - What?
- What? - What is it?
(The staff has prepared...)
(the last traitor that remains in the science of 21st century.)
(Shocked)
This is the worst.
That looks scary.
Why didn't you get rid of the mustache?
My goodness.
It's okay.
(It will make them burst out laughing.)
(What could it be?)
(It's made with advanced computer graphics.)
They're combined.
(What will happen...)
(when So Min meets other male members?)
(Horrible)
(What will happen...)
(when Ji Hyo meets other male members?)
(Silly-looking faces)
(He winces.)
- It's the worst. - It's the worst.
It really is.
Se Chan plus So Min looks terrible.
Look at that.
One person had such a big influence.
(It's just Se Chan.)
I'm so ugly. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(Se Chan's genes eliminates So Min's.)
Mixing with my face is a penalty.
This happens when their daughter takes after her father.
No way.
(This happens when their daughter takes after her father.)
I must have a son.
It's the worst.
(It's terrible to imagine.)
- It's so funny. - Se Chan with Ji Hyo...
look okay.
No matter how pretty she is...
When Se Chan is involved, the face gets ugly.
Let's never be together.
You have such strong features.
Goodness.
Don't give birth to a daughter.
He's a champion. I'm so sorry.
This one looks like a handsome man.
(It's Ji Hyo and Haha.)
Why didn't you get rid of the mustache?
Why did you add the mustache?
This one looks perverted.
This one looks gross.
- Kwang Soo. - Listen.
Haha and So Min's looks like a man with long hair.
It looks like Sung Hoon.
So Min, ours looks okay without the mustache.
(Is it just the mustache?)
Kwang Soo and So Min.
It looks like Ae Bong from "The Sound of Your Heart".
(He points to So Min and Kwang Soo.)
- This is... - You're right.
definitely it.
Kwang Soo and So Min's mix looks annoying.
What did he say? Why does it look annoying?
- The face is attractive. - It's very annoying.
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo's mix looks sad.
"Sad"?
It looks very sad.
It looks creepy.
I can see both of our faces, and it's creepy.
Isn't with Jong Kook the best?
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's mix looks just like Ji Hyo.
Me and Ji Hyo together looks the best.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's mix looks pretty.
It'd be great if we have a daughter.
Me and Seok Jin looks okay too.
- It looks good. - Seok Jin and Ji Hyo?
The lower part is similar to mine.
Me and Ji Hyo's looks intelligent.
- Doesn't it look okay? - Yes.
- It looks like a doctor. - It looks intelligent.
It'd be perfect as a doctor.
The photos that involve me look smart.
This one looks like someone who's smart.
It's someone successful. This one is still a student.
(It's a senior in high school.)
Jae Seok, this one looks like Park Hwi Soon.
It's definitely Hwi Soon.
It's Park Hwi Soon.
Me and So Min's doesn't look anything like us.
So Min.
You and Seok Jin look horrible.
What are you talking about? It's not bad.
(It's Seok Jin with short hair.)
- Seok Jin's nose is apparent. - I know.
- This is incredible. - They look okay.
The technology has advanced. They look natural.
I cried because it was so funny.
Did you enjoy the photos?
- Why did you make these? - Why?
All of a sudden?
Here's the secret to the photos.
Today is a couple race called Familiar Partner.
"Familiar Partner"?
It's a couple race.
It's people that we know.
Behind these four doors,
there are four female returning guests whom you know.
Today,
you'll look at rendered photos.
Then you will pick the partner you like.
- Is that so? - As a couple?
Do you have the rendered photos?
Guests will accept the partner if they wish.
If not,
you may let others choose him.
Two members who aren't chosen will be picked by Ji Hyo and So Min.
They'll be generous enough to pair up with them.
- That's sweet. - Gosh.
So Min and Ji Hyo...
will be saving those who aren't chosen.
From their perspective,
they may not be happy.
Right.
Everyone might try not to be chosen.
- You're right. - That's possible.
(We never know.)
(What kind of couples will form?)
- Shall we take a look? - Reveal the photos.
Who are the guests?
Anyone with me will look terrible.
(Who has the best genes will be clear.)
(4 familiar partners)
(How will their rendered photos look?)
(It's beyond imagination.)
- What are these? - Don't.
- Look at this. - Stop it.
I feel terrible for them.
- She's beautiful. - Let's start with this person.
- She's beautiful. - She is.
She's very...
The first guest is really beautiful.
She's pretty. Who is she?
- Look at this. - You're right.
She's beautiful.
Me and her look good, right?
- It looks good. - It's not bad at all.
- It looks good. - It looks great.
Her face rendered with mine looks beautiful.
- She looks good with Seok Jin. - Look at mine.
Look at mine.
Mine looks beautiful.
This one is with Jong Kook.
There I am.
My face is more apparent.
Jong Kook, your daughters would look pretty.
- All of yours look great. - Right.
Mine is great with a mustache.
- Haha's looks good. - Mine looks pretty.
- Haha's always looks masculine. - No.
- They look more masculine. - All of them do.
Look at the other ones. They look masculine.
They look so pretty.
- It's because of the mustache. - That's right.
It's because of the mustache.
This looks too masculine.
- Kwang Soo, yours is a success. - Kwang Soo's looks good.
- Yours is a success. - Mine looks pretty.
Yours is a success.
Mine looks pretty.
Se Chan's is...
- Se Chan's is... - Kwang Soo's looks good.
Look at Se Chan's.
His features are too strong.
- They're too strong. - Right?
His mouth is too obvious.
Even she can't overcome Se Chan.
I don't know who she is, but she can't.
Who can overcome Se Chan's features?
My goodness.
Look at this one.
Mine looks okay, doesn't it?
- She looks good. - It isn't bad.
The faces look masculine.
She's pretty too.
- She just needs braces. - This guest is...
- Look at Jong Kook's. - It's okay.
It has Jong Kook's features.
Jong Kook's looks pretty.
- It looks good. - Mine looks pretty.
- She looks familiar. - Mine looks pretty.
- This is masculine again. - It's pretty.
It's pretty.
It's very beautiful.
She's pretty without the mustache.
Look at her eyes and her cheeks. They look amazing.
It looks strange.
The second guest looks...
- terrible with Kwang Soo. - She takes after her father.
- Right. - Look at the one next to it.
Yes.
Look at the one next to it. It's worse.
Goodness.
(Kwang Soo's is not bad at all.)
(The real thing appeared.)
It's Se Chan's.
- It's Se Chan's. - Mine?
- What's wrong with you? - Really?
(You're terrible.)
- What did you do in your photo? - He ruins all photos.
I feel so terrible.
I'm getting tears.
You have such strong features.
You have nothing to say even if they sue you.
That's true.
This one is cute. Aren't these cute?
I blend well with other people.
Jae Seok blends well with others.
- It looks like an idol singer. - That's right.
It looks like an idol singer.
- Isn't this pretty? - Kwang Soo's looks good.
- Look at Kwang Soo's. - Mine isn't bad.
You can tell Kwang Soo's features.
- This is the worst. - My goodness.
(It's the worst photo of all.)
- It's Se Chan's. - It's Se Chan's again.
(Se Chan's is shocking and scary.)
(How does the rendered photo look?)
- This is the worst. - My goodness.
(It's the worst photo of all.)
- It's Se Chan's. - It's Se Chan's again.
(Se Chan's is shocking and scary.)
(How does the rendered photo look?)
This is so funny.
I'm sorry.
Mine's not too bad though.
This is what it is. 1st, 2nd, and 3rd sister.
(1st, 2nd, and 3rd sisters are all the same.)
(Happy sisters)
We should only say good things.
- Stop it. - He's right.
He has strong genes.
I think this one is the most beautiful...
- of Se Chan's sisters. - I agree.
She's the most beautiful.
She looks good.
- I don't think so. - She's fine.
What do you mean? This one's not good.
- It's kind of... - It looks a lot like you.
I agree. It looks a lot like me.
She's pretty.
(I'm pretty.)
She's the prettiest.
- She's fine. - She's the prettiest.
Doesn't she look kind of mean?
- She's scary. - She's kind of scary.
I agree. This is your first failure.
- She looks violent. - This is your first failure.
She looks like a good fighter.
- Isn't this a man? - It's Jun Hyun Moo.
- It's a man. - It's Jun Hyun Moo.
You have to agree to this.
I agree.
This is Jun Hyun Moo.
- Kwang Soo is pretty. - She looks better.
- The fourth one is the best. - She's pretty.
Kwang Soo looks the best.
She looks cute.
(This is Kwang Soo's best picture.)
- I like this one. - It's not bad.
- I like it. - His is the best.
Look at the last one.
(Look at the last one.)
It's Se Chan.
I made eye contacts with her!
(It's overwhelming to look at.)
I made eye contacts with the last picture.
It looks too like me.
- This is... - There...
There are so many other pictures.
(It's completely Se Chan.)
(He refuses to get mixed with anybody else.)
It's Se Chan.
(It's 1,000 percent Se Chan.)
This is a nightmare.
- Look at his eyes. - This is so scary.
Is she holding a deadly weapon?
Se Chan's genes...
- are so strong. - My mouth is a weapon.
If you ask me to pick a person that suits me...
(It's time to choose their partners.)
I think the first person suits me the most.
The third person suits Se Chan.
This one's the best.
- I agree. - It's the least bad.
- Number three for Se Chan. - Me too.
- Me too. - Okay.
Number three isn't bad.
She's pretty. She's my style.
- This one suits you. - It's not bad.
- She suits you. - She's...
- beautiful. - Is this one good?
- Is this one the best? - I say number two for you.
- I think it's the best. - I agree.
Take the picture you like and stick it on your chest.
- Should we? My picture? - Just our own?
This is really...
I don't know who she is,
but she should be in a commercial for glasses.
Did the guests see these pictures?
They haven't seen it yet? What should I do then?
How do I show her this?
Don't do it!
(So Min...)
So Min.
(She sticks it on.)
Don't do it.
It's so scary.
Don't do it! Don't squeeze me.
(Both So Min and Ji Hyo pick Se Chan.)
- Se Chan! - This is not fair.
- Me too. - Yang Se Chan!
- Yang Se Chan! - Yang Se Chan!
This should be your profile picture on the internet.
- This is driving me nuts. - Change it for a week.
I know. I really want this picture.
(Desired Partners)
Let's welcome the first guest.
I have no idea who she is.
- I wonder who she is. - I have no clue.
I can't tell from this picture.
First guest...
(Jae Seok's and her face were combined, but she still looks fine.)
All her pictures looked fine.
(Who is the first partner who looks pretty in all pictures?)
Han Na!
It was Han Na?
(Kang Han Na is like family.)
(She said ballet was her hobby, but she showed an old-style dance.)
(On Family Project, she went around the world with Running Man.)
(Running Man knows her very well.)
Kang Han Na.
(How have you been?)
It's Han Na.
It's Han Na. I didn't know it was you.
(Nice to meet you, friend.)
- I had no idea. - Han Na.
- How have you been? - How are you?
- It's been a while. - Han Na.
Did you see these pictures?
Look.
- What is this? - This is you and me.
- That one's not as bad. - I agree. Right?
- That one's the best. - Mine's not bad either.
How's this? Look at Se Chan's.
Se Chan.
(Collapsing)
- Hey... She collapsed. - She collapsed.
- That one's the best. - I agree.
This might not be true,
but she's comparable to Han Na.
- She's not bad. - Is it a tie?
Han Na looks too good.
The mom is too beautiful,
so even if the dad is this bad...
(He's correct.)
"This bad"? Don't say that.
- The result is very... - That's not nice.
I think the lips are mine.
- Is it? - That's true. These are your lips.
That's fortunate.
- That's important. - If these were your lips...
I didn't know the lips were important.
- It's important. - Second guest.
Please come on out.
- Jong Kook and Haha. - Number two.
- Jong Kook and Haha. - Who is it?
- Who is it? It's me. - Who has number two?
- Number two. - Me.
(She looks rather sophisticated. Who is the guest?)
(Seol In A, master of breakdance freezes)
It's In A.
(She made a mark with her sophisticated dance.)
(She was the first female guest to show off a freeze.)
(She showed great teamwork with Haha. They're happy to have her.)
In A. Gosh, In A.
- Is it you? - It's me.
This is amazing. You should grow a mustache.
This is amazing.
- He stole her. - Have you been well?
Jong Kook is awkward.
(In A, I chose you too.)
- Okay. - He stole her.
- Okay! - "Okay".
- Jong Kook is mad. - Don't be.
(He's scared.)
Okay.
- It's okay. I'm fine. - Don't feel bad.
- It's okay. I'm fine. - Let it go.
- Come here, In A. - Hello, In A.
You must be busy with a drama. How did you come?
It's over now.
- No wonder. - I missed Running Man, so I'm here.
Right.
(There's tension. In A's partner will be revealed shortly.)
Third guest, come on out.
- Third guest. - I don't know who this is.
- I looked at the face and knew. - Who is it?
Who is it?
(Seok Jin and Se Chan chose this partner but it's hard to tell.)
(The third guest is...)
Irene!
(This is her 4th time on the show. She's always beautiful.)
(She's a cute partner here rather than a charismatic leader.)
Irene!
Irene. Come on.
It was Irene? No wonder the picture came out good.
- Goodness. - It was Irene.
- Irene. - Irene, come here.
What's that?
(Are you shocked?)
It's been a long time.
(She's petrified.)
Irene, look at this.
She couldn't overcome this.
(Would you like to be my partner?)
No way.
You don't want to?
Look at the other guys. This one's the best.
This one's not bad.
This is Jun Hyun Moo.
(Haha plus Irene)
(It's a familiar face.)
Mine is the prettiest.
Irene and...
- It was her. - She couldn't overcome this.
(Who will be Irene's ugly partner?)
Last guest.
- Last one. - Let's welcome her.
I'm curious. Who is it?
(She didn't look too bad when combined with Kwang Soo.)
Come on out.
(Who is this guest?)
Who is it? It's Joy.
(Joy is Kwang Soo's ex-girlfriend on variety shows.)
(Her first ever partner on TV was Kwang Soo unfortunately.)
(With her slapping dance, she shook Kwang Soo's heart.)
It's Joy.
(He welcomes her.)
Right.
Look, Joy.
(How have you all been?)
- Look. - Oh, dear.
- I'm sorry, Joy. - Look at Se Chan.
(I'm doing well. Long time, no see.)
(I'm sorry for welcoming you like this.)
She's the best out of Se Chan's pictures.
Doesn't she look like a good fighter?
She looks like a school bully.
I'm really sorry.
- Is this combined with me? - Yes, I'm sorry.
(The effect of strong genes on future generations)
So we have Han Na, In A, Irene, and Joy.
(Welcome, our friends.)
Come on.
- What was that? - Let's go!
Today's guests are like family.
- Right. It's nice seeing them. - They've been here many times.
We've seen them many times.
As for Han Na...
- We went abroad with her. - Right.
Running Man helped...
- Han Na become famous. - That's true.
Running Man raised Han Na.
We raised her.
- On Running Man... - Through Running Man,
- we produced many stars. - That's true.
In A.
- In A as well. - In A!
According to your manager,
you were envious of Da Hee...
- when she joined Family Project. - Yes.
I was so envious of her. We came on the show together.
They came to Jeju Island together.
(She was envious of Da Hee.)
(They were both guests on Couple Race in January.)
(In A dominated the dance stage, and Da Hee stole it from her.)
- Good job! - What is she doing?
(How do you beat that?)
Da Hee even tied her hair up.
- She did that. - Before Da Hee came on the stage,
- In A was dominating it. - That's right.
- She did hip hop. - It was sophisticated.
In A, since you are here, can you show us the freeze?
(Would you like to redeem yourself?)
- Should I? - Fur freeze.
- Fur freeze. - Can you do it?
- What's "fur freeze"? - Can you do it?
Look at her.
She can do it.
Goodness.
(Are you watching, Da Hee? This is the fur freeze!)
- She's amazing. - Look at her.
- She's incredible. - She's great.
- This is great. - You're great.
You're incredible.
That was good. And then...
- Irene. - You two must be busy.
Thanks for joining us.
Congratulations on receiving an award.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- They recently received an award. - It's good news.
You both received the award.
Are you releasing a new song?
- Yes. - Yes, we are.
- Is it a new song after "Power Up"? - Yes.
We have to see it.
- Really? - Show us.
- There they go. - It hasn't been released yet.
- This is the initial release. - We're the first ones hearing it.
This is the very first time.
("Really Bad Boy" by Red Velvet gets revealed for the first time.)
(Skipping)
Red Velvet's highlight move.
(Sophisticated and cute)
This is the highlight.
(Red Velvet's highlight moves are always addictive.)
It's easy to follow.
(It's addictive and sexy on top of that!)
(It's provocative.)
(It makes their hearts pound.)
It goes like this.
(They're sexy and mature. This is the upgraded Red Velvet.)
- This is it. - This will be popular.
This is it.
My gosh.
- That was so good. - It's a great song.
That was a great song.
We have to...
choose the partners.
By the way, Ji Hyo and So Min...
are not saying a word.
(There are no male guests.)
They didn't say a single word.
(Was it too obvious? Were we too quiet?)
(When everybody was excited looking at the pictures...)
(During the dance time...)
(Clapping)
Are you doing this because there are no male guests?
We can pick the person we want to be partners with, right?
(What? You are going to choose one of us?)
(They're in trouble.)
Doesn't that go against the rules?
Shouldn't we receive a penalty for that?
(He's totally against it.)
But that's more work.
Let us...
Let us choose too.
(Don't disturb us.)
You can, but this complicates things.
Let us do it this way just for this week.
- You want to ruin everything. - She's mad.
- We'll now choose the partners. - Okay.
First of all,
- Han Na will choose her partner. - Han Na.
Han Na,
I have your picture.
I'm already here.
I have so many great memories...
- with Han Na from Switzerland. - That's true.
Do you remember the suspension bridge?
(Haha and Han Na had to cross the longest suspension bridge...)
(during Family Project.)
(Laugh, Han Na.)
(She's happy.)
(They completed the mission thanks to Han Na's laugh.)
- If it weren't for you... - I almost teared up.
Do you have anything special with Se Chan?
We ate together.
- In the train. - Train, right.
- Do you dislike me that much? - No.
- Did you erase that memory? - That's not why.
(They ate together for a short time on Swiss Alpine Train.)
(Can we order some kimchi too?)
(They shared some jokes, but it wasn't anything special.)
That's not why. We ate together.
- Do you have anything? - We were a couple for a moment.
- Is that true? - We were.
- We were. - When was that?
Didn't we have to buy something?
- Oh, right. - You... Hold on.
- What's this? - The sheep costume.
Black face and sheep costume.
- We were a couple for a short time. - Right.
You should remember...
that In A is by your side right now.
Well...
I just thought it was my turn to...
- I thought he picked me. - He didn't.
But...
I'm more popular than I thought. I was worried.
- I'm surprised. - Of course.
- Of course, Han Na. - We all love you.
I thought there would be nobody, so I wasn't sure what to do.
You can say something if you want, Kwang Soo.
I like you for real.
(Let me say something.)
- This is a confession. - Your hair...
- is long in the back. - It is, right?
Your pants are kind of short.
- It's nice. - They're short.
- I know who I want to be with. - Who is it?
No way. Think carefully.
(She has more candidates than expected. Who will she choose?)
(Original candidate is Jae Seok.)
(Haha has many memories with her.)
(Se Chan was forgotten.)
(Jong Kook was also forgotten.)
(Kwang Soo really likes her.)
2, 3.
(Who does she have in mind?)
- Kim Jong Kook! - My gosh.
(She makes an unexpected choice.)
- That was bad. - Really?
- Why him? Why? - All of a sudden?
Now Jae Seok looks silly.
I'm speechless.
Go away! Go away.
(He's treated coldly.)
- No way. - In A.
- Okay! - Right.
What is this?
(She returns Han Na's picture.)
(He switches to In A's picture right next to it.)
In A! In A!
Seol In A!
We can object, right?
We can object.
Let's see if anybody has objections.
Who wants to be partners with Jong Kook?
Me!
(In A objects.)
Oh, dear.
(Jong Kook and Han Na are confused.)
What's this?
What does this mean to you?
- What are you doing to Haha? - What is this?
(What? I thought we were almost partners.)
(He's bitter.)
Fine. I don't need In A.
(He returns it right away.)
No.
You can't do that.
- Irene. - What are you doing?
- Irene. - Hey. What's wrong with you?
- What are you doing? - Move.
- What are you doing? - Hey.
- Go away. - Hey.
- Look at this, Irene. - Move.
Look at this.
Look.
(That doesn't look too nice.)
Isn't it so charming?
She can go to South America.
This is a mess.
There's no sense of loyalty.
Then, with In A...
(Hold on!)
What's this?
Do you want to be partners with Jong Kook?
- Yes. - Yes.
(They object to Jong Kook and Han Na being a couple.)
Stop it, you guys.
- Honey! - Hey.
(I'm here, honey!)
Hey!
She called him "honey". This is no joke.
- Don't split us apart. - Honey.
- I'm going to break your arm. - Honey...
- Darling! - Go away.
- Darling... Darling! - Stop it!
- You guys! - This is a freeze for you, honey.
- No, no. - This is nice.
What a mess.
- Freeze? - This is good.
- Oh, dear. - Then Jong Kook.
- You need to decide. Han Na, - Do I?
- In A, So Min, and Ji Hyo. - I'm in trouble.
Jong Kook is popular.
I didn't know this would happen.
If I become partners with you, I can live with this face.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
(She's very serious.)
I didn't even imagine this.
For now,
you can say which ladies should leave.
- Those who can leave? - Yes.
Go, you two.
- Why, darling? - Stop it.
- Why, darling? Let's talk later. - Stop fooling around.
- Look at those two. - Then...
- choose between Han Na and In A. - Oh, gosh.
(Jong Kook's avid fans are left.)
What do I do?
(He's deep in thought.)
I have an acrostic poem for Jong Kook.
- Do you want to tell us? - All of a sudden?
- An acrostic poem. - What? Really?
I'm so thankful.
I'll stand next to Jong Kook and recite it.
- Okay. This is awesome. - She wasn't like this before.
(She's anxious.)
- Let's watch. - "Kim".
- It's an acrostic poem. - Yes, "Kim".
This is fogging up.
(She wipes it away.)
(Why is it fogging up?)
"Jong".
Is it because of Jong Kook's warmth?
(She gets close to him.)
(I'm a warm person.)
(What's going on?)
- "Kook". - Oh, dear.
"Kook".
Cute.
(Jong Kook, would you be partners with me?)
(He's dizzy.)
Hold on.
Why aren't you looking at me? I'm trying to be cute.
That's not why.
Me too.
- Me too. - That's not why.
(Han Na wants to do an acrostic poem too.)
- Me too. - Do you want to do one?
I think I can do it too.
Really? Han Na?
(Han Na as well?)
Han Na has something.
"Kim".
(Kim)
You put on long pants, Jong Kook.
(She noticed it.)
- Yes, you're right. - Han Na.
- Can you hurry up? There's no time. - Okay.
I'm taking long.
- "Jong". - "Jong".
Do you want to have chicken soup in Jongno?
(I do like chicken.)
- Jongno. - I see.
- I don't really go there. - "Kook".
"Kook".
(She acts cute.)
(This disarms everything.)
(Han Na's cuteness disarms Jong Kook.)
She did it.
- Her cuteness worked. - This is driving me nuts.
(Wiping)
(She can't lose!)
- This is fogging up. - "This is fogging up."
- Jong Kook. - Oh, dear.
(Of course I remember.)
Is Jong Kook that good?
- What's his charm? - Why are there so many?
- Ji Hyo. - We can't win, So Min.
Goodness. Oh, my.
I'm in trouble.
- What should I do? - You must be happy.
I haven't done this since "X Man".
- I have to choose. - All right, Jong Kook.
I'm in trouble.
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
- Do this. - Do this.
(Why don't you show us the legendary ear covering gesture?)
Hold on.
I can't do that. I should stop doing it.
(It's a legend in the history of variety shows.)
(He covered her ears so that she doesn't have to hear sad words.)
- We will see it in real life. - Seriously.
(They focus their attention on him.)
I want to keep this video.
I am curious about it.
Let's go.
- In 1, 2. - Gaze at them in a romantic way.
- Two. - Please.
(The one whose ears get covered loses.)
Three.
(Whom did Jong Kook's heart decide?)
(Cute versus Funny)
(I am sorry.)
Go.
(Go, Han Na.)
(Does this mean I lost again?)
Han Na!
The winner!
Okay!
(Jong Kook and In A become a couple.)
Han Na, go over there.
Go over there.
- Come here. - She humiliated herself.
- You belong here with us. - It's not like that.
I missed Ji Hyo, but she was too far.
That's why I came here.
Is this final?
- It's over. - No way.
What is Haha going to do?
(He returns In A's picture.)
Am I making the right choice?
(He picks Han Na since there is a higher chance.)
- Now, - All right.
it's Irene's turn.
Irene.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
- I know your weakness. - What is it?
(Hold on.)
(Joy suddenly reveals that she knows Jae Seok's weakness.)
- What is it? - What weakness?
(Can it shake his position as the national MC?)
I know your weakness from 10 years ago.
What is it?
(Is it a bluff or a truth?)
What weakness?
Whether I reveal it or not depends on whom you choose.
- What? - What weakness?
Is that a threat?
I have my eyes set on Jae Seok.
(It is a threat.)
- Really? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo throws Joy's picture.)
(Then I promise I won't have my eyes on you.)
(I am the one who picked you first.)
- What was that? - My goodness.
(Joy's revelation makes the competition fiercer.)
What was that?
This is fiercer than I expected.
On Running Man,
Kwang Soo is your love interest.
He feels a bit like an ex-boyfriend.
(Kwang Soo is Joy's ex-boyfriend on a variety show.)
Nothing ever happened!
(Be well. Don't get sick.)
- Joy. - Yes?
In that case...
What are you doing?
(He returns Irene's picture.)
- Joy. - Now...
Joy! Joy! Joy!
What is wrong with you?
Joy! Joy!
(One man silently changes a picture.)
(Joy, have a good life.)
Joy is my pick.
- Irene will choose first. - Irene.
Didn't you have Irene's picture?
- He is like that. - I switched to Joy's picture.
We can choose freely.
Pick Irene's picture for now.
Bring Irene's picture.
- I will... - He is so fickle.
You never know.
- Then I will reveal your weakness. - All right.
(That's not good.)
What's the weakness?
What is it?
- Does he have a weakness? - What's my weakness?
I want to know.
What is up with her? She visits the show and says...
she knows my weakness.
Come.
(Do you want to know?)
(She reveals it to Jae Seok.)
Running Man only knows one weakness of his.
What is it? Can't you tell us?
(Will Joy be able to become Jae Seok's partner?)
(Hold on.)
It's not a secret.
- Isn't it a secret? - No.
I heard it from someone who is closely related to this.
- Really? - Yes.
It's not a secret.
- What is it? - I had pimples 10 years ago.
(I am sure everyone knows this.)
- It's not a secret. - What was that?
What was that?
It's not much of a weakness.
Did I get dumped because of pimples?
Irene!
No, no.
- No. - I had pimples as well.
Se Chan still has pimples.
Don't get me into this!
- Right now, - What is going on?
we exchanged a lot of words.
The only couple is Jong Kook and In A.
- Irene! - Irene! Irene!
(They suddenly form Irene's fan club.)
- I never strayed. - Irene!
Everyone brought a picture, right?
- Yes. - Everyone brought a picture.
- Irene! - Give me a chance.
Make a three-line poem about Irene.
(Show your charms with a three-line poem, okay?)
The first line.
(Se Chan promotes himself first.)
What a picture!
(She is satisfied so far.)
The second line.
Irene, I will let you sleep at someplace warm.
- The third line. - Rinnai.
(He mentions a heater company.)
That was great.
(Se Chan is the best.)
Yang Se Chan!
- That was funny. - Good job.
- I'm sorry, Irene. - Yang Se Chan.
That was the best.
(He is number 1 in my heart so far.)
- It was the best. It was funny. - It was the best.
It was the best.
Rinnai.
The first line.
(Why did he have to do so well?)
Anything else will be the same.
- Middle-aged man. - "Middle-aged man."
(What is he going to say?)
- The second line. - Stop now.
The third line.
(The poem was ordinary so far. What will the last line be?)
- The third line. - Rinnai.
(He plagiarizes Se Chan's poem right away.)
It's hard.
(Although he plagiarized, it was funny.)
- It's hard. - Go to the end.
You should show Irene how much you love her...
with a three-line poem.
The first line.
- Let's go, stingray! - All right.
Go back in the line.
(After the first line,)
(Haha gets eliminated.)
That phrase is too old.
I haven't heard that phrase in a long while.
Irene wouldn't even know the phrase.
The first line.
I am your dad's friend.
Go to the end of the line.
(There is no need to hear more.)
(He gets eliminated since the poem is too realistic.)
What was that?
Go to the end.
What?
Why would you say that?
She is laughing.
"I am your dad's friend"?
- Why would you say that? - Everyone knows that.
- What was that? - Everyone knows that.
The first line.
(Jae Seok is the last.)
Irene.
- The second line. - Without you...
The third line.
(It's the hardest part.)
There would be no Rinnai.
(It's hard to tell if it's plagiarism or not.)
What was that?
- Irene! Irene! - Irene! Irene!
- Irene, pick a member. - Irene.
We won't hold grudges,
- so you can pick comfortably. - That's right.
It's only a game.
I have been overlooked for 10 years.
(So it's okay.)
I will pick...
(Who will Irene pick?)
(Se Chan, the first one to mention Rinnai)
(Kwang Soo, the plagiarizer)
(Haha, the one with an old taste)
(Seok Jin, Dad's friend)
(Jae Seok, the half-hearted plagiarizer)
(Among these contestants,)
I will pick Yang Se Chan.
(Irene picks Se Chan.)
(Se Chan and Irene become a couple.)
Are you serious?
He is so happy.
(Thanks to Rinnai, he becomes a couple.)
Yang Se Chan! Yang Se Chan!
I object!
(Throwing)
(Don't get in my way.)
- Get lost! - I object!
(Se Chan's family gathers.)
- I object! - No way!
Se Chan!
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't you dare ruin this.
(Don't take away my partner.)
Now, it's Joy's turn.
- Joy! Joy! - Joy! Joy!
(We love you, Joy.)
- Joy! - She is holding my picture.
She is holding my picture.
Here are all the familiar faces.
Hello.
- Hello. - We meet often.
I am here to have a new life.
I used to like Irene,
but I switched over to Joy.
- I am on Running Man for Joy. - Of course.
Let's make a two-line poem about Joy.
Two-line poem? Again?
(Let's see what you can do.)
The first line.
I really like you.
- That's good. - The second line.
It's you.
She hates it.
(She fails to school her face.)
(Was it that bad?)
It's just that...
I know he has a family.
(I know he has a family.)
What does it have to do with this?
Everyone has a family!
I don't have a family!
- He has parents. - I don't have a family!
What are you saying?
- I am serious. - It's your turn.
Give us a 2-line poem. The 1st line.
(The first line)
Joy is...
The second line.
Strange.
(Is he picking a fight?)
- Are you picking a fight? - Two-line poems are easy.
No, no.
Don't you like it?
No.
- The first line. - The nation cherishes this woman.
Go to the end of the line.
(He establishes himself as Dad's friend.)
- What? - How patriotic!
What was that?
(Every time he opens his mouth, he takes people back to the 70s.)
- He startled me. - Do we live in the 70s?
It was like the principal's speech in elementary school.
The principal.
Why won't you let me finish?
(He is annoyed.)
The first line.
(Jae Seok is last.)
Joy!
(Since he started off powerfully, he just needs to conclude it well.)
The second line.
You know what?
- Is that it? - You know what?
(What?)
- What was that? - Is that it?
Is that it?
You should have concluded it.
I don't know!
(He fails to show his charms.)
- I don't know! - If you want to hear more,
pick me.
If you want to hear more, pick me.
If you want to know why you are strange, pick me.
Do you want to know what comes after "It's you"?
Guess what comes after "The nation cherishes this woman."
I bet you are curious.
Pick someone.
The nation cherishes this woman.
I will partner up with Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo and Joy become a couple.)
- Come here. - In the end...
Why did you do that earlier?
I am sorry!
Gosh, you startled me.
(So Min tries to break them off out of habit.)
(Kwang Soo, our child is here.)
- Gosh, you startled me. - She objected.
(What is that face?)
- Lee Kwang Soo! Lee Kwang Soo! - My goodness.
(Stop bothering me and get lost.)
Three people without a partner should come here.
(3 couples have been born.)
We need to make couples...
out of the rest of the people.
For goodness' sake.
All of us have emotional scars.
- Let's overcome this. - Try to come to a middle ground.
- Try to compromise, everyone. - Now...
We'll partner up for just one day.
Let's just flip our hands for this.
- Let's flip our hands for it. - It's "Flaming Youth" here.
(You can't fool the atmosphere.)
(The middle-aged celebrities become friends on this reality show.)
- How could you say that? - "Flaming Youth".
Look at Han Na. She's in that group.
What are you talking about?
- What? "Flaming Youth"? - How could you say that?
- Will my wish finally come true? - Look at Seok Jin.
- My wish has come true at last. - His wish has been fulfilled.
- Hey, let's just flip for it. - You know,
let's be civil about this.
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - Right.
- Actually, I don't want to do that. - Okay.
I had a great time in Switzerland...
- with Han Na. - I want to pair up with Haha.
(They made such great memories in Switzerland.)
(Should we recreate that in Korea one more time?)
- No way. - Goodness.
(She sounds firm.)
Why am I so darn attractive?
- No. - I have a family with two kids.
- I have a family! - You're mine on Running Man.
- I have a family! - This is frustrating.
- No! - Then please let me dodge...
Seok Jin.
(She targets a niche market.)
I don't like you either. You think I want to pair up with you?
- Please. Please not him. - Okay then.
- Why? - Here's what we'll do.
Let's be cool about this and just point at the one we want.
- We'll get matched like that? - If it's mutual, you'll pair up.
- I haven't seen that for a while. - It's been a while.
- Don't drag this out. Be quick. - Okay.
- Once you're matched, it's over. - Okay, okay.
- Han Na, you're first. - Okay.
(Han Na chooses Haha.)
(How dare you?)
(Biting)
She really bit me. She didn't fake it.
You can choose now. That's right.
- It's your turn. - Point at someone.
(Ji Hyo and Han Na chose Haha.)
I want to enjoy this.
(This is the first he's been chased by two women.)
Don't make a fool of yourself, and just pick someone.
Shouldn't I listen to their acrostic poems?
Acrostic poem?
- Yes. - Then forget about him.
- Haha. - Go ahead.
(Chuckling)
- That was great. It was great. - She did well.
Ji Hyo.
- Haha. - Go ahead.
- Haha, you can't go anywhere. - "Ha".
- Ha. - "Ha!".
(Snorting)
- That was pretty good. - Goodness, it was great.
- That was quite charming. - She did a great job.
Me too. I don't want him, but I just want to do the poem.
- What is it? - Go ahead.
Haha, you're so sexy.
- "Ha". - "Ha".
(Letting out a moan)
(A deep sigh)
- What was that? - She's driving me crazy.
- She did so well. - What are you doing?
- You disheveled your hair. - Seriously. I can't understand her.
- Now, she's rising up on my list. - Seriously.
- I can't believe it. - That was cute.
- That was beautiful. - Both of them are such eyesores.
That was so cool.
- Okay, I'll choose now. - 1, 2, 3.
(Whom will Haha choose?)
(Han Na, whom he faced the penalty together in Switzerland?)
(Or his regular partner during couple races?)
- Han Na! - Gosh.
(He chooses Han Na, his partner in Switzerland.)
- Go, go. - It's over.
(Only the unwanted members remain.)
- Tell you what. We're already... - Hey.
- All of us here are wounded. - Hey.
I'm here to work too. Let's just focus on working today.
- Listen, since we're all hurt... - Gosh.
All of us are hurt right now.
- Let's just pair up. - Let's just do it.
- Let's just pair up. - Let's pair up.
- Let's flip our hands for it. - Should we?
- Let's flip for it. - Face it up or face it down
(Jae Seok and So Min pair up. Ji Hyo and Seok Jin pair up.)
- Okay. - Fine.
(They'll focus on working to the max today.)
Let's just work today.
- It's been a while. Green Siblings. - Hey, Jae Seok. Yes, that's right.
Yes, it's been a while.
(How will they perform during the race next week?)
(Joy is weird!)
(I should say that to you.)
(She's back with her weirder self.)
(These previous partners...)
(make a strange comeback to the variety show.)
(Why are we going this far today?)
(There's a reason for their hard work.)
(A thief stole the partner's heart under the name of love.)
(Deceived by love, the members are in pure torment.)
(What kind of a person are you?)
(Find the thief partner who stole the members' hearts!)
You never know what can happen.
(How will the flaming race of love and deception end?)
(Fantastic Partners become...)
(Crazy Partners)