(Previously on Running Man)
(Two weeks ago, Luxury Package versus Shuddering Package began.)
(They heard the good news that only 3 people can wing walk.)
(They had 4 missions to avoid wing walking.)
(Pirate Roulette decided who will have levels 1, 2, and 3.)
(Jae Seok got level 1, Da Hee got level 2, and Kwang Soo got level 3.)
(Jae Seok finished the experience as he screamed for freedom.)
(Meanwhile, Luxury Package in Switzerland)
(They had a train ride at the Alps and fondue at Observatory Hotel.)
(They finished the paragliding experience.)
(However, the tours had to be paid by the members.)
(A secret poll decided who will pay for each tour.)
(Jong Kook paid for the mountain railway train and fondue...)
(while Se Chan paid for paragliding.)
(There is a way to receive a refund.)
If you experience one...
(Experience one of the activities of Shuddering Package for a refund.)
(Who will pay for the luxurious trip in the end?)
You paid for the cost of paragliding.
With the cost of heli-skiing...
and the cost of dining at a Michelin restaurant on the line,
we will play a game.
(The total comes to a big amount.)
- I hope I don't get chosen again. - This one is big.
- It must be around 1,000 dollars. - It has to cost over 1,000 dollars.
- I bet it costs over 2,000 dollars. - It's too expensive.
You will spin the roulette.
We will give you a roulette with eight slots.
- Eight? - You will decide the rules.
We talked among ourselves earlier.
We came up with 30 games.
- The game we can readily play... - We can stay up all night.
in this hotel is...
Spot the Difference. We can change things in the room...
and find what changed in a few seconds.
You have a minute. Change up the room in a minute...
and spot the difference in a minute.
- Find 5 differences. - 5 differences?
This trio can be a team.
No, I don't want to do that.
- Why not? - Why not?
- Men versus women. - That's a good idea.
- Really? - It will be like "Family Arcade".
- "Family Arcade". - "What's the score?"
Hold on. None of us have a good memory.
That's why I made this game.
That's why he wants us to be a team. That's why I refused.
That's not true.
The two of you slept together yesterday.
- We... - Don't say it like that.
(Don't say it like that.)
The viewers will misunderstand. We are roommates.
We are roommates.
People will think we are closer than we actually are.
It's 3 against 3.
- It will be fun. - All right.
This place reminds me of "Guys N Girls".
- The sitcom! - That's right.
("Guys N Girls" was a sitcom that aired from 1996 to 1999.)
(Shin Dong Yeob, Song Seung Heon)
(That's right.)
I am Song Seung Heon!
- I am Shin Dong Yup. - I'm Lee Eui Jung.
- You are Hong Kyung In. - Am I Hong Hyung In?
Am I Hong Kyung In? I suddenly became Hong Kyung In.
- I am Jennifer Lee. - Jenny.
- Hello. Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Change up the room first. - You can go ahead.
Shall we go first? Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(The team that answers the question observes the room for 30 seconds.)
When you open the door, we will be ready.
You have 30 seconds to spot the differences.
(The team that asks the question makes 5 differences.)
(The 3 losers get their names written on the roulette.)
- Hold on. - It's time to set the default.
This is the before.
- Why don't we use this shirt? - What do you mean?
(What is their plan to confuse Team Three Ladies?)
They are setting the default.
- The default? - Why are they doing that?
They should leave things as they are.
They will make things look unnatural from the beginning.
- They're too unnatural. - Gosh.
I saw it coming when they wanted to team up.
I didn't think Jong Kook was like that.
- He likes to force things. - He's crafty.
- Enter, and check right and left. - I will...
- Right, left, and the center. - Check right away.
- I'll take the center. - Okay.
(Opening)
- What? - Wait. Come on.
What was that?
(How did Team Three Guys set up the room for before the change?)
- What... - Wait.
- Come on. - What is this?
(Their set-up clearly looks unnatural.)
(Remember the set-up of the room to spot 5 differences soon.)
Don't do this.
- Did you already decide on changes? - You guys...
This is confusing. Why are you guys in the room?
Why... Why did you do this?
Why am I still standing here?
I don't know about this. I really don't. We're ruined.
(Their strategy is to distract them.)
- He's crossing his left leg. - You have five seconds.
Gosh, I can't do this.
- Time's up. Come on out. - Gosh.
- Please exit the room. - Goodness.
- Please exit the room. - Time's up. Please leave.
Please leave the room.
(Their 30 seconds to observe are over.)
(They're panicking and already lost.)
- Get ready. - Okay.
- Start. - Hey, move aside.
Take it off.
(How will the room look after applying the changes?)
Since they're in the room, I get distracted to look at them.
- The guys are distracting indeed. - Right.
We have to check if there are cookies on top of the bed.
Darn it. I didn't check the shoes.
- I checked Jong Kook's shoes. - Gosh, I didn't check the shoes.
We'll give you 30 seconds. You can begin now.
- Let's go in at once. 1, 2, 3. - 3.
(Can the ladies recognize the five changes?)
- 1, 2, 3. - 3.
Unbelievable.
The t-shirt.
(He catches her eyes at first glance.)
(Is he the male version of the Statue of Liberty?)
(Did you spot their bold and unnatural changes?)
This is crazy.
(Viewers, most of you probably spotted the differences, right?)
(3 minutes ago)
- This? This? Do I switch these two? - You have 10 seconds.
(They began the grand-scale construction from that point on.)
- This. This. - This one?
Should we switch them?
(The second change is Haha's chair.)
(Se Chan's change is bolder than Haha's.)
- Haha, tie this for me. - Hold on.
(They made four changes including Se Chan's goggles and gown.)
- The last one will be funny. - What is it?
(He holds a very big ice bucket instead of a small glass cup.)
(They aimed to be funny instead of making meticulous changes.)
Okay.
(They aimed to win and to be entertaining.)
(Team Three Ladies is flustered by their bold changes.)
Gosh, this is crazy.
(Your changes are obvious.)
Se Chan changed.
Please be precise.
He changed his gown and goggles.
(She's confident.)
Those two changed.
(Just two changes? She didn't spot the ice bucket?)
(Trying to hold back his laughter)
Hey, your gown...
What's different about him? Hold on.
- Hey, you... - Gosh.
- Don't you think this is too much? - You have 10 seconds.
And Haha...
(At that moment...)
(Did Han Na finally spot the difference?)
Haha's t-shirt...
and his hand's location.
(She's certain.)
Why are you laughing?
(Why is she talking about his t-shirt out of the blue?)
(Am I wrong?)
(After she senses Haha's scoffing, she doubts herself.)
Wait, this. This, this. The location changed.
(Jin Young guesses wrongly about Jong Kook.)
- Or is it the frame? Is it? - Start with Se Chan first.
(Their 30 seconds are up. It's time to guess the changes.)
Se Chan's gown and goggles changed.
Seriously.
- What's wrong with her? - She's a fool.
- Hey, you fools. - They're so dumb.
- We made it so easy for you. - Next.
- What is it then? - The gown and goggles.
I want to go next.
We'll tell you the answers now.
How many did we get right?
Right now, you only figured out two.
- You got the goggles and the gown. - Okay.
I can't believe you didn't get the glass.
- I was so shocked. - Seriously.
- How could she not spot it? - That was just a giveaway.
We changed three things about Se Chan.
And Han Na was hilarious.
- Didn't he change his t-shirt? - She said that my t-shirt changed.
- What's she going on about? - Your hand.
- Not my hand. I changed my chair. - He changed his chair.
- He switched the chairs. - How can you not...
- I was just giving this away. - How could you not spot that?
- I changed nothing about myself. - Right. I didn't either.
- How could you not see that? - This is unfair.
Let's switch teams.
- She's like Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo, does it fit with the look?
Does this go well with the look? I mean, let's be honest.
- It was funny that she didn't know. - It was really funny.
Didn't I tell you earlier?
- Our team has a bad memory. - How many did they get right?
- 2. - 2? Okay. Let's switch.
- Let's switch. - Two.
- Han Na, weren't you shocked? - We made major changes, not small.
- I had no idea. - You guys...
- She had no idea. - Haha, Haha.
She has the best detective skills indeed.
We didn't make small changes.
- Please leave. - We didn't even touch minor things.
- I thought that it looked easy. - It's over.
(It's time for Team Three Ladies' turn to set up the room.)
- We should... Yes, I agree. - We should make it fun.
- The three of us. - Hey, look. Let's do this.
We should cross our hands and legs...
- and make funny faces. - Or we can stand on top of this.
We can strike weird poses.
Our blood won't circulate.
That's it. Just like this.
(To get back at them, she plays dead.)
(And she copies Se Chan's pose.)
Gosh, this is hard.
(It's so hard. We have to go the extra mile, right?)
I got a cramp in one of my legs.
- This is so hard. - It is.
- This is before the changes, right? - We'll enter after 3 seconds.
They're here.
- They're coming in. - Three.
2, 1.
Go.
Is this before the changes?
(You did some stuff around here.)
- Take the left corner first. - They worked hard.
- Look at the big picture. - You prepared a lot.
(You prepared a lot.)
She's near the window.
I see.
(They observe closely for 30 seconds.)
Left hand, apple. Right hand, orange.
She's good.
- Let's wait and see. - She's looking at something.
- You have 10 seconds. - The left leg is on top.
- Okay. - Get out. It's getting hard.
- Get out now. Hurry. - Okay.
It's hard.
(Their 30 seconds to observe are over.)
(Let's hurry up and apply the changes.)
(To match the guys' bold changes, they make their own bold changes.)
- I changed it. - You did?
(She forgets about her image and puts on a disguise.)
(Wait and see, Team Three Guys.)
(We're trying so hard.)
(The set-ups clearly look forced.)
- Hold on. - I changed the earrings.
(In pain)
I got a leg cramp. I should use the other leg.
(They put their 30 seconds into good use and complete their set-up.)
This is hard.
(Clueless of these changes, Team Three Guys sets out.)
Is my posture okay?
When will we start?
- Okay. - We're coming in.
(Team Three Ladies' shocking changes which they spared nothing for)
(Can Team Three Guys spot all the changes?)
Let's see.
What? What is this?
(Is Team Three Guys flustered as expected?)
What should I do?
(The guys are flustered.)
- Wait. The location changed. - Hold on a second.
- I think the rug has been pushed. - Was the remote here before?
- The location seems different. - Wait a second.
(What? You can't spot these changes?)
Her right and left legs seem correct.
(Are they pretending not to have recognized the obvious changes?)
She had the orange in her left hand and grapes in her right.
But if she changed those, it won't be fun.
Or should we not guess them on purpose?
"Wait, what is this?"
Should we pretend to do that?
- I like it. - Sofa... The remote changed.
Imagine how happy they would feel. "He's so dumb."
(They're immature just like elementary school kids.)
- Should we get them wrong? - Just on purpose?
- As a present in Switzerland? - Yes.
- It's a gift. - So we can make them happy.
Should we give them a gift?
(It was the guys' plan to prank them.)
- The crease of the sofa... - Her legs seem correct.
(Thus began the festival of their poor acting.)
(Oh, no. I can't spot any differences at all.)
Wait, the charger. The line was on top.
- They're doing it on purpose. - Hold on. Wait.
- We don't have much time left. - How many seconds do we have?
- This is so annoying. - Wait a second.
- You have 10 seconds. - It's not here.
- Hold on. My gosh. - Wait!
- Come on. - What did they change?
- What did they change? - Three seconds.
What changed?
- Is our time up? - The weather has changed!
- Time is up. - You... You...
(What did he say? The weather has changed?)
- You can go 1st. - I'll go 1st.
There were 3 creases before, but there are 4 now.
- Okay. - Four.
I named two changes.
- My goodness. - The leather got peeled off.
- Totally. I was going to say that. - Right. Okay.
- I was going to say that. - This looked different before.
I saw a definite change. Look at her. Come here.
(Did Haha spot a change on Han Na?)
Look at her now. Her pants got one more line.
(How intriguing.)
- One more line on the side. - Good eyes, Haha.
- That has to be one of the changes. - Okay.
- Isn't it? Right? - Okay.
- Seriously. - You.
- The weather. - The weather? Okay.
These are our answers.
We definitely got all of them.
- Unbelievable. - You didn't get anything right.
- You didn't get anything right. - What?
- What are you talking about? - No way.
- No way. - You're so annoying.
- Come here. Come. - Tell us the answers.
- What? Why? - Who said that you could act?
- We weren't acting. - What's wrong with you?
- Who said that you could act? - What's going on?
- Who said? - We did our best.
- You made us into fools. - Stop lying.
- What do you mean? - Gosh, Jong Kook.
- You have changed. - Gosh.
- Your acting was awkward. - You knew all of our changes.
What did you change?
- We really didn't know. - What? "The weather has changed?"
- "The weather has changed?" - The weather was different before.
It changed over 30 seconds?
- No, it was really different. - It took so long.
(Their prank is a success.)
- Is that what you want? - Gosh, you startled me.
- What? What is it? - Hey.
(Do you know how hard we worked to prepare it?)
- What? What is it? - Hold on. Come here.
- Why? - Listen.
- Look. - Why? What's this about?
- Why did you do that? - Listen.
- Was it not fun for you? - I don't understand.
- Why? Why did you do it? - We were serious.
- Why did you do that? - We really didn't know.
- We couldn't spot the changes. - It looked exactly the same.
- You three worked very hard. - You were geniuses.
- How annoying. You're a good actor. - We focused on...
- We focused on the objects. - Jong Kook.
You're a great talker.
The victory goes to Team Three Ladies.
- Why don't I feel good about this? - No, we lost.
Write down your names on the roulette.
Let's write it down. We have to write our names on each slot.
- We wrote down our names. - They wrote on the roulette.
We wrote our names down.
(It's time for their meal which will restore their peace of mind.)
We have four forks.
- I don't know which one to use. - There are five.
(A luxurious meal prepared by a Michelin star chef)
- Great. - To be honest, dining...
It's a Michelin-starred restaurant, and we also get to see the view.
Right, the view is beautiful.
Here we are.
I'm Yang Cruise.
- This is Yang Cruise. - I'm Seung Ri.
I look like Seung Ri.
That's right. He looks like Seung Ri.
I'm like Seung Ri in Switzerland.
Why did you change into robes?
I dress like this at home.
- What? - What is it?
- Han Na's hairband is pretty. - I finished making it.
- It's the prettiest thing you wore. - It's the prettiest.
- That's it. - It looks great on you.
- You should wear it. - It looks perfect on you.
- Really? - You look like a cosmetics model.
- Seriously. - It's the face before washing.
It's Swiss cosmetics and toner.
You look perfect for that.
Han Na, make a toast.
Let's have a glass of champagne.
I'm not used to making a toast. What should I say?
Ask Jin Young.
- What should I say? - Jin Young is good at this.
(Shall I teach you?)
It's bottoms up, right?
How long will you make me hold my glass?
One shot outside the neighborhood.
- One shot outside the neighborhood - One shot outside the neighborhood
(Jin Young leads the toast.)
(Despite a humble toast, they drink elegantly.)
Gosh, champagne.
It's really delicious.
- The champagne is good. - Gosh, champagne.
It's very good.
They're oysters.
I love oysters.
These are appetizers.
- Enjoy them. - Are these appetizers?
Yes, they are.
(This is what a Michelin-starred restaurant offers.)
(Fresh lobster and cheese)
(Chewy mini pizzas)
(Including tuna, squid, and oysters, the appetizers are sophisticated.)
(Shall I taste some?)
How many times did I say it?
- The squid tastes amazing. - Is it?
It's amazing.
(Squid can't be that amazing.)
- It's amazing. - It's not fishy at all.
- Is it lobster? - It's good.
(Appetizers at a Michelin-starred restaurant are impressive.)
- Do you see the man over there? - Yes.
- He's the chef. - Hello.
(He's a top chef in the industry.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(It's nice to meet you.)
Welcome. I'm Alfonso, the chef.
It's a big pleasure to prepare dinner for you.
- Thank you. - Thank you very much.
It's interesting how he makes food in the kitchen next to us.
Here's something about the oysters.
This is what I just heard. There's no ocean near Switzerland.
- Right. - They're caught in Italy.
- For four hours... - Isn't Italy next to Switzerland?
They're sent by plane over four hours.
Really?
- That means these are very fresh. - Right.
- They were caught four hours ago. - Yes.
(Shall we have a taste of the Mediterranean Sea?)
(He slurps it in one go.)
Oysters are like milk.
It's very delicious.
(This is only the start.)
(Get ready for amazing scallops.)
Would you like to taste our Petite Arvine wine?
- White wine? - Do you want to taste some?
This is white wine that goes well with the first course dish.
- We should listen to him. - Thank you.
Switzerland.
I need to express well.
Look at her swirl. She's drank a lot of wine.
(She smells it first.)
- You look fancy. - Smell it first.
Put it closer to your nose.
Right, that's how you smell it.
(After smelling it,)
(she gargles it three times.)
(She saw it somewhere.)
(Slurping)
(She's trying her best.)
(Why is she being so frivolous?)
- That's good. - Stop it.
How does it taste?
I like her a lot.
(How does the wine taste?)
- How is it? - It tastes...
- It tastes like... - Is it astringent?
It tastes like cow leather. Can you check if it's right?
- Really? - Could you ask him?
She said that she could smell the leather of cow.
(It tasted like cow leather.)
- Are you sure? - There are many cows in the region.
- Really? - Yes.
There are many cows around.
Does it smell like cow leather?
- It has a cow leather flavor. - Really?
How do you know how cow leather tastes?
Is it from a watch strap?
- I'm not sure. Can I try again? - No, you can't.
(She tastes some more to verify.)
(She slurps.)
(What did Han Na taste?)
- How is it? - It'll taste like what he said.
It tastes like cheese.
She can smell the cheese.
- Yes. - Cheese?
- Yes. - Right?
(She guessed it correctly again.)
She's a sommelier.
- She's Sommelier Kang. - It's not easy.
(As she finishes her tasting,)
(the first dish is served.)
(Scallop with carrot mayonnaise, onion jam, beet, and pineapple)
The colors are beautiful.
(She takes grilled scallop with carrot mayonnaise.)
(Flavors explode in their mouths.)
How is it?
It's sweet and savory.
- You must eat all together. - Eat them all together.
Try some with pineapple and pumpkin. It's so delicious.
Is everything okay?
- Yes. - It's amazing.
The taste is like walking in paradise.
May we watch him cook?
You may.
- May we watch? - Yes.
(The chef is cooking pasta.)
It looks like cream. The noodles are thin.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- It's so pretty. - It's pretty.
It's amazing. It's served with truffles.
- It's served with truffles. - Really?
That amount of truffles...
is very expensive.
- It's blended and served. - It's blended.
Give us a lot, Chef.
(Give us a lot of truffles.)
I'm excited about the pasta.
- How do we eat it? - Eat it like this.
(He wraps the pasta around the fork.)
What should I do?
My goodness.
Do you like it?
(Slurping)
(This is how it tastes.)
Would you like to have some more truffles?
Thank you.
Seriously.
I thought it'd be salty, but it's not.
Does anyone want more truffles?
The flavor is amazing.
(The flavor satisfies all five senses.)
The flavor is incredible.
(Se Chan also gets more truffles.)
Thank you, thank you.
(He slurps very loudly.)
Who keeps eating jjolmyeon?
(Who keeps eating jjolmyeon?)
(Se Chan teleports everyone to a cheap restaurant.)
Those who have tasted it can enjoy it, right?
(We never had it either.)
I feel a bit behind.
It's so funny because he's being honest.
Try some pasta with shrimp.
It's so delicious.
- The noodles are... - Try it like this, Ji Hyo.
Have some pasta.
(Fill your mouth with pasta.)
Dip the shrimp and then eat it.
It's like dipping in chojang.
The noodles are different.
- They get dry. - They get dry?
(He slurps loudly.)
(Slurping and sucking)
(The sound doesn't belong at this restaurant.)
It's not regular pasta.
(An amazing main dish gets ready to be served.)
(Pork steak and cheese souffle with red wine sauce)
It breaks easily.
(Let's taste it.)
(Team Switzerland is enchanted by the taste of paradise.)
(Who will be paying for their expensive meal?)
- I'm getting teary-eyed. - Why?
- I'm moved. - Since you're treated so well?
This is very luxurious.
(It's time to account the costs.)
Everyone, did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes. - Yes.
The amount will be very high.
It's heli-skiing and a Michelin-starred restaurant.
We talked about how much 1kg of truffle costs.
- It's 3,000 dollars. - He gave us a lot.
He blended a lot.
- We must decide. - Right.
- The restaurant and helicopter. - The restaurant and helicopter.
This is the last game.
(Who will be unlucky?)
Next is Da Hee.
This is level two for Da Hee.
Is she doing it?
The ride will include a twist.
(Level 2 will be difficult.)
- What is a twist? - I tried it before.
My goodness.
(A twist tilts by 70 degrees.)
- I tried it before. It's doable. - What is a twist?
(Don't worry.)
What do you mean? You never tried it.
- Have you tried it? - You never rode with a twist.
- Didn't you see me? - You didn't do anything.
I gave the pilot a signal, and he turned the plane.
It was like a sailboat ride on a river.
(Stop lying.)
Do you know anything about twists?
- What? - Have you tried them?
- I was on a sailboat? - It seemed that way.
You looked at ease.
It was really stable. Da Hee, don't worry so much.
- I polished most of the routes. - What?
There are routes in the sky. Don't you know that?
There are routes in the sky.
What you did is different from what Da Hee will do.
As the leader of the adventure...
Didn't you cry a moment ago?
(You're not a leader.)
No? Didn't you cry?
- I didn't cry. - What kind of a leader cries?
Why would a leader cry during a sailboat ride?
"A sailboat"?
It wasn't a sailboat.
What are you talking about?
Your lips are very dry.
Weren't you scared when you went up?
Is it scary?
- Take me as an example. - Weren't you scared?
When your emotions start to collide,
how do you control your mind?
What you concentrate on is very important.
He almost passed out when he landed.
He was shaking. I saw it.
- He was almost unconscious. - Be quiet.
- "Be quiet." - You're shameless.
- Stop making fun of me. - I saw it.
- You passed out. - Gosh.
Da Hee seems excited.
She should enjoy it. She's our girl crush.
(I have something on my goggles.)
(Let me use your sweater.)
(Wiping)
- Do I have to stand it? - What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Blow on my goggles.
Blow on them. Yes.
- Why? - They have lip balm on them.
Da Hee, that's meaningless.
- Why? I want to see. - Once you go up...
- What? - I want to see.
I guess you do.
(You want to enjoy the view?)
I just let my goggles fog up.
(Then I don't see anything.)
I want some black tape on my goggles.
It was better when my goggles fogged up.
- Should I go now? - Next up is Da Hee.
Girl crush.
- She's so cool. - She's our girl crush.
- You can do this! - So Min, watch me.
Let's do this!
Level two includes a twist.
I won't fall off, will I?
- She's our girl crush. - Da Hee must be...
the bravest one among us.
You can follow me so far. You can come up here.
- Wait. I'll go first. - Okay.
(She shows no sign of fear.)
Good. That's it.
There we go.
Welcome.
- Da Hee is already up there. - That was fast.
Didn't Jae Seok take 30 minutes to get there?
(It's a huge difference.)
She went up so fast.
(10-times speed)
(The preparation took longer than the actual flying.)
I felt so sorry for Jae Seok.
- So did I. - His legs were shaking.
I'll come and get you when you're finished.
- Thank you. - Have fun.
(The pilot gets in the cockpit.)
Da Hee will go up a bit higher.
- Really? - To be able to do a twist.
- To do a twist? - She'll go up higher?
- It was high last time too. - Level three will be even higher.
Kwang Soo, watch me.
You can do this! Aren't you scared?
- No. I'm excited. - She seems so relaxed.
- She seems really relaxed. - Look how she's sitting.
- She's so relaxed. - Her position looks relaxed.
(If you're ready...)
Clear.
(Let me start the airplane.)
(The propeller starts spinning.)
She's not holding on to anything.
She's putting on lip balm.
- What? - She's putting on lip balm.
(She makes sure she looks good.)
- She's so relaxed. - It's incredible.
She seems happy.
(The airplane starts to move.)
(Fiddling)
(She fixes the self-camera angle.)
Will this work?
(She's finding the right angle.)
She looks like a general.
She's amazing.
I'm sorry to say this, but Jae Seok looked miserable.
It reminded me of "Old Partner".
- It had the same feeling. - I know what you mean.
I get it.
(The airplane arrives at the takeoff point.)
(Here we go.)
(Preparing for level 2,)
(the airplane starts to accelerate.)
(Da Hee relaxedly fixes her helmet.)
- It's taking off. - It's moving.
- It's moving. - It's taken off.
(The wheels leave the ground.)
(The airplane flies up at high speed.)
This is nice.
(It's refreshing.)
Look at her hands.
It looks as if she's controlling the airplane.
With one hand there.
It's beautiful.
(She waves at the camera.)
It's fantastic.
(Amazed)
(Let me show you.)
Look at the fields.
(She even films the beautiful view herself.)
(Her legs are in the air.)
Her legs are in the air.
- What? - Her legs are in the air.
Her legs are in the air? Why?
- Really? - Her legs are in the air.
- Her legs are in the air. - Why?
- Da Hee... - It's like raising your hands.
How will I look compared to her?
(She's making him look like a coward.)
When my leg moved a bit, I put it back right away.
(He kept his legs in place.)
Da Hee, be careful with your legs.
(Her legs are still in the air.)
(She is enjoying wing-walking to the fullest.)
(The real fun starts now.)
(The airplane tilts.)
(The twist starts.)
(The strong wind makes her mouth twist.)
- That must be the twist. - That's...
- Here we go. - Compared to Jae Seok...
(It tilts the other way.)
(The airplane is rocking from side to side.)
(This is pretty scary.)
- That must be the twist. - Here we go.
(That looks scary.)
Da Hee.
She's incredible.
(Da Hee is amazing.)
(After the twist, the airplane shoots up.)
(She can't control her face.)
It must be scary when the airplane tilts.
It's completely different from what Jae Seok experienced.
- It is. - It's completely different.
- It's not that different. - It is.
The only difference is that the airplane tilts a bit.
There was nothing like this when you tried.
It only moved forward.
(It only moved forward when Jae Seok tried.)
Be quiet.
What do you know? Gosh.
(Da Hee is experiencing vigorous twists.)
(Her face twists too.)
(She covers her face.)
(Is it time to get down?)
- They're coming down. - They're coming.
She did a good job.
(What will level 3 be like?)
Good job, Da Hee.
Please wave at us.
(She waves relaxedly.)
- She still looks relaxed. - She's so relaxed.
I should treat her like a big brother from now.
- Well done. - Thank you.
- The wind is very strong, right? - You did a great job.
The problem is not that it's scary.
Your helmet strap keeps hitting your face.
- Be careful. - How was it, Da Hee?
It was beautiful. It must have been very enjoyable for you.
- You're right. - Did you enjoy it?
No.
(I didn't enjoy it.)
When the airplane tilts,
- is it scary? - It is.
Right before the twist, the airplane goes down.
It feels very scary.
- It's like a pirate ship ride. - Really?
- It goes down so fast. - Kwang Soo must be worried.
- All right. Finally... - Poor Kwang Soo.
In addition to the twist, Kwang Soo will experience a vertical descent.
A vertical descent. It's the one you see at air shows, right?
(Level 3 consists of the basic flying, twists,)
(and a vertical descent from 457m high at 127km per hour.)
It's Kwang Soo's turn now.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo, you can do this.
- Good luck. - You're amazing.
To decide who will pay for the meal,
you'll play a game called The Last Room.
- Okay. - "The Last Room"?
The rules are simple.
- There are 2 rooms downstairs. - 2 rooms.
You'll go downstairs one by one.
The names of the members in the room with less people...
will go on the roulette wheel.
- What if it's 3 to 3? - Then nothing happens.
Let's start from Jong Kook.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Winning this game will lower your chance of paying.)
- Let's go. - I'll talk to you by telepathy.
Okay.
Go straight or turn left. A man should go straight.
A man should go straight.
(Jong Kook chooses the room at the end.)
(Which room will Han Na choose?)
Let's go.
(Knocking)
(Which room will Han Na choose?)
(Opening)
What? No one is here.
(Han Na chooses the first room.)
(It's 1 to 1 now.)
Go.
(Which room will Jin Young choose?)
Well...
(The female Kim Jong Kook goes straight too.)
- Let me see. - Of course.
(Jin Young is here.)
- We're two. - Hey.
Good.
- We're two. We might win. - We might win.
See you later.
Is it a good thing if we see each other? I'm not sure.
You'll come to me.
Ji Hyo attracts me today. I'll come to you.
(Which room will Ji Hyo choose?)
(Opening)
Yes.
Good. It's done now.
- You should always go straight. - It's done now.
We'll win.
(The room at the end is safer now.)
(Han Na is still alone.)
This is actually my room.
(Lonely)
Well... Let me see.
I should get ready to welcome a guest.
(I should calm down.)
(She even prepares flowers for the guest.)
- Next is Se Chan. Please go. - I'll see you later.
I should hurry.
(Han Na's fate depends on Se Chan's choice.)
(If Se Chan goes to Han Na's room, there's a chance for tied scores.)
(If Se Chan doesn't come, her name will be written on the roulette.)
(Will Se Chan choose Han Na's room?)
(He flies away.)
(No, come back.)
(Opening)
Come on.
Why not?
Why did everyone go to that room? This is closer.
Wait, who's in the other room?
(Only Haha remains.)
Why...
Why did everyone pass without thinking?
Why?
(He hesitates.)
(1 in the closer room, 4 in the farther room)
(Whether his name will be written on the roulette depends on his choice.)
He might come here.
(He survives if he chooses the room with more.)
(If he chooses the other, his name will be written on the roulette.)
(Ringing)
- You startled me. - My goodness.
(They startle each other.)
- You startled me. - You really startled me.
I got so startled.
I was so startled.
(He chooses the wrong room, and his heart almost stops beating.)
He really startled me.
Seriously.
- Why didn't you go in? - I heard the bell sound.
- Did you go in? - I thought there were many people.
He got tricked.
(The roulette is filled. Only payment remains.)
We'll calculate the cost for Heli-skiing and the restaurant.
- What's the current score? - Now...
it's 2, 2, 2, and 1.
(Jong Kook, Han Na, Haha score 2, Se Chan and Jin Young score 1.)
We'll select who will pay the cost for Heli-skiing.
- There's no practice. - No.
- Can we start without practice? - Of course.
- Let's go. - Is it one round?
- This is it. - Okay.
Only Jong Kook and I have debt.
- Right. - You startled me.
Please don't let it be me.
Spin.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will pay the cost for Heli-skiing?)
It's done.
- It's done. - Please.
Haha!
(Haha is selected.)
(This must be a dream.)
(Everyone celebrates except Haha.)
I'm a coward
- It can't work with Haha. - Okay.
(Haha pays 900 dollars.)
- How about this? - Spin it.
Next is the restaurant.
- It's the restaurant. - Haha spins it this time.
- Shall Haha spin it? - Okay.
Let's go.
If you get selected again,
it'd be the best.
The cost won't be low.
Come on, Haha.
- This is expensive. - Let's go.
It's done.
(Who will pay for the restaurant?)
It's spinning fast.
It's Han Na.
(Han Na is selected.)
(She's surprised.)
It's Han Na.
- 1 is 1, it's not 2 - It's not 2
- 2 is 2, it's not 3 - 2 is 2, it's not 3
(She pays 1,500 dollars.)
Do you remember the rule I told you earlier?
To determine the debt,
there were three activities in Shuddering Package.
(A set of three activities for Shuddering Package)
(For members who paid out of their own pocket,)
(there's a chance to get a refund.)
(3 activities for Shuddering Package)
(If 1 of 3 activities is done,)
(the total expense will be reimbursed.)
Due to the circumstances and the weather,
the only available activity is the suspension bridge.
That's terrible.
(That's terrible.)
(Charles Kuonen Suspension Bridge is the longest suspension bridge.)
(Cross a bridge of 494m in length and 85m in height.)
If two of you...
cross the suspension bridge,
everyone will be exempted from paying debt.
We got it.
Do two members have to volunteer?
We have to decide.
- We have to pick two members. - Two members?
- They would sacrifice themselves. - Right.
I'll hand you a roulette.
The four of us should write down our names.
Spin the roulette once.
The person who is picked...
- He picks the second person? - selects another person.
That sounds good.
- It's fair. - Does he get to pick one?
- Picking is harder. - It's fair.
(Jong Kook, Se Chan, Haha, and Han Na)
(They write their name on two pieces.)
Your fate depends on me.
If your name gets picked,
- goodbye - Goodbye to suspension bridge
- Here I go. - If I get picked,
I want to go with Haha who is the worst coward.
That's why I want to be picked.
I want to cross the bridge with Haha who's the worst coward.
As Han Na wishes, will Kang be picked?
Here I go. Spin it.
1, 2, 3, let's go.
It's spinning well.
(The roulette of fate will determine who crosses the suspension bridge.)
(Which members will be selected?)
1, 2, 3, let's go.
- It's spinning well. - That was a good spin.
(It's Kang Han Na.)
(Dreams come true.)
That's amazing.
(Am I also selected?)
If I'm crossing the bridge,
I'd like to go with Haha.
I want to have a good time for the last time in Switzerland.
We'll take a jumping shot in the middle of the bridge.
Make it clear, Han Na.
Whom will you go with?
- Me? I'm going with Haha. - Okay.
It's 6am.
Good morning.
- "Good morning"? - I can't thank you enough.
- Won't it be refreshing? - Yes.
I prayed for a storm today.
- So the trip is canceled? - Yes.
With all my heart,
I prayed hard.
(However, the weather is clear.)
I think the weather will be good.
(They arrive at Randa Station.)
I haven't hiked in a while.
(They even stretch.)
It's a morning exercise.
- Shall we go? - Let's go.
- We can do it. - We can do it.
- Let's go and try it. - Let's go.
- Everyone else does it. - Right.
Why is he giving us hiking sticks?
How hard will the hiking be?
We aren't going to ski. Why do we need them?
(They're given hiking sticks.)
I don't know how to use them. Should I just keep them?
We might need them later. We'll find out.
(They start hiking.)
Does it take two hours?
It hasn't started yet,
but we seem so serious already.
(They're flustered by the situation.)
Goodness.
Han Na thought that it'd be a trail.
Look at her outfit.
- This? - Look what she's wearing.
Carrying a water bottle is inconvenient.
This is why.
My stylist said that we don't know what we're doing on the last day.
We might go to the city near the airport.
We have to go to the airport anyway.
But we're hiking.
It doesn't matter.
The stylist told me to wear it on the last day.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
The way is already beautiful.
It is beautiful indeed.
It's still beautiful.
- It's what I expected. - Really?
It's a typical walk in Switzerland.
This is easy.
Han Na is definitely different...
from So Min.
However, you're similar in a way.
- No, we're completely different. - Of course.
When I'm with So Min, I stand out less.
(They see a cute trampoline.)
Look.
It's a trampoline that we paid 50 cents to use when we were young.
It's a big trampoline for a house.
I had a small one at home.
I'd play there all day.
She never stops talking.
- Seriously. - Who?
You.
- Are you tired? - No.
So Min is also talkative,
but you're different.
So Min and I went to Hong Kong together.
She talked nonstop.
That's what you're doing now.
(He explodes.)
(She pretends not to be.)
I'm sorry.
- Are you angry? - No.
It's pretty.
(They pass a small and cute village.)
It's so beautiful.
(It's silence after a long time.)
Are you looking down for snakes?
Look at the view.
It's so beautiful.
(He walks with talkative Han Na.)
(They charge forward to the suspension bridge.)
This is great.
(The air is very fresh.)
It's amazing.
This air can't be bought.
This is what luxury is about.
It's amazing.
(They find something.)
Look at them.
- We finally see them. - Don't startle them.
(They finally see Valais Blacknose.)
(Han Na runs into what she wanted to see in Switzerland.)
This is amazing.
They're hard to be so close to them.
Hello.
They're so cute. They're like dolls.
I was born in the year of sheep.
(They're from a region called Valais.)
They're just like dolls.
(She stops for the sheep.)
(Who am I? Where am I?)
Hello.
Ji Hyo would have loved to see them.
It's dangerous here.
(Thanks to the clean air and the view, they don't get tired.)
It's so nice here.
How much would this air be worth?
(The air is so precious.)
Before I came here, I blamed Han Na.
But I'm thankful now.
- It's nice, right? - With our sticks...
(They're happy to be here.)
- Seriously... - This is so nice.
It smells like poop.
- But I even like that. - Please say it in a nicer way.
I'm so happy I was chosen.
The roulette chose me.
(The road is nice, and the view is beautiful.)
- You have to take this path. - That path?
(According to the sign...)
- No way. - That path?
- That's not our path. - The path begins here.
It can't be.
- This... - It's right here.
- But... - This...
- No, it's not our path. - Will it get better later?
Or will it be like this all the way?
We have to walk on this path for two hours?
- About an hour and a half. - No way.
I don't believe it. I'm already tired.
Tell them your ankles hurt.
Let's call it a day.
I couldn't abandon my colleague.
We even saw the sheep on the way.
We've seen enough.
- We've filmed enough, right? - Right?
(They still have to film some more.)
Let's go.
This path is so narrow.
(Serious)
Our survival starts now.
- Yes. - Let's focus on surviving.
(Focused)
Haha, look at this.
- Just go on. - Haha, look at this.
Isn't that an acorn shell?
You just said we should focus on surviving.
- I mean... - Just keep going.
- It's just... - My goodness.
- You're driving me crazy. - I mean...
I saw acorn shells. Are they pine nuts?
- Be careful. - We should really be careful.
This is survival.
(Serious)
- Haha. - Just go.
You have to film it. It's a slug.
- What's that? - Look.
Is it gross? Please film it.
- What's that? - I've never seen it before.
- You call that a slug? - It has no shell.
Gosh. This is... Switzerland... Mother Nature...
(What is she saying?)
I don't know what to say.
Now that we've filmed a slug, let's go on.
(After 10 minutes)
There's an observatory.
- Okay. - Okay.
We're here.
(They stop by at the observatory.)
Look.
(This is incredible.)
We're here.
(They're awed by Mother Nature.)
We're here!
This place is so sacred.
It's a cliff?
Be careful.
(If you take a few more steps...)
It's incredible. Look at that.
(It's not computer graphics.)
The air is so clean.
(The trail is full of...)
(beautiful surprises.)
- This whole place is beautiful. - I feel bad.
I don't want to walk on it.
It's so beautiful.
(They stop for a moment.)
(They're playing music with their phone.)
- Haha is crying. - This is...
- so moving. - It is.
(They're not tired anymore.)
- I got goosebumps. - Me too.
- We got goosebumps. - At the same time.
- Please take a close up. - It's so beautiful.
(The cameramen's first close-up of goosebumps)
I still have goosebumps.
I'm speechless.
(They're eating jelly.)
That's crazy.
- I saw it. - What did you see?
Hold on.
I'm not thankful anymore.
(While walking through the nature,)
(they see something ahead of them.)
(This is it.)
We can't do this.
- What is this? - This is impossible.
We can't do it.
(Charles Kuonen Suspension Bridge is 494m long and 85m high.)
- I got goosebumps. - Gosh.
We can't do this. We just can't.
Forget about Mother Nature. This is ridiculous.
Why would you have this in the middle of nature?
Why... We can't do this.
- I got goosebumps. - Come on.
(What will they do?)
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- You can do this. - Be careful.
You're amazing.
- Let's sing for him. - Sure.
- You were born to be penalized - You were born to be penalized
(You were born to be penalized, Kwang Soo)
(Even in the UK, you are destined to be penalized)
(I appreciate it.)
(You were also born to go to the ghost castle)
(Sighing)
Stop it.
(What are you doing?)
(You should take a picture before being penalized.)
We should take a picture.
- That's enough. - He looks funny.
Seok Jin is bad at reading others' feelings.
(Did you see that?)
I've known him for more than 20 years,
and he's really bad at reading others' emotions.
Don't worry.
You just have to sit there.
Drink some water.
This is today's Hayashi rice.
Hayashi rice?
(Hayashi rice)
That's a dish.
"My bladder will burst."
- Let's get it. - He said, "My bladder will burst."
(My bladder will burst.)
(Did you mean, "We've been cracking up a lot"?)
(This is today's Hayashi rice.)
(Seok Jin keeps saying wrong words.)
- Think before you say something. - I'm jet-lagged.
- Why... - "Hayashi rice".
- Why can't you keep quiet? - You can do this.
It's finally Kwang Soo's turn.
Today's highlight is Kwang Soo.
- All ready? - Yes.
You can do this! You're the best.
(This is it.)
All right. I'm in trouble.
(He's been watching in fear.)
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
(Kwang Soo gets on the airplane.)
Your right hand on the handle here,
and your left hand there.
Kwang Soo can't close his mouth.
He's a coward just like me.
- Okay. - There you go.
And then be careful. Are you okay?
(He carefully moves his foot.)
- Here? Should I hold here? - Yes. Okay.
Hold on.
You'll be fine.
It's scary when you go up there.
- It is? - Yes.
- He must be nervous. - It's scary just to be up there.
(He manages to sit on the chair.)
The chair is too small.
(We thought everything was fine.)
- What was that? - The chair is too small.
- The chair is too small. - Too small?
No, it's not. It's fine.
(Determined)
You'll be okay.
What is he doing?
He sat on the chair.
Kwang Soo, it'll be fine.
Smile. Say hi.
Hi.
(He does as she says.)
Remember, if you want to come down,
put thumbs down, and the pilot will land as soon as he can.
I'll come and take you when you're done.
The pilot put his helmet on.
Look at that.
What's going on?
(The UK, wing-walking, level 3... What is going on?)
This must be a dream.
What is...
(Everything is set.)
(The engine starts.)
- It's moving. - It's moving.
(The airplane is moving.)
See you!
(Rummaging)
(He takes something out of his pocket.)
- It's a relaxing pill. - That's awesome.
(Sang Yeob gave a relaxing pill to Kwang Soo.)
Did you bring it in case you go wing-walking?
(Thanks, Sang Yeob.)
(The airplane starts to move as soon as he takes the pill.)
It's moving.
(He can't say anything.)
Kwang Soo is shaking.
What will happen to him?
(Shaking)
Once it turns, it'll take off.
It'll take off soon.
(It's time to take off.)
How did you feel right before the takeoff?
- I felt scared. - It's scary, right?
- Right? - It was scary.
- I was scared too. - You were?
- I was scared. - Right before the takeoff?
With the earplugs, you don't hear anything.
(Description service)
You realize that you're alone.
The sound of the propeller gets louder and louder.
Just when you wonder when the airplane will take off,
everything starts.
(That moment is here.)
(Just when you wonder,)
(it takes off.)
It's taking off.
I'm flying.
(The airplane flies up at great speed.)
- He's going up. - It took off.
- How do you feel at this moment? - My goodness.
Like I said, you feel bad the whole time.
(Screaming)
(Bad mood)
Cowards never let go of the handles.
We hold onto them.
(He is holding onto the handle firmly.)
(He hasn't taken his hands off even for a second.)
(The airplane is high up.)
You start to ask yourself,
"Should I put my thumbs down and go down?"
- This? - Like this?
Between the show and yourself,
that's where the inner conflict begins.
(The twist starts...)
(before he has time for an inner conflict.)
(His lips twist in a funny way.)
It looks like his body is slanted.
(He's almost lying down.)
(The anti-anxiety medicine spills out due to the intense twist.)
This is much higher than before.
- I think he's going to drop soon. - Will he?
(The vertical descent...)
(has started.)
(Hold on.)
(What's this?)
(This is the highlight of level 3.)
(The vertical descent starts.)
(The plane accelerates towards the ground at a steep angle.)
I'm scared.
(He can't even scream.)
- Kwang Soo. - It's high.
(They're shocked by how different this is from level 1 and 2.)
(Before the shock subsides,)
(here comes the 2nd vertical descent.)
- It's scary. - Gosh, what now?
(At this angle, the plane is so close to the ground.)
It's scary.
(He's about to faint.)
He's holding on tightly.
(This is the 3rd consecutive vertical descent.)
Kwang Soo.
- What should we do? - Gosh, Kwang Soo.
It was completely vertical.
- He went so far. - Where did he go?
He went really far. He disappeared.
- He's over there. - Did he go home?
- Did he go to Korea? - He went so far.
He's going straight to Korea.
(That's possible.)
- He's going to Incheon Airport. - He'll be hanging like that.
(This vertical descent...)
(goes straight to Korea.)
(We won't see you off, Kwang Soo.)
(Please take me home.)
- This is on a different level. - This is much higher.
- This is endless. - I think he'll come down now.
He should. He has to live.
- He's coming down. - You feel a relief.
- "This is over." - Right.
(He lands safely.)
Kwang Soo did a good job.
(He's wrecked.)
- He did a good job. - Good job, Kwang Soo.
That was great. He did an excellent job.
- I think he's crying. - He's almost...
fixed to the chair.
(Is he fixed to the chair?)
- He's stuck to it. - What is wrong with him?
You're a true coward.
- His lips are blue. - His lips are not together.
He lost consciousness.
(The employee comes to help him get down.)
Is everything all right?
- Okay. - Are you okay?
(Is everything all right?)
(Is something wrong with him?)
(He's covered in the anti-anxiety medicine.)
(He thought it might be helpful,)
(so he took it right before departing.)
(He spit it all out.)
Can we please have some tissues?
(There's brown fluid.)
- Tissues. She wants some tissues. - Really?
Tissues?
Kwang Soo, good job.
(Coward Kwang Soo did it.)
- I'm so proud of you. - Good job. I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
(You're welcome.)
(He also gives a salute.)
Thank you.
- Very well done. - Thank you. Thank you so much.
I have a sword, so I'm going to knight you now.
(I praise you in the name of twists, vertical descent, and wing walking.)
Look at the captain.
The vertical descent was incredible.
What's on your face?
Why is your saliva that color? Is that the relaxing pill?
Is that poop?
(Could it be?)
- There's poop around your mouth. - Did you puke?
- It's anti-anxiety medicine. - It came out.
You should have taken it earlier, not just before.
The medicine spilled out.
You should have had it earlier.
How can you poop through your mouth?
I told you to take it 30 minutes before.
- Kwang Soo. - I departed before I swallowed it.
(I should have done that.)
- Can you give him some wet wipes? - Goodness.
When I was going down,
- That was awesome. - I wanted to spread my arms,
but I couldn't let go.
- I'm serious. - How was it?
- Wasn't it scary? - It was so scary.
He's lying. He was on a sailboat.
That wasn't it. It was so scary.
The medicine I took came out from my eyes.
(He was that scared.)
- I'm serious. - Hey.
- There was brown water in my eyes. - Hey.
- It came out from my eyes. - Kwang Soo,
- when were you most scared? - It was going down,
and I couldn't spread my arms. That was the scariest.
I couldn't let go.
(You were supposed to let go.)
(He was screaming.)
I did this with my fingers.
He couldn't see.
The wing walking penalty has been completed.
(They have completed their mission.)
- Good job. - You were awesome.
- Great job. - Let's not get the penalty again.
- We didn't do anything wrong. - Oh, gosh.
Everybody, congratulations. The only thing left is...
a night at the haunted castle.
(It's not over yet. Next penalty is staying at a haunted castle.)
(They must spend a night in Oxford Castle where spirits appear.)
Everybody, congratulations. The only thing left is...
a night at the haunted castle.
(It's not over yet. Next penalty is staying at a haunted castle.)
(They must spend a night in Oxford Castle where spirits appear.)
Why would we sleep there? They already went through enough.
So Min.
Would you like to stay for a night, Seok Jin?
The new mission has to be fair.
(He's adamant.)
Seok Jin.
(It has to be fair.)
Before going there for the night,
we prepared the best dishes in the UK.
(Dinner is on the staff for completing wing walking.)
You can head there together.
- We finished one penalty. - Right.
That's right. Great job. 1, 2, 3.
- Great job. - Great job. You were awesome.
Great job.
- Good job. - The food is coming.
Can people not go there freely?
I thought this was sliced radish.
- The shrimp looks so good. - Thank you.
(It's dried jamon and shrimp with homemade sauce.)
It's jamon.
What's this called?
(He takes a bite.)
(This is good.)
It's good.
You worked hard, so we're providing you with this.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
There's something else.
(Shrimp and jamon were appetizers.)
- It's steak. - Steak?
- That looks good. - That does.
You'll be sleeping at the haunted castle.
- How do we decide who goes? - That sounds so scary.
We're going to play a game in there and decide.
- In there? - I'm sorry for asking,
but how many games are we playing?
We're like game addicts.
We're all professional gamers.
You have to keep your promise with the viewers and sleep there.
(It doesn't matter who it is.)
That's right. We have to keep our promise with the viewers.
Then...
(Okay, then.)
- For Seok Jin. - For Seok Jin.
(Cheers)
No. It's not me today.
Don't do that.
- For Seok Jin's good sleep. - For Seok Jin's good sleep.
It's not me. Don't do that. Be careful what you for.
(He can't speak properly.)
(Spitting)
(Seok Jin has started again.)
What did he say?
- He mumbled the words. - What did he say?
He tried to say, "Be careful what you ask for."
What was that?
- What was that again? - Oh, gosh.
The jet lag is driving me nuts.
(Who will get to spend the last night in the haunted castle?)
I can't say things properly.
Why did Mother Nature create this?
Why? How are we supposed to do this?
- I got goosebumps again. - Oh, gosh.
Oh, gosh. I'm so mad.
I just had jelly, and I feel like I'm going to throw it up.
This is insane.
It's so long. It gives me goosebumps just by looking at it.
It moves so much. Look, Haha. Just look.
The whole bridge is dancing.
You know why I feel slightly better?
- Why? - I'm not crossing that bridge.
- Why? - I feel okay. I gave up.
I feel calmer after giving up.
- Are you going to pay? - Yes.
What is this about?
(He'd rather pay and starve than cross that bridge.)
No, join me. I can't cross it by myself.
- That... - Wait.
- I can't even look. - How can you cross that?
There are holes.
On the floor? Stop lying.
Look.
I can't even look.
Let's go. I'm not scared.
- You're not? - No.
I'm not crossing it.
(I'm not going to cross it anyway.)
I'm not afraid anymore. I'm not crossing it.
I can't cross this.
Can the camera show how terrifying this is?
Are you going to pay money and give up...
or cross the bridge? Please decide.
They're telling me to do this.
Haha, are you going to pay... How much is it exactly?
I want to hear it and think about it.
If you think about it, we had such a good tour of Switzerland.
I don't feel bad about paying. Do you?
(They're scared to cross it but also don't want to miss the chance.)
Hold on. It gives me goosebumps just looking.
According to our staff, it's doable.
The weather is nice, and it's not windy.
It's the perfect condition for crossing.
(Hesitating)
- Haha, let's do this. - Let's go.
(Haha, let's do this.)
Let's do this. We're already in Switzerland.
We came all the way up here. Let's do this.
(Let's see.)
- Okay, let's do this. - I think...
the drama I'm shooting right now will be a success.
Viewers, thank you for your interest.
(She promotes her drama while deciding to cross the bridge.)
Good. Let's go.
(Let's do this. Let's cross it.)
I'm here, so I should do it.
(He's scared.)
It's shaking.
(The starting point of this 494m long bridge)
(Han Na starts first.)
(Shaking)
Haha.
It's shaking.
Gosh, why is this shaking so much? Hold on.
There's a person in front of me.
(Because the cameraman is in front of you.)
- Haha, it's shaking so much. - Don't do that.
It's shaking so much. Stop shaking it.
It's shaking so much.
What do I do? What do I do?
Hold on.
(She stands awkwardly.)
This is shaking so much.
- Why is this shaking so much? - I... Wait.
What's this? Don't look down.
Don't look down.
(You can see the bottom.)
I can't.
(Should I go or not?)
(He gets up.)
I love you.
I love you all.
(I love you. I love you all.)
(He crosses with the people he loves in his heart.)
Haha is coming.
I feel stable now. When he gets close,
I might shake it.
(He looks down.)
(I can't go.)
Haha.
(He looked down.)
It's shaking.
Haha.
If you come to the middle, it's less scary. Hurry up.
Goodness.
- Don't look down. - It's shaking so much.
Haha, it's better to keep walking.
I feel stable now. Never mind. I'm not stable yet.
I think it's better to keep walking.
I'm used to it now.
(I'm strong.)
I'm... Wait.
What's this? I'm okay. I'm used to it.
I'm going to puke.
(He's so scared that something pops into his mind.)
Make sure you air this as a long segment.
We're almost there.
(Don't be mad.)
Dream and Soul, watch.
Daddy didn't crouch.
I'm walking with my shoulders square.
This is your daddy.
The lady over there...
- I'm scared. - is Han Na. She's so strong.
I'm scared.
- I'm humming. - I'm scared. Why is this shaking?
Don't look down.
(Glancing)
I looked down.
- Why did I look down? - I told you not to look.
(Why did I look down?)
- I told you not to look. - Oh, dear.
- What now? - Sung Yong.
Sung Yong?
You have to answer loudly when I call you, punk.
- I'm going to faint. - I love you.
Me too.
I love all the Running Man members.
Thank you for joining us, Han Na.
- We're almost there. - Han Na, can you laugh?
- Sorry? - Can you laugh?
Good.
I feel calmer.
We're almost there, Haha.
(They're finally at the end of the suspension bridge.)
We're almost there.
(Is Haha still alive?)
You're a coward.
The coward is coming.
Coward.
(The coward is coming.)
We did it.
My debt is forgiven.
(Success! All the members write off their debts.)
Thank you.
- Haha, it's not shaking. - Thank you very much.
Thank you. Bridges in Switzerland are so sturdy.
Thank you.
It's hot. It's so hot.
This is beautiful.
(They overcome the longest suspension bridge in the world.)
- Good morning! - Good morning!
(Meanwhile, the ski resort is not cloudy like yesterday.)
Let's go.
(Se Chan is not resenting anymore.)
(Ji Hyo finally gets to fly on the snowboard.)
Is this for real?
Is this for real? Let's go.
Luxury Package.
(Darkness sets in the UK.)
We're actually going.
It's the haunted castle.
(They head off to the haunted castle to finish off the package.)
(Sighing)
The castle is on the right.
- On the right? - Where?
- I can't see it. - It's in between.
- Is that it? - That's it.
(That's...)
(the last stop of our Shuddering Package.)
It's a real castle.
(Oxford Castle, a haunted castle)
This is the last stop in Shuddering Package.
Welcome to the haunted castle.
(This is finally the last stop, the haunted castle.)
(It's in the middle of the night, so they get chills down the spine.)
This used to be a prison.
Doesn't it look like one?
- I looked at myself. - Okay.
Why didn't anybody say that I'm really pale?
(You guys are heartless.)
- We told you. - I'm so pale.
- Excuse me. - That's not why.
I was supposed to contour, but I didn't bring my makeup.
You should have asked me for it.
- Why are you getting angry? - I'm not.
It's your fault.
I just said I was pale.
I'm sleepy, so I'm edgy.
Stop it. You thanked me for doing it.
You said you won't forget it. Have you forgotten already?
Thank you.
(She feels better now.)
- Where do we go? - All right.
Go to the basement.
- It's the basement? - Why is it the basement?
(They enter the haunted castle through the basement.)
- This is driving me nuts. - I really don't like...
these kinds of things.
What's this?
Oh, gosh.
Are there any ghosts?
(It feels eerie as if ghosts will come out.)
What's this?
That scared me.
Goodness.
(Why is the entrance like this?)
It crazy.
"It crazy"?
(He's so scared he mumbles.)
Aren't you supposed to say, "It is crazy"?
Words keep spilling out.
(He's terrified.)
What's this?
- Hurry. - What's wrong?
(He's frightened.)
I hear footsteps.
I think it's recorded.
(Why does he hear footsteps in an empty hallway?)
- This is no joke. - It's so scary that...
you'll fall while running.
What's this?
It's so narrow.
I'm scared.
(It's an unknown space covered by four walls.)
You can see the outside.
Is this the room?
In order to understand the history of this place,
please watch the video.
- What's this? - Oh, gosh.
(Why are you doing this?)
Hey, why would you...
- This is Oxford Castle. - Oxford Castle?
(It was built in 1071, and it has been abandoned.)
(Since the 18th century to 1900s, it was an infamous prison.)
(It was known for cruel torturing and death penalties.)
- This is so scary. - It is.
(There's a mysterious male ghost in the place of execution.)
(The ghost of a monk is witnessed in the basement every night.)
(Screaming)
(He's most frightened.)
- You're scaring me more. - I'm sorry.
(UK broadcast)
(This is a mysterious place that was aired in the UK as well.)
(What happened in this castle for over 1,000 years?)
- What's this? - What's this?
- Look at that person. - Look at that picture.
I feel like I'm going to dream about this...
after watching the video.
This is a bad idea.
We can't sleep here.
We can't do that.
This doesn't make sense.
This room...
is the oldest space in the building.
Matilda, who could have been the first queen in the UK,
was locked up here for three months and died.
So her ghost appears here often.
Also, 70 prisoners got massacred for having an infectious disease,
so this is the most cursed space in the building.
Many people have witnessed ghosts with deep resentments.
Here's a mission that can exempt all of you from sleeping here.
(In this cursed space, they'll have the final mission for an exemption.)
This is the last stage of Shuddering Package.
- Exemption for everybody? - Exemption for all?
We have to succeed.
It's a frightening loyalty game.
We'll conduct What Is the Ghost's Name?
(Last mission: What Is the Ghost's Name?)
I am up for anything else but loyalty game.
(Please)
- I know. - This is impossible.
We would rather fight tooth and nail.
- A loyalty game won't do. - That would be preferable.
We would rather fight.
There is a historical figure...
whose ghost appears the most often in this hotel.
The name of the ghost has five syllables.
The syllables are at the places the ghost is frequently sighted.
The members will take turns finding the syllables...
and take a Polaroid picture of it alone.
Alone?
Do you want me to go alone?
(Am I hearing things? Alone?)
If you correctly guess the name, the mission is a success,
and you will be exempted from sleeping at the hotel.
If you take a picture of the ghost,
you will also be exempted from sleeping at the hotel.
(Taking a picture of the ghost exempts them as well.)
(I can't believe them.)
- I can't believe them. - That's impossible.
Now, we should decide...
Why doesn't Sang Yeob go first?
- I want to see it. - Why doesn't Sang Yeob go first?
Really? Should Sang Yeob go first? That's a good idea.
Okay. Sang Yeob is dependable.
Sang Yeob, you are an actor.
(It's sudden.)
What does being an actor have to do with this?
Come on, Sang Yeob.
All right. I will go.
- That's a good idea. - I don't even know.
Sang Yeob hates ghosts the most.
- I hate them. I hate them so much. - I know.
He repeatedly said that he hates ghosts.
If you take a picture of the ghost, we don't have to do this.
Okay. I will be back.
- All right. - I will be back.
(Sang Yeob goes in a nervous state.)
(From the beginning)
Gosh, I am so scared.
Let's go!
(He chases away his fears by making a loud noise.)
(He enters the corridor of the prison cells.)
(He gathers up the courage and enters the torture chamber.)
(He gets scared of the instruments.)
I have to pull through.
Gosh, that startled me.
(He gets startled by the cameraman's footsteps.)
Is there a name?
(I don't know why I agreed to go first.)
Please pick the next person to go.
Let's play the game with hands.
- Apartment? - Yes.
Let's play Apartment.
What's that?
- You stack the hands. - Let's begin.
Then you take them out.
(You lose if you get caught at the designated story...)
(or make a sound when you get slapped.)
(She watches the others.)
(The other members are absorbed in the game.)
(Awkward and off-beat)
Da Hee, what are you doing?
- You haven't played this game. - Da Hee, what was this?
I will learn as I play the game. Let's keep going.
- Will you be able to do it? - Yes.
Let's begin.
(The Apartment Game starts again.)
(Da Hee listens to the members...)
(and sings and dances diligently.)
Why are we doing this in the UK?
(Why are we playing the Apartment Game in the UK?)
Why am I doing this in the UK?
- Your apartment - Your apartment
13th floor.
- What's the floor? - 13th floor.
(So Min has to slap Da Hee first.)
One.
(Is this how the game goes?)
This is how the game goes.
Really? Okay.
Two.
(Ouch.)
- Did it hurt? - Kwang Soo.
- You slapped her so hard. - This is how the game goes.
- What? - This is how the game goes.
- This is how the game goes. - That's right.
So Min is out.
(So Min is out because she made a sound.)
Two.
(Jae Seok's strong slap eliminates Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo is out.
(Three members remain.)
- 11th floor. - 11th floor.
(They have to build a 11th-floor apartment.)
11th floor.
(Seok Jin has to get slapped by Jae Seok first.)
One.
(Slap)
- Seok Jin endured it. - He is good at it.
It's Seok Jin's turn.
(It's Seok Jin's turn to slap Jae Seok.)
(Evading)
(Seok Jin slaps his own hand.)
I am out.
For goodness' sake.
(Come here.)
What? I said I am out.
Seok Jin's face turned red.
(While they play the Apartment Game)
I can't find it.
(Sang Yeob is navigating the haunted castle by himself.)
A syllable.
This is no joke.
(Where is the syllable?)
(He goes into the prison...)
(where many prisoners were held.)
Gosh, that startled me.
How do I use this camera?
(He finds a syllable from the name.)
(He finds "Bl" from the 5 syllables.)
I hate this.
(He returns without looking back.)
He startled me. Did you find it?
- Did you find it? - He found it.
Did you take a picture?
Ta-da!
(I have one.)
He found one.
(They have respect for Sang Yeob.)
- Bl? - Bl?
(Sang Yeob succeeds.)
It's Da Hee's turn to slap Seok Jin, right?
(It's Da Hee's turn to slap Seok Jin.)
It's a full swing.
(Moaning)
(Da Hee's full swing makes Seok Jin groan.)
It must have hurt a lot.
It stings.
(I am sorry, Seok Jin.)
(It's decided that Da Hee will go last.)
- Kwang Soo, you have to find it. - You have to find a syllable.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn to find a syllable.)
I will try.
- Make sure you do it. - Bring back a picture.
We will end you if you don't bring back a picture.
We will scold you.
(Let's see if the 3 cowards will succeed.)
(Coward number 1, Kwang Soo, sets out.)
What was that sound?
Let's go together.
(Let's go together, Mr. Cameraman.)
(Yoon Sang, let's go together.)
- Let's go together. - You have to go alone.
- No, let's go. - You have to go alone.
Let's go together.
I really can't go in there.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(They are the same.)
Stop walking back and forth. It's annoying.
- Go. - Do you want me to go first?
You need to go first and film me.
(Another set of cowards argues in front of the prison.)
- Go. - Fine, fine.
Why would you film me from behind?
- You have a camera. - What are you talking about?
(He gathers his courage and takes a step forward.)
(He ends up running away.)
(Jae Seok, wait for me.)
(A director on the move)
(Don't scare me.)
You...
Sung Yong.
(He gives up right away after getting a scare.)
(The 3 cowards fail.)
Which way do I go down?
They said it's scary.
(So Min goes to the underground prison.)
(I wonder why the members failed. How scary is it?)
(The lighting is spooky.)
(It feels like someone will come out.)
What should I do?
What should I do? What should I do?
It was so scary.
Of course it was.
The air itself...
- The walls emit chills. - I know.
That's scary.
(So Min braves the chills and moves forward.)
That's the bed.
(She arrives at the bedroom where the ghost is frequently seen.)
Isn't it here?
Isn't there a syllable?
(Isn't there a syllable?)
Should I take a picture just in case?
(I hope I take a picture of the ghost.)
Gosh, that startled me.
(So Min runs out of time before she finds a syllable.)
- So Min. - Hold on.
Did you find it?
You know, I went downstairs.
- Did you find a syllable or not? - I went down...
the scary underground prison.
I took a picture of the bed in hopes to capture the ghost.
I hope the ghost is in the picture.
What?
(What?)
(Is there something in the picture?)
Isn't this it? It's a ghost.
(Is there a ghost in the picture?)
(She took a picture of the wall.)
There is something strange on the wall.
It's a wall.
- Isn't it a smudge? - No, it's not.
(Isn't it a smudge?)
(The smudge is far from a person's face.)
A ghost?
Let me see it.
It's not a smudge.
I took a picture of the ghost's head.
- Look at this. - It's not a ghost.
(The members only have one syllable so far.)
How will we find four syllables?
Would you give us more time?
The time isn't enough.
Let's go, Da Hee.
(Let's find the rest of the syllables.)
I will be back.
She is brave.
It was the same with wing walking. She doesn't get scared by anything.
I get scared of things like Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear...
where they intentionally try to scare you.
Since this isn't that, I'm okay. I hate when people try to scare me.
The sounds won't scare me.
You're so cool.
Da Hee, can I treat you like my brother from now on?
- Pardon? - Can you go without a cameraman?
- Me? - Yes, alone.
Sure. I'll go without one.
- Really? - Are you serious?
I'll try going there alone. It's a bit scary, but I'll try.
- I want to try going there alone. - Why?
(They're unable to understand.)
Why would you? It's better with a cameraman.
(She's strolling around with a selfie stick as if it's her house.)
(She explores the room with the bed in question without any hesitation.)
(The cowards are trying their best to guess with just a word.)
- "Bl". - We have to put it on there.
- There's a number here. - Yes, which number is it?
- It's number 1. - The 1st syllable must be "bl".
That's the first syllable.
It's Vladimir. Right?
(All right! The first syllable is "bl".)
- Blanka? - Blanka?
Isn't Blanka from Street Fighter?
That's right. Blanka.
Brazilian?
(A five-syllable word that begins with "bl"?)
- She's... - Did you find them?
- Yes, but I... - Did you find two?
No, I think I found the entire name.
- Really? - Yes.
- The entire name was in there? - I couldn't find syllables.
- Da Hee is amazing. - What good news.
So listen. I couldn't find syllables...
written in Korean.
(Not like the syllables you found earlier.)
- Hey, you must find them. - I...
(Suddenly feeling disappointed)
I went to the place where this person shows up a lot.
- Was it written there? - Isn't this it?
So what did you take photos of?
Wait, you didn't find what you were supposed to.
- The Korean syllables... - How could you sound so shameless?
- What? - Take your hands out of the pocket.
I have the photos in this pocket.
- Did you take photos? - Show us now.
The English name... Isn't this it?
Mary... Isn't it Blandy? Blandy?
- The first syllable is "bl". - It can't be Mary.
Isn't it Blandy? Isn't it Mary Blandy?
- No, "bl" is the 1st syllable. - That's the 1st syllable?
- Blandy Mary? - It has five syllables.
When I hear, "bl", all I can think of is Vladimir.
That was Horowitz's last name.
But Vladimir was from Russia.
- Yes, he was from Russia. - Right.
- Blair. - That's a woman's name.
- "Blair Witch" is a horror film. - Yes, there is one.
- There's a film by that name. - I even remember the poster.
- It's red and about a woman, right? - Right.
Well, Blair is a woman's name.
I think that movie is about witches.
- Is the movie about witches? - Yes.
Anyway, she's a witch. She can be a ghost.
Hey, let's go with Blair Witch.
Let's try that. That's the best answer we can come up with.
- Let's go with that. - Right?
- 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
- Blair Witch. - Blair Witch.
(Their answer is Blair Witch.)
(If Blair Witch is the answer, they won't stay at the haunted hotel.)
(Blair Witch...)
That's not correct.
(Blair Witch isn't the right answer.)
(We're doomed. We have to sleep here.)
The right answer is...
Mary Blandy.
(The right answer is Mary Blandy.)
The right answer is Mary Blandy.
I told you so. It was Mary Blandy.
But you said "bl" was the first syllable.
I never ever said so.
- It says number 1 here. - It says number 3 here.
- Really? - What did you say?
(The name Da Hee discovered earlier was...)
(the right answer the staff had hidden.)
(And the hint, "bl" which Sang Yeob took a photo of...)
(was the 3rd syllable.)
- There's a number here. - That must be the order.
It's the first syllable.
(After this, they kept thinking about words that began with "bl".)
I don't know why, but Kwang Soo said that it was number one.
- You said it was number 1. - Why did you say that?
You all said it was number one after reading it.
- Gosh, Mary Blandy. - You all agreed that it was one.
- She took a photo of that. - She took a photo of the answer.
Hey, who said that was the first syllable?
- Everyone said it was number 1. - No, you said it was number 1.
You all looked at it and said it was number one.
- No. - I asked if it was number 1 or 3.
- Everyone said it was number one. - Did I take a photo of the answer?
- It was Mary Blandy? - Yes, it was Mary Blandy.
Everyone said it wasn't right. You all said I was wrong.
(They will stay at the haunted hotel despite getting so close.)
(We'd like to welcome the guests of our hotel.)
The small one came in.
(Seok Jin, So Min, and Da Hee will sleep here.)
I'm glad. I should pick a good spot.
I won't sleep near the wall.
I have no choice.
(Gosh, how am I going to sleep in here?)
Darn it. What if I get sleep paralysis while sleeping?
What's going on with you, Da Hee? You had to wing walk during the day.
- Right. She did every penalty. - Yes, she did.
- You have the worst luck. - Today,
she did all the heavy lifting for this week's filming.
No, I don't have the worst luck.
I just don't get good members.
(You have no idea.)
Da Hee was the unluckiest.
Gosh, this room is so chilly.
I hate this cold air.
When you close your eyes and open them, you might see a ghost.
(In that case, I won't close my eyes.)
This is my concern. They said that this place was cursed.
I'm scared that I'll carry it.
(It won't rub off on me, right?)
Matilda, you're so beautiful.
(Matilda is a British ghost.)
(They lie down with a sense of foreboding in the spooky air.)
(The morning breaks at the hotel. Did the members survive the night?)
(Snoring)
(They're sleeping well as if it's their house.)
Everyone.
(They are in deep sleep and won't move an inch.)
Everyone, it's morning now.
(We should head to the airport.)
I'll just sleep here.
(She's half asleep.)
(Don't wake me up.)
What is it?
Everyone, a car is waiting outside. Let's hurry.
(We should go back to Korea.)
The location of this place isn't bad at all. I slept so well.
I slept like a log and didn't have any dreams.
(They're enjoying the trip as much as Team Luxury is.)
I slept so well.
(I couldn't visit since you were sleeping like a rock.)
It wasn't cold at all.
It was warm like the embrace of my mother.
(The hotel was comforting like his mother's embrace.)
Seok Jin is so funny.
- He said it was warm like his mom. - Gosh, I slept so well.
(I think I might be back given how warm it was.)
- I'm going to get in the car now. - Why did you wake me up?
You should've let me sleep. I was sleeping really well in there.
(We got you a morning flight. We didn't know you'd enjoy it.)
- We're leaving now. Okay. - The tickets are in the car.
- Good job. - We're leaving now.
(They completed their mission at the scary, haunted castle.)
(The Shuddering Package ends at last!)
(The Shuddering and Luxury Package Projects are completed!)