(6am, Gimpo International Airport)
Please come this way.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin are...)
(the only ones here.)
- Let's get you your microphones. - Microphones.
(Why are they the only ones here?)
For goodness' sake.
We are here due to the briefcase. What are the others doing?
(Last week)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin had to pass on the penalty.)
(It was a match between them and the others.)
(It's game over if we get caught.)
(They escaped to the best of their abilities,)
(but defeat was inevitable.)
(The penalty belonged to Jae Seok and Seok Jin.)
You know,
it was impossible to escape from six members.
Jae Seok, I had nine bells on me.
You had one bell on you.
How could you get caught with one bell on you?
I had bells all over my body.
I felt like I was having an exorcism.
It sounded like it.
I got caught the moment my chase began in earnest.
- For goodness' sake. - It was ridiculous.
- For goodness' sake. At least... - Gosh.
I went down a floor. I took the elevator down a floor...
and got caught by Haha.
- I don't feel like listening. - What?
(Jae Seok cuts him off.)
Stop talking.
I don't care how you feel.
- I care more about how I feel. - Listen.
Stop talking.
I am only talking because there are cameras.
I wouldn't talk if there were no cameras.
- That's why people call you fake. - Fake?
You only talk when there are cameras.
- You do the same. - No, I don't.
- I talk whether there are... - Do you want to be punched?
Do you want to be punched?
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
(I have to carry out a penalty with this annoying man.)
- This is driving me crazy. - All right.
Your Blank Penalty Ticket now has a destination.
(They don't know where the ticket will take them.)
Where are we going?
(The destination is...)
(Busan)
It's Busan.
(We are going to Busan.)
- Busan? - Thank goodness.
That's the beauty of life.
(He talks as if he is from Busan.)
- We are going to Busan. - Seok Jin.
Be glad that you are still alive.
Seriously.
Let's go right away.
Now, we will go to Busan...
and meet many people there.
Why are you running the show by yourself?
- What? - Let's get some toasts. Come.
(Let's get some toasts. Come.)
- Toasts? - Come on. I am buying.
I like running the show.
There is such thing as editing.
They will edit out the process of getting there.
- What are you talking about? - There is no need to say goodbye.
People in Busan, we will see you soon.
What are you doing?
Are you meeting friends there?
- I haven't been there in a while. - Me neither.
(Let's see how their penalty trip goes.)
(Seoul to Busan)
(What kind of penalty awaits them in Busan?)
(Chuseok Brothers arrive in Busan.)
What are we doing?
This is the penalty tour of Jae Seok and Seok Jin,
the Century Couple, whose combined age is 100 years.
The number you have to get through the part-time job...
(The number you have to get through the part-time job is...)
Part-time job?
What?
The number is 100. It's 100 in a Day Race.
Part-time job?
(It's 100 in a Day Race.)
(The talk about part-time jobs and number 100 is driving me crazy.)
- This is driving me crazy. - This is driving me crazy.
- Take the map of part-time jobs. - Part-time job?
Seok Jin has never had a part-time job.
What kind of part-time job do we need to do?
- Take a look at the map. - We can't do 100 jobs a day.
We prepared the part-time jobs that represent Busan.
You must choose three at the very least.
Depending on the job, something like 1 serving, 1 box,
or 1 doll gets added up.
You can go home after you reach 100.
- Listen. - It's 100 for the both of us.
While the idea is good, I can't work with someone like him.
Hey. I work if I have to.
- I had a part-time job. - When did you?
I had a part-time job when I was in university.
That's ridiculous.
- I had a part-time job too. - What was it?
I worked at a coffee shop.
My friends came and drank so much coffee.
And they put it on their tabs,
- so I paid 13 dollars with my pay. - Goodness, Seok Jin.
- Putting aside the part-time jobs, - I...
I'm better off doing it alone. He hasn't had any part-time jobs.
He can't hold down a job.
- Hey, I can do it. - Seriously.
Hold on. Can 2 people fill up 100 by today?
It won't be easy.
Hold on. This isn't possible.
- We need at least one more person. - No, no.
There's no one.
- You know what? - What?
I have two more chances to hit Kwang Soo.
(It was last week after a mission during their match.)
(Jae Seok still has two more chances to slap Kwang Soo's forehead.)
(Jae Seok decided to keep them and hit him whenever he wanted.)
- That's right. Gosh. - What?
I didn't plan this,
- but I didn't hit him. - What?
- You didn't. - I didn't slap his forehead.
- What is it? - I still have two more chances.
Yes, you do.
- Do you want to call Kwang Soo? - Hold on.
(Here's our chance.)
Think about it. We can't do it by ourselves.
- Tell him to come get his slaps. - Whenever...
We must tell him to come.
He's not coming here to do the part-time jobs with us.
- He's coming for the slaps. - That sounds fun.
I should tell him to come so I can slap him.
- He has to keep his promise. - Precisely.
- Nice. Good thing I didn't hit him. - This turned out well.
- Then we couldn't have called him. - Hold on. It's Kwang Soo.
- He's not supposed to come. - Hello, Jae Seok.
Where are you?
I'm at a hair salon.
When does your filming start today?
When does it start?
It's 10am, but you're getting your hair done at the salon.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Remember that last week,
I didn't slap your forehead when I was supposed to, right?
(He starts the conversation.)
Yes.
Your voice already sounds a bit nervous.
(You must have caught on already.)
I still have two more chances to slap you.
- Yes, I should get them later. - Yes, you just said so yourself.
You said you'd get them later.
- I'll slap you later, not now. - Fine, I'll take those slaps.
- I'll take them. - Okay, great.
Come to Busan.
(Okay, great. Come to Busan.)
(Come to Busan to get your forehead slapped.)
(Did he say, "Busan"?)
You said so yourself.
You said that you'd get them later.
- Why Busan though? - Come to Busan.
Seok Jin and I came to Busan to carry out our penalty.
- Hey, come. We told you to come. - Come to Busan.
- Kwang Soo. - Are you being serious right now?
- Yes, I'm serious. - We're serious.
If it's a joke, stop it.
This isn't a joke. This is really happening.
- We're serious. - Come quickly.
- No. - I'm telling you this again.
- Other members... - Why didn't you slap me last week?
I told you. Last week, I was...
Anyway, you must come to Busan.
(Stop talking, and just come to Busan.)
- Jae Seok. - What?
Cut me some slack this once.
That's not the point. I can't do that.
Come now.
If I go there... Okay.
Okay.
I'll go to Busan because I'm angry.
- I'll be there. - Come quickly.
- When I get there... - Hey.
Hey, just get this.
With you here, it will be the Unlucky Trio.
It will be complete only when you join us.
I can just go and get two slaps, right?
- Yes, come get your slaps, and go. - Right.
Come get your slaps, and go. That's it.
- Okay. Okay. I'm coming. - My gosh.
Hurry. Come quickly.
- Okay, Jae Seok. - Okay.
(To take advantage of this guy...)
And as for the forehead slaps,
- I won't do it when he arrives. - Right.
- He needs the slaps before leaving. - Slap him later.
(He needs the slaps before leaving.)
(I can use him as much as I want and slap him afterwards.)
- Keep stalling him. - I mean...
He'll wait until we finish working.
Think about it. We need to get every help we can get.
- Gosh, this will be fun. - Two people won't be enough for it.
Are we close to Busan Station now?
Yes, you can see the map there.
- Let's go to the closest one. - Let's go to the closest one.
- Let's go to Busan Station first. - Sure, sure.
Seok Jin, let's not kid around today. Let's work hard.
- I'm going to. - Work hard.
- Do you think I won't work hard? - Don't be lazy.
- Hey, you know... - Hey.
- You know... - I read the online forum too.
(I'm going to work hard!)
A lot of people criticized me there.
(Seok Jin, the lazybones)
- I'll work when we're rolling. - Okay.
- You cannot leave his side today. - Hey.
- Take your time changing tapes. - Seriously. Today,
you must keep filming him. Stay by his side at all times, okay?
Let's go. Let's get going now.
Gosh, this is crazy.
(What kind of part-time job awaits them at Busan Station?)
(Meanwhile, at a fried chicken restaurant in Seoul)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Jong Kook. - Look, fried chicken!
- It's fried chicken. - Go inside.
- Go inside. - Is this real?
- Can we have this? - You're going to make us...
do something hard today. Is that why you're feeding us?
(Anyway, they're being too nice. Something is off.)
Where did everyone else go?
- Everyone. - Yes?
Good job on solving the secret of the briefcase for two weeks.
- That's right. - Eat as much as you want today.
(This is a reward party!)
(Thanks to winning the Chuseok Race, it's a feast from the start.)
This is good. Isn't it good, Ji Hyo?
(Thank you, Chuseok Brothers.)
- This is good. - It's good.
- This is good. - I don't usually eat fried chicken.
It's delicious.
(Jong Kook has a taste of the victory at least for today.)
Where did Kwang Soo go by the way?
- Right, where is he? - What about the other members?
- They had that flight ticket. - Right.
- Did they leave for the penalty? - Blank Penalty Ticket.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin received the Blank Penalty Tickets.
Right now, they're carrying out a penalty to reach the number 100...
with their part-time jobs.
- My gosh. - I just hate the thought of it.
Where did Kwang Soo go?
And Kwang Soo...
and Jae Seok had a reckless bet.
- Kwang Soo owes him two slaps. - Right.
Jae Seok summoned Kwang Soo to Busan so he could slap him.
(Kwang Soo is going to Busan thanks to this playful guy.)
He called Kwang Soo then.
- He did it because he's bored. - That's right.
(What did Kwang Soo do to deserve that?)
(At that time, at Gimpo Airport)
(Kwang Soo who got tangled up out of Jae Seok's boredom shows up.)
(Hello. Am I really going to Busan?)
(Gosh, the weather is perfect for a trip to Busan.)
Let me put the microphone on you.
(He really starts filming now.)
Is this really happening?
(He keeps checking as he gets his microphone.)
Is it really happening?
Yes, didn't you get the call?
I mean, I did get the call.
(I mean, I did get the call.)
Seriously?
Am I really going to Busan?
(Yes, you're really going.)
(Even in front of the boarding gate,)
(he keeps questioning the reality.)
(Even after getting on the flight,)
(Seok Jin. Jae Seok. I'll see you soon.)
That playful guy started again. What a jokester.
(Kwang Soo, have a safe trip.)
What are we doing today?
Everyone, today,
since you guys won the race last week,
you can enjoy your vacation to the fullest and go home.
- We're going to have fun? - Yes.
- We can do whatever we want? - Of course.
- I can do what I wanted to do. - We can do anything?
- A one-day date. - Last time...
(Then I want a one-day date.)
- With whom? - Yes, go on a date for a day.
(Who is it? Is she going to start again?)
- She'll say whomever she wants. - Ahn Jae Hong.
- Jae Hong? - Great. You two make a nice pair.
- Or Lee Je Hoon. - Lee Je Hoon?
Or Woo Do Hwan.
(Here's another one.)
- Her type is so clear. - Do Hwan is nice.
I didn't know, but he's from Anyang.
- Is that why you like him? - He's nice because he's from there?
- Of course. - Is that why he's nice?
And he has a serious face too.
(He's handsome just like guys in Anyang.)
His face belongs to Anyang. His eyes are nice too.
I like Jinyoung from GOT7.
I became his fan now.
He's handsome. He's really handsome.
We can go on a date until I get my name tag removed.
(Is this a race of love?)
I'll take it off right away.
You two will be on a date while running away.
- We can chase after you. - That's right.
You'll put on the tracking device.
You two will hold hands and run away.
- Gosh, you'll run away. - We'll hold hands while running.
So what's going on with you and Hong Jin Young?
(We're way more interested in your story with Jin Young.)
- That was sudden. - The ratings keep going up.
I want to date someone on TV too.
You two can be just like Noh Sa Yeon and Lee Mu Song.
Since it's our vacation, we can do whatever we want, right?
I want to do fun games. I just want to have fun.
- That sounds great. - I like that.
I want to do drinking games.
Hey, he's the best at drinking games.
- I want to play those games. - Are you good at those games?
- The one that goes like this? - I'm the best at it.
(Of course, I know.)
(It sounds familiar and feels nostalgic.)
(She seems like she made others drink a lot.)
- Something like that, right? - Can't we just drink in peace?
- I saw Jong Kook... - Why play games?
- do this a lot at gatherings. - What is it?
- Raise your glasses high. - Seriously?
- Is this... - May our friendship go deep.
- Seriously, Jong Kook? - Raise your glasses high.
- Jong Kook. - Level the glasses evenly.
That's how he is.
- Jong Kook, you're being too lame. - My gosh.
Only old geezers do that.
Seriously?
- Loyalty! Yes! - Yes!
- Let's go, men. - Drink it, men.
- Bottoms up. - Right.
- Bottoms up. - Be a man.
- A man must empty his glass. - A man must empty his glass.
Gosh, that's scary.
Okay, you will...
present your idea for your vacation one by one.
- Should I go first? - Should I start?
- Mine is really simple. - Okay.
- We're going to grill pork belly. - Gosh.
- We'll grill pork belly. - That sounds awesome.
Instead of eating pork belly at restaurants,
- I want a place with a nice view. - Nice.
(Eating pork belly on a rooftop with a nice view.)
A place on a high hill where we can look down and eat.
Like a rooftop with a nice view.
(Let's eat pork belly while looking at the busy city.)
I want to eat at a rooftop with a nice view.
- Sangsang Madang has the best view. - Totally.
(The best view is at the front of the yard in Hongdae.)
That has a nice view.
Isn't that the place for the best view?
- That place is also... - That place has an awesome view.
- I'm serious. Right. - You can see Geun Sik there.
- There... - Here's mine.
- I've been wanting to try this. - What is it?
Riding a bicycle...
- on a sunny, breezy day. - Okay.
- That one is nice. - Riding a bicycle is nice.
- This will refresh us. - It's the perfect season for it.
- We can only do it now. - Right.
(How about riding a bike to wherever the wind and the sun lead us?)
We can get on the tandem too.
- A bicycle for one? - No, a tandem.
- A tandem? - Tandem?
- We should call Jin Young then. - Then...
(If it's a tandem, we should call Jin Young.)
- Call Jin Young too. - Right.
(Everyone with the same name might show up.)
- I should give her a call. - You should call Park Jin Young.
- You should call Park Jin Young. - Ji Hyo will call Park Jin Young.
We can invite Park Jin Young too.
Let's see what So Min wrote.
I want to go to a sauna.
(So Min wants to go to a sauna.)
- You want to wash yourself. - We could relax there.
- We could eat eggs too. - Sounds good.
- Saunas have everything these days. - Sikhye too.
They even have karaoke rooms.
- You can get a massage too. - That's right.
- They have everything. - Okay.
I wrote this.
"Enjoying surfing".
(Jong Kook wants to go surfing.)
I love surfing.
I went surfing in Yangyang County, and it was so fun.
(Surfing in Yangyang County relieves stress.)
Surfing is so nice.
Wouldn't it be boring on the way there?
(What did you say?)
- What? - Hold on.
Once we get there, it'll be really fun.
You want me to make sure you're not bored even on the way to Busan?
(You want me to make sure you're not bored even on the way to Busan?)
I can make you run along the street once in a while.
- Run? - You won't be bored.
- We could play games too. - Of course.
I want to help you out, but I can't.
Also, don't sit so far away from me.
What? Why?
Our seats have changed.
Don't sit far from me.
Sit down.
It sounds like fun.
There's something I really want to try.
Escape rooms.
(It's popular these days.)
I've never done it.
Only those who manage to escape can go home.
- Really? - Doesn't it sound fun?
- It sounds difficult. - If we work together,
- we can finish early. - I like it.
I love escape rooms.
But we need someone smart.
- We have some. - We have some.
There's me.
You...
- What did you say? - Hold on.
Hold on.
You want to take a quiz with me?
I'm definitely going to lose.
I might be able to beat Haha though.
- Hey. - Come on.
You and your brother can't beat me.
- My brother? - I can even beat you both.
You just brought up my brother?
Come on. I can beat Haha.
Now, I've heard your wishes.
Let me announce the real rules for today.
(Let me announce the real rules.)
Real rules?
(What's the real theme?)
What is it?
(What are they going to do?)
Winners Get to Relax.
Special Vacation, Relax for Now.
Relax for Now?
You've written down five vacation plans.
You have to carry out all of them.
But you have to pay for all the expenses...
with the money given by the staff.
(They have to pay for the expenses with the money from the staff.)
As soon as you run out of money, you'll be sent to Busan.
(If they run out of money, they'll be sent to Busan.)
In Busan, you'll help Jae Seok and Seok Jin complete their penalty.
- That's not okay. - That's not okay.
It takes so long to go to Busan.
(We don't want to go to Busan.)
To save money, you can get help from acquaintances.
(They can get help from acquaintances.)
How much money do we get?
You'll choose a pouch randomly.
10 dollars is too little.
- We can't even buy the meat. - We can't afford everything.
Even if we get 200 dollars,
we won't be able to afford all the activities.
- That's right. - 200 dollars is not enough.
- Who wants to pick a pouch? - Ji Hyo.
Okay. Ji Hyo should do it.
- Se Chan, pick one. - Pick 200 dollars.
No. If I do it, I'll be humiliated.
Ji Hyo, pick 200 dollars.
- "Humiliated"? Hold on. - What?
Is that the appropriate word for this situation?
If I make a mistake...
No. It's wrong. Hold on.
It doesn't...
- suit the context. - It doesn't, right?
Let's say you were teasing Haha. You were saying you could beat him.
But you lost to him 5 to 0.
That's when you say you were humiliated.
- Is that right? - Yes.
You can't use that word in this situation.
How smart you are.
(How smart you are.)
(You're so smart, sir.)
Okay. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
- No, no. - He just said you're smart.
You're smart.
I just said you're smart.
Even if you say I'm smart, it all depends on the nuance.
Try it again.
- How smart you are. - There you go.
How did you say it before?
How smart you are.
It's different, right?
- Yes. - Se Chan.
Don't make Jong Kook angry.
His nipples are...
While I'm wearing this t-shirt, I get horns if I get angry.
Don't make him angry.
I get horns not on the head, but on the chest.
Don't give me horns. Do you know why I'm wearing this bag?
To cover them up? I should focus. Okay.
- He just got horns. - I'll focus.
- It's pretty thick. - Really?
It's thick.
Good. It's thick.
- Are there many bills? - Are there many bills?
There are many.
(It's not just 10 dollars.)
Let me see.
(It's 50, 100, or 200 dollars.)
(The more money they get, the less likely they are to go to Busan.)
- Let me see. - It must be a lot.
- No. - How much is it?
(Just 50 dollars?)
Gosh. It's not a lot.
- 30 dollars? - It's 50 dollars.
We can't afford everything.
It's 50 dollars.
What can we do with that money?
We can't do much with 50 dollars.
(Each member can spend 10 dollars. What will happen to them?)
- This place is so nice. - It is.
What kind of work will we get?
Let me tell you what you'll do first.
Full of old stories from Busan,
Story Bicycle Tour.
- Story Bicycle? - Story Bicycle?
Senior docents...
give tourists a bicycle ride...
around the city.
They explain the history behind the tourist attractions.
He doesn't just give a bicycle ride.
- He chats. - He... Gosh.
- That's not the right word. - I mean...
He talks.
Please be more polite.
I mean...
He's older than us. Use a more appropriate word.
He seems to like it.
Story Bicycle...
- He seems to like it. Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you, sir.
- Nice to meet you. - Hey.
- Don't try to speak in a dialect. - Be quiet.
He thinks he can speak in a dialect.
I'm good at speaking in the Busan dialect.
That's good.
What do you think?
- It's okay. - It's okay?
- It's close enough. - Close enough?
- Hey. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Hey.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
I'm Yu Jae Seok, the Son of Busan.
Why are you the Son of Busan?
You're from Seoul.
When I'm in Daejeon, I'm the Son of Daejeon.
- I'm... - I'm a Story Bicycle rider,
Jang In Gu.
Mr. Jang In Gu.
We have to do a part-time job today.
Can we work...
as Story Bicycle riders?
Yes, you can.
You're supposed to explain to the tourists...
about the modern history and culture...
briefly.
- To do this job, - How are we going to do that?
we should know a bit about the modern history and culture.
I'm not sure if we can do it.
I'll briefly teach you how to do it.
How long have you been doing this?
It's been four years.
That's not so long.
What are you talking about?
Story Bicycles haven't been around that long.
This job hasn't been around that long.
It started four years ago.
So you've been doing it from the beginning.
That's right.
- You're one of the oldest. - During the peak season,
how many customers do you get?
We get group customers too.
Sometimes, 80 to 100 students visit at once.
(80 to 100 students)
If we get 100 customers, we'll be done.
Do you get more customers on the weekends?
Of course. We get more then.
On the weekdays, we get less.
You must have been very busy yesterday.
It must have been a busy day,
- but I was away. - Why?
It was a personal reason.
(A personal question makes him shy.)
May I ask what it was about?
I'm afraid I can't answer.
You don't want to talk about it?
- No. - Okay.
- Did you just take a break? - Kind of.
(He ends up telling the truth.)
You're changing your words.
You're making me curious.
- It is a personal reason. - That's right.
Are there things to remember while working?
- Tell us. - There are.
There are two very important things.
- What are they? - When you start the bicycle,
keep your feet off the ground.
- Isn't that obvious? - If you do that,
your feet can get stuck.
Who would put their feet on the ground?
- It happens. - That's right.
It's okay while the bicycle is moving,
but when you start,
you should never accelerate. The bicycle might fall.
It can fall backwards.
It must be important...
for the passengers' safety.
It's important for your own safety too.
(It's important for your own safety too.)
(I protect myself.)
- You know... - Don't forget...
these two things.
Our own safety is important too,
but we should put the passengers' safety first, right?
That's right.
You should protect both the passengers and yourself.
Your glasses are a bit small. They look like your eyes.
It looks like you have very big eyes.
We'd like to try riding it first.
- Try it then. - Okay.
We should know how it works.
I'll explain about a few places on the way.
- Okay. - We should memorize them.
This is it.
It's called a Story Bicycle...
because you listen to stories.
- It's a Story Bicycle. - Story Bicycle.
Right.
How fast can it go?
It's not that fast.
But the speed is not important.
It should go slowly.
It's for sightseeing.
(They'll look around the city on a Story Bicycle.)
(Busan Harbor Bridge, 168 Stairs)
(Choryang Catholic Church, Choryang Elementary School)
- Oh, my. - It's moving.
- It's pretty strong. - It's...
It's quite fast.
You shouldn't put your feet on the ground.
The driver shouldn't.
The wind is so refreshing.
(He's like a tourist.)
The sea wind is blowing.
(They forget about their mission for a moment.)
It's so refreshing.
Feel the sea wind.
The wind is blowing from the mountain and the sea.
This area is so beautiful.
It's so cool.
It reminds me of my childhood neighborhood.
Small alleys like these are disappearing.
This is so nice.
- I lived in an area like this. - Me too.
(Every alley seems to have a story.)
Do you see that bridge...
- across the sea? - Yes.
It's Busan Harbor Bridge.
- Busan Harbor Bridge. - Busan Harbor Bridge.
There's Namgu on the left.
It's connected to Youngdonggu on the right.
The total length is 3.3km.
- "The total length is 3.3km"? - Yes.
There are 168 stairs in this staircase.
It's the only shortcut that connects the two neighborhoods.
If you don't take this route, you must go around.
However, no one takes the longer route.
- Right. - No one would.
- This is Choryang Catholic Church. - I see.
In the south of Hangang, this is the oldest church.
- South of Hangang? - Yes.
Celebrities have graduated from Choryang Elementary School.
Famous people graduated from here.
- Who? - Who are they?
- Singer Na Hoon A. - Who else?
- Lee Gyeong Gyu. - Did he graduate from here?
- Right, he did. - From this school?
- You should get going. - Okay.
- Seok Jin, try it first. - Shall I?
- Wait a minute. - On the left...
- are the brakes. - The brakes?
This is the accelerator. Did you hear what I said?
- Yes. - Keep your foot on it.
If you accelerate too fast, it'll jerk up.
Wait, let me get off.
(He's worried.)
Get off.
I'm holding the brakes right now.
- Give it a try. - Okay.
Wait.
(Surprised)
Take the wheel and look forward.
(Seok Jin is flustered.)
- Goodness. - It jerked.
(Tumbling)
- Seriously. - That's why I warned you.
It's not that. Get out of my way.
Director, it's dangerous.
He can't control it very well.
Go slowly.
- He's bad at driving. - Okay, I got it.
I got it. Okay.
(Let me drive anything with wheels.)
(He drives smoothly.)
It's very sensitive.
- You drive it well. - It's sensitive. I must be careful.
You still drive it well.
I'll start the part-time job.
- We need customers first. - Customers?
- There aren't many. - We need tourists...
- instead of Busan locals. - On Mondays,
- there aren't many tourists. - Right.
- There aren't many on Monday. - Right?
There are some my age though.
- Shall we talk to them? - Did they come for sightseeing?
Wait.
Hello.
- Hello. - Are you here to travel?
- Yes. - Where are you from?
- We're from Taiwan. - You're from Taiwan.
- Would you like to go on a tour? - Would you like to look around?
- Okay. - Can you understand Korean?
Seok Jin will take you around here.
I'll take you around. You got very lucky.
Please enjoy your trip.
See you.
(Jae Seok lets Seok Jin take the customers.)
There aren't many tourists here today.
(There aren't any tourists.)
Hello, hello.
- Hello. - Do you live here?
- Yes, I own this place. - You're the owner?
- We are... - It's nice to meet you.
I assume you were too busy running your store.
- Have you gone on a tour here? - No, I haven't.
- You never went sightseeing? - I wanted to get on the bicycle.
They told me to ride it at Busan Station.
- Would you like to ride it? - Yes.
What do you think? Would you like to ride it?
- Where are you going? - I'm going over there.
Please come with me.
They live here,
but they never rode the Story Bicycle.
Please get on. It's this way.
(He invites 2 customers.)
Come this way.
We'll get going. Are you ready? Are you ready?
- Yes. - Yes.
Did you put your seatbelts on, Kang Soon and Min Soon?
Here we go, Kang Soon and Min Soon.
- Be careful driving. - Yes, don't worry.
- Here we go. - Goodbye.
- Enjoy your ride. - Thank you.
(Story Bicycles take off.)
- Are you having fun? - Yes.
I'll work hard to make the trip enjoyable.
- Let's see. I'll explain. - Okay.
Look at the building on the side. It's Choryang Catholic Church.
This is Choryang Catholic Church.
Repeat after me, "Choryang Catholic Church".
- "Choryang Catholic Church". - "Choryang Catholic Church".
I say "Choryang", you say "Catholic Church". Choryang.
- Catholic Church. - Choryang.
- Catholic Church. - It's Choryang Catholic Church.
This is the first church in Korea.
Wait, a bus is coming. I'm in trouble.
(He reverses.)
A car is coming.
(He goes back again.)
Wait, what's wrong with this?
(He's completely flustered.)
It's sliding back.
(Is this for fun?)
(I'm in trouble.)
I'm in trouble.
Why doesn't it go up?
Did the engine turn off? Since when?
(He needs to be taken care of.)
Now, it works.
I'm sorry.
(Will he finish his tour safely?)
Can we use it all at once?
- Of course. - By the way...
- Okay. - I never rode Jong Kook's car.
- It's a great start. - It's lively indeed.
It's lively.
Let's say two members can go on a trip.
- Pardon? From what? - You can pick two members.
(He hopes that she picks him.)
- Whom would you pick? - Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
(Her answer is curt.)
(Their feelings get hurt.)
It's better to be with my peers. I don't have to do as much.
Whom would you pick, Haha?
- Right. - That's a good question.
- I pick Se Chan and Kwang Soo. - See?
Look at his look. I pick Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
(What about me?)
- Look at the look on his face. - Wait a minute.
I was just kidding.
This is a variety show. We should laugh.
- It's entertainment. - Wasn't it funny?
We traveled abroad a lot.
- I know. - Were you that uncomfortable?
- What about you, Ji Hyo? - Don't touch me.
How dare you touch my hand?
Let's hear Ji Hyo's answer.
Whom would you pick?
(Jong Kook trusts Ji Hyo.)
I also pick Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
It's okay.
What about you, Jong Kook?
- He won't pick me either. - What about you?
- What about me? - Who would you travel with?
I pick Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
(Jong Kook picks Jae Seok and Seok Jin.)
(I won't pick you.)
The three of us will go. I'll take Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
- This is funny. - Imagine how fun it would be.
- It would be fun. - Wouldn't it?
(Where is the van going?)
- Are we going to a sauna? - A sauna?
We're going to your destination and to ride the bicycle.
Are we doing them all at once?
- Of course. - I'm curious.
(Is Jong Kook recommending the first vacation spot?)
(They thought about the first vacation spot.)
(I know a place for bike riding and sauna.)
(Do you mean a sauna where you get beaten?)
(The sauna is free, and Jong Kook knows best.)
We'll do them all at once.
(Just trust me and follow me.)
(The car arrives in the middle of Gangnam.)
- Here we are. - Where is this place?
- Where are we? - Where are we, Jong Kook?
Let's go in first.
Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go in.
Hurry.
(Where is this place where bike riding and sauna are possible?)
- Okay. - It's a gym.
(It's a gym.)
- It's a gym. - Okay.
- Is this the place? - This is it.
(Is this where they'll take their vacation?)
- It's free. - The bike ride is free.
(He's right after all.)
- Look at this. - We could also...
If you ride it, the wind comes out. Do you feel it?
- There's wind. - Ride it with the wind.
- This is not what I meant. - Check out the breeze.
- There's wind. - This isn't it.
Do you feel the breeze?
- This isn't it. - Have a seat, Ji Hyo.
- Hurry and sit. - Ji Hyo.
- Just do it, Ji Hyo. - Sit down.
Have a seat. Once you pedal, you feel the wind directly.
This isn't the bike ride I was talking about.
That costs money. We can use these for free.
- What do you say? - This is his strategy.
That's right.
- Do you agree that it's a vacation? - Agree.
It's true that it's a bike, and we can feel the wind.
- We should agree. I like it. - I say...
- This is what I imagined. - Okay.
- I like it. - That's right.
Traveling with Jong Kook is the best.
- Be honest. Don't do this. - What's wrong?
- He's the best guide. - That's right.
This isn't it.
We're happy.
This will be accepted as Ji Hyo's...
- bike riding in the wind. - Okay.
- That's right. - It's perfect, Ji Hyo.
Get on. This is the vacation you wanted.
This is a special bike for you.
When you pedal, the wind comes out. See? It's cool.
- It's cool here, right? - Stand in front of me. I'll do it.
- I like this place. - You shouldn't just stand there.
- Go and walk. - Where?
- Shall I? - Jong Kook, give it a try.
- It's a strange equipment. - This is...
- What is it? - Try it. It has a parachute effect.
- "Parachute effect"? - Walk while pushing without hands.
- Like this? - Okay.
Jong Kook is so excited.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- This is great. Okay. - Look at Jong Kook.
Can you lower the seat?
- Lower it? - Yes.
Stand up. Wait. It's done. Try it.
- How is it? Okay. - It's great.
- This is good. - Are you okay?
- Yes, Jong Kook. - Are you okay?
He's so friendly because we're at a gym.
- Seriously. - He's friendly.
- He's very excited. - Hold it and be stable. Right.
Doesn't it feel like an amusement park?
- It does. - Right, everyone?
It's amazing.
- Se Chan, are you uncomfortable? - I'm great.
- Why? - I was just curious.
- On my back on this side. - Your back?
- Okay. - Why?
(Drilling)
Wait a minute, wait!
(This massaging drill will free you from all soreness.)
- Wait! - What?
Why are you using that on my back?
- Wait. - What's that?
It's a massage gun.
I was so surprised.
What do you think? Doesn't it feel nice?
You too, Haha.
I...
I got a massage yesterday.
Your neck is stiff, right?
Your neck is stiff.
(Screaming)
(He can't deal with Jong Kook's kindness.)
Seriously...
We need to loosen up your muscles.
It's a drill.
(You don't have to thank me.)
Hey, doesn't it feel nice?
I have to escape.
Run!
- Run! - Where's So Min?
- So Min! - I'm okay.
- I'm really okay. - Come here.
- I'll work out on the stepper. - I'm exhausted.
I'll work out.
Let me massage your neck.
(Massage)
(She spits out the water.)
(Jong Kook's kindness makes her spit out water.)
- Hey! - So Min.
- Hey! - What?
Are you trying to kill me?
I'm just giving you a massage.
It feels nice.
It hurts.
- Massage his bottom. - Okay.
- You have to lie down. - Do it.
- Lie down. - Lie down.
Lie down on your side. Position your legs like this.
Bend your leg. Keep the other leg straight.
Right here.
- Here. - No.
You can't use it just anywhere.
You're an expert.
It...
(The treatment begins.)
Hold on!
Hold on. It feels weird.
- It feels weird. - It's okay.
It feels nice.
(It feels nice.)
(He confesses while fighting for his life.)
- It feels nice. - What?
- What do you mean? - Hold on.
(They're done riding bicycles in the wind.)
Let's start.
It's very breezy today.
- The weather is very nice. - Don't be afraid.
You picked the right day.
It's a perfect day for a stroll.
(Jae Seok's bicycle is going up the hill smoothly.)
I heard it takes two hours.
It takes an hour or two.
I've seen it.
I didn't know it went to small alleys too.
You didn't?
- Small alleys are disappearing. - People don't know.
They don't.
This is where it goes.
You didn't know?
You live around here, but you didn't come here often?
I had no reason to.
I get up in the morning, work, and go home at night.
I've been doing that for 40 years.
- 40 years? - Yes.
I moved here from Seoul in 1977.
You're from Seoul?
I worked at an office...
until 1977.
(The Busan citizens start to talk.)
We worked so hard.
We exported a lot in the 70s.
The neighbors were so friendly.
It was so nice.
People were very kind.
(The Busan citizens can't stop talking.)
I wanted to get on one of these today.
- You wanted to try it? - Yes.
I was lucky.
I wanted to get on one of these since it's so breezy.
(Jae Seok can't find the chance to talk.)
- The 168 stairs are here. - Yes.
Have you seen them?
- I take them every day. - You do?
Do you take the monorail too?
Yes. I take it every day.
We live up there.
But we don't take it on weekends.
- Why not? - There are so many tourists.
They should take it.
I want to promote Choryang-dong.
I didn't know there was a street like that.
I didn't know they were selling old snacks.
I had no idea.
- Here are the 168 stairs. - That's right?
I wanted to explain about it,
but you already know so much about it.
Bye.
(They're the natives.)
Don't be afraid.
I've had no accidents for 25 years.
Look at that.
That's...
- Choryang Elementary School. - "Korean Wave Stars"?
There are some famous stars who went to this school.
(Many Korean Wave stars went to Choryang Elementary School.)
Have you heard of Na Hoon A?
- No. - No?
(He suddenly starts to sing.)
(What? We've never heard that song.)
Well...
I know a Chinese song.
Which one?
(Confident)
- You know this one? - Yes.
("Fairy Tale" by Michael Wong)
- You know this song? - You're a great singer.
(The customers are impressed.)
(Sing with me.)
Together.
(In an unfamiliar place,)
(they met a familiar face and a familiar song.)
(The tour may not be much, but they made a lot of memories.)
You know this one.
(Our fairy tale will have a happy ending)
(We love it.)
Thank you.
(Seok Jin succeeds in providing customized service.)
Which Running Man member do you like the most?
(We just sang together, remember?)
Ji...
(Is it me?)
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo?
(You like Ji Hyo?)
- Song Ji Hyo. - She's beautiful.
I see.
(Yes, she's beautiful.)
Look at that. You can get closer.
Those are the 168 stairs.
There are 168 stairs in total.
Up there...
Uptown...
and downtown...
(He explains in simple words.)
The stairs connect the two neighborhoods.
The residents think it's so convenient.
(Photo time with Seok Jin)
(Seok Jin is a great singer, but we love Ji Hyo.)
Have you seen that bridge before?
Yes. But I've never crossed it.
It's Busan Harbor Bridge.
I've only seen it.
I've never crossed it.
It's 3.3km long.
- It's really long, right? - It's so long.
It's beautiful.
It's even more beautiful at night.
- The night view is amazing. - I heard it's amazing.
It's very colorful.
(Busan Harbor Bridge looks even more beautiful at night.)
You've never taken a picture here, have you?
No. This is my first time.
- All right. - Please take a good one.
She lives here, but she's never seen it before.
All right. Here we go.
I wanted to show you around, but you already know...
- so much about this area. - No, no, no.
It would have been too hard to talk alone.
(Let the native people help you.)
(He gains respect for the Busan natives.)
(Jae Seok and his customers are back to the starting point.)
Where is Seok Jin?
(Speaking of which...)
- Did he take another path? - This is the only path.
This is the only path.
(There's no other path.)
(They're on the right path,)
(but they're struggling.)
(It's hard to control the bicycle.)
(We'll be a little late.)
(Please go first.)
Don't worry. Nothing will happen.
- That was good, right? - Yes.
(It suddenly stops.)
(The bicycle suddenly stops again.)
(Seok Jin fails to finish the ride.)
We're finally back.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You're a great driver. - Let me unfasten it.
- He's a great driver. - There you go.
Thank you.
High five.
See you. Bye.
- Go, Running Man! - Running Man.
Go, Running Man!
It's four down now.
- Just four? - Just four.
Hold on.
It's almost noon already.
At this rate,
we'll have to stay here for a month.
We won't be able to go back today.
Hold on. Where is Kwang Soo?
- He should be here. - Choryang Elementary School...
Okay. Goodness.
(You want to know where I am?)
(I came to Busan,)
(but is this really happening?)
Okay.
(My phone is ringing.)
- Hello. - Hi.
Where are you?
I think...
I'm almost there.
You should be standing in front of me right now.
Okay.
- Hurry up. - I should keep my promise.
- Hurry. - Okay.
Where is he?
I'll let him flick me twice, eat wheat noodles, and go back.
We should do another part-time job.
- Let's go. - Hold on.
- We can't go back at this rate. - We can't.
- When will we finish 100? - When will we finish 100?
(They have to hurry up and finish 100.)
He's here. Kwang Soo is here.
(Kwang Soo traveled from Seoul to Busan to be hit on the forehead.)
Okay.
(100 in a Day Race's guest, Actor Lee Kwang Soo)
You really came?
You came?
Okay.
I shouldn't have said it.
(You should be careful with what you say.)
Okay. I should keep my promise.
- Pick up your phone. - Hello.
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
What is this?
- Why is he here? - Why aren't you here yet?
I'm here!
- I'm in Busan! - He really came.
- I'm here. - Just go back.
- He's here now. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Don't get the wrong idea.
The thing is,
I didn't skip it on purpose last week.
Everyone forgot.
- I forgot too. - Exactly.
Everything has been recorded.
- I admit it. - Okay.
All right. Then...
- Let's move to the next spot. - Let's go.
(You admit it?)
What are you talking about?
He didn't say when he'd hit you.
Did I say when?
- I didn't, right? - What?
Let's just go.
- I have a shoot in Seoul. - What?
(Are you serious?)
Hit me right now.
- Do it. - Get up.
What's going on?
I have to go back.
Get up. I have to go back too.
We were supposed to start at 10am, but it's past that.
I have something to do at a chicken restaurant.
- Look. - What do you mean?
- We're shooting too. - Aren't we shooting?
- I know. - Look.
- Do you know him? - I...
- Do you know Kwon Ryeol? - I do.
- You don't know him? - I know everyone.
Exactly.
- Listen. - This is Running Man too.
I'm different from you.
I heard the other team is having a party.
- They're having a party. - What party?
- Theirs is a vacation race. - It's a vacation race.
People who were invited aren't there yet.
(What party?)
This is a vacation.
(Only Jong Kook is excited.)
Shall we go to Gukje Market?
Let's go to Ohryuk Island. Let's go there.
Let's go to Ohryuk Island, Kwang Soo.
- Let's go there first. - Ohryuk Island?
- Let's go there. - Okay, let's go.
You still get a flick on your forehead.
(Ohryuk Island)
(They go for their part-time job.)
We have to get 100 people. We're in trouble.
100 people?
It could be 100.
- You don't need to worry. - Don't worry.
You won't be penalized, so don't do anything.
- Okay. - It makes no sense.
You'll only get a flick on your forehead.
(Don't worry about 100.)
(You need to flick my head then.)
I can't flick your forehead because I'm working right now.
How long will this take?
Kwang Soo, I'm here to be penalized.
This is my work for today.
I shouldn't have said that.
(He regrets saying it last week.)
Think about it. We must get 100 soon...
for my work to be over.
You can help us so that work finishes soon.
What?
(What? Help?)
- I don't want you to. - Come on.
- I don't want you to help us. - I don't either.
However, we have to finish soon so you can go back to Seoul.
You're horrible.
I've never seen such a brat like him.
I can't stop him.
I gave up.
It makes no sense.
The way you're thinking is already not making sense.
(They arrive at Ohryuk Island, their next part-time job's destination.)
(What kind of part-time job will they do here?)
We'll go do our part-time job.
(However,)
(where's Seok Jin, the other part-timer?)
(Part-timer Seok Jin)
(Wake up. It's time for your part-time job.)
(He was sleeping deeply.)
Is he sleeping?
(He looks around.)
(Do you feel refreshed?)
Hey.
Why did you get out so discreetly?
- Goodness. - Why did you leave discreetly?
Why did you sleep?
What about our part-time job?
I was recharging my energy during transport.
You should've said, "Seok Jin, we're here."
Why don't you use your mouth?
It's the same for you. You're rude.
- Seok Jin. - Goodness.
You got so startled.
This is great. Is that Ohryuk Island?
(It's a beautiful island.)
Thanks to me, you get to see this view.
- It's beautiful here. - You should pay me.
It's really beautiful.
What's skywalking?
(What job will they do?)
(It's time.)
- Jae Seok. - This is great.
(I have something to tell you before your work starts.)
What?
Not here.
I can't do it here.
- I'll do it later. - I came all the way here.
I have to work now.
(I'm too busy right now.)
I'll explain.
Your second part-time job is cleaning skywalk glass floors...
at a cliff that's 35m above sea level.
(Skywalk Glass Cleaning)
What?
- What? - Skywalk?
Take a look.
(Today's part-time job)
There's a skywalk at a cliff 35m up.
The skywalk is made up of 24 glass tiles.
We'll count the number of tiles you clean.
(The number is subtracted from 96.)
Clean the floor?
Isn't it see-through?
(They're afraid of heights.)
Listen.
Should I stay here?
Where would you go?
You came all the way here,
so if you help them, we'll count yours too.
So you...
- What are you talking about? - Don't do it.
Don't do it.
Why would I be penalized?
This isn't your penalty.
I won last week. I even got a gift set.
Don't do it.
- Just stay. - Just stay for now.
The manager will explain the details.
- I think... - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - This is what I just heard.
- Do we have to clean the skywalk? - Please stand here.
When it rains, the water remains on the glass.
We have to clean it for other people to see.
- That's why. - To make it look transparent?
- Do you actually do this cleaning? - Yes.
Did it rain yesterday?
It didn't rain yesterday but the day before.
(What does he mean?)
- When? - The day before?
- The day before? - Two days ago?
The day before yesterday.
The day before yesterday?
- The day before yesterday? - The day before yesterday?
- Two days ago? - Yes.
- I see. - He meant two days ago.
- The day before yesterday. - That's right.
After yesterday is today.
- After yesterday is today, right? - Gosh.
- Is it because I'm too handsome? - No.
(His answer is direct.)
I couldn't hear very well.
- Is that so? - You spoke too loudly.
I'm sorry.
Do your ears hurt?
How can he call himself too handsome?
People say that often. People are surprised...
- by my looks in person. - That's an exaggeration.
- Kwang Soo, in person... - Yes?
(How do I look in person?)
(Kwang Soo looks terrible too, right?)
You look different in person.
(You look different in person.)
What?
Did I misunderstand?
- How does he look? - Why?
- What do you mean? - Does he look so ordinary?
- Yes. - I see.
He looked handsome on TV.
- What about now? - It means that you don't in person.
He looks like a regular tourist here.
(You look ordinary.)
(He's complimenting on his ordinary looks.)
- It's a compliment. - Is it?
- Of course. - It's a big compliment.
It's a compliment that you look ordinary.
Thank you.
You seem quite witty.
- Let's go there first. - Okay.
We'll take a look.
Gosh, let's look first.
How bad is it?
Please come this way.
(They approach the skywalk with confidence.)
- It's made of glass. - Is it?
(What's this?)
Are there 24 of them?
If you succeed, 24 gets subtracted.
(They must clean the glass floor over the sea.)
It's okay up to here. There's something underneath.
- You're right. - There's something here.
There are rocks.
We can clean this part.
You must wear these.
- Overshoes? - Okay.
The total must be 28.
Right.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin put on the shoes.)
We can clean up to here.
Put the shoes on, Kwang Soo. What else will you do?
(He gets strategic.)
I'll take a look around.
Put them on. You have nothing else to do.
- Come for now. - Just come.
(Put the shoes on first.)
This isn't hard.
(He's confused as to what's going on.)
- This isn't... - The ground is underneath.
Gosh, it's high up.
- Look at that. - Goodness.
- Look over there. - I can't go.
(It's okay up to where the rocks are.)
I'm sweating.
How can we clean them?
What do we do?
(How can we clean them?)
The sea is below us.
What are you doing? Come here.
(He looks at the floor.)
(He takes off his overshoes.)
(I'll just look at the view.)
- What? - Come here.
- Why? - Why are you taking them off?
- What? - Why are you taking them off?
Come here.
You need them to clean.
You want to leave soon, right?
- I should leave. - Then you should clean too.
- Why... - Clean the floor.
- Help us, Kwang Soo. - What?
You came all the way here. You want to leave soon, right?
- I have to leave soon. - I know.
This isn't your penalty.
You're just helping us.
Let's do it together. Help us.
- Then... - Yes.
I will...
(Is this how you'll play?)
I will clean eight floors.
After that, flick my forehead.
(Flick my forehead as a return.)
Just once.
I'll clean here.
I'll clean four on each side.
- No way. - No.
We should play rock-paper-scissors or something.
Otherwise, you have to stay here.
- It'd be funny. - Exactly.
How shall we divide it?
That's the most difficult one.
1, 2.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
The highest difficulty level is...
- level 3. - Level 3.
This is level 2 and level 1.
This is...
level two.
Level three is insane.
Level three is like being in the air.
Okay.
(How will they assign the levels?)
How about Race of Wits?
No way.
(Stop playing Race of Wits.)
Hey, no.
- Come on. - No way.
Do you like Race of Wits?
(Please, Kwang Soo.)
- It's not bad. - Come on.
(It isn't so bad.)
- No. - What else would we play?
- There's nothing else. - It can't be Race of Wits.
I'll get level three.
You don't know that. Just play quickly.
I'll say one.
- Go ahead. - I'll say one.
Get ready.
- I'll say one. - Me too.
Start.
(Race of Wits starts.)
- 1. - 1.
I was first.
(I said it first.)
- I said it first. - We said it simultaneously.
- The three went at the same time. - It was simultaneous.
- My goodness. - Let's go again.
Do it again.
Get ready.
Start.
- 1. - 1.
(It's simultaneous again.)
- Stop it. - I can't do this.
- Stop. - I can't do this.
I can't do it either.
It doesn't work. Everyone is saying one.
This game doesn't work.
How about drawing lots?
Let's do that.
- Sir? - Yes.
Give these out randomly to the three.
Mix them up randomly.
Mix them up and hand them out to us.
(The three part-timers' fates depend on this man.)
(Please hand out the papers.)
What was that?
(Throwing)
- Was this for me? - Sir.
It looked like you were feeding pigeons.
- That startled me. - I automatically picked it up.
- He did a great job. - Let's do this.
(How's this?)
- What? - Let's show the papers to him...
and decide whether we'll switch or not by watching him. It's clean.
Open the papers in front of you.
- 1, 2... - Don't look at the camera lens.
I won't. 1, 2, 3.
(They show the levels to him.)
- All right. - Did you see them?
- Yes. - Close them.
- Should we close them? - Yes.
Would you like to switch?
(Thinking)
(Should I switch with Jae Seok?)
(His face is hard to read.)
Should I switch with Kwang Soo?
(What does that facial expression indicate?)
Five...
- Okay. - Okay. Switch.
You open yours first.
- Hold on. - 1, 2, 3.
(Seok Jin was only watching him. What level does he have?)
(It's Level 2.)
This is not bad.
We got the extremes.
(Would you like to switch?)
Level two is not bad.
If Kwang Soo had the bad one, he would have smiled, right?
(Will Jae Seok take the offer?)
- Let's switch. - Okay.
Are you switching?
- You never know. - That's true.
1 is Level 1 while the other is Level 3. Guys!
(1 person is closer to land, while the other is closer to the water.)
(Who will be mopping the glass floor above the sea?)
Okay!
(Kwang Soo is Level 1.)
(Okay, this is great!)
(Am I Level 3?)
(Mopping the glass floor is the best.)
(Let's say we didn't switch.)
What? You two deal with it.
I like being in the middle.
- Let me make a suggestion. - Okay. Good.
If you slap my forehead right now,
we'll mix the papers up and I'll let you pick first.
- That's great. - Are you giving me a chance?
Yes. You get to pick again.
Right. That's great. He's being generous.
(Jae Seok is a coward, so that's a tempting suggestion.)
He needs to be slapped on the forehead twice.
(He has to slap his forehead twice anyway.)
- If I slap your forehead once... - He'll mix the papers up again.
We'll mix them up, and I'll let you pick again.
This is a great bargain. This is unprecedented.
- Okay! Good. - Okay.
(It's a deal.)
- Of course, you'll accept it. - Good.
I have to slap your forehead over there.
- Where? - By the water.
(By the water on the bridge)
Go there.
Once I hit you, you'll be in the water. I'll be on land.
- This sounds fun. - Go.
You'll only need to be slapped one more time.
- That sounds fun. - I know.
(Halting)
Just a little bit more.
- By the metal. - Goodness.
- By the metal. - By the metal. Over there.
This is no joke. You can go this far.
- This is just water. - There's no time.
We have to work. You have to go that far.
A little bit more.
(He hesitates.)
I've never seen anybody who's so enthusiastic about this.
(It's time to subtract one slap.)
He has to get slapped on the forehead to leave.
- Every slap is precious. - Right.
(The humiliation I faced for this moment)
(For two slaps on the forehead,)
(he went to Busan instead of Seoul.)
(For that one slap on the forehead...)
I never thought I'd be doing this in Ohryuk Island.
(He speaks all of a sudden.)
- Kwang Soo, - This is thrilling.
- this is significant. - Indeed.
- All right. It's one slap, right? - Yes.
(This is going to end the cycle of malice from last week.)
It's just one slap.
(He'll get 1 out of 2 slaps taken care of.)
One slap.
(Slapping)
(He aimed accurately.)
(That sounded good too.)
(Crawling)
(In the midst of this, Kwang Soo is scared of the sea,)
(so he runs away on all fours.)
Hey. He got up in a second.
(I'm sorry.)
(Kwang Soo takes care of 1 slap.)
That was the loudest slap I've ever heard.
- Are you all right? - That was the loudest.
There was water, so I slapped harder than expected.
- You'll have calluses on your hand. - I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I swear that was the best slap on the forehead...
- I've seen. - Right? That was really intense.
(Kwang Soo made history again with this slap.)
- This is the last chance. - Yes, it is.
You have to accept the result this time.
Nobody knows.
(It's time to pick again.)
- Catch them in the air. - What?
- Catch them in the air. - In the air?
- Okay. Good. - Catch them in the air.
You can see them fall.
(There's no turning back now. This is the last chance.)
- You have to accept this. - This is the end.
There are no more chances. We have no time.
- We have to finish and move on. - Right.
We have to move on.
(Jae Seok throws the papers.)
(They are going to take one each.)
(They all want to avoid Level 3. Who has it?)
I don't know. I just grabbed one in the air.
- We have to accept the result. - This is it.
This is.
- 1. - 1!
(They must accept the result whatever it may be.)
Two!
Three!
(Who picked Level 3 and will have to stand above the water?)
This is it.
This is.
- 1. - 1!
(They must accept the result whatever it may be.)
Two!
Three!
(Who picked Level 3 and will have to stand above the water?)
(Kwang Soo has Level 3.)
(Seok Jin has Level 1, and Jae Seok has 2. That's not bad.)
(I'm not even supposed to be receiving a penalty.)
(What am I doing in Busan?)
- Let's start. - We can't do anything about it.
Level three gets switched between you and me.
(His forehead hurts, and he's scared to start cleaning.)
I got level one.
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- Here. - Okay. Start cleaning.
- Please hurry. - We have no time.
- Kwang Soo, there's no time. - Let's go.
The butterfly effect is enormous.
- Let's go, Kwang Soo. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
We promised though.
I'm so refreshed.
- We worked out... - Please pick the next one too.
and got a massage,
so let's go to a sauna.
(She's nervous.)
- Do we have to go somewhere? - There's one here.
- Here? - Of course.
(Trust me.)
- Where's the sauna here? - There's an awesome one.
I'm scared. I'm getting scared now.
We won't stop.
Let's go!
- This is a vacation! - I'm scared.
- Stop it! - I'm scared.
- I'm scared too. - Jong Kook.
It's okay. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Okay. Let's go.
(They're nervous but follow him regardless.)
Where's the sauna here?
It doesn't have to be hot.
- What do you mean? - There's...
Is this what you meant?
Yes. It's a cold sauna.
- What? - It's a cold sauna.
- Really? A cold sauna? - Athletes around the world...
would submerge their bodies in ice baths...
right after they work out. This is the cold sauna.
It's great for recovery.
- Is it refreshing? - You drop the body temperature.
Men can take up to minus 160°C.
(Their faces feel numb just by looking at it.)
What if you break?
Does this hurt?
- What? No. - Does this hurt?
- It's just refreshing. - Is it refreshing or cold?
It's refreshing. It will improve your condition immensely.
Would the five of you accept this as a sauna?
- Well... - This is good.
This is much better than the regular saunas. It's refreshing.
- Have you seen the cold saunas? - Yes.
It's just like that.
This is the cold sauna. It's refreshing.
When we go to the sauna, some people go in...
and others stay outside to eat snacks.
You can eat snacks. Of course.
(They're falling for it.)
- It's the same thing. - If you think about it...
Cold sauna makes sense too.
Yes, it's still a sauna.
- This isn't bad. - Okay.
- I'll approve this as a sauna. - A cold sauna.
- Okay! - You can eat some boiled eggs.
Don't worry, So Min.
(Trust me, So Min.)
- Do we get sikhye and boiled eggs? - Yes.
So Min and I'll go get them.
Okay. The youngest two.
Then...
let's sit on the mats.
I'll bring some.
(The gentleman brings out the mats.)
Two should be good.
I've never seen Jong Kook so motivated.
- He hasn't been this happy... - Look at him walk.
- in a while. - He's light on his feet.
- Look at his face. - We have to hurry.
- Spread them out. - Okay.
Let's spread them out.
He's so bright.
Okay.
This actually looks like a sauna.
(Our boss is insane! Kook's Sauna)
Do you want a massage?
We're in a sauna anyway.
(Free massage)
- Do I? - Yes.
- Where are you hurting? - My lower back.
- I see. - My lower back.
You just have to loosen your muscles there.
- Is it left or right? - Both.
Watch. This is great.
I'm serious.
If you loosen up this part, your back will get better.
- I'm serious. - Jong Kook.
(His customer is satisfied, so he's happy too.)
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook! I'm not kidding.
- Your feet too. - Goodness!
(This is his first customer, so a foot massage is a bonus.)
(I love it!)
You have to loosen your feet.
- You should, Haha. - No.
Is this from "Infinite Challenge"?
- What? - Your hair.
This is the hybrid style.
(He also gets his hair done.)
(While the first customer is getting a full service...)
I never thought we'd be coming to a gym.
You tried to provoke him a lot.
- To whom? Jong Kook? - Yes.
I'm going to act up now.
I tried a few times, and he didn't hit me.
Wait. He'll be shocked once he sees this on TV.
Edit it out.
(I'm sorry, Jong Kook. I tried to look strong.)
I want this chocolate milk.
If you drink that, Jong Kook will...
- Get it. I can get it for you. - I really want this.
(They only have 50 dollars. They can't get anything else.)
- Do I just get one? - Let's share.
Okay.
- We have to just in case. - Here are the eggs.
(They decide to share the milk.)
Should we get these ones?
- No, this is stone-baked. - Okay.
The other ones taste better though.
- Sikhye. - This is good.
Hold on, So Min.
- Can't we get these? - Let's get these.
Right? Let's get these.
- We can save some money. - This is stone-baked too.
Jong Kook will compliment us for this. Get two.
- Six? - Tell him you got them.
- He'll give you credit. - Okay.
Drink this.
- Aren't you going to drink it? - I will,
but we have to get rid of the receipt.
(She pays for it separately so that Jong Kook won't know.)
- You can do that. - That'll be 4.80 dollars.
(She's so meticulous.)
(They have 43.90 dollars left.)
Hurry and drink this.
Is that right?
I don't want to drink it.
(He betrays her.)
- I don't want it. Wait. - You have to drink it.
- Wait. No, So Min. - Take a sip.
- I... - Hurry.
Take a sip.
- It's okay. - My bad.
- Hey. - You.
- Hurry up. - You hit me.
- Take a sip. Hold on. - Let's walk.
- You have to drink it first. - Let's walk.
Take a sip.
Me first?
- We have to wait for them. - Do we? Okay.
Drink it now.
Drink it. You have to.
- You are so... - Look.
If you're going to get into trouble, it's better to spare one person.
Take a sip. Hurry up.
Stop faking it. Drink it.
Drink it, you punk. Hurry up.
- I'll drink it. - Drink it.
- I will. - Hurry up.
Okay.
(The one who can't drink and the one who has to make him drink)
Hurry up.
(10 minutes later)
Guys.
- What is this chocolate milk? - What is this?
- It's So Min. - This wasn't on the list.
She had one.
Hey, So Min.
- What is wrong with her? - She was smart though.
You might blame her,
but we got these eggs.
(Don't be so harsh on her. The quail eggs were her idea.)
- This is her idea. - Good job.
- So Min, they're okay. - Good job.
Come in. You're good.
- She had this. - Come in.
Okay. Let's get in the sauna.
We have to get going.
- Did you want to go? - Well...
I usually lie down on the floor when I go to the sauna.
Same here.
Let's go.
You have to put these on. Get changed...
and put these on. You have to put on a gown.
(You have to wear fur boots?)
Do I have to put those on?
How cold is it?
(How cold is it?)
- Jong Kook, you go first. - Me?
- We want to watch you first. - I've done it many times.
Show us what it is.
Okay. I wanted to do it.
(What kind of a sauna is this?)
Is this cooled down already?
It needs to be cooled.
The temperature dropped.
It's minus 180°C... It's minus 174°C. Oh, dear.
(Do you go in minus 180°C with no clothes on?)
Oh, my goodness.
It's getting cooled down.
(Jong Kook is used to this, so he's relaxed.)
Is minus 170°C good?
Is that minus 170°C?
(This is not the sauna I imagined.)
This is great for improving your condition.
(The door to the world of ice opens.)
(There's thick smoke, and Jong Kook goes in.)
This is great.
- Does it start at minus 160°C? - What?
He can handle up to minus 180°C.
Is this what athletes do?
Yes, like Cristiano Ronaldo.
This is what he does.
It's decreasing more.
He's doing what Cristiano does.
It's minus 180°C, Jong Kook.
- Are you all right? - Yes.
This is great.
- Is it good? - Yes.
I can feel it on my skin.
This is what I'm talking about.
This is a great vacation for him.
(This is great for Jong Kook.)
It's prickly.
(We don't need to go to a hotel. This is a sauna vacation.)
I'm serious.
My hairs are frozen.
- I'll give him the gown. - My hairs are frozen.
- Your arms... - They're shiny. They're frozen.
Hurry.
- Hey. - Goodness.
(He opens the door.)
His buttocks are so high.
Goodness.
Why do you only show this on "Mom's Diary"?
(He finishes by flashing his muscular back.)
Close it.
This is good. You showed it on Running Man too.
(Jong Kook's sauna is endlessly generous.)
- Who's next? - I'll go.
All right. Let's go!
Haha! Don't do it!
Don't do this!
I'm serious, Haha.
Please, Haha.
Don't do it.
No, you're almost there.
- How many seconds do I have? - You're almost there.
How many seconds do I have?
Tell me!
- This is good. - Don't talk down to me.
(He's flustered.)
(It's the personal trainer's fault.)
(I'm so sorry.)
(He doesn't even have the gown on.)
(What did I just see?)
Put this on.
(I'm sorry for not protecting you.)
Take your hands out. Good.
- You're going down to minus 160°C. - I'm in so much pain.
- No, you're good. - Go down to minus 160.
For goodness' sake.
(As the temperature drops, he turns more vulgar.)
- I'm in so much pain. - You're not.
- It's okay. Take your hands out. - I'm in so much pain!
- I'm in pain. - Take your hands out.
- Right. - I did. Don't you see them?
- Stay like that. - Hurry.
- 10 more seconds. - 10 seconds.
Stop lying.
Really?
(His lips are frozen.)
Come out, kid.
(She's the only one not laughing.)
(This is not the vacation I dreamed of.)
(I wanted to relax somewhere warm.)
- I... - Go in, So Min. Hurry.
- Go in. - This is not the right sauna.
Just go in.
I'm so cold.
- It's minus 127°C. - I'm cold.
- It's below minus 100°C. - I'm so cold.
- This is refreshing. - Really?
Right?
(She gets used to the cold.)
This is refreshing.
(She's enjoying it now.)
There's smoke coming out from her mouth.
This is refreshing.
- I feel younger. - Do you?
I feel younger.
My legs... They're prickly.
It's over.
(Team Seoul completes the second item on their agenda.)
(Success)
(Meanwhile, on the skywalk at Ohryuk Island, Busan)
- Come over here. - Okay.
(They start cleaning.)
- Take this... - Yes.
and wipe off the moisture.
You point down.
You remove the water through the gap.
- Level one is the easiest. - Is it?
You can start. Two of you,
get the clothes.
- Remove the moisture. - All right.
(He's slow.)
Remove the moisture.
- Use more force. - Okay.
Go farther.
- You can't leave any moisture. - I know.
- He doesn't clean at home, right? - No, he doesn't.
- I knew it. - Right.
(He can't deny it.)
Hurry up. You have to cover the whole area.
(Honey, I'll do better.)
Start wiping this area first.
Here first?
(They start wiping the glass.)
(They're gathered around the first tile.)
This...
(Wiping)
I can't help but look down.
- I can't help it either. - Right?
This system was set up so that you have to look.
I'm in trouble.
- Excuse me. Go down there. - I...
6th and 7th tiles.
Excuse me. Go down there.
(There?)
Seok Jin will do 1, 2, and 3.
I'll do this one.
(I can't go.)
Goodness.
- Keep going. - This is driving me nuts.
Oh, gosh.
This is the Maginot Line.
(You come across the edge of the cliff.)
What should I do?
It's fine up to here.
(Level 2 is fine.)
(Kwang Soo can't even get to Level 3.)
(How's Seok Jin doing in Level 1?)
Oh, gosh. Goodness.
(Is Level 1 easy?)
(Wiggling)
It's fine up to here.
(If you keep going,)
(you reach the end of the cliff.)
1, 2, 3, 4.
This is the end of the 8th tile.
This is the end.
I did the eight tiles.
(He completes the task.)
(They are jealous.)
(He moves hurriedly.)
Gosh, that was easy.
Level one was easy.
Okay.
- I am done. - Don't look down.
(His back is hunched.)
(It's the blood-chilling Level 3.)
(I don't know how I will go there.)
(He first removes water with a mop.)
- This is no joke. - I am going to die.
(There is only the sea below his feet.)
I don't think I can do this.
(He feels helpless.)
(It's impossible for Kwang Soo to enter Level 3.)
(Shall I muster up my courage?)
(How is Jae Seok doing with Level 2?)
This really is a part-time job.
(He mops the tiles diligently.)
(He looks like he is on "Real Life Experience".)
The tiles became really clean.
(Jae Seok is almost done with 8 glass tiles.)
(Hesitant)
It's so scary here.
It feels really different when you go over there.
I wouldn't be able to go over there.
(Welcome to the seaside cliff.)
(Only 8 glass tiles of Level 3 remain at this point.)
(Scrubbing)
(He spends 5 minutes on the 1st tile.)
(He has no intention of moving forward.)
Hurry up.
Kwang Soo, I have an idea.
(You aren't getting anywhere.)
Work without looking.
(Without looking?)
(Like this?)
(What is he doing?)
Kwang Soo, you can do this.
- What? - Do this.
(Like this?)
Mop like this, Kwang Soo.
(His eyes are open, but they don't see anything.)
Don't look.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Don't look. Don't look.
- Look down. - No.
Kwang Soo, don't look.
Kwang Soo, don't look. That's it.
This is why you should pick well.
I can't believe him.
What?
Kwang Soo is helping us even though this isn't his penalty.
What about it?
"What about it?"
You should come and help.
You should go farther down. Why aren't you moving an inch?
You can't go farther down.
Kwang Soo.
My heart is there with you.
(Kwang Soo is the only one at Level 3.)
(He moves his limbs in solitude.)
Give it to me.
(The second most timid man comes to help the timidest man.)
- This is no joke. - I will wipe without looking.
I will wipe without looking.
(The two timid men switch places.)
(His neck is stiff.)
(Dragging)
Jae Seok.
- You didn't wipe the tiles. - You removed a lot of water.
- You removed a lot of water. - I did, right?
You removed a lot of water.
Move closer to the inner wall.
(He moves closer.)
That's good.
- It's not working. - Jae Seok, it's not working.
- Really? - Yes.
I will do it.
(He steps forward confidently...)
(and looks into the distance.)
Move closer to the inner wall.
This is driving me crazy.
(Screaming)
(Waddling)
(The three timid brothers find it hard to mop the floor.)
Is there a better way?
(He sinks to the floor...)
(and wipes the floor as if he is moonwalking.)
- That's good. - That's good.
He is like a machine.
- That's perfect. - That's good.
You are doing a good job, Kwang Soo.
My goodness.
(The timidest man is doing a good job.)
- That's good. - That's good.
- That's good. - You are doing a good job.
- Don't look down. - Keep going.
Don't look down.
That's right.
That's good. Don't even blink.
That's good.
Don't think about anything.
(He forgets to blink.)
That's good. Don't look down. Don't look down.
Come this far. It's okay.
- There you go. - Kwang Soo.
You can wipe like this.
Kwang Soo, this is a good idea.
Gosh, you are pathetic.
- Wipe like this. - I didn't wipe the frames.
Hold on. I will wipe the frames.
I will wipe the frames. I can do it like this.
(He cleans the glass tiles with a rag and a vest.)
(Let me try it.)
My goodness.
It calms your mind, right?
I feel fine because I don't see anything.
(They begin to clean lying down.)
(Lying down)
Is there still water?
It's right there.
It's right beneath your head.
There you go.
A little to the left. That's good.
That's good.
That's good. That's good.
That's good. Jae Seok.
Clean the tiles like Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is doing an amazing job.
(Like a mermaid swimming towards her dream,)
That's good. That's good. That's good.
(he kicks his feet against the glass tiles.)
Kwang Soo is doing an amazing job.
(Kwang Soo, the mermaid)
That's good. That's good.
That's how you should do it.
(I want this to end.)
The task will be over when the two of you meet.
- That's it. - That's good.
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
The two of you met.
You cleaned all the glass tiles. They became clean.
I will wipe the frames one last time.
They are perfect.
(This is the end.)
You are done. Get up.
I cleaned the frames.
He says we are done.
- Don't look down. - Don't look down.
- We need to go. - Don't look down.
Okay.
All right. Hurry up and go. Hurry up and go. Hurry up and go.
(He hurries over.)
Hurry up and go.
Kwang Soo, grab this.
Grab this.
Hurry up and go.
Get the towel. Get the towel.
(The towel?)
There is another towel.
It's a bit farther up to the right.
Move your hand down a little bit.
There you go.
(The second part-time job finally ends.)
You can stand up now.
It's safe here. It's safe here.
My goodness.
Jae Seok.
- The tiles are clean. - You are right.
The tiles became really clean.
(You can enjoy the beautiful views in a scarier way.)
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you for your hard work.
(The glass floors are 300-percent transparent.)
- We did a good job, right? - Yes.
- My goodness. - I became so nervous.
You should do it again some other time.
Can we come again?
- Come. - Really?
I will buy you sashimi.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - It was so scary.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
We have 72 to go.
(The status of 100 in a Day Race: 72 left)
- Here is the map. - Okay.
(Let's pick the next part-time job.)
Where should we go?
It looks like Hari Wharf is close to Ohryuk Island.
Let's go there.
I hope we won't wipe anything at the wharf.
- If that's the case... - We already did the wiping.
In that case, I will...
No, no.
You still have one more flick.
You still need to get flicked on the forehead.
Stay.
How many do we have left?
- We worked a lot. - We have 72 left.
(Despite their hard work, they still have 72 left.)
This is driving me crazy.
(They begin to wonder where everything went wrong.)
Why are we doing this from early in the morning?
I am yawning so much.
The part-time jobs are exhausting.
(They arrive at Hari Wharf.)
What is this place?
What is this?
- For goodness' sake. - Is that for us?
(At the wharf,)
(a board with pictures of fish for shoe-throwing greets them.)
No way. Are we going fishing?
- What is this? - Are we going fishing?
Is this the part-time job?
When will we get done at this rate?
This is taxing.
You have 72 left.
For this job,
you will experience the lives of the fishermen in Busan.
- Hold on. - No!
Can I remain standing here?
- Listen. - Kwang Soo.
- Leaving won't help you. - What are you going to do there?
Jong Kook is really mad at you.
You are better off with us. You aren't doing much anyway.
I will stay here.
- That's good. - Stay here.
"You aren't doing much anyway"?
(I can't believe you said that.)
My underwear is soaked with sweat.
"You aren't doing much anyway"?
Both my back and my underwear are wet.
- Why are they wet? - For goodness' sake.
This part-time job is...
net fishing at a fishing village.
Net fishing? That's different from using a fishing rod.
That's right. It's not a regular type of fishing.
I haven't tried net fishing.
- You can get 100kg of fish. - I haven't tried net fishing.
You haven't, right?
All of us get seasick terribly.
- Seriously. - Hold on.
- This is the worst team. - I won't get on the boat, right?
- I will wait here. - What are you going to do here?
- You have nowhere to go. - We don't want you to get bored.
You have nothing to do.
On the board are nine fish species that are in season.
Only the fish species you choose by throwing your shoes...
will be counted for the number.
(4 flounder and 4 filefish)
Only the two of you will throw.
- Kwang Soo won't throw it. - That's right.
I won't throw it.
If Kwang Soo throws a shoe...
and gets the same fish species, we will remove it from your list.
- Okay. - Kwang Soo won't throw a shoe.
He is just a helper. He is just...
- Don't be like that. - Listen.
- Kwang Soo, you... - I will throw one too.
You don't need to do that.
If I get a different species...
- If I get a different species... - That would be amazing.
- That would be amazing. - Throw a shoe.
- If you get flatfish... - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- This must be the line. - Yes.
This is the line. Excuse me. This is the line.
Hold on. That is obviously the line.
When I take a step back and watch them,
I can tell that they are cheaters.
- This is obviously the line. - Come on.
- Both of you pretended not to know. - You stay out of this.
- Everyone knows this isn't it. - It's so obvious this is the one.
- It has to be this one. - Why is there a line here then?
- That one is too far. - They put tapes on the ground.
This is where we play our games often.
(These crafty guys are something else.)
- You kind of look like a filefish. - What? Are you moving the board?
You didn't move back to the line, so we'll move this.
- We'll move back then. - Fine, goodness.
No, it's not that.
(Gosh, those petty staff members.)
Goodness, you are too petty.
- Unbelievable. - Did you just call us petty?
Excuse me, but what kinds of fish are in season right now?
- Seok Jin, stay quiet. - Flatfish!
- Sorry? It's flatfish. - Flatfish.
- That will help us a lot. - Flatfish.
- It's the farthest one. - It's at the corner.
- That's too far. - It's not that far.
We can just kick it like this.
- Let's just do it. - What if it goes out of the board?
- We'll do it again? - We should do it again.
We'll do it until we get a fish. Kwang Soo.
We'll begin once you say, "start".
- Let's do a practice round. - This is just a practice round.
(Kicking)
- There you go. - We got the filefish.
- Are filefish in season now? - They said sea bass is in season.
Those three are highest in season now.
- It's sea bass. - Sea bass.
- We should have started. - We should've started this.
(Picking up shoes)
- It was hard to get that one. - Come on, let me try now.
When I come back, you keep kicking. Let me try too.
- Go ahead. - You should try it.
You look like a local from this area.
Hold on. Why isn't anyone getting that for me?
Why isn't anyone getting it for me?
Weren't we going to help each other out?
(Laughing)
- Hey, no one but I would do this. - Yes?
- Seok Jin would never do this. - Thank you.
Look at him. He's not moving at all.
- I'll do it. I'm on a roll. Start. - Start.
Let me go first.
(Seok Jin will start first.)
- Darn it. Come on. - It's out of the board.
(His first attempt goes out of the board.)
- You will try again. - I'll try again.
(Dashing)
- Thank you. - He should go get it. Don't go now.
No, he should exercise when he's young.
What are you talking about? You've been sleeping up until now.
- What do you mean I must exercise? - Make him go get his shoe.
(Seok Jin attempts to use some of his leg muscles.)
(It's out again.)
- Hey. - Don't go. No, don't go.
- You should go get it. - You should go, Seok Jin.
Goodness.
(You should exercise too. Go get your own shoe.)
(Limping)
- Hey. - Go faster.
Move it.
(He's almost there after forcing himself to walk.)
- Hey, you jerk. Hey! - Hey.
(I was almost there.)
You come here.
(Tossing)
(Tossing it back)
(Goodness, these punks.)
- Hey. - You must keep moving.
- You should exercise. - Give it back.
Hey, you should move more. You need to exercise.
Kwang Soo and I are trying to help you live a long life.
- Okay. Start! - Seriously.
(Seok Jin will try.)
- He got it. - That's great.
- Rockfish. - That's great.
(It falls on top of rockfish.)
- Is rockfish in season? - Is it in season?
- Okay, we got rockfish. - Great.
Next.
(Jae Seok will try next.)
I'm aiming for the flatfish.
(Kicking)
(Will it fall on top of the flatfish which is everyone's wish?)
It's flatfish!
(Going out of the board)
(Please let it be the flatfish. That was so close.)
Hey, hey! Make Jae Seok go get his.
You go. Go get your own shoe.
(He's on his way to get his shoe.)
(Stealing)
(He comes and steals the shoe before anyone else does.)
(Clapping)
(His Shoe Dance explodes.)
- That's great. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
(Come get your shoe!)
- Kwang Soo. - Great, great.
Kwang Soo.
(He's venting out his anger by playing with Jae Seok's shoe.)
(Come get your shoe.)
(They are hilarious.)
Let's get the flatfish.
(Jae Seok gets his shoe back.)
Please.
(He will really try now.)
It's flatfish.
- It's rock cod. - Is that in season now?
You can catch a lot of rock cod. There are a lot of fish here.
- We can catch a lot of that too? - Yes.
(Seok Jin: rockfish, Jae Seok: rock cod)
- Kwang Soo, your turn. - Just don't get the same fish.
- Okay. - Kwang Soo, aim for the flatfish.
(If it doesn't overlap, the number of species will go up.)
(Can Kwang Soo overcome his humiliating past?)
- Hey, don't get the same fish. - That looked great.
(Will he be able to become a hero after getting the flatfish?)
(Out of the board)
It fell on the flatfish.
- Hey, don't get the same fish. - That looked great.
- It fell on the flatfish. - Go get it.
(Rushing)
(He gets playful again.)
Hold on.
(Gosh, Jae Seok.)
Until where are you running?
Goodness, you're full of energy.
(Thus began the chase of young guys in broad daylight.)
Ma'am, take this with you.
- Wait. - Ma'am.
(Okay, I got it.)
Ma'am!
(This is how the relay race with his shoe began.)
- Let's shake hands. - Please give it back.
Ma'am, please give it back. Please let me have it.
- Ma'am, it's sponsored. - Here you go.
Wait.
(Kwang Soo's shoe isn't coming back.)
- That's hilarious. - My stomach hurts.
(Trudging)
Kwang Soo, come on. Get the flatfish.
- It fell on the flatfish once. - We should...
- We'll be doomed otherwise. - We should go back home now.
- Okay. Let's end it here. - Please?
- Let's end it here. - Start.
(Flatfish will put an end to this.)
Yours can't fall on the rockfish or the rock cod.
(Will Kwang Soo be able to put his shoe in the flatfish box?)
(Please Kwang Soo, get the flatfish!)
- Flatfish! - Gosh!
(It falls on top of the flatfish.)
Good job. Great work.
- Great. - Great. This is it.
- We can get off work soon. - Kwang Soo, we're good now.
(They can count the fish if they are rockfish, rock cod, or flatfish.)
Seasickness is all about your confidence.
(The weakest members brace themselves.)
There are a lot of fish.
All right. Let's get on the boat first.
Let's get going now.
(They set out to the sea with the hope of a full boat.)
Our part-time jobs are hard today.
I had no idea that we'd be on a boat.
(What kind of future will unfold on the job?)
(The ultimate part-time job begins at last.)
- Gosh. - It's not coming.
(They endlessly spin...)
(and continue to reel it up.)
(But there's no sign of their job ending.)
(They finally open the mysterious pouch.)
I don't know when it will end.
(And)
(When the pouch opens,)
(another game begins.)
(Some chase.)
(Some get chased.)
(A hair-raising twist that no one saw coming)
(What on earth has happened to them?)
(I was told to open this when things get really hard.)
(That would be the end of this.)
(Dangerous Trip Finale: The Pandora's Pouch)