(A culture center in Pyeongtaek is on the brink of early summer.)
- Is this why we're here? - What?
- Are we here to write that? - I guess so.
They said we had to write something. This is driving me crazy.
(My gosh, I have a bad feeling about this.)
Why is my heart beating fast?
- Besides, the space is tight here. - It's beating fast right away.
- We're crowded over a small table. - What's going on?
Before we start our filming today, you must fill out a form.
That's why I asked you to come in.
This is the consent form for the wing walking in England.
(This is the consent form for the wing walking in England.)
(A consent form for wing walking?)
- Listen. - Wait.
- The consent form... - Only the ones who will...
(It's the highlight of the Shuddering Package in England.)
(They'll stand on a plane at 217km per hour without gear.)
(They must have a physical checkup and fill out the safety agreement.)
I was so excited to film today. You should've given this after work.
Exactly. It's bringing down my spirits.
(They are feeling dejected.)
(Feeling gloomy)
To be honest, from what I heard,
- people over 78kg can't ride it. - Is that so?
- It's 80kg. - Right now,
- I weigh... - People over 80kg can't ride it?
People over 80kg can't participate.
- Right now, - I should eat a lot of meals now.
- I weigh 76kg. - I should gain weight.
- I should eat a lot of meals now. - I should gain weight.
I weigh 76kg now.
- Really? - Yes.
- Hey, we should gain weight. - I'm serious.
If you pull a trick like that,
we'll come up with projects which will enable you to lose weight...
- before going to England. - My gosh.
We can start eating a lot starting with the in-flight meals.
How much do you weigh?
I weigh 62kg now.
Goodness, Jae Seok.
Will you gain 18kg?
You are nowhere near close. You can't gain 18kg.
(Is he thinking about consuming an entire cow on the plane?)
- Will you gain 18kg? - Don't say anything.
- If he gains 18kg, exempt him. - Don't say anything.
- Through in-flight meals? - Then you should exempt him.
I'll respect that.
That's right. If he gains 18kg,
I will wing walk without a complaint.
- 18kg through in-flight meals? - Right.
(Please give me high-calorie meals.)
If you do that, we will exempt you.
That means Da Hee and I have no choice but to go.
- Who? - Da Hee and I have no choice.
With Da Hee, you never know.
(Since women weigh less...)
(You never know how much she weighs.)
- Da Hee is tall. - That's right.
So Min...
I will have to gain 30kg.
- Stop lying. - Stop lying.
- What are you talking about? - I am telling you the truth.
- You are lying. - You just need to gain 2kg.
- I am telling you the truth. - "Princess Aurora" was ages ago.
I am telling you the truth.
- So Min, don't be like that. - I am telling you the truth.
Also, why did you say that you needed to gain 30kg...
when no one else did?
- Seriously. - What's wrong with you?
Don't be like that, So Min.
Alcoholics are forbidden as well.
Isn't that for you? Seizure patients can't wing walk either.
Seizure, my foot.
You won't be able to do it.
- Why not? - High blood pressure.
It says here that mental stability is important.
What about it?
- Aren't you two unstable? - No, we're not.
No?
Look at this. "Poor vision poses no problems."
Jae Seok.
(Poor vision poses no problems to wing walking.)
(Do you wear glasses? It's not a problem.)
That won't do.
Losing 18kg is the only way.
(He wishes he had reasons for disqualification.)
For goodness' sake.
- That's his only weakness. - Poor vision?
We have the right to cancel on the day of the flight.
- Can we cancel once we are there? - Oh, they have the right.
(Oh, they have the right.)
Who are they?
Who do they think they are?
We don't have the right.
- We don't have the right. - Really?
Hold on.
I can't climb up the wing through the cockpit.
(The directions for wing walking shock them.)
- Where is it? - You just need to sign...
the official consent form.
(Thinking)
Jae Seok always said that...
- we must watch what we sign. - Of course.
I am serious.
I almost got into a big trouble by signing a document carelessly.
We can never be too careful when it comes to contracts.
We might lose our entire fortune.
Back in the days, stuntmen did this on TV.
- Right. - It makes no sense for us to do it.
Didn't Tom Hanks become famous by doing these stunts?
- Right? - What about Tom Hanks?
He did his own stunts for movies.
- When? - That's Tom Cruise.
I see.
(That's Tom Cruise.)
(The Toms confused me.)
Tom Hanks?
Doesn't he have an intelligent image?
I can't believe you.
This is...
(Time passes, and they become more stressed out.)
You are signing the forms, right?
No one is signing it.
- No one is signing it. - I can't.
- Come on. - Why isn't anyone signing it?
- I can't. - Why isn't anyone signing it?
Isn't there a height restriction?
There is no height restriction.
I am 205cm tall.
Is that okay?
Is it safe for someone my age?
You are closer to the age limit than you are to the weight limit.
- The limit is 65 years or older. - Right.
(He is closer to the age limit.)
- You are closer to the age limit. - You should have been a bit older.
(Grabbing)
What are you doing? What are you doing?
(He tries to sign Kwang Soo's consent form.)
Even if Seok Jin signs...
Hello.
- This form... - Hello.
- We are signing the consent form. - What are you signing?
- The consent form? - It's for wing walking.
- Is that the consent form? - Yes.
Jong Kook, the restroom's upstairs.
- What? - Go away.
- Don't I need to do this? - Get lost if you aren't partaking!
You don't need to wing walk!
I am sorry.
(Gosh, I am sorry.)
Let me take a look.
"Physical fitness"! What is this? Why is this...
- Go to the second floor. - Doctor...
"Doctor certificate"!
(He continues to be flippant.)
I can't believe you need it.
He is so annoying.
(He is so annoying.)
I guess it's possible to get killed. In any case, take care.
You should consult your lawyers...
before you sign that form.
(He is 10 times more annoying than usual.)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Write your names in English in capital letters.
Look at this. You are 53kg.
Why did you say you needed to gain 30kg?
It's only a difference of 2 or 3kg.
(Don't be so fastidious.)
I don't want to write my name.
(He makes sure the others are filling out the form.)
Let's do this. It won't kill me.
- Seok Jin filled out the form. - Are you waiving your life?
Hey.
It has nothing to do with you.
(Another unwelcome guest visits.)
I feel bad.
He should be here.
Haha, you should be here.
He should be where I am.
- Haha. - Yes?
Don't say that you feel bad when you can't even read the form.
- Doesn't it say, "psycho"? - "Psycho"?
It says, "physical", for goodness' sake.
- "Physical"? - "Psycho", my foot.
- He should be here! - For goodness' sake.
Nothing brings a smile to my face.
I can't smile.
I feel bad.
Haha.
If you have signed the form, please turn it in.
Okay, I will collect them.
(Okay, I will collect them.)
(It's none of my business, so I am inclined to help.)
It says here that we need leg muscles.
(They finish filling out the consent form for wing walking.)
Do we really go out the door and climb up the wing?
That's impossible.
We will take your physical abilities into consideration...
and adjust accordingly.
Even if you only hang on without doing anything,
it will be frightening.
I don't even like airplane rides.
I get scared of airplane rides.
(Serious)
The atmosphere is bad.
(He realizes that taking his leave is the best option.)
I can't believe him.
He is so annoying.
He smiled in such a carefree way.
- He's going to Switzerland. - Can we be put on anesthesia?
(Desperate)
I had the same thought.
(I want to wake up in Korea.)
(They finish signing.)
It's the weather you get in LA.
(They go outside for an opening.)
The weather is nice.
Please sit on the chair with your name.
Hey.
Would you stop bringing the giraffe every time we do this?
It's not the giraffe.
(It's not the giraffe.)
It's the giraffe.
(I can tell.)
- It looks like the giraffe. - It's not it.
The silhouette makes it obvious.
For goodness' sake.
- Really? - Really?
A poll that was conducted on Teachers' Day revealed that...
Jae Seok is the top celebrity the students want as a teacher.
Second is Park Bo Gum.
Third is Kang Daniel.
- He beat Daniel. - Really?
Thank you.
Those students are asking to be tired.
He nags all the time.
If Jae Seok is a teacher, the students will suffocate.
He says that if I am a teacher, the students will suffocate.
If Jong Kook is a teacher,
the students won't be able to go to school.
- That's right. - I will be strict.
- It will be too scary. - It will be too scary.
(Only those who can brave his Spartan ways can go to school.)
I will tell you why I asked you to sit down.
What are we doing?
Like I told you in advance,
you must be isolated at one location for the entire day...
for today's Isolated Race.
(You must be isolated for Isolated Race.)
This is bad.
Why do we keep getting isolated?
For goodness' sake.
We asked each of you to bring three items...
another member would need to live in isolation.
"Please bring three items Kim Jong Kook would need..."
"to live in isolation."
Are you serious? Is this really happening?
Don't be like that, Se Chan.
Should I give him stir-fried small octopus?
It needs to be microwaved.
Don't do that. It's mine.
Three items Song Ji Hyo would need.
Firstly, you need toilet paper.
(Ji Hyo's best friend, Kim Sung Oh)
You need to go to the restroom even if you are in isolation.
(Haha needs toilet paper if he goes to the restroom.)
You are right.
The three items Jae Seok needs when he is in isolation.
I prepared three items...
as if I was his biological brother.
It's a pack of scorched rice.
(He gets a pack of scorched rice for So Min.)
Seaweed bloats in your stomach.
It's kelp.
- It's kelp. - Isn't it seaweed?
- It's kelp. - Kelp?
Let's start over.
Kelp.
(They finish picking 3 items for the members.)
The seating arrangement reveals who brought items for whom.
So Min has items for Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo has items for Jae Seok.
My items...
cater to Se Chan.
- Do they cater to me? - Yes.
My items cater to Jong Kook, too.
(My items cater to Jong Kook, too.)
Haha,
you didn't bring fatsia shoots, did you?
If you did, I hate you.
I really didn't.
Let me tell you this in advance.
If that's a stuffed giraffe, I promise I will end you.
It's not a stuffed giraffe.
(If that's a stuffed giraffe, I promise I will end you.)
If that's a stuffed giraffe, I promise I will end you.
I...
I think you are getting rid of the stuffed giraffes...
- since you have so many at home. - That's not true.
I started off as a joke,
- but I soon became absorbed. - Right.
- Jae Seok is alone on an island, - You need to be serious.
and I am the only 1 who can send him 3 items.
I soon became absorbed.
Do you remember Wilson in "Cast Away"?
(Do you remember Wilson in "Cast Away"?)
(Wilson, the only friend for the lonely man)
For Jae Seok,
I brought Wilby.
(A friend for an isolated life, Wilby)
(After Danbi...)
(and Dolby,)
(Wilby appears.)
(Kicking)
(You "will be" dead.)
- What? - Kwang Soo.
- Bite him. - Wait.
- Kwang Soo. - No way.
(They see the giraffe too many times.)
This is Wilby who will be Jae Seok's friend.
He can't stand on his own.
He brings the stuffed giraffe every chance he gets.
This is the real thing.
Goodness.
(He's rather excited.)
If I didn't know Jae Seok well,
- I couldn't have brought it. - Really?
When we're shooting or when we're on a break from shooting,
- Yes? - he always looks for this.
It's a cloth for wiping glasses.
(It's a cloth for wiping glasses.)
Seriously, Jae Seok.
You wipe your glasses often.
(You always look for it.)
(That's definitely necessary.)
It's necessary.
- Really. - Why would he wipe his glasses?
He's about to die.
- Don't you see how genuine I am? - Come on.
(Kwang Soo brings Wilby, a magazine, and a cloth.)
I brought some items for Kwang Soo.
- Be serious. - Show us.
These are for when he's isolated.
- I'm on a deserted island. - They must be necessary.
(What does she think Kwang Soo will need?)
First of all...
What's that? It looks nice.
- What is it? - It's a microphone.
(A microphone?)
- It's so that he doesn't get bored. - It'll keep him from being bored.
So that I can sing?
That's great.
(Is there a meaning behind this microphone?)
He can do this too.
"Save me!"
(Save me!)
"I'm Lee Kwang Soo. Please save me."
- He can use it for this. - That's good.
- I see. - I can see how genuine she is.
- Right? - Right.
- That's a good idea. - I thought about it very carefully.
I thought you'd need a paper and a pen.
I brought them because when he's isolated,
he might die.
You must let people know about your death.
He has to report his death.
A will?
- You should write a will. - Right.
- Death? I shouldn't die. - It's just in case.
Kwang Soo, I'm jealous of you.
- I'm satisfied. - It's as if she's his girlfriend.
Thank you so much.
This is why people think you're dating.
There are always rumors.
Even if there are rumors,
- no one... - No one cares.
- They just laugh. - People don't really care.
- It's not exciting. - Right.
They don't follow the 123 of a typical couple in love.
- "123"? - I'm getting angry.
(123 means an equation that resembles something.)
It's a professional term. They don't work.
Just because he's experienced...
(Jong Kook tries to be arrogant.)
(Kwang Soo gets a sketchbook, a pen, a gas lighter, and a microphone.)
I brought these for Se Chan.
I thought about what I would need when I'm isolated.
That's good. Jae Seok wouldn't get playful.
Of course not.
We need water when isolated.
(We need water when isolated.)
(Jae Seok is genuine.)
He's like an honest teacher.
Look, we need water the most when we're isolated.
- That's impressive. - Water?
Wait.
(Let me drink some.)
Why are you drinking it? It's my water.
- I'm thirsty. - It's mine.
I got it.
He'll give you a new one.
- Right? - Of course.
- Here's water for Se Chan. - This is good.
I brought this while thinking that I'm isolated.
I'm also thirsty.
- Also... - Give me some too.
He's so genuine.
He was serious about it.
(Everyone is thirsty.)
Is this the last? Will you give me a new one?
We won't.
(What are you talking about?)
Come on.
Stop him.
(He takes it after the water is almost gone.)
There isn't much left.
Goodness.
You'll survive 15 days with that amount.
You'll survive 15 days.
(He had no idea then.)
(Will limited resources cause a fight for items?)
(Who will be the last to survive in the Isolated Race?)
The three items aren't related at all.
Each item is unique in its own way.
(Cup noodles, water, and a board game)
For me, it was So Min. I really pondered for a long time.
So Min is quite special.
All she needs are fatsia shoots and chogochujang.
No, I don't like fatsia shoots.
This is what I brought.
What is it?
- This is... - What is it?
That looks interesting.
- Isn't it a cleaner? - Is that what you thought?
This catches bugs.
(Impressed)
- Does it suck them in? - Watch.
(Watch what I'm doing.)
(Sound of a motor running)
The bugs get sucked inside.
Take this off and close the lid.
You can see them through the magnifying glass.
Does it catch insects?
Like ants?
That's good.
You might think that this was its sole purpose.
However, it's more meaningful than that.
It's when So Min is struggling.
(It's when she's at risk.)
What will she do about the smell if she has to fart?
She can use it behind herself.
(Suck in the smell.)
- You can magnify it too. - Right.
- It can be used for anything. - She can see that too.
It's one machine,
but it can be used for several purposes.
That's impressive.
It's an insect catcher.
(List of items while isolated)
(Microphone, sketchbook, water, Wilby, magazine, cloth for...)
(wiping glasses, cup noodles, board game, book, soccer ball...)
- Everyone gave their items. - Yes.
Today is Isolated Race, Pick Me War.
- "Pick Me"? - "Pick Me"?
You'll be isolated here and survive only with the items given to you.
(Survive until the end only with the given items.)
- How can I survive with this? - I know.
What about food?
Goodness.
- I'm in trouble. - Will you give us food?
You will vote once every hour.
The member with the lowest number of votes...
will be flogged by the winner as many times as they want.
- What? - Okay.
What did you say?
(Infinite number of flogging?)
(The flogging hurts from head to toe.)
(The winner gets to beat as many times as they want.)
- That's too harsh. - The penalty is too harsh.
There will be three rounds of voting.
Each person gets to vote five people.
You can't vote for yourself. You may vote one person twice.
For example,
Seok Jin may vote for Ji Hyo five times.
Each member receives...
a promissory note with a limit of 1,000 dollars.
(Each member gets a promissory note with a limit of 1,000 dollars.)
With the given promissory note,
you may exchange your items.
How do we use it?
You can buy my items.
- Write how much money you'll pay. - To buy it?
Write down the amount.
You must fulfill what you promise on the note.
Can I sell my items?
Yes, you can.
The member who gains the highest amount in promissory notes...
gets to exchange it with a prize that's worth the amount.
A three-item set for the summer looks good.
There's also food.
We can win some food too.
- Some are helpful. - We get to eat.
- We can survive at least. - Right.
You may exchange anything with the promissory note.
Kwang Soo brought this which I can't even sell.
You might be able to sell it.
I should sell "Anger Management" to Ji Hyo.
No, thank you.
Jong Kook doesn't get angry when he doesn't see anything.
I should sell the sleep mask to Jong Kook.
- To cover his eyes? - To cover his eyes?
He won't get angry if he can't see.
What's that market?
(Running Man Market is open.)
(It will be an oasis for a difficult isolated life.)
(There's everything from daily necessities to snacks.)
Can you tell us how much a bottle of water is?
Yes, it's 500 dollars per bottle.
- What? - What?
- What? - What did you say?
- Really? - Are you insane?
- I'll sell my water... - Are you insane?
for 200 dollars.
This is 490 dollars.
- You're such thieves. - It's 200 dollars.
I won't buy any water even if I die of thirst.
I won't buy it.
(He claims a boycott.)
The items that you have now won't be enough...
- to survive, right? - Yes.
Among 1.5L of water,
toilet paper, and ramyeon set,
you get a chance to win one of them.
(They get a chance to win one more item.)
You'll play Pirate Roulette Game.
(Pirate Roulette Game)
We're playing it again.
- Okay, okay. - Wait.
Take turns sticking a knife in the pirate barrel.
The one to catch the pirate and put it in another barrel wins.
Divide into groups of four.
It's worth playing as long as I can avoid Jong Kook.
It's over if you play with Jong Kook.
What color Jong Kook picks will be important.
Mine is yellow.
Mine is red.
Yellow is better.
- What about Seok Jin? - I got yellow.
Weak players got together.
(The weak players increase their chances.)
Mine is red.
(Se Chan picks red.)
Mine is yellow.
I'm playing with weak players.
(Team Yellow is made up of weak players.)
- Mine is red. - Kwang Soo.
(Team Red is made up of strong players.)
- I'm in trouble. - Will it be So Min or Jong Kook?
(Which team Jong Kook is in is important.)
Join Team Yellow, So Min.
One. So Min should be Team Yellow.
1, 2, 3.
(Which color did So Min pick?)
Mine is yellow.
(It's yellow.)
- I have a chance. - It's worth playing.
It's definitely worth playing.
- Mine is red. - Jong Kook.
I don't want to play with Kwang Soo either.
Jong Kook is the strongest.
(Will Team Red be okay?)
(Haha, Seok Jin, Jae Seok, and So Min are on Team Yellow.)
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Kwang Soo, and Jong Kook are on Team Red.)
(Team Red plays first.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Jong Kook will win anyway.
Rock-paper-scissors
- You'll start? - Yes.
- Hands on ears. - Keep the pace fast.
Kwang Soo is in the best position.
Let's go.
(Rattling)
Okay.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
- It's Ji Hyo's turn. - It's Ji Hyo's turn.
(Please)
(In)
(It's the master of this game, Kwang Soo's turn.)
It'll pop out.
(In)
Is it my turn?
(Is it my turn?)
(Wobbling)
(What?)
- He cheated. - Jong Kook.
- What is this? - You can't do that.
- You have to hold it. - It has to pop out first.
- What is this? - I was getting ready.
There's no problem with getting ready to catch it.
Okay.
(They accept it.)
It has to go all the way in.
It's not going to pop out.
It won't pop out.
It's incredible that he's not making it pop out.
(It's Jong Kook's turn again.)
Hey!
(Wobbling)
- Gosh. - So this is okay?
- He's a cheater. - Don't make things complicated!
- He's a cheater. - He's definitely a cheater.
- It's too complicated. - He's a cheater with strength.
- What did you do? - Why did you have to do that?
- What's with you? - It's really not okay.
It's seriously not okay.
- Hold on. - There you go.
- It'll be fine. - It's going to pop out.
Is it in?
1, 2, 3.
- There aren't many left. - It's been going on for so long.
It's going on forever.
(There are only 4 empty slots.)
(It's about time.)
(Moving)
(Kwang Soo is getting ready.)
(Wriggling)
- Stop it. - What are you doing?
That's not okay.
It's not going to pop.
(It pops out.)
(It hits Jae Seok's face.)
(The pirate that's popped out by Kwang Soo...)
(hits Jae Seok's face hard.)
(Hit)
(Knockdown)
(He is so unlucky.)
(Meanwhile)
Kwang Soo, stand over there.
How did you get hit?
(It's Jong Kook versus the other three.)
Gosh. No one is asking if I'm okay.
- Go away! - Go away!
- Go away! - It's your fault...
- Jong Kook caught it. - Gosh.
How did you get hit right in the face?
You have to stop him.
- Jong Kook shouldn't move on. - It must hurt.
(Everyone's tense.)
I'll be in the front.
Show us that you can beat him.
The three of you can do it.
- You can do it. - They're holding him.
- Ji Hyo! - They're holding him.
- They're competing. - Ji Hyo!
There you go.
(It's a mess.)
(The struggling starts.)
See? We're lucky not to be in there.
(Jong Kook shakes his head.)
(No one is giving in.)
- It's in! - My finger.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Her finger was already in, and I stuck the pirate in.
I...
- Gosh. - I'm sorry.
- Are you okay? - Her finger was already in,
but the pirate went all the way in.
Are you okay?
Gosh.
Seong Moon, are you okay?
- It's Ji Hyo. - It's Ji Hyo?
I thought it was Seong Moon.
(Ji Hyo sacrifices her finger.)
(Kwang Soo moves onto the finals.)
You can relax in the beginning.
(It's the weaker members' turn.)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Haha attempts to win.)
Done!
(But he fails.)
So Min!
(The pirate pops back up, and Jae Seok wins.)
- Let me see. - So Min!
(Among the weaker members, Jae Seok moves onto the finals.)
(The mean Jae Seok versus the unlucky Kwang Soo)
The finals are going to be fun.
- Seriously... - This is a problem.
- It's going to be a mess. - It's going to be crazy.
I have to win.
(It's a battle between two cheaters.)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo goes first.)
Okay.
(Who will win additional necessities?)
(Kwang Soo's first try makes the pirate pop out.)
(Is this even possible?)
(Hi, Kwang Soo.)
(It's mine.)
(What?)
(No...)
How is this possible?
At his first try?
They'll be running around all over the place. Get the jimmy jib ready.
Fly the drones too.
How did it pop out at the first try?
(No one knows who will win yet.)
It's beginning.
(The battle starts.)
He's being clever.
(Jae Seok tries to distract Kwang Soo.)
(He hides among the staff members.)
(Kwang Soo is staying around the barrel.)
- Kwang Soo, to the right. - Where is he?
- To the right. - Where did he go?
(Where is he?)
Where did he go?
- To the right. - Where did he go?
Defend the right side.
(Kwang Soo doesn't see Jae Seok.)
(Looking around)
(Between them are two rows of staff members.)
(Jae Seok has to move while Kwang Soo is distracted.)
(There you are.)
(Jae Seok has been spotted.)
Hold on.
(It's a head-to-head match now.)
(Pushing)
There you go.
(Jae Seok gets to the barrel in just 3 steps.)
(He looked like a grasshopper.)
(He successfully sticks the pirate in the barrel.)
- Jae Seok wins. - No!
- He didn't win! - I win!
- Yes! - Jae Seok.
He pushed the camera away.
How did he find his way?
My defense was impenetrable.
Jae Seok wins. He gets to choose a necessity.
- Thank you. - It was cool.
The ramyeon set looks nice.
(3 prize candidates)
The ramyeon set would be the best.
Jae Seok would definitely choose the ramyeon set.
Among these three? The ramyeon set, obviously.
This is it.
- Jae Seok chose the ramyeon set. - Yes.
That's incredible.
- Unbelievable. - Let's start Pick Me War now.
(What?)
(Drinking)
(That's my water.)
(The cheating hasn't stopped.)
(It's a mess to the end.)
(Snatching)
Hey! What are you doing?
I was thirsty!
Gosh. He drank my water.
What can you do?
You can't steal others' stuff from now on.
- What? - You can't steal from now on.
Only now?
You can't steal from now on, right? Okay.
(Cool)
You can make stir-fried ramyeon.
Let's start Isolated Race, Pick Me War.
There will be the first vote in an hour.
You can also use the snack bar.
I'll have to buy something.
(They look around the snack bar first.)
How much is that?
(The snack bar has everything.)
(The problem is the prices.)
A spoon and chopsticks cost 300 dollars?
That's a rip-off. A boiled egg costs 500 dollars.
How many eggs can you get for 500 dollars?
- Just one. - Just one.
You're a thief.
Electricity costs 200 dollars?
Why is it so expensive?
- You'll be broke afterwards. - When you eat ramyeon,
- a spoon and chopsticks... - Do we have to buy them?
- Do we have to? - You have to buy them.
- Se Chan, do you want to share... - Bo Pil, you know me, right?
We've known each other for a long time.
Everyone here has known him for a long time.
- Step back. - What are you doing right now?
- This is robbery. - Bo Pil, I'll pay you later.
Lend me the chopsticks.
- What are you doing? - You have to pay 300 dollars.
You're ripping us off.
If we report this to the news program,
you'll be arrested. 500 dollars...
(A snack bar makes enormous profits.)
(It's a rip-off.)
(Give me 200 dollars.)
(Behind this suspicious snack bar...)
(is a giant broadcasting station?)
Kimchi costs 300 dollars? We could even make some ourselves.
I'm one of the richest members for now.
- I'm very rich. - So am I.
- You should thank me. - Seriously.
You should seriously vote for me.
- I will. - It's worth at least 500 dollars.
It's worth 500 dollars.
Let me tell you something.
If someone gives me five votes, I'll write that person a promissory note.
(I'll write that person a promissory note.)
- Haha! - Come to me.
- I want to make a deal. - Me!
- Me! - I'll write you a promissory note.
- I'm here. - You can give up to 1,000 dollars.
I have food, so I don't have to buy anything.
You have to carry out what you write on the promissory notes.
If you don't, you'll be penalized.
- Really? - You have to?
- You have to keep your promise. - That sounds good.
Why don't we give each other a vote right here?
- Good. - Okay.
(They give each other a vote.)
- Are you going to write my name? - Write my name first.
(So Min and Kwang Soo exchange votes.)
Why are you writing it in the corner?
- You'll scratch that later, right? - I always write this way.
Write, "Jeon So Min", big here.
(Coughing)
- You'll scratch that later. - Don't you see I'm coughing?
(I'm not in the mood for jokes.)
(I'm extremely ill.)
You're faking it.
You have to carry out what you write on the promissory notes.
You can change the name on your ballots...
before you throw them into the ballot box.
- Se Chan... - Come on.
- Why would you say that now? - Yang Se Chan.
It won't matter for me. That rule doesn't matter for me.
(They write down names on the ballot for the time being.)
Let's go. Let's go back in.
(They enter the building for a one-hour break.)
Members with water and ramyeon are the wealthy ones.
My gosh, this is...
(Wilby is the most useless item.)
No way. Look what I have.
Am I running a stationery store? Look at this, Haha.
I bet you'll have the most fun.
(So Min Stationery Opens.)
I should've brought 2L of water.
But the most useful item here is the red ginseng.
I can drink this instead of water when I get thirsty.
- It will make you thirstier. - I'll drink it when I'm thirsty.
- That's the most useless item here. - I have wet wipes.
I have fire. No one can live without fire.
I have fire too.
You have the portable stove.
I can't spend any money.
- When would I need the fire? - I have a pot here too.
When you put this on the floor,
- it sucks in all the ants. - You can do that?
Come inside, mosquito.
(She uses the vacuum on Jong Kook.)
(Let's catch Jong Kook, the mosquito.)
My gosh, this is so much fun.
Look at Jong Kook's face.
Look at him.
She's cute.
(Come on.)
You didn't even look at her while saying that.
- "She's cute." - I got scared for a second.
Jong Kook, you lied, didn't you?
- He was looking at the ledger. - You didn't look at her.
He said that when he was looking at the ledger.
- Mosquito. - Hey, hey.
She's actually pressing on the button.
- She's pressing on it. - Wasn't that really dangerous?
It just zapped.
- Wait, my hair. - Is my hair burned?
- It doesn't work on people. - That's true.
- It zapped? - Wait, my hair.
Wait, does it work?
(Buzzing)
It works. It works.
(No way. It fully functions.)
It works. It'll burn him.
I'm quite shocked.
- Did it work? - Why does that work on him?
It doesn't work.
- Maybe, he's not human. - You pressed it earlier.
- He must be a bug. - No, I didn't press it here.
I pressed it over there.
- Isn't that weirder? - But my hair...
You can get comfortable.
Now, you must cook ramyeon.
If you need to buy anything, use the convenience store.
This...
Having this won't help me much.
I saw a small space where there were a lot of animals.
(It is an animal farm.)
I'll put this in the lot.
- Will you donate it there? - Yes, I'll put this in there.
- Why would you donate that? - What?
Why would you do that?
Why wouldn't I? This is mine. I can do whatever I want, right?
Wait.
You must return it to me when we're done.
Then you should buy it from me.
- Yes, you should buy it. - What?
- Buy it from me then. - Buy it.
I don't need this at all.
I have to bring this back if we need it for another episode.
(That's my Wilby.)
- Then buy this from me. - How about this?
I'll buy it from you, but vote for me in exchange.
(He starts negotiating.)
- That's a nice deal. - You ought to comply with that.
- Use your promissory note. - Give me 200 dollars check then.
Hey, he's a complete swindler.
No, he's not. The boiled egg costs 300 dollars.
- That's cheap. He should get 700. - I agree.
A paper cup costs 300 dollars.
- Then I'm sorry, - You should buy something.
- but give me 300 dollars. - There you go.
- What's happening? - 200 dollars won't cut it.
After listening to them...
- But you have more money. - The paper cup...
- The paper cup costs 30 dollars. - You do.
- One vote... - The boiled egg...
- Can I buy your vote for 300? - Pardon?
No, I'll buy it.
I'll sell it to Seok Jin.
- No, no. - I'll sell it for 300.
- I'll give you 350 dollars. - Seok Jin.
- Great. I'll take 350 dollars. - 350 dollars?
- I believe that it's only right... - Okay.
- that you take this giraffe. - Okay, okay.
Write on the note that you'll pay 350 dollars in exchange for 1 vote.
- Of course, I'll vote for him. - Please write that on it.
(He's done issuing the check.)
- I'll give you my vote. - It's 200 dollars for 1.
- I'm sorry, but hold on. - Did you buy it?
- What did he write on it? - What?
- You wrote 35 dollars on the check. - I did? I'm sorry. Sorry.
(He's flustered.)
(He's shameless.)
(He sneakily wrote 35 dollars.)
I'm sorry. I'm pretty bad with numbers. I'll fix it. I will.
- You're such a jerk. - I will fix it.
- I'm sorry. I'm bad with numbers. - Seriously.
- I've never done this before. - Should he be arrested for that?
- Really? - When would I have the chance?
- No. I can't do this then. - I'm sorry.
(The note is void as the seller is angry.)
I'll fix it. I'll issue a new one.
- He should go to prison for that. - I'll give it to you.
- I'm bad with numbers. - Make the zeros bigger.
- They're too small. - Okay.
You're quite picky.
- I can't believe this. - I gave it to you. I did.
- You can't pull this trick on me. - I'm bad with numbers.
When would I have ever issued a promissory note?
- Seok Jin, how much is the ginseng? - My gosh, 350 dollars...
- Why are you ignoring it? - What?
- You saw the sketchbook. - I didn't ignore it.
- She does weird stuff. - Why?
I should have some red ginseng.
She wrote a chain letter when she gave the sketchbook to me.
(She wrote a chain letter on the sketchbook?)
(One day before the shoot, So Min's self-tape)
I'll write a chain letter.
"This letter initially started in England..."
(It took her 30 minutes to write a chain letter for Kwang Soo.)
This is bad luck. What is this?
- Seriously? - You have to write one too.
You have to write one too. Or it'll bring back luck.
- I was going to ignore it. - That's right. You must write back.
- Or you'll die. - You'll be in trouble then.
You'll be in trouble if you don't write one.
She told me to send this to 7 people to bring good luck for 7 years.
You know, if you don't, you'll be unlucky, right?
- You should hurry. - He's going to send one to us.
(He's really writing it. How could he ignore this letter?)
(He forgets about the shoot and writes the letter for good luck.)
The one who started this letter...
sent this to 7 people in the 1930s...
and won a two-million-dollars lottery.
- Right. - But the person was shot to death.
When the person ignored the letter, he was shot to death.
- He was assassinated. - Hey.
Don't go that far.
- Ignoring it brought him death. - Hey, how could you...
write the chain letter on the sketchbook?
Se Chan.
How about a promissory note for a book?
- Can I see the cover of the book? - Okay.
That's great.
It feels like this is an illegal dealing.
- This book has good information. - Okay.
In exchange, give me your vote.
- What is that? A book? - I'll put that in.
Yes, it's a book.
I really want that book.
- Buy it for 50 dollars. - 50 dollars.
Write on the note that you'll buy it for 50 dollars and vote for me.
You'll give me your vote.
- Yes, right there. - My name?
- Hey, hold on. - You'll write my name.
(He's shocked.)
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with Jae Seok? Excuse me. Hey, look.
My face is right here.
- Is that so? - Come on.
(This salesman doesn't even turn back.)
You can give me 50 dollars for it.
(Hitting with all his might)
(He hits Jae Seok's bottom.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I'm sure it hurt a bit.
(You're fooling no one.)
He's holding it in. His face got red.
- He's pretending it didn't hurt. - He held it in. His face got red.
(He endures the pain because showing it would mean he lost.)
I have the dating horoscope for May.
(It's inside the magazine.)
- The dating horoscope for May. - Read the dating horoscope.
Tell me if you want to hear it.
- Read So Min's. - So Min?
- There's one for the Year of Tiger. - Yes, it's our year.
- She should pay to hear that. - Of course, she will.
- It's 10 dollars. - You can read it for free.
- 10 dollars. - 10 dollars?
You should pay at least 10 dollars.
- Can I hear mine? - But this is quite juicy.
(He asks out of nowhere.)
- You can't. - Why would you want to?
- Why would you hear yours? - You can't hear yours.
Seok Jin, what year were you born?
- I was born in 1966. - 66.
- The early 1966. - His year isn't in it.
(The horoscope for 1966 isn't in the magazine.)
1976 is the earliest.
1976 is the last year.
(The one for his health might be more popular at his age.)
That's too harsh.
Who wants to have cup noodles?
- Hey, that. Se Chan. - Yes?
If we combine our water, it'd be enough for the ramyeon.
Should we join hands and make a business out of this?
Yours is 700 dollars, and mine is 500 dollars.
- Really? - Then...
- you should give him 200 dollars. - That's right. That's only fair.
- Why? - Because...
- Mine costs 700 dollars. - You said so yourself.
- I should pay him 200 dollars? - What?
But who is this guy? Does he get a commission in the middle?
(But who is this guy? Does he get a commission in the middle?)
- Who is he? He gets commissions? - He's an agent.
- Are you an agent? - Why does he raise the price?
- Of course, I am. I'm an agent. - Are you the middle man or what?
Jae Seok, you and I must work together.
If we cook this, they'll want to have a bite.
Issue a note that promises that you'll write my name.
Okay.
We're joining hands now.
(For the synergy effect, they cut a deal.)
I have nothing to offer here.
My gosh, So Min.
I have nothing to offer here!
- It's the same with me. Look. - I'll sell you this microphone.
Kwang Soo, don't you want to cover your eyes?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Why would I want to do that? I have to look around here.
- I'll give you a great price. - What? Why would I want that?
It warms your eyes.
We can cook both of them together.
(Jong Kook ends up eating ramyeon out of hunger.)
How much is it to boil water?
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo spot Jong Kook eating ramyeon.)
You should sell it. Why are you eating this?
(And she eats Jong Kook's ramyeon.)
- Why would I sell this? - You should sell it.
Or you should eat only half of it.
Then you should buy it from me.
(What?)
Why are you telling me to sell if you're not buying it from me?
- You just gave some to me. - My gosh.
(Kwang Soo got a piece of the ramyeon.)
I'll give you 10 dollars for letting me dip the noodles in the soup.
- What? - Let me just dip the noodles in.
- No, no. We can't do that. - I'll dip it in and take it out.
- No, we can't do that. - 10 dollars.
- Just this piece. - A bit of seasoning is 10 dollars.
- No. - Hey, this is ruined.
- I have the seasoning over there. - Then forget it.
It's over.
You said you'll pay me for this, but you just keep on eating.
You had enough now.
(She's been eating for 5 minutes while pretending to care.)
Since you had some, go away.
She keeps on eating mine.
- I'm just eating the crumbs. - My gosh.
- I thought you were my wife. - Hey.
Hey.
She nagged me about selling this.
- But she kept on eating. - But she kept eating?
- All right. - I'll pour the water now.
- Okay. - Why isn't the water boiling?
- It's boiling, right? - Wait. I'll add the seasoning now.
Can I dip it in the seasoning just once?
That'll be 50 dollars.
(You must pay for that.)
- My gosh, he's so petty. - No, listen.
I have to survive too.
Seok Jin.
You don't need the seasoning, right?
Jong Kook, you don't want the seasoning, right?
- What? No. - The seasoning.
- Wait. - Can I get it?
- Come on. - Give the seasoning to me.
Just because I shared my ramyeon with you doesn't mean...
- Give the seasoning to me. - Give it to me, please.
- No, no. - Hey.
You should cut back on sodium. Just eat it plain.
You gave him a block,
but you called me out when I ate the crumbs.
- You ate more than that. - No, that's not true.
- The crumbs... - I've been saving this piece.
- You ate a lot of crumbs. - I've been saving this.
Go back to your spot now. Go.
- I got this earlier. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo, your paper. - Sell it to me.
I won't give you any.
(Are they using Kwang Soo's letter as an oven mitt?)
Jae Seok, what are you doing?
I was going to sell it.
- Sell what? - You're in trouble.
- What happened? - You.
Your life is over now.
No, what do you mean?
Do you know why President Kennedy got killed?
You know what?
On this letter...
(What's wrong with tearing it a little?)
You should never throw away or doodle on this letter.
- He's right. - Really?
It'll be fine.
- It's okay. - You're in trouble.
Hold this.
- Goodness. - Line up for ramyeon, So Min.
- How could he? - Seok Jin.
The first ones in line can buy it cheaper.
- Me. - Get in line.
- Get in line over here. - Okay.
Come to my left if you want to collaborate with me.
- It's cheaper if you come first. - It should be.
Is it 50 dollars?
(Finally, ramyeon is ready.)
- It smells so good. - It looks delicious.
Who wants to eat it?
Gosh, it smells so good.
It's great.
I should bear it. How many rounds will we play?
It's 50 dollars.
It looks so delicious.
We should sell it.
(The looks and smell make it irresistible.)
(He tastes it to advertise it.)
(It tastes amazing.)
Haha, this is it.
It changes my mood.
Is it called oxytocin? I can feel it suddenly.
This is great.
- Oxytocin. - What's oxytocin?
Isn't it something that's released?
Isn't it adrenaline?
That's when you're nervous.
- Do you mean endorphins? - That's what I meant.
Endorphins got released.
That's really serious.
What's oxytocin?
- I want that. - There's also oxytocin.
Oxytocin is a hormone to signal contractions of the womb.
Really? I'm sorry.
What did you say?
It costs 10 dollars to dip the noodles in the soup.
(Jae Seok keeps tasting it.)
- There it is. - I'll give you 10 dollars.
- Let's divide it in half. - Look at me.
- I'll give you 10 dollars. - Really? Okay.
Here are 10 dollars.
- It's to dip in the soup. - Here are 10 dollars.
- Are you dipping the noodles? - I'll do it for you.
You're spilling the seasoning powder.
- They're dipped. - I'm giving you a lot.
(Hitting)
(He takes the whole bite.)
(How dare you eat all of it?)
Spit them out.
I paid for it.
- He's a crook. - I'll cancel one.
Stop it.
Goodness.
He gave me the whole bite.
I shouldn't have trusted him.
You should have known better.
(One hour of free time is over.)
All right.
(It's the first voting time.)
The first voting will start.
- Se Chan. - What shall we do?
- I wrote your name. - I'll write yours too.
- Write my name once. - I will.
- Did you vote for me? - I'm about to.
We're voting for each other, right?
Where's my ballot?
My ballot is missing.
- Where did you put it? - Who took it?
- For the last voting slot, - I'll sell it.
- I'll pay 50 dollars. - That's not what I mean.
It's 1 by 1.
- Listen. - Me.
- Write my name for 50 dollars. - 50 dollars.
- Haha. - Right?
- Really? - I'll pay 100 dollars for 1 vote.
- What? - I'll sell it.
- I'll write your name. - I will.
If someone pays me 200 dollars,
I'll write your name five times.
- Really? - Yes.
(I'll write your name five times.)
- I'll pay you. - Hurry up.
- Really? - 200 dollars?
- I'll pay you. - Is it really 200 dollars?
- I'll pay you. - I'll vote for you five times.
I'll take it, Jong Kook.
- Really? - Haha.
That's why small businesses go bankrupt.
- Jong Kook is... - He's a corporation.
You can't compete against corporations.
- Hurry. - I'll pay you 250 dollars.
- What? 250 dollars? - 250 dollars.
- How about 400 dollars? - "400 dollars"?
I can't pay that much.
- Ji Hyo called 400 dollars. - 400 dollars.
You have 30 seconds before the voting is over.
I can't find my ballot.
(Seok Jin can't find his ballot.)
Where's my ballot?
Who took my ballot?
I have 50 dollars.
(She brags about her promissory notes.)
- And Ji Hyo... - Where's my ballot?
- What have you done? - Where did it go?
- What's wrong? - Kwang Soo.
(Write So Min's name on the sketchbook?)
- Kwang Soo. - What's wrong?
How dare you, Kwang Soo?
Come over here.
I have three more votes left.
- That's not what's important. - What's this?
- I'll write it on my sketchbook. - Where's my ballot?
Give it back to me.
- Come on. - What's wrong?
- Why did you write that? - Where's my ballot?
Wait a minute.
- What? I don't have it. - Write my name down.
- Write my name. - I already voted.
Where's my ballot?
- Give me one more. - That wasn't the deal.
You thieves, where's my ballot!
I'll write your name if you pay me 100 dollars.
- That's mine. - No.
- Five. - What is it?
- Listen. - I'll pay you.
- I'll vote for you for 100 dollars. - 4.
- I'll vote for you for 100 dollars. - 3.
(The 1st voting is over.)
- Here you go. - My goodness.
Where's my ballot?
Money is important,
but everyone is making strange deals.
Can we change whom we voted?
- Do you have another ballot? - Isn't it Seok Jin's?
- Where did it go? - Isn't it Seok Jin's?
- Isn't this yours? - It's the sketchbook.
My goodness.
- Here are the promissory notes. - Where was it?
- The voting is over. - Didn't he have it?
I got a promissory note.
Wait, why did Seok Jin write Kwang Soo's name only?
(Why did Seok Jin write Kwang Soo's name only?)
- Hey, you. - What?
- You're a crook. - You misunderstood.
- This isn't mine. - I thought it was a dream.
- You misunderstood. - This isn't real.
- I don't know when it happened. - This is fake.
Your bag was on my shoulder.
(While Seok Jin and Kwang Soo were fighting...)
(Seok Jin turned around and gave up.)
(What happened?)
(He smiles.)
(Kwang Soo took the ballot from Seok Jin's bag.)
What's this?
(Then he voted on behalf of Seok Jin.)
What are you doing?
- Where's mine? - What are you doing?
Where's my bag?
(He finished voting with boldness.)
Here it is.
(Kwang Soo committed a crime without much effort.)
(How dare you?)
- Goodness! - It was around my neck.
Your bag was hanging on my neck.
(It's not a big deal.)
How is this possible? How could he steal my ballot?
(They submit their ballots.)
- I'll announce the result. - Okay.
This is important.
(The voting result is announced.)
The one with the most votes during the first round...
- It's Jae Seok. - It's Kwang Soo.
It's Ji Hyo with 10 votes.
- What? - How?
Ji Hyo got 10 votes.
She could have gotten 11,
but Haha misspelled her name.
That's why she got 10 votes.
She won't lose at all.
- Of course not. - I'm jealous.
The 2nd most number of votes was 7.
- It was Kwang Soo. - Really?
Seok Jin voted him five times.
I didn't. Kwang Soo voted for himself.
- I didn't steal it. - Stop kidding.
I swear.
Next is Haha with six votes.
- All right. - See?
Jae Seok received five votes.
I only got five votes.
Jae Seok bought a lot.
Next is Seok Jin with four votes.
(Seok Jin places 5th.)
One vote made a difference.
Next is...
(Only three members remain.)
(One of them is last.)
The numbers tied.
So Min and Se Chan received three votes.
(The youngest members place 6th.)
Is Jong Kook last?
Jong Kook received one vote.
- Hey. - You placed last.
- Wait a minute. - What?
Didn't you vote for me?
(Didn't you say that a while ago?)
I did vote for you, but you gave your votes away.
Is that why?
Isn't that obvious?
- What I mean is... - Okay.
It's because of the promissory note.
You have two more rounds of voting.
- The tables may turn. - Did I only get three?
(Who will be penalized?)
(The main mission starts.)
Why are there squeaky hammers?
(There are 8 squeaky hammers on 8 chairs.)
Here's what I expect.
The game will get messy.
- It will be. - You're right.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(Kwang Soo is startled.)
- Wait a minute. - What is it?
I saw what happened.
You were about to sit here until you saw Jong Kook next to you.
Why did you run away?
- Sit down. - No.
No, it was because of the squeaky hammer.
(A moment ago)
(Is Jong Kook sitting here?)
(I should avoid the seat next to him.)
He was going to sit here, but when Jong Kook sat down...
- No. - That's wrong.
- Go back to the seat. - You can't read my mind.
(Don't read my mind.)
- Goodness. - Enjoy it if you can't avoid it.
Enjoy it if you can't avoid it.
Before the second round of voting,
you get a chance to win two additional voting slots.
(A chance to win two additional voting slots)
- 2? - 2 additional?
(This mission is important.)
- This is good. - It's a good chance.
We can sell it.
- Right. - We can sell it.
You get a chance to win two additional voting slots.
Let's start Famous Line Number 3.
- "Famous Line Number 3"? - "Famous Line Number 3"?
Listen to famous lines from three movies that play simultaneously.
You win if you guess the movie titles correctly.
The member to answer the most wins two additional voting slots.
However, if you say the wrong answer,
the ones sitting next to you will hit you with the squeaky hammer.
- They'll hit you with the hammer. - From both sides?
- Is it the one on the right? - Is it both?
Whether it's the left or the right is the most important.
- This is what I think. - Decide by majority rule.
Do you hit the person on the left or on the right?
Let me change my seat.
We should play a game to determine the seats.
I'll give you my seat for 300 dollars.
- 300 dollars? - Yes.
Just bear it with your body. You won't die.
Of course, I shouldn't die.
You can buy my spot for 300 dollars.
How hard are you going to hit me?
I'll keep it controlled so that it can still air.
Try hitting the floor so that we know.
I'll keep it controlled like this.
(The sound is so loud.)
300 dollars, you said?
(Kwang Soo wants to buy So Min's spot.)
- Seriously? - That's a good idea.
Don't worry, Kwang Soo. It just makes a loud sound.
Maybe you're right. Try hitting my head.
- See? - 300 dollars.
(It hurts.)
It seemed like your head got a dent.
- It just makes a loud sound. - His head got a dent.
- Is it a real hammer? - No.
- You've become shorter. - Let's do it like this.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors outside...
and decide who sits where.
- Okay. - What do you think?
That sounds great.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, Jae Seok, So Min, and Ji Hyo win.)
- We're divided. - We're divided.
- Scissors. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan is at the bottom.)
Gosh, I'm at the bottom.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- I'm second to last. - Please step back.
- Let's go in 1 by 1. - I'm 3rd to last.
Why do I get to go first only in situations like this?
We haven't decided on the direction yet.
I'm going in.
(So Min, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook,)
(Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Haha, Seok Jin, Se Chan)
I'll sit here.
(The 2nd seat)
(Let me see.)
Be careful. Don't come here.
Don't come here.
I don't want you! Go away.
- Number three, please come in. - I don't want you.
(It's the man Kwang Soo is determined to avoid.)
There are many empty seats.
(You're not sitting next to me, are you?)
(You brat.)
Why did you win?
Hold on.
He has a point.
What did we do?
The problem is that Jong Kook is right after you.
- What did we do? - Hold on.
Aren't the winners supposed to sit later?
(Now that I think of it...)
- But... - What are we supposed to do?
What are we supposed to do? What's the best way?
What should we do?
- I'm in second place. - Then you can sit later.
You can sit later.
- The winners will sit later. - The winners will sit later.
- The winners will sit later. - Okay.
- You're at the bottom, right? - Yes.
- You sit down first. - Okay.
Where's the chair? Okay, I'm done.
I have no choice. It's weird.
This is not bad.
I'll sit here.
It's my turn, right?
Se Chan is scary.
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, and So Min are left.)
- Then... - Okay.
It's the same.
(It's the same as before.)
(What?)
If you sit here...
(Among the remaining three seats,)
(Jong Kook chooses the middle one.)
(Kwang Soo has to sit next to Jong Kook.)
This is so funny. I love it.
- It's the same. - What can we do?
- What can we do? - You have no choice.
Should the winners sit first?
(It's confusing.)
Get out, all of you! I'm in second place.
- The winners should... - Let's try one last time.
The winners will sit first one last time.
I'll sit at the end.
The winners should sit first.
Are you sure?
It's the same. So Min, you go first.
This is strange.
(So Min and Kwang Soo go first again.)
- I'll sit here. - Okay.
(What should I do?)
What should I do?
Sit at the end.
(He sits at the end.)
It's my turn, right?
(It's my turn, right?)
(He sits next to Kwang Soo.)
(Go away!)
(Why are you doing this to me?)
- What? - There are many seats.
There are many seats.
- I want to sit here. - Why me?
- Why me? - I want to sit here.
- Sit here. - Sit there, Kwang Soo.
- You have no choice. - I'll sit here.
(Jae Seok)
- That's my seat. - Ji Hyo's next to So Min.
Seok Jin is next to me again.
This spot is terrible.
(The others come in.)
Isn't it almost the same as before?
(If we sit like this...)
- It's almost the same. - Nothing much has changed.
He's sitting between the nasty members.
Let's decide on the direction now.
Left, please.
Why don't the two at the ends play rock-paper-scissors?
- Good. - If So Min wins, this way.
(If So Min wins, each member will get hit by the one sitting right.)
- If Kwang Soo wins, this way. - Okay.
- Right? - Okay.
- I have to win. - Rock-paper-scissors.
I'll throw rock.
(If Kwang Soo wins, he can hit Jong Kook.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo loses.)
Okay! So Min!
(Because he trusted So Min and lost, Kwang Soo will be hit by Jong Kook.)
- Unbelievable. - Okay!
- Nothing changes for me. - Okay.
So Min, you shouldn't be too happy.
You'll be hit by Kwang Soo.
(You'll be hit by Kwang Soo.)
- That's right. - That's right.
So Min, don't worry. He won't be able to hit you hard.
(So Min, don't worry. He won't be able to hit you hard.)
- He won't be. - His legs will fail him.
(He'll fall.)
Kwang Soo will struggle for a while.
Here goes the first question.
You'll hear lines from three movies.
- We just need to get it right. - That's right.
- We can say the right answer. - We can say the right answer.
Play the movies.
(The first question)
(What are the 3 films?)
(What is this?)
Answer.
(We haven't even heard everything. Does he know all 3 titles?)
- You have to say all 3 titles. - You have to say all 3 titles.
(You have to say all 3 titles.)
- All 3 titles? I'm sorry. - Hit him.
(He thought he could say only one title.)
- I'm sorry. - You should hit him.
- Se Chan, you should hit him. - Jong Kook should have said...
- all three titles. - Yes.
Serves your right.
Hit me.
What?
I don't want to say it.
Jong Kook can't hit you. Just hit him.
- Okay. - Yes.
(Se Chan hits Jong Kook.)
Hold on.
(It was pretty hard.)
- The direction won't change, right? - Good.
Se Chan looked like Thor.
- The direction won't change, right? - No.
- It won't change. - You never know.
I have nothing to do with it.
Let's try again. Play the movies.
(The first question)
(What are the 3 films?)
(Wait. I think I hear something.)
- I need to figure 1 more out. - Just 1...
I just need to figure one more out.
Answer.
(Answer)
Well... I take it back.
Hold on.
(Haha hits Jae Seok.)
- You can't take it back. - Why did you hit me?
- I take it back. - You can't take it back.
- What was that? - I take it back.
- You can't. - Let's try again.
Play the movies.
(The first question)
(What are the 3 films?)
Answer!
(I really know this time.)
"The Face Reader", "Assassination", and "No. 3".
("The Face Reader", "Assassination", and "No. 3")
"No. 3"?
(Is "No. 3" included?)
Play the movies.
(The first question)
(What are the 3 films?)
Answer!
(I really know this time.)
"The Face Reader", "Assassination", and "No. 3".
("The Face Reader", "Assassination", and "No. 3")
"No. 3"?
(Is "No. 3" included?)
- No? - Answer!
(Jae Seok is wrong.)
- Answer! - "No. 3" is wrong.
- I thought it was "No. 3". - Answer!
- Answer! - I thought it was "No. 3".
- It wasn't "No. 3"? - No.
"The Admiral", "Assassination", and "The Face Reader".
("The Admiral", "Assassination", and "The Face Reader".)
(Wrong)
- Answer! - He should be hit.
(It's time.)
(Scared)
Hold on.
- I know it from "X-Man". - Me too.
(Kwang Soo's ear is smashed.)
That was awful.
- He hit Kwang Soo's ear. - He got hit on the ear?
(Kwang Soo pays for what he did during the first vote.)
Is your cochlea okay?
(Clapping)
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- I hit his head. - What is this?
Mosquitos?
I hit his head.
- I don't know the other one. - The other one is hard.
You got "Assassination" and "The Face Reader" right.
(The other one is hard to figure out.)
I have six Japanese bullets in my body.
I got shot while assassinating Terauchi in Gyeongseong in 1911.
Do you think I'll become the king?
Why aren't you answering?
- I can't figure out the other one. - Play the movies.
(They just need to find out the last movie.)
(What are the 3 films?)
Can you mute Lee Jung Jae's lines?
(Let me hear the last one.)
(What are the 3 films?)
- Answer. - So Min?
(So Min answers.)
I don't want to get hit.
(Say it.)
What...
"Assassination", "The Face Reader", and "Architecture 101".
("Assassination", "The Face Reader", and "Architecture 101")
(Is the last film "Architecture 101"?)
(She's right.)
- "Architecture 101". - It was "Architecture 101"?
- What part? - Which one?
It's the kissing part.
They mix.
One at a time.
You rub them.
Just rub them. Rub!
It's fantastic.
This is kissing.
"They mix." The part about kissing.
It was. I heard it too.
I tried to listen, but suddenly,
"Do you think I'll become the king?"
("Do you think I'll become the king?")
"There are seven."
That's all I heard. That's all I could hear.
"There are two bullets in my body."
That's all I heard.
Good job, So Min. I would have never gotten this right.
- Here's the next video. - Okay.
Play, please.
(What are the 3 films?)
(What are they? I have no clue.)
I have no idea.
- This is so confusing. - Answer.
(Kwang Soo shouts out.)
Really?
(Do you know?)
It's too late. You have to say it.
(He's ready.)
- You have to do it. - You're done.
- I can't cancel, right? - No.
"The Priests", "The Wailing", "Along with the Gods".
("The Priests", "The Wailing", "Along with the Gods".)
(Will he be able to avoid Jong Kook's squeaky hammer?)
"Along with the Gods"?
(He's wrong.)
All right.
- This is fun to watch. - This is why we do this.
Say hi to the deities for me.
That wasn't it.
(He takes a full swing.)
Why does it sound different?
- It sounds different. - It was a thud.
(He can't speak now.)
It's not that bad. It doesn't hurt.
Kwang Soo was about to say that it hurt,
and Jong Kook said, "It doesn't hurt."
It's not that bad. It doesn't hurt.
It's okay. Don't give the wrong idea to the viewers.
Tell them.
- It was strong. - Answer.
"The Priests",
"The Wailing",
and "Train to Busan".
("The Priests", "The Wailing", and "Train to Busan")
(He's wrong.)
- That was close. - That was.
You got two right.
Exactly.
I know it's "The Priests" and "The Wailing".
I can't hear the last one.
- It sounds like a similar genre. - Can we hear it again?
Play the films.
(Second question gets played again.)
(What are the 3 films?)
Answer.
(What? Does she really know?)
Who's the female voice?
"A Tale of Two Sisters "...
and...
(That was "A Tale of Two Sisters"?)
"The Priests" and "Train to Busan".
("A Tale of Two Sisters", "The Priests", "Train to Busan")
(She's wrong.)
I'm dead.
You got two correct.
(I'm coming to hit you.)
Please, Kwang Soo.
- Why are you walking like a zombie? - It was "Train to Busan".
I guess so.
(It was "Train to Busan".)
He got infected!
This punk got infected.
He's going to turn into a monster too.
Do you want to die?
He threw the bait,
and your daughter took it.
Since the girls came to this house,
strange things keep on happening.
("Train to Busan", "The Wailing", and "A Tale of Two Sisters")
It's not my fault I sat here. You know that, right?
- Your eyes. Focus. - I know.
(Open your eyes properly.)
Okay? Focus properly.
(Focus properly.)
(Hitting)
(So Min is wrong.)
Everybody, you just have to put it together.
- Answer. - You just have to mix them.
Answer.
Go.
Try it.
- Do it. - I know now.
Answer.
(Hurry up.)
I'll get hit. It's not "The Priests".
(I'll get hit. It's not "The Priests".)
"The Priests"...
(He didn't get a heads-up.)
(It breaks.)
Answer.
(Jong Kook's squeaky hammer breaks apart after three uses.)
- Answer. - It broke.
- Answer. - That hurt so much.
"A Tale of Two Sisters",
"Train to Busan",
- and "The Wailing". - He's right.
(Jong Kook is right.)
I was going to say the same.
That was "A Tale of Two Sisters"?
- I didn't hear that one. - That was hard.
- That was hard. - That was.
Here's the next question.
Play, please.
(What are the 3 films?)
(I know this line.)
I think I know. I do.
I know this music for sure.
(I know as well.)
This is driving me nuts. I can't remember the title of the film.
I know two of them.
- I'm sure about two. - I know for sure.
- I don't know the third one. - I can't hear it at all.
- It's not good to speak first. - Right.
(In this situation, it's bad to speak first.)
Try it then. Pick a third film.
(What? Why would we?)
(He doesn't know any of them.)
Whom are you speaking to?
I guess you don't really know any films.
- Can you tell me? I only know one. - What is it?
Should we tell one each?
- Should we? - Okay.
- What is it? - You tell me first.
You tell me first. I know two.
(I'll tell you first.)
- Answer. - Why?
(He's very sly.)
"The Lawyers", "A Taxi Driver", and "1987: When the Day Comes".
- What did you say? - What?
- No? - Answer.
"1987: When the Day Comes",
"The Attorney",
- and "A Taxi Driver". - No, you're wrong.
("1987: When the Day Comes", "The Attorney", and "A Taxi Driver")
(He's wrong.)
- You have to hit him. - Oh, right.
Why would you hit me?
(It's time for Seok Jin to be punished.)
(Wriggling)
(He looks intimidated.)
(Here I go.)
All right.
- Please hurry. - I thought I was right.
- Hurry up. - Okay.
(Wriggling)
- But I... - Hey.
(He tries to stall.)
- What? - Why?
- Hurry up and hit me! - Fine.
- Like this? - That's too much.
This much?
(Should I hit him or not?)
(Hitting)
(He hits Jae Seok's private part.)
(Seok Jin couldn't wait, so he attacked first.)
I'm so mad.
That was great.
That looked painful.
His face is red.
(He gets an emergency massage.)
- Think about something sad. - Goodness.
You have two children, so you're fine.
- Hurry up. - Oh, gosh.
(They're both wrong.)
- Should we put our heads together? - What's the last one?
I know. Answer.
"Anarchist from Colony".
- Give me 200 dollars. - 100 dollars.
(They start bidding to hit him.)
I say 100 dollars.
(200 dollars? Let's do 100.)
- 100 dollars then. - Is that okay?
- 100 dollars. - And write my name once.
(As soon as Se Chan loses, they make a deal.)
(I thought Jong Kook wouldn't get to hit me,)
(so I hit him so hard.)
- Take it off. - Hold on.
Wait.
- You said you won't hit the back. - I know.
I won't hit the back of your head. I'll hit the crown.
Hold on. Wait!
- It's like he hit me already. - Sit down.
- Hold on. Okay. - Sit down.
I thought I was getting hit.
You shouldn't have said it if you weren't certain.
(He takes a full swing.)
Isn't this from your head?
(Something came out.)
- This... - You lost a screw.
- Isn't this from your head? - Can you put it back in?
(Whatever it is, please put it back.)
(Se Chan acted up and learned about life with 100 dollars.)
- Stop. This is over! - Can I have it back?
It's mine. Mine flew away.
What if you become stupid?
Can we hear it again?
Please play the films.
I can't remember the title. It was that one.
(What are the 3 films?)
I know two for sure, but I can't remember the title of the last one.
I know the film for sure.
The examiner hit the table,
and he gasped...
I'm sorry, Eun Jung. I have something to do.
(The background music sounds familiar. You knew this one, right?)
Let's go on a picnic another time.
(The music was from this scene.)
I know all of them. What's the last one?
What's the last one?
(Is it a film with Gong Yoo in it?)
(I think you're right.)
What's the title?
Let me give you a hint.
- No. - Tell us.
- You can't. - I know for sure.
- Don't. - Give us a hint.
- They might know. - I'm sure about this.
It's 50 dollars.
(It's not free.)
- Are you going to whisper? - Yes, I know for sure.
I'm sure about this.
Okay, I'll do it. 50 dollars.
I have 50 dollars.
(They trust Se Chan's words and buy the hint with 50 dollars.)
- Line up. I'm sure about this. - 50 dollars.
- I'll give it to you. - Write it down.
Will this be good enough?
As soon as you hear this, you'll get it right.
I'm certain. I'm certain about this.
- Hold on. - Aren't you going to do it?
- Here. - Okay, Jae Seok.
- What was it? - What is it?
- I'll give you 50 dollars. - Jong Kook.
If you promise to write my name, I'll tell you.
You can get it right. Can you write my name in round two?
- I'll write your name. - My name. No.
- Do you know the titles? - I'll tell you.
- Can you just write my name later? - Your name?
- I will. - What is it?
It has Gong Yoo in it.
You keep betraying. You even betray on the subway,
and then you betray some more.
What is that called?
I gave it to you. What is that called?
What is that called? What is it?
So I...
There are two syllables.
(This is it.)
- Answer! - What?
- Answer. - Two names, okay?
- If I'm right. - Okay, two names.
(Something about betraying)
- What is that? - You're right.
If he gets it right, Jae Seok did that for nothing.
Two names.
(So Min wanted 2 names for it. What was it?)
"1987: When the Day Comes",
"A Taxi Driver"...
("1987: When the Day Comes", "A Taxi Driver")
"The Age of Shadows".
(The last one is "The Age of Shadows".)
(That was So Min's hint. Is it right?)
- It's "The Age of Shadows". - Two names.
It's "The Age of Shadows".
It was "The Age of Shadows". I'm sorry.
Why didn't you get it right?
Jae Seok, didn't it occur to you?
I told you it was betraying.
I couldn't remember the title.
- Hey. - It was "The Age of Shadows".
Get off the car and tell me, you arrogant punk.
- Where did he go? - We don't know yet.
Two names for me.
(She gets 2 secured.)
Wasn't that "Assassination"?
We thought it was, but it was "The Age of Shadows".
- That's right. - I got confused.
- I thought it was "Assassination". - That was the betraying.
So...
Jong Kook gets two extra votes.
- That's the result. - Well...
You all worked hard, but I get to have it.
He said he'll write my name down.
- Thank you. - How much would you like?
Let's not do that. I'll sell...
- Sell it. - the ballot. What do you think?
- What do you think? - Two ballots?
I'll sell them if you write my name for all seven of them.
(That's his condition for selling.)
- All seven of them. - Jong Kook.
We have to write your name for all seven?
- You have 2 left. - 7?
I'll give you a good amount of money.
- Me. I'll take it. - I'll do it.
- I'll write your name. - Jong Kook.
- Really? - You trust me, right?
- Me. - Your name on all seven.
- And? - Yes.
How much will you pay me?
I have to pay you?
Sorry, that was wrong.
- You're taking the ballots. - This guy.
- Shouldn't I be paid? - Write my name.
And you have to pay me.
I know. How much would you like?
That's what I meant. I have to pay you.
I'm thinking 500 dollars.
- 500 dollars? - 300 dollars for me.
- 200 dollars. - 200.
(They can do it at 200 dollars.)
- You're dropping the value. - Jong Kook.
(Jae Seok approaches him.)
I'll do it at 10 dollars.
(I only want 10 dollars.)
Why did you call 10 dollars?
- For this? - Don't do that.
Don't do that.
Big corporations shouldn't do this.
- Why can't I do it? - You're dropping the value.
- Don't do that. - You have to vote for me.
- I'll make a deal. - You have to vote for me.
(The small business owners are gathered by him.)
I'll vote for you.
Excuse me. I feel like I'm solving the quiz again.
Their voices are getting mixed.
Listen to me, Jong Kook.
I'll give you 10 dollars.
Jong Kook.
(He's very satisfied.)
- Okay. - Okay? Is that good?
- What was it? - You're going to pay him, right?
Why would you pay him?
- You're going to pay him? - You can't do that.
- Let's do it amongst ourselves. - Let's do that.
- Who wants to join? - Come.
- Hold on. - They're not being fair.
- We're self-employed. - We'll do it amongst ourselves.
We're all self-employed.
We can't fight the big companies.
- 100 dollars. 2 votes for that. - 100 dollars?
- Okay, two votes. - Okay.
You have to vote four times for me on the promissory note.
- This is for certain, right? - Two each, right?
Here are the results of the second vote.
The person with the most votes...
is Ji Hyo with 15 votes.
(Ji Hyo is currently in 1st place.)
She has so many votes.
How did she get so many?
Next is tied in second place.
- 3 people with 11 votes. - What?
Haha, Kwang Soo, and Jae Seok.
(They're tied in 2nd place.)
- How did that happen? - What happened?
- How did this happen suddenly? - How much did you spend?
- I bought them. - I did too.
I need to make money now.
- You're done. - In fifth place is...
Jong Kook with nine votes.
- I'm in 5th place? - 9 votes?
You got so many.
- 3 people are tied for last place. - 3 people?
Seok Jin, So Min, and Se Chan with 8 votes.
That's close.
- I'm in a risky place. - I'll buy some too.
Oh, gosh.
- Let's go to the last location... - We're close.
- for round three. - I see.
(Current number of votes)
(This is the last round where results will be determined.)
Look at this.
Is this where...
(This mission is a matter of life and death for the losers.)
The results will be decided here.
They're giving us something. There's assorted beef.
Really?
(What is the last mission with assorted beef as the prize?)
(The curling board is back.)
There's jjajangmyeon too.
What did you say? Jjajangmyeon?
What's the chance card? It must be something.
Everything will be decided here.
Before the final vote,
this is your chance to win special ballots and snacks.
It's called Rice Bowl Lid Curling.
(Rice Bowl Lid Curling)
You need to slide your rice bowl lid, and depending on...
which zone it's the closest to, you get the designated snack.
The person whose lid is the closest to the chance card...
gets to vote for themselves.
- They get that in addition. - For all five?
(You can vote for yourself?)
You can use all five ballots.
We have to get this.
- I have to hit gold. - For sure.
- I have to do this. - I have to try.
If you hit the chance card, it's all over.
It's not a bad idea to defend in the beginning.
The person who wins this round...
Quiet down.
(Quiet down.)
(You especially.)
(Goodness)
- Focus. - Excuse me.
This is a tense moment.
- This is so tense. - This is.
I was saying the key point.
- Be quiet. - Quiet down.
(Fine, okay.)
- Seok Jin. - Okay!
I want the chance card, but I want jjajangmyeon too.
Jjajangmyeon is worth it.
- You only have one chance. - I know.
(This is his last chance to climb up from last place.)
- Is this our last chance? - This much.
- Yes, this is. - This much.
(He's currently in last place. Will he get the chance card?)
- You only have one chance. - I know.
This much.
(He got it.)
(Aim your rice bowl lid.)
Good one.
(It goes straight for the chance card...)
(but overshoots.)
(Assorted beef)
(He misses and lands on assorted beef.)
Good.
(Nice. It's assorted beef.)
(He's currently in assorted beef zone.)
Assorted beef.
That's unbelievable.
I was so close to the chance card.
(Ji Hyo is next.)
Don't touch mine. Hey.
Pretend like you're going to hit his.
- You can hit his. - If I hit Seok Jin's,
- Right. You'll get the chance card. - I'll get the chance car.
Don't.
- Ji Hyo, that has to be your plan. - You can't.
Try hitting his.
(What do you mean I can't?)
- Oh, dear. - Good. It's tofu.
(She misses and gets tofu.)
(She's currently in tofu zone.)
- It's tofu. - That's not bad.
(Gosh, it's tofu.)
Tofu is not bad.
She gets tofu even if she fails.
Assorted beef is amazing.
(The lids can slide, so you can't be sure just yet.)
Why did it go that way?
This is interesting.
Don't hit mine.
- He's weak at games like this. - No, no.
Okay!
- Let's see. - No, no.
(What?)
Out.
- Look. - Okay!
- He's out. - It's out.
- Out. - Is it out?
- He gets nothing. - Out. Okay.
- That's better. - What do you mean?
- He says it's okay. - It's better than a lemon.
(So Min, who's also in last place, goes next.)
(To throw the lid...)
It doesn't slide that well.
(To throw the lid, she waited for this moment.)
Soup.
- Jjajangmyeon. - Okay.
- Really? - Why?
(She got assorted beef in the 2nd practice run.)
Assorted beef.
(If she does as she did during practice, she can win.)
(Where will her lid land?)
What?
Out.
That was unexpected.
- What was that? That's not fair. - Hey.
- Okay. - Hey.
It's fine.
Haha, you have to get Seok Jin out of there.
(Seok Jin's lid is closest to the chance card.)
Seok Jin's lid is closest to the chance card.
You have to hit Seok Jin's.
I'm going to sell assorted beef.
You have to pretend like you're hitting his lid.
He's closest to the chance card.
- Don't. - Hit his.
What?
(Let's bring it close to the chance card.)
(It goes straight for the chance card.)
(It slides in a straight line.)
- Gum. - No.
It's gum.
(It lands in gum zone.)
- It's gum. - It's gum.
- No, it's not. - It is.
- It's gum. - It is.
It's still closest to the chance card.
(It's still closest to the chance card.)
- Haha is closest to chance card. - I needed gum.
(He's close to the center, so it might move.)
- Se Chan. - Don't hit mine.
- You have to hit his. - You can't.
(Se Chan, who's also in last place, goes next.)
(If he doesn't get the chance card, it'll be hard not to lose.)
(He's desperate. Where will the lid go?)
(Sliding)
- Lemon. - Lemon.
(He's currently in lemon zone.)
Why did I follow Jong Kook?
Yes, beef!
(At this rate, beef will be mine.)
- Beef! - I'm in trouble.
(The other two in last place didn't get anything.)
Should I go for the center?
Excuse me. It's not like you can get it...
- if you aim for it. - Come on.
I was telling myself that.
You sat down and said, "Should I go for the center?"
What was that?
Just get the flogging later.
(You have no chance.)
- Oh, dear. - I'm just saying.
- You're trying too hard. - What are you doing?
(As the round comes to an end, it gets more tense.)
- Try to hit Seok Jin's. - Okay.
(Jae Seok is up next.)
What?
(He slides his lid with his eyes wide open.)
Okay!
(Out)
- It's out. - It's out.
(Jae Seok's lid is out.)
- It's out. - Why did you slide it so hard?
Why am I so unlucky?
2, 4, 6. This is the last one.
I can't make it land on the target. There is no way.
I have no choice but to make it hit the wall first.
- Do it. Make a cushion shot. - Make a cushion shot.
- Make it bounce off. - One-cushion shot.
It needs to hit the wall first.
(He plans to bounce it off.)
Hold on. This is too much.
(This is too much.)
- This is important. - I know that.
(Touching)
(Tickling)
Hold on. Do you want me to ignore you?
- How am I supposed to react? - What?
Don't ask me. Go ahead and make your shot.
- Okay. - Do it comfortably.
This is the last one.
(Can Kwang Soo make his lid land on a nice zone?)
Go for the middle.
(He slides the lid.)
- Sophora root tea. - Seok Jin got sophora root tea.
(Hitting)
(Seok Jin gets sophora root tea.)
(Kwang Soo gives sophora root tea to Seok Jin and gets lemon.)
(Sophora root tea?)
Sophora root tea.
(Staggering)
- Sophora root tea. - You...
(Rice Bowl Lid Curling ends without anyone winning the chance card.)
(Jong Kook wins assorted beef with the additional mission.)
What is that? Is that Korean beef?
- It's Korean beef. - There is a lot.
(The thick cuts of Korean beef sizzle beautifully.)
It has been grilled to perfection.
It should be made into a wrap.
Let me try it.
Who has 370 dollars?
So Min.
(I am jealous.)
Ji Hyo has 400 dollars.
(Is this a snack time or a penalty time?)
I will go to the snack bar and buy food.
- I will eat ramyeon. - Unless you really want to win...
Ji Hyo might feel that way, but you have no chance.
You can write my name on one of them.
How many spaces do you have left for the names?
I haven't written any names yet.
Jae Seok, why don't we write each other's names twice?
- Shall we do that? - Yes.
You will write my name twice, right? Okay. That's good.
- It will be cooked, right? - Yes.
(Peeking)
What are the three of you doing?
What?
Let me join in.
I will write your name if you are close to the bottom.
(Let's make a deal.)
Please write my name, Seok Jin.
Okay.
(What does he mean?)
(It's only a scheme.)
Okay.
- So Min. - Yes?
Do you want to write each other's names five times?
Let's do that. Let's turn the tables.
- Let's use our promissory notes. - We must fulfill this promise.
That's right.
We will write each other's names five times.
(That's a lot.)
(So Min and Seok Jin teamed up for their secret deal...)
(of writing each other's names 5 times.)
(I believe in Seok Jin.)
- Do you have cup ramyeon? - No.
- Ramyeon comes out cooked, right? - Yes.
Okay. Okay, okay.
- Here are 700 dollars for ramyeon. - Give me a discount.
Cook me ramyeon.
(With her faith in Seok Jin, So Min shops like a rich woman.)
I will buy chopsticks for 100 dollars.
- What? - Chopsticks for 100 dollars.
- I will sell them. - I will buy them for 100 dollars.
(She squanders her money.)
I don't have chopsticks.
(I know that Se Chan will lose.)
Okay.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan...)
If I write Seok Jin's name here,
Seok Jin will have more votes than you.
- Really? - Yes.
I will buy that vote. I will give you 100 dollars.
Just know that I still won't write your name.
(Just know that I still won't write your name.)
I won't write Seok Jin's name.
(He says he won't write Seok Jin's name or his name.)
What are you talking about?
So you will take my money without writing my name.
Yes. Does money mean anything to you at this point?
- No, it doesn't. - Do you want a beating?
(The penalty is flogging.)
- No. - Do you want a beating right now?
(Threatening)
- Why would you ask that? - Excuse me?
- I mean... - Are you talking back to me?
- I will write Seok Jin's name. - I understood your point.
How much do you need?
Not writing Seok Jin's name costs 400 dollars.
Not writing So Min's name costs 300 dollars.
I will pay for the latter.
I just need to get more votes than her.
(I want someone else to have the lowest number of votes.)
It will be either me, So Min, or Se Chan.
- Seok Jin. - I don't know.
So Min, did you sell a lot of votes?
- What do you mean? - The votes for the names.
- The names? - Yes.
Did you buy ramyeon instead of other members' votes?
- I was too hungry. - What are you going to do?
(She has her faith in Seok Jin.)
It's really tasty.
- Se Chan bought it. - How about me?
Tell me...
- how much money you have. - Chopsticks.
Let me see if I can flog you or not. It's meaningless otherwise.
Here.
I can use these, right?
(They are toys he received from Jae Seok.)
- Yes. - I will use them as chopsticks.
My goodness.
(Jae Seok didn't expect this.)
(I need chopsticks.)
I will sell these chopsticks for 100 dollars.
Forget it. I might win.
100 dollars.
(Let's see.)
- 100 dollars. - I couldn't help but eat.
- Me neither. - Those are mine.
(He is the owner of sophora root tea.)
If you write my name, I will give them to you.
Let's clear the snacks now. You will now spend...
about 10 minutes to vote.
- Are we clearing the snacks? - We will do that now.
I didn't even get to eat it because I didn't have chopsticks.
- Give me chopsticks. - I will give these to you...
if you write my name.
I will give these to you if you write my name.
- I can't do that because... - Then don't write Se Chan's name.
- Then you can have these. - Kwang Soo.
- Don't write Se Chan's name? - That's right.
- Okay. - Okay.
- I will give you 400 dollars. - Take his offer.
Take his offer and write his name.
It's everything I have.
I will give you 400 dollars.
- I will give you 400 dollars. - Okay.
It's a competition between the ones at the bottom.
I will reveal the result where the penalty will take place.
(It's the final moment.)
What is that? My goodness.
(The equipment for flogging is on standby.)
I will reveal the result.
With the promissory notes,
the person who has the most amount of money is...
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook with 2,400 dollars.
(Kim Jong Kook with 2,400 dollars)
- Me? - My goodness.
- He can buy that. - I received so much at the end...
that I didn't know how much I had.
- Please pick a present. - That's incredible.
I will take the humidifier.
- I don't have a humidifier at home. - Jong Kook chose the humidifier.
Also, Jong Kook has the right to flog the member...
with the lowest number of votes.
Jong Kook will do the flogging.
It's going to hurt.
When will I ever win in a race like this one?
In terms of votes, the 1st place is Song Ji Hyo with 18 votes.
(Song Ji Hyo with 18 votes)
She looks after people.
The 2nd place has 16 votes. It's Lee Kwang Soo.
(Lee Kwang Soo with 16 votes)
(It's an unexpected result.)
Does he have 16 votes?
(Everyone is incredulous.)
- 16 votes. - No way.
Thank you. It's heartwarming.
Now, I will announce the last place.
(Now comes the last place.)
- Now? - Is there a small difference?
- Yes. 1 vote divided the result. - 1 vote?
- 1 vote divided the result. - Yes.
- 1 vote. - 1 vote.
(Among them, who is fated to place last?)
(So Min teamed up with Seok Jin and exchanged 5 votes.)
(She even ate ramyeon because she believed in Seok Jin.)
(Se Chan stopped Seok Jin and So Min from getting votes.)
- You don't have to write my name. - Really?
I will give you 400 dollars.
(Seok Jin spent his entire fortune to buy votes.)
The last place has 13 votes.
(Who is fated to place last?)
(This person must be flogged by Jong Kook.)
Jeon So Min.
(It's Jeon So Min.)
How many votes did Seok Jin and I get?
- 15 votes. - We promised to write...
each other's names five times.
I spent the rest of my money to buy votes,
but she ate ramyeon. That made the difference.
I ate a 800-dollar ramyeon.
- You truly are the tiger moth. - Why did you eat ramyeon?
Kwang Soo, if I gave you...
100 dollars in real life, would you get flogged instead?
- In real life. - I am not a beggar.
You look interested.
I think you will be swayed if the amount is 150 dollars.
In that case, maybe.
(50 dollars make a difference.)
So Min, get your wallet out.
- It should start at this height. - Really?
It should start at this height.
Jae Seok, do you want to give us a simulation?
This is how you get flogged.
(It doesn't need a simulation.)
- Give it a try. - Kwang Soo, come here.
(Kwang Soo, come here.)
- This is how you get flogged. - I am up for it.
- This is how you get flogged. - Watch.
Kwang Soo will give us a simulation.
- Go ahead. - I don't want to surprise So Min.
- It doesn't hurt that badly. - I know that.
- It's not that bad. - Okay.
- You don't need to be scared. - You don't need to be scared.
If you hold the oar about this high and hit here, it doesn't hurt.
(Watch carefully.)
(I don't think you hit the right place.)
- It doesn't hurt, right? - It doesn't hurt at all.
That's the blow.
- That's the blow. - It only sounds bad.
- Here I go. - The height is just right.
- Here? - Yes.
- Do I swing like this? - That's right.
- Shall I begin? - Go ahead.
1, 2, 3.
Three.
(This is not an act, is it?)
That must have hurt.
(Viewers, this is the danger of ramyeon.)
- Hey, this is... - What is it?
- That must've hurt a little. - You told me to do it.
- Are you okay? - Listen.
Hey, everyone should get it.
To invigorate your energy,
we prepared a race to build up your health.
(These delicacies will arouse your disappearing appetites.)
(That's amazing. We have to eat that!)
(However,)
(these aren't your regular, invigorating dishes.)
(Their pupils are dilated.)
(This race for invigorating dishes will make their jaws drop.)
(A mysterious mission awaits the members too.)
(No one can taste these delicacies.)
(They end up hurting themselves while trying to eat these dishes.)
My body aches every week.
(The War of Flavors)