(The morning in Seoul signals the start of winter.)
I'm starting alone today again.
I'm nervous. What are we doing today?
Hello.
- Hello. - I'm starting alone today again.
Is it because I'm getting a special assignment?
It's very early in the morning.
- Hello. - Hi.
Why did you ask me to come here?
For today's race, your teammates will matter a lot.
Okay.
So Min and Ji Hyo...
will be the team leaders for each team.
- I'm the team leader? - Am I the team leader?
- Yes. - Yes.
You're all dead.
The team leader must pick up three members of your team...
and drive to the place for the opening segment.
To find where it will be held,
you will find out once you have picked up three members.
The team that arrives first will get a great advantage.
- I'll go by car? - Yes.
I'm the team leader?
I feel like I have been given a great task.
I'll get started. I can just pick up anyone, right?
I have to drive.
It's been so long since I drove. This will be a problem.
(The members just heard about the team leaders' mission.)
So Min is the team leader?
Wait, I haven't even been the team leader yet.
I think it was too early for her to be a team leader.
This might make her become too arrogant.
(She was the last member to join the show.)
Hold on a second. I think Ji Hyo will...
go for Haha first no matter what.
I'm sure Ji Hyo will choose Haha first.
(Whom will the team leaders pick first?)
He said whom I'll pick is important.
(It's crucial to today's race.)
I'll choose the most trustworthy one.
Hey.
Where are you?
I'm near my house. You?
We have to get there quickly.
I know. We have to.
I'm already outside.
Are you?
- Yes. - Jae Seok.
The director said whom I'll pick will be very important.
It is.
But...
I know you're going to pick up Haha first.
(She gets caught. She's always on Haha's side.)
I know you're going to pick him first.
- All right. - Okay.
We have to hurry.
Okay. I'll call Haha...
and then pick you up. Hold on a second.
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
Who is the best...
(So Min's still pondering.)
Who's the best at all games? Who's the best at everything?
Someone who's good at quizzes...
and someone who's agile.
Then it's obviously...
Jae Seok.
I'll go to him.
(She picks Jae Seok as well.)
Let's go.
Is this the gas pedal? I'm right.
(Driving is still awkward for her.)
Which one's for the blinkers? This? Oh, I'm right.
It's been too long since I last drove.
And...
I need to pick Jae Seok so that he'll drive for me.
I have to go before someone else does.
(I can't let Ji Hyo take him first.)
I'll pick him up.
Then I'll discuss with him.
The number you called is busy.
He's on the phone.
(Which one of them will get to him first?)
Please let me in.
(She wants to switch lanes.)
Please, Mr. Bus.
I should go in right now.
(Glancing)
I suck at this.
When should I go?
I'll go after that taxi.
All right.
This is my chance.
(As soon as I get used to driving, I'll come straight for you.)
I did it.
(Ji Hyo is good at driving.)
Is this the place?
(She arrives before So Min does.)
Is he outside?
Where is he?
(He said he was outside already.)
Oh, there he is.
(So Min arrives soon after.)
(There he is.)
Hello, fellow team member!
(She's happy to see him.)
(Which one of them will meet him first?)
Ji Hyo.
(Isn't he Jong Kook?)
(Jong Kook is her first pick.)
- Is no one else in the car? - You're my first pick.
- Let's hurry. - We should.
You have to wear this since we're on the same team.
- Okay. - Here.
There he is.
(Why are you opening this one as well?)
- What? - Jae Seok, hop in!
So Min.
You're here quite early.
- Hey, Jae Seok. - Hey.
- Do I need to sit back there? - I'm kidding.
Do you want to drive?
Sure.
This is great.
You were the closest.
You're the best.
(She's glad to have met her driver.)
- I knew... - I knew you'd be in Apgujeong-dong.
Ji Hyo wouldn't come for me.
I didn't expect much from her.
By the way,
whom should I pick for the other two members?
I'm still thinking.
- Two? - Yes.
The director said whom I pick is important.
(She needs to pick her team members and go to the destination.)
- What about Se Chan? - Where are we going?
- Call him. - You want me to?
I heard he's at a nearby park.
Then you probably have to turn right here.
It's Jong Kook.
Hey.
Hey, our lovely Se Chan.
Yes, this is your lovely Se Chan.
Where are you?
- I'm in front of the park. - Where?
There he is. He's waving.
(Hello, boss.)
- Hey. - Hello, sir.
- Just get in. - Hurry.
- Get in. - I'll hurry.
Get in, our lovely Se Chan.
Okay.
(They need to pick 1 more.)
If this is our team composition, we already won.
- Okay! - Okay!
Whom should we pick?
Let me think.
Who's nearby?
- I think... - Seok Jin...
- is the nearest. - Then let's go to him.
But we'll be at a disadvantage during games.
(Jae Seok is rather cold-hearted.)
(He may be nearby but won't be of great help during games.)
(He waits endlessly while exercising.)
Why is no one coming?
(He keeps fidgeting with his phone that is ever so silent.)
Kwang Soo called.
- He did? - Yes.
- Hello? - Hey, what are you up to?
I'm waiting for you. Where are you? Why aren't you here?
Where are you waiting?
We're still thinking whether to go to you or not.
"We"?
(Is someone already in the car?)
Whom are you with?
There's someone.
- Are you nearby? - I'm near the department store.
The department store?
- I hung up. - Let's see...
You did?
(As soon as he tells her where he is,)
(she hangs up.)
(Loss for words)
(Scoffing)
(He swallows his pride and calls her back.)
(How dare you ask questions and then hang up?)
- We're a bit far from you. - The call got cut off, right?
You didn't hang up, right?
- It was an accident, right? - Yes.
It got cut off.
- Wait there. - Okay.
Hold on. We're close...
to Kwang Soo and Seok Jin.
- Where's Seok Jin? - I'll call him.
His place is very close by.
(She attempts to call Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin...
- I think... - Whom I pick is important,
- so I was hesitant. - Hey, So Min.
- Seok Jin, where are you? - What?
I'm in front of my house.
- He sounds so arrogant. - Where are you?
He doesn't sound too desperate.
- That's not true. - He's not desperate.
I'm very much desperate.
Make an acrostic poem with So Min's name.
- Jeon. - Jeon.
I love Jeon So Min.
Hang up. That's enough.
I... Those little...
(He is agitated.)
(So Min picked Jae Seok first.)
She's with Jae Seok.
There he is.
He is.
- He was very near. - You were right.
- He was quite close. - He lives nearby.
Right.
(Is he talking on the phone with someone else?)
- Is it Ji Hyo? - I think so.
- Is it? - Ji Hyo.
(Jae Seok is dumbfounded.)
I'm in front of my house.
What a traitor.
How dare he?
- Seok Jin. - Where are you?
What? Hold on.
(Seok Jin spots Jae Seok.)
Goodness.
Hey, when did you guys arrive?
Gosh, Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin... - Forget it.
- Forget it. - Hey.
Ji Hyo, hang up for a second.
Open the door.
"Jeon". Jeonju bibimbap.
- Open the door. - Jeonju bibimbap?
- "So". So delicious. - Let's take him.
We'll let you in since we have no time.
- Did you call Ji Hyo? - You guys are mean.
- Because we didn't pick up? - Goodness.
You're too rude.
But I hung up right away.
What are you talking about?
I hung up.
- Goodness. - Seok Jin.
- I think it's the next block. - Wait a second.
There he is.
- What is that? - Haha's here?
- Look at him. - Why does he look so dark?
- He's too dressed up. - Why are his clothes so big?
(Oversized Leon)
It is indeed Haha.
(His fashion sense is from another realm.)
Haha, your clothes...
Haha.
Are you trying to look funny?
(Are you trying to look funny?)
Haha.
Are you trying to become a comedian?
- What is that? - What are you wearing?
I like your clothes.
- Are you trying to look funny? - Should I lend you this?
Doesn't my fashion evolve?
You're right.
(With Haha as their last pick, Ji Hyo's team is finalized.)
- How many do you need? - A total of three.
We need one more.
- One more? - Yes.
- Whom should we pick? - Let's see.
I heard Kwang Soo's nearby.
- Kwang Soo? - Yes.
It's always the same team members.
Although he may be nearby, choosing him...
would complete Team Penalty.
He's right.
Come to think of it, you're right.
Maybe we shouldn't pick anyone.
- What? - Let's not pick.
No one?
(While they're busy discussing about whether to pick him or not,)
(there's a lonely man who looks like an old tree during wintertime.)
(He keeps looking at his phone, checking to see if it's broken.)
Kwang Soo's calling.
Hey.
- Hey. - Where are you?
Just in case you'd get lost, I wanted to explain the route.
- No, we're already here. - We're here.
Really? I'll come down.
I see you. Hi.
(He has waited way too long and is very happy to see them.)
(Now, he is on his way to them.)
Jae Seok, hi...
(Speeding away)
Hey! Stop!
(Your team member is still outside, so where are you going?)
(We don't want to get penalized. I think we'll pass.)
(They decide to let him in.)
What were you doing?
You're quite fast.
(Hello, our last team member.)
- Goodness. - What were you doing?
You were quite fast.
You're still quite healthy.
- Get in. - Get in first.
- All right. - Goodness.
Jae Seok wasn't interested in having you in our team.
What do you mean?
This is great.
- Where do we go? - Where's our destination?
The director said we'd know once our team was created.
Are you ready to go?
- Yes. - Yes.
Before that,
please check your phones for new messages.
Why is he asking us to do that?
(You want us to check our phones?)
(What is this message that's been sent to every single one of them?)
"The contents of this message should be a secret."
We can't tell each other?
I didn't get that warning.
(It doesn't say that in mine.)
"Find the address to your destination."
"The team that takes the flag first gets an advantage."
I didn't get that warning.
"The contents of this message should be a secret."
What? I can't tell anyone?
(A new female team leader is waiting at Banpo Hangang Park.)
(She has the address of where the opening will be.)
(One from each team can be her team member.)
My message doesn't say it's a secret.
What? Your...
(Secret? A new team leader?)
Mine doesn't either.
(What is going on?)
Please check your text messages.
(Team So Min receives the same text message.)
- I got a text message. - I didn't get any.
I got one too.
"The contents of..." Oh, my.
(It's obvious that Kwang Soo was surprised.)
Hold on.
He just said, "The contents of..."
But mine doesn't start with that.
What's going on here?
(The team members make eye contact...)
(and start laughing.)
No one is saying anything after reading the message.
It's because of the first line.
- I was so surprised. - The first line...
- The first line surprised me. - Me too.
My goodness.
(The text message to the team leaders says,)
("The address is hidden in Banpo Hangang Park.")
(The text message to the team members says,)
("A new female team leader is waiting at Banpo Hangang Park.")
("She has the address of where the opening will be.")
Wait, I think we're here. Banpo District.
(They arrive at Banpo Hangang Park as the text message says.)
- Are we here? We're here. - Banpo Hangang Park.
- That's right. - We're here.
- Should we get out? - Let's...
Let me get out first.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Why are you in a hurry?
(The team leader wants to find the opening address,)
(and the team members want to find the new team leader.)
I think we're here.
- Okay. - Okay.
- You're not going to run, are you? - No.
I have to go straight to the bathroom.
You do? So do I.
I've been holding it in for so long.
It's driving me crazy.
(They have to find the new team leader secretly.)
- We should start looking for it. - Where should we look?
- What are we looking for? - A flag.
- Is this the place? - Are we here?
We're here?
What are you doing?
What?
(They definitely look distracted.)
(The team leader wants to find the opening address.)
Those two are acting strangely.
What's going on?
Do you have a different goal from us?
Are you looking for something else than a flag?
- What? - Aren't you looking for a flag?
We're looking for a flag.
Hey.
(We're looking for the same thing, right?)
Hurry up! We have to find it.
Find what? You know something?
The opening address.
(Sorry, we're looking for a new team leader.)
Really?
What's going on? Do you have another mission?
What are you talking about?
(Haha leaves his team.)
(A white car catches his attention.)
(He pretends nothing is happening.)
What's going on over there?
(That white car must have...)
(something inside.)
(Careful)
(His target is the white car. Come up with something, Haha!)
(He decides to pretend he's joining the team...)
(and then turn back.)
Hi, Haha.
- Hi. - Hi.
It must be inside the park.
(Kwang Soo can feel that Haha knows something.)
(Mumbling)
(It seems like I've been joined by someone who can be a nuisance.)
(The betrayer brothers start to walk the same path.)
- Haha. - Yes?
You got the text message, right?
(He already figured it out.)
- You got the text message, right? - Yes.
I'll find her by all means.
Where is the flag?
The flag must be around here.
(Those guys must know something.)
(Let's keep pretending we're looking for a flag.)
Wait!
(What's that white car?)
(Kwang Soo rushes to the white car.)
(While Haha was looking around,)
(Kwang Soo found the new team leader in the white car.)
(Lucky me! I have to get in the car.)
(Only two can join her. Haha rushes to the car too.)
(What is going on?)
Hurry!
- Hurry! - I'm in.
(They get in the car as fast as they can.)
- Gosh. - Lock the doors.
(The doors are locked.)
Who is it?
Hold on.
We found her.
We found the new team leader.
(The epitome of girl crush, Lee Si Young)
Are you the new team leader?
(From romance to action,)
(this versatile actress can pull off anything.)
(Everyone has a girl crush on this boxer that represents Korea.)
(6 years ago on Running Man, she proved how good she is.)
(Passionate team leader Lee Si Young is here!)
- It's been so long. - Si Young.
- Si Young. - Yes?
- Si Young. - Hi.
- Si Young. - Si Young.
- I can't believe it. - You were here?
- What happened? - My goodness.
- You betrayers. - This is crazy.
You betrayers.
(What is going on here?)
- Si Young. - She was here.
I had no idea Si Young was here.
Hi.
He's so cheeky.
- He's so cheeky. - Gosh.
What's going on?
Hey.
You scumbag.
- How can you do this to me? - I'm sorry.
- What did you do? - Go away.
I need to talk to Si Young.
You're not on my team anymore? So suddenly?
- Si Young... - I got a text message.
locked the doors.
What should we do now?
What should we look for?
Address? Guys!
Guys! Team So Min!
(Ji Hyo searches the place too.)
I like this team.
- It feels so different. - I know.
(The new team leader already has the address.)
If I was on Ji Hyo's team today too...
This feels so different.
Wait.
There's something here!
(Team So Min finds something.)
- Wait. - Where?
- So Min! - Where?
I found it!
(They found the address.)
"161, Mokdongseo-ro, Yangcheon-gu, Seoul".
- This way? - It's in Mok-dong.
- It's in Mok-dong. - We have to go to Mok-dong.
Let's go. Hurry up.
(The firstcomers will get benefits.)
They found it!
Should we just follow them?
Did they see us?
Let's go!
I think we're all headed to the same place.
161, Mokdongseo-ro... Hold on.
Follow them.
They're moving.
(Team Ji Hyo starts to follow Team So Min.)
I think we'll definitely win.
- Definitely. - We should win.
I'm serious today.
So am I.
When they asked me, I chose you two.
- Really? - Yes.
- I told them I wanted you two. - Really? Thank you.
I wasn't going to let others in.
Seriously?
(They're so happy to be on the same team for now.)
(A moment later)
(You jerk!)
(Verbal and physical violence?)
(Punching)
(A national boxer's punch?)
(What's going to happen to this team?)
(You'll soon find out the truth behind the Lee Si Young incident.)
(Team Si Young arrives at the SBS headquarters.)
- We're here. - Hurry. There must be something.
(To win, you have to pull out the flag.)
There's a flag.
Where?
This is it?
Hold on.
We did it!
What happens now?
You arrived first, and you'll get benefits.
I like it.
(It was a good idea to betray the others.)
Is there nothing here?
(Nothing is left for Team So Min and Team Ji Hyo.)
- It's over. - It's over.
It's over.
Today's hidden team leader was...
Lee Si Young.
- Hi. - It's been so long.
I saw a bus advertisement on my way here.
It was an advertisement for her new movie.
- You shot a movie? - Yes.
- It's an action movie. - It's an action movie, right?
- "Action"? - "Action".
I didn't use any doubles.
- Really? - I did everything myself.
Can you show us some self-defense moves?
- Should I show you a little? - Please.
There are different stages.
Show us a lot. Use Kwang Soo.
Please stand here.
Show us a lot.
Let's say you grabbed me by the collar.
I grabbed you by the collar?
- Let's pretend. - It can happen.
I grabbed you by the collar.
(How will Si Young deal with it?)
- You should all try. - It can happen.
- It can happen. - Let's pretend.
- They can do that to you. - I grabbed you by the collar.
You grabbed me by the collar.
(Using her body weight, she drags Kwang Soo down.)
(The bad guy falls to the ground.)
It's very simple.
I didn't fake it.
- I didn't fake it. - It's real.
- It works. - This...
So Min, try it.
(When grabbed by the collar,)
(how will So Min react?)
Not that.
(Jae Seok lets go of her because he's dumbfounded.)
You should sit down.
My goodness.
Try it on Seok Jin. Sit down.
Hey!
Get your act together!
(Will she be able to follow the instructions this time?)
(She gets stopped.)
Don't just hold his hands.
Use your body weight.
So Min, you should use your body weight.
- Use your body weight. - This was nice.
- Try it. - Put your weight on it.
(Will she be different after the lesson?)
I sat down for you.
(They train their legs together.)
- I sat down for her. - Si Young, try it.
- She can't do it. - Si Young, try it.
She can't do it.
Si Young, try it.
You sat down for her? Si Young, try it.
- She can't do it. - You sat down for her?
(Let the female warrior show him the right way.)
- It's no problem. - Si Young, show him.
(I think I can resist.)
(Will Seok Jin be able to resist?)
Grab me by the collar.
Don't sit down for her.
(He falls.)
(Don't sit down, just lie down! Big Nose Man)
She's different.
- My goodness. - She's different.
- It was different. - You have some poop on your pants.
(You have some poop on your pants.)
- Hey. - What's that?
(He was already embarrassed.)
It's really poop!
What is this?
- It's really poop! - You got poop on your pants.
(It's true.)
Let me show you...
- It's amazing. - something easier.
When someone grabs you from behind, you can do something really easy.
Grab her from behind.
- But he's too tall. - You have to grab me tightly...
so I can't escape.
Like this.
I'll do it for real.
If someone grabs you like this, it's difficult to lose him.
Then...
What you do is, you push your bottom to the back.
And move your arm like this.
(Push out the bottom and use the arm and legs to make him fall.)
(This way, you can protect yourself even from a tall person.)
I see. That's cool.
It's completely possible.
- It will work on you too. - Me?
I bet it does.
- I'll grab you. - You grab me.
(Will Si Young's self-defense work on Jong Kook?)
Right.
Goodness.
(Her charisma dominates him immediately.)
That was...
- Are you okay? - It really works.
That's amazing. Try it, So Min.
- After you do that, you should run. - Try it, So Min.
(Come on, come on.)
Push out your bottom. No, use the other leg.
What was that?
(She falls down after using the wrong leg.)
(Use the other leg.)
What did you do?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you, So Min?
Why can't I do it?
- Si Young is impressive. - She's impressive.
- I knew it. - She's different.
Si Young's passion is impressive.
Everyone, did you bring your passport?
Yes, I brought it because you told me.
I brought my passport and suitcase just in case.
Among all of your global missions from the past,
you'll make another attempt at those you had failed.
- Those we failed? - Make another attempt?
It's the Year End Special, Losers Bracket.
- What? - Like the Giant Swing?
(They must clear global missions that they failed.)
(Losers Bracket)
(List of countries and missions)
(Tsushima Island, Osaka, Okinawa, Hong Kong, Russia, Mongolia)
(Mongolia)
(Milk 4 liters of sheep milk)
(Mission failed)
(Fishing king crabs and 10 types of fish in Russia)
(Trying the most recent hairstyles in Osaka)
(Mission failed)
(Trying food recommended by the locals in Okinawa)
(Be the 100th in line for an experience in Hong Kong)
(Mission failed)
(Catching seafood you ate at a restaurant on Tsushima Island)
Missions should be cleared at original locations.
Due to shooting complications,
you will divide into one Team Hong Kong,
and two of Team Gangwon Province.
Like that?
Missions will be adjusted...
based on the location.
(Missions will adjust based on the location.)
- Will they be substituted? - Is that so?
- I thought we were traveling. - Okay.
If you fail, the members will be punished based on...
- the number of failed missions. - The number of members?
Yes. Each team will be given 10 votes.
You may distribute them within the team.
Team Si Young will get...
three additional votes.
(Team Si Young gets 3 additional votes.)
That must be nice.
(Clear missions that you had failed once.)
So Min and Seok Jin.
- Shall we go to Okinawa? - Let's do that.
That sounds good.
- We pick Okinawa. We've been there. - Okinawa.
We have regrets.
Let's go with Genghis Khan.
- Let's do that. - "Four liters of sheep milk"?
- Sheep milk? - They're over there.
There are many sheep in Gangwon Province.
- Let's not catch seafood. - How about...
We can't fish.
Fishing abroad is difficult, and we might travel abroad.
The hair salon mission is absurd too.
We made our decision. In 1, 2, 3.
- Hong Kong. - Hong Kong.
Everyone made a decision.
This is the most important part.
Random vehicle pick will determine the location of your mission.
- Really? - Is it random?
Two vans head to Gangwon Province.
One van will take you to the airport where you'll depart for Hong Kong.
It hasn't been decided yet.
Is it possible to milk sheep in Hong Kong?
It won't be easy to find sheep milk in Hong Kong.
It'll be difficult.
- Gangwon Province has a sheep farm. - It's possible.
There's a sheep farm, so it's possible over there.
Pick your van. Go.
For the team going to Hong Kong,
what time is their flight?
- It'll be in the afternoon. - In the afternoon, right?
- Gangwon Province is better. - It's better.
- Let's go. - Shall we go?
So Min, choose the van that you want.
I hope you two will bring me luck just this once.
Let's get on the van that you choose.
But...
- Which one is it? - This one?
- All right. - I like this one, Ji Hyo.
- This one? - Let's pick the middle one.
Let's get on the far right.
- This one? - Let's get on this one.
- Okay, this one? So Min. - We pick this one.
Doesn't it look like it's going to Gangwon Province?
- Okay. - Doesn't it?
Let's go.
Let's go to Gangwon Province.
We must get on it.
(All teams picked their vans.)
(Please let this head to Gangwon Province.)
(The driver gives them the destination.)
- I'll just open it. - Okay.
Gangwon Province.
- Can you see it? In 1, 2, 3. - No way.
(We won't go to Hong Kong, will we?)
It's Incheon International Airport.
(No way.)
(Is it really Hong Kong?)
(It's hard to clear their mission even in Korea.)
My predictions are never wrong.
Sad predictions are never wrong.
(In that case)
It's Gangwon Province.
(Team Si Young heads to Gangwon Province.)
I knew it.
Yes.
(Team Ji Hyo heads to Gangwon Province.)
- Okay. - Thank goodness.
(Team So Min wants to deny the reality.)
Sir, is this going to Incheon International Airport?
- Yes. - It's true.
I asked just in case.
It was a torture with soba and ramen last time.
- It was difficult being nonstop. - It was hard.
I wish I wouldn't go abroad with you all the time.
My goodness.
We're at the airport.
- Goodness. - See you again.
- See you tomorrow. - See you tomorrow.
Bye.
(We'll have a blast this time.)
- This is a relief. - We'll be great.
(Team Si Young stays at SBS.)
We're a perfect team.
We have to do well.
We have 13 ballots. Don't we have to distribute them?
I'm the team leader, so I'll decide.
- No. - I'm the team leader.
(She could be a dictator.)
- So I'll decide. - No.
- Listen. - You need to be democratic.
Someone has to keep the ballots.
- I'm sorry but... - I'm the team leader.
You know what the worst is?
Don't simply hold the leader title.
- I'm the real team leader. - That's why...
- Make us look up to you. - Listen.
- I'm the real one. - We need to pick you.
Hey, listen up.
(She's impatient.)
"Hey, listen up"?
I'm the real team leader, so I'll hold on to them.
You knew I was the leader, so trust me.
Follow my lead. Let's go.
If you trust us, give us four ballots each.
Okay, okay.
- For now... - Listen.
- What is it? - I'll give you one each.
My goodness.
Come on.
- Come on. - I'll give you one each.
Can I change teams now?
I can't be on a frustrating team like this.
- How can you do this? - Listen.
Here's your mission for today.
Please open this.
Inside this is our real mission.
(What's the mission adjusted to Gangwon Province?)
(Find a descendant of Genghis Khan and milk 4 liters of sheep milk)
- "Gangwon Province". - "King"?
"Find a ranch related to the king and milk four liters of sheep milk".
Is it okay as long as we relate it to the king?
Okay.
The person's nickname could be King.
It could be Annoying King or King Nose.
That's right.
(Annoying King or King Nose?)
"King Nose"?
Let's do some research.
- Is there anything king-related? - How about this?
Let's go outside and do it.
We don't need to hurry.
- Finish by Team Hong Kong's return. - Right.
Sheep Farm.
There's Samyang Ranch in Daegwallyeong.
There's no king ranch in Gangwon Province.
I know the answer.
It's King Dasan Ranch.
- King Dasan. - You have to call them.
This isn't a quiz, Si Young.
I'm sorry.
You're too much.
Let's call the first ranch that we find...
and ask the name of the owner.
(They decide to ask the name of the ranch owner.)
- Let's ask. - Okay.
- That sounds good. - I'll do it.
- Hello? - Hello?
- Is this a ranch? - Yes.
Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo on Running Man.
All of a sudden?
There are no sheep for milking.
We don't have sheep that give milk.
You can't milk these sheep.
What do we do? We can't milk any sheep right now.
I'll call. We have no choice but keep calling.
(It's hard to find a ranch.)
Hello?
Hello, we're shooting Running Man right now.
- Yes? - Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
I see.
(Who is Lee Kwang Soo?)
(He doesn't seem to know who he is.)
Haha is next to me. Hold on please.
Hello.
I'm Haha on Running Man. Hello, sir.
- Hello, Haha. - Hello.
(He's excited to hear his voice.)
It's nice to meet you. Do you know Lee Kwang Soo?
- I don't. - I see.
(His answer is firm.)
(It's a huge embarrassment.)
- Sir? - Yes?
It's nice to meet you. We have a mission on Running Man.
Can you move aside?
We have to milk four liters of sheep milk.
- Sheep milk? - Yes.
Do you have any sheep that can give milk?
Yes, we do.
(They finally find someone after 8 attempts.)
Can we get four liters of milk?
- I think... - I'm very tall.
Who cares?
I'm very tall.
Among Korean celebrities,
I'm 1 of the 5 tallest ones.
When was the last time you watched Running Man?
- What are you doing? - Wait.
Have you seen Running Man?
I'm sorry.
You might think that he's Han Gi Beom.
- Han Gi Beom? - Yes.
- The basketball player? - Yes.
(He doesn't know Lee Kwang Soo but knows Han Gi Beom.)
He knows Han Gi Beom but doesn't know Kwang Soo.
I know him.
We went to Yangpyeong High School.
(They're high school colleagues.)
(I should have tried basketball instead.)
This is so funny.
(Although their faces are the same, one is popular, and one isn't.)
- Sir. - Yes?
Do you have anything related to kings or have such connections?
- Like you're from a royal family... - I...
(The owner of the ranch doesn't know Kwang Soo at all.)
(Does he have anything related to kings at his ranch?)
Yes, my ranch is in Wangsan.
(His ranch is related to their keyword, king.)
Wangsan?
- Wangsan? - This is amazing.
- What does that mean? - Sir.
The location? He's located in Wangsan?
We'd like to head over there and meet you.
(The ranch is located in Wangsan, Gangneung of Gangwon Province.)
We'll see you soon. Thank you.
- Okay. - Thank you!
This is incredible!
- It all worked out. - His ranch is in Wangsan.
- That will definitely work. - We'll see you soon.
- This is amazing. - This will definitely qualify.
I can't believe the name happens to be Wangsan.
We'll accept the name of the sheep ranch.
(Even the staff will allow it.)
Hey, Joo Yong.
When we get there,
you should wear Kwang Soo's jacket...
- and pretend to be Kwang Soo. - What are you saying?
- Yes, let's try that. - We don't need to go that far.
- He'll hold the camera. - Must we go that far?
Let's check if the owner can recognize you or not.
I'm really curious.
- I'm sure he'll recognize me. - Will he?
- If not, give us two ballots. - It's just my name.
If he recognizes you, we'll give you one ballot each.
- We'll give you ours then. - Let's do that.
You're a celebrity and the Prince of Asia. He has to.
- That's right. - You must bet your pride.
(Am I at an advantage?)
If he doesn't recognize you, give us all of your ballots.
- All of them? - Yes.
If you...
- Hear me out. - Her logic is weird indeed.
I think she really thinks I'm an idiot.
I know how to add and subtract.
This is a good deal for you.
- Think about it. It is. - Listen.
I get only one from each of you, but I give you all of mine?
No, listen.
Say that you only have two ballots.
Then you have to give two ballots to each of us.
Then you owe two ballots.
When you earn more ballots, you'll have to give them to us.
But if you give us everything you have now, it could end with one.
Will you give us all of yours? Or just two ballots each?
Are you a couple of scammers?
(Are you a couple of scammers?)
(They almost convinced him.)
- Haha, am I wrong here? - Listen.
- That was really wise. - No, I'm not.
I'll decide after I play the game.
I'll do it. I'll do it by all means.
- Sure. We'll see. - Okay. We can be flexible.
- Okay. Let's get going first. - I understand.
(Can the owner recognize Kwang Soo?)
This is the board for the missions.
- Be the 100th in line. - What is it?
Be the 100th person in line and go in.
We did this mission for the Hong Kong Special.
- It won't be easy in Korea. - Gosh, we're in Gangwon Province.
1, 2, 3.
(Goodness, what is this?)
- What? - Goodness.
- Oh, gosh. - Treat 100 people to a meal.
We must have 100 people line up and treat them to a meal.
Then does it mean we have to cook?
- Do we have to cook too? - Yes.
We have to cook too?
It's really hard to cook for 100 servings of food.
We have to cook the meals...
and gather people around.
And make them line up too?
- Gosh, this is so hard. - This is terrible.
Since this is a large-scale mission,
we have invited a special guest...
- to help you with the mission. - Really?
It must be a chef.
The guest must be a chef. That will definitely help.
(Even his outfit seems unusual.)
(Is this the outfit for the armed forces chef?)
(She seems as if she can cook 100 servings without any problem.)
That will definitely help.
- The spot next to you looked empty. - I knew it.
There's no way two cameras would film me.
- You're right. - There's no way.
- We have a special guest. - Who is it?
Let's go.
I hope we get a special guest who can cook.
We'll prepare the ingredients while you're on your way there.
- Will you buy them for us? - Yes.
Then do we just need to decide...
- on the meal we'll cook? - That's correct.
I don't know who this special guest is.
We should listen to the guest.
- You're right. - Right. That's right.
If the guest is a good cook,
- The guest will know what to cook. - it's covered then.
Is the guest good at cooking?
I heard the guest is somewhat good.
- That will suffice. - "Somewhat"?
- Well... - The guest isn't a professional.
The guest must be a TV personality who can cook.
Wait, if we're turning this way...
(Wait, if we're turning this way...)
Hold on.
- Come on. There's no way. - Are you serious?
No way.
(No way. Could it be that person?)
The guest turned around.
Can you see the guest? Is the guest there?
(A special guest to accomplish their mission of cooking 100 servings)
(Who is this special guest?)
Byul.
(Byul, the queen of ballad songs, Haha's wife of 6 years)
- It is her! - Go Eun!
(She's another family member.)
- Hello. - Hi. Hold on. Let me go back.
We were right about this.
- Did you guess it was me? - We guessed it right.
Yes. My gosh, I can't believe this.
- Go Eun! - Wait, Haha doesn't know?
- My husband doesn't know. - He doesn't?
- This is fun. He doesn't know. - Really?
Let's talk while we head there.
- Sure. - This is unbelievable.
Byul, did you hear about the mission?
- Do you know what we're doing? - The mission?
I heard we're cooking today.
- We don't know much about cooking. - We have to do this.
Do you cook at home?
I cook soup and side dishes.
I can cook all of the basic dishes.
- Really? - That's great.
- You cook all of your side dishes? - Yes, the basic stuff.
- I can season vegetables. - We're all good. We're set.
- You're right. - That's perfect.
(She's totally reliable.)
I looked up some stuff while waiting for you guys.
- The dough soup isn't that hard. - Is that so?
- Really? - It's doable.
- The dough soup? - We should cook...
- pancakes. Pancakes. - Pancakes?
To cook pancakes, you just need to make a lot of batter.
All you need to do is fry them.
- Pancakes. - Pancakes.
We have to serve some meat.
- We should... - Suyuk?
- Suyuk. Suyuk. Yes. - Yes.
We did think about making suyuk.
I think that will be nice.
But tell you what.
- I've cooked before. - Go on.
Cooking for 2 to 3 servings...
- and cooking for... - Isn't it different?
- Yes. - I'm sure. It's so different.
- Getting the portion right is hard. - Yes, it's really hard.
- Seasoning it is hard too. - Seasoning is hard as well.
- We have to cook in a big pot. - Right.
We might fail, Byul.
(What if we fail the mission?)
He probably has no clue.
- Right? - He'll be so shocked.
(I think I saw my wife in my dream.)
Byul, how old were you when you got married?
I was 30.
- 30? - You married early.
- You did marry early. - You married early given your job.
Haha was 34 when he married me.
- Haha was 34? - Yes.
- Haha got married early too. - That's right.
- He did, given that he played hard. - He was...
(He did, given that he played hard.)
- Jong Kook. Don't say that. - I'm sorry.
- Byul is here. - I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - I really wanted to bring this up.
Dream watches this show.
(Our kid watches this show that requires the viewers' discretion.)
- Sometimes... - Beep this part.
- Edit this part out. - Dream.
- Beep it out. - It happened today.
Replace it with a chick's sound to make it cute.
- When he meets Kwang Soo, - I didn't know...
- he grabs Kwang Soo's collar first. - he watches this show.
Dream watches the show now.
Of course.
I can't say that now.
I should be more careful now.
- We must be careful. - My goodness, Dream.
For today's special, please make what I said...
into a cute expression for Dream.
(Haha doesn't play hard anymore.)
(Dream's father is born again into a new life.)
- Let's form a club. - Yes.
(Meanwhile)
What should we name our club?
We should name our club.
Let's...
go with...
Gangster.
(Haha who doesn't play hard joins a new club, Gangster.)
The name has two meanings.
- That could be possible. - He used to be a gangster.
But he's not a gangster anymore.
We can give the name more meaning.
- We're giving like the sheep. - We're giving.
- We don't spare to give. - We're giving.
We, who don't spare anything to give,
are the best.
(Trying to come up with a meaning)
I don't think we'll have a better one than this.
There are times when things go wrong.
It's when we go astray...
- from our original intention. - Right.
- We can use this as our mantra. - We won't think about other stuff.
- Okay, okay. - We should remind ourselves.
- When someone says, "Like sheep", - Okay.
We, who spare nothing to give,
- are the best! - Are the best!
(A mantra that will help them stay grounded)
The more I hear it, the more I like it.
- This is great. - It's great.
(This gangster is feeling proud.)
I can't believe we haven't even started...
- our mission yet. - Right.
- I thought it'd take two days. - At least halfway...
I think this will be a long journey.
(They fought, found a ranch, and made a slogan.)
Like sheep,
- We, who spare nothing to give, - We, who spare nothing to give,
- are the best! - are the best!
- Exactly. - We spare nothing to give.
(They arrive at a rest area to divide their ballots and eat.)
Will you divide the ballots now?
The first place will stay seated.
The 2nd and 3rd place will leave and come back later.
As you suggested, Kwang Soo will stay first.
The two of you can go outside and wait.
(Haha and Si Young leave the area for Kwang Soo.)
(How many of 13 ballots will Kwang Soo take?)
I'll take 13 ballots.
(He doesn't even think about it.)
(This is a game of loyalty, but he takes all 13 ballots.)
(Clueless of this, they're taking selfies with people.)
Two of you can come back in together.
Come back in together?
(Why are we coming back together?)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Pardon? - You said to come in together.
Why should we come in together?
(What is this? There's nothing on the table.)
- What is it? - Let's eat.
(I took them all.)
What just happened?
Is it over?
It's over.
(The loyalty game of the ballots ends.)
What happened? Explain what happened.
What happened?
I took all 13 ballots.
He's really like a gangster.
(She really gets angry.)
- We had a deal. - I have no choice now.
- We were supposed to get one each. - And I...
I'll post this on my social media now.
- Post what? - Sit down.
- Listen. - Post what?
A picture of Kwang Soo's ex-girlfriend.
(He plays the hardest card.)
- Why would you do that? - Let's do this.
You broke our agreement.
- A verbal agreement still counts. - You know?
I was kidding.
Don't upset me.
(He generously gives 1 ballot.)
- Don't upset me. - I'm sorry.
I'm still furious about this.
Then I'll just post her initials.
- I gave you a ballot. - I'll just post her initials.
- I gave you one. - Just the initials.
Listen.
- You think I'd give you just one? - Wait, me too.
(You think I'd give you just one?)
- You know? - I'm really hurt too.
- No way. Haha. - What will it be? What?
- I'm Kwang Soo. - I was really shocked.
- I'm like your brother. - Listen.
Look at me.
I'm really hurt too.
Hear me out.
(Let's talk it out.)
Listen. Hey, hey.
Hold on.
I get that you know self-defense martial arts.
You can't get anything if you don't play dirty.
Si Young.
Remember? Like sheep!
- We, who spare nothing to give, - We, who spare nothing to give,
- are the best. - are the best.
- Give us one more each. - Come on.
(Haha prepares something while they're arguing.)
Kwang Soo.
(I prepared this just for you.)
I'll just show you the first photo.
- What? - I'll let you check first.
Do you see this?
Please blur it.
I even have a video of this.
What's that?
- What are you doing? - How many can you give me?
How many can you give me?
Let me show you the video too.
It's being blurred, right?
For now, it's blurred.
What's with him?
This one...
- is amazing. - I gave you some!
- I already gave you some! - After this...
Give me two more, and I'll leave.
How can I give you two?
Haha, I'll...
(Haha plays the video.)
- It's a video. - I think you should give him.
(What is the video?)
(Give him 2 more if you want to keep working as an actor.)
I have a video.
- Why did you do that? - Give me two more.
- Were you drunk? - I'll give you one.
What? I'm just sleeping in that video. I was tired.
And you had no idea?
I was asleep.
I'll give you one more.
Give me.
I can't give you more than this.
(Haha takes 1 more vote away from Kwang Soo.)
Give it to me. I won't upload this one.
- Okay. - If you keep doing this,
I won't milk the sheep.
(Shameless)
- Let's go separately. - Send me one of those photos.
(Send me one of those photos.)
Do you know what she just said?
"Send me one of those photos."
- She's so funny. - Hey, scumbags.
That's enough.
"Scumbag"?
What did you say?
- Kwang Soo. - This won't do.
Hold on. Give me a pen.
Give me a pen.
(Will they be able to milk the sheep today?)
We're here.
(Team Ji Hyo arrives in Gangwon Province.)
- I see a senior citizen center. - We'll probably cook with those.
That's too much.
There are so many ingredients. It's going to take forever.
(It's a lot.)
We're doomed.
We've prepared ingredients for potato dough soup,
suyuk, japchae, and jeon.
Is this for real? Does it even make sense?
It'll take two hours to just wash them.
Are they for sale?
Even the supermarket near my place doesn't have this much.
Even they don't have this much.
These are ingredients for dough soup, right?
It's not going to be easy.
All I can do is sigh after seeing all these ingredients.
I mean...
Come on.
Hold on.
I mean...
Look at this.
It's from the picture...
you can see at me and Haha's restaurants.
That's right.
Exactly.
- That's right. - Right?
- Right? - The picture...
- Really? - When we talk to people,
we should tell them what time the food will be served.
- At 8 or 9... - That's right.
- We have to decide the time. - At this rate,
- we won't be done until tomorrow. - we won't be done until tomorrow.
We should ask them if it's okay if we serve the food at 2am.
We should ask them if it's okay if we serve it as a midnight snack.
Let's start. We don't have time for this.
- I'll do my best. - Okay.
I'll work hard.
What should we do?
- Let's divide up. - Okay.
- Let's work hard. - You guys need to hurry.
- Okay. - Don't take too long.
- Let's do this! - Good luck!
- We can do this! - Good!
I get scared just by looking at the ingredients.
Do we have any aprons?
We should take off our jackets, right?
Yes, it's too thick. We should take it off.
Let's start by washing the ingredients.
(The girls start cooking for 100 people.)
(The guys will try to attract 100 people.)
- We should... - Should we visit that house?
visit each house, right?
I see someone.
Hello, ma'am.
(They try to sound cute.)
- Do you... - We're shooting "Running Man".
We're shooting "Running Man".
Do you recognize me?
- Kim... - Kim.
Kim.
Kim Gook Jin?
(Kim Gook Jin?)
It starts with "Kim Jong".
Kim Jong.
What's the last syllable?
(He tells her almost the whole name.)
- You said it before. - Kim Jong Kook.
(After thinking for a moment, she says, "Kim Jong Kook".)
(Otherwise, he would have been hurt.)
- Kim Gook Jin. - She must have remembered "Kook".
She remembered "Kim" and "Kook".
Can you guess who this guy is?
- Do you know my name? - Can you guess his occupation?
- He's... - What?
(She doesn't even hesitate.)
(While she didn't recognize Jong Kook, she knows Se Chan?)
Isn't he a cameraman?
(Confident)
(Yang Se Chan, 33, cameraman)
Ma'am.
That's right.
That one really hurts.
- It hurts so much. - She hurt you.
- It hurts... - She hurt you.
I'm a cameraman.
He is.
He's a cameraman.
(The lady is serious.)
I'm a comedian.
- Stop it. - I'm...
- Ma'am. - Leave her alone.
We're shooting "Running Man" today.
We'd like to cook...
some food for you all.
We'll serve the food a bit late, around 6:30pm.
Can you come later?
- I can come. - Really?
- Bring everyone. - Bring all your neighbors.
- Everyone. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - I'll bring other people.
See you later.
- Let's go this way. - Okay.
When...
she said I was a cameraman,
I lost all my confidence.
I can't say anything right now.
- I can't talk to anyone anymore. - It's okay.
It's okay.
It's no big deal.
- This is so funny. - This is so funny.
(It's okay. The next person will recognize you.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Welcome. - Hello.
We're from SBS's "Running Man".
(They find a lady who is working.)
Ma'am.
Nice to meet you.
- I've seen you on TV. - Do you know who I am?
- I don't remember your name. - You don't remember my name.
- Kim. - Kim.
Jong Kook?
(Kim Jong Kook?)
Do you know what this guy does?
(Please...)
(shout out my name.)
- I'm not sure. - You're not sure.
(Again)
I just know who you are.
He's our cameraman.
He's a cameraman.
She doesn't even look at me.
I'll work harder.
We'd like to cook some food for you all.
- You don't have to. - It'll be served around 6:30pm.
If you have time, please come. Please tell your family too.
- Bring everyone. - Okay.
- Do you want some persimmons? - Persimmons?
- Do you have persimmons? - Please.
Hey, why don't you carry a camera?
Carry it around.
They look so tasty.
Please film it. Look at this.
You don't get to see these often.
- Please film me too. - Okay.
- One second. - They've become too soft.
- That's enough. - That's enough.
- Oh, my. That's too much. - That's enough.
Please keep filming it. What are you doing?
(Please keep filming it. What are you doing?)
Okay. That's enough.
That's enough.
Thank you so much.
I never expected to see you in real life.
(She says goodbye only to Jong Kook.)
- Please come... - How did you come here?
We just happened to come here.
I see.
- We'll get going. - Thank you.
- Thank you for the persimmons. - Bye.
- Good job. Okay. - Good job. Okay.
Where should we go now?
(Team So Min arrives in Hong Kong.)
Welcome to Hong Kong.
- I'm suddenly so excited. - So am I.
- I'm so excited. - You're always like that.
When you arrive somewhere,
- I get excited. - you get all excited.
But it doesn't last long.
- You'll become depressed. - It's not going to last long.
You'll soon find out...
Bye!
Bye, airplane!
(He reacts enthusiastically to an airplane.)
- I'm so excited. - You guys know, right?
He's like this in every opening.
- It's exactly the same every time. - I'm so excited.
But by the time we're in the city...
- He becomes lethargic. - "Why do we have to walk so much?"
- "How long do we have to walk?" - "I can't eat anymore."
(Please stay excited until the end.)
Here's the mission you have to complete in Hong Kong.
- What is it? - What is it?
In Okinawa,
- we ate noodles. - Yes. We failed.
(Eat the food recommended by a local.)
(In Okinawa, they wanted to have steaks.)
(Soba)
(Ramen)
(Ramen again)
(They couldn't even smell any steaks...)
(and got caught up in a noodle maze.)
Let's try it here.
(What food will they eat in Hong Kong?)
Hong Kong is known for dim sum.
Then it won't take a lot of time.
- If it's dim sum, it'll be easy. - Right.
(Will they get to eat dim sum...)
(and complete the mission right away?)
(Find a local person who recommends the dish the members choose.)
(Hong Kong: Steaks)
(Steaks?)
Steaks?
(They were hoping it'd be dim sum.)
- This is not okay. - Hongdae... Wait.
- It's Hong Kong. - Hong Kong...
It's not Hongdae.
Hong Kong is...
known for dim sum.
- Hong Kong is known for dim sum. - Like we said,
we adjusted the mission to the new country.
Then you should have...
changed it to dim sum.
There's even no roulette.
Hong Kong is known for its food.
There are so many good dishes in Hong Kong.
- Steaks... - There are.
We didn't change it because we thought it'd be possible.
(The staff concluded it'd be possible.)
(In addition to its fascinating night views,)
(Hong Kong has so many delicious dishes.)
(Along with all the other nice dishes,)
(Hong Kong is known for steaks too.)
Now, you'll pick the conditions for the local person.
- There are conditions? - There are conditions?
Four different professions are written on this roulette wheel.
After spinning the wheel, if the local person recommends...
something else other than steaks,
you have to eat that dish before trying again.
We know that.
It was the same in Okinawa.
Then let's pick the conditions for the local person.
It'll be the first person we'll meet, right?
- There are a lot. - "Taxi driver", "store clerk"...
"Hong Kong old lady".
- "Old lady over 70". - "Old lady over 70".
- "Someone called Wang". - "Someone called Wang".
- Last time, "store clerk"... - There wasn't "old lady" last time.
It has to be an old lady from Hong Kong.
- Are there many Wangs? - Yes.
- Here we go. - Let's go.
- Okay. - Let's go.
We have to spin it every time, right?
- Every time? - I hope it's "taxi driver".
(This choice might determine the result.)
Right. That'd be the easiest.
(A taxi driver would be the easiest to find.)
A taxi driver could tell us things like...
It's "taxi driver".
(A taxi driver is picked.)
- Jae Seok. - Let's ask...
- on our way. - Let's ask on our way.
Last time in Okinawa,
- we asked a taxi driver. - It was a taxi driver.
He recommended us a soba restaurant.
- That's right. - Okay.
Do you speak Chinese?
- Chinese? - Do you speak Chinese?
I tried the automatic translator.
The language spoken in Hong Kong...
doesn't work.
- We prepared this for you. - Really?
Here it is. Try it.
"Excuse me, but could you recommend us a restaurant and a dish?"
- Goodness. - Look at this.
- I'll definitely understand. - Since my childhood,
I grew up watching Hong Kong movies.
Me too.
I watched Chow Yun-fat.
- Chow Yun-fat. - Chow Yun-fat, Andy Lau,
- Andy Lau. - and Leslie Cheung.
I grew up watching them.
"A Moment of Romance".
They represent my high school years.
(Jae Seok doesn't know Cantonese.)
(These men made him fall in love with Cantonese.)
(He learned from these men.)
(Here's my Chinese.)
There's an intonation.
Listen carefully.
(Listen carefully.)
(Speaking Cantonese)
- What? - What did I say?
It sounds like Jeolla Province dialect.
(It's definitely Chinese.)
(However, it sounds like a Korean dialect.)
(He talks in an alien language.)
- Do you see it? - What do you mean?
- So Min, do you see this word? - There is.
- Do you see it? - How do we read it?
We should ask...
- the local. - We should learn.
- Let's go. - Let's go to the city...
- and take a taxi. - Okay.
- Okay. - We should take a taxi in the city.
I know the lyrics to "Love of the Past".
"Love of the Past"?
(He sings in Chinese.)
Seok Jin looks good singing it.
(As they reminisce the past,)
(they go to meet a taxi driver.)
(The sun sets on the street of Hong Kong.)
We start to see the night view.
I have the ballots.
Yes.
(So Min has the ballots.)
- Give them to me. - You shouldn't keep all of them.
How will you distribute them?
- I'll keep them. - I'll keep them...
since I'm the team leader. What if I distribute them...
by 2, 2, and 6?
By 2, 2, and 6?
- "2, 2, and 6"? - So Min.
- Who gets six? - Hey.
- Has it begun already? - Shall I poke you with my elbow?
- There she goes again. - When you smile,
do you want to have missing front teeth?
Who do you think should be penalized?
- Who do you think? - It's Si Young.
For me, it's Si Young.
She should be penalized.
- It should be Haha. - Why?
Haha pretends to be nice.
(He pretends to be nice.)
- I see. - Did you notice?
- I recognized it. - Suddenly,
- he changed his character. - He used to be a traitor.
It's not fun at all.
He said acting nice is his thing these days.
I mean, anyone can do that.
I've always been nice.
- No way. - At home.
(I've always been nice.)
- Hey. - You're not mean, but...
- I'm warmhearted like a heater. - What?
(What is he talking about?)
- I'm warmhearted like a heater. - No way.
- I am. - Seok Jin.
- You aren't cold, - I'm very warm.
but you aren't warm either.
In terms of water temperature,
you aren't as warm as 100°C.
(Seok Jin is lukewarm.)
- It's not the boiling temperature. - Right.
- He's about 60°C. - That's a perfect metaphor.
- She's good with metaphors. - That was good, So Min.
- He's about 60°C. - I hadn't thought of it.
- It's not quite there. - Warm enough for baby formula?
- Yes. - For baby food?
I imagine you as baby formula.
It's warm enough for baby formula.
Have you ever made baby formula?
I had baby formula since I was born.
- Really? - Yes.
Even after I stopped drinking milk as a child,
I liked baby formula so much that I ate spoonfuls of it.
- I liked eating that too. - It's really delicious.
Isn't it sweet?
I don't touch baby formula anymore.
- It can get really addictive. - Right.
(It's an addiction.)
That's why I don't touch baby formula anymore.
- Isn't it tasty? - Sometimes it's on the table.
I really want to eat it, but...
You must have...
- baby formula at home. - There's a lot of it.
That's right. It's really delicious.
- I want to scoop it with a spoon. - It's so tasty.
- It's delicious. - But I don't do it.
- It's so nutty. - I don't do it.
I want something similar to your baby formula.
Do you know peanut butter?
- I do. - When I take a spoon of it...
- and eat it... - It's so good.
Why don't you eat it then?
I'll gain weight. You know I watch what I eat.
"Gain weight"?
- You'll gain weight? - I watch what I eat.
Didn't you ask for two pieces of bread?
I eat in the early evening at this hour.
You don't even have a watch.
- He doesn't have a watch. - He doesn't.
I thought I did.
- Why did you check? - I know it by feeling.
- Don't be flustered. - I'm old enough...
- to know by feeling. - Don't be flustered.
Seok Jin's talk isn't interesting either.
It's just boring.
(Seok Jin's talk is lukewarm and boring.)
What did she say?
- It's always... - It's boring.
It should be exciting.
Right, what he says isn't interesting.
Sometimes it's surprisingly amazing.
That's so funny.
- Look at the night view. - It's beautiful.
- It's amazing. - It's beautiful.
It's a precious night view.
I want to take photos.
Let's distribute the ballots fairly.
The winner of Folding Finger Game gets a ballet.
- What? - Folding Finger Game.
The one who folds most fingers loses?
- Yes. - I see.
- You're eliminated if you fold all. - Right.
- Eliminated? - Yes.
- I'll start. - Okay.
Fold if you're a woman.
(His target is So Min.)
(Jae Seok is next.)
- That's so cheap. - No, it isn't.
- You're next. - Fold if you got a nose job.
(How about this? Fold if you got a nose job.)
(He reduced the size of his nose.)
(He folds his finger.)
Fold if your glasses have no lenses.
Two of you.
You're working as a team. Okay.
I'll target only one person.
- I'll target only one person. - Next is Seok Jin.
Fold if you're shooting a drama.
- Okay. - 2 to 1.
- I'm next. - Okay.
(So Min and Seok Jin folded 2 fingers each.)
Fold if your last name is Jee.
(He assists So Min.)
(Mr. Jee folds his finger.)
My goodness.
- Okay. - Fold if you use hair powder.
(Fold if you use hair powder.)
My goodness.
Hair powder.
Both of you are mocking me.
What are you doing?
- We're not. - Listen.
Come on.
Do you have to mock me?
This really hurts my pride.
Who suggested this game?
Next up is Seok Jin.
- Okay, okay. - Okay.
Fold if you have a bob cut.
- What? - Fold if you have a bob cut.
- A bob cut. - A bob cut?
- Goodness. - All right.
(Next is Jae Seok's turn.)
(He could either eliminate Seok Jin or make their scores tie.)
- Fold if you're my junior. - Get her.
Fold your finger.
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
(He gets mocked and loses ballots.)
Fold if you're my junior.
- You fold one. - I did.
(He has to fold his finger.)
(Junior Seok Jin folds his finger.)
Okay, fine.
- Just don't betray the team. - Okay.
Let's do well today, Seok Jin.
- Today... - In one go.
If we succeed in one go...
- Please send us home. - We can go home.
If you clear the mission, you can go home today.
- Can we go home? - Really?
Can we have free time?
There are early morning flights from Hong Kong.
- There are until 3am. - Really?
I promise you that if you clear the mission today,
you can take the early morning flight home.
- Okay. - Let's try.
- Seriously. - Or we can have fun today...
- and go back tomorrow. - Let's have fun.
We can have free time.
- Let's have fun. - We will without cameras.
- Without cameras. - Without cameras.
Here we are. We arrived.
(They arrive in the city at 6:30pm.)
Where are we?
Gosh, I'm hungry.
- I can enjoy any food. - Me too.
(They must meet a taxi driver.)
Please give us a recommendation.
- There's a taxi. - No.
It's already taken.
Is this where we catch a taxi?
All the taxis are taken.
Let's wait here.
- There's an empty taxi in the back. - Where?
(She finds one.)
There's an empty one here.
- Where? - Here.
(They find an empty taxi.)
Taxi.
(They finally catch a taxi.)
(They need a recommendation from the taxi driver.)
We have to ask carefully.
- Excuse me. - Hi.
- You ask. - Excuse me.
Ask and see if he understands you.
(He asks him to recommend them a dish.)
- Show it to him. - I'll read it out loud instead.
Okay.
(Hesitating)
(I...)
(He speaks Cantonese.)
(What are you reading?)
(Asking a question is already difficult.)
- I don't think he understands. - He doesn't?
- Choose a restaurant. - Please?
- Tell me. - Menu.
- Menu. - Menu.
- Menu. - Yes.
(He finally understands.)
(If he recommends steak, they succeed the first mission.)
(What will the driver say?)
- Menu. - Menu.
- Menu. - Yes.
(He finally understands.)
(If he recommends steak, they succeed the first mission.)
(What will the driver say?)
- Wantanmien. - Yes.
The noodle.
(Wantanmien is noodles.)
Okay. Noodles again?
- Noodles. - Does this continue?
Okay, wantanmien.
- Wantanmien. - Noodles.
- Okay. Go. - Okay.
Please.
- I didn't mishear that, right? - This is driving me nuts.
- He said "noodles". - Noodles.
It's not like we told him to say that. Noodles again?
Does the noodles party continue...
in Hong Kong?
(They're off to a gloomy start. Will they be okay?)
- Gangwon Province seems to have... - Right?
- cold air. - I can't sleep.
Let's go!
(They arrived at the ranch.)
(They have another purpose besides the mission.)
This is D-Day.
- Protect Kwang Soo's pride! - But...
- This is the main event. - You can't do that.
(Will the owner recognize Kwang Soo?)
(If he takes the producer as him, Haha and Si Young take his ballots.)
Joo Yong, come here. Switch your clothes.
- But... - Good.
(If he takes the producer as him, Haha and Si Young take his ballots.)
Don't do anything that makes you stand out.
- I can't allow myself to do that. - Right.
That's so cheap.
My pouch...
Why would you hold on to it?
- This... - That makes you stand out.
- Goodness. - No way.
I'm not trying to stand out.
(Gosh, he saw that.)
If the owner thinks he's Kwang Soo,
should we just go along with it?
(If they think he's Kwang Soo, should we just go along with it?)
(Will Kwang Soo's part be edited out automatically?)
(That's going too far.)
It'll be funny if they mention you at the end.
Because...
- they might be... - I'll wait until they recognize me.
embarrassed.
We'll give you 10 minutes.
- Let's not laugh. - Okay.
(He's somewhat bitter.)
Zip it.
Put it in your ear.
(They're thorough only at times like these.)
(Sighing)
That's good.
(He turns into a staff member.)
Kwang Soo.
- Do you want my mic? - No, it's okay.
(Kwang Soo and Producer Lee Joo Yong switch.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
We have no time. The sun is setting.
(They leave to meet the owner.)
(He's determined and serious.)
Kwang Soo, join the staff.
Hold the camera next to the audio person.
Why are we doing... Okay, fine.
Just do it.
Should we practice?
- Like sheep, - We, who spare nothing to give,
- are the best! - are the best!
(They show great teamwork.)
They might recognize me right away.
This might end faster than expected.
(Will Kwang Soo keep both his pride and his ballots?)
He looks so cool.
Sir.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Haha. - Nice to meet you.
(Mr. Kang owns a ranch in Wangsan, Gangwon Province.)
It's very nice to meet you.
There's a beautiful lady as well.
- Hello. - Hello.
(The fake Kwang Soo approaches Mr. Kang.)
- Are you Lee Si Young? - Yes.
(He recognizes Haha and Si Young.)
- Lee Si Young. Nice to meet you. - It's Lee Si Young.
I'm Lee Kwang Soo. You know me, right?
- You're short. - I...
(Mr. Kang is suspicious. Will Kwang Soo win?)
I'm standing on the bottom.
Oh, you're tall.
Nice to meet you.
(He doesn't question it.)
It's nice meeting you.
(We're nice to meet you too!)
(Mr. Kang, it's nice to meet you.)
(They celebrate overcoming the 1st hurdle.)
We need to get 4L of milk.
I'll let you get 5L.
- Really? - Thank you.
- Are the sheep in good health? - Yes, they're good.
(The sheep are waiting to be milked.)
All right.
Do you have a question, Kwang Soo?
Is it difficult?
(He carefully asks a question.)
(Mr. Kang may notice something odd once Producer Lee starts talking.)
(Staring)
No, you just milk them.
- There's nothing hard about it. - I'll try my best.
You haven't done it, so it might look hard.
(You're not looking here. Kwang Soo is actually here.)
- Kwang Soo... - Kwang Soo was a little worried.
I'll take a picture for you and Kwang Soo.
Si Young can join as well.
In 1, 2, 3.
That's good. I'll be in it this time.
In 1,
- 2... - I'll take it for you.
Sure, please take it for us.
I think our staff member is taller.
- Right? - In 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo stands across from Mr. Kang. Will he know?)
(Let's go, Running Man!)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Clicking)
Can you adjust the mic?
Are you a staff member?
(Are you a staff member?)
You look like a celebrity.
(This staff member looks like a celebrity.)
He's tall, right?
You're working hard.
I think his mic needs to be adjusted.
(Lee Kwang Soo, a tall staff member who looks like a celebrity)
(He's working very hard.)
We should get going now.
Oh, dear.
- It's not hard at all. - Thank you.
Pat them.
They're very sensitive.
Herbivores are very sensitive.
You have to pat them with soft hands.
They know when you're being rough.
I see.
I get scared easily.
(This mission makes me reflect on my life.)
(He won the Top Excellence award in 2016 Entertainment Awards.)
(What if he's Asian Prince in other countries?)
(To Mr. Kang, he's just...)
We have to get going.
- Mr. Kang, let's go! - Let's go!
(This is a party.)
10 minutes have passed.
For 10 minutes, he took Producer Lee as Kwang Soo,
so Kwang Soo's ballots all go to Haha and Si Young.
(He loses both his pride and ballots.)
Come here, Kwang Soo.
This is Kwang Soo.
(He's confused.)
- This is our member Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
(I see...)
This is our producer.
- Really? - He's a producer.
It's true.
Take this off.
(You have to switch your jackets again.)
He's not sure yet.
Why are you taking your jackets off?
(Why is the staff member taking his jacket off?)
So he...
He's Lee Kwang Soo.
I have to wear my own jacket.
I'm going to wear my jacket.
Right?
(He pretends like he knew.)
You're making me feel even worse, sir.
We played a fun game.
Thank you, sir.
Right?
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
- Give me 13 ballots. - Who is he then?
He's a producer.
- Right? I didn't recognize him. - Yes.
Sit in the front, Si Young.
(They go to the ranch before the sun sets.)
- You can sit on top of the tire. - Okay.
You can face the back and sit on it.
You're tall.
- Yes, it's okay. - It'll be a long journey.
It'll be a difficult journey.
(What does he mean by that?)
("It'll be a difficult journey.")
"It'll be a long journey."
(What does he want to warn them about?)
Are you all right?
(Mr. Kang starts the car in silence.)
I'll go up slowly, okay?
- Okay. - Yes.
(He starts driving on a steep mountain path.)
This feels like an adventure.
He's driving across a creek.
I know.
I've never done this before.
Are you all right?
(Where are we going?)
Oh, no.
(It's a rough unpaved path across a creek.)
At night, you can get trapped.
You should be careful when driving.
I always go back and forth.
Still.
(They start seeing something at the end of the path.)
There they are.
(There they are.)
- Are they? - The white ones.
I see them.
Me too.
(Exclaiming)
They're beautiful.
(It's a rough path to get here, but the ranch is in a safe area.)
The dog is so cute too.
They're bigger than I expected.
This is what I expected goats would look like.
I know.
You'll now start milking the sheep.
(It's time to get 4L of milk.)
The big bottles you see on the side add up to 4L.
The mission is complete once you fill up four of those.
Okay.
- Let's do this! - Okay.
Let's do it before the sun sets.
- They're not moving too much. - Hurry.
(They must get all 4L while the sheep are active.)
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
- You can do it. - We can do it.
You should meet the sheep first.
- Give them some pine needles. - Can I have some?
Hello, guys.
Would you like some?
They're big.
They like it.
There you go. They're eating it.
She's so cute.
(The sheep are not scared. They won't have a problem.)
(Chewing)
(Running away)
Baby.
Baby?
He's so fast.
If they go up even more, they might not come back down.
(However, the other sheep are following him too.)
Eat this.
Hello. Oh, dear.
Are they running away?
I'm not sure.
- There are many people. - Yes.
There are too many people all of a sudden.
(What's going on?)
Can you get them back, Mr. Kang?
They'll come back once we leave.
(They're running away from the guests.)
They will.
- They must be scared. - Come here, guys.
They'll move farther away if we try to move closer.
Once we go down and ring the bell, they come down.
There are too many people suddenly.
- Hey. - This...
I have a bad feeling.
(We'll milk you and leave right away.)
(The sheep have hidden. They may not even get to try.)
(He rings a bell to call the sheep.)
(Will the sheep come back down?)
- Daddy rang the bell. - They're responding.
They're coming down.
(As soon as they hear the bell, they come down.)
This is fascinating.
Shouldn't we get away? Right?
(Let's go down for now.)
- They're coming so fast. - This is fascinating.
Go. Let's get away first.
(Are the guests gone?)
(The sheep have to come inside now.)
- This is fascinating. - Come inside, Kwang Soo.
How did they know?
This is...
(It's the bell. Get together!)
Can you close the door?
Come here, guys.
(They start hesitating.)
- They are... - Go behind and herd them.
Come here.
Come inside.
We have to herd them before they get out.
- No way. - Herd them and get them in.
(A staff member herds them, but they get out!)
What do we do, Mr. Kang?
(What's wrong? Where are they going again?)
Come here. Eat this.
- What do we do? - Let's go inside.
What do we do?
We need a person to herd them. Should we do it?
Should we go out and do it?
- Should we? - We have to go around.
- Go this way. - Let's herd them.
Guys, let's go.
- Let's go this way. - Go that way.
Let's go.
- Let's go this way, guys. - Come here.
Let's go to your daddy.
- Let's go to him. - Go inside.
No, please! Please.
(They run away to the mountains!)
(This is an emergency situation.)
That's not the right way.
(They escape for the 2nd time.)
What now?
(They're going even farther now!)
We have to get the cameras out...
and try again.
(They're in trouble. Can they get 4L of milk?)
(In Hong Kong, the members are in a taxi.)
He said "noodles".
I think the whole world knows that you like noodles.
- You like noodles. - I do love noodles.
They know.
- I think... - Here.
- Here? - Here?
(They must eat the recommended dish first.)
- Here? - Yellow...
- Yellow. - Yellow. Thank you.
I was shocked.
Noodles again.
Here.
It looks really good.
- It does look good. - It looks really good.
- Right? - Excuse me.
Wantanmien?
(Wantanmien is Cantonese-style noodles with shrimp and pork.)
- Wantanmien? - Yes.
There's meat too.
(Next, come.)
Our staff members have to come.
(Kwon Ryeol is the only staff here.)
- Our staff has to come. - Right.
Excuse me.
(The staff got lost while following the taxi.)
Where is the staff?
(This is a real situation.)
- Should we get seats first? - Right? I think that's better.
- I can film everybody. - Sure.
- Sure. - We have no time.
Okay.
Excuse me. Three.
(They can't keep waiting, so they enter the restaurant first.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It looks good.
I wonder how it tastes.
This is our first meal in Hong Kong.
(How will it taste?)
Wantanmien.
(The noodles are finally here.)
- Thank you. - Wantanmien.
(The noodles are firm.)
- There are dumplings inside. - Let's try it.
(He tries the soup first.)
It tastes like shrimp, right?
- It does. - It tastes like shrimp.
There's a strong scent of shrimps.
It tastes like shrimp.
The soup tastes like shrimp.
What do you like better?
This is seafood.
Let me try the sauce.
What do you like better?
(The two men try the soup first.)
It's sour.
(She inhales the noodles.)
(This is the textbook way of eating noodles.)
- It's chewy. - Look.
- Look. - These are dried noodles.
- Right. - They're kind of dry.
- How is it? - Look.
(Jae Seok goes after the dumpling.)
How is the dumpling?
- Does it taste like shrimp? - Yes.
Does it?
The shrimp...
(There's a whole shrimp inside.)
There's a whole shrimp.
It...
- tastes good. - The texture is amazing.
It's a whole shrimp, right?
I didn't know we were going to have noodles first.
Me neither. I had no idea.
(This was the same in Okinawa.)
This is our first menu.
It won't be noodles again, right?
- No way. - Not again.
It won't be noodles again.
It can't be twice.
This is good.
You have to drink the soup.
Seok Jin really likes it.
That was really good.
That was good.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The staff joined late.)
- You'll vote again. - Okay.
Turn the roulette.
Here we go again.
Steak please.
(He hopes it'll be steak this time.)
(The roulette is spinning!)
(Who will recommend the menu this time?)
We can't have noodles again.
(A Hong Kong grandma over the age of 70!)
- "A Hong Kong grandma over 70?" - A Hong Kong grandma.
I don't think there'll be anybody over 70 on the streets.
(They're helpless.)
Over 70...
It has to be somebody local.
We have to ask for their age.
- A local? - Yes, a local.
- A grandma, right? - There isn't anybody in downtown.
- They were in the restaurant. - In the restaurant?
We have to look.
This...
We're in trouble.
We're in trouble today.
Where do we find a grandma over 70?
There are some grandpas.
- What about grandmas? - I don't see any.
Let's take a look.
(Where are the grandmas?)
There are no grandmas over 70.
(Are there grandmas?)
(It's late, so the streets are quiet.)
Where do we find a grandma over 70?
- What do we do? - This is too...
Oh, gosh.
We're in a foreign country...
There's a grandma.
(There's a grandma.)
(They finally find a Hong Kong grandma!)
- Hello. - Excuse me, but how old are you?
(They finally meet one.)
(Is she the person they were looking for?)
- She's 60. - 60.
(Oh, dear.)
- That was close. - She looked young.
She did.
(Thank you for answering.)
We're in trouble.
We have no time.
Seniors are not outside.
(It's empty.)
There are some grandpas.
- What do we do? - There are no people.
Why did you pick that one?
Why did you pick a grandma in her 70s?
- Jae Seok. - Grandmas in their 70s...
This is starting again.
- Hey. - It's late,
and you're getting mad.
Why did you pick that?
This is starting again.
- I should have spun it. - Yes, you should have.
There are no grandmas out right now.
There are some grandpas.
Why did you pick that?
You could have picked a convenience store.
- This is driving me nuts. - Oh, gosh.
Gosh.
We're in trouble. There's nobody.
We had to find a Japanese grandma last time too.
(Hold on!)
- Is she in her 70s? - I don't think so.
(They see somebody in passing.)
(Is she the person they were looking for?)
Excuse me.
(They start talking to her carefully.)
Is English okay?
Excuse me.
How old are you?
- Me? - Yes.
(Me?)
- 78. - 78?
(She's 78.)
(They finally found her!)
- She looks so young. - Really?
(Is she really that age?)
- You look 60. - Thank you.
(They found a person over 70.)
(It's time to ask for a recommendation.)
(Then can we...)
- Where... - Philippines.
- Philippines? - I see.
Philippines.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Bye.
(She's not a local, so it doesn't count.)
Can't we ask a Filipino?
It has to be a Hong Kong grandma.
We found her.
- She looked so young. - I agree.
I was shocked. I thought we found her.
Where are we now?
I don't think there will be grandmas here.
What do we do?
- We're in trouble. - Here.
- There are grandpas. - There's a grandma.
What?
- Her? - Can we ask?
(Is she the person they were looking for?)
Can we ask?
Excuse me.
(The local guide explains the situation and asks for her age.)
- She's young. - She might be.
- 73. - 73.
(They finally found a Hong Kong grandma over 70.)
(It's for real this time!)
73?
Can we...
Can we ask you a question?
(She's a local, so they can ask for a recommendation.)
(Well...)
("Please recommend a menu" in Cantonese)
(If she recommends steak, the mission is complete.)
We can't have noodles again.
Steak please. Steak.
(What will the grandma recommend?)
- Wantanmien. - Wantanmien?
Chaomien.
(What did she just say?)
There's wantanmien and fried noodles.
(The local guide translates.)
(Sorry?)
(Noodles? What noodles?)
- Fried noodles? - What did she say?
Fried noodles?
(When they had it the first time, they thought it wasn't possible.)
(Not again.)
(They were sure.)
(There's nothing impossible.)
(It got them.)
Chaomien?
(He confirms.)
- Yes. - Chaomien?
- Delicious? - Yes.
Very cheap.
- Very cheap? - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(She recommends wantanmien and chaomien highly.)
Is Hong Kong known for noodles?
- No. - It's dim sum.
- It's dim sum. - It is, right?
I'm not even hoping for steak. It's dim sum.
It's the yellow sign.
Is this it?
I think this is it.
- They ran out of ingredients. - What a relief.
(What? They ran out of ingredients?)
This is great. This worked out.
- Gosh, I'm relieved. - Goodness.
- This is great. - We should spin it one more time.
- Right? We... - We have no choice.
Hey, didn't he just say...
he can serve you food?
- Great. We have no choice. - Hey, didn't he just say...
(He is saying something.)
He can serve us?
- He does have noodles there. - Those are egg noodles.
- It's a paradise for noodles. - Hold on a second.
(No way. Could it be possible...)
Come in, come in.
(Bad inklings always come true.)
He has food?
(He said he was out of food.)
- Come in, come in. - He has food?
Wait, he just said he couldn't serve us.
- He said no earlier. - He can serve you food now.
He ran out of ingredients.
He said he has enough for a bowl. Try his food.
- Thank you. - What noodles are we eating?
- It's over there. - Hello.
(They're our last customers.)
I can eat two bowls of noodles.
- But if we get the noodles again, - Unbelievable.
I'll feel sick.
This is... What's going on? Look how this is...
turning out to be. Are we having noodles again?
Is this Part Two of Along with the Noodles?
(Is this Part 2 of Along with the Noodles?)
(The deceased will be born again when they eat the steak.)
(Since you have awful karma, you'll be punished to eat noodles.)
(The curse of the King of Noodles ever since the Okinawa trip)
(They had noodles after noodles.)
(And they had some more noodles.)
(Into the Underworld of Noodles that doesn't get untangled)
("Part 1 of Along with the Noodles in Okinawa")
("Part 2 of Along with the Noodles in Hong Kong")
- Wantanmien. - Is this "Along with the Noodles"?
- The old lady earlier... - Okay.
recommended either wantanmien or stir-fried noodles.
- The stir-fried noodles... - They only serve wantanmien here.
So we'll eat that.
- We already had one. - We just had the same dish.
- We just had one there. - All right.
You want us to eat two bowls of that?
Listen. The old lady...
- We already had 1 bowl. - 2 bowls?
I gave up on the steak, but they won't recommend dim sum.
You know what? I feel as if the nightmare in Okinawa...
is coming back to me, but with wantanmien this time.
- Here's my opinion. - No way.
Do you think the staff could have "logged" this?
- This is weird. - It's not "logged".
- It's "rigged". - "Rigged".
(The second bowl confuses her.)
The staff "logged" it.
(This incident questions her vocabulary.)
- You didn't study in school, right? - You really surprised me.
It's not that.
I think it's because I'm next to Seok Jin.
- That can't be right. - Right now...
You're not as educated as I thought you'd be.
- You didn't study, did you? - Seriously. I was so shocked.
- The staff "logged" this? - Seriously.
- You're not that knowledgeable. - Right.
- I can't think straight. - Here's my opinion.
I'm not sure if we'll get it or not.
We must choose a taxi driver.
- We must leave this neighborhood. - We must leave here.
- Do you know what I mean? - You're right.
- In my opinion, - This place only has noodles.
- this is the wantanmien street. - Every restaurant sells wantanmien.
We didn't know, but this street is full of wantanmien restaurants.
- I agree. I see it everywhere. - That's why we must leave here.
There are too many wantanmien restaurants.
They'll recommend it if we ask people here.
- That's right. - That will certainly happen.
(Clueless of their plan, he's making a delicious bowl of wantanmien.)
(A mix of shrimp wontons, chewy noodles, and rich broth)
- Here it comes. - It's coming.
- It's here. - Wantanmien.
(Here are our last two bowls of wantanmien.)
- The portion is a lot. - Thank you.
- Thank you. It's the same. - It's exactly the same.
(This soup and the previous soup are the same.)
They put the same wontons here.
It's identical.
(Feeling dizzy)
Since we're here,
we'll compare this one to the previous one.
(He's eating wantanmien again?)
- I'll compare to the first one. - This is...
(- This is his second bowl. - How does the second one taste?)
(Where is that restaurant?)
What is this? This is just like that time in Okinawa.
(How does the second wonton soup taste?)
How does the broth taste?
(- Seok Jin is there too! - He's eating that again?)
(- Is it good? - Hey, So Min is there too!)
(Thinking back...)
It tastes similar.
(It's the same.)
It's similar to the one before. I'm serious.
(Try it.)
The first one had a strong aroma of the shrimps.
- This one has a weaker aroma. - You're right.
This is milder.
- It tastes like shrimps too. - It tastes just the same.
So Min.
- You'd better eat noodles. Or else. - It tastes just the same.
It tastes just like shrimps too. It has the same flavor.
- This... - I guess people in Hong Kong...
must really like wantanmien.
Let me try the wonton in the soup.
- It's good. - This is good.
- This is good. Isn't it good? - Yes, this is so springy.
(The previous one was delicious.)
(And this restaurant's wantanmien is great too.)
Their shrimp wontons are bigger.
But is there kimchi?
(Can you give us some side dishes?)
- Is there sauce? - Do they...
Hi. Excuse me.
- It's very delicious. - Thank you.
Do people from Hong Kong like noodles?
- Do they like noodles? - Yes.
Do a lot of people from Hong Kong like noodles?
Yes, they like noodles very much.
They just like noodles.
(That must be it, right?)
Excuse me. Excuse me.
(They ask her their 2nd question.)
Do you like steak?
- Steak? - Steak?
- Do you like it? - Beef?
- Do you like it? - Yes, I like it.
I like both steak and noodles.
Beef. I see.
(She likes both steak and noodles.)
- You know what? - We still have a shot.
- What if you get noodles again? - Let's bring it in.
- Let's do this. - 1, 2, 3.
Even if we don't get a steak...
- Let's at least get dim sum. - Something else like dim sum.
- We should get dim sum... - Dim sum or...
- Or bubble tea for desserts. - Desserts.
- That sounds good. - Yes. Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- We can do this. - We can do this.
(They're fine as long as it's not noodles. Good luck!)
- We won't get noodles again. - Right.
- Let's go. - Let's spin and go.
- Let me spin it. - We have to get out of this area.
- I want a taxi driver. - We should get a taxi driver.
(Getting a taxi driver is the best to get out of there.)
- I'll spin it. - All right.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
Get the taxi driver. The taxi driver.
(Please let it be the taxi driver.)
Please be the taxi driver.
(Amazing! They get the taxi driver.)
- Bravo! Bravo. - We got it. It's the taxi driver.
- We did it. - We're good at spinning this.
(They must get on the taxi, move far, and get a recommendation.)
They all recommend...
- Let's at least get something good. - Let's get out of here.
(After finishing two bowls of wantanmien...)
Gosh, noodles.
I want to stop eating noodles.
- Let's go. - I'm dizzy after having two bowls.
- If we get noodles again... - We would be in pure torment.
(Can they avoid the underworld of noodles?)
Okay.
Hi.
(They stop a taxi, their savior.)
- Excuse me. - You got the taxi.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
My gosh.
Okay, let's get out of here.
- We should get out of here. - Out of the wonton street.
Okay.
(Step 1: Leave the wonton street.)
We should leave here for now.
- Let's go. - We should just leave here for now?
- Let's just go. - What does that even mean?
Yes, just go. Go.
Please drive away.
We have to leave this neighborhood.
Let's get out of here.
(They escape from the wonton street.)
- Let's go. - Not to come back here,
please go as far as you can.
- Just go, please. - As far as we can go.
- Just go. - "Just go"?
- What are you saying? - Just go.
I'm asking him to just drive.
(After they escape the alley...)
So Min, we should talk to him now.
Please.
(Let me see.)
Anywhere. Pick any dish.
- Pick the dish you like. - Yes.
Anywhere. Any dish.
Please pick the best dish.
(Hold on.)
It's your choice.
- Just one dish. - We were on this road earlier.
It won't be a problem.
Please pick the best dish you like.
- Hey, he shouldn't go this way. - Wait.
- No, no. Wait. - Hold on.
- Jae Seok, wait. - Hold on a second.
- Look at the map. - A good dish.
- Hey, he shouldn't go this way. - Wait.
Hold on.
- Jae Seok, wait. - Hold on a second.
Where are we going? Hold on.
- We were just here. - Just go.
Hey, we were just here a while ago. Hey, we were here earlier.
- Hey, isn't it the same street? - It's the same street.
Hey, it's the same street.
(I'll recommend this restaurant.)
- What? - Okay. Here.
- Here? - We were just there.
(He recommends the same wantanmien restaurant.)
(They barely managed to get out by asking him to just drive.)
(They came back after going around.)
- Okay. Thank you. - It's the same restaurant.
- Let's get off. Get off! - Hey, this is...
They ran out of food.
Hold on. It's the same restaurant.
Here? Here?
- Here? - Here?
Here?
I can't believe this.
(I get that this restaurant is great, but...)
- I mean... - Hold on.
- Wait. - Should I get off?
- Wait, this is... - Wait.
(Please stop telling us how great this restaurant is.)
- I can't believe this. - Jae Seok.
- We should've gone farther. - How is this possible?
- He said the restaurant was here. - Listen.
- I think there's an evil spirit. - This is crazy.
- How can it happen again? - This is like the Mobius strip.
(Is this Mobius strip continuing from Okinawa?)
(They went to the same restaurant twice even in Okinawa.)
How could we come back here?
(Just like the trip in Okinawa,)
(it happens again in Hong Kong.)
(The curse of the noodles repeats exactly the same.)
It's the same restaurant.
(Why can't we get out of this neighborhood?)
(They tried to get out, but their effort was futile.)
(They're locked in the wonton street, the curse of noodles.)
(What will happen to Team Hong Kong who returns to the same place?)
(They thought things would be different at another area.)
(We must get out of this area now.)
(However,)
(they face another confusion at a new place.)
(The swamp in Hong Kong hasn't ended.)
(Will they be able to come back safely?)
(You're working. Where are you going?)
(No one can escape this.)
(Everything will end if they gather a total of 100 people.)
Were you talking about me?
(Suspicious movements are spotted all over the place.)
(Will they be able to accomplish their mission?)
(Their struggle with Mother Nature has finally begun in full-force.)
(Team Si Young must complete their mission in the wild.)
(The last mission awaits them.)
(The war of ballots unfolds on the boat.)
(What has happened on their boat?)
What is this?
(Year End Special, Part Two of Once Again Even If You Hate It)