(9th summer on Running Man)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
We're in Iksan, North Jeolla Province.
- Iksan. - The weather is great.
This is my sister-in-law's hometown.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Wait, I've never met your sister-in-law.
- Is this her hometown? - I have a sister-in-law.
- It's my friend's hometown. - Really?
It's home for many people.
- It's my distant cousin's hometown. - Everyone knows someone.
- My sister-in-law's hometown. - Since it's her hometown,
- make an acrostic poem with Iksan. - Okay.
- Come on. - Okay.
- That's out of the blue. - Seok Jin is getting prepared.
- Am I next? - Really?
- Ik. - All right, Ik.
- "It's getting ripe." - That's good.
- San. - "I must climb up a mountain."
(It's getting ripe. I must climb up a mountain.)
That's good. Good shot.
- Good shot. - Okay.
- Good shot. - You started it in 10 seconds.
- He's so sly. - What do you mean?
- It wasn't even good. - Good shot.
- Gosh, I saw someone... - He thinks it was.
making a bitter smile. It was So Min.
- Look at her facial expression. - I already know.
I was shaking Se Chan's hand, but I was looking at her.
- She gave him a look. - You should be careful.
- Did she make you upset? - I don't like her.
- By the way, Seok Jin has... - I feel a lot of pressure.
- a friend in Iksan. - Is that so?
- You started as a comedian. - Don't do that.
- Right. - How can I make one with Iksan?
What can I make a poem with Iksan?
Yes, you're less experienced than me.
- I can't think of any. - Be quiet.
- Be quiet, everyone. - I can't think of any.
- Be careful not to fall. - Get ready to laugh.
Ik.
(An experienced comedian shows off his talent.)
"I'm used to this atmosphere."
(I'm used to this atmosphere.)
(Impressed)
San.
(Here comes the last line.)
- San. - "I need a drink of Cornus fruit."
(I need a drink of Cornus fruit.)
(Disappointed)
Isn't it predictable?
- What do you mean? - Listen.
How is it different from "climbing up a mountain"?
- You give it a try then. - Goodness.
- Say "Ik". - Ik.
- "Excuse me." - That's good.
(That sounds original.)
San.
(Jae Seok shows off his talent to Seok Jin.)
"Sansei, excuse me."
(We assume that he meant "teacher".)
- "Sansei", "dojo". - You're speaking Japanese.
- Dojo. - "Dojo"?
- You can't speak Japanese. - Stop it.
Today, we came to a historic site from Baekje.
It was selected by UNESCO.
Look at that.
- This is great. - It's a historic site.
- Mireuksa Temple Site. - Mireuksa Temple Site.
It's National Treasure Number 11, Mireuksa Temple.
It's a World Heritage site selected by UNESCO.
- Really? - I've never seen it before.
When I mentioned Mireuksa Temple, this is what Se Chan said.
- He's interested a lot in history. - Does he know about the temple?
When I said that I'm happy to visit Mireuksa Temple,
he said, "This is where Gung Ye used to live."
(This is where Gung Ye used to live.)
I recognized it from the word "mireuk".
- I wondered where we were. - "I know how to read people."
- I mistook it as Gung Ye's place. - "I'm Mireuk."
He thought it was where Gung Ye lived.
- Why did you bring it up? - Why not?
- Why did you say that? - It's embarrassing.
He's the most ignorant among us.
- Right. - You're the most ignorant.
We invited four guests who will be with you...
- here today. - Really?
Look, the color is pink.
- It's a heart. - Who will be today's guests?
- What? - What's going on? Look.
What's that?
(Who's the first special guest?)
- It's Son Dam Bi. - Dam Bi.
- It's Dam Bi. - Who is it?
- It's Son Dam Bi. - Son Dam Bi?
- It's really Dam Bi. - Is it Dam Bi?
- Dam Bi is here. - I can't believe it.
- Hello. - She pretends to be bubbly.
- Dam Bi. - She's pretty.
- Hello. - Dam Bi.
- Hello. - I saw you at Nam Mountain.
- That was the second episode. - Right.
- Long time no see. - Hello.
- She's still pretty. - As Kwang Soo mentioned,
Dam Bi looked expressionless when she was waiting.
But when she got out of the tent...
She pretended to be all bubbly.
- It looked mechanical. - Seriously.
It's been so long since I saw someone spin like this.
- Goodness. - She's been on TV for 10 years now.
- Yes, it's been over a decade. - We filmed a movie together.
- Dam Bi... - They filmed a movie together.
- filmed a movie with Kwang Soo. - My gosh.
- Yes, I did. - "The Accidental Detective 2"?
- We also filmed "Rose of Betrayal". - That's right.
- Our two movies will be out. - They'll be out in June and August.
- Really? - I see.
Do you play his love interest?
No way.
(She's appalled.)
(You didn't have to say it like that.)
- I shouldn't have said that. - Was that necessary?
- Did you not see her? - She's offended.
We have to sympathize if they're a couple in the film.
- But we can't sympathize at all. - Let me just put it simply.
- You're just friends, right? - I see.
- He's just an acquaintance. - Yes.
I'm just a passer-by.
(He has given up.)
- That's the perfect role. - Now, I get it, Kwang Soo.
- Right. - He just passes by.
She was greatly loved with her song, "Saturday Night".
- That's right. - She's here on a Sunday night now.
- This is great. - Thank you.
- Saturday night - Saturday night
I'm sorry, but you don't have a Saturday show now.
(I'm sorry, but you don't have a Saturday show now.)
- Hey. - You keep mentioning Saturday.
That won't last forever though.
- But you don't have work. - Right.
- Goodness. - You should give...
- other people a chance. - We won't be on a break forever.
- Haha is lowering his head. - My goodness.
Gosh, Haha. He still hasn't gotten over the shock.
(He does a sudden gesture.)
(Choking up)
You were doing a palm blast, right?
- Wave motion fist. - Wave motion fist.
(They does their Saturday wave motion fist all they want.)
(You haven't forgotten about us, right?)
- That's a palm blast, right? - It's a wave motion fist now.
- Should I leave my Thursdays open? - What?
- Wave motion fist. - Wave motion fist.
- You guys are hilarious. - All right.
By the way, compared to that time eight years ago,
she started mumbling more than before.
- Really. - I'm getting old.
- But I prefer this. - Is that so?
She keeps saying, "That's ridiculous. Look at him."
- It's been eight years. - Before, she'd be quiet.
- She didn't do much. - I followed my agency's advice.
She didn't even talk much when I asked her questions.
And the sound of her laugh changed.
She chuckles like a man.
(The sound of her laugh changed. She chuckles like a man.)
- A man? Really, Seok Jin? - See? Did you hear that?
- It sounds like that a bit. - A man.
- It's very... - I'm a single woman. How could you?
- We like it. - I just meant that we liked that.
You seem very easy-to-earth.
I'm sorry,
- what does, "easy-to-earth" mean? - What?
- Easy-to-earth. - Did you mean, "down-to-earth"?
- Down-to-earth. - She's down-to-earth and easygoing.
Down-to-earth and easygoing.
- I jumbled up two expressions. - I like that.
Because we were so happy to see Dam Bi,
- we ended up interviewing her. - Right.
- We'll do it after everyone is out. - When everyone is introduced? Okay.
- It's been a while. - I'm looking forward to today.
Dam Bi started us off. How high should my expectations be?
My goodness.
- The thing about Seok Jin is... - This is crazy.
that he never says things with an ounce of sincerity.
- But I should say these things. - Do you think he meant it?
- I thought he was Alpha Go. - I'm flattering the guest.
- "Dam Bi started us off." - I should, shouldn't I?
- It feels nice, doesn't it? Right? - "I'm looking forward to today."
I'm trying to flatter the guest at the age of 50.
- You're not 50. You're 54. - Be quiet. It's 53!
- Are you 53 years old? - Yes.
They're unstoppable.
- We'll move onto the next guest. - Okay.
- The next guest. - Here's the next guest.
(The second guest has a cute silhouette.)
Who is it?
(Who is the second guest that brings out their sincere reactions?)
It's Seo Eun Su.
(Actress Seo Eun Su, the symbol of innocence and cuteness)
(She appeared in "My Golden Life" and "Dr. Romantic".)
(This popular actress has been in many recent hit-dramas.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Gosh, hello.
- Nice to meet you. Come this way. - Hello.
Eun Su.
- Goodness. - My gosh.
- Seriously. - You were in "My Golden Life".
- That's right. - Kwang Soo.
- He knew the exact title. - That's right.
- He watches every drama. - I do.
Haha asked...
if she played a golden role in "My Golden Life".
Stay out of it.
- She had the "golden" role. - Don't get involved.
This is Eun Su's first variety show.
People usually can't sleep the night before their first show.
- I... I couldn't sleep. - How long did you sleep?
- I... I slept for 2 hours. - 2 hours.
- She kept saying she was nervous. - I think she's really nervous.
- I'm so sweaty. - Don't worry.
- She's one of the youngest members. - That's right. She is.
- Eun Su is nervous about the show. - Right.
- Give her helpful advice. - Talk to her.
- Kwang Soo, say something. - Okay.
Just have fun, trust us, and follow our lead.
- You just focus on doing your job. - She should trust you?
Goodness.
You're so frustrating. This is really frustrating.
You're very tall.
(She carefully asks a question.)
Kwang Soo? He's really tall.
She's not your love interest. Don't take it the wrong way.
(Will I have a love interest today?)
- Tell me now. What will you do? - Don't get the wrong idea.
- So... - Do you not like me?
He'll get the wrong idea. Don't say that. He'll misunderstand.
- It will really happen. - It will happen.
- Don't give him your number. - Dam Bi.
Dam Bi, what do you think? Do you think he has a shot?
Not even close.
"Not even close"?
- Her answer was so blunt. - How could she say that?
- Goodness, Dam Bi. - Her answer stays to the truth.
- She's like Geum Bo Ra. - That was excellent.
Geum Bo Ra?
- How do I sound like Bo Ra? - I mean it.
- I really liked that answer. - I knew it.
She's back after eight years with awesome talking skills.
It's like she fermented her skills in a nice oak barrel.
- It's like wine. - Eight-year-old wine.
- It's like wine. - I'm serious.
- She's great at talking now. - I agree.
- I love it. - Look forward to it.
Eun Su, you must be nervous since it's your first variety show.
Just like Dam Bi who's standing next to you,
- follow her lead. - Come back after eight years.
Eight years?
- Follow her lead. - Come back after eight years.
- Eight years? - Ferment it in the oak barrel.
After today's shoot, I'll be back eight years later.
- Just like doenjang. - You told her to come back later.
- I'm "not even close." - "Not even close."
(Eun Su seems promising.)
Everyone,
- we'll introduce the next guest. - Okay. Let's do that.
All right. Come on out!
Who is it?
(The third special guest appears with a cheerful song.)
It's Gyeong Ree!
(Gyeong Ree from 9muses, Ms. Perfect)
(She becomes a sexy queen that excites men on stage.)
(Compared to her competitiveness, due to her weak strength,)
(she thrived on variety shows as Paper Human.)
(She doesn't spare herself.)
(She's an adorable guest the members admire.)
- It's Gyeong Ree! - Gyeong Ree!
- Gyeong Ree. - It's been so long.
- Long time no see, Gyeong Ree. - Gyeong Ree.
- We were at the sea that time. - We haven't seen her...
- at a place like this before. - Right.
When she came out, he didn't know. He asked me who she was.
- I thought you said, Gyeon Ree. - What's wrong with you?
- I thought she was Kyeon Mi Ri. - Gyeon Ree?
(I thought she was Kyeon Mi Ri.)
- Listen. - She was coming toward us.
- What are you talking about? - It was the pronunciation.
- I thought you said Kyeon Mi Ri. - What's wrong with him?
- And Mi Ri is quite old. - By the way, Ji Hyo,
you haven't said anything today, but your eyes are doing the talking.
Didn't you say, "Has he gone mad?"
- I say your eyes just now. - I thought he had gone mad.
I thought Mi Ri had a nice silhouette.
- How could... - All right.
Gyeong Ree is joining us today.
- We'll introduce the last guest. - Okay.
This is the important point. It's really hot.
- Right. - An actress is inside.
- You can look forward to it. - She's sweating a lot.
- Really? - We should hurry then.
- Really? Eun Su, you're smiling. - Sorry?
- I can't wait. - You can't wait?
- I seriously can't wait. - Is that so?
- This great actress is... - Okay, okay.
- sweating profusely. - She's the last one too.
Let me introduce the last guest.
- Park Ji Yoon? - This is "Adult Ceremony".
(A great actress who suits "Adult Ceremony"?)
(The grand, last guest)
- Ms. Slurping. - Ms. Slurping.
(It's... It's Gook Ju.)
All right. Let's get it!
It's been a long time. It's been a while since she came.
(The great actress shows off her charms.)
She's the best dancer. She is the best indeed.
- She's the best. - It's really hot. It's so hot.
(The grand, last guest is Gook Ju, Ms. Slurping.)
- It can't come off already. - Come on, Ms. Slurping.
- What's that? What is this? - That was so sudden.
- What's up with your hair? - What was that?
She pulled out her hair.
- What was it? - Why did you pull out your hair?
- Her hair came off. - What?
- Something came off. - This...
- I have a few more here. - This.
- Three of them managed to stay on. - You put on the hair pieces.
Then I'll put this on.
- My gosh. - G-Dragon.
(Yu-Dragon)
- Fantastic, baby, dance - You're G-Dragon.
(G-Dragon, who's in the army, might be appalled at this sight.)
See? I told you so.
- They're busy trying to be funny. - Right.
I brought this, so I can wear it.
All right. Please welcome Gook Ju.
(Lee Gook Ju, the laughter generator)
Gook Ju is known for...
- her legendary lines. - Right.
- She said many, funny lines. - There are tons.
"Kwang Soo, take care of your toenail." The rotten toenail.
- She said that to me. - He's under Toenail Kwang Soo.
(There's a painful secret behind Kwang Soo's toenails.)
(In July of 2015, Kwang Soo and Gook Ju had to partner up.)
(His toenails are rotting away!)
(She refused to pair up with him due to his rotten toenails.)
(Gook Ju made Kwang Soo take care of his toenails.)
- They're fine now. Yes. - Really?
- Kwang Soo's rotten toenails. - Right.
- Viewers, they're not rotten. - He can't find shoes in his size.
Anyway, including Gook Ju,
these four guests are joining us today.
(The special guests are all introduced.)
Today's race...
will unfold in Iksan, Buyeo, and Gongju...
which are considered the Baekje Historic Areas.
Today's race is Don't Trust Them: Thieves Race.
(Don't Trust Them: Thieves Race)
"Don't Trust Them"? There are thieves?
(There must be something hidden in the race.)
- It will be a couple race today. - It's a couple race.
There are 12 people. Among 6 couples,
there are five thieves...
and seven civilians.
- I can already spot the thieves. - What are you saying?
The leader of the thieves, Boss, is hidden among them.
And the leader of the civilians, King, is hidden among them too.
However,
among the five thieves in Team Thieves,
the four thieves know who one another are.
- What? - What? Really?
The four thieves know who one another are,
but they do not know the identity of their Boss and the King.
(The 4 thieves know each other, but not the Boss and the King.)
The King of Team Civilians...
knows the identities of the four thieves,
but the King doesn't know the identity of the Boss.
So the King knows everyone except for one.
(The King knows who the 4 thieves are, except the Boss.)
In other words, the King knows who the four thieves are.
Team Civilians wins if the members eliminate the Boss.
Team Thieves wins if the members eliminate the King.
The members of the losing team get the water bomb penalty.
(The members of the losing team get the water bomb penalty.)
The weather will be cold when it's time for the penalty.
I don't know...
if it's because we have done this for so long,
but there are members whose subtle changes are obvious.
Seok Jin is like an open book.
(Seok Jin is like an open book.)
- Why do you say that? - Give us some examples.
When the producer explains the rules,
Seok Jin never copies his hand gestures.
He is holding his hand now.
I have never seen him do that before.
(The producer explains the rules.)
(Team Thieves and Team Civilians)
(Unnatural)
- Seriously. - He is too passionate.
- He is too passionate. - You are almost like Jong Kook.
I can't believe him.
Fine, I have a position.
(Fine, I have a position.)
He let himself go.
This is a disaster.
- This is a disaster. - Seriously.
- We got him. - Don't do this from the start.
- We got him. - He is making the race boring.
He should be given a new position.
Okay. Think what you want.
Seok Jin, you need to smile more naturally.
The smile isn't reaching your eyes.
- I guess he has something to hide. - Okay.
The winning couple of each round has the right...
to single out two couples to have their identities revealed.
Those couples will go up to the platform.
Please do your best as the couples you choose...
should reflect the role you play.
The first mission will determine the couples...
and who goes up the platform.
Okay.
I will explain the rules of Steal My Charms.
Do we need to steal something?
During the preliminary interview,
the female guests turned in the keywords of their charms.
(There are 6 keywords for the charms.)
The male members will guess the woman behind the keyword.
The moment they choose a keyword, a couple will be formed.
Okay.
Please take a look at the keywords...
and pick one to determine your partner.
- Let's go. - This is nerve-wracking.
Who is "Dancing Queen"?
Is it you, Gyeong Ree?
- Who is "Ms. Forehead"? - Who is it?
- Who is "Lovely Dialect"? - Dialect.
Isn't that Gook Ju?
- Is it? - No way.
Is it you?
("Lovely Dialect" is Eun Su.)
(It's me.)
- It's Eun Su. - She is a new face.
Jong Kook is lucky these days.
He looks so happy. Did you see his fist pump?
- They look good together. - He looks happy.
- They look good together. - You know,
when it's time to choose the partner,
- Jong Kook usually doesn't do this. - He is happy.
- She is someone I don't know well. - That's right.
- She is Jong Kook's type. - That's right.
- A natural beauty. - She is Jong Kook's type.
(Everyone gets paired up.)
(Jae Seok and Gyeong Ree, Haha and Dam Bi, Kwang Soo and So Min,)
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo, Jong Kook and Eun Su, Seok Jin and Gook Ju)
The couples have been decided.
- We need to find who the thieves, - We need to find them.
- the King, - The King.
and the Boss are.
I don't think Jong Kook cares about that today.
They look good together.
Sit on a mat and spend some time together.
(Forget about the mission.)
Don't be ridiculous.
"Don't be ridiculous."
- He didn't become annoyed. - I know.
Please don't misunderstand. I don't become annoyed.
What is he saying?
(Please don't misunderstand. I don't become annoyed.)
- What is he saying? - What is wrong with him?
(What is he saying?)
- Are you serious? - What an eyesore!
- What is up with you? - What?
- What an eyesore! - He really likes her.
- I don't want her to misunderstand. - What?
- Your ears are red. - It's because the weather is hot.
- I can't believe him. - I feel hot.
He must be serious about her.
She is Jong Kook's future girlfriend.
Future girlfriend?
Don't make things uncomfortable for her.
They look good together.
Your mom will be happy.
(Jong Kook has a partner who suits him.)
(Let's see if he can find the thieves and love today.)
Now, you will verify your charms...
to win the right to send couples to the platform.
(Verify Your Charms)
If you think you can be better with a certain keyword,
yell "I challenge you" and have a charm battle.
Let's check out the first keyword.
Shall I pick one?
(What's the first keyword?)
(The Fairy of Flexibility)
- What is it? - "The Fairy of Flexibility".
- Flexibility. - That's us.
(The Fairy of Flexibility, Son Dam Bi)
Haha, I am not very confident about my flexibility.
(Even though it's my keyword...)
What?
Don't you think it's too late to say that now?
(Dam Bi confesses she isn't very confident.)
"Haha, I am not very confident about my flexibility."
(She says she isn't very confident.)
- Dam Bi. - That was so sudden.
- Didn't you pick the keyword? - Yes, I did.
It's too late to back out now.
I will tell you the rules.
We will verify Dam Bi's flexibility...
with Rock-paper-scissors Split.
(Rock-paper-scissors Split)
One person from a couple will come forward.
After each round, the winner will take a step back,
and the loser will slide his or her foot forward.
The one who can't go further or loses his or her balance loses.
(You lose.)
Eun Su is stretching.
It really is Eun Su's first time on a variety show...
because she doesn't know whether she should participate.
(Glancing around)
- She asked me... - She took off her shoes already.
if she can participate.
She kept asking me that.
(Embarrassed)
Can anyone participate?
- Anyone can participate. - Really?
(Glancing around)
(She looks around as the rules are being explained.)
She reminds me a bit of Lee Da Hee.
The others should watch out.
Eun Su and Da Hee are a bit different.
She is already taking off her shoes.
Go out there.
- Go out there. - Eun Su, come on.
- Her shoes... - Eun Su, come on.
All right.
- From the start... - She took off her shoes.
It's been eight years since Dam Bi came out on a variety show.
Eun Su visited a variety show for the first time.
Let's get the match started. Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Dam Bae learned pilates for years. - Listen.
- What? - Stop talking about pilates.
(She becomes annoyed.)
Stop it. Also, watch how you pronounce her name.
- What did I do? - Her name is Dam Bi.
You called me Dam Bae, "Cigarette", didn't you?
(She becomes annoyed again.)
- I made a mistake! - He did it earlier too.
- For goodness' sake. - I heard it.
She might avoid variety shows again because of you.
Make sure you open your mouth and enunciate.
Don't call her Dam Bae.
It was Dam Bi's nickname from her school days.
- Right? - "Alcohol and Cigarette"?
("Alcohol and Cigarette"?)
- "Alcohol and Cigarette"? - Was that your nickname?
Son Dam Bi does sound like "Alcohol and Cigarette".
I got that nickname because of my name.
- She talked about it on a show. - You know,
the generation gap just became apparent.
Seok Jin heard the nickname as "Sol Cigarette".
(Seok Jin heard the nickname as "Sol Cigarette".)
Sol Cigarette was popular back in our days.
- Sol Cigarette. - Sol Cigarette was popular.
That's right.
- It was popular back then. - He is an old man.
Let's get started.
I am really inflexible.
It's annoying if the person who says so is flexible.
(It's annoying if the person who says so is flexible.)
Dam Bi changed a lot.
- What is wrong with her? - Your talk...
- improved. - She wasn't like that before.
- Her tone changed. - What happened in the eight years?
She wasn't like that before.
She wasn't like that in "Family Outing".
She is the feistiest woman I know.
(She is the feistiest woman I know.)
- She is the feistiest woman. - Seriously.
I guess it's true that she disciplined the junior singers.
(Jong Kook frames her.)
That's not true. I was a solo artist.
Get ready.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(The loser must split her legs.)
(Dam Bi wins.)
(Dam Bi takes a step back.)
It's okay.
That's it.
Can I switch my feet?
- No. - Really?
You have to stick to the foot you chose.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Dam Bi wins again.)
(Eun Su splits her legs further.)
- That's good. Come on. - Okay.
She is good at rock-paper-scissors.
It's okay. You can win this time.
That's good. Come on.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Eun Su wins.)
You just need to win this time. Okay!
(Being good at rock-paper-scissors can change the result of the game.)
Like this?
You just need to win rock-paper-scissors.
- You just need to win. - That's how it works.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Eun Su wins again.)
- Okay. - That's good.
- It's okay. - Rock-paper-scissors
Finish her.
Win one more time.
My goodness.
(Dam Bi has to win the next round.)
- It's almost over. - This round is important.
Win one more round.
- Win one more round. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Dam Bi wins.)
- Okay. - Okay, okay.
Eun Su, split your legs.
(Eun Su must split her legs as Dam Bi has.)
(Can Eun Su succeed?)
- Okay! - You did it.
That hurts! I have a cramp!
(The split comes with a cost.)
- I have a cramp! - She is good.
- I have a cramp! - She really has a cramp.
- She really has a cramp. - She has a cramp.
- She has a cramp. - She has a cramp.
(Eun Su has a cramp.)
- Are you okay? - You need to stretch the muscle.
- Are you okay? - Pull her foot back.
(Pulling)
Don't do that.
- Stretch the muscle. - She has a cramp.
- Pull her foot back. - My goodness.
She has a cramp.
Do you have a cramp?
- Eun Su, are you okay? - Yes.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
This is the last round.
- Let's go. - This is the last round.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Eun Su wins dramatically.)
She won.
(Screaming in happiness)
- She won. - What will Dam Bi do?
You can do it.
That's good. That's good.
(Stretching)
(She easily succeeds.)
She can go further.
She sat down. She sat down.
- She is so flexible. - She is so cool.
I am so impressed.
She is a hero.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(At this critical moment, Eun Su wins again.)
(Something is not right.)
She managed it.
Hold on.
(Moving)
(Dam Bi moves her foot.)
- Her foot moved. - Hold on.
- How far did it move? - It used to be here.
(Let go!)
It was here before.
No, it wasn't.
- It was here. - Hold on.
It wasn't there!
- Hold on. - It was there.
- What are you doing? - It was there.
- Dam Bi, calm down. - We have to obey the rules.
- Calm down. - It wasn't there.
- Dam Bi has to win this time. - Then you can be the winner.
Dam Bi has to win this time.
Rock-paper...
(Dam Bi couldn't stretch any further.)
You can do this.
You can be the winner.
(The result depends on this rock-paper-scissors.)
(Who will be the winner?)
Scissors
(Eun Su wins.)
- She threw it late. - No, I didn't!
(Complaining)
- She threw it late. - She threw it late.
I didn't!
Hey! She didn't.
- Calm down. - She was on time.
- Hold on. - Please review the video.
- Okay. - Please review the video.
- Haha, talk to her. - She is right.
- Talk to Dam Bi. - She is right.
- This is unfair. - Dam Bi threw it high,
- and Eun Su threw it low. - No. She...
- Jong Kook. - Okay.
(Jong Kook)
Gosh.
Okay.
Okay, Dam Bi.
(Nice job, Dam Bi.)
Let's do it again.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Eun Su wins.)
Okay.
(Dam Bi moves her foot again.)
- It's over. - You shouldn't move your foot.
It should be here.
Eun Su wins!
Good job.
We win. Good job.
It was Dam Bi's specialty, but Eun Su won.
You have to win rock-paper-scissors at the right time.
- Rock-paper-scissors is important. - Go.
It's more important to win rock-paper-scissors.
(Gook Ju is pushed into participating.)
Oh, my. I'm sorry, but...
(I'm sorry, but...)
I can't put my feet together. Is that okay?
- It's okay. - Because of my thighs,
I can't put my thighs together.
(There is a gap.)
- I can't... - We will...
Hold on.
- She loses. - Gook Ju.
- Gook Ju. - They can use computer graphics.
They can put your feet together with computer graphics.
It's so hot here.
- Good. - Are you okay?
Here comes another participant.
(Here comes another participant.)
- Kwang Soo? - Yes.
- It's hot. - You can do this!
- My big feet will help. - Your long legs will help too.
- Let's start right away. - Is he wearing flippers?
No. They're my feet.
- Are they really your feet? - Yes, they are.
It doesn't look right.
- His feet look weird. - Are they really your feet?
(He has 290mm feet.)
Your toenails are still rotten.
(Your toenails are still rotten.)
Be quiet.
Gosh.
(Now everyone knows Kwang Soo has rotten toenails.)
After all these years, they're still rotten.
Don't say that in front of Eun Su.
Eun Su, don't look at it. It's just a disease.
- It's rotten. - No, it's not!
(It's just a disease.)
It's not rotten. Don't say that in front of Eun Su.
Who can hear it then?
Please don't step on my foot.
Did you hear that? Eun Su said, "Please don't step on my foot."
(She asks Kwang Soo not to step on her foot.)
She says what she wants to say.
It looks like a sand-covered clam.
- It looks like a clam. - It looks like a clam.
What is he doing?
- Paint his toenail. - He's painting Kwang Soo's toenail.
- My goodness. - What's wrong with him?
His feet are hairy.
Isn't it a clam?
It's a cockle.
Gosh, I quIt.
(Gosh, I quit.)
(Kwang Soo gives up.)
- Kwang Soo, it looks okay now. - I quit.
- It looks much better now. - It does.
It's just a disease.
That's why I painted it.
It looks dirtier now.
(It looks dirtier now.)
She says it looks dirtier now!
Dam Bi says it looks dirtier.
What?
Sorry.
(Kwang Soo gives up.)
Next, Ji Hyo!
- Win four times in a row. - Rock-paper-scissors
- She's good at rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors - Yes!
- Ji Hyo wins. - Ji Hyo wins!
Yes! Ji Hyo!
It's Gyeong Ree's turn now.
- You're good at this. - Ji Hyo.
Gyeong Ree, you saw it, right? Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo wins.)
That's no problem.
It's meaningless.
You haven't been watching? Move the foot in the front.
"You haven't been watching?"
- He's scary. - Just tell her what to do.
Why did you say, "You haven't been watching?"
- We've played four rounds so far. - Gosh.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- Hold on. - She touched the ground.
(She almost falls.)
- She's out! - She didn't fall though.
Gyeong Ree, what happened to you?
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - You used to be flexible.
(Wobbling)
Are you walking a tightrope?
- Did you drink last night? - What's wrong?
- I didn't get enough sleep. - You didn't?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- What is this? - What is this?
Does she have BPPV?
(Does she have BPPV?)
- It makes you unstable. - Be quiet.
What are you talking about?
- I'm sorry. - I think she has it.
(Gyeong Ree keeps wobbling.)
- Are you walking a tightrope? - Stay still.
- What's wrong? - What are you doing?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Gyeong Ree wins rock-paper-scissors.)
- Yes! - It's over now.
Ji Hyo's legs are not long enough.
You won't reach even if you lie down.
Ji Hyo does look short today.
- I can do it! - Be quiet. She can do it.
I can do it!
You'll have to dislocate your legs to reach here.
What are you talking about?
Don't say that.
It's scientifically impossible.
You'll have to pull your legs out.
- What if she can't walk? - Come on.
- I can do it. - She's doing it.
- Come on. - Your left foot.
- She has to dislocate her legs. - It's too far.
You can start now.
(If Ji Hyo pulls it off, she'll win.)
It's not going to work.
(Ji Hyo fails.)
Gyeong Ree wins!
- This is so disappointing. - This is so disappointing.
(I wish I was taller.)
If you had won only one more time...
I didn't do much, but I won.
- Kwang Soo, pick one. - Okay.
Pick a good one.
(What will be the next game?)
"Dancing Queen".
(Dancing Queen)
- Is it ours? - Whose is it?
It's Gyeong Ree's.
("Dancing Queen" is Gyeong Ree's keyword.)
Gook Ju will be good at it.
We have many dancing queens today.
There will be a random dance battle.
(Random Dance Battle)
When music plays, anyone can step forward and dance.
The couple who receives the most enthusiastic reaction wins.
When music plays, Gyeong Ree will start.
Okay. Gyeong Ree will start.
- Music. - Come on!
- Go. - Come on!
Let's go.
It's "Havana".
(It's the sexy song, "Havana".)
"Havana".
(She fixes her hair...)
(and steps forward relaxedly.)
(She uses her towel.)
- She's using her towel. - She's so sexy.
- She's good. - She's starting.
(Her hip dance overwhelms everyone.)
- She's so good. - She's an amazing dancer.
- Her shoulders move on their own. - That will do.
Look at that.
(She suddenly lies down on the grass.)
- What is she doing? - What is she doing?
Hey.
- What is she doing? - You can lie down?
- You can lie down too. - That's so amazing.
- That's amazing. - Your microphone.
Your microphone.
(She picks it up.)
(She uses her microphone too.)
- She picked up her microphone. - She uses everything.
- She's using her microphone. - She's using everyhting.
- She can use everything. - Did you see that?
She can use everything.
That was Gyeong Ree. Does anyone want to try? Come on.
Is it the same song?
(The original dancing queen, Dam Bi, participates.)
- There's a chair! - Can you use a chair?
- There's a chair? - Amazing.
(She raises her leg.)
Beautiful.
- She looks so sexy. - Let's go!
(The original dancing queen starts out intense.)
- Good! - We haven't seen this in a while.
- She looks so sexy. - Good!
Good.
(After dancing relaxedly for a moment,)
(she conquers the stage with a split.)
She should have done it earlier.
- That's my move. - I lose.
(A bit of air cycling)
That's my move.
(She finishes with a kiss.)
- That was amazing. - Thank you.
- That was fantastic. - Who else wants to try?
Eun Su?
(Spinning)
(She warms up with cute moves.)
- That's so cute. - She's cute.
I like it.
Jong Kook, you should join.
That's so cute.
(Eun Su's one gesture makes Jong Kook join.)
What should I do?
Why are you so sweaty?
That's so cute.
(The audience is enthusiastic.)
Look at that.
(I want to dance with Eun Su too.)
Stop it!
(What?)
Oh, my gosh!
(So Min goes through Kwang Soo's legs to stop him.)
(You can't go anywhere.)
(Couple dance)
We were dancing. What are you doing?
- What was that? - What's wrong?
What is she doing?
Kwang Soo wasn't standing there for you.
It was for Eun Su.
Did you pass under me?
- Why did you? - What's wrong with you?
How could you?
- Kwang Soo. - Why did you do that?
I thought a dog passed by.
Kwang Soo came out for Eun Su.
- By the way... - You startled me.
- You're so rude. - Eun Su.
(Jong Kook and Eun Su's dance stops.)
Let's dance to Korean pop songs.
- Okay. - It'll be exciting.
- Exciting Korean pop music. - That sounds good.
Korean pop songs?
(Brave sounds play.)
- This is amazing. - Goodness.
("Crazy", a hit song by Son Dam Bi in 2008)
(A sexy dance with a chair was key.)
Dance however you want even if you don't know the dance.
(She sits on the chair.)
- That's good. - Let's go.
That's good. It's the same so far.
- It's a perfect song for So Min. - She knows the hand movement.
- It's her song. - You're really crazy.
(So Min is really crazy.)
(She moves lightly.)
She's really crazy.
(She reenacts the dance perfectly.)
- Does she know? - She knows the dance.
(We thought that she knew.)
(But she's just crazy.)
She lifted her leg.
Let's go.
It was harder than this.
- Is that the dance? - No.
One more time.
(She turns around.)
Why are you looking at me?
(You should look at the camera instead.)
You should look at the camera.
(We're still filming.)
(It's a crazy dance where she abandons the camera.)
That's enough.
Gosh, she danced while looking at me.
So Min turned...
- That's funny. - to the wrong direction.
(How was my dance?)
Next up is...
- Ji Hyo. - Let's see.
Let's win some points.
I want to win points.
- Get ready. - You didn't warn me at all.
Just do it.
Are you starting with your leg on?
Start with your leg on. That's right.
That's good. That's right, Ji Hyo.
Shake your legs, Ji Hyo.
- 1, 2, 1, 2. - She put on her legs.
- That's good. - You're cute.
Even girls like her.
You're doing well.
Is that how it goes?
It doesn't matter.
That's good.
(Her charms attract women.)
(While being charming, she throws down the chair.)
(She acts like a gangster.)
Look at that.
She's like an old real estate agent.
She's what people want now.
That was great.
- She was charming to women. - You did it.
- That looked real. - You did well.
That was pretty.
It's the perfect pose for today's world.
- It was unique. - However,
I expect the score on her dance to be quite low.
(However, I expect the score on her dance to be quite low.)
- She didn't consider the score. - Why?
- What about her legs? - Her attitude was good,
but the dance score is...
- She didn't dance much. - She didn't dance much?
Yes. She didn't dance much.
Who's next?
(Dancing Machine Gook Ju is next.)
- That's amazing. - Someone else goes.
- She's amazing. - Gook Ju is good at it.
Can you swing your leg around?
(Can you swing your leg above the chair?)
Can you swing your leg over it?
Shall I help you?
Leave her alone.
You're great.
(She reenacts the dance perfectly.)
She's good.
(She has to swing her leg around.)
(What's going on?)
(She's about to fall off the chair.)
Gook Ju.
(She hits him.)
(She hits him in the face.)
(Gosh, I'm so sorry.)
The chair sank.
(What's more serious is the sinking chair.)
(The chair sinks to the ground.)
- I'm sorry. - What happened?
Pull it out.
(They struggle to pull it out.)
This is unbelievable.
(She leaves the scene.)
- It wasn't me. - This is unbelievable.
(The chair finally comes out.)
My goodness.
- Did the chair bend? - What?
Come on.
(The legs got bent.)
- The chair got bent. - Stop joking.
Did it bend?
It got bent.
- Hey. - The chair went right in.
We might find petroleum here.
- What? - Did she bore a hole?
- It really got bent. - That was good.
(She's embarrassed.)
Gook Ju.
- Gook Ju. - Yes?
- That was great. - What? I'm not done yet.
I love situations like this.
I still want to dance.
It's over. Everyone laughed.
Gosh, what happened?
That was amazing.
It's been a long time.
Next is Dam Bi.
I've only seen it on TV.
- This is real. - It's real.
It's been eight years.
I want to watch her from here.
That's great.
- That's amazing. - I want to watch her.
Her legs look sexy.
(The song starts to play.)
(She doesn't move at all.)
- You're supposed to hold here. - You aren't supposed to move.
You shouldn't move yet.
It isn't time to be silly.
This was it.
Her shoulders are still.
You weren't supposed to dance.
(She holds completely still in the beginning.)
So Min danced silly from here.
I've wanted to see you in real life.
(The real is finally here.)
(She waits for the right timing.)
(She moves at the right beat.)
(She's as beautiful as she was 10 years ago.)
(She swings her leg easily.)
(The real dancer is here.)
This is it.
(That's exactly it.)
(The original dancing queen finishes warming up.)
- She's different. - She really is.
The original is different.
- Her dancing is different. - That's real.
(She moves her head.)
(This is the real dance to "Crazy".)
- It's different. - That's right.
- Right, this is it. - It's different.
- More, more. - It's different.
It's really different.
(Here comes the famous dog legs dance.)
Here it is.
(She moves her legs like dog legs.)
(The original dancing queen)
(She dances perfectly to the song "Crazy".)
Goodness.
That was the best.
- It was perfect. - That was amazing.
- That was great. - In the beginning,
she doesn't get annoying.
- I think... - You have to control yourself.
Here's what I think.
- You have to control yourself. - Give it to Dam Bi.
Give it to me.
- It's obvious. - Just accept it.
- I agree. - That's right.
- Everyone. - I agree.
She has unanimous votes.
The winner is Son Dam Bi.
I completely agree.
I forgot that she could dance.
- I knew she was good. - Now...
the final winning couple is...
Haha and Dam Bi. They win three points.
(Haha and Dam Bi are the final winners.)
All right.
Please bring the platform.
Is there a platform?
- We need to put up a platform. - Already?
- They said it'll be on immediately. - Already?
The winning couple may place two couples on the platform.
We'll tell you if any of the four is King or Boss...
as well as the number of thieves.
Okay.
- I see. - We should choose wisely.
They should pick carefully.
Pick two couples...
to be placed on the platform after discussing.
Is there King on that side?
Do you think one of them is King?
- It could be one of us. - Right.
We should find out about others.
Raise your hand if you've ever stolen anything as a child.
Anyone can lie.
Has anyone stolen a cherry at a fruit market?
You must select that couple.
(He whispers to them.)
Okay.
- What are you doing? - Why are you cornering us?
- Why are you cornering us? - What's wrong with you?
- He's being suspicious. - The one who's cornering is.
- He's being suspicious. - I agree.
I was suspicious of Seok Jin.
- He could be. - I'm not.
Shouldn't we put him on first?
Why would you do that?
He seems to be hiding something.
- I'm curious. - I'm not.
- I'm curious. - I really am not.
- We made a decision. - We made a decision.
Which couples did you choose?
(Which is the first couple Haha and Dam Bi chose?)
- Jong Kook's team. - You choose us?
- Yes. Jong Kook's team. - You choose us?
- Did you choose us? - Yes, and Jae Seok's team.
Good job.
Haha.
- Dam Bi. - We'll find something.
- We'll find something. - You aren't what I expected.
- Stop being silly. - Stop it.
- I hope we find something. - Haha.
Between two couples...
I'm curious too.
Is there King or Boss?
(Is one of them King or Boss?)
Did we find both?
(Is any one of them King or Boss?)
- None of them are. - That's right.
(None of them are.)
- I told you. - That's good.
- None of us are. - None of them?
- Seriously? - We did a good job.
And...
- How about thieves? - the number of thieves is...
(How about the number of thieves?)
- It's zero. - See?
(It's 0.)
- We're civilians. - You chose well.
- Did you suspect us? - All of us are civilians.
You selected well.
(We're all civilians.)
- They're all here. - That's right.
There are six thieves.
(It's full of thieves.)
We're King, Boss, and thieves except for two people.
- No. - It's you.
- It's all of you. - It's not me.
Civilians should team up.
- I'm a civilian. - You're terrible.
I'm a civilian.
- You picked the right couples. - This is incredible.
- Okay. - This is incredible.
- Now... - They're all civilians.
He's starting again.
My goodness.
- Jae Seok. - It's you, right?
- Okay, we must catch two. - He's definitely one.
It's not me. Take a look.
- Just take a look. - I think you're a thief too.
- Me? I'm not. - So Min.
So Min doesn't say these things.
- That's not true. - Why are you shy today?
- I'm not. I'm not a thief. - You weren't like this before.
- That's good. - You weren't.
- Now... - Okay.
let's move to the next destination after changing the team outfit.
Come on.
(They move to Buyeo.)
How did we choose only the civilians?
- There's one left. - Here's what this is.
There are seven civilians.
- One of them is King. - Among seven civilians?
Yes, among seven civilians.
Among 5 thieves, there's 1 Boss.
- Among five thieves? - Yes.
But if the King is caught,
Team Civilians will lose.
(The members of Team Thieves are unknown,)
(and Team Civilians is Jong Kook, Eun Su, Jae Seok, and Gyeong Ree.)
If you think about it...
- Tell us what you are. - I'm a civilian.
- I'm a civilian. - You're thief, right?
I'm a civilian.
Let me be a brigand instead. Seriously.
- To be honest, - I think you're a thief.
I didn't know about my role before I came here,
- and I was disappointed. - Why?
I thought I could be a good thief.
Usually, one of the guests is given a special role.
Yes. But I didn't get any.
Anyway, that's not important.
- Thieves. - Jae Seok.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you the ones that look like thieves.
- Who are they? - Dam Bi is definitely a thief.
Haha has been acting weird too.
Haha is definitely a thief.
I agree.
I even suspect that...
he is Boss.
One thing is bothering me.
Our first choice was so smart.
But it gave Jae Seok...
a special role.
- He suddenly became a detective. - Right.
- He's a detective now. - He's so excited.
It was such a smart choice.
He was just a civilian at first.
We should have chosen Seok Jin.
- But... - Then...
We shouldn't do that.
He'd be too embarrassed.
- This has happened many times. - Seok Jin...
- I felt to sorry for him. - He definitely has a special role.
- So... - I'm sure he does.
He has a special role, and it shows.
I feel bad.
I was guessing...
it might be Seok Jin's team versus So Min's team.
There's something going on between them these days.
When So Min has a special role,
she becomes quiet.
- She doesn't talk? - She doesn't want to get caught.
She's been like that today.
But if it's So Min and Seok Jin,
won't they get caught too early?
- Right. - They'll get caught right away.
- But it's confusing. - It is.
We don't know who is which.
That's hard.
Anyway, Detective Kim and Detective Yu must be...
grilling the two.
- The two? - They must be grilling them.
I'm so glad I'm not on the same team as them.
- Right. - Seriously.
- It's under the seat. - It goes over your waist.
It goes over your waist.
(Jong Kook helps Eun Su with her seat belt.)
- Thank you. - He's so sweet.
- He's so sweet. - You're so sweet.
Oh, my.
You're smiling so big.
- You're smiling. - I'm happy.
- Kwang Soo is smiling. - I like watching these things.
- I like it too. - Watching what?
I like watching lovey-dovey people.
What are you talking about? I'm too old for her.
Jong Kook, age is not important.
I love this.
Eun Su, if you keep doing that, it'll make us uncomfortable.
- It'll make us uncomfortable. - Right.
It'll make Eun Su uncomfortable.
How old are you?
- I'm very old. - Are you...
- 38? - I'm older than that.
- Are you over 40? - I'm over 40.
You're pretty old.
(I'll pretend I'm not listening.)
You're older than I thought.
I'm sorry, but we'll take a taxi instead.
I can't say anything.
Be quiet. Let's just listen. I'm curious.
I love listening to these things.
Do you have any siblings?
- I have an older sister. - How old is she?
She's married.
When did you debut?
Two years ago.
You should be careful with guys.
- Even when you're young. - You're right.
You shouldn't meet bad guys for the sake of experience.
When you meet someone you really like,
it might make you regret.
If you work out and don't smoke or drink,
you age more slowly than others.
(Glaring, shy)
We're just talking.
- The thing is... - I mean it.
I'm curious.
You two are...
- civilians, right? - Yes.
Then you should be questioning us.
(You should be questioning us.)
"What's your role?"
- The thing is... - "Are you a thief? Are you Boss?"
- It's just that... - That's your usual style.
- He's usually very harsh. - It's not like that.
- Right now... - Look.
- They don't care about the mission. - Listen to me.
Look. We need something...
We need hints to pressure you with.
- But we have nothing. - When I got in this car,
I thought Jong Kook would hit me.
What are you talking about?
I thought, if I didn't tell him I'm Boss, he'd hit him.
I haven't heard Jong Kook's voice this soft in a while.
- Is he being soft? - Very.
Then usually...
You're smiling a lot today.
Jong Kook is smiling a lot.
I'm smiling because you guys are making this up.
I smiled when you did this with Jin Young too.
Can you two talk for 10 minutes pretending we're not here?
I'm so happy.
Whether I win or lose, I'm so happy today.
(They're entering Buyeo.)
(Buyeo was the capital of Baekje 1,500 years ago.)
(The five-storied stone pagoda and Jeongnimsa Temple Site)
Oh, it's beautiful.
(They arrive at Gungnamji, the palace pond of Baekje.)
What's that?
That's a lotus, right?
I see something.
That's what we used when Gook Ju appeared last time.
Isn't it the one that you push each other out?
(2 years ago, they had to push each other out of this bowl.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
We have to push each other out.
Then we should try to be partners with Jong Kook.
To decide who gets to eat and send people onto the platform,
let's start Lotus Flower War.
You'll be divided into three teams...
and dance in the flower. When the whistle blows,
you have to push the other teams out.
Only the winning teams...
will get to eat a lotus leaf rice meal.
- A lotus leaf rice meal? - Only the winning teams?
Only the winning teams?
(Only the winning teams get to eat and send people onto the platform.)
(Group 1)
(Group 2)
I won't care who it is.
It's "Bboom Bboom".
(Let's warm up.)
(Shall we warm up with "Bboom Bboom"?)
(They forget about the war for a moment and have fun.)
- Let's relieve our stress! - Bboom bboom!
(Whistle)
Has it started?
- Se Chan. - Jong Kook.
You haven't felt it for real, have you?
What do you mean?
You can't hit me.
I'm not hitting you.
- I'm just grabbing you. - You can't hit me.
Here we go.
- Okay. - Grab his leg.
- Okay. - There you go.
You can't lift me anyway.
Grab his leg!
You can't lift me.
It won't work.
(Ji Hyo and So Min attack Jong Kook's partner, Eun Su.)
Seriously.
Push Eun Su out first.
(I should rescue Eun Su.)
Eun Su!
Grab his leg!
You can't lift me.
(What?)
(Eun Su won't budge.)
(She resists the two girl's attack.)
Gosh.
She's so strong.
Look at Eun Su.
(Eun Su is surprisingly strong.)
Eun Su is so strong. Look at her.
Let's just play rock-paper-scissors.
Eun Su lifted So Min.
(Screaming)
(So Min is put down on the ground.)
(Eun Su, please spare my life.)
Is it over?
- She lifted her. - She's being pushed out.
Look at that.
(Eun Su even succeeds in overpowering Kwang Soo.)
Ji Hyo, grab here!
(Jong Kook pushes Se Chan out.)
It's over.
Gosh.
Look at that.
(Jong Kook lifts Ji Hyo...)
(and throws her out.)
What is this?
Kwang Soo!
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo are out.)
(Celebrating)
What should I do?
I'm scared.
(Jong Kook, the Undertaker...)
(and Eun Su with shocking strength)
I'm scared. Let me out!
It's like UFC.
- Help! - Here we go.
- Help! - So Min.
Help!
(The green sheep are surrounded by black wolves.)
Kwang Soo, just cheat.
I'm so glad that I'm not in his position.
Please!
I'm so relieved.
He looks like a chicken.
Eun Su, don't look at me.
Eun Su!
No!
(Kwang Soo's favorite trunks)
- Hey. - Kwang Soo, just get out.
Let's just give up!
- Let's give up! - Let's fight just a little longer.
- Just a little longer. - Let's give up!
- Just get out! - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let's not give up.
Give up, you stupid.
I can't give up.
(The husband is beaten up,)
(and the wife tries to save him.)
Kwang Soo, if I had a towel, I'd throw it at you.
Please. I'm sorry.
(As expected, Jong Kook and Eun Su win.)
It'll be so tasty.
We can't eat, right?
I can't eat? I want to at least see it.
It's bulgogi.
(Bulgogi hot pot)
Lotus leaf rice.
(Bulgogi and lotus leaf rice taste amazing together.)
All we have is dried seaweed and rice.
I can't believe this.
Gosh.
Are we eating soy sauce and rice?
Dried seaweed and rice.
Eun Su is so strong.
They're the strongest team.
I haven't seen such a strong girl in a long time.
She's really strong.
Even Ji Hyo admits it.
She reminds me of Eun Hye.
Since Eun Hye...
(The strong girl, Yoon Eun Hye, stole Jong Kook's heart.)
(Eun Su reminds everyone of Eun Hye.)
Since Eun Hye...
Jong Kook.
(Of course.)
Hold on.
Congratulations, Eun Su.
(They all celebrate the new couple.)
Okay!
(Everyone cheers at the potential of becoming a couple.)
Hold on. I'm okay with everything, but here's what's funny.
When you talk about that, she does this. Why is she doing this?
- It's my first show. That's why. - She saw too many shows.
(Eun Su is adorable.)
- Sorry, but is it your birthday? - She's playful.
- Pardon? - Why are you sitting there alone?
- Is it your birthday today? - It might as well be my birthday.
- What's a birthday if not today? - Is that so?
Let's be reasonable, and give me some.
(It's my birthday.)
- Why? - Why?
Can you not see that my left eyebrow is gone?
- We should give some to him. - Come on. Be considerate.
I brought this upon myself because I was goofing around.
(It was during the dance time for the 2nd round of Lotus Flower War.)
(He got into BTS' "Fake Love".)
(He was dancing all over the stage just like BTS,)
(but he failed to control his excitement and fell over.)
(It was painful and embarrassing.)
(Even the people who were watching were flustered.)
(Feeling embarrassed)
(BTS almost hurt a man.)
(He must've been so excited. He jumped all the way up there.)
(This goofball put on a bandage on his left eyebrow.)
Can you not see that my left eyebrow is gone?
You're such a goofball. Seriously.
(I shouldn't goof around.)
- We keep eating this. - Try to bring that.
(Doesn't the zucchini pancake look good?)
- The meat is disappearing. - Sneak that in.
- I'm still eating this. - You are?
- I'm not supposed to eat the leaf. - You are?
(She fixes her eyes on Gook Ju.)
I'll divide what I eat and what I don't eat.
People get the wrong idea. I'm not mad.
Hey, hey. What was that? Bring that back.
- Why? - How dare you pull a trick on us?
- You took the zucchini. - We had three pancakes.
- We had three. I checked. - What did he do?
(What's this under the dried lavers?)
- They are definitely the thieves. - They have to be the thieves.
- Come on, Mr. 40. - No, listen.
- It's because I'm 40. - It's because you're 40.
- I can't let this fly. - It's because you're 40.
- They're showing signs of thieves. - That's right.
(This Mr. 50 struggles to overcome the adhesion of his name tag.)
- Eun Su. - I'm a loyal servant.
- You can just share it with us. - We were in the same team.
- Who? - So Min...
- We can't just give this to her. - Eun Su.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
I want to see the mosquito dance.
The mosquitoes bit me a lot, it was itchy
(No problem. We'll both do it.)
(The Mosquito Couple flails out of hunger.)
I scratched my arm without thinking much
(It was itchy, but I endured it)
- I wanted to see it in person. - Do you know how to do it?
- What should I show you? - This one.
- Eun Su, thank you. - Gosh, Eun Su is so nice.
- She gave us so much. - Gosh, she gave you a ton of food.
- Gosh, Eun Su. - Eun Su.
- Thank you. - This isn't a place for that.
- No, no. Why? - Put that down.
- Okay, okay. - If you spill it, it's over.
- Okay. Let's talk over there. - Put it down.
- Why did Eun Su give that to us? - We'll talk at the table.
- Don't do anything stupid. - I won't.
You two better not fight and eat it at your seats.
- Don't force it. - Listen.
(They sit down calmly first.)
- Take it. - Give it to me.
(She gives him the rice cake.)
- Take this much for now. - Give me that one.
- What was that? Come on. - Hey.
- Take that for now. - What's this?
Do it one more time.
(The meat is mine!)
(Give me the meat!)
(He begins the forceful process of taking back the meat.)
(This is my first time seeing something like that.)
(He manages to get the meat out from her mouth.)
- Look at them. - What are you two doing now?
(Give me back my meat.)
(There they go again.)
Goodness, you and So Min are so disgusting.
- Ji Hyo ate the rest of it. - Come on.
(They're fighting again? Gosh, they have no table manners.)
You should've given them a big portion with a ladle.
(She calmly holds the meat plate and slurps everything in.)
(Keep fighting. I'll enjoy this.)
- Ji Hyo ate the rest of it. - Gosh.
(That's amazing.)
No!
- So Min. - It was right in front of me.
- Good job. - It was right in front of me.
- Gook Ju, move your feet. - Hey, it's the same here.
(Is Jae Seok plotting something to steal the lotus leaf rice meal?)
What is he doing?
- What are you doing? - Just go rest.
Jae Seok, you're going to skin your forehead again.
(Don't hurt yourself. Don't do anything.)
- You'll skin your forehead. - Hey.
- My goodness. - That won't work.
My gosh.
Seok Jin, please give me some food.
(This sexy singer tries to scrounge food with the dried laver mole.)
Come on, she's trying.
- Do the dance here, Dam Bi. - Seok Jin.
(I'm going crazy)
- Please give me some. - Okay, okay.
- You're good. - Sure, sure.
- You're great. - He's so generous.
- Gook Ju, do you want the snacks? - Really?
- What is it? - Why? Why is she getting snacks?
- She said she has a special talent. - I see.
- Copy her, and you'll get food. - Like this.
- Really? What is it? - I want to try it too.
(What's her talent with the snacks?)
- How do you do it? - I did it a long time ago.
I don't do it anymore.
- What's that? - I know what it is.
(Her special talent is popping the snack bag between her thighs.)
(How does it look in real life?)
No, no. Watch. Just watch.
What was that?
(So your special talent was popping the bag and rolling next?)
Gook Ju, did you get shot?
- What's wrong with you? Gook Ju. - Did you get shot?
- What happened to the snacks? - Did you get shot or not?
- I mean, listen. - The chips are destroyed.
Did someone shoot her from there?
(Are you okay? Do you have a gunshot wound?)
Gook Ju, did you get shot?
- What's wrong with you? - We heard something pop.
- Are you okay? - You can't use your fingers.
- Okay. - Can anyone do this?
- Me! - I can just try this?
- Dam Bi will go first. - I think I can do this.
- Dam Bi. - Gosh, she's doing her best today.
- You have to do it in 1 go. - 1, 2, 3.
- Can I do it like this? - Yes.
(Can Dam Bi successfully pop the bag?)
I think I can do this.
- Dam Bi. - Gosh, she's doing her best today.
- You have to do it in 1 go. - 1, 2, 3.
- Can I do it like this? - Yes.
(Can Dam Bi successfully pop the bag?)
- She can't do it. - That won't count.
(In a gentle manner,)
(she fails.)
- Dam Bi is out. - I guess that's hard.
- Give me back the snack. - Why can't you do it?
- You might try to eat the chips. - Why can't I do this?
- You can sit on it. - How did she pop that?
- One. - You can't do that?
If you can't do it in one go, it won't count.
- So Min can't do it. - So Min is out.
- So Min, why can't you? Let's go! - So Min is out.
- Ji Hyo is out. - No!
- You have to do it in one go. - I did it.
- Can guys try it? - Eun Su.
- Eun Su. - I'd like to see her try.
I think she can do it.
(Eun Su showed the Herculean strength with her thighs.)
If Eun Su succeeds, she'll choose someone to get some food.
- Okay. - We'll give out our food.
- Eun Su has to try. - You must do it at once.
- I think she'll succeed at once. - 1, 2, 3.
(Will she become the woman of strength after she pops the bag?)
(Crushing)
- Hey. - What was that sound?
1, 2, 3.
(Crushing)
(What was the sound just now?)
(It sounded too sharp unlike the one before.)
- What was that? - That didn't sound right.
- She broke her bones. - Didn't your pants get ripped?
- Eun Su, what was that sound? - It ripped.
- But she did it. It popped. - Hey.
- I know that, but the sound... - It should have that popping sound.
- Didn't it come from her body? - From her body?
- Seok Jin makes this kind of sound. - My gosh.
- It sounded like plates. - She pretended to be weak.
- It sounded like something cracked. - I also heard a cracking sound.
- It sounded like my jeans ripped. - Your jeans are fine.
- Your jeans are fine. - Right.
I don't think Jae Seok can do it.
- No, I can do this. - His thighs are slim.
Don't do it. You'll hurt your forehead again.
(Don't do it. You'll hurt your forehead again.)
- You'll hurt yourself. Stop it. - Stay quiet.
- You'll hurt yourself again. - I'll be fine.
- I'm okay. At least, I'll get food. - Exactly.
- Jae Seok, what are you today? - What?
Are you Mona Lisa or what?
(Beauty without eyebrows)
- Mona Lisa - You don't have the eyebrow.
- Jae Seok, come here. - I still have an eyebrow.
- Come here. I'll put one on you. - Draw it for him.
- Hey. Do it for him. - There you go.
- It's done. It's done. - All right.
- I have both eyebrows now, right? - You look much better.
- I have both eyebrows now, right? - It's a much better look.
(Beauty of unbalanced eyebrows)
- All right. - Go for it!
- I'll give you this if you succeed. - You only get one chance.
- 1 chance. Okay. - Only 1 chance.
- You can do this. - Hold on. I think...
every guy can do this. You should put it between your thighs.
- Between the thighs. - This? This is really hard.
- Really? - I guess she can do that too.
- Between there? - I haven't done it for a while.
- How do I do this? - Gosh, how can she do that?
(Popping)
(The bag clearly pops right in the middle.)
- How's that possible? - This is amazing!
(This is amazing!)
- Look. I didn't spill the snack. - You didn't spill it.
I didn't drop the chips.
This buddy tried to come out, though.
She did it just right.
It's unbelievable.
- Do men have a chance? - Yes, they do.
- I'll try. - It's amazing she did that.
- We men will do that in a row. - Okay.
You should do that in 1, 2, 3.
You're confident.
- Kwang Soo, you go first. - All right.
(Kwang Soo succeeds at one go.)
(Se Chan goes next.)
You failed!
(His face turns red.)
Se Chan failed!
- It doesn't work. - Next! 1, 2, 3!
(Haha succeeds.)
(People admire the power of his thighs.)
(Only one man is lonely now.)
Se Chan.
This one doesn't work.
It's all right.
- You're a weak man. - It doesn't work.
Doesn't it work?
It doesn't.
It doesn't work.
It doesn't work all right.
(Haha made it earlier.)
No, it doesn't work.
(The snack pack stays still despite Haha's giddy act.)
Jong Kook, you should try.
Jong Kook should do it. Jong Kook, give it a try.
Jong Kook can do it.
(Nothing's wrong with it. Your thighs are just weak.)
Jong Kook, you can do it if you use your power at one go.
Look at his muscles.
(Holding tight)
- Like this? - Here he goes!
1, 2, 3!
(Can he pop the snack pack with his powerful thighs?)
Gosh, this one doesn't work.
(The snack pack stays still.)
Jong Kook can't pop it!
It doesn't work.
- It doesn't work. - It doesn't.
Even Jong Kook can't pop this one. Take it away.
- It's nonsense. - He picked a wrong one.
- This is a tough snack. - It's a tough snack.
- It doesn't work, Gook Ju. - It doesn't.
- It's tough. - We can't pop it.
(Lotus leaf rice meal ends with a mysterious snack pack.)
Everyone, did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes! - I'm full.
Jong Kook and Eun Su took the first place in the game earlier,
so they can select two couples and put them on the platform.
All right.
- Here... - First,
So Min and Kwang Soo...
Let us stand on the platform!
They should absolutely stand on the platform.
- What are you saying? - It rhymes.
I want to do that myself.
So Min and Kwang Soo didn't suspect each other at all.
It's strange.
I suspect Kwang Soo.
- I suspect him. - You'll see.
They didn't suspect each other in the car.
And about the other couple, as I see it a while ago,
- these two... - Yes.
(Us?)
They put four of us on the platform...
- and if this time... - It's not like that.
- If they were thieves, - Yes.
they would have selected a team with at least one thief...
- and made us confused. - That's right!
- However, they put four civilians. - You got it!
- There might be no thief here. - I see.
- So I'll put them on the platform. - Okay!
What is he saying? Gosh, really.
All right.
Come on. Here you go.
What?
What did you say?
I got a hole in my socks. My goodness.
Dam Bi got a hole in her socks.
You have passion, Dam Bi. I like that.
- She really does her best. - She's changed over eight years.
She has changed a lot over eight years.
(Dam Bi slaps Haha on the shoulder.)
Gosh, it really hurts.
By the way, Dam Bi,
what has happened to you for the last eight years?
The result is out.
- This is important. - I'm curious.
This is important.
(1 King, 1 Boss, 4 thieves are not found yet.)
There must be one thief among them without question.
There must be at least one.
- There should be about 2. - Of course there are more than 2.
As a result of the second judgment,
the number of thieves among these four...
(The number of thieves among these four)
(So Min and Kwang Soo didn't suspect each other at all today.)
(Dam Bi and Haha put four civilians on the platform.)
The number of thieves...
is three.
- See? - It's three.
(The number of thieves among these 4 people are 3.)
(3 out of 4 are thieves.)
I can't believe it.
(3 of them are thieves and they've met before the opening.)
- I told you. - Unbelievable.
- I told you. - You're framing us again.
- Really? - She's framing us like that.
Is that true?
I really heard it in detail.
It's not me. I mean it.
Dam Bi, what was that you said in the car?
And,
the other is...
a Boss.
(A Boss)
(3 thieves and 1 Boss)
- Unbelievable! - I can believe it!
I told you.
It's incredible.
You're mean.
Wait a minute. That means all of them are thieves.
(All of them are thieves.)
They're all thieves.
Gosh, they're thieves!
- To sum up, - It comes out in the open.
3 of these 4 have known one another already.
I really got goose bumps.
- Stop acting! - Dam Bi, please.
Then, wait a minute.
Stop acting!
Then one of these is...
I'll tell you what was really funny.
When he said there are three thieves,
Dam Bi stared into the air.
I didn't stare into the air, Jong Kook!
(Dam Bi reacted suspiciously earlier.)
(She didn't know what to do.)
(What did Dam Bi's response mean?)
She didn't look around the members, but she stared into the air.
Gosh, really.
Are you framing me this way?
(Was everyone acting?)
I know that there's one thief left there.
Excuse me, but it seems that you have nothing to do with this.
Aren't you just being mischievous?
You're just being naughty, right?
I'm not being mischievous.
You seem to be a cilvilian without an eyebrow.
I'm not being naughty.
You're being mischievous.
You should draw your eyebrow.
- She can take care of it. - Can she?
Please draw my eyebrow.
Draw it like a real eyebrow.
What would you have done without the marker today?
Draw it lightly.
He got his eyebrow tattooed.
It's much better, right?
- It's good. - You should draw that side too.
(How does Jae Seok's new eyebrow drawn by Gook Ju look?)
It's fine.
You should draw here more.
It looks very natural, right?
It's a little bit raised, though.
- That's why people tattoo eyebrows. - I'm surprised.
- Jae Seok! - It's good, isn't it?
Where have you been?
I had a tape on my eyebrow a while ago.
May I speak now?
You look charismatic. You look like this now.
You're not feeling well, right?
You're like Dwayne Johnson.
Are you framing me like this?
Wait minute. On the contrary,
then civilians are...
- among the rest of these people... - We're four.
- 1 of 4... - 1 of 4 here is a thief.
There are a thief and a King here.
- Please. - Because...
(A King and a thief are here.)
You really act well.
- I swear. - I really swear.
Ji Hyo, you're a thief, aren't you?
I swear, Jong Kook.
Don't regret this later.
- There's a King. - I really...
(Which team will have the last laugh?)
I have no idea.
I have no idea either.
By the way, from the first round,
we're so mixed up.
(We're really mixed up.)
See it this way.
You're...
If you're thieves,
you should have put the team with a thief on the platform.
At that time, we lacked judgment.
No, it happened while we were going back and forth.
And I...
Then if there were a thief and a Boss...
among these two,
you might have not known that.
That's for sure.
That's a rule,
(What if they are a Boss and a thief who don't know each other?)
You put only civilians on the platform as you didn't know.
(You put only civilians on the platform as you didn't know.)
That's possible.
Wait a minute. I won't speak anymore.
Then one of you...
Here we see a field.
- One of you... - Here are trees.
might be a Boss.
Why are you looking straight suddenly?
- That's possible... - That's possible.
or not.
On the first round, they were...
I have no idea.
I'm just a civilian. I don't know. It's complicated.
I still don't get the rule.
- I'll ask just one thing, Seok Jin. - Go ahead.
May I call you the King?
You can do that. I don't care. But I'm not a King.
I'm not on the civilian's side,
and I have no idea. But I'm not a King.
I'm just a civilian.
It's somewhat strange. He twisted words.
You're a King, Seok Jin.
Listen to me.
You don't know what I am.
You don't know. You're asking me if I am a King.
That means I'm not a thief, right?
No. You fixed it this way.
Thieves fixed it up.
- It's driving me crazy. - You did that.
Who's the thief you have in your mind?
It's you.
- Who's the King? - You're the one thief left.
I don't know about the King. I should look for that.
Why do you look for the King? You should look for the thief.
I've found the thief. I've done that already.
You should look for a Thief Prince.
Is there a Thief Prince?
Isn't it a Boss?
What's a Thief Prince?
I mean a Boss.
I should look for a Boss.
We don't have to talk at all. We can find it as they keep talking.
If there's no King here, it's either Se Chan or Ji Hyo.
The King knows everything.
What comes last?
What's that?
(What's that?)
Why are constables there?
- There are constables? - Yes.
What's that? Are they really going to flog us?
- It looks like they'll flog us. - Do we have to get flogged?
(What's the last mission for them here?)
It's cool now.
Now that it's time for us to get wet...
Seriously, it's time to get wet.
Thieves gather together.
It's so obvious.
They're conspiring in a group.
Are you thieves acting like that explicitly?
- You're amazing. - It's incredible.
Here's the last mission.
We'll proceed with Get Together for the Right Answer.
Get Together for the Right Answer.
We need to win this first.
Listen to the question and examples,
dance to the children's song,
We're dancing all along.
- They love dancing. - How much are we dancing today?
Why are we dancing so much?
(Gook Ju loves to dance.)
- In the brook is a tadpole - Are yo doing this because of her?
I feel like this game is designed for Gook Ju.
Is this Lee Gook Ju's Running Man?
Let me dance. Let me dance.
Jae Seok loves to dance too.
- So we dance. - When you hear the whistle,
make a group of people...
in the number of the correct answer.
If you think number three is the answer,
make a group of three.
If the group's answer is correct, each member gets one point.
The couple with the highest score...
will get to decide which couples go up the platform.
If your answer is incorrect,
the policemen will give a random penalty.
- What? - Please form a group with caution.
That will be hard.
A random penalty.
Here comes the first question.
Among the following, which one is a pure Korean word?
It will be hard.
This kind of a question is hard.
They always give the most difficult questions.
Number one, trotter.
Number two, bossam.
- What? - Number three, sundae.
Number four, hotteok.
- A pure Korean word? - Number five, porridge.
- Is there only 1 answer? - Is there only 1 answer?
Pick an answer.
Isn't it sundae?
A pure Korean word.
- A pure Korean word. - A pure Korean word.
Are we picking an answer that isn't a pure Korean word?
We are picking an answer that is a pure Korean word.
Isn't it hotteok?
- Is it number four? - I think it's sundae.
- Hotteok. - Are you certain?
Hotteok must be an onomatopoeia.
Is it hotteok?
Number four.
We need to dance.
(The song signals the start of the dance.)
Let's go.
(They begin to dance.)
(Dancing)
Seok Jin, shouldn't you dance over there?
Go away. You are making us uncomfortable.
- Go away. - I am not a thief.
Shouldn't you dance over there?
(Thieves mingle with civilians.)
Don't do this to me.
(Whistling)
What?
(Thieves and Seok Jin form a group to pick number 5.)
Is it number five?
- Is it number five? - I don't know what to do.
Is it number 3? Is it number 3?
I guess we are a group.
- Number three. - The answers are divided.
You chose numbers 3, 4, and 5.
The answer is...
(Which one is the answer?)
- number three, sundae. - Okay!
- Number three, sundae. - Okay!
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Gook Ju get it right.)
- It's number three. - I told you so.
(Our answers are wrong.)
(Shouting)
What?
What is going on?
(The policemen hit them with flour.)
(We are safe.)
(Their faces turn white thanks to the flour.)
Ji Hyo.
How can you put flour in my eye?
(This thief becomes angry.)
(Her eyeball is especially white.)
- Is the answer sundae? - Seriously.
Trotter uses a Chinese letter for "Foot".
Bossam uses a Chinese letter for "Blanket".
Hotteok uses a Chinese letter for "Barbarian".
Porridge uses a Chinese letter for "Porridge".
We knew the answer, but there were four people left.
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Gook Ju succeed to get 1 point each.)
- The next one is a picture quiz. - That's good.
In the following picture,
- which person isn't present? - "Which person isn't present?"
- This is hard. - Number one, Song Ji Hyo.
Number 2, Song Hye Kyo. Number 3, Jun Ji Hyun.
Number 4, Lee Young Ae. Number 5, Kim Hye Soo.
The combined faces...
(My goodness.)
I think I am in love.
(His eyes go wide.)
(The combined faces are beautiful.)
She is in it.
Ji Hyo, are you in it or not?
- I don't know. - Ji Hyo is in it?
- How about Jun Ji Hyun? - Dance.
- Number three isn't present. - Dance.
Number three isn't present, is it?
- Jun Ji Hyun isn't present. - I don't have a clue.
Jun Ji Hyun isn't present.
Let's pick number three.
She isn't, right?
- Is Song Ji Hyo in it? Where? - Yes, she is.
She is in it.
(Both civilians and thieves think the answer is number 3.)
Number three.
Save me.
- You are in. - We are a group.
- Come here. - You are in.
I think number three is the answer.
(I think number 3 is the answer.)
I will count people in each group.
He latched onto us.
(Kwang Soo latches onto another group.)
- I will count people in each group. - He latched onto us.
- He latched onto us. - He latched onto us.
Kwang Soo latched onto us.
3, 3, 4, 2.
- For goodness' sake. - The answer is...
We might be right.
Number four, Lee Young Ae.
- Are you serious? - Our answer is correct.
(Our answer is correct.)
(It's time for a penalty.)
- Our answer is correct. - Our answer is correct.
- This is incredible. - It was pure luck.
- It's all thanks to Kwang Soo. - Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- Thank you. - Kwang Soo, thank you.
We got it right thanks to Kwang Soo.
Lee Young Ae isn't present.
- The combined faces are beautiful. - Seriously.
Doesn't the picture resemble Lee Young Ae?
Thus,
the winning couple is Yang Se Chan and Song Ji Hyo.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo win with 3 points.)
All right. We did it.
You keep moving further away.
- Why are you running away? - You keep moving further away.
(Was Kwang Soo's mistake a coincidence or a strategy?)
(The last platforms)
Se Chan and Ji Hyo,
please choose the two couples that will go up the last platforms.
We choose...
(Which couples are fated...)
(to go up the platforms?)
- We choose Haha and Dam Bi. - What?
- Okay. - Why?
(They decide to make Haha and Dam Bi go up the platform again.)
You know that I am not a thief, right?
- I know. - You know, right?
- Ji Hyo isn't a thief? - No.
- Are you sure? Why? - Yes.
I am the King.
(I am the King.)
Se Chan is the King.
(Is Se Chan the King?)
- Really? - Yes.
- You are the King. - Yes.
Serve me.
- I did a good job, right? - Are you serious?
I did a good job, right?
I also know who the Boss is.
The Boss.
(Who is the Boss?)
- Dam Bi. - I knew it.
(That's why he is making Dam Bi go up the platform again.)
Why would you go that?
We also choose...
- Jong Kook and... - Hey.
- Eun Su. - Okay. Fine.
- They know you are civilians. - Okay.
They know you are civilians.
- This is incredible. - Okay.
(It's a strategy to hide information about the King.)
This is huge.
- I will make the announcement. - Okay.
The third judgment revealed that...
(The result of the last judgment)
among the two couples...
(Is either Haha or Dam Bi the Boss...)
- Dam Bi. - I knew it.
(like Se Chan said?)
Among the two couples,
there are 1 thief and 1 Boss.
I knew it.
(Among the 2 couples, there are 1 thief and 1 Boss.)
(Either Haha or Dam Bi is the Boss.)
One of them is the Boss.
Who is the Boss?
You won't know until the very end.
We will have the final vote to arrest the Boss.
- The Boss. - We just need to catch the Boss.
Based on the results of the judgments,
vote for the person you think is the Boss.
Two people with the most votes will go up the platform.
The winning team will administer...
the water bomb penalty to the losing team.
If both the King and the Boss go up the platform,
the final match will determine the losing team.
If neither the King nor the Boss gets caught,
everyone will receive the water bomb penalty.
(Everyone will receive the water bomb penalty.)
Take the ballot.
Did you write down the name?
It's her, right?
Dam Bi? It's obvious.
- Hold on. - In that case,
whose name should we write down?
(Between Seok Jin, Gook Ju, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo, who is the King?)
Hold on. Hold on. Here is what I think.
(He is writing down Dam Bi's name.)
It's Haha.
- Isn't it Dam Bi? - It's Haha.
(The Boss is Haha.)
- Really? - It's Haha.
- Isn't it Dam Bi? - It's Haha.
(Is Haha the Boss?)
The King is Se Chan.
I don't know if it's true.
The King...
(They mumble so that the other team won't hear.)
- Did you talk to him? - Yes.
Did Se Chan say that he is the King?
- What? - Did Se Chan say that?
The King...
(The King...)
Seok Jin said that he is the King.
(Seok Jin said that he is the King.)
(Is Seok Jin the King?)
I am the King. Write Haha's name. He is the Boss.
(I am the King. Write Haha's name. He is the Boss.)
It's true. It's true.
- No way. - Trust me.
I am not kidding. It's true.
(Seok Jin says he is the King and Haha is the Boss.)
- He isn't the King. - This is driving me crazy.
- He told me that. - He isn't the King.
- What should I do? - Hold on. This is...
This is...
(Se Chan says Dam Bi is the Boss and Seok Jin says Haha is the Boss.)
- Dam Bi is the Boss. - Right?
(Who is telling the truth?)
Think about it.
- This is so confusing. - What is going on?
This is driving me crazy.
(The civilians become confused.)
Are you doing okay?
Stop saying that I am a thief.
(Among the 4 of them, there are 1 King and 1 thief.)
They are confused.
In that case...
- Among the four of you... - Trust him.
- What? - He is telling the truth.
Se Chan isn't the King.
He isn't the King. He is a thief.
- No, he isn't. - He is a thief.
- He is a thief. - Who am I supposed to trust?
This is confusing.
- Hold on. - You have 10 seconds.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
I am sorry.
- You have 10 seconds. - For goodness' sake.
- 10. - I wrote down Gook Ju.
I wrote like this.
No, this is right, Jae Seok.
No, I wrote this.
- Let's go. - Seven,
- six, - I wrote like this.
- It might be wrong. - I have no idea.
four,
three,
(Thieves don't have enough clue as they've lost the last game.)
two,
(What choice did civilians and thieves make?)
one!
Please submit your votes!
(Vote closed.)
- This is so hard. - Gosh.
- This is so tough. - We made a right decision.
How can you work together for so long with such a relationship?
(They all act so well.)
I'm so confused.
Two people with the largest number of votes will stand on the platform.
It's unbelievable.
(2 people with the largest number of votes will stand on the platform.)
We have people with 6 votes, 5 votes, and 1 vote.
- Who got one vote? - Who's that?
Who made that vote?
A thief must have made that vote.
I guess a thief must have made that one vote.
First, the one with the largest number of votes, six, is...
- It's Dam Bi. - I guess so.
(The suspects for a Boss are Haha and Dam Bi.)
- I'm the King. Haha is the Boss. - Same here.
Dam Bi, please go on the platform.
- This is crazy. - Gosh, it's crazy.
(Se Chan insisted that Dam Bi is a Boss.)
(10 seconds before the vote closed)
(Jae Seok wrote Haha for a Boss.)
(No, this is true.)
(Dam Bi's look on her face was so bad.)
The look on her face was so bad.
(Most of them insisted to trust Se Chan.)
(They changed their mind to write Dam Bi in the end.)
(The consensus was formed to write Dam Bi's name at last.)
I'm crazy
The one with the 2nd largest number of votes, 5, is...
(Who's going to stand on the platform next?)
(What's the thieves' choice between Seok Jin and Se Chan?)
Seok Jin, please go on the platform.
(Seok Jin is chosen.)
Look at his face.
(Thieves chose Seok Jin as a suspect for the King.)
This is...
(I hope we made a right choice.)
Let's take off Seok Jin's name tag...
- and check out the result. - All right.
- I mean... - Let's see it first.
- I might have goose bumps. - 1, 2...
(Is he a civilian who acted to deceive the thieves?)
(If Se Chan is the King, the thieves fail to find the King.)
(What's Seok Jin's identity?)
three.
(King)
(Seok Jin is the King.)
I told you!
(Is Seok Jin, not Se Chan, a King?)
(We caught a King.)
Let me join!
Ji Hyo, I told you!
I told you so many times.
(If Seok Jin is a King, what's Se Chan's identity?)
(Of course Se Chan is the only thief left.)
(In the end, Se Chan deceived everyone with his acting.)
I did it!
- You made it! - You certainly did it!
(A hidden mission was sent before the real race started.)
Today, we'll do Thieves Race in Don't Trust Them.
You're a Boss, the leader of thieves.
Am I a thief?
It was my dream when I was little.
I wanted to be a cool thief.
(The leader of thieves, a Boss, Haha)
Are four of us doing something?
We don't trust one another now.
It's such a weak combination, four of us.
- All of us are so weak. - I'm so...
Are we special or the others are special?
We're special in a strange way.
(4 weak thieves)
(The Boss and the thieves didn't know one another at first.)
(They ended up meeting one another on the platform.)
(The second judgment was the critical moment.)
(Haha is the Boss.)
(The only unidentified thief, Se Chan, started his action.)
(Because I am the King.)
(His game changer put the civilians into a trouble.)
(Your Majesty.)
(You must serve me.)
(Time for the last vote)
(Seok Jin)
(Now...)
(Se Chan gave me a look that it's Seok Jin.)
(Se Chan's intelligence made it possible to find Seok Jin.)
(I'm the King.)
(When he received the secret instruction...)
Actually, if we all found Haha, we could have won the game.
We were larger in number.
What's the use of it? Everyone wrote down Dam Bi's name.
- Everyone wrote down my name. - All wrote down Dam Bi's name.
- I'm pissed off. - We were such fools.
By the way, the King was so weak.
- A weak king. - He's so weak.
For your information, I was going to go behind Jong Kook,
but So Min insisted she would go behind him.
(Got caught)
I told her that now she even pours water on me.
- Then now you're going to get wet. - Okay.
All right.
(Water dropping)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean it. - Don't do it little by little.
- Don't do it little by little. - I really didn't mean it.
The bucket is so full, that's why.
(Team Thieves won the game, so they're pouring water.)
Is it cold, Gook Ju? My goodness.
- 1, 2, 3! - Go ahead!
(Pouring water)
(Water bomb makes them regret.)
(Screaming)
Well,
- Gook Ju, are you all right? - Yes.
You look like Undertaker.
(Undertaker, a professional wrestler is here all of a sudden.)
Now Undertaker...
Gook Ju.
Thank you for your effort, Gook Ju, Gyeong Ree,
- Eun Su, and Dam Bi. - Thank you for your effort!
This is amazing!
(Thank you for your effort, Dam Bi, Eun Su, Gook Ju, and Gyeong Ree.)
(Here we go at last.)
(Luxury Package, Switzerland)
(The magnificent view heals you just by looking at it.)
(It's really luxurious!)
(I'm a lucky boy.)
(The luck doesn't last long.)
(Team Luxury is in a crisis.)
(What on earth happened to them?)
(The hardest mission ever is disclosed.)
(They arrive there at last.)
(Shuddering Package, England)
(Out of all knowledge)
(Incomparable)
(Wing walking!)
(Forget everything you have experienced so far!)
(The hardest penalty ever!)
(The last battle for wing walking!) (The last chance for the exemption!)
(Who will stand on the wing?)
(So Min, you got your booger out.)
(A sudden journey)