- Hello. Hi. - Hi.
Haha, you should dance now.
Haha, come on.
(Humming a melody)
Haha, what's that outfit?
Haha, my gosh. What's up with your outfit?
My gosh, his outfit is terrible.
(He can't understand the outfit.)
Unbelievable.
- Did he wear that on purpose? - No, no.
- When Jong Kook saw Haha's outfit, - My gosh.
he seriously scolded him.
- I... - He really did.
I understand that Haha looks up to me,
but I had no idea he'd wear my Turbo outfit.
(Jong Kook, please keep your eyes on me.)
He can't make it obvious that he's brown-nosing Jong Kook.
Actually, the contestants on "High School Rapper"...
- wear this kind of outfit a lot. - That's true.
- People wear it on that show. - But he's not a high school rapper.
- He wants to look young. - He's not in high school.
My dream is becoming a high school student.
Did you see his hair earlier? A lot of his hair went gray.
(That dream isn't possible.)
- Stop it. - That's enough.
- Stop it. You might beat him up. - Listen.
- We didn't start today's filming. - I thought...
he played a game with flour. His hair went white.
- Hey, Se Chan. - What is it?
- You're copying Jong Kook now. - I am?
- I am? - Your outfit is black too.
- You should wear your own outfit. - So Min, you come here.
- Unbelievable. - The 4 of you make 1 team.
The 4 of you make 1 team.
- This is great. - I'm in.
- That's right. - I love this team.
- I like it. - This is great.
I'm the only girl.
How could she care about that now?
- Se Chan's outfit is neat. - I like this team.
Come on. Look at Jin Young.
- I looked at her earlier. - Look at me.
- You must look at me. - I looked at you a lot earlier.
I did.
- Only she can control Jong Kook. - I agree.
They make a great couple.
Kwang Soo went to a hair salon because we teased that he was ugly.
- Right. He got his hair done. - Where?
Where?
(I don't see any difference.)
What do you mean?
(He's utterly disappointed.)
How is it different?
What do you mean? You should see the difference straight away.
- I... - It's obvious.
I thought you were sleeping right before you came here.
- What? No. My hair is different. - You weren't sleeping?
I'm not wearing a hat.
Now, you do resemble Han Gi Beom.
- What's wrong with you? - You know who he is, right?
- He's the basketball player. - What's your deal?
You stupid beggar.
- Hey, why is he cursing so much? - You do resemble him.
This is ridiculous, but why is this so funny?
(He earns another nickname out of the blue.)
Let me recap regarding the stickers.
Oh, right. I forgot about the stickers.
Only two people, Jin Young and Jong Kook,
earned the Luxury Stickers two weeks in a row.
- Good for them. - They look like a couple.
Their outfits look similar.
2 people who earned the Shuddering Stickers 2 weeks in a row...
- are Sang Yeob and So Min. - My gosh.
- It's just the two of us? - We're like a couple too.
It's just the two of us.
Since it's beautiful springtime, we decided to shoot outdoors.
The race begins now. Tear off each other's name tags.
(Remove the name tags now.)
- What? - What's going on?
What's this?
(Remove the name tags from the start?)
(The Name Tag Elimination begins in the midst of their confusion.)
- Why? - Why?
- Why? Why? - What are we doing this?
(Jin Young is the 1st member to get a name tag.)
Why?
(Sang Yeob gets Jin Young's name tag when she's perplexed.)
- Hey. Hey. - Did you get it?
(Fast Han Na gets Slow Seok Jin's name tag first.)
Why is she so quick?
(Can you give me your name tag?)
- My gosh, Han Na. - Hey, Han Na.
Come here. You. You!
- You. - Go. I need to get the name tag.
Get hers.
(Kwang Soo tries to get Da Hee's name tag.)
Hey, Kwang Soo!
- You... - I got Da Hee's.
(The race ends.)
- I got two name tags. - Unbelievable.
(He's feeling confident.)
(The heat of the race doesn't subdue.)
(It's not over. Give me back my name tag.)
- Did you lose yours? - I lost mine. Look.
(What was this surprise game for?)
Raise your hands if you tore off someone's name tags.
- Sang Yeob has the most name tags. - Yes.
- The first member to remove one... - It's Jin Young.
was Jin Young. Play rock-paper-scissors to form teams.
We'll form a team?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to break into teams.
- I'm really bad at it. - Jin Young.
(If it's a 6-on-6, team match,)
(they must pick Jong Kook first.)
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jin Young wins.)
- I knew it. - I choose Jong Kook!
(She picks him right away.)
(I see.)
Go. Go now.
- Are you happy? You're happy? - Yes, I'm happy.
- Great. - He said...
he's happy.
- I have to choose too, right? - Yes.
He said he's happy.
Haha.
(Haha, join me.)
- Me? - Yes.
- Why me? - Come here. Come.
- Jin Young, please pick me. Please. - Seriously?
Please pick me. I will treat you with respect.
- Jin Young, pick me too. - Play rock-paper-scissors again.
- Sang Yeob. - Play rock-paper-scissors again.
(For some intelligible reason, he chooses Haha to defeat Jong Kook.)
- Listen. - What's his deal all of a sudden?
Don't we keep picking members?
- Should I pick guys first? - That's better.
- Yes. Se Chan? - Se Chan?
- You can do that. - We pick Se Chan.
- Okay. - Okay!
Okay!
- Hey. - I...
Hey, let me make my escape. You're in on this too?
- Be quiet. - Se Chan.
- I was joking. - Pick the dirty one.
- Kwang Soo. - Why me?
(No way.)
Let's play dirty!
- We need Kwang Soo. - Let's play dirty.
- This is Team Daema Island. - Let's go with that.
They will be Team Daema Island with Ji Hyo.
- We have to choose someone. - We need to pick.
- After that, we'll pick again. - Jae Seok.
- Hold on. - Okay.
- Hey, hold on. - Why are you happy?
- Jae Seok, you're with us. - The game is over.
It's over now.
We got Jae Seok and Jong Kook.
- We won. - It's over.
Get ready to get beaten up.
- Fight physically and verbally. - Hey, this is...
- Get ready to suffer. - You can choose now.
(You'd better watch out.)
- That's right. - They're like the shadows.
- I'll do my best to serve you. - Hey.
- Congratulations on escaping. - We'll be physical and verbal.
- It's over now. - Can I choose now?
So Min.
(What?)
- I pick her. - Why me? Why?
I need to do well this week.
I can't get a Shuddering Sticker this week.
You are in the same team as Sang Yeob.
- Why are you reacting this way? - Sang Yeob is in your team.
Sang Yeob will protect you.
- I will protect you. - That's right.
I am tired of Sang Yeob now.
(I am tired of Sang Yeob now.)
How did you get tired of him so soon?
That's so sudden.
- He didn't do anything. - I didn't do anything.
We will have members who pay dirty. Lee Da Hee.
- All right! - Me?
We will show you the dirtiest play.
Ji Hyo.
- Yes! - Is this like a love triangle?
I am sorry, sir.
Han Na, come here.
(Sang Yeob makes the strangest team by recruiting an eccentric member.)
This isn't bad.
- We have no other choice. - Let's go.
(Jin Young's Team and Sang Yeob's Team)
You will have a team competition today...
for Steal House and Get Out Race.
(Steal House and Get Out Race)
- Get Out? - Get Out?
There will be three rounds in total.
For each round, the winning team gets a Luxury Sticker,
and the losing team gets a Shuddering Sticker.
Let's get a Luxury Sticker today.
- We have to get it. - We have to get a Luxury Sticker.
The winning team also gets Get Out! Time to Steal...
in which they have a chance to get more Luxury Stickers.
Time to Steal?
In five minutes,
the winning team can steal an object from the losing team.
(The winning team can steal an object from the losing team.)
(They can steal anything in the house.)
If they succeed to move the object to their house,
they get another Luxury Sticker.
If they fail, they get a Shuddering Sticker.
However,
the object you steal must be bigger than the previous one.
(The object you steal must be bigger than the previous one.)
- It must be bigger. - It must be bigger.
You don't steal with the other team inside the house.
You get five minutes to steal an object.
Okay.
There is a hidden rule.
Each team will now choose three objects inside the house...
that are likely to get stolen by the other team...
and compile the Shuddering List.
If the other team steals an object on that list,
they get a Shuddering Sticker.
- Three objects. - This is hard.
It's a counterattack.
- This is hard. - I know.
It's a game of wits.
Now, choose 1 of the 2 Running Houses,
and write down three objects on the Shuddering List.
- Really? - Okay.
- Let's choose the nearer one. - We choose House A.
What? That's ridiculous.
We wanted House A as well.
We chose first.
- Our team has senior members. - That's right.
Please be understanding.
Gosh, they can't do that just because they are old.
- Please be understanding. - Who are you?
What do you mean? I am the youngest member.
Must you ask? I am the youngest member.
Wake up. You had better be on your guard today.
(The bold, youngest member enters House A.)
How many objects do we choose?
- 3? - 3.
There is a doll. Shouldn't it be on the list?
This doll.
We need to beware of trash cans.
A table.
The first object can be...
- Jae Seok. - How about a window?
- The first object can be a door. - How about a window?
- There is no bigger object. - That sliding door is heavy.
- It's heavy. Someone will get hurt. - It's heavy.
Does the curtain rod count?
- The curtain rod? - They measure an object's length.
Do you work in interior design?
- Do you work in interior design? - They have a business.
Are you the chief?
Yes, I am the chief.
(Ji Hyo designs a place of happiness.)
- I see. - This is...
I think a door is a good idea.
- A door. - A door.
It won't occur to them.
Will they be able to remove it in five minutes?
You know,
we are only thinking about the game. This house is rented.
- It's a damage to property. - It's okay.
- We can put it back. - We can put it back.
- It's okay. - The owner will be taken aback.
The production crew paid accordingly,
so the owner should understand.
Who are you to decide?
Don't tell the owner what they should understand.
Put yourself in the owner's shoes.
A variety show comes for a shoot...
and removes the door of your house.
- How would you feel? - How would you feel?
(Put yourself in the owner's shoes.)
Then I would ask for an additional 100 dollars.
(Then I would ask for an additional 100 dollars.)
It's something...
- the production crew can work out. - Really?
Yes, we should negotiate.
- It's not a big damage. - No, it's not.
It's not a damage.
Receiving more money will make the owner feel better.
Of course. The owner will feel much better.
- Stop being so intimidating. - What did I do?
You keep doing this.
Seriously.
(He flexes his muscles in an intimidating way.)
- Why did you take off your jacket? - It's a bit small for me.
You became strange ever since you joined "Mom's Diary".
- What's wrong with you? - What did I do?
I plan to become a problematic son.
(That's my goal.)
For goodness' sake.
The members of the other team are small-minded.
Their decision will be affected by their small minds.
- Hey. - There are more ladies there.
It takes a small-minded person to know a small-minded person.
- Seok Jin. - What?
Give us your insight.
- In my opinion... - He is small-minded.
It takes a small-minded person...
to know a small-minded person.
I will tell you what I would take.
The first object I would take is a blanket.
- A blanket. - It's light...
- and long. - That's right.
- I would definitely take a blanket. - You are small-minded.
I think they would take a mattress.
Or a blanket.
(Seok Jin was right.)
- A window. - A curtain.
- A window. - A window.
We can take a window.
- A window. - That's right.
- They wouldn't think about it. - No, they wouldn't.
- A window. - A window.
- It's easy to remove a window. - It's a must.
- They would take this. - Yes, they would.
We need to be careful. A curtain rod is easy to remove.
It's very big.
(Their thoughts are the same.)
If they are thinking about stealing big objects,
- we need them on the list. - I will visit them...
and see what they are doing.
That's a good idea.
- I will drop them a visit. - Are you serious?
- There is no point in worrying. - Drop them a visit.
Stay here. I will be back.
- Be brazen, okay? - Okay.
Ask them what they will steal.
(Fast as the wind)
(Invisible as the air)
(He plans to take a peek and run away.)
For goodness' sake.
You sure play dirty.
- Jae Seok! - I am not playing dirty.
He is the only member in that team...
- who plays dirty. - I am not playing dirty.
You should have tried to come quietly.
- No... - Since when were you here?
What do you mean?
I came here to borrow a spoon.
- Why would you borrow a spoon? - I want to eat noodles.
You eat noodles with chopsticks, not a spoon.
So this is your house.
Now that I am here, let me take a look inside.
- Where are you going? - Get out of the way.
- What do you think you are doing? - Go away.
Go away.
- Go away. - I can't believe him.
- You are unbelievable. - What do you think you are doing?
Get out of our house.
- Don't you know me? - What?
- I know you but... - Don't you know me?
I appear on TV.
Everyone here appears on TV.
Sweep the way for him.
- So Min, what are you doing? - I brought a spoon.
So Min, what are you doing?
You can go now.
I was going to give him chopsticks.
Gosh, you are heartless.
I am sorry to ask,
but may I have dinner here?
Jae Seok.
Kick this beggar out.
You gave me a spoon.
- May I have dinner here? - Give me back the spoon.
(You can take a cleaning tool instead.)
- You are so annoying, So Min. - Leave.
- For goodness' sake. - Bye.
(He fails spectacularly.)
We need to choose objects...
they are most likely to steal.
That's right.
- A window. - A window.
- That's right. - That curtain rod is too long.
That curtain rod...
- It's bigger than any object. - It will be exhausting to move.
This curtain rod...
- It must be 7m long. - It's really big.
(There is a high chance they will steal the curtain rod.)
I think they will steal the curtain.
The curtain is more likely than a blanket.
- It's really long. Look at this. - I know.
Let's put that on the list.
- Let's add that. - That's a good idea.
- It's long. - It's longer than the sofa.
- Shall we take a picture of it? - Shall we?
- Let's take a picture of it. - Put vacuum cleaner on the list.
- All right. They will take it. - I think they will take it.
- Okay. - All right.
(House A's Shuddering List)
(Curtain rod, curtain, and vacuum cleaner)
One of the objects on their list must be ordinary.
It could be the teddy bear.
Teddy bear? You want to put it on the list, right?
- Yes, I do. - It's on your mind, right?
I don't think they will steal the teddy bear.
I want to put it on the list because it's cute.
You have a kind heart.
That's right, Haha.
The teddy bear is on my mind.
- That's because you are innocent. - Shall we choose the teddy bear?
Give me a break.
(Give me a break.)
- Why are you feigning innocence? - The teddy bear is on my mind.
I want to choose the teddy bear.
I want to put the teddy bear on the list.
The teddy bear must be lonely outside.
It's scary to see Haha act that way in that outfit.
(A spirit in black that chases after teddy bears)
- He looks like a spirit. - Teddy bear! Teddy bear!
Someone should restrain his arms.
(Thank you for bringing my teddy bear.)
So Min, you brought the teddy bear!
For goodness' sake.
Will you lay it down?
(Do you want to lie down?)
So Min, the teddy bear is cold.
- I will bring a blanket. - Bring a pillow, too.
Give me a break.
(Give me a break!)
Don't kick the teddy bear.
We don't have time for this.
Are we really putting it on the list?
- What's the purpose of this? - It's cute.
- What? - It became cute.
It will confuse the other team.
They will think about what this means.
Do this, and put the teddy bear on the list.
- Okay. - They will think it's a trap.
- We will use that. - Will it be the teddy bear...
Shall we do this and put a blanket on the list?
Let's put something on its paw.
I vote for the teddy bear.
Why are you suddenly voting for the teddy bear?
- You were against it. - What made you change your mind?
It's really cute.
What's wrong with you?
(Forget your innocence.)
Have you gone crazy?
What's wrong with you?
She hates you.
(From this moment on, we are bear hunters.)
(Which objects are on House B's Shuddering List?)
Each team chose three objects...
and turned in the list.
It's obvious what they chose.
They probably chose whatever objects they saw first.
- A refrigerator. - That's right.
- We... - Tell us.
(Suddenly)
I can estimate the size.
No way.
- Is it about this big? - Can we carry it like this?
It's about this big.
It's something that you can show.
Here's a hint.
Basically,
- if you were to carry it... - You won't give us a hint.
(He doesn't believe Kwang Soo.)
That's nonsense.
- You wouldn't give any. - It was funny.
I have to say something.
You should go home while you still can.
You're not in good shape.
- Listen to Jae Seok. - Goodness.
It's because he's on Jong Kook's team.
I have nothing to fear here.
- Hey. - You punks.
Calm down.
- He suddenly seems strong. - Seriously.
- Even his legs look big. - He seems strong.
- Let me borrow your shoulder. - Hey.
- We're the boss. - Let me borrow your shoulder.
- You'd better watch out. - Watch out.
- How dare you? - Be careful of your glasses.
- Watch out. - Say what's wrong.
- What about our glasses? - Be careful.
His kick looks higher.
He looks more flexible today.
- By the way, So Min. - Yes?
- You have eye booger. - Where?
(Jae Seok acts friendly.)
(She isn't embarrassed after 2 years of being on Running Man.)
It's off now.
It was booger from her nose.
It was eye booger.
So Min has...
dead skin on her feet. She has boogers in her eyes.
- She also farts. - Did she fart?
- No, I didn't. - We were talking...
with So Min while sitting on a blanket in the waiting room.
Suddenly, she made a noise.
(There's a sound from So Min.)
- Really? - She let it go easily.
I pretended not to hear it.
That sound is from this song.
(Singing)
Fatsia shoots are seasonal in the spring.
The sound was very cute.
- It was cute. - Goodness.
Here's the first mission.
It's called Tactless Quiz.
(Tactless Quiz)
Three members from each team will participate.
One team answers while the other team distracts.
Then the roles switch.
The teams listen to the question. Make a guess out of five choices.
You stand up when a sound is given.
If the number of standing members equals to the answer,
the team that answers earns a point.
If they don't equal, the distracting team earns a point.
However, if no one stands up...
or everyone stands up,
the answering team gets a chance to answer the question.
The team with more points...
wins a Luxury Sticker and a chance to steal at the opponent's house.
The losing team gets a Shuddering Sticker.
(The losing team gets a Shuddering Sticker.)
We must win.
- Seriously. - Let's do it.
You seriously won't.
We have an advantage.
We have many smart members, don't we?
- Smart? - We have many smart members.
- Who's smart? - There's Han Na.
Compared to the other team, we're definitely smarter.
Definitely.
Has anyone led the class?
- I have. - I was also the school president.
- I was the school president. - I was too.
- I was the school president. - I was physical education leader.
- I was the class president once. - I did accounting.
- Accounting? - Accounting?
(She brings up accounting.)
- Accounting sounds good. - That's right.
- You lead. - Okay.
- Listen. - I approve of accounting.
- Was anyone a class president? - I was physical education leader.
- Was anyone a class president? - You sit down.
- You sit down. - Class president, sit here.
- Basically, - It was in elementary school.
that team is too ambitious.
- Them? - They're full of ambitions.
It isn't such a big deal.
No one is doing it for the team.
- We only want attention. - Goodness.
We have to win the first game no matter what.
- We have to play until the end. - It's easy to win.
- Get ready. Here we go. - It could be difficult.
(Team Pink wins a point if they answer correctly.)
It's a mountain famous for 12,000 peaks.
Its name differs...
based on four seasons.
Which is not a name of this mountain?
- This is so easy. - I like this.
- Okay. - It's so easy.
Number one, Kumkang Mountain.
That's right.
Number two, Bongrae Mountain.
- Okay. - Right.
Number three, Kooknae Mountain.
(What's Kooknae Mountain?)
Number four, Pungak Mountain.
Number five, Gaegol Mountain.
Gosh.
I learned this a long time ago.
It was a long time ago, but I remember all.
- I don't know. - The one that isn't...
- or is? - They don't know the answer.
(They're shocked.)
- What? - Which is it?
- The correct name? - No.
The one that isn't?
Excuse me. I have a question.
How do you spell Gaegol Mountain?
(She's serious about her question.)
- Just imagine the spelling. - It's Gaegol.
(Why is that important?)
- It's G-A-E-G-O-L. - I see.
Gaegol Mountain is wrong.
Which number was it?
It's number five. Gaegol Mountain doesn't exist.
- What was the spelling? - Isn't it number three?
- Isn't it Kooknae Mountain? - No.
- When they say Foreign Mountain... - In the past,
they asked what was something that always spun.
The answer was a bear, which is nonsense.
Kooknae Mountain sounds suspicious, but that may be wrong.
That's why Gaegol Mountain is the answer.
(Is that so?)
- I don't think they know. - No.
- I don't think they know. - I don't think so.
What should we do?
- I think this is it. - Right.
Let's do this.
- You and me. - Okay.
We need to distract them,
but no one knows the answer.
(What's Team Green's answer?)
- Okay. - Stand in the count of three.
- Okay. - I'm not sure if it's right.
1, 2.
(If it's not 3, Team Green earns a point.)
(What's the result?)
Three.
(Team Pink fails to answer.)
I knew it.
(Team Pink's answer is Bongrae Mountain.)
Number two, Bongrae Mountain.
It's incorrect. What's the correct answer?
Number five, Gaegol Mountain.
(She's sure of herself.)
The answer is Kooknae Mountain.
(The answer is number 3.)
- I told you. - You were wrong.
It was Kooknae Mountain.
- I knew it. - What did you listen to Da Hee?
Come on.
How could you? You deserve respect.
What have you done, So Min?
- Only I told the truth. - Han Na.
I thought it was strange.
I didn't expect much from the other two.
How can you say that?
- They thought it existed. - I know that much.
- Me too. - That was cheeky.
No one said anything about the answer except Da Hee.
- We said something. - No way.
Didn't you know?
Da Hee.
- We had to answer simultaneously. - What?
- No. - They didn't know the answer.
Right.
They thought that number five was the answer.
That's frustrating.
Let's play again. The roles switch.
Shall we change? Have a seat.
- Jin Young and Ji Hyo. - Shall we?
Has anyone gotten all As?
- I haven't gotten all As. - Not all A's.
I'm sure someone scored 2 in math.
- What? Who? - Two points in math.
Did anyone score two points in math?
- I scored 4. - 4?
I'm sorry.
- My score was 7. - Stop it.
- Are you looking down on us? - Why did you bring that up?
I shouldn't have said it.
I cried after scoring four points during the college entrance exam.
(Did Jae Seok score low too?)
You can score higher than four even if you guess.
I cried after scoring four points.
I went to the movies after scoring four points.
Your grades aren't everything.
- Right. - I'm serious.
Despite that, he became a great man.
Studying isn't for everyone.
- Right. - That's right.
- Studying is an inborn talent. - Of course.
- One is born with such a talent. - Right.
- Here's the next question. - Let's go.
It's a question for fourth graders.
- It'll be so easy. - Okay.
I was smart until then.
Among numbers that round up to 70,
what's the largest natural number?
Number 1, 72. Number 2, 73. Number 3, 74. Number 4, 75. Number 5, 76.
Is it for fourth graders?
- Natural number? - Yes.
What's this?
- How can a number round up to 70? - Isn't it too hard?
- Isn't it too harsh? - Wait.
- It has to be from 75. - I know.
When rounded up, it becomes 80.
- A natural number? - It's 74.
It's 74.
- Is that right? - Yes.
- Isn't it 74? - Is that the largest?
- It's 74 because... - It has to round up to 74.
- What's a natural number? - It's 74.
Let me ask the other team.
Do you know what a natural number is?
(Who do you think we are?)
- Are you doing that on purpose? - Tell us.
What's a natural number?
Naturally...
(Naturally, it is...)
"Naturally"?
- "Naturally". - Look at them.
Da Hee said...
Don't say it.
- I won't say it. - What did she say?
I asked her what a natural number was.
"There's such a thing?"
Da Hee.
- No, stop it. - Okay.
It's because she started working when she was young.
- It's possible not to know. - What did you say?
While others were studying...
- Haha. - What are you talking about?
- Da Hee is crying. - I'm sorry.
She's a good person.
She really is.
- She's good at... - Right.
long jumps.
She's good at jumping.
It's okay as long as I'm kind.
It's nothing embarrassing.
- Are you ready? - A number that's...
Shouldn't we answer this correctly?
- What's a natural number? - I thought about it too.
- This is the most convincing. - A natural number is...
(It's the team that distracts.)
- They think we know the answer. - Right.
(At least, one person will stand.)
Listen. I'll talk in numbers.
- Do this... - Right.
- or this. - Okay.
- No, I pick this. - I pick the first.
- Me too. - Really? Okay.
- Okay. - Okay?
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- I'm certain. - Let's go.
- Stand up in three. - Okay.
Let's go!
1, 2, 3.
(Team Pink, who must distract, may fail.)
Okay.
- All right. - They stood up.
(What really happened?)
(Standing up)
(Da Hee suddenly stands up.)
Why did you stand up?
- Did she stand up later? - What?
- No. - What's wrong?
Why did you do it?
- You said you'd sit. - Isn't it over?
- Is it 75? - No.
No.
- No, the answer is number 3, 74. - Okay.
We almost lost it.
Did you think that number four was the answer?
Wait, Da Hee.
- We didn't check. - Wait.
That's not it.
She didn't stand up, right?
(He interrupts.)
She didn't stand up.
- She didn't stand up. - She did.
She got up.
- She got up. - What's with you?
She got up? I just wanted to double-check.
- She got up. - Stay out of it.
She got up.
- She didn't get up. - You didn't get up, did you?
- She didn't. - Why did you get up?
- Aren't we supposed to answer? - Go see the sea.
- He's acting strange. - Go dig some cockles.
- Stay there for a while. - What's with him?
Stay there.
- Calm down. - Collect yourself.
Good.
We knew Da Hee would get up.
- I... - Well...
- I just don't understand. - We kept saying...
it was either 0 or 3.
- The thing is... - We knew the answer.
We agreed on zero.
The only explanation is that she's a spy.
I'm really sorry,
but I thought the other team was going to answer.
- So I was watching... - It's like the Zero Game.
- She got confused. - We agreed on not getting up.
Anyway, thank you, Da Hee.
- Did you drink last night? - No, I don't drink.
- Seriously... - Da Hee.
- Do you want to attract attention? - No.
- I don't want to. - Be honest.
- I really don't. - Tell us the truth.
- It doesn't make sense. - I'll just stay quiet.
- I can't do this. - Can you get down on the ground?
- Can you get down on the ground? - Okay.
I'm sorry. I mean it.
(What did I do?)
Get down on the ground for a moment.
Can we arrest a spy now if there even is one?
I mean it.
I understand it now. I'll stay quiet.
- We could have a spy today too. - I'm not a spy.
Da Hee's cap has the same color as our uniform.
(Da Hee is wearing a pink cap.)
No.
(She throws her cap on the ground.)
(Da Hee explodes for the 3rd week in a row.)
Please trust me this once.
I can do better.
She's been acting suspiciously since last week.
If we say something, she cries.
No, I won't cry. I'll work hard.
You better not cry right now.
Haha's cap is impossible to read.
(Which team am I on?)
- That's right. - He can be on either team.
- All right. - I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry. - She's crying.
- No, I'm not. - This time,
Se Chan and Seok Jin will play.
Okay.
Let's just leave it to luck.
- Should guys try? - Only guys.
- Only guys. - Okay.
This question can be a bit tricky.
- It'll be tricky. - Okay.
Which of the following terms is not related to beverages?
- Beverages? - Beverages?
Number one, brewmaster.
Number two, barista.
Number three, digerati.
Number four, negociant.
Number five, sommelier.
A digerati must be someone who makes desserts.
It seems so.
Negociant?
It must have something to do with "Hometown Report".
That's right.
Or "this is my place."
- I love that. - "Hometown Report".
- That's what it means. - "Digerati" means "drop dead".
(What?)
No.
- What did you say? - Nothing.
What are you doing?
I thought she swore.
- I thought she swore. - I thought she swore.
- Did you mean "digerati"? - It's number three.
I just read number three.
I was so surprised.
- Digerati. - Gosh.
- I think this is the answer. - Yes.
(Number 3, digerati)
- Okay. - I think so too.
Then...
We should all get up.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Why are you three sitting?
Only one person is answering.
(It's not like that.)
- Are you robots? - No.
- Are you robots? - It's not like that.
Are you avatars?
Avatars?
- What are you saying? - Are you just...
- his flags? - Avatars?
Gosh. Avatars?
Don't be absurd. What are you talking about?
We're not listening to him.
Do as Seok Jin said.
We should, right? Okay.
- Look at him. - He's happy.
- He can do what he wants. - "I was right."
Without realizing...
If they don't know, they'll go for this.
- They'll go for this. - Yes.
Let's go for that.
What about this?
Okay. Let's do that.
- Team Green, are you ready? - You...
You get up. Yes.
Here we go. One...
1, 2, 3.
(If they answer correctly, Team Pink will earn 1 point.)
(What's the result?)
(5 people stand up.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Number 5, sommelier is obviously wrong.)
- Good job. - Well done.
- Why did you get up? - Why did you get up?
- You said we'd leave it to luck. - Why did you get up?
- You said we'd take a chance. - Why didn't you get up?
- Why didn't you get up? - We should have all gotten up.
- Exactly. - Why didn't you get up?
Number five, sommelier, is wrong.
The correct answer is number three, digerati.
- Is it someone who makes desserts? - That was right.
It must be related to desserts.
The word, derived from "digital" and "literati",
- means the elite of digitalization. - No cakes?
- No cakes? - No desserts?
- No desserts. - No cakes.
(Team Green gets ahead by luck.)
1, 2, 3.
- Okay. - Okay.
(But Jong Kook's robots catch up and win.)
- We win! - See?
I was right!
Team Pink wins a Luxury Sticker.
(1 Luxury Sticker goes to Team Pink.)
A Shuddering Sticker for you.
Well done.
(The winning team has another benefit.)
As I informed you earlier,
Team Pink can play Get Out! Time to Steal.
(They can win another Luxury Sticker.)
Steal and move one item from Team Green's house...
to your house within five minutes for another Luxury Sticker.
Okay.
If you fail to steal something or the stolen item is on the list,
you'll get a Shuddering Sticker.
- You'll get a Shuddering Sticker. - Okay.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Forget about it.
When the whistle is blown,
- your five minutes starts. - Okay.
Ready.
Let's go!
- We don't have much time. - Let's get it!
Let's get it!
(They enter Team Green's house.)
Guys.
(What is this?)
They put some things together here.
Well...
(The teddy bear definitely looks suspicious.)
(It's almost asking to be stolen.)
They're in the house now.
They're inside.
They might pick up information from our conversation.
Not this.
Guys.
The window.
Let's take it.
I think it'll be safe.
(The window?)
Let's go.
- That one? - Let's go.
- What's that? - What's that?
- It's the window. - It's the window.
Look at their faces. They don't look happy.
(There's a story behind the window.)
(2 hours ago, they were writing the list.)
(The window was included at first,)
(but it was taken away at the last minute.)
It's probably not on the list.
We have some time left. Let's see.
- Let's go. - Have you decided?
- Yes. - Gosh.
(Disappointed)
Come here!
- Okay. - At the last minute...
You changed it?
(They've stolen a window.)
Here we go.
(It's been 1 minute and 30 seconds.)
Okay.
(Screaming)
We should all just die.
I'm so angry.
They seemed surprised.
It was probably on their minds.
They seemed very frustrated.
They probably included it in the list...
- and then took it away. - At the last minute.
- Yes. - They changed their minds.
Are they done?
- Not yet. - No?
They're watching us.
We should act.
Keep smiling.
Some of us should smile.
- They're acting. - No.
- They are. - They are.
They're acting.
Stay still.
(They try to look suspicious.)
- It's a mind game. - Should we change?
No.
- Is it done? - Is time up?
(Cheering)
- Wait. - I think they mean it.
- He's acting. - We're acting.
- Exactly. - We're acting.
- Keep acting. - Gosh.
That was too obvious.
Time is not up yet.
Let's get something else. They mean it.
- They do? - I'm sure.
- It's on the list. - Should we get something else?
- They mean it. - Should we change our minds?
- I'm sure. - Get something else.
- Get something else! - Hurry up!
- Don't put on your shoes! - Hurry!
- They bought it. - We tricked them.
Gosh!
- What are you doing? - Time is up!
- What are you doing? - Time's up!
Teddy bear.
Let's take the teddy bear.
(Team Pink takes the teddy bear instead.)
Time is up!
Time is up, Ji Hyo!
No. We have 30 seconds left.
(It's stolen.)
Good job. We have three seconds left.
My teddy bear!
Gosh.
(Is the teddy bear on the list?)
Team Pink stole the teddy bear...
within five minutes.
The teddy bear...
(Is it on the list?)
Is...
Not on the list.
(They succeed.)
You get another Luxury Sticker.
(Team Pink stole the teddy bear.)
Will they steal the teddy bear?
I don't think they'll touch it.
(They removed the teddy bear from the list.)
(That was close.)
We did it.
You should take something ordinary.
Something ordinary.
(Team Pink wins another Luxury Sticker.)
Let's move to another place for the next mission.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
I have a good feeling.
We have 2 Luxury Stickers, and they have 1 Shuddering Sticker.
One member from each team...
will move together.
Please decide the order now.
- Okay. - Will there be a vote?
- What vote? - To find a spy?
We have two stickers right now.
We could vote who should get the stickers.
They have two Luxury Stickers.
We have one Shuddering Sticker.
- Then why don't we... - Should we just go in order?
- Go in order. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. - Okay.
- Should we do that? Sure. - Let's do that.
(It only takes them 10 seconds to decide.)
Which members will go first?
- I'll be first from Team Pink. - Okay.
- Make it interesting. - Then I'll go first.
(Wait, Han Na will join me?)
(Does this mean...)
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Let's go. - "Let's go."
- She sounded too business-like. - I know.
- Han Na is strong, - Yes?
and you're weak.
(We hope it works out with her.)
- "You're weak." - What do you think it is?
- Our team thought it'd be a vote. - A vote?
Which two members will take the Luxury Stickers?
- Se Chan. - What's that?
- I see a roulette. - Seriously?
(She exercises her reasoning skill.)
(Han Na turns into a detective after spotting a mysterious roulette.)
- I see a roulette. - Seriously?
- No, we need to go up. - I see.
- My gosh. That looked like it. - You're a terrible detective.
We have to take the stairs.
- Come on, Han Na. - Be careful.
- What's that? - What's this?
- Yes! - It's time for our lunch.
(It's time for our lunch.)
(Today's lunch is rice,)
(stir-fried sausages and vegetables, steamed eggs,)
(stir-fried spicy pork,)
(dried laver, kimchi,)
(lettuce,)
(and seaweed soup.)
- Can we eat? - Can we eat now?
Aren't you hungry?
- Yes. I'm starving. - Yes.
Now, you'll do a mission, and your lunch is at stake.
I will tell you the rules of Get the Dish! Time to Steal.
Each member will choose a dish that they want in order.
Overlapped dishes will be taken out after everyone has picked a dish.
A point will be accumulated per remaining dish.
You can have your lunch with only the remaining dishes.
The team with higher points will receive a Luxury Sticker...
and time to steal.
The losing team will receive a Shuddering Sticker.
(The losing team will receive a Shuddering Sticker.)
This is crazy.
Everyone will choose the stir-fried spicy pork and sausages.
My hunger is clouding my judgement even more.
I knew it. You wouldn't let us eat in peace.
I want to eat everything. What should I do?
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
But Jong Kook won't like any of these dishes.
I'll be quick...
(Meanwhile, Han Na from Team Green...)
- I'll choose stir-fried spicy pork. - Stir-fried spicy pork?
- Are you sure? - Yes.
I think a lot of people will choose that dish.
I think that's why people won't choose that dish.
I did some detective work.
Here she goes again. She's bad at that.
If I were to speculate,
I will take a big portion of the stir-fried spicy pork...
so that everyone can enjoy this. I'll take a lot.
My gosh, I'm so torn.
- They will try to guess your dish. - Right.
- Right. I'm weak. - They will do that.
- You're not weak. - When they think of me,
my image is closer to lettuce.
- Is that so? - We can't choose the same dish.
I will take lettuce.
- You chose your dishes, right? - Yes.
- You can go to your tables. - Okay.
- This is driving me crazy. - I don't know about this.
I wonder which dish Han Na took.
My gosh, your team will have a hard time guessing.
I'm in trouble. I shouldn't have come second.
(Team Green is swarming with members who are prone to betray.)
I get the feeling Kwang Soo will choose spicy pork.
Haha and Sang Yeob will choose the same dish.
- Right. - So Min will choose that too.
Everyone who's ambitious will choose stir-fried spicy pork.
I am worried about my team.
To be honest, we didn't see eye to eye earlier.
I can't trust my team.
Seriously, So Min. Your team can be a handful.
- Yes! - Okay.
Ji Hyo, I knew you'd pick that.
- He really did. - Did you know I'd get dried laver?
- Of course, I did. - It's true.
- I knew you'd choose that. - Han Na.
- You got the pork? - We didn't get the same one.
But Kwang Soo will definitely pick that one.
But he might not choose this because everyone expects that.
No, he doesn't think like that.
- He just takes what he wants. - Really?
- He doesn't think? - No, he doesn't.
(He never thinks about that.)
He doesn't do that?
I hope Kwang Soo can be smart and bring rice.
I think Jong Kook will bring...
- The eggs. A healthy dish. - Right.
- Will he bring lettuce? - No, no.
I think he will probably pick steamed eggs...
(I don't think so.)
- Our dishes can't overlap. - If they do, we'll take them out.
- Is rice part of this too? - Yes, it is.
People might not choose steamed eggs because...
- they might think I will. - That makes sense.
I'll choose steamed eggs!
(This is Jong Kook's reasoning.)
(Just like Ji Hyo predicted, Jong Kook chooses steamed eggs.)
I can just eat this.
(The plates fly away with the wind.)
Hey, you fool!
If you took one, you should've placed the stone on top.
Why are you so selfish?
(Jong Kook scolds Kwang Soo.)
You only play a considerate cop which I don't know how it happened.
(It's his first time being scolded for playing a nice cop.)
But you only think about yourself.
I wasn't going to come third.
What are you talking about?
Get your food. Take a lot of food.
If the dishes don't overlap, everyone will get their own dish.
(You don't need to take a lot.)
That's why I took a lot.
(You should've told me that earlier.)
- I thought they were bricks. - If the dishes don't overlap,
- we'll give you more. - No wonder.
If he eats that much, he will lay eggs.
(What if he lays eggs?)
(I didn't know.)
(What did Kwang Soo, who doesn't use his reasoning skills, choose?)
The main dishes are the spicy pork and sausages.
That's so disappointing. I really want to eat the sausages.
I'm sure Kwang Soo will bring us sausages.
In my opinion, Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob...
will bring the sausages and spicy pork.
- They're coming. - They're coming.
(Jong Kook is here.)
- Did you bring rice? What is it? - My gosh, Se Chan.
(3 of Team Pink's dishes don't overlap.)
- I didn't think you'd get that. - Is that rice?
You got steamed eggs, right?
(Team Green's dishes won't overlap if it's not spicy pork or lettuce.)
Please.
Kwang Soo!
(Which dish did Kwang Soo choose?)
- Is that spicy pork? - I told you.
(No way that's spicy pork.)
(Yes, it's the stir-fried spicy pork again.)
I told you. You lost the stir-fried spicy pork.
- Okay! - I told you he'd bring that.
I told you so.
We can't eat the pork now.
See? I told you.
I knew that he'd bring the dish he wants to eat.
- You wanted to eat that, right? - All right.
- Take out the spicy pork. - I really like meat.
- He even brought a big portion. - I thought about it and took this.
(Poor you. We secured all three dishes.)
- I should've brought dried laver. - So Min should have...
- If we're going to lose this... - So Min, you can't eat now.
Hey, hey, hey. What do you think you're doing?
(Licking)
You tasted the sauce. Lucky you.
(Let me smell it at least.)
Kwang Soo, you can't do that.
(My gosh, my spicy pork.)
- Seok Jin has to bring rice. - If you think about it,
the oldest must bring us rice. He's providing us the staple.
Here's what I think. The rest of our teammates will bring...
spicy pork, spicy pork, spicy pork, and sausages.
Right? Da Hee seems like...
the very competitive type. She wants to win.
- She needs to be in the spotlight. - She must be in the spotlight.
To be in the spotlight, she has to bring the spicy pork.
It's time for the spicy pork.
I bet...
(Da Hee hovers around the spicy pork.)
I bet people before you took it.
But that might be why people might not have taken this dish.
Spicy pork. You're craving spicy pork, right?
I really want to eat it.
Today...
No, I shouldn't follow my instincts today.
(I really want the spicy pork, but I mustn't follow my instincts.)
Here they come.
- Da Hee, what did you bring? - Which dish is it?
(Da Hee chose another dish.)
- Please. - What about you, Seok Jin?
(They still have a shot.)
What did you bring, Da Hee?
(They still have a shot to catch up as long as it's not lettuce.)
(What? What is that?)
Please.
What did you bring, Da Hee?
(What was that face just now?)
So Min, I don't think you and I can get along.
- Lettuce? - It must be the lettuce.
(Out of all the dishes, she had to choose the lettuce.)
(Team Green has 0 dish now.)
- We don't have to eat lettuce. - Yes, it's out.
- That's all right. - We won't just eat this.
- We still have two more shots. - But we will get the sticker.
We still have two more members. It's all right.
- Their dishes will overlap too. - You didn't bring two, right?
- What did you bring, Seok Jin? Why? - We still have two more members.
- My goodness. - Why?
What did you bring, Seok Jin? His plate must be light.
(Team Pink wanted rice. Which dish did Seok Jin bring?)
Tell us.
Hey, we're awesome.
(They succeed 4 times in a row. It's rice!)
(They don't overlap miraculously 4 times in a row.)
Look. Didn't I tell you?
- I said the oldest will bring rice. - It's because...
- we need to have rice. - I told you so.
This is awesome.
- It's over. - I got goosebumps when I saw this.
- We lost, right? - No, no.
It's tied if ours don't overlap and theirs overlap.
It's not over yet.
(Where did we go wrong?)
- I mean... - If Haha brings that, he's a hero.
- My gosh, this is crazy. - Someone probably took the pork.
- Who's left in your team? - It's Sang Yeob.
- I see. He's unpredictable. - Right.
He might bring the spicy pork.
- I should've brought the sausages. - Just bring sausages.
- I really wanted to eat sausages. - Please bring sausages.
(It'd be nice if he picks sausages.)
- I'll take this. - Me too.
- You won't regret it, right? - No.
I wanted to take the other dish.
Someone probably already took it.
- It could be tied. - It might be sausages or rice.
(Depending on their dishes, the game could be tied.)
Please. We don't need lettuce.
Please, Jae Seok.
- What is it? - What did you bring?
It seems light. It's not spicy pork.
Why? Why? Did a lot of you choose spicy pork?
- What did you bring? - Is it pork? It's red!
- It's lettuce. - What is it?
(He brought something red. Did he bring spicy pork?)
- What is it? - It's red!
Kimchi.
(I got you, didn't I? It's kimchi, not the stir-fried spicy pork.)
(We didn't overlap this time again!)
- Good job. - Sang Yeob.
- Great job. - Okay.
- Their dishes must overlap now. - I thought...
- Their dishes must overlap now. - It's Jae Seok.
- It has to. - It must be sausages or spicy pork.
- Please. - Kimchi will be good too.
Or the seaweed soup.
- Overlap 1 more dish. - Jae Seok, 1 more dish.
- Please. - You brought what you like, right?
My gosh, the rice...
(What does this mean?)
- He's a moth too. - Hey, Grasshopper.
What is it, Jae Seok?
(If it overlaps, it will be 2 to 2 and tied.)
- He must've brought rice. - Is it rice?
- My gosh, the rice... - He must've brought rice.
- Is it rice? - No, he brought a delicious dish.
I should've gotten the spicy pork.
(Feeling disappointed)
(He chose seaweed soup which doesn't overlap.)
What is it?
- It's soup. - What?
(The soup doesn't overlap.)
Spicy pork.
- What is it? - Bring it.
You should've brought spicy pork.
(They're disappointed.)
Why did we bring so much?
(Feeling hopeless)
Why did our dishes overlap so much?
I should've brought spicy pork.
- I thought someone took some. - I know.
Everyone thought so.
The dishes don't overlap.
- I know. - I'm so happy.
- We still won. - We definitely won.
We did. I knew it.
(We knew it.)
It's about teamwork.
- We can't do it. - Teams without teamwork can't.
(They give up.)
Remove the dishes that overlap.
Remove two rice.
(Team Pink earns one Luxury Sticker.)
That's for that team.
(Steamed eggs and kimchi come.)
This is unbelievable.
We aren't learning about history. What's this?
- Can you give us more steamed eggs? - They aren't enough.
- Goodness. - Lunch is served
Lunch is served to you
- Start playing the music - Goodness.
Play music
(What did you say?)
Play music for us while we eat delicious food
- Play music - Play music
- Let's eat quietly. - Okay.
Why is the rice so sweet?
- It's sweet, it's so sweet - It's sweet, it's so sweet
- Rice is so sweet - It's so sweet
(I can't take it anymore.)
There's a dish for each person.
Hey, Han Na.
(She steals some sausages to take revenge.)
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
(I'm sorry. I won't steal it.)
Goodness, Jae Seok.
- That's nice of you. - Hey.
What is it?
(He gives some to So Min.)
Wait a minute.
(She takes a bite.)
(What's wrong?)
Come on. Hey, hey.
Look at her. Hey.
(Kwang Soo eats this time.)
(Give me back my sausage.)
Stop it, Kwang Soo.
(She eats it herself.)
- Han Na is weird. - You'll be scolded.
(You like to steal and eat.)
What's wrong with her?
- How is it... - It's so delicious.
How is it so delicious?
- Seriously. - I'm not kidding.
How could it...
Can you give us a wrap?
- Yes. - What do we have to do?
Those who can sing may sing.
(We're willing to listen.)
(Goodbye)
What did you say?
(Forget everything)
- The lyrics are wrong. - You should sing.
Be serious about singing.
If you sing seriously...
(Kwang Soo sings seriously.)
(I was taken somewhere, and when I opened my eyes)
(He's quite serious.)
- He sings well. - Stand up and sing.
(He suddenly stands up.)
(Everyone joins.)
(To get at least a grain of rice...)
Everyone is singing.
(The whole team stands up because they're hungry.)
You're not in harmony.
Are they singing the same song?
You should sing in sync.
(With the current)
(Let the harmony flow)
(Forget harmonizing)
(From the start)
(They sing in chorus.)
(Spicy pork, your existence)
(Sausages, you didn't exist)
(Rice, as I wasn't in your life)
I'll give this to someone who sings with desperation.
(Sing with desperation.)
With desperation.
(They're all desperate.)
(As hungry as I was)
Seriously.
(Someday)
(I'm more desperate.)
Keep singing.
(I must eat the wrap)
(For myself who must eat the wrap)
- How about dance music? - Dance music is the best.
(Sing a dance music.)
- Dance. - Dance music is fun.
If not, I'll eat it.
5, 4, 3.
(Here comes a dance song.)
(Barefooted youth)
(Chanting)
(However, I won't stop here)
(Here we go, give us a wrap.)
- That was great. - Sang Yeob did the best.
All right.
- Sang Yeob. - This one was good.
I sang an entire song.
Sang Yeob did it better than you.
- What? - He did better.
(The wrap is delicious.)
I wrapped sausage and spicy pork.
I washed my hands beforehand.
So Min.
(She dances without music.)
That's not dance music.
(I'll help you out, So Min.)
(He sings for So Min.)
- Keep dancing. - Come here.
(There's no wrap with discount in this world.)
(Goodness, Jae Seok.)
(Give me the wrap.)
(Laughing)
You have to earn it.
(Try eating this wrap.)
(While he gives the wrap,)
(the sausage drops.)
- It fell out. - The sausage...
(Did you drop the sausage?)
(I'll eat it for you.)
Hey.
(They fight for the sausage.)
It's mine!
(I grabbed it first.)
Goodness.
He ate it.
Isn't it delicious?
That was hilarious.
(Did that sausage mean that much?)
Do something like singing.
Otherwise, you'll starve.
(The others should do something.)
(I shouldn't starve.)
(What?)
- What's going on? - Is she drunk?
(She overworks her throat.)
Is she drunk?
(Please stop, Da Hee.)
(She sings diligently.)
(She cries without finishing.)
If you turn back time...
(I'll pretend that I didn't see it.)
Think about it again.
This isn't right, Da Hee.
Go back.
This is wrong, Da Hee.
It's so embarrassing.
I feel more embarrassed for her.
Wait.
This isn't a musical.
(What Da Hee did was wrong.)
Did anyone order lettuce wrap?
- Did anyone order spicy pork? - Bring it here
- Excuse me - Give me lettuce
- Here's your lettuce and spicy pork - Give it to me
Who wants to eat it?
I want to eat it
(She gets back to the musical mode.)
Do you want some, Da Hee?
I do
Give me one bite
Show us your talent as much as you want to eat
(Singing in a high tone)
(Jo Su Mi appears.)
(Only a wrap will end it.)
(It's a frightening version of "Queen of the Night".)
All right, I'll give it to you. Open your mouth.
Isn't it delicious?
(A sausage falls out.)
(Another fight for the sausage breaks out.)
- My goodness. - It's unbelievable.
- How did he find it? - He's a hyena.
(I worked hard to earn it.)
- Han Na. - You get it if you dance ballet.
I'll do it.
Just show us your pose.
- Should I turn? - Music should be...
(She's convinced.)
Sang Yeob, can you play some music?
- Could you? - Yes.
She needs music to dance.
Make it look graceful.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(She turns like a ballerina.)
(The background music doesn't stop her.)
(Han Na turns gracefully.)
(Take this wrap immediately.)
Do it one more time, Han Na.
Do it from here.
Can you give me half since I sang?
(Laughing)
(She turns very well.)
(The background music makes it look like a circus trick.)
(Her circus show is over.)
Han Na.
- She dances well. - She does.
I shouldn't have sung.
I got hungrier.
- I got hungrier after eating. - I could turn well as I'm hungry.
- Try some spicy pork. - Today's spicy pork is excellent.
Spicy pork is really delicious.
(Will Team Green have enough time to steal?)
Get Out! Time to Steal will start.
You may start from here.
If Team Pink succeeds, you may earn a Luxury Sticker.
- I forgot about that. - Oh, no.
(They win a Luxury sticker if they succeed again.)
You get another one.
- If we succeed? - Okay.
Did you give up?
- No, of course not. - We can do it. Let's try it.
Do you have a screwdriver?
Really?
You have to find it.
- Really? - Really?
- Shall I try to find it? - Are you ready?
Get ready.
Start.
(The time limit is 5 minutes.)
(Get Out! Time to Steal starts.)
Start.
- Is ours House B? - Where is it?
- House B. - It's right here.
It's here.
(They must steal something bigger than a teddy bear.)
Let's see. We have time.
Shall we take this?
Isn't it too heavy?
- How about the mattress? - The mattress.
- The mattress. - Shall we take it?
Let's go and see.
What should we do?
- We made the wrong decision. - We haven't won once.
- It's driving me crazy. - I gave the benefit of a doubt.
It's not happening.
(They lose the game and get stolen.)
It's quite serious today.
Guys.
- What? - The red cabinet.
- Where is it? - It's in there.
What?
It might be too obvious.
Exactly. That's why we should take it.
- I found it! - What?
You found it.
(Screwdriver)
- We found the screwdriver. - Hurry!
(They've been looking for it.)
Where did you find it?
(If we can find a screwdriver,)
(we can take the door off.)
- We can do it. - We could do that.
- They probably didn't think of it. - Right.
(Team Pink has been planning to steal a door.)
- We don't have much time. - Hold the door.
- It's working. - Hold the door.
- Are we stealing a door? - We're stealing a door.
It's working.
It's just like I expected.
They're taking the door off.
I knew it.
- Keep going! - Not yet.
Hurry.
Be careful.
- 40 seconds left. - Hey.
Move!
Let's go!
- They took it off! - Hurry!
- You took it off? - They can't take it out.
(They really took the door off.)
- Let's go! - Hurry!
- Come! - Hurry!
Run!
- Go barefoot! - Come out!
- Run! - Move!
- Get out of the way! - Run!
- Hurry! - Run!
Let's go.
- Hurry! - Hurry!
Run! Hurry!
Okay!
Put it down.
(Time is up.)
(Did Team Pink succeed?)
We took the door off.
We didn't expect you to find a screwdriver.
- Our teamwork is amazing. - Totally.
Has their teamwork always been that good?
Since when was it so good?
When Jong Kook is on the other team, I fight with him.
- Yes. When we're on the same team, - But when we're on the same team...
- we couldn't get along any better. - Exactly.
Gosh, that's so annoying.
Anyway, you finished within five minutes.
- Please. - This item is...
There's no way they thought of the door.
This item is...
(The door is...)
On the list. You failed.
(You failed the mission.)
Seriously?
The door is on the list?
(They expected us to steal the door?)
(They were discussing.)
They must want to surprise us.
- They might take this door off. - I thought so too.
(We know how the other guys think.)
(Shuddering List)
(Door)
(Like Haha suggested, they included the door in the list.)
- We did it! - We did it!
(Haha's clever idea turns the situation around.)
How did you think of the door?
Haha is so...
Aren't you happy too?
(1 Shuddering Sticker goes to Team Pink. What will happen now?)
This is the third round...
and your last chance to win a Luxury Sticker.
You're Out! Kick the Can.
The two teams will take turns and attack.
The offense team has to either kick the can...
or try to save as many members as possible within five minutes.
Is it a physical game?
It's over.
- Jong Kook is smiling. - Jong Kook.
- He's smiling. He knows he'll win. - Do something!
You guys are so weak.
But you still have a chance. Four on the defense team will...
try to protect the can, and two will chase the offense team.
The defending members can remove an attacker's name tag...
and eliminate them.
The chasing members on the defense team can move freely.
They can eliminate their opponents...
by touching them.
The can has to go out of the lines.
1 can will earn you 3 points, and 2 cans will earn you 10.
Each surviving member will earn the team one point.
If everyone survives, the team earns 10 points.
10 points?
Are you allowed to fart when you're defending?
Please allow that. We have no choice.
A short one is okay, right?
Please give us one point if we fart.
For example...
(Is this okay?)
- Would this be okay? - That deserves 10 points.
(Are they really my teammates?)
If you pull that off, you win.
If you pull off that melody, you'll win 10 points.
- That's great. You can do it. - Can you do it?
Can you do it?
(How can I possibly do that?)
Please decide which team will attack first.
- We should defend first. - Let's figure it out.
Who wants to protect the can?
1 can earns you 3 points, and 2 cans earn you 10 points.
Why don't we focus on just one can?
- So that they can't kick both cans. - Should we?
I think someone strong should protect it.
Jong Kook should be the guard.
- You should. - And...
Let's come up with strategies.
We can't.
We need to know where Jong Kook will be.
Jae Seok is strong too. So is Se Chan.
Ji Hyo will be outside.
Jin Young and Jong Kook will team up.
Me and Jong Kook will be the guards.
- Jong Kook, I have a question. - The girls will...
(I have a question.)
Will you be guarding the cans, or will you be moving?
(Tell me your position.)
We can't tell you.
- Randomly? - I'm being polite.
Please tell me.
Are you...
I'm sorry, but we're not that close.
We're being polite.
Kwang Soo, you should have come.
- We're not that close. - You should have asked him.
What should we do?
Go away. I'll talk to him.
Can you do it?
Jong Kook, please stay in the lines.
- What? - Stay in the lines.
Stay in the lines? All right. You can go.
- Go. - Okay.
We can't tell you.
I think he'll keep his promise.
They want you to be in the lines. You shouldn't.
They might be playing with us.
Right.
We'll invite you to our farting show.
- Can you really do that? - I can't!
- Practice! - How could I do that?
Just give it a try. You almost succeeded.
Just add some melody.
(Melody)
Gosh! This is so annoying!
Jump. Go down.
I heard it.
(Farting)
- Is it your superpower? - It was too obvious.
It showed.
They're ready. Who is defending?
That's Jong Kook.
- There. - Jong Kook is defending.
- Yes. In the lines. - In the lines?
- In the lines? - He's guarding the cans.
(Guards: Jong Kook, Jin Young, Seok Jin, and Se Chan)
(Chasers: Jae Seok and Ji Hyo)
All right. Team Green, please go hide.
(Team Green's strategy is to hide well and avoid physical fights.)
(Hiding)
Okay.
- Let me borrow your cap. - 30 seconds left.
(Kwang Soo dresses up as a staff member.)
(Haha is disguised in a referee's uniform.)
I'm of no help.
I need to run away to survive.
(I'd rather run away.)
(Panting)
(Han Na is wandering around the defense zone.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
I'll push the opponents away...
from inside the lines.
- Then you should touch them. - Okay.
Do you get it? I'll throw them at you.
- I'll throw them at you. - Okay.
Touch them.
- You'll throw them at me? - Yes.
Okay.
(Will my strategy fail?)
You have 10 seconds left.
(10 seconds left)
10, 9,
eight...
(They won't be able to find me.)
(Da Hee aims to win a point by not getting caught.)
- 8, 7... - Hide.
(Kwang Soo hides behind a cameraman.)
Five,
four,
3, 2...
(3 seconds)
2, 1. Start!
Start!
Hold on.
- You took it off to quickly. - Jae Seok.
Here, Seok Jin and Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. - This wasn't my plan.
Let's eliminate her first.
- Hold on. - Don't move.
Don't move.
- Don't move. - Look at Han Na.
Han Na is out.
- Han Na is out? - She's out.
- Have a seat. - Okay.
(At the same time on the opposite side)
- What's that? - He's right here.
(Sang Yeob was close to Seok Jin and Se Chan and got caught.)
- This won't work. - Here.
He's here, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok goes after Sang Yeob as soon as he hears Seok Jin.)
I touched you.
- Sang Yeob is out. - Oh, gosh.
(Meanwhile, So Min is in the mudflat.)
What do I do?
What should I do?
Goodness, I'm being dragged in. My feet.
What do I do? I can't move them.
What do I do? Can you hold my hands?
What should I do? I'm done.
I can't move my feet.
They could be hiding as a staff member.
(Let's have a look.)
Touch.
You touched him?
(Haha is out.)
- Haha is out. - How did you know?
Why would you point the camera right at me?
(Hold on.)
(I got caught.)
Go after him, Ji Hyo.
He's by the camera.
He's here.
(He runs away.)
- Come on. - Hey, Kwang Soo!
(They both go in the mud.)
Help me. My feet are stuck.
(Help me! My feet are stuck!)
My feet are stuck.
What is she doing?
What is she doing there?
- My feet are stuck. What do I do? - Run away.
(Stop there!)
- But my feet are stuck. - Run away!
- But my feet are stuck. - Take them out!
(Take them out right now!)
(I don't know anymore.)
(I'm leaving first.)
I'm done.
Hi, So Min.
Kwang Soo.
Hey!
Look at him.
Kwang Soo.
(I'm sorry,)
(So Min.)
What do I do?
The cameraman fell.
His feet got stuck.
(It's extremely difficult being Kwang Soo's cameraman.)
Don't come!
Kwang Soo, don't cross that river!
Don't cross that river!
(My love, don't cross that river.)
Please don't come!
Go away!
(Panting)
- What if he goes to North Korea? - I know.
You'll get shot, Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- You'll get shot. - Is that...
- North Korea? - Seok Jin.
Stop.
Stop, Kwang Soo.
Come back.
- Kwang Soo. - I can't.
- Kwang Soo. - Don't come!
Come back, Kwang Soo. Come back.
- One minute remaining. - Stop it. Come back.
Please go!
I can't give up.
Please.
Is that necessary?
Does this game have to be that extreme?
10 seconds remaining.
10 seconds!
Come back, Kwang Soo!
10,
nine,
- Did we catch them all? - eight,
- It's over. - seven...
Da Hee didn't get caught.
(Cheering)
(Kicking)
Four...
(I did it!)
2, 1.
(Team Green gets 1 can.)
- Haha. - This is it.
(Haha, we finally did it!)
Where's Kwang Soo?
- When is he coming back? - Kwang Soo,
come back.
- Come back, Kwang Soo. - Jae Seok.
(They don't know it's over yet.)
(Panting)
No!
Tell them it's over.
Kwang Soo and Jae Seok don't have to do that.
Stop. Stop!
Tell them it's over.
(Jae Seok, please stop following me.)
(A staff member runs to get them.)
- Hold on. - It's over.
- Tell them to come back. - It's over!
Is it over?
(I did it!)
(Gosh, Kwang Soo.)
I'm sorry, Bo Pil.
Bo Pil, I...
I'm sorry.
Bo Pil,
what are you doing?
(Flailing)
(Being a Running Man producer is a difficult job too.)
Hey.
Why is this necessary?
This isn't supposed to be this extreme.
I'm sorry.
- Why would you do that? - Jae Seok.
Look at the faces of the staff members.
I'm sorry, everybody.
Is this necessary?
I'm sorry.
I lost my shoe.
Where is it?
It fell in the mud.
We can't go this way.
- Okay, Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Let's go that way.
Oh, gosh.
Why would you do that?
- My goodness. - Bo Pil, I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry. - What are you doing?
Bo Pil.
- I'm sorry. - What are you doing?
- Isn't that Bo Pil? - Did Kwang Soo survive?
- He did. - Yes.
I think he lost a shoe.
Do you have boots on?
Hey. Look at Bo Pil. He's a mess.
What happened?
- He cursed at me so much. - What did he say?
"This isn't supposed to be this extreme!"
Can you find my shoe, Bo Pil?
It's not mine. It's sponsored.
- Oh, dear. - Are they looking for his shoe?
He tricked me.
I'm sorry, everybody!
It wouldn't matter if it was my shoe,
but it's sponsored!
(They are in the mud, looking for his shoe.)
Everybody!
The sun is setting. Please hurry up.
Let's do this, everybody!
It was on that side.
3 on the left, 2 on the right.
Divide yourselves up.
They found it.
They found it!
(It's almost as if they found his long-lost mother.)
Thank you! Is the shoe okay?
Is it okay? Thank you!
After five minutes,
Kwang Soo and Da Hee survived, so that's two points.
Da Hee kicked a can,
so that's five points in total.
Yes.
We should have said no...
- to going into the mudflat. - You're right.
- I'm sorry. - Across from there,
Kwang Soo and I looked in this direction. The entire staff...
(They were thinking, "Why is he doing this?")
- Really? - Yes.
"Why is that necessary?"
- That's true. - "That's going overboard."
I'm sorry, everybody.
It's okay. You looked cool.
The same rules apply. Team Green will defend.
1 or 2 people...
could go around...
to distract them. It's not a bad strategy.
It's not necessary.
- Do 3 on 3? - That's the best way.
Jae Seok,
this will be over in two seconds.
(What is Team Pink's 2-second strategy?)
It won't last long.
- It's a dark tunnel. - It isn't.
The tunnel never ends.
I want to wake up from this nightmare.
- Me too. - I'm having a night terror.
Wake up. Wake up.
I feel helpless.
I don't think anything will work.
- Let's have fun. - What do we do?
Let's end this on a successful note.
It was great being on the same team with you guys.
I had fun.
- We worked hard. - I have no regrets.
- I have no regrets. - Me too.
We were the best warriors today.
- You are all warriors. - Warriors.
We already won. We won by ourselves.
We are the real victors.
- See you again. - Let's get together after.
We'll have a team dinner.
Let's eat noodle soup with seafood.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- This is sad. - Let's do this.
This makes me tear up.
Please take positions, and put the blindfolds on.
- They'll hide then. - I'll go left, and you go right.
(Sang Yeob and Han Na are in the left defense zone.)
- Da Hee. - We just can't touch it.
(Da Hee and Kwang Soo crouch in the right defense zone.)
Why are you going back and forth in front of me? It's scary.
Everybody.
Nobody...
Nobody knows yet.
I'm going to tear up.
Let's try our best until the end!
We can win!
It's not over until it's over.
I loved you guys!
I loved you all!
10,
nine,
8, 7,
- Haha. - Let's do our best.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
What's this?
(1 second)
(2 seconds)
(Kicking)
It's over.
(They kick 1 can in just 2 seconds.)
Run away.
(What about the right defense zone?)
One.
(Pulling)
(Struggling)
Catch one.
(Da Hee and Kwang Soo resist.)
(My gosh)
Touch them.
(Kicking)
(Team Pink gets 10 points in 22 seconds, and it's game over.)
Let's celebrate.
That was so easy.
That was easy.
- Why would you run to the mudflat? - Let's go.
(They get both cans by going straight for them.)
(This hurts my pride.)
That was...
That was such a simple game.
This is how you play the game.
- This is how you play it. - Why would you run to the mud?
(Goodness)
I'm so mad.
I'm so mad!
Hey, rather than doing this,
- we should have just stood outside. - I'm so mad.
I'm so mad.
(Punching)
So Min.
So Min,
- this is how you play the game. - Jae Seok.
- So Min... - Jae Seok.
Jae Seok, you... Jae Seok.
(Kicking)
(I took my anger out.)
You earned 10 points in just 22 seconds.
(Team Pink earns 10 points in 22 seconds with 2 cans.)
That was so simple.
We work so well together.
Jin Young grabbed my hair. Is that allowed?
- Is that okay? - You should've ripped the name tag.
- How? - You should have.
That's the rule.
Take the Shuddering Stickers.
Gosh, Shuddering Stickers.
Yes.
We have to go in the house now.
Team Pink also gets the last chance to steal.
Take it all!
(Take it all!)
But there aren't that many things bigger than that.
Team Pink has to bring something bigger than the door.
- There's nothing bigger than that. - It has to be the door.
- Ready. - Okay.
- Set... - This is so much fun.
- I am lucky today. - Let's go.
- Let's do this. - What should we steal?
- What can we take? - In any case,
we can't take this.
Is this smaller than the door?
It is smaller.
What about the sofa, mattress, or the curtain?
- Does the sofa work? - Don't you think...
- they would've picked the sofa? - Lift it.
- I can lift it. - We can carry it.
Jong Kook, do you think they picked the pole?
Really? This pole?
(The curtain pole is the 2nd candidate.)
- I don't think they picked it. - The pole?
- The curtain works too. - Right.
They might've not thought about the pole.
(Is it the curtain pole or the curtain?)
Two minutes remaining.
- Two minutes remaining. - Se Chan.
You don't have too much time left.
- Hurry. - We have two minutes left.
- We're in trouble. - Blanket, mattress, curtain...
- Choose one. - The curtain.
- The curtain. - Should we take this?
- The curtain. - Let's take it off.
The curtain or the pole. Decide.
- We can take it off. - There's no time.
You have no time for that.
- Seok Jin. - Yes.
Isn't this better?
- The pole won't come off. - The pole?
Why wouldn't it come off? It comes off.
Take it off.
(Goodness)
- See? - Come in the room.
- They took the pole off. - They took the curtain off.
It's not the curtain. It's the pole.
(Why is Team Green sensitive about the curtain or the pole?)
(I vote for the curtain.)
(Or we can do the pole.)
(Team Green also hesitated between the curtain and the pole.)
(They took a picture of one of them.)
(Did Team Green choose the curtain or the pole?)
- The curtain pole. - They took it?
They took off the curtain pole.
Good. Take it.
Should we choose the curtain or the pole?
- I got it. - Decide.
- Do this. - Should we do the curtain or this?
- Curtain pole. - Let's take both and decide.
- Take both and decide. - Go. Take the curtain.
- Go. Take the curtain. - The pole came off?
- Let's take both and decide. - They went in the room.
What is it?
We have to decide on one.
- What should we choose? - We have to decide.
You have to put it in your room before the time's up.
- What should we do? - Jae Seok, which one do we choose?
- Let's do the pole. - Should we do this one?
- Just choose one. - Let's choose the pole.
- I'll put it in our room. - No.
- Let's do the pole. - I'll put it in our room.
- I'll take this one. - No.
- The pole. - Choose that one.
This one?
Are we going to be on the same team next week?
Good work.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They celebrate their 3 losses and do a cheer.)
You can only take one.
- 15 seconds left. - Choose the curtain then.
- The curtain. - Yes.
Choose the curtain then.
(Team Pink chooses the curtain at the end.)
It would work. If you open it, it's really big.
You moved the item on time.
- You took the curtain, right? - Yes.
That's the item you took.
On the opposing team's Shuddering List...
(Was the curtain on Team Green's list?)
(Curtain or the curtain pole. What's the result?)
It was not included.
(Team Pink steals it successfully.)
What about the pole?
(How about the pole?)
It was on the list.
(The curtain pole was on Team Green's Shuddering List.)
(They had a hard time deciding between the curtain and the pole.)
(At the end,)
(they decided on the curtain pole.)
(That's too bad.)
Seok Jin.
We would have lost if he didn't speak up.
- I almost left. - I told you.
They might not have taken a picture of it.
- I thought we got it. - Seok Jin went in the room.
This team gets Luxury Stickers again.
We have the results of Steal House and Get Out Race,
and in order to distribute the stickers,
we'll play Line Stealer.
"Line Stealer"?
Each member will throw their shoe...
and will be ranked according to how close they are to the line.
Luxury Stickers will be given to the winners,
and Shuddering Stickers will be given to the losers.
It means that for this team,
five people who are closest to the line...
- get Luxury Stickers. - That's right.
One person will get a Shuddering Sticker.
I am really bad at this.
I won't lose.
It would be better if the game is based on luck.
This is not based on luck.
You never know.
For this team, three people who are the farthest away lose.
If you're closer to the line, you get a chance.
- Is it 2 or 3 people? - You have to be closer to the line?
So Min, we have to win.
This is the last game.
Let's get started.
(Who will get the Shuddering Stickers?)
What if you pass the line?
It's okay. It doesn't matter.
- Who would like to start? - So Min first.
- So Min first. - No, he's going first.
- Sang Yeob first. - She's going after him.
We're next to each other again.
I'm sick of Sang Yeob.
I thought you were in love with him.
- Why are you sick of him? - That was quick.
You wanted to be a couple with him on the first day.
Hey, you're not the only one.
I'm scared too.
Go.
I can do this.
- Wait. - Just take the Shuddering Sticker.
- I can really do this. - Take the Shuddering Sticker.
Just take it.
That was beautiful.
Kick it hard.
(Kicking)
Too short.
(He couldn't control the force.)
We just have to pass him.
- Okay. - Good job.
- Okay. - It's too far.
- You got intimidated. - But this...
- No way. - No, no.
(He can't get near it.)
What are you doing?
My gosh.
- So Min. - So Min.
- So Min. - You stepped on the line.
(She comes out of nowhere.)
(Da Hee starts interfering with So Min.)
Kick it hard.
(She's being annoying.)
Put it next to Sang Yeob's.
What?
Put it next to...
(So Min punches her.)
(What just happened?)
(I'm sorry, Da Hee.)
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I got so mad.
I got mad at Da Hee.
- So Min. - Fart Lady.
- Let's go, Fart Lady. - Put it next to his.
(Fart Lady is ready.)
- Sang Yeob. - Hey.
Fart Booster.
(They cheer for the Fart Lady.)
So Min wasn't singing, but I heard a sound.
(She didn't move her mouth. Where did the sound come from?)
I have to get married.
- I have to get married. - You can get married.
Go to the Shuddering Package first.
- So Min. - Put it next to his.
I can't focus.
- I'll be careful. - It won't be good enough.
In 1, 2, 3.
She did it.
(Nice shot)
Good shot.
- In 1, 2, 3. - She did it.
(You can see how much she wants to avoid the Shuddering Sticker.)
(So Min is currently in 1st place.)
- Good shot. - Good shot.
What?
- Good shot. - So Min won.
Nice, Fart Lady.
She's good when you talk about farting.
Hey.
Next.
Kwang Soo's shoes are in pain.
They're in pain.
My shoes are still not good.
- You'll have the energy of the mud. - This will be fun.
Are his shoes stuck to his feet?
- He lost. - You have the energy of the mud.
He lost already.
He's done. He lost the mental game.
- Kick it hard. - He lost the mental game already.
Stop it.
(Take it easy.)
Let me give it a try.
Okay.
I think he's going to kick it in the air, and it'll land here.
- He's uglier when he focuses. - He's so ugly.
Kwang Soo is also...
- Why is he standing like that? - Were his legs always that short?
- I know. - Kwang Soo...
(Spitting)
He spat at us.
(The Shuddering Sticker depends on this.)
- I'll go. Okay. - He spat at us.
Kwang Soo didn't gel his hair,
so he looks like an idiot.
- That's a bad spot. - I know.
(He makes up his mind and kicks.)
It's not bad.
(It lands in between Sang Yeob's and So Min's.)
This is not bad.
Move, Kwang Soo.
I'm looking forward to this.
Da Hee has big shoes, so she'll be fine.
I don't think it'll be easy for her.
- One person will lose. - I know exactly what to do.
If you do this, it bounces back.
It springs back like this.
(If you kick it straight, it bounces back.)
- It comes back. - This...
- It does. - It bounces back.
It goes forward then comes back.
This looks fun.
(She watches Kwang Soo carefully.)
- So... - How do you do it?
it's better to kick it sideways.
I think it's a good idea.
This is really good. Let me borrow your shoulder.
It's going to roll in front of her.
(This is the chance to show her move...)
(after observing the others.)
See? Look.
See? I told you.
I told you.
(Da Hee is currently in last place.)
See? I told you.
I told you.
- This doesn't work. - Yes.
- This won't work. - No.
- You can't touch it. - Move.
- I told you. - Can I try like this?
- That was so bad. - No way.
It rolls like that.
This is pretty intense.
I'm next.
Haha, you don't have to worry.
There's hope.
(Kicking)
(He lands in 3rd place.)
- Nice! - Oh, gosh.
(Haha is in 3rd place.)
What just happened?
(Kwang Soo and So Min get to choose the briefcases.)
- Congratulations. - Han Na.
No way! What have I done?
(Han Na is the last one to go.)
- Han Na hasn't gone yet. - Han Na.
It will be over if Han Na's shoe falls here.
Seriously.
(The fate of Team Green lies on Han Na's shoe.)
(So Min is 1st, Kwang Soo is 2nd, and Haha is 3rd.)
What have I done?
(If Han Na is in 3rd place,)
Han Na!
(So Min, Kwang Soo, and Han Na get to choose the briefcases.)
(If not, So Min, Kwang Soo, and Haha get to choose the briefcases.)
Oh, yes! This is incredible.
Is Han Na's shoe farther away from the line?
Let's measure the distance.
(The result is unclear to the naked eye.)
Measure the distance from Han Na's shoe.
It's nowhere close to the line.
The distance is similar.
90cm.
(Han Na's shoe is 90cm away from the line.)
I don't know the result.
(Haha is in 3rd place...)
(if his shoe is less than 90cm away from the line.)
(Who is in 3rd place?)
- This is neck-and-neck. - 60cm.
(Haha's shoe is 60cm away from the line.)
60cm. You won.
Haha.
(Haha is in 3rd place.)
He survived.
Only one of you will get a Luxury Sticker.
The rest of you will get a Shuddering Sticker.
- Only one of you will get it. - Only one of you.
- Really? - Only one of you will get it.
Don't be so sure of yourself.
Becoming the loser in this team will hurt.
- Seriously. - It will hurt.
- Jong Kook will go first. - Okay.
Becoming the loser in this team will be the saddest.
- You know, - It will be really sad.
becoming the loser in this team will be the saddest.
(Then you get a Shuddering Sticker despite winning the race.)
- Shall I go? - Yes.
(He is cool-headed.)
(Throwing a shoe is a piece of cake.)
- Put yourself at ease. - I will do that.
(The thrower is at ease,)
(but the onlookers are nervous.)
(There is no need to worry too much about throwing a shoe.)
- My goodness. - What?
(A total disaster)
What was that?
- He is ruined. - What was that?
It didn't even go halfway.
(My goodness.)
- What was that? - Stay still.
(They celebrate in silence so as not to anger Jong Kook.)
- Don't move. - What was that?
What was that?
- Oh no. - Did Jong Kook really do that?
Stay still. Stay still.
(I am sure you remember what they said earlier.)
(The worst is losing due to a shoe after winning the race.)
(I can't believe it happened to me.)
- The loser has been decided. - Is that really Jong Kook's shoe?
The loser has been decided.
- Hold on. I can't believe this. - Jae Seok!
- This is the best. - I worked hard all day.
I know. You worked hard all day.
Only a fool wouldn't be able to get it past halfway.
- I am next. - Ji Hyo is next.
- Put yourself at ease. - There you go.
(Ji Hyo got hers past his.)
All right.
My goodness.
Stop it.
Good shot!
- It was great. - Okay.
Jong Kook sacrificed himself.
He is a good man.
(Who will take the remaining three slots?)
There is only one opening for the Luxury Package.
(1 of the 3 briefcases contain it.)
This is a game of luck.
Which one will you choose?
I choose this one.
So Min should choose next.
I am sorry but...
- Let go of your expectations. - 1, 2, 3.
(What is inside Kwang Soo's briefcase?)
I am sorry but...
- Let go of your expectations. - 1, 2, 3.
(What is inside Kwang Soo's briefcase?)
(He gets the Shuddering Package.)
See?
I told you to choose this briefcase.
- It's done. - Shuddering Package!
- Take it out. - Congratulations.
Congratulations.
(Haha and So Min remain.)
So Min, choose this one.
So Min's fate will be sealed...
- if she messes up again. - Please.
Please let me get what I want.
You can do this.
I don't care if I remain single. Let me use all my luck right now.
(Please hear my prayer.)
- "I don't care if I remain single." - Please.
That's a bit extreme.
- 5, 4, - Please let me get it.
3, 2, 1.
It's the other one.
Please open the briefcases at the same time.
1, 2, 3.
(Who has the Luxury Package?)
(Luxury Package)
(So Min gets the Luxury Package.)
You know, you won't get married now.
You sold your soul.
My goodness.
(I am happy right now.)
(The 3rd week of Family Package)
(Luxury Package and Shuddering Package)
(Next week)
(They take a break from Family Package.)
(The war for TV rating notice begins once again.)
(It has become more fierce.)
(There is only one main character.)
(Ruthless scenarios)
(Who is fated to be the victim?)
(However, do not give hope.)
(Avengers-like stars are here to help.)
(They will show remarkable plays.)
(However,)
(they are of no exception.)
(They undergo ridiculous missions...)
(that kill their brains.)
(What will be their fate?)
(You know,)
(I feel extremely uncomfortable right now.)
(TV Rating Notice Part 2: Infinity War)