(P Botanical Garden in Pocheon, Gyeonggi Province)
(It's a fall day...)
(with the bright, morning sunlight.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - What are Face and Voice?
- Hello, Ji Hyo. - Hello.
- Hello. - Anyone would think...
the two of them have a mission.
(They are dressed like a couple.)
- What? - Anyone would think...
the two of them have a mission.
- That's not true. - There is a concept going on.
- That's not true. - That's not true.
This is why there are rumors.
We have the same stylist.
- Don't be so blatant. - We have the same stylist.
They shouldn't date.
- We have the same stylist. - This is the look she likes.
- Don't be ridiculous. - It seriously looks like...
Hong Jin Young and Kim Jong Kook shouldn't date either.
(Let me say this, too.)
(Jin Young gets dragged into this.)
Let me say this again. They shouldn't date either.
There is nothing between us. Don't edit this part out.
- Nothing. - The relationship is impossible.
- It's impossible. - Why did you get started so early?
- Seok Jin! - Why did you get started so early?
I didn't know Seok Jin wasn't here.
- I didn't know. - Seok Jin wasn't here.
I didn't know either.
Why did you get started so early?
Seok Jin shouldn't date either.
- What are you talking about? - Seok Jin shouldn't date either.
You will know once you watch the episode.
Will the episode air this week?
- What do you mean? - This episode.
(His eyes shift.)
- What? - I was just curious.
You don't make sense, Seok Jin.
- That's no way to talk to an elder. - Listen.
- He's older than you. - You don't need to...
- How could you say that? - rush things because you're late.
- I wasn't rushing things. - Is someone chasing you?
He's worried that he might not be in the opening segment.
He's being chased.
He's Running Man's Slave Hunter.
- He stays away from talking. - He stays away from talking?
- The moment he opens his mouth, - Fine.
three of you are attacking him.
He can't counterattack them.
(Until the day he's free from his chasers...)
Not by himself.
Today,
you'll split into Team Face and Team Voice and have a race.
- Team Face and Team Voice? - Face and voice?
Behind you, it's divided into Team Face and Team Voice.
Line up behind the team that you feel confident about.
(It's between their faces or voices. They'll choose their own teams.)
Well, say no more.
- You should go to Team Voice. - What are you doing?
- Go to Team Voice. - Come on.
- You should join Team Voice. - Go to Team Voice.
I should join Team Face.
Wait, my voice is pretty good too.
(I'm good-looking and have a great voice. What should I do?)
I should go to Team Voice.
My voice is great.
Ji Hyo should stay here. I agree she should be in Team Face.
- Jong Kook and Haha should... - Come on, Se Chan.
- What is it, So Min? - You do belong here.
- I'm handsome among comedians. - I belong to Team Voice.
- Be quiet. Come here. - Why?
(What are you talking about?)
- Why? - You're talking a load of nonsense.
- Jong Kook, I'm decent, you know. - What?
Hold on. As for your team,
you didn't need to pick based on your looks or voices.
- You just followed Jong Kook. - No, no.
- He told me to join this team. - That's not true at all.
- I was observing you. - Okay.
- Everyone here is for Team Face. - Right.
Kwang Soo.
- Are you a thug? - Why?
I definitely belong to Team Face.
- I totally belong here. - Listen.
I belong to Team Face.
- You belong there. - Good looks are a given for us.
On top of that, we have a great voice.
But he doesn't belong there.
- Mister, come over here. - What?
- Come on. Don't you feel guilty? - You're driving me crazy.
- Mister, I belong to Team Face. - Come join us, mister.
- I make people laugh with my face. - What is he talking about?
(I make people laugh with my face.)
- What? - He's right. It is true.
- I just slipped. - He does have a funny-looking face.
- That's not what I meant. - You're right.
- I didn't mean to say that. - People do laugh at your face.
I think I might have said the wrong thing.
All right. Hold on. You chose Team Voice, right?
- Yes. - You picked Team Voice.
- Is everyone here for Team Face? - Yes.
- Wait, Se Chan chose Team Face? - Yes, include me too.
All right. You have divided into two teams.
(They all choose their teams.)
I will introduce the captains of each team who will lead you today.
(It's time to reveal the captains of the teams.)
- Captain. - I can't wait to find out.
- Who's our captain? - It's our team leader.
Team Face's captain, please come on out first.
Gosh, Team Face.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(Who's the captain of Team Face?)
(The team called for people who were confident about their looks.)
- It's a woman. - It's just one person.
(Who is the captain of Team Face?)
- Soo Hyang. - It's Soo Hyang.
- Soo Hyang, long time no see. - "My ID Is Gangnam Beauty".
(Im Soo Hyang, an actress with a glorious return)
(She was a former, rising star, and now, she's indispensable.)
(6 years ago, she was a gem on this show and won the race.)
(She's thriving beyond genres, both in dramas and on variety shows.)
(My ID is Versatile Beauty.)
- Soo Hyang. - Hello.
- That explains the team's name. - It's Soo Hyang.
- "My ID Is Gangnam Beauty". - Right.
- I'm in Team Face. - By the way, Soo Hyang...
- joined us a long time ago. - It's been so long.
She was my partner.
That's right. It was a special for Pretty Trio.
It's been so long.
- You remember everything. - Of course.
- Right. - You're amazing.
After that, Soo Hyang returned as a big star.
(We heartily welcome our big star.)
- She's a big star now. - Right.
- I joined you when I was new. - Right.
I came back after seven years.
(Today, she's the captain of Team Face.)
Then our show fostered you.
- Our show is fostering you. - It's you.
- How many years has it been? - Please help me a lot.
We're almost spoon-feeding you.
- He's not growing up at all. - He should be walking about now.
He's not growing up.
- I'll do better soon. - My gosh.
- Okay. - We'll continue now.
We'll introduce you the captain of Team Voice.
- Who is it? - Please come on out.
Don't you think it'd be a man since it's about the voice?
- No, I think it's a woman. - Show me your hands first.
Show us your hands first. It's a woman.
- That's a lady's hand. - My gosh.
- No, it's a man's hand. - No.
- No. - Is it a guy?
She didn't get her nails done.
- Isn't that a lady's hand? - Is she getting nervous?
- It's a guy? - Is she nervous?
- It's a lady. Her hand is pretty. - Her hand looks delicate.
- Her hand is pretty. - It's a woman.
(Who is the mysterious captain of Team Voice?)
- Hello. - Ha Na.
- It's Lee Ha Na. - I get it.
- "Voice". The drama, "Voice". - My gosh.
(She steals the scenes for fun and is good at sweeping the TV screens.)
(She's the heroine who led to the success of a seasonal drama.)
- She's just like her character. - No way.
- "Voice". - She looks the same in person.
(Lee Ha Na appears on Running Man.)
That's why we have Team Face and Team Voice.
- Hello. - Hi.
"Voice". I'm a hot fan of you.
(This turns into a fan meet all of a sudden.)
What's a "hot fan"?
- What is that word? - A hardcore fan.
- A hardcore fan. - The biggest fan.
- Thank you. I'm a fan too. - We say a hardcore fan.
She can even hear the smallest sounds.
Seok Jin, don't fart in secret today.
- She can hear everything. - She hears even the smallest sound.
(Stay tuned to find out Ha Na's performance with her super hearing.)
- Let's do short introductions. - Okay.
Could you say hello to the viewers?
- Okay. Hello. - Okay.
(Looking shy)
I'm Actress Lee Ha Na. It's my first time on Running Man.
I've been supporting Running Man for a long time.
- Really? - Yes.
- Her voice is so sweet. - My gosh.
- She has such a great voice. - I knew it.
I'll tell you my favorite episode.
- Okay. - Please tell us.
The one with Kwang Soo's fan.
- It was a long time ago. - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
The Namyang Middle School episode?
I know. We found her with a photo.
- That's right. - We visited schools too.
We even went to houses too.
That's when Kwang Soo wasn't popular. He really wasn't.
- You know what? - That's so true.
It was when Kwang Soo had three fans.
- Don't be so mean. - I know this very well...
because his three fans used to criticize me a lot back then...
for teasing Kwang Soo.
It was fun to watch, but it was also touching.
You like touching episodes.
I can't believe Ha Na pointed out a specific episode.
Have you seen the Sherlock Holmes Special?
That's one fantastic episode.
- I don't remember that one. - You haven't watched that one?
(Trailing off)
- Seok Jin ruined that episode. - Looking at your eyes, it seems...
as if you just found out that Seok Jin is on Running Man.
- She's a fan of Running Man. - I'm a huge fan.
- It's our ninth year. - Right.
The viewers are just getting to know him.
He's a new recruit to our show.
- I'm a new recruit. - For nine years?
People are commenting that he's funny now. It just happened.
Finally, he's getting a lot of hateful comments now.
- People are interested now. - He never got those comments,
and people commented that he wasn't entertaining,
- but now, people criticize him. - Seriously.
Criticisms about me fill up an entire page.
People are giving you attention now.
Every week, I'm swimming in an ocean full of hateful comments.
Finally, Seok Jin is in the center of funny jokes.
I'd like to ask the viewers to look forward to his performance.
All right. Recently, the second season of "Voice" ended.
- That's right. - Yes, it did.
Please tell us how you feel about finishing the drama.
Well, I mean this.
- I'm grateful. - Okay.
Actually, for the second season to be successful...
That rarely happens. That's not easy to accomplish.
- You want to say yours did well. - We should have mentioned that.
(The 2nd season was a hit too.)
- That wasn't an easy thing to do, - Yes.
but yours did well.
- Is that your point? - "I am..."
"I am amazing."
"I did it."
(You're amazing, Ha Na.)
"You can't pull this off."
- This is how you do things here. - That's right.
- I should watch my tongue. - Right.
On top of that,
one of the main leads was switched out during the season.
- This isn't an easy thing to do. - "I'm the only one who wasn't cut."
- I accomplished that hard task. - Right.
You did it.
You pulled off that hard task.
- She doesn't hold back. - She's so cute.
- I really want to do a good job. - Seriously.
- I don't want to be shy today. - That's great.
- Ha Na, that's trending nowadays. - That's right.
- People toot their own horns now. - You have a point.
- Being modest isn't a virtue now. - Exactly.
Next up is "My ID Is Gangnam Beauty".
Let me introduce you to Im Soo Hyang.
- Hello, I'm Im Soo Hyang. - She's really nice.
- Her drama just ended. - Exactly.
I came here after doing a great job on "My ID Is Gangnam Beauty".
(She smoothly starts promoting herself.)
- She tooting her own horn now. - Right.
- Being modest isn't a virtue. - That's right.
- You took a page from Ha Na's book. - I'm following that.
Anyway, Soo Hyang is joining us today.
Here's what's important.
- We have to split into teams. - That's right.
Ha Na, for your teammates,
- you have Jong Kook and Haha. - You must feel reassured.
Soo Hyang, you have members who are confident about their looks.
- That's right. - You're confident about your looks?
- We all chose this team. - I think she's laughing at me.
- No, no. - The moment she saw me...
No, no.
- The moment she saw me... - You bring laughter with your face.
- Let me explain. - That's what you do.
I'm confident about my looks in many ways.
- You can't change your face. - Right.
Don't feel like she's kicking you out.
You have no choice but to form your own team, Soo Hyang.
Make your decisions just based on their looks.
(Two of them will join Team Voice.)
Just decide based on our faces.
- Faces? Based on your faces? - I'm serious.
It's Team Face after all.
In that case, there's someone who totally suits the theme.
Who is it?
Should I tell you?
- She looked at me for a second. - Just do it based on their looks.
I'm sure she looked at Seok Jin too.
- He's just dodging her eyes. - I didn't look at her.
- Soo Hyang. - I won't look at her.
There's an official game we play at times like this.
- We can play the Race of Wits. - Come on, don't do that.
How about sending the loser to the other team?
- Should we play that? - Shall we play that?
- We'll start. - He loves the game.
- I don't have to play, right? - Of course not.
Hold on. I'm not sure if I saw this right.
When Jong Kook lifted his arm, you put your shoulder there.
I wasn't imagining this, right?
What did you say?
- Did he really do that? - When Jong Kook lifted his arm,
you walked and put your shoulder there. I'm not wrong, am I?
Isn't this how things should be?
You really did that?
(When they were about to start the Race of Wits...)
(Coming closer)
(His shoulder-leaning service takes initiatives.)
Why did you put your shoulder there?
I act as his keychain and armrest.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I thought I was imagining it. I'm sorry.
We have our arrangements you don't know about.
- There's an arrangement. - If I'm fine, everything all right.
(He defends himself.)
Of course.
I was just wondering if I was seeing things.
He has a point.
All right.
The loser will be sent to the other team.
- Okay. - I'll stay here.
(Who will leave Team Face?)
Start.
One.
- 2. - 3.
Four.
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin are the only ones left.)
Five.
- 2. - 3.
(Hesitating)
(In the end, he says, "five".)
(Gosh)
- Why didn't you sit down? - He was confusing me.
(Ha Na welcomes Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo lost.
Come here.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
(Welcome, Ji Hyo.)
I was hoping she'd come to our team.
- Really? - That's great.
Ji Hyo was sent to the other team.
- The second... - Should Soo Hyang push someone?
Should we do that?
- She should push someone. - That sounds good.
She'll push someone she wants to kick out.
But the other team might reject that person.
- Right. - If you're too ugly, we'll refuse.
- All right. - I think So Min is safe.
(Who will be the second person to leave Team Face?)
What should I do? Whom should I choose?
- She touched me. - What should I do?
- She touched my back. - Mine too.
Some of them look worried.
(Worried)
Why is she lingering behind me?
I think she's behind me.
(Who will Captain Soo Hyang choose?)
It doesn't feel right.
Is it me?
(Pushing)
(I knew it was coming.)
(Should we accept him?)
She must hate him.
Let me just go home then.
- Let me go home. - Stay.
Don't feel offended. She likes you.
Se Chan.
It's okay.
You're getting more parts.
What?
(He's been kicked out, but he gets more parts.)
(Ha Na holds Se Chan's hand.)
- Yes! - I...
- Is it done? - Yes.
Se Chan.
Okay.
I wanted you to come here.
- Okay. - Team Face.
- We're the penalty members. - That's right.
What do you mean?
We're all so unlucky. Totally.
Team Face and Team Voice will compete...
in the Legendary Captain Race.
(Legendary Captain)
The Legendary Captain Race.
After three rounds,
the team with more money left will win.
The winning team will get a prize,
and the losing team will be penalized.
I can already see.
But the member with the most money...
in the losing team won't be penalized.
The member with the least money in the winning team...
will be penalized.
I want to go to that team.
This team will definitely...
We'll...
They'll definitely be penalized.
(What will happen to Team Face?)
- Captain, let's do this. - Let's do this.
Do you like your captains?
- Yes. - Of course.
I just want our captains to like us.
The captains will distribute money among us, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Okay. - Captain, I'll work hard.
Okay.
I'll be watching you.
(Let me see who works hard.)
Of course.
- We'll do well. - We will.
- Right. - When we started shooting,
Ha Na said,
"I'm ready."
(She's eager.)
I heard it too.
For this race,
you can change the captain who has absolute power.
(The captain can be changed.)
You can do it through a vote.
What?
(They can secretly vote?)
The captains should...
- be careful too. - They should be nice to us.
If you want to be the captain,
write your name on a ballot...
and give it to a cameraman.
When the captain changes,
the old captain and the new captain will switch their accounts.
Oh, my.
Those who voted yes...
get to see their balances.
We'll be voting many times.
(They're all ambitious.)
There will be many votes.
(The most suspected member feels guilty.)
(I'm getting worried.)
Gosh.
Kwang Soo, you already wrote your name?
(Is he already voting?)
What's that in your right hand?
(What's in his right hand?)
He folded his ballot.
(He's already holding a ballot.)
(No way.)
- That's right. - He's already holding it.
He's holding it in his hand.
What?
(When did the ballot get into his hand?)
(As soon as he found out he could vote,)
(he took out a ballot.)
(Please take it.)
(He pretends to be innocent.)
What's wrong? Why are you ripping it up?
(So Min makes sure Kwang Soo can't vote.)
Why did you rip it up?
- You... - You're out.
- Captain Im. - Let me explain.
- Captain Im. - Thank you.
Did you see that?
- I did it just in case. - Okay.
Okay. I saw it.
- Remember it. - I will.
Good.
- You don't understand. - When did you write your name?
(Captain, you don't understand.)
Kwang Soo is lying over there.
- That's right. - Kwang Soo is lying over there.
So Min, Kwang Soo is lying over there.
Kwang Soo!
(What are you talking about?)
Kwang Soo is lying over there.
(The wooden sculpture looks exactly like Kwang Soo.)
That looks exactly like Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Even the hair is long on the back of the head.
It doesn't look like me at all.
It looks like Kwang Soo.
Look at the legs.
It looks exactly like Kwang Soo.
Even the legs are thin.
No way.
It doesn't look like me at all.
- It does. - The hairstyle looks the same.
The profile looks the same too.
The hairstyle looks exactly the same.
Before the first mission,
you need to take out a loan to make a bet.
But the conditions are a bit complicated.
(They need to take out a loan before each mission.)
(What are the loan conditions?)
For the first loan, you have to use your face.
Wrap Monster.
Wrap Monster?
(Wrap Monster)
The number of plastic wraps each captain breaks through...
within the given time multiplied by five...
will be the amount you can borrow.
With your face.
(That sounds harsh.)
We should protect their beauty.
We just need to break through?
(The captain gets worked up.)
Ha Na is all worked up.
- Her eyes are glowing. - She's very competitive.
Her eyes are glowing.
- Will you be okay? - Will you be okay?
I've never tried it, so I don't know.
Well...
Forehead?
I don't know.
- Use your forehead. - Okay.
Forehead?
(She heard it?)
You heard it?
Just like in "Voice".
She's from "Voice".
She can hear everything.
His voice was very low. How did she hear it?
- How did you hear it? - She can hear everything.
How did she hear it?
- Don't even think of whispering. - Gosh.
There was Sommers in the 1980s.
- In the 2000s, we have "Voice". - Sommers.
- She can hear everything. - Oh, I know what that is.
Ha Na will go first.
- You have 30 seconds. - Okay.
Break through as many as you can.
Stay calm.
- It might be harder than you think. - It might be harder than you think.
It's hard.
We get 50 dollars per plastic wrap.
Ready, start.
Yes. Like that.
(She is determined.)
- That's not okay. - There you go.
- It doesn't count. - It's okay.
It doesn't count.
- One. Continue. - Continue.
Continue. Okay.
Good.
Two. Good.
- Three. - Good.
I'm in trouble. What should I do?
(Her facial ability is amazing too.)
- She's so determined. - Put it down.
Put it down.
No.
(She really is a wrap monster.)
Please stop.
Stop!
Please stop!
Bring some more!
Ha Na.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
Oh, my gosh. I can't do that.
Good.
She's so fast. Good.
What should we do?
(The captain of Team Voice is full of determination.)
- My goodness. - Okay.
(Ha Na has broken through 8 plastic wraps.)
Okay!
Ha Na, you're amazing!
That was incredible.
You were amazing.
(The team members are touched.)
Ha Na looked so sad.
We saw it many times.
- Her lips were rolled. - It was amazing.
We should make them into emoticons.
- You were amazing. - Will I be able to get married?
Of course.
We won't have to change our captain.
- Soo Hyang. Come on! - You can do this!
- Captain. - I've never tried it.
(What should I do?)
- Ready. - I think it'll be hard.
Check the angle.
Watch from the front. You have to use your face.
- Ready. - 1, 2.
(Soo Hyang starts.)
- Good. - I can't do this!
Break through!
(She puts her head in,)
(but she can't get out.)
- I can't do this! - Break through!
Break through!
Soo Hyang!
- Hey! - Where are you going?
- Hey! - Okay.
Hey!
You have to do it!
- Break through! - Break through!
Break it!
Okay!
(They're no match for us.)
- Break it! - Break through!
(She finally breaks 1.)
Soo Hyang, hurry up.
Use your forehead.
- This is the second one. - It's too hard.
- Soo Hyang! - What are you doing?
Why is she so bad?
They'll definitely change their captain.
- Soo Hyang! - Hold on.
Break it!
(Soo Hyang breaks 3 within 30 seconds.)
- Let's change our captain! - How did you do it?
Ha Na did an amazing job.
(It just worked.)
- Lee Ha Na! - Lee Ha Na!
- She's good. - How did you do it?
- Soo Hyang. - Let's change captains!
It...
(So Min has an idea.)
(She attacks Kwang Soo.)
(She picks a fight.)
Soo Hyang!
I did my best.
I can't believe this. I don't like our captain.
(It's an artwork.)
Stop it!
- Stop it. - Kwang Soo...
Which one is Kwang Soo?
My face got squished, so it looks ugly.
I'll pay three dollars for it.
- I'll pay three dollars for it. - What do you mean?
- Let's start at three dollars. - No.
I don't look like this.
- 10 dollars. - 10 dollars?
- We have 10 dollars. - 15 dollars.
- We have 15 dollars. - 15 dollars.
- 20 dollars. - We have 20 dollars.
- 25 dollars. - 30 dollars.
That's not me. I don't look like that.
- 20 dollars. - We have 20 dollars.
- Why? - We have 30 dollars.
- 50 dollars. - 50...
(I call 50 dollars.)
(The original artist participates in the auction as well.)
(His competitors are nervous.)
- 70 dollars. - 50 dollars?
- 70 dollars. - 70? Sold!
(He didn't want to lose.)
- I don't want it. - 70? Sold.
("Face Off" gets sold to Seok Jin for 70 dollars.)
Here you go.
(Jae Seok ends the auction abruptly.)
- Hey. - 70 dollars.
(They all congratulate him.)
- Congratulations. - You took it from me.
- 70 dollars. - This is not how auctions work.
Somebody was supposed to call 80 dollars.
- This is not a proper auction. - Sold at 70 dollars.
Gosh, I wanted it too.
- Hand it to your manager. - His face got printed really well.
Captains, you need to decide under whose name...
you'll get a loan.
Soo Hyang, I have something to show you.
What are you going to show me?
- I'll give you my trust. - I'll try my best.
You can watch me.
I trust you.
I broke through two earlier, and somebody wasn't happy with me.
- He said "I don't like my captain." - That was Seok Jin.
- That wasn't me. - I didn't say a word.
Okay.
No, I didn't.
Is there anything you'd like to say?
- Don't feel pressured. - Will you trust me?
- Yes. - I trust you.
- I trust you. - I trust you a lot.
We'll do our best with the games.
- We'll win. - Right? We can win.
All right.
(Under whose names will the captains get a loan?)
Let's go, Soo Hyang.
Captain Im, I trust you.
- I'm serious. - Captain Im.
I think Soo Hyang is the prettiest actress out there.
I was shocked at how pretty she was.
I was amazed. She's unbelievable.
- I can borrow 150 dollars, right? - Yes.
Then...
(Team Face can borrow 150 dollars.)
(She can also distribute the loan to the team members of her choice.)
There's a person who said he didn't like the team captain.
(One of our team members said that.)
(Seok Jin yelled, "Let's change our captain.")
Put everything under Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin didn't like the team captain.)
There'll be other chances.
She's done. There's our team captain.
- Are you done? - Yes.
You are sharp, Captain Im.
- She didn't hesitate. - Everybody will be satisfied.
You'll all be satisfied.
- Did you distribute it equally? - All right.
- I trust you. - Do you?
- Yes. - I see.
(She keeps a poker face.)
- I can't tell. - I don't know what she's thinking.
- I don't know at all. - I have no idea.
How much can I borrow? 450 dollars? 400.
(Team Voice can withdraw 400 dollars.)
(Including me...)
There are five of us.
Wait. I think she's deep in thought.
I said I'll give it my all today.
She's the type of person who goes with her gut.
Exactly.
Then I'll do this first.
Okay.
We're going to win in games.
(She's convinced they'll win in games.)
(Whom did she give 400 dollars to debt to?)
The loans have been processed.
Here's the first mission to win some cash prize.
It's called Sleeping Bag Express 999 Karaoke.
(First mission: Sleeping Bag Express 999 Karaoke)
- "Sleeping Bag Express"? - "Sleeping Bag"...
- Sleeping bags? - Sleeping bags.
Each team will put on sleeping bags that are connected front to back.
Listen to the song lyrics we'll read to you...
and guess the song title and the singer.
The team that takes the microphone...
gets to guess first.
Each captain should bet money first.
If we win, we can get two times the amount we bet.
- That's right. - We have to consider that.
We can get two times the amount we bet, right?
They might bet everything they have,
because they can borrow more.
They're impulsive, so they might bet everything.
- 150 dollars. - We have 150 dollars.
How much shall we bet?
(Farting)
(He farts suddenly.)
- He farted. - What are you doing?
- That sounded like a frog. - This is awful.
Who was that?
He was startled too.
- He farted and... Goodness. - Hey.
- Excuse him. Please move back. - No.
- That wasn't me. - Move back.
That wasn't me.
What do you mean?
- What are you doing? - Don't laugh.
- Don't laugh! - What was that?
What are you doing?
Why are you staring at nothing?
You should get checked, Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - This is bad.
- Seok Jin. - What?
- No. - Everybody heard it.
- We're competitive. - Of course.
- Okay! - Life is one shot.
- This is our style. - According to the results,
Team Face bet 140 dollars.
- Team Voice bet... - We'll win.
- 110 dollars. - I knew it.
See?
The winning team...
will take 500 dollars which is double 250 dollars.
(The winning team will take 500 dollars.)
(We must win.)
- We have to win. - If we win,
- we'll win overall. - We have to win.
- We'll win. - We have to win.
This looks difficult. What do I do?
Soo Hyang, we have to win.
- Okay. - Pay attention, Soo Hyang!
- Be quiet. - Who are you?
- Be quiet! - Be quiet, Seok Jin.
(You need to pay attention, Seok Jin.)
(Okay.)
All right. Here's the first question.
(It's the first question.)
"Love, a new love".
("Love, a new love".)
(She got it.)
- Do we go? - I think she knows.
- I think she knows. - We're faster.
- 2, 3... - Just go.
(Hopping)
- We're fast. - Catch up.
- We're fast. - We're faster.
We're much faster, Soo Hyang.
- Go. - We're much faster.
- Do you know this? - Love...
- Do you know? - "New Face" by Psy.
(Team Face goes first. Soo Hyang's answer is "New Face" by Psy.)
(Are these lyrics from "New Face?)
("New Face" by Psy is correct.)
- Why are you so good? - You're right.
(Our captain is the best.)
(They get it now.)
(Here's the answer.)
I danced to this.
(They're dizzy because the answer makes their hearts flutter.)
(Let's win.)
Let's go back and get a good spot.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Let's get a good spot while they're having fun.)
I'm going crazy
(They only got one question right, but their hearts are fluttering.)
(She reproduces the dance perfectly.)
(So Min does too.)
(They're in a trance.)
(This is Team Face.)
Let's go!
- We started late. - We have to move fast.
- I'll just go. - Let's think on the way.
I'll grab them too.
- I was being too nice. - Let's go!
(They don't know what's going on, and they're still dancing.)
Good job.
(They try their best.)
(Team Face is the best.)
(When are they going to stop?)
Okay.
- That was good. - I danced to this in a drama.
- Really? - That's great.
She did this dance.
(Team Voice gets a good position while the other team celebrates.)
Hold on.
(When did they go back?)
- Weren't we supposed to dance? - You had to watch us.
They got mad and left.
- Goodness. - They left.
Come back if you're done.
- Come back. - Back to position.
That's not fair, Ha Na.
They left because they lost.
They can't leave us while we're dancing.
- Congratulations. - We're in position.
Our team captain told us to leave.
That's not fair, Ha Na.
- We were fast. - We were so fast.
- That was great, Soo Hyang. - That was excellent.
- Excuse me, Captain Lee. - Yes.
I saw you clapping and smiling.
You could have come down there,
- but when we were speaking... - Sorry.
I...
(She clapped without sincerity.)
I thought you were all smiley and kind,
but she doesn't act that way.
Why would you get mad because you lost?
- That's not what you do. - Why?
She's doing her job as the team captain.
She looked so pretentious.
She wants you to start.
- She wants you to start. - Start.
Do you want us to show you?
- Let's go. That was good. - This is so funny.
- Here's the second question. - Let's go.
We have to win this time.
- Let's go, Soo Hyang. - All right.
Go as soon as you know.
Go right away.
(Their plan is to block Team Face.)
(Second question)
"Think twice".
"I can't act nice"...
Go.
(Go, go, go!)
(Go first.)
What is it?
- Go. - 2, 3, 4.
(Shall we go too?)
Go.
(Pushing)
(Falling)
Hey.
(Go first.)
Hey, Jong Kook.
- What was it? - "I can't act nice"...
What is this song?
(Team Voice is at the microphone.)
- Kim Hyun Jung? - What was it?
- Kim Hyun Jung? - 5, 4,
3, 2...
(They're here, but they have no idea. What's her answer?)
Kim Hyun Jung?
(She's not sure.)
"Think twice".
(Is it a song by Kim Hyun Jung?)
(It's incorrect.)
(There's a penalty for saying the incorrect answer.)
There's cold air.
This is our chance.
(Let's go and guess.)
- Start. 1, 2... - I have to get up.
I have to get up!
(I have to walk too.)
(Dragging)
Just go.
(Sorry, but we have no time.)
Hold on!
(Seok Jin falls as well.)
Hurry up.
(Soo Hyang doesn't know the answer either.)
The lyrics sound familiar.
"I can't pretend to be nice like other people".
(Team Voice has no idea.)
"I can't pretend to be nice"...
"Bad Girl, Bad Boy"...
- "Bad Girl, Good Girl". - Miss A.
"Bad Girl, Good Girl" by Miss A.
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin think it's "Bad Girl, Good Girl" by Miss A.)
(I can't pretend to be nice like other people)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(Wrong)
(It's wrong?)
It's our turn, right?
Here's the next line. Listen carefully.
"You probably don't know yet".
"If you want, test me".
(I think I know.)
- Test me? - Text me?
"You're too obvious".
(I think I know. Let's go!)
There are lyrics like that?
I think it's a pretty new song.
"Ddu-du Ddu-du" by BLACKPINK.
(Ha Na thinks it's "Ddu-du Ddu-du" by BLACPINK.)
(Is this finally the correct answer?)
(Correct)
- Gosh. - Really?
There are lyrics like that?
- The lyrics did sound familiar. - Ha Na is amazing.
(Correct answer)
Oh, it was that song.
- Ha Na. - I can't pretend to be nice
(Ha Na managed to remember the song.)
Shoot!
(Ha Na is really excited this time.)
(Let us dance too.)
(It doesn't matter whether we get the question right or not.)
You did a great job.
(We respect Ha Na.)
- It sounded so familiar. - Goodness, Ha Na.
- Ha Na. - It was a famous song.
Let's get two questions right, Soo Hyang.
Let's get two questions right.
- Otherwise, we'll go under. - We'll go bankrupt.
There's one question left.
Move a little.
We're too close.
Ha Na won't move. I can't believe it.
She's so competitive.
(This question will determine who will win 500 dollars.)
All right. Ha Na.
(Team Voice is determined. Team Face has bet almost all their money.)
(What's the last question?)
"I've been waiting for today".
- Go! - Go!
(Both teams start to run as soon as they hear the question.)
I know it. Definitely.
Definitely.
(Let us say the answer.)
Seriously.
(They fall.)
Why do we keep falling?
(They're forced to take a break again.)
They pushed us.
We know the answer.
"Invitation" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
- I've been waiting for today - "Invitation" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
(Ha Na says the right answer.)
We got it right!
Play the music!
- You're the best. - Dance time!
(We've been waiting for you)
- Lee Ha Na! - Lee Ha Na!
(We've been waiting for a captain like her)
(Team Voice has amazing teamwork.)
(The other team has great teamwork too.)
(Team Voice wins 500 dollars, double of what they bet.)
(Kissing)
- Goodness. - Thank you.
Let's take it off.
Are you having a picnic?
Ha Na, when we fell, you didn't even look at us.
You're so mean.
You should get up.
- What? - You should get up.
- What did you say? - Stop pretending to be nice.
You're just pretending to be nice.
- "They're so cute." - She thinks you're cute.
(Team Voice wins the 1st mission.)
The winner of the 1st mission is Team Voice.
(They win 500 dollars.)
- Ha Na, you're the best. - You're amazing.
I'm so disappointed. We did well in the beginning.
That's enough.
Yes!
(Haha teases the other team.)
Ha Na!
We can do it.
The captain will distribute the prize money.
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
- Let's do this! - Lee Ha Na!
(How will Ha Na distribute the prize money?)
(It's time to distribute the prize money from the 1st mission.)
Like I expected...
(How should I distribute it?)
You trust me, right?
- Yes! - Se Chan.
I trust you.
- Don't worry. - Okay.
(The team members trust their captain.)
(The captain has all the power.)
(What's her decision?)
It didn't take long.
I'm getting the hang of it.
You are?
(It's hard to know what Ha Na is thinking.)
Who wants to see the balance?
Me.
Should we let the captain choose one person?
Choose the one you trust the most.
Se Chan.
- Me? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
She must have given the money to Se Chan.
She must have given a lot to him.
(Why is she letting Se Chan see his balance?)
(How much money does he have?)
How much do we have in total?
You won 500 dollars.
(500 dollars?)
(How much did Ha Na give to Se Chan?)
(The first distribution is over.)
Everyone.
A moment ago...
- What's that? - Someone put it back together.
That's been ripped up and put back together.
Two ballots arrived at the same time.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
- Really? - That one is crumpled.
What is this?
Who did it? You?
No.
The candidates are...
(Who are the candidates among the 4 members?)
Lee Kwang Soo and Jeon So Min.
- Gosh. - You guys...
(You guys are unbelievable.)
I knew it.
(Kwang Soo and So Min rebel at the same time.)
You wrote your name?
- The thing is, - You guys...
I had to do something for my team.
- I'm sweaty. - How could we not know?
Exactly. "Ddu-du Ddu-du"...
(Kwang Soo hid behind Running Bank.)
(He put the pieces back together.)
This team is doomed.
We'll be penalized at this rate.
(I have to rebel.)
(So Min had the same idea.)
(They register as candidates.)
(Jeon So Min)
There are three candidates.
Im Soo Hyang, the current captain,
Lee Kwang Soo, and Jeon So Min.
The rest of the team will vote.
If you want to keep the current captain, write Soo Hyang's name.
If you want a new captain, vote for 1 of the other 2.
- Okay. - We need to change something.
(The campaign starts.)
- Tell us about your plans. - Let's start a new age.
Let's listen to them.
Do you think they can really change anything?
(What?)
Kwang Soo looks flustered.
Please tell us your specific plans.
How are you going to distribute the money?
- If I become the captain... - This is important.
I won't distribute the money...
equally.
I'll give everything to you two.
(I'll give all the money to you two.)
- Really? - Yes.
- What's the ratio? - What's the ratio?
I'll take everything from these guys...
- Everything? - and give it to you.
- You'll get double. - Double. Good.
Let's give her a big hand.
- Are you serious? - Next.
- I'll be straightforward. - Do it.
If we win money,
I'll divide it 2 to 4 to 4.
(Jae Seok boos Kwang Soo.)
I'm not finished.
Why are you booing me?
Okay.
I don't have to win.
I just don't want to finish at the bottom.
5 to 5...
(He boos again.)
(Everything Kwang Soo says gets booed.)
Okay.
(He plays his final card.)
- Is there more? - You'll get 100 percent.
(I'll give Jae Seok 100 percent.)
(What?)
What about me?
- You... - What?
(Kwang Soo will give 100 percent to Jae Seok.)
I'll divide it 4 to 4 to 2.
- Okay. - 4 to 4 to 2.
- 4, 4, 2. - Next.
- Soo Hyang. - I'll give everything to you too.
But...
look at these betrayers.
Can you really trust them?
Your hand.
Raise it.
If you trust these betrayers,
they'll stab you in the back again.
Okay. Let's vote.
(The 3 of them vote.)
Soo Hyang. You're not done yet, right?
Let me tell you one thing.
- I... - I'm done.
(Cold)
(You're done?)
(That's too bad.)
I'm sorry.
You should have said it earlier.
(The voting is already over.)
- Good job. - Soo Hyang is so attractive.
- She did a good job. - She's so cold.
The result is out.
The captain of Team Face is...
(The rebellion vote result)
(Who will be the captain?)
Jeon So Min.
(So Min becomes the new captain.)
(The age of Captain Jeon begins.)
Guys!
- How? - Really?
So suddenly?
We voted for you.
Thank you.
- That's right. - Thank you so much.
Oh, my gosh.
(I'm doomed.)
Then...
So Min and...
Soo Hyang will switch their accounts.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin, who voted for So Min,
can go to the bank...
and see their balances.
Let's take a look.
(How did Soo Hyang distribute the money?)
Is this mine?
Please give me mine. Thanks.
What is this?
(Jae Seok has no money.)
(Meanwhile...)
(Seok Jin has minus 150 dollars.)
(I'm sorry.)
Hold on.
(He can't believe it.)
Does this mean...
I'm in debt?
I'm in debt.
(His bank account has a negative balance.)
- Am I in debt? - Yes.
(He has a negative balance for forcing his team to go in debt.)
- This world is awful. - Excuse me.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
I have no balance.
Did you take it all?
(Did you take all the debt?)
I didn't. This world is awful though.
How much do you have, Seok Jin?
I have money.
I think he got a lot of the loan.
Here's the next round.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(They move to the next location.)
Why are you there by yourself?
They're discussing.
There's going to be a revolt.
Ha Na, don't trust them.
(They're talking without me.)
- Se Chan... - Let's hear what he has to say.
(Se Chan saw the balance earlier, so let's listen to him.)
What happened?
Should I say it?
I wanted to say it openly.
- Can you do that? - Yes.
I don't care.
How do you know if we'll support you or not?
That doesn't matter because I'm not in the last place.
- You're not? - No.
So it's not me.
It's not me.
You don't know what other people have.
- Those who have a lot... - But from my balance,
somebody doesn't have any money.
I'm not in the last place though.
You three should rise in revolt.
You have to do something.
(She's so nervous.)
They're going to change the captain.
They're mean.
(They're changing their minds. What will happen to Team Voice?)
- What's this? Is this water? - What's this?
This is a giant water bomb.
Before we start the second mission,
we'll proceed with the second loan.
- Okay. - This is a voice loan.
It's called Burning Forehead.
Forehead?
Do you have to get slapped on the forehead?
You slap your teammate on the forehead,
and you can borrow 10 dollars...
for every decibel.
(You can get 50 dollars.)
10 dollars?
Jae Seok's slaps...
are really loud.
I'm confident I can do this.
Let's go for 200.
Kwang Soo and I...
(They're partners.)
(Am I confirmed?)
- Give them a chance. - The important thing is...
- We work great together. - Right.
- I'll keep that in mind. - Remember what you did in Busan.
We'll do what we did in Busan.
(I'll go around the country with Jae Seok this way.)
I heard something earlier.
Ha Na boxes these days.
Does she?
- Jang Hyuk recommended it. - Yes.
She boxes.
She's been doing it for six months.
(She's been boxing for 6 months thanks to Jang Hyuk.)
- Show us. - Shadowbox for us.
(Show me the punch.)
(That's a perfect punch.)
She's good.
She looks cool.
Go again. 1, 2, 3.
1, 2, and 3.
Great.
("Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee.")
We're in trouble. I bet she's strong.
(They have to get slapped later. They're in trouble.)
What if she punches us?
(Team Face goes first.)
I'm sacrificing myself.
This is teamwork between Kwang Soo and me.
Sacrifice this once.
(It's time to appreciate their teamwork.)
Hold on.
(He thinks about it.)
Why am I crouched down here?
- It's for the team. - What?
Your forehead is the widest.
When will he stop slapping my forehead?
- I followed him to Busan last week. - We only have 10 dollars.
You're awesome.
Soo Hyang thinks you're awesome.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - He's happy.
- She thinks you're awesome. - You're doing it for the team.
You're much more handsome with your hair back.
(That did it.)
(Soo Hyang knows it.)
He's happy.
(I'll put my hair back...)
(and be handsome then.)
Hey, Eun Woo was her partner in the drama.
- Eun Woo was her partner. - That's right.
You look much better. You should do that.
- Okay. - Okay!
(Soo Hyang, I'll show you what my forehead sounds like.)
(Slapping)
(It always sounds sweet and clear.)
(Oh, dear. Where did that sound come from?)
(This is worth 840 dollars.)
That was so loud.
(We have to win.)
- How do we beat them? - 82?
If you use this part of the hand, it's not too loud.
You have to hit hard. Use your whole hand.
Your whole hand has to make contact.
Okay.
Let's go. Let's do this.
(The lesson is over. Let's go.)
(Jong Kook cares about Ha Na. What is his winning strategy?)
(His forehead is reliable.)
(It's too reliable.)
(Jong Kook is a passionate team member under a passionate leader.)
(They're focused.)
You're too close.
- You're too close. - I see.
- You can't hold that. - What?
(That's cheating.)
You can't do that.
- He might move back. - He's scared.
(He tries to get the instrument close to him.)
Slap hard.
It's okay.
(Hesitating)
- It's okay. - Swing a few times.
Swing a few times.
It's okay.
(How will she swing?)
You're the best in the world, Jong Kook.
(Slapping)
(Did she hit his eyes?)
(No, my eyes.)
(She aims at the wrong place,)
(and his small eyes widen.)
(How does such sound come from the eyes?)
She hit his eyes.
- Are you all right? - Did you get hit in the eyes?
(His legs give out from Ha Na's smash.)
I'm sorry.
- Are you all right? - Hold on.
- Did you yell? - She hit my eyes.
(Ha Na's legs give out because she feels bad.)
- Do you see this? - Hold on.
Do you see this?
That was a good slap though.
Goodness.
- The sound was... - Jong Kook, your eyes...
I'm so sorry.
He saw a light.
I've never heard him make a noise when he gets hit.
Me too.
(They've never seen him like this.)
He was cute.
We know...
something from this.
Jong Kook feels pain too.
- I know. He's so humanly. - He's a human, not a robot.
"Sponge" is back after a long time.
- Jong Kook feels pain too. - He feels pain.
(Jong Kook feels pain too.)
This is so humanly.
(Thanks to Jong Kook and Ha Na, they earn 830 dollars.)
- It's a 10-dollar difference. - Please decide...
under whose names you'll borrow the loans.
- 830 dollars? - Yes.
(Captain Ha Na goes first.)
Earlier, how much did I borrow?
(She considers how much she borrowed the 1st time.)
I'll do that.
(She decides on the 2nd amount.)
I want to divide it up.
So Min, remember who voted for you.
Remember who made you the leader.
(Captain So Min borrows the 2nd loan too.)
This is very fair.
I got some of it too.
- I got some too. - Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
(How did she distribute the loan?)
All right. The second mission is Flour Puck.
(Mission 2: Flour Puck)
There's flour in the middle of the table.
Each team gets 100 paper pucks.
You play 1 on 1 and take turns blowing at the stack.
The person who blows away all 100 paper pucks 1st wins.
These are pucks. I'm good at this.
Pucks?
(Those who've played it before are confident.)
I'm good at this too.
The remaining team members will receive the penalty...
as soon as the loser is decided.
(They get the penalty as soon as the losing team is decided.)
According to the mission betting results,
the winning team will take 2,680 dollars.
(The winning team will take 2,680 dollars.)
- Hey, we got 1 shot. - This is 1 shot.
This is one shot.
Who goes first?
(Kwang Soo versus Se Chan)
Jae Seok, do I have to put my chin here? Should I go first?
- What? - Should I go first?
- You can't switch. - I have to put my face here.
It's okay.
What's okay?
- Why are you okay? - It's okay.
- It won't hurt. - I know it won't.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Soo Hyang likes men with fair skin.
(She drives him into doing it.)
(Does she?)
(Smiling)
He's happy.
(Can you take it for the team?)
(I'll do it.)
Your name is Namyangju Handsome Face.
- You're handsome, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(Namyangju Handsome Face and Gangnam Beauty)
(I can take the flour if she likes fair skin.)
- Let's win, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo! - We have to win!
(These two...)
(Kwang Soo can topple the whole stack.)
(Se Chan's technique is to blow softly.)
(The rivalry starts now.)
(How will Se Chan's first attack be?)
- Okay. - Nice.
(That was expected.)
Nice.
(He flips over many in one blow.)
(That was amazing.)
That's amazing.
These ones are flipped.
1, 2, 3, 4...
- 17, 18, 19, 20, - 17, 18, 19, 20...
- 21, 22. - All right.
- Can you win? - I can do 22.
I can flip 100. Okay, trust me.
This is not bad.
Good luck.
- Good luck, Kwang Soo. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - Let's go!
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
- Trust me. - Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
(You can trust Namyangju Handsome Face.)
(He's done it before.)
(He hopes he can flip all 100.)
(His lips remember how it's done.)
There's not that many. Okay, don't move!
(That's it?)
(If this cost money, people would have asked for their money back.)
- Referee? - Not many flipped.
What is this?
- Gosh. - What is Kwang Soo doing?
Kwang Soo.
- What is this? - 1, 2, 3,
- 4, 5, 6. - Kwang Soo!
If the surface was hard,
everything would have flipped.
But here, only the flour gets blown away. Now, I get it.
- You should blow in the middle. - Okay. I get it.
You need a technique.
- Shouldn't the captains compete? - Sounds good.
- Let's do it. - Ha Na versus Soo Hyang.
Okay! You can do it.
- Roll your lips in. - Like Choi Bool Am.
(Soo Hyang is receiving a lesson.)
- Like this. - Roll your lips in more.
Not like that.
- Completely... - Your lips are bleeding.
Bleeding?
You're bleeding.
- You're bleeding. - Really?
Kwang Soo's lips are bleeding. Look at this.
(His lips are bleeding.)
He must have blown really hard.
- Really? - It's okay. It doesn't hurt.
- It doesn't hurt. - It doesn't hurt.
You didn't even know.
I didn't.
- You have to do it like this. - It's so funny.
Roll your lips in.
(Soo Hyang is receiving lessons from the members.)
Like Choi Bool Am.
(Ha Na is practicing on her own.)
Soo Hyang, you need to sit down.
- She's good. - You're doing well.
It looks good.
She must have spat a lot.
(Was she a bully in the past?)
Blow as hard as you can.
(Let me flip all the pucks.)
But I feel too bad...
to blow the flour all over her face.
But that's the point.
(Ha Na is worried about Soo Hyang. How will she do?)
Did she...
Did she spit at Soo Hyang's face?
- Hold on. - It's like the Red Sea.
Let me see.
- Hold on. - She hit Soo Hyang's face.
She aimed at Soo Hyang's face.
- Good job. - She spat at Soo Hyang's face.
- Good job. - I don't have a technique.
It's okay. You have nothing on your face.
Three flipped.
Five flipped.
There you go.
It feels like she spat at me.
- Sorry. - Okay.
(Ha Na, you humiliated me.)
I think we'll win.
(Are you ready?)
- Soo Hyang, let's do this. - Show us.
- Come closer. - Come closer.
(Ha Na,)
(I'll pay you back.)
(Will Soo Hyang get her revenge?)
(Just two?)
- 1. - No, 2.
It's two.
- Two flipped. - Okay.
- Two. - It's hard.
- I guess I'm not lucky today. - It's not easy.
- Ha Na is amazing. - We win.
(Team Face: 92, Team Voice: 73)
Let me try.
I can blow very hard.
(Confident)
- Should I go? - Okay.
- Se Chan. - Should I go first?
Okay. Se Chan should go first.
(The real battle starts.)
- It wasn't hard enough. - You need to take a long breath.
You need a long breath.
(Will Se Chan win many points?)
- Okay. - Seok Jin got in the way.
- Okay. - Four.
- Four. - This is our chance.
- Okay. - He got in the way.
- That's good. - Good.
- Goodness. - Seok Jin's face got in the way.
He blew everything away. Se Chan, you can do it too.
Don't be too greedy.
Right.
(Seok Jin gets ready.)
Blow in the middle.
Come closer.
(Seok Jin is full of confidence.)
(Will he save his team from a crisis?)
Great! Okay!
(Shocking)
(Unbelievable)
- Nice. - Good.
It was beautiful.
- It was amazing. - We did it!
I told you I'm good at this.
- 2, 3, 4... 33... - 33...
(It makes them hum.)
(It takes so long to even count the pucks.)
- 40, 41, 42. - 40, 41, 42.
(Seok Jin turns the tables around by flipping 42.)
- We did it! - Okay!
When it comes to classic games, no one can beat Seok Jin.
I used to play this a lot back in school.
- Let me try. - Aren't you going to shout my name?
Let me try.
- It's not over yet. - Let me try.
(Jong Kook steps up.)
(So you're good at this?)
Let me do it.
(I welcome any challengers.)
I'll start.
(Jong Kook looks determined.)
Okay.
(Shaking)
(He's even shaking. What's the result?)
- It worked. - Okay.
(A lot of pucks flipped.)
Hold on.
What about those standing?
- They don't count. - No?
- They don't. - What should we do?
- They shouldn't count. - They're standing.
They don't count.
They definitely don't count.
- They didn't flip. - Okay.
- 25. - 25.
We're catching up.
- Good. - Good.
(The match between the strongest contestants)
(When Seok Jin attacks,)
(Jong Kook counterattacks.)
(The pucks keep flipping.)
Nothing flipped.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Nothing flipped. - Let's switch players.
- Should I try? - Let's put an end to this.
- You? Okay. - Yes.
It's not easy.
(He needs to flip 8 pucks to turn the game around.)
- Nice. - He's good.
- You don't have to blow so hard. - Yes, Coach.
Go!
(The players from the first round compete again.)
Flip everything.
(Se Chan attacks first.)
Gosh. His face.
(Kwang Soo blocked the pucks with his face.)
(Se Chan flips only 3 pucks.)
He flipped three.
It was perfect otherwise.
- Only 3. - Kwang Soo!
- Let me do this. - We have to put an end to this.
You did well. Let's do this!
- It was perfect. - Flip seven.
(Show us what you've got.)
(Let me put an end to this.)
It's okay.
There's only one left.
- No. - There are some below.
- There's only 1 left. - There's only 1 left.
- Okay! - Just one left.
- There's only one left. - This is the last round.
- Gosh. We're broke. - Kwang Soo.
There's only one left, Kwang Soo.
- Okay. I'll do it. - There's only one left.
- I'll do it. - You have to do it.
- You have to flip it. - You have to flip it.
We've got your back. Don't worry about anything!
Bite it if you have to.
(Jong Kook shakes again.)
(Blowing)
- What? - Did it work?
(How many did Jong Kook flip?)
- Did I flip everything? - There are three left.
There are three left.
I'd be happy even if we lose.
I'm that amazed. You're incredible.
There are three left.
Oh, my.
(It's hard to predict the result.)
- Let me start. - Go!
- Start! - Let's end the game.
(Let me make up for all the humiliations.)
Kwang Soo's lips are bleeding. Look at this.
(The two team's fates depend on Kwang Soo's lips.)
(This round will determine the winner of 2,680 dollars.)
(What will be the result?)
(The two team's fates depend on Kwang Soo's lips.)
(This round will determine the winner of 2,680 dollars.)
(What will be the result?)
- It's standing! - It's standing!
- What? - It's standing!
(The last puck is standing.)
- It doesn't count. - We decided it didn't count.
We decided it didn't count earlier.
- Look at this! - You said it doesn't count.
How can this be possible?
- It doesn't count. - How could this happen?
- It flipped now. - I mean...
(Why...)
(did I say that...)
(in that situation?)
Your team said it didn't count if the puck was standing.
- Right. - Gosh. It's...
It's so annoying.
Why is it standing?
(He's annoyed and frustrated.)
Jong Kook, you're the best!
You're amazing. You made it happen.
(Ha Na showers Jong Kook with compliments.)
Ha Na compliments others a lot.
- Kim Jong Kook! - Let's do this!
Kim Jong Kook!
What if everything flips?
I didn't know I'd be this nervous.
(Why are we so nervous?)
Good luck!
(If you make a mistake, you lose.)
(So Min puts the pressure on.)
(Blowing)
(Let's flip three at once.)
(He blows hard. What will happen?)
It's still left.
(She blocked it.)
(Thanks to her defending, 1 puck didn't flip.)
- There's 1 left. - There's 1 left!
- This is great. - Good job.
- This is great. - It's 1 to 1.
- Goodness. - Look.
It hit her face and went down.
- What do I do? - One hit her face.
- You can do it. - Let's go.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
I'm so nervous.
So Min, this is the last one.
- Last one! - If you can't do it now, it's over!
Let's go!
Please.
(She blows lightly.)
- Please. - Please.
(Both teams' fates depend on So Min.)
Please.
(What will the result be?)
Did we win?
(It flipped.)
- Did you do it? - Did we win?
(She floats like a butterfly and stings like a bee.)
(The winner gets all the cash prize,)
(and the loser gets the penalty.)
- So Min. - We did it.
- Captain Jeon. - Captain Jeon.
- Thank you. - So Min.
You were awesome.
Team Face wins the match.
(Team Face earns 2,680 dollars and wins Flour Puck.)
That was awesome.
Please distribute...
- 2,680 dollars. - So Min.
- You know, right? - Captain Jeon.
We have to conclude this well.
We can be happy. Don't think otherwise.
- We were one. - We were.
We were one during this game.
How did we make it here?
You have some on your eye.
All right. They contributed.
(To thank them for their contribution...)
Seok Jin and...
(It's 4 to 4 to 2.)
(She said she'd distribute the money to Seok Jin and Jae Seok.)
(She pays Seok Jin and Jae Seok. Did she keep her promise?)
That was a wise choice, right?
(So Min allows Soo Hyang to check her balance.)
(I trust the captain. Let's see.)
How much did we win?
- 2,680 dollars. - 2,680?
20... 2,680?
(She only gave me 200 dollars?)
So Min.
- Why? - Was it bad?
I think she took it all.
- She was so fair. - Really?
I was being fair. I followed my pledge.
- You said 4 to 4 to 2. - Did you do it?
I considered your contributions too.
- She considered it a lot. - Right.
Really?
In the game.
Team Voice has a candidate for captain.
(Team Voice has a candidate for captain.)
- When? - When?
In such a short time?
Is it you, Se Chan?
- No? - What? Do you think it's me?
- I knew it. - Me too.
The candidate's name is...
(The candidate's name is...)
Haha.
(The candidate's name is Haha.)
(I'm the candidate.)
The towel...
(During the puck game,)
(he pretended like he was taking a towel from his cameraman...)
(when nobody was paying attention.)
(A revolt is bold and secretive.)
He's ambitious.
- He always dreams of betrayal. - Right.
(Goodness, it was Haha.)
I did this to save the team.
We'll all die like this. There must be a way.
I want to discuss that with you...
and win together.
That sounds appealing.
I'm convinced.
Trust me.
I'm about to tear up.
Oh, gosh.
You did your best.
Haha.
No, actually.
Just pick me.
Pick me.
- What's your reason? - Why?
(Why should we keep trusting you?)
I'll make you laugh.
(That was random.)
In the end...
Will we be so speechless that we end up laughing?
"Goodness".
- You got it. - We'll be speechless.
I think...
she'll make you laugh...
on the ride back home.
"Gosh, Ha Na".
(Goodness)
- That's it. - Right.
"Goodness".
We're doing this to have a good time, right?
At this rate, we'll be laughing until tomorrow morning.
Right when we wake up.
All right. Let's do this.
If Haha doesn't get picked,
- he'll fall out of favor. - Right.
Here's the result.
Team Voice's new captain...
has been unanimously changed to...
Haha.
(Haha has been voted unanimously.)
Really?
(Haha gets elected as the captain.)
Ha Na got ousted.
(That means she voted for Haha too.)
- This is so beautiful. - I'm sorry,
but can I have the badge?
(Stop talking.)
She's shaking her head and saying it's beautiful.
"This is so beautiful."
It's the opposite. She talks and behaves differently.
(She's unique in that she talks and behaves in opposite ways.)
Try your best.
Thank you.
Ha Na is so cute.
He was awesome.
You can all check your balances.
- Let's go. - Let's check.
(Since it's unanimous, they can all check.)
Ha Na is not coming, so she must feel bad.
(She's loitering. Is she sad or does she feel guilty?)
No, this isn't it. Give me the switched amount.
- Sorry? - That's the switched amount.
- Stop joking. - I'm serious.
Give it back once you're done.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
(Did something happen to the new captain's balance?)
(Minus 400 dollars)
(Minus 1,230 dollars!)
(The entire loan is under Haha's name.)
Haha.
Look at him.
Haha...
(What happened to the balance?)
(Will you trust me?)
(Everybody trusted her.)
I'll do this for now.
I'll watch Se Chan for a bit.
I'll distribute it equally.
(She distributed the cash prize from Round 1 equally.)
She's honest.
(Se Chan checked how honest she was.)
(He mentioned the possibility of somebody having no money.)
(She felt threatened and made a decision.)
I have to switch.
(I'll give all to the traitor.)
(She put all the loan under her name.)
What are you doing?
Stop playing with me.
Give me the new balance.
Is this a drama?
(This is unbelievable.)
Are there people like this in the world?
Haha, try to look cool and walk back.
It's not too late.
You have a lot of loans, right?
Is she a swindler?
(You should have trusted me.)
- Is she a good or bad person? - Is she good?
She predicted this?
I don't think she predicted it.
- She was nice and was fortunate. - Right.
(He fell victim to his own scheme. The new captain takes the loan.)
(Round 2 is over. It's time to move onto the final round.)
(This is the final mission!)
It's Legendary Treasure Hunt.
(This is the last chance to win additional cash prize.)
A treasure hunt?
- Can I turn the tables? - It sounds fun.
You take turns attacking and defending.
The defending team has...
20 minutes to find the hidden cash prize.
The attacking team will have bells attached to them.
You have to eliminate the defending team by ripping their name tags.
(Name Tag Elimination?)
It's Name Tag Elimination.
If the captain finds the cash prize, the amount is doubled.
(If the captain finds the prize, the amount is doubled.)
You have to find it.
The captain has to find more.
However, if the entire defending team...
gets eliminated before the time is over...
or if the captain gets eliminated, the race is over.
Is it over if the captain is eliminated?
This is all you.
If I get eliminated, this is over?
We have to protect the captain.
I'm in trouble. What do I do?
I'm weak.
- I want to win. - Me too.
- This is the most important round. - That's true.
We have to redeem ourselves.
Even if we get eliminated, we have to find a lot of cash prize first.
Haha, you should...
go around with Se Chan.
Go around with Jong Kook. I'll look for the cash prize.
Haha has to look for it,
and I'll be right behind him.
I can grab two people.
(Trust me.)
All right.
They have Jong Kook, so they have the advantage.
- What do I do? - I know.
We have to eliminate him quickly.
Jae Seok, we have to eliminate him first.
- How? - But then...
We have to eliminate the captain.
He'll be going around with Jong Kook. I'm sure.
How do we get rid of him?
How does he die?
We have to stop him from finding the treasures.
We have the disadvantage. We're in trouble.
(Those looking for the treasures versus those preventing them)
- I'll count down. - Go down.
(Try if you can.)
- Was it 20 minutes? - Yes.
(The teams' fates depend on the captains.)
Two...
- One. - Go.
- Start. - Okay.
(The grand finale, Legendary Treasure Hunt, starts.)
Let's go, Haha.
There. Let's go.
I think it'll be down there.
- Come here. - Good luck.
- Good luck. Go that way. - Let's go.
(They go as fast as they can.)
- You have to run away from them. - Okay.
- You can't be eliminated. - Okay.
I don't see it.
(Where are the treasures?)
(What's that?)
I found it.
(She finds a treasure in 1 minute.)
- I found it. - Okay! Gosh, she's fast.
(The 1st treasure is 500 dollars.)
Ji Hyo, good job.
- Put it away. - Haha should have found it.
I will put it away.
(It's too bad Haha didn't find it.)
- Which way should I go? - Hurry up.
(If Haha finds a treasure, the amount of money is doubled.)
Go. Keep going.
- Which way should I go? - Haha! Come here!
Haha! Come here!
Here. There is a treasure.
You should get it.
Okay.
Gosh, it's perfectly hidden from the view.
- Okay. I got it. - Let's go.
- How much is it? - 300 dollars.
Okay. Okay.
That's incredible.
It's meaningless for us to split up.
- That's right. - We should stay together.
If we split up, we won't be able to remove the name tags.
- We just need to get the captain. - That's right.
The captain will be protected...
- by Jong Kook. - Jong Kook will stay by his side.
Who will stay by Captain Jeon's side?
- Seriously. - I think...
So Min should take care of herself.
- So Min. - Take care of yourself.
You should hide underground.
(Why don't you dig a hole in the ground?)
We need to find the treasures.
(Unlike the relaxed Team Face,)
(Team Voice focuses on finding the treasures.)
- Where is it? - I found one!
Did you find one? Okay.
(She finds one.)
- 100 dollars. - Okay.
100 dollars. Okay.
- Okay. - Did you find one?
(Team Voice prepares to turn the tables.)
Ha Na.
- My goodness. - Let's go.
Good job. Good job.
There might be more.
The atmosphere is friendly.
You know, our team is too weak.
- Our team... - It's okay. We are doing well.
We are winning. Let's defend our position.
We don't need to do anything. We just need to defend our position.
We are winning.
(The best offense is a good defense.)
(The time passes.)
- There they are! - Where?
There.
- Come here. - Haha.
Haha is there as well.
- Really? - Haha is there as well.
Haha, come here.
(Unaware of the danger, they keep searching.)
Let's take off his name tag.
Let's go. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Hold on. Be careful. - Let's go.
- Be careful. - Let's go.
(The sound of the approaching bells...)
(is noticed by Haha.)
Jong Kook!
- What? - They are coming.
- They are coming. - Come here.
This is...
(He has to find the treasures and protect the captain.)
- Se Chan, keep looking. - Okay.
(Ha Na looks for the treasures on the other side...)
(and finds Kwang Soo.)
Come here, Ha Na. Let's run away.
(She lures Kwang Soo away from the captain.)
There she is!
Run! Catch Haha! You need to catch Haha!
They are going that way.
(He suddenly turns towards Haha.)
Be careful.
Take out the captain.
(Our target is the captain.)
(He hears the command.)
(Haha and Jong Kook are trapped.)
- Go to the other side. - Be careful.
It will be over once we take Haha out.
They are coming.
Where is the way?
Is there no way out?
They are trapped.
- Go that way. - Let's go up.
Let's go up.
I will fend them off.
It will be over once we take Haha out!
(They run to the forest.)
There they are.
Be careful.
(The 5 members of Team Face surround the 2 of them.)
(You can't pass.)
- Take him out. - Hurry up and go.
Get Haha. You need to get Haha.
(Jong Kook stops Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.)
Get Haha.
Go to the other side!
Get Haha!
(While Jong Kook stops the others, Haha runs.)
Get Haha.
Get Haha. Come on.
Run, Haha.
- Go. - Run, Haha.
He is going to the other side!
(Jong Kook stops Kwang Soo from pursuing Haha.)
- Gosh, he is so fast. - Hurry!
(Haha,)
(are you running away?)
Hurry up. Soo Hyang, stop panting and take off his name tag!
(I am okay as long as you are safe.)
Take off Jong Kook's name tag.
Hurry up. Take off Jong Kook's name tag.
(I am happy that I got to save you.)
(Jong Kook, thank you.)
Take off Jong Kook's name tag.
Take off Jong Kook's name tag. You did it.
(He protects Haha and gets taken out.)
- Good job, Soo Hyang. - Did Haha run away?
- He ran away. - Thank goodness.
Which way did he go?
(I wonder who will protect Haha now.)
Haha is fast.
(This is a disaster.)
Kim Jong Kook is out.
(The hero is out.)
We have to find the treasures fast. We have to find them.
The other team is chasing after Haha.
- Really? - We have to...
We have to find the treasures fast.
(To turn the tables, they must find the treasures.)
- Okay. - I found it,
- but we should... - We can't get Haha.
We should...
We must find the treasures fast before Haha gets eliminated.
(While Ha Na and Se Chan find the treasures,)
(Ji Hyo finds one as well.)
(They still have a chance to turn the tables.)
My ankles hurt.
(Captain Haha manages to escape.)
(He is really nervous without Jong Kook.)
(Where is Haha?)
(It's Haha!)
(He doesn't get to take a breather.)
There he is!
Go to the opposite direction!
(Jae Seok joins in.)
(Stop right there.)
Keep going! We must get Haha!
(Haha without Jong Kook is like Pororo without his glasses.)
Hold on.
Let me go this once.
(Come on.)
- This is the last round. - We have no choice.
(Jong Kook, where are you? I miss you.)
(I wish I weren't eliminated.)
Jae Seok, please.
(Haha misses him dearly.)
(Captain Haha is out.)
The end!
(Team Voice's treasure hunt ends.)
(I hope the members found a lot of treasures.)
This is a disaster.
Round One is over. The teams will switch positions.
You saw that, right?
- We did it. - We were cool.
Our team is really strong.
I didn't think that would be the case.
Seriously.
- You know who helped, right? - Who helped?
- Soo Hyang is the difference. - I am the new face.
Jong Kook must be mad.
I should finish them off.
(I want my revenge.)
He might rip off your back along with the name tag.
That's scary.
Be careful. He is mad.
(I am sure he will go for my name tag first.)
Our team is the best.
- Our team is the best. - That's right.
- Yes. - This is so much fun.
Right?
Let's begin the treasure hunt.
The two of you should take this side.
We will meet in the end...
(Team Voice plans the attack.)
so that they can't run away.
Taking off So Min's name tag would be the best.
- Okay. - We must remove her name tag.
We can't let them get more money.
- That's right. - We found...
a considerable amount of money.
That's right.
We must take out So Min or the other members...
before they find the treasures.
We must take off their name tags.
Let's take out whomever we find first.
Okay.
Round Two starts now.
(Team Voice is attacking, and Team Face is defending.)
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
(They run at full speed.)
It's dangerous for us to stay together.
- What should we do? - Let's split up.
So Min, it would be better for you to hide.
Where should I hide?
Behind the toilet?
Hide behind the toilet.
(I am sure no one will know.)
It will be too smelly.
Go behind the toilet.
She is incredible.
(For the team, I can endure the smell.)
- Kwang Soo, stay by her side. - Okay.
- Let's find the treasures. - Let's find them.
- Go that way. I will go this way. - Okay.
(Seok Jin, Jae Seok, and Soo Hyang go looking for the treasures.)
This is the perfect place to hide the treasures.
(The members of Team Voice split up to find So Min.)
I will go up this way.
(So Min, where are you?)
(They search every nook and cranny.)
It's too smelly here.
It's too smelly here. What should I do?
- This is too much. - It is.
I feel like there is poop right in front of my nose.
No one will find us if we stay here.
- Gosh, it's smelly. - I feel like I am going to puke.
(There is a possibility the smell will knock them out.)
For goodness' sake.
(She heads to the smelly place.)
- Move closer to the wall. - Move closer.
- Move closer to the wall. - Come on.
(Don't let them see you.)
If we get caught, I will stop them.
- You should go up that way. - That way?
Okay.
(Is she hiding in here?)
(Even Jong Kook approaches the toilet.)
(This is bad.)
(She searches inside the toilet.)
(The extreme tension numbs their sense of smell.)
(Their hearts beat faster than the sound of the bells.)
It would be absurd.
(Is she behind the toilet?)
(She isn't here.)
(Her heart almost stops.)
I am sure she is hiding somewhere.
She's going away.
(I think that took 10 years off my life.)
It wouldn't be here, right?
(Soo Hyang is looking for the treasures.)
By the way,
(In the middle of the treasure hunt)
this is nice.
Fall is here.
(She fully enjoys the phytoncide and the mood of fall.)
The air is really nice.
(She has all the time in the world.)
The weather is the treasure.
(Isn't it a good day to get your name tag ripped off?)
Hold on.
(Screaming)
(How dare you take off my name tag? I'm gunning for you.)
(Did you think you'd be okay?)
Wait. Hold on.
(Eye for an eye.)
No!
I'm sorry.
(He successfully gets his revenge.)
- That was unbelievable. - Here you go.
(Trembling)
That was so scary.
That was so scary. He completely got his revenge.
(Now that I'm done with my revenge, let's go find So Min.)
(Meanwhile...)
- I checked that part earlier. - You did?
(Meanwhile, Ha Na, Haha, and Se Chan are looking for So Min.)
(They already checked most of the places.)
Let's go this way.
- The restroom? - No.
Let's hurry.
(What?)
(Let's check it out for now.)
The restroom?
(It's coming.)
(The sound of their bells are coming close.)
The restroom? Are they in the restroom?
Ha Na, I already checked.
You did?
(Just in case,)
(she checks the back.)
Are they in the back?
(They're totally meticulous.)
(What? Did he say, "back"?)
(What should we do?)
(I found them!)
(She finds Captain So Min who was in hiding at last.)
(Kwang Soo blocks Ha Na and Se Chan.)
- Catch her. - Hold on. Let me go.
- Go, Ha Na. You should go. - Run away.
- So Min, run away! - Kwang Soo is out.
Climb up.
(It's impossible to stop Haha too.)
- Go! - No!
- So Min. - Hold on a second.
Hit them. Kick them!
No, not yet.
- So Min, run! - No!
- So Min, kick them! - Okay, I'll go down.
(Ha Na gets close to So Min while So Min is resisting.)
(She held out even if it meant she had to smell the restroom.)
(So Min doesn't have a way out...)
(because of Ha Na's thoroughness to check the back of the restroom.)
(So Min, Captain of Team Face, is out.)
- Come on. - I got her.
There's no need. It's over.
(He's in despair.)
Gosh, how did you find me?
How did you find me?
(Legendary Treasure Hunt, their last mission, is over.)
Your final mission is over.
During the race, some of you...
- Did they find it? - found the treasures.
Really?
All right, first. Team Voice's captain...
will divide the total amount of cash prize first.
Goodness, the captains have all the power today.
(How much money will Captain Haha give to his members?)
I'm sure it must be hard for the captains too.
(It must not be easy to divide the money among the members.)
All right. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
So Min.
- So Min. - Ms. Jeon.
- You have a big responsibility. - So Min.
Should I lift you?
- Ms. Jeon. - So Min.
Just remember my last voice when I was telling you to run.
I've never made such a difficult decision.
Soo Hyang was the only one who didn't do anything. Remember.
(You know how I feel about you, right?)
What are you doing?
- Is this the total amount of money? - This is the total amount of money.
(Will she distribute the money to Jae Seok and Seok Jin as promised?)
Can I make a transfer? Can I make a transfer from my account?
- A transfer? - Yes. To someone else.
Here's the result of the race, Legendary Captain.
(The total amount of cash prize for Team Face is...)
As for Team Face's cash prize,
they have 1,200 dollars in total.
(The final cash prize is 1,200 dollars.)
(That's lower than I expected.)
- It's because of the loan. - Is that so?
As for Team Voice's cash prize...
(Please...)
I found it.
(During the final mission, with an elaborate plan,)
(they didn't lose the hope of winning the race.)
(Let's beat them! Races with twists are the most fun.)
As for Team Voice's...
(Considering the money we found,)
(it's enough to turn the tables around for this race.)
(The total amount of cash prize for Team Voice is...)
It's 890 dollars. It's Team Face's win.
- Okay. - Okay.
- I can't believe it. We won. - Our team won.
- I didn't even imagine we'd win. - This is amazing.
I thought we would...
So Min, you should've picked me.
- I thought we had a shot. - Right.
So Min, I thought that too.
- Team Face won the race. - Okay.
- We'll give you a meaningful gift. - You'll give us a present?
Since it's autumn when reading is most fun,
we'll give you 5 classic books. You can each read 1 book.
- You'll give books? - That's great.
I'm so jealous.
(Fill the heart of your knowledge.)
- Seriously. - Thank you.
- Hold on. Among these five books, - You're smiling too much.
- I want Seok Jin to have this book. - Okay.
(A book for me?)
"The Last Leaf".
("The Last Leaf" suits Seok Jin perfectly.)
Seok Jin, please don't fall.
(Seok Jin is hanging by a thread.)
- He's barely hanging there. - "Hanging there"?
Hey, this one is "Crime and Punishment".
You'll read the first part.
- Isn't that So Min? - You'll read the second part.
1st and 2nd books of "Crime and Punishment".
- "My Sweet Orange Tree" is yours. - It suits her.
I'll take "The Great Gatsby". He'll take "The Old Man and the Sea".
(The oldest member will take one more book.)
("The Last Leaf and the Sea")
- It worked out perfectly. - I'll give one to Ha Na.
I can't let go of "The Old Man and the Sea".
(This is mine.)
I'll take this. You take "The Last Leaf".
- Really? Thank you. - Yes.
- Seriously. - From the winning team,
- One of us will face it. - the one with the least money is...
Let's do this.
You should have picked me.
- It's not you. How could I do that? - Exactly. You should've done that.
I would have been fine with the penalty.
Me too. I would've been okay. I haven't been here in a while.
If anyone has to face it, I'd feel better if it was me.
- My heart is beating fast. - Soo Hyang should get it.
- Let her face it. - The one with the most money is...
- So Min. She has 1,590 dollars. - That's right.
(Captain So Min has 1,590 dollars.)
- What? - She has 1,590 dollars?
(The cash prize is 1,200 dollars. And she has 1,590 dollars?)
- No, this wasn't planned. - I don't believe this.
(They can't believe their ears. Did we hear that right?)
- No, this wasn't planned. - 1,590 dollars?
- Hold on, what's going on? - Then the rest of the money...
- is the loan. - All of them are placed last.
- That's not it. No, it's not. - Is everyone placed last?
- That's not true at all. - Do we owe money?
- No. - The second place goes to...
Soo Hyang with 300 dollars.
- You gave me 300 dollars? - That's a lot.
(Thank goodness. I dodged the last place.)
- The third place goes to... - It depends on the contribution.
- Kwang Soo with 110 dollars. - Okay!
He's in third?
(Smelling the toilets with her paid off!)
What is this? Then it's Seok Jin or Jae Seok.
(One of them is placed last.)
- Hey, you. Are you serious? - My gosh.
- It's not me, right? - Seok Jin.
- Okay, okay. - Jae Seok.
- This is what's important. - Fine, I got it.
- I thought... - I know myself.
- All right. Let's go. - You have 1,590 dollars.
(Please let me not be placed last.)
- The fourth place... - Okay.
(The one in 4th place will dodge the penalty.)
- Who's in 4th? - He has 50 dollars.
- 50 dollars. - 50 dollars. That's great.
- Fourth place will be safe. - I'd be grateful.
That's good enough.
(Which one will be placed 4th?)
- Jee Seok Jin. - Yes!
(I'm not placed last!)
(By default, Jae Seok will face the penalty.)
- Jae Seok owes 850 dollars. - Yes!
You got this all wrong.
(I'm already upset to face the penalty after winning.)
- No, listen. Hear me out. - You owe them money.
- Hey. - It just happened during the race.
I don't think it could just happen.
Jae Seok didn't contribute to our victory at all.
- That's not true. - You have 1,590 dollars.
- It's Team Voice's turn. - I'm a great captain.
For Team Voice, only the member in first place will not face it.
We'll start from the bottom.
Se Chan is placed last and owes 20 dollars.
- I owe money? - He owes money?
- He only owes 20 dollars. - Hey.
The losing team owes only 20 dollars.
- How could you be so heartless? - My gosh.
And I'll announce the fourth place.
It's Haha with 10 dollars.
(Haha has 10 dollars.)
(He's the captain, but he's in 4th place?)
- He placed himself fourth. - My gosh.
- I knew he'd do this. Goodness. - My gosh.
- And... - I had no expectations.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Ha Na are...
- placed 1st with 300 dollars. - My goodness.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Ha Na are placed 1st altogether.)
- Seriously? - What will happen to us?
- The three of you are exempted. - Really?
(They won't face the penalty.)
(This is Haha's leadership skill.)
- Haha, why? - Is this even allowed?
- This can't be allowed. - This isn't fair.
- Seriously? - This isn't fair.
- I knew you'd be great. - Haha, what about me?
What about me? Answer me.
- Listen. Stop acting cool. - What was that? What are you doing?
What about me? Come on, this isn't fair. You can't do that.
- He can't do this. - What is this?
- Hey, what did you do? - Listen.
You should have placed all of us in first place.
If we were all in first place, no one would've been in last.
I should have placed some of you in last.
- You're going to face the penalty? - This doesn't make sense.
I should have done that.
(3 members are chosen to face the penalty.)
All right. Three of you will face the penalty,
but we only prepared two cannons.
- Among the 3 of you... - I owe 10 dollars.
He owes 20 dollars, and Jae Seok, 850 dollars.
- Race of Wits. 1. - 2.
(They're suddenly playing the Game of Wits.)
(He hasn't grasped the situation. He's in a daze.)
Hold on. Wait.
(You love the game, but the game will end you.)
- That was amazing. - Hold on a second.
- You love the Race of Wits. - We have to say, "start".
- No, you love this game. - We have to say, "start".
Please go sit over there.
- Why would I do that? - Go sit there. You love this game.
- Go sit, Jae Seok. - You lost the game. Go sit, please.
- We didn't start yet. - Sit over there.
- Please go sit over there. - You love that game. Come on, sit.
(Jae Seok who's slow-witted will face the penalty.)
I can't believe this.
All right. You two must decide between yourselves.
Why don't I choose one of them?
(How about I choose?)
(Darn it.)
- That's a great idea. - This is good, right?
All right then. Jae Seok will choose someone.
(Hello, quick-witted friends.)
- "Infinite Challenge". - Haha.
(He's quick on his feet.)
- "Infinite Challenge". - Haha, you can't do that.
What are you doing?
(Think about our old days together.)
Let's smile even if it hurts.
It hurts.
(I know how you feel, Haha.)
(Our friendship is very special, isn't it?)
- You should face the penalty. - Okay!
(That's why you should face the penalty.)
(Yes! I'm exempted. I'm saved!)
"Infinite Challenge".
- "Infinite Challenge". - "Infinite Challenge".
(Let's continue our friendship all the way to the cannons.)
Okay!
(Our friendship is indeed infinite.)
Say a few words beforehand.
Everyone, I had so much fun today.
(These two original captains put on the best performances today.)
Thanks to the members of Running Man,
I had such a great time today.
- All right. - The 2 of you should count to 3.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- In 2, 3 - In 2, 3.
(It hits their faces perfectly.)
That was great.
(The Legendary Captain Race ends.)
(Next week)
Sit down.
(They disregard the age.)
Gosh, you ugly jerk!
(Mockery is an everyday occurrence.)
(There is no rank in Running Man.)
Why would you hit a senior member?
(It's time to form a new rank.)
(That's how the war of the rank begins.)
(They let go of their images to go up the rank.)
(They struggle to bring changes to the show.)
(If you win the war,)
(can you rule the show?)
(However,)
(someone is changing the show.)
(The secret of the war of the rank get revealed.)
(What's the secret that shocks everyone?)
(Game of Thrones)