- Hello.
- Hi, hi.
- Hi.
Hello, Si Hyun. You're here today.
- Hello.
- Hi, everyone.
(Wait. What's that?)
- Can you film his bottom?
- Hi.
(Cameramen, can you film his bottom?)
(His pants are sagging today.)
- Look at his bottom.
- Hold on. Look at this.
- Come on.
- Show it to them just once.
- Show it to the viewers.
- Why would I do that?
- Look at your bottom.
- These are just pants.
Your pants look weird.
I don't know if I have to pull up the pants or lower them.
- They are baggy pants, - Those are baggy pants.
But his pants are too tight.
- Take a photo.
- They are baggy pants.
Why are you taking a photo?
It's because your bottom isn't curvy.
My bottom isn't the problem. It's the pants.
What is it?
Hold on. Is the problem with the design?
Or is it your body?
(What's the problem here?)
- It's him. His bottom isn't curvy.
- The pants are designed this way,
- It's not that. - and his body doesn't suit it.
- His bottom isn't perky.
- They aren't curvy at all.
(Both the design and his figure are the problem.)
There's this thing inside his pants. Look.
- I wore a diaper just in case.
- What's this?
I think he was trying to cover up that his bottom was flat.
- Put pads on your bottom.
- Yes, you should wear those.
- We wear that for the colonoscopy.
- Hey.
Don't pay attention to my pants.
- Your pants are delaying the shoot.
- Stop that!
- Why did you wear baggy pants?
- My gosh.
- You're unbelievable.
- The string is thin too.
Kwang Soo, hold on a second.
(The shape... What... What?)
- They are yellow.
- My gosh, the pants.
- What's wrong with my pants?
- Hey.
(What did the pants look like?)
- What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with my pants?
Lower the pants, will you? My gosh.
- What should I do?
- Hey.
- It looked weird.
- Hold on.
We wear those pants when we undergo the colonoscopy.
Hey.
- What should I do?
- It's not that.
Kwang Soo, you should tie it here.
- How?
- Tie it in the back.
We'll tie it with a rubber band.
- Let's tie it.
- Hey, you should tie it.
- Right here.
- There you go.
- Why did you wear this pair?
- This is it.
- You shouldn't have worn them.
- That's a good idea, Jae Seok.
- He really is high-maintenance.
- That's perfect.
- Look what I did for you.
- It's all done now.
(He unexpectedly acquires a tail.)
- Is it okay? Thank you, Jae Seok.
- It worked.
(My gosh, let me touch it.)
- Look. Look at that.
- It looks good now.
- What is this?
- It's all done now.
- It's good now.
- What's up with my pants?
- It's finished now.
- Hey.
Being his stylist is a hard job.
Seok Jin dressed too young for his age.
- This is too much.
- Now, I am...
Don't you think pink is too much for your age?
- No, no.
- Isn't that your son's?
I want to wear outfits that make me look young instead of handsome.
That's my focus.
At this rate, he will wear baby clothes.
(Following your logic, you'll end up in baby clothes soon.)
Seok Jin, how young do you want to look?
- Seok Jin.
- If you want to do that...
- Later, his wife will...
wrap him up in a blanket.
(He will be wrapped with a blanket.)
"Hello, I know that he has to film today."
"I brought him."
During the breaks, she will change his diaper.
(Changing diapers during breaks)
(Seok Jin's time goes backward.)
- Okay.
- Give him baby clothes.
- I wouldn't look good in those.
- Get them in pink.
- Baby clothes don't have pants.
- Come again?
(What? That came out of nowhere.)
- Why wouldn't there be pants?
- Probably not.
- Why do you think about that stuff?
- It's not that.
- I was just curious about them.
- My gosh.
- Right? There are no pants.
- He can wear the diaper.
(Actually, there are no pants.)
Before we wrap up the Family Package Project,
- it's a break week.
- That's why...
- the others aren't here.
- We'll have a break.
Sang Yeob and I exchange text messages every other day.
- My gosh.
- He's so talkative.
- It was due to the scheduling.
- They wanted to come today.
- They are actor and actresses.
- Right. Today, we will take...
a break and have TV Rating Notice Race Part Two.
(TV Rating Notice Race Part 2)
It's about time.
- Yes, please!
- Yes, let's change that!
- It lasted longer than I thought.
- This is great.
- Yes, it lasted quite long.
- It lasted more than a month.
(Jae Seok won the chance to direct the first TV rating notice.)
(He directed his TV rating notice with animals and sea creatures.)
The current one is great. Why would we change that?
I keep missing the opening segment because I don't want to see that.
Seriously. I don't want to watch that notice.
- It comes up again midway.
- Exactly. Right?
I get called an idiot every week.
- It's in the clip.
- Right. That's right.
That's the only thing I hear from the notice.
The part two of the TV rating notice is called Have a Nice Day.
(Have a Nice Day)
Since it's part two, we've improved the race.
Not only will you get to direct the five-second clip,
but you'll also handle the poster and photo on our official website.
- Even the photo on the website?
- That's a lot.
The same photo will be used for the website, right?
- It will be our official photo.
- That's great.
We'll distribute the posters all over the TV station too.
Can you throw in one more?
(One more, please.)
When the preview airs,
can't you add, "So and So's Running Man" in it?
- No, they can't do that.
- That's being greedy.
- Right. That's asking too much.
- People think it's Jae Seok's.
It could be, "Haha's Running Man" or "Seok Jin's Running Man".
- Haha is trying too hard.
- Haha, cut it out.
Shouldn't we try harder?
Haha.
Don't overdo yourself because you lost a weekend-show.
(Don't overdo yourself because you lost a weekend-show.)
- Just carry on like usual.
- He wanted to spice things up.
Haha, don't feel hasty.
"Don't feel hasty."
You already feel anxious?
What's wrong with him today? It's making me uncomfortable.
- Hey, take it slow.
- He's making it uneasy for me.
Don't show them your weak side.
- What is this?
- Rest on Saturdays.
Just for a while. Just rest for a while.
- Keep your chin up!
- I'll keep my chin up!
I can do this!
(I'll keep my chin up. I can do this!)
(Our challenge...)
(can be put on hold for a while.)
I saw Jun Ha in passing. I only smelled meat on his hands.
He's been having a lot of barbecue.
Why are they doing this on this show?
- I have a problem with Haha.
- What is it?
We do a lot of businesses together.
I feel like his value is decreasing.
- Really? But he's on Running Man.
- Even so.
If Jong Kook feels this way...
I mean, he loves Haha unconditionally.
- His value seems to be decreasing.
- My gosh.
You will have two rounds of missions today.
After the missions, the winner will win the TV rating notice trio and...
- direct however they want.
- This is great. Great!
Before we start the race,
you will come up with your own storyboards...
- and present them.
- We have to do that again?
- Right, we should do that.
- With the clip, I brought fame...
- to Ji Hyo and Haha.
- What are you talking about?
(Haha was Toshio, and Ji Hyo was Kaonashi. They became stars?)
- She was Kaonashi.
- Me? Me?
I turned you into stars with the notice.
- Thank you!
- No problem.
(Thank you, Jae Seok!)
(I did it for you, punk.)
- That's enough.
- Don't be weird.
Why do you keep hugging each other?
(We don't need to rush.)
I can do this. I can do this.
That was great. Well done.
- Right.
- That was good.
- Whenever he hugs you, - Kwang Soo.
- Your value increases.
- Is that so?
(Is it because of Jae Seok's influence?)
Come on.
- Hug him. Hug him often.
- What are you talking about?
- You're unbelievable.
- "Hug him."
- Hold my hands. Hold them.
- Hug him. Hug him often.
(Riding his coattail is the best.)
Then should we go draw?
- Let's do that.
- Okay.
What should I draw?
- Can we search things online?
- Sorry?
- We can use the Internet?
- Of course, we can.
You can do whatever you want.
So Min, you're not scheduled to be in a film or a drama, right?
No, why?
- I thought about cutting your hair.
- No, you can't.
- No, no.
- Are you on a project?
What did you say? Cut my hair?
We won't be using a wig. You will really have your hair cut.
You will really cut my hair?
You can't use a wig.
Okay, fine. Are you good with shaving your head?
(Okay, fine. Are you good with shaving your head?)
- Let's do this.
- So Min.
The Chinese queue would be funny. The Chinese queue.
- We can spell R with it.
- He will have hair on the back.
- He will have hair up to here.
- Right.
I'll just have hair in the back? Okay.
How about just poop?
Poop?
- Poop?
- With my hair?
(That's going too far.)
- Will he pluck all of his hair?
- All right then.
I will base mine on a film I recently watched.
"The Greatest Showman".
(I have my inspiration.)
(It's a musical film about a circus troupe's fight against prejudice.)
There are some characters in the film.
- The bearded man. The giant.
- Right, right.
I will use those characters.
So Min, you'll be doing this.
Jae Seok, how?
- How will I hang onto that?
- Right now...
(So Min will do an advanced, aerial stunt act.)
- How will I hang onto that?
- You'll be doing this.
That's none of my concern.
That's right. It's not his concern.
You can use duct tape, can't you?
As long as Jae Seok doesn't win...
I really hope mine gets picked this time. I really do.
As for Kwang Soo,
it's bigger than last time.
- How much bigger can it get?
- What's that?
- Sorry?
- I'm afraid of heights.
(Stop it, please.)
- I can't go higher than that.
- This is a circus troupe.
Every time yours gets picked, I'll be at least 3m tall.
(What a coincidence.)
Hey, I'm trying to make you famous.
- Okay.
- That's the spirit.
Ji Hyo, what about yours?
I'm going to use kaonashis, Jae Seok.
How many are there?
Everyone ought to dress up as it.
That's a family of kaonashis.
Everyone is a kaonashi.
(This time, everyone is a kaonashi.)
Hey, don't you think it'd be too much if everyone was a kaonashi?
- That's cute.
- And as for Jong Kook,
he will be wearing a sleeveless top.
(Jong Kook will get special treatment.)
- That's adorable.
- He will wear a tank top?
- Hey, that's not the same.
- I like that idea.
- That's a good idea. Good job.
- That's great.
You're doing well, Ji Hyo!
- It only sounds the same.
- That's a good idea.
Everyone will be dressed up as a kaonashi,
- but Jong Kook will be...
- He will have manlike fortitude.
- He has broad shoulders.
- The tank top will look tough.
I can wear the tank top and act tough?
(Look forward to your part, Jong Kook.)
- Isn't that Seok Jin?
- Ji Hyo, I like that.
Right. I forgot about Seok Jin.
(She realizes she forgot Seok Jin after finishing her drawing.)
Hey, are you serious?
My gosh. What do I do?
- That happens.
- Hey, Seok Jin.
- I have a problem.
- Make him the lotus flower.
- The lotus flower?
- Don't forget me.
- Everyone, did you all finish?
- Yes.
- Let's take turns presenting.
- Okay.
It's my favorite anime series, "Demetan Croaker, The Boy Frog".
("Demetan Croaker, The Boy Frog" family)
So Min, your drawing is very good.
As you can see,
Haha is Demetan,
- the main character.
- I am in the middle!
Thank you.
He is Demetan, and Ji Hyo is Ranatan.
- Ranatan.
- Yes, Ranatan.
- Why do you keep...
- It's cute.
Treating them like they are lovers?
There is nothing between them.
I gave the matter much thought,
but they resembled the characters the most.
Now,
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...
are Demetan's dad and mom.
- What?
- I must ask,
- why is Kwang Soo Demetan's mom?
- Is there a problem?
- Who is the mom?
- The character has my eyes.
- Kwang Soo is. Her silhouette...
- Kwang Soo is the female frog.
- I guess they have similar looks.
- In the anime series, you'll see...
- that they both have a sleek image.
- They have similar looks.
Isn't Demetan's mom sick?
(Isn't Demetan's mom sick?)
You are right. She is sick.
You should dress up as a woman.
Jong Kook is Gyata.
- It suits him.
- He has a big build like Gyata.
- Se Chan is Zari.
- Zari, the crayfish.
I forgot about Seok Jin at first.
- That's why...
- I can't believe you did that.
- I drew...
- There aren't a lot of members.
Grandpa Loach.
- There is Grandpa Loach.
- He is in the anime series.
- He is very kind.
- Really?
- He is wise.
- He helps the others.
He is in the anime series.
Seok Jin is Grandpa Loach.
Everyone will have balloons on their bellies.
- On our bellies?
- Yes.
- Will they pop?
- Yes, they will get bigger.
In the corner, I will say,
"Running Man is..."
Haha will say, "for 12 years..."
- Ji Hyo will say, - Gosh, you are so nice to me.
"and older".
Then Jong Kook and Se Chan...
will pop the balloons on the members' bellies.
- Do we punch their bellies?
- Yes.
(Punching?)
You should remember that this show is for 12 years and older.
- Don't you think it's too violent?
- It's too violent.
This show shouldn't have such a violent TV rating notice.
Ji Hyo and Seok Jin will be exempt.
Only Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Haha will get their balloons popped...
by the two villains.
(Only Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Haha are in this predicament.)
- The two villains.
- We became villains.
May I pop their bellies instead?
Of course.
However, you are not allowed to express pain.
(Don't show your pain even if you get punched.)
- We are not allowed to show pain.
- No.
- You need to stay cheerful.
- That's right.
Then you must say, "Ribbit, ribbit."
- After the balloons pop?
- Yes. After the balloons pop.
"Running Man is for 12 years and older."
Punch, punch, punch. "Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit."
(She gives them a summary.)
(I like the scenario.)
I want to see...
- if I will throw a good punch.
- For goodness' sake.
- It's like a baby's doodle.
- An elementary schooler's doodle.
As you can see, the theme is "The Greatest Showman".
- I couldn't tell.
That's not "The Greatest Showman".
Anyone would know it depicts "The Greatest Showman".
If you have seen the movie, you will go,
"Right."
My drawing will touch you...
the same way the movie did.
- He really can't draw.
- Seriously.
That looks nothing like "The Greatest Showman".
Hugh Jackman's character, the greatest showman,
- will be played by me.
- The main character.
As you can see,
there is a werewolf.
- Is that a werewolf?
- Yes.
Isn't it a Yorkshire Terrier?
- It's it a fluffy dog?
- Anyone...
- who has seen the movie...
- From that drawing?
Would know it's a werewolf.
It's a sapsali.
- No, it's not. It's a werewolf.
- How is that a werewolf?
- Who will play it?
- Se Chan.
- Me?
- Se Chan will play it.
I think I will look terrible.
A werewolf would be a good choice.
- Also, Kwang Soo will be...
- The Joker.
Taller than the last time...
so that he'll go out of the screen.
(Kwang Soo, the giraffe)
- He will go out of the screen.
- How high should my heels be?
- A very tall man.
- A very tall man?
Until when do I have to play a very tall man?
You can be a joker.
Another choice would be a building.
Let's say this show is taking place in the 63 Building.
- That's a good idea.
- It's monumental.
It can be the 63 Building or Lotte World Tower.
Why would 63 Building appear in "The Greatest Showman"?
Kwang Soo always plays the same type of characters.
As you can see, So Min is hanging...
upside down.
- Why do I always hang from things?
- Blood will rush to her face.
Actually, she has...
the most important part in my scenario.
In "The Greatest Showman", the character is beautiful.
Is there really a character who hangs upside down?
She has a love interest, too.
(It's a romantic role with a love interest.)
So Min isn't playing that character.
I will dress her up as another animal.
(Her dream is shattered.)
She will be a bat or something.
Is there no bat in "The Greatest Showman"?
No.
So Min will be a bat...
- or something.
- Something that hangs.
Now, Ji Hyo is...
someone I like very much.
I made her a star by assigning her the right character.
Ji Hyo rose to stardom.
Kaonashi and Toshio.
(The super rookies, Toshio and Kaonashi)
They will appear in the TV rating notice once more.
(It's all thanks to their popularity.)
Is that dot supposed to be me?
(Is that dot supposed to be me?)
Yes.
Is that me?
- Okay.
- The two of them...
- We are a set.
- A set.
Since they are my favorite characters,
they will make an appearance.
We will need makeup.
I know.
My scenario is very impactful...
- and simple.
- Let's see it.
The title is, "With Se Chan at the Fish Market".
It sounds like a hassle.
(With Se Chan at the Fish Market)
I dressed up as a fish for the last TV rating notice.
- I was so unsatisfied with it...
- That's right.
That I decided to make everyone dress up as fish.
Upon consideration, I realized that each member...
- resembled a specific fish.
- Yes, there is.
Since Haha has...
an image of a delinquent, he will be flying fish.
- Flying fish. I like it.
- Flying fish.
As for So Min, I couldn't decide easily.
Because you told me that the catfish costume suited me,
you will be a catfish.
- Catfish.
- So Min...
will wear the same costume.
- So Min will be a catfish.
- Catfish.
She will have whiskers.
(I must avoid it.)
- Jae Seok...
- Which fish will I be?
Likes to chitchat and talk.
- Dried pollack.
- Dried pollack?
- He should be dried.
It's impossible to dress up as a dried fish!
- It's possible...
- He should be dried.
To dress up as a dried fish.
He is like dried seafood.
Dried seafood? For goodness' sake.
Seok Jin is...
This is a bit heartbreaking.
When I am next to him, I can see his white hair.
(Seok Jin is in his 50s.)
That reminded me of white marlin.
- White marlin.
- He has white hair.
(He accepts his fate.)
Why doesn't he play shellfish?
- Clam?
- Cockle.
- Then he will be shellfish...
- Sea cucumber.
That is closed.
He will be inside.
(Se Chan's choice is a closed clam.)
- He will be inside it.
- He will be inside the shell.
- Will it be closed?
- It will be closed.
A closed clam.
How about he sticks out his tongue?
(He can stick his tongue out of the shell.)
Okay. Hold on.
(He can be a scallop.)
I came up with a scenario.
It's Kaonashi's Day.
- She was Kaonashi last time.
- Kaonashi.
(Kaonashi's Day)
Jong Kook will be behind me.
- I am still thinking.
- He is wearing a sleeveless top.
I will make him wear a sleeveless top.
I don't know if it will be a cropped sleeveless top...
- or a regular one.
- Go with a cropped top.
- Let's go with a cropped top.
- That's right.
It's not appropriate for 12-year-olds.
Go with a cropped top. He went shirtless in "Mom's Diary".
That's right. Let's go with it.
People might like it.
- Female viewers will love it.
- That's right.
- They will love it.
- Also,
everyone...
- will gather slowly.
- We will gather around.
- We'll see only half of Kwang Soo.
- Why?
(The members and half of Kwang Soo)
- Only a half of him will appear.
- Why?
- He will be at the edge.
- That's right.
I thought it was a tree.
Only half of him will appear.
What did you do to make Ji Hyo love you so much?
Seok Jin is next.
(It's Seok Jin's turn to present his scenario.)
Seok Jin's drawing is a sea of blood.
(Seok Jin's drawing is a sea of blood.)
- Look at the color.
- Sea of blood.
- What is wrong with you?
- It's a misunderstanding.
This is a red carpet.
A red carpet in Hollywood.
(The Global Stars on the Red Carpet)
Which one is Jong Kook?
- My drawing is a bit off, - What is that?
But this is Jong Kook...
as Sailor Moon.
(This is Jong Kook as Sailor Moon.)
- My drawing is a bit off.
- I see.
Sailor Moon is too much.
It will be too much of a hassle. Let's prevent him from winning.
(Let's prevent him from winning.)
I won't let that happen.
- I will do my best.
- Let's work together.
I won't let that happen.
"It will be too much of a hassle."
It's a scenario no one wants.
Mine is simple.
The makeup will be simple, too.
My scenario involves the sea.
A mudflat...
- by the sea.
- Let's stay inside the studio.
We don't want to go to the sea.
(Mudflat Is My World)
Dressed in a suit, I will look at the sea.
You should wear those pants. Gosh, what is that?
Gosh, what is that?
What is up with your bottom?
Those pants are for endoscopy.
I know because I got one.
Then I will turn around and say,
"Running Man is..."
In the distance...
will be the seven of you dressed up as spoon worms.
(7 members as spoon worms)
You will shout, "for 12 years and older".
- Only you are human.
- Yes.
You should wear those pants.
Haha, you will be...
(He clenches his teeth.)
Haha will be inside the sea.
- He will be inside the sea.
- He will be in the water.
That's right. He will be a spoon worm in the water.
Okay.
Okay. I will do that if you wear those pants.
(He pokes fun at Kwang Soo again.)
He will be deep inside the sea.
He will be inside the sea.
- That's my scenario.
- Okay.
- It's simpler than I expected.
- That's right.
Why does Jong Kook's drawing...
have everyone hanging?
Mine is simple. You will hang from the horizontal bar.
(Prince Jong Kook of the Horizontal Bar Kingdom)
- In teams of two, - He loves it too much.
The members will do a chin-up and shout, "Running Man is".
Why would we do that?
Why would we do a chin-up? Isn't that too much?
Why?
- It's too hard.
- Doing one chin-up is not hard.
Every time you complain,
I'll add 10kg sandbags to your legs.
I mean...
We could do something easier.
For Jae Seok, I'll add...
a 10kg sandbag to each of his legs.
- And do three chin-ups?
- Yes.
That'd give you more balance.
It's better than only one leg.
- Okay.
- Why are you so quiet?
No.
Why are you suddenly...
- What do you think?
- I like it.
Why...
More than anything,
I think it suits the concept...
- of our show.
- Hey.
- Why are you suddenly quiet?
- No.
So Min, why are you so quiet?
- Hey.
- I love the idea.
Se Chan, say something.
Chin-ups are easy.
- Yes.
- It's a good idea.
- I agree.
- Gosh.
I'll start preparing right away.
- You flatterer.
- Flatterer...
I'll start preparing.
- Gosh.
- Chin-ups are no problem.
- You're right.
- Exactly.
I have a really simple idea. Do you want to hear it?
- What is it?
- Seriously,
- it'll be so easy.
- What is it?
It's really simple.
- You don't need...
- any costumes or makeup.
- What is it?
It's a doppelganger theme.
Jae Seok is going to bring Jung Bum Kyun.
(Comedian Jung Bum Kyun)
Se Chan is going to bring Yang Se Hyeong.
Seok Jin is going to bring Jo Woo Jong.
Ji Hyo is going to bring Cheon Seong Moon.
Her brother.
Kwang Soo is going to bring Han Gi Beom.
(Kwang Soo is going to bring Han Gi Beom.)
What?
- And...
- Why...
You two look alike.
I don't even know what he's doing these days.
He teaches basketball.
- They look alike.
- It might be tricky for So Min.
- So Min's dad...
- My dad?
If he can appear...
- Woo Min looks like her too.
- He's okay too.
But her dad would have more impact.
Also, it can be a bit difficult for Jong Kook.
Park Se Ri...
(The queen of golf?)
They look alike.
- If she can appear...
- They look exactly alike.
I don't think she can come.
- They look alike.
- Just ask her to appear.
You don't have to do anything...
except asking them to make an appearance.
- Just help with their makeup.
- That sounds easy.
Who is your doppelganger?
I'm the main character so...
Shouldn't your mom appear and say, "Running Man..."
His mom should say, "Running Man..."
She'd love that.
- My mom should appear?
- Of course.
She'll dress like you.
She'd love that.
Yes, I'm afraid she'll love it too much.
- She'd love it too much.
- My dad would say yes right away.
It's a good idea, isn't it?
- It's not bad.
I love it.
Every idea seems tricky this time too.
- You're done with the scripts now.
- Yes.
For the first round, you'll form teams of two.
- Let's decide the teams first.
- Okay.
Outside, you'll see four different parts of beef.
We've prepared two sets of each part.
(The ones who choose the same parts will be a team.)
You'll choose a part one by one.
The ones who choose the same part will be a team.
Each part will be out when it's been chosen by two people.
(Each part can be chosen by up to 2 people.)
Let's decide in which order you'll choose a part.
(Round 1 depends on whom you team up with.)
(The order has been decided by drawing lots.)
- Should we start?
- Let's go.
What will we be doing today?
(Haha, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Se Chan, So Min, Jong Kook, Jae Seok)
- The smell is driving me crazy.
- I smell beef.
I guess we'll be eating beef.
- Please start.
- Okay.
- See you.
- Haha.
- Make the right choice.
Here?
(Everything looks tasty.)
It all looks tasty.
Look at that tenderloin.
(Every part looks delicious.)
Rib eye.
It looks high-quality.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
(I can't make a choice.)
Look at that marbling.
(Mouth-watering)
I choose chuck flap.
(Haha chooses chuck flap.)
- I'll be right back.
- Seok Jin.
- See you.
- Bye.
(Let me see.)
I choose rib eye.
(Seok Jin chooses rib eye.)
I'm supposed to choose one?
Chuck flap, ribs, rib eye, and tenderloin?
Are we going to eat them?
What did you choose?
(Kwang Soo could be Haha or Seok Jin's partner.)
- What did you choose?
- What did you choose? Rib eye?
- Tenderloin?
- Tenderloin.
Tenderloin.
Tenderloin sounds great.
(They've all chosen different parts.)
I'm relieved that...
we'll all be on different teams.
(They'll be on different teams.)
I'm relieved too. It would have been terrible.
Let's play dirty.
(Let's play dirty.)
I'm ready.
Please support my doppelganger idea. Isn't it great?
- I liked it.
- Right?
- It's not bad.
- It's good, right? It's so simple.
Has anyone chosen chuck flap?
(Has anyone chosen chuck flap?)
(I chose chuck flap.)
You chose it? What about tenderloin?
- I chose it.
- Oh, there are four options.
(Haha chose chuck flap, and Kwang Soo, tenderloin.)
- What did you choose?
What did you choose?
He chose tenderloin.
(Se Chan chose tenderloin.)
Tenderloin? Okay.
Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- Let's do this.
They'll play dirty.
I'm so relieved.
This is the first time we've been partners.
Is that right?
This is the first time.
Today,
- I'll definitely play dirty.
- Okay.
I'll do everything...
- I've stayed away from.
- Me too.
I'll do everything I want for a change.
There are many things I've been staying away from...
for the show's sake.
I'll imagine that I'm on an internet show.
- Okay. Let's do this.
- Okay.
I just want to avoid Kwang Soo.
(It's exhausting.)
- It's exhausting.
- So Min is coming.
I can see it.
(She's even worse than Kwang Soo.)
- What is it?
- Chuck flap?
(Did you choose chuck flap too?)
No, it's not okay.
- She chose ribs.
- No.
- She chose chuck flap.
- I'm partners with Haha.
Gosh, it'll be exhausting.
(So Min and Haha are on the same team.)
She's the female version of Kwang Soo.
(The female version of Kwang Soo)
That team is going to fail.
- It'll be a mess.
- We'll beat at least those two.
Haha and I don't get along.
(We don't get along.)
I've met many different people,
but you're difficult to me.
Gosh.
I don't get to choose.
I'll have to take what's left.
Exactly, the leftovers.
- That's right.
- It's sometimes good...
to have no choice.
But it's not always good.
Still, you can't have everything...
- your way.
- It's frustrating...
to have no choice when that's not what you want.
It makes things easier.
(Arguing)
- I feel so uncomfortable.
- This is uncomfortable.
(We feel uncomfortable too.)
- I mean...
- I'm getting annoyed.
Please put them on the same team.
Don't separate them.
You know what?
As soon as we're on the same team,
we get along very well.
They couldn't get along any better.
We become invincible.
That's right.
Okay.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
- I better make the right choice.
- It's still cold to wear shorts.
It isn't.
Cut it out.
Here?
(He has to choose between ribs and rib eye.)
I choose ribs.
(There are ribs and rib eye left.)
- There are two left.
- What are they?
Ribs and rib eye.
(What will Ji Hyo and Jae Seok choose?)
- They're here.
- What did you choose?
(Jong Kook chose ribs, and Seok Jin, rib eye.)
- Gosh.
- What did you choose?
(What did you choose?)
What did you choose?
I chose ribs.
This is what we were talking about.
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin versus Jae Seok and Jong Kook)
(Did you choose ribs?)
It'll be exhausting.
My goodness.
They kept arguing.
Gosh.
(My goodness. Let's do this.)
Let's do this.
- We'll be the winners.
- Gosh.
I can't believe it.
(They become invincible together.)
The ones who chose the same parts will become a team.
- I knew it.
- Please enjoy your meat.
After that, I'll announce the first mission.
Gosh, So Min.
- Really?
- Oh, my.
- Let's eat.
Here comes charcoal.
(They're exhausted after deciding teams.)
- That looks delicious.
- Yes.
It looks so tasty.
The meat looks fantastic.
- It looks delicious.
- My mouth is watering.
(The beef makes their mouths water.)
(This is crazy.)
It's so tender.
It's high-quality.
(Eat up.)
- Thank you for the meat.
- Thank you.
It tasted so good.
Everyone, did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes.
- Really.
Let me announce the rules for the first game.
Each team has to find a celebrity who can appear as a guest.
- What?
Then you should know many people.
Kwang Soo and I don't know many people.
(They have to find guests.)
We don't know many people.
You know I don't have many friends.
(What is the mission about?)
Let's come up with a strategy. Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
If your guest is the oldest...
or the youngest, you'll win no points.
The 2nd oldest will win 20 points,
and the 3rd oldest, 10 points.
It's better to be older.
- It's tricky.
- But the oldest wins no points.
(You should go for the 2nd or 3rd oldest.)
If some of them were born in the same year,
we'll look at their birthdays.
1987, 1986, 1985,
- 1984...
- It should be around there.
We should go for the middle.
- It's difficult.
- It's tricky.
It'll be hard to win.
(They have to predict the other teams' strategies.)
You'll also play games with the guests...
and win points according to the result.
(They can win additional points.)
- It's hard.
- It's driving me crazy.
Should we start calling?
Please get in the cars.
- Okay.
Please start.
(The mission starts.)
Ji Hyo, whom should we call?
- We should go for the middle.
- Yes.
Should I play my hidden card?
What is it?
Kim Seok Jin of BTS.
(What?)
Really?
BTS?
I think he is about 22 years old.
- Should I call him?
- Do it.
(He brags about his friendship.)
- See?
- There you go.
(It's at least ringing.)
- Hello.
- Seok Jin.
- Hi.
Hi.
(Surprised)
Hi, Seok Jin. This is Seok Jin.
- How are you?
- It's good to hear from you.
Hello, Seok Jin.
Blood, sweat, tears
This is Ji Hyo.
Hello, Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
- Are you shooting Running Man?
- Yes.
- We're shooting Running Man.
My voice is on Running Man.
I can't believe it.
It's our honor.
Say hello to the Running Man viewers.
Hello, viewers of Running Man.
This is Jin of BTS.
As my name is the same as Seok Jin's,
we maintain our friendship.
I'm Kim Seok Jin.
(He talks sweetly.)
You talk so well. You're good at everything.
Where are you now?
I'm at a shoot with the other members.
- Really?
- Are you at a shoot?
- Yes.
- Are you in Korea?
I'm in Korea. Call me anytime you want to see me.
Really?
(I'm in Korea. Call me anytime you want to see me.)
(Call him anytime?)
Call me anytime.
How about today?
- Today?
- Do you have time?
(Do you mean today?)
It's so sudden.
You told him to contact you anytime.
- Do you mean today?
- Today.
- It won't take long.
- Which area are you in?
I'm in Gwangju, Gyeonggi Province.
- Your shoot is in Gwangju.
- Really?
Gwangju, Gyeonggi Province?
(Whom will Seok Jin and Ji Hyo invite?)
Is there anyone to call? It has to be predictable.
So Min.
Someone young will put us at a disadvantage.
- It'd be uncertain.
- Someone young is dangerous.
Inviting someone young will be dangerous.
Let's do this.
You should call Kwang Soo right now.
Put down a bait.
Tell him that we should place 2nd and 3rd.
- Then...
- Will he believe me?
Propose it, and make him confused.
(Will he believe us?)
You and I are on the same team.
Tell him sincerely.
- Hello?
- Kwang Soo.
Yes?
I spoke with Haha.
- What if we try to place...
- 2nd and 3rd place.
2nd and 3rd together?
- We could do that.
- Right.
How?
Tell us the year the person you invite was born.
Tell us the year he was born.
The eldest person will be born in 1965.
- 1965?
- Or early 1947.
We aren't sure yet.
- Early 1947?
- You know someone of that age?
It's because Jae Seok's team said...
- that they'll meet Song Hae.
- What?
Really? That's helpful information.
Yes, you should invite the eldest person possible...
or the youngest one possible.
- Okay, I see.
- Okay, Haha.
- Bye.
They're both...
such cheaters.
They're terrible punks.
(He's furious.)
- We must place 2nd...
- For 20 points.
To earn 20 points.
How about someone born in 1982?
- 83.
- 1982.
(Shall we look for someone born in 1982?)
When was Sae Ho born?
Is he going somewhere today?
Was he born in 1982?
I met Sae Ho yesterday.
He doesn't have much work these days.
- Hello, Haha.
- Sae Ho.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hello.
- Yes, Haha.
- How old are you?
What year were you born?
I was born in 1982.
- 1982?
Yes, many people are calling me today.
Why? Who?
I'm not sure. I don't know what's going on.
I was getting ready today.
May we come see you?
You may come, but I heard that someone else is coming.
I don't think I can tell you what's going on.
Does it happen to be Jae Seok?
I have to respect their place.
It's Jae Seok, isn't it?
I'm not sure.
It's Yu Jae Seok, right?
I can't say much, but it's an interesting situation.
All right.
I'll be here alone.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Isn't it amazing?
This is amazing.
- We got helpful information.
- Right.
(Haha and So Min found out that Jae Seok invited Sae Ho.)
It's hard to predict.
This mission is hard to predict.
- What about Sae Ho?
- Sae Ho.
- Cho Sae Ho.
- Sae Ho would be great.
- Wait.
- We should...
Sae Ho needs work.
- Right.
- He isn't working.
Jae Seok.
You keep inviting members from that show.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Did I?
- Did I misunderstand?
- Of course.
I wouldn't.
You keep inviting them.
(He tries to call Sae Ho.)
Ho Sae, Ho Sae, Ho Sae, Carlos.
This is Ho Sae, Ho Sae, Ho Sae, Carlos.
Where are you?
I'm at Joo Ho's cafe.
- Why did you go there?
- That means you aren't working.
I have to go to Busan soon.
When?
I leave on a train at 6pm tonight.
- That's great.
- That's good.
- What?
- I wanted to find you some work.
You lost work recently.
I wanted to find you something.
- Yes. That's right.
- Are you in Apgujeong?
We'll see you there.
(They invite themselves.)
Is something going on?
- See you soon.
- Let's talk in person.
Sae Ho, I live in the area.
- Is this Jong Kook?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- Ask the owner...
to prepare what I always have.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes?
You know my favorite drink? Order it for me.
- You've never been here.
- Hey.
You still know my favorite drink.
- Sae Ho.
- I got it.
Order what I always get.
- Okay.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes, Jae Seok?
- Pay me back today.
I never borrowed money from you.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, but I never did.
You borrowed money two weeks ago.
- What?
- How much was it?
Can I say it on TV?
Yes, you can.
You borrowed 1,500 dollars.
- This is true.
- What?
- It's a scary world.
Gosh, this must be true.
For now...
- I got it.
- You must pay people back.
Let's talk in person.
- Okay, see you.
- See you.
I think the best age would be of someone...
- born between 1985 and 1987.
- Right?
Shall we call Park Jung Min? He was born in 1987.
Really?
- Shall I call him?
- Yes.
- Is he an actor?
- He was born in 1987.
- That's fine. He's 32.
- Right.
Hello.
- Hey, where are you?
- Why?
I just came back home right now.
Were you at a shoot?
Yes. Did you call to ask me to give you something?
- No.
- Is it for something?
(He's flustered.)
- In the past, - What does he mean?
We shot Running Man at Jung Min's house.
- Did you ask for something?
- We stole his bidet.
- Really?
- Yes.
He's never been on the show, but his bidet has.
That's nice.
(Hideout Race in March of last year)
(Jung Min decides to donate his bidet.)
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo enter Jung Min's house without him.)
(Jung Min's bidet appears on the show.)
Can you come to Gangnam?
Where in Gangnam?
Nonhyeon.
- Here's why.
- Yes.
You were selected as the person...
we'd like to invite the most.
Stop lying.
It's true. You got 20 votes.
From whom?
All the members including the staff.
What do I have to do there?
- You'll receive a trophy.
- Right.
- Okay.
- We give you a prize.
(Will Jung Min pretend to fall for Kwang Soo's trick?)
Anything is possible. Send me the address.
(He's very kind.)
Okay, I'll send it to you now.
- Okay, Kwang Soo.
- See you soon.
See you.
(They successfully invite Jung Min.)
- Who was born in 1983?
- 1983?
- Born in 1983.
- There aren't many.
We have to find out. We got helpful information.
- You're right.
- It must be younger than Sae Ho.
That's right.
- It's better that we place second.
- Right.
Among celebrities born in 1982,
I'll look up for their birthdays.
Kang Hye Jung, Lee Si Young, Wheesung, Sae Ho.
Lee Young Eun? Wait.
- Lee Young Eun.
- Her birthday is August 9th.
Sae Ho was born on August 9th.
They have the same birthday.
(They find actress Lee Young Eun.)
It'd be fun to compare by hour.
It's unbelievable.
Don't we want to make Jae Seok and Jong Kook upset?
You and I agree on matters like this.
What time was Sae Ho born?
He was born in the morning.
- Is that all we know?
- Let's ask her...
to say that she was born at 11:50pm.
Ask her to say that she was born at 11:58pm
- Don't we need...
- Don't give them a chance.
Proof?
No, ask her mother to say it.
It's fine.
She'll say that she was born at 11:58pm.
Hold on. Haha is so scary.
- Why?
- Your scale is so big.
Is there a scale to fraud?
- The scale of your fraud is big.
- "Scale"?
Winning is important.
(That's why people talk about Haha.)
- Finally.
- I learned something important.
It's necessary.
(It's a fraud on a higher level.)
She replied to me.
- She did.
- Here it is.
(Lee Young Eun is an old friend of Haha.)
Sound positive.
We must invite her.
(She's also So Min's colleague from college.)
- Hello.
- I'm So Min from Running Man.
- We're from Running Man.
I'm Haha.
You're selected as the most-wanted celebrity...
- on Running Man.
- Congratulations.
- Was I?
- Hello, Young Eun.
This is Haha. Do you remember me?
- Hello, Haha.
- Hello.
Young Eun, this is So Min from class of 2005.
- Hello. She's my senior.
- Hello.
- That's right.
- It's a connection by fate.
- Right.
This is out of the blue. Why was I selected?
- Were you born on August 9th?
- Why me?
- Yes.
- Unbelievable.
- Do you have the same birthday?
No, mine is August 20th.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Mine is August 7th.
- Really?
- This is amazing.
- Is it about people born in August?
- That's right.
(Is it about people born in August? That's right.)
Pardon me for asking, but what time were you born?
I was born around 12:20am.
It was around then.
On which day?
Wait, I did some research.
- You were born...
- Yes?
- On August 9...
- Okay.
At 11:59pm.
- I was?
- Yes, yes.
I heard it. I really did.
From whom?
From your mom.
Is that so?
You were born around 11:50pm. I'm serious. You really were.
Isn't that true? Why don't you think about it again?
- Was I?
- "Was I?"
No, no. I was told I was born between 11pm to 1am.
Come again?
You know they used to count hours by two back then.
(The 1st pair goes from 11pm to 1am the next day.)
- You can forget about that now.
- Okay.
- You were born at 11:59pm.
- Congratulations.
- Yes!
You were born around 11:50pm.
- Right.
- Sure. I got it.
Congratulations.
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- My gosh, this is crazy.
(Haha invites Young Eun to complete his grand scheme.)
Haha, I have so much respect for you.
- How do you come up with this?
- My gosh.
Is this your innate quality?
- Since when were you smart?
- Well, this is...
Well, it's just that...
I never had the chance to show this.
- Is that why you were...
- If I had shown my intelligence,
- You couldn't survive?
- I couldn't have survived.
(My gosh, it's so hard to be me.)
That's why you were a bit...
I mean, you taught yourself everything.
I'm a bit what?
What were you going to say?
- That I was a jerk?
- No, no.
Do I sound so conceited?
You taught yourself that, right?
- You trained yourself for it.
- You were on it too.
- No, I just helped you a bit.
- Weren't you?
Hey, stop lying!
All the momentum came from you.
I have a question.
Time to time, you talk to the camera when you're alone.
Why do you do that?
- Is it because you're frustrated?
- I don't have anyone to trust.
Now, my only friend is the camera.
The camera listens to me when I talk and puts up with me.
The truth airs without being distorted.
It doesn't betray me like people do.
- It accepts me as I am.
- I see.
(They compete to see who can be more emotional.)
I know what you mean.
That's why I film myself a lot at home.
(I know exactly how you feel.)
(He's weird. I don't go that far.)
Dream's baby nickname was Selfie.
"Selfie, Selfie."
I don't have anyone I can trust. It's the truth.
(His doubt regarding people has grown due to Running Man.)
All right. You invited your guest.
Before we reveal the mission you will try with the guest,
predict the outcome of the mission,
and bet on the victory or loss.
(They can bet on the victory or loss in secret.)
If you bet on the correct outcome, you will earn 10 points.
If I make the correct bet, I'll get the points?
Yes. And if you guess the outcome correctly,
the guest will get...
- the Korean beef gift set.
- Really?
- Let's do our best.
- Right.
(Do it for Young Eun's sake.)
I mean it. Seriously. Let's be civil about this.
Let's be nice about it.
(Contemplating)
- We should both bet on the victory.
- No, Haha.
Let's make sure we don't jeopardize each other.
If we accomplish the mission, it will be good for everyone.
- We can both get 10 points.
- We can give her the Korean beef.
- Exactly. Our intention is good.
- That'd be better.
Victory, then.
(What? Loss?)
(She writes down "loss" without missing a beat.)
Did you really write down "victory"?
Since my handwriting is bad, let me rewrite this.
- Hey, hey.
- What?
I can see everything through your camera.
I didn't write it, Haha. I was going to write it again.
(She pretends to be unaffected.)
(Feeling embarrassed)
(Despite her instincts to cheat, her acts are sloppy.)
I can't believe her.
I'll trust you this time.
I did it. I really wrote it.
(I really wrote down, "victory".)
- You really wrote it.
- I did.
Then me too.
(I will write the same.)
(So Min shows that she has written "victory" too.)
(They both bet on the victory. What will happen to them?)
Will you bet on our victory or loss?
I might write "victory"...
or "loss".
Victory or loss.
(What's he saying? I'll follow my guts.)
- We must make sure we win.
- You bet.
But I can't show you mine just in case.
- Yes, cover up, and write it down.
- I have to write it in secret?
But if you bet on the loss,
- we don't need to play at all.
- It ruins the purpose.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan finish betting too.)
Let's not lie. Come on. Goodness.
We can both get 10 points.
- You're right.
- Aren't I right?
Hey, for this mission,
we are in the same team.
Did you say, "hey"? Don't forget that we're filming.
- When did I call you that?
- How could you say that?
- How could you call me that?
- When did I say that?
Didn't you hear him say that?
- He said that.
- When did I say that?
- This is weird.
- I'm not that rude.
You called me that.
(Jong Kook and Jae Seok finish betting while quarreling.)
- My gosh.
- Unbelievable.
(Anyway, what's today's mission?)
I will announce the mission you will try with your guest.
The team mission you will try with the guest is...
- Nice Bowling.
- What?
The three of you will take turns to bowl.
If the final score is over 150, you succeed.
My gosh, this is a hard one.
Wait, we'll bowl at a bowling alley?
Yes, we'll go to a bowling alley.
- I'm terrible at bowling.
- What?
This is what I mean. I think you're already setting it up.
My gosh, I'm serious.
Had I known, I wouldn't have bet on the victory.
My gosh, Jae Seok.
- Stop acting.
- I'm serious. I'm bad at bowling.
I will do my best though. I will.
(Something is fishy. Jae Seok is never humble.)
- But 200...
- When I bowled last time,
the score was 70 or something.
Jae Seok, I'll make you do well.
- I mean it.
- It's not that.
- I'm bad at it.
- No, I'll help you.
- You can do it.
- That's not the point.
You can do it. You will improve with my coaching.
- I'm talking about myself. Why...
- Listen.
I'll give it a try. I'll help you become a great bowler.
- I can give you a crash course.
- This is crazy.
- My gosh, Jong Kook.
- I got this, Jae Seok.
I'll give you a crash course.
I'm sorry,
- What is it? - but your hand keeps coming over.
Keep it midway.
We're not supposed to split the space in half.
- I didn't do that.
- Let me tell you what it is.
- You need to call dibs on it.
- It's not about calling dibs.
Why don't you push my hand then?
Push it away.
- No, listen.
- This is my natural angle.
If it's too close,
- it's not comfortable.
- The centrifugal force...
I'm comfortable with this angle.
(I shouldn't have bothered.)
I don't like my partner, but I should still put up with him.
I can't believe he can't bowl.
I'm so upset.
Let's cut. 1, 2, 3.
(He's sick of this.)
(And they head to the bowling alley for 30 minutes in silence.)
I used to come to this area often when I was young.
- It's cool in here.
- Come inside.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Honey.
(It's been a while since he said, "honey".)
Sae Ho.
- What's going on?
- My gosh.
(Sae Ho guarantees to be funny.)
- You're already at the cafe.
- What brings you here?
It's been a while.
(Viewers of Running Man, it's been a while.)
No, it hasn't been a while.
- I must say hello.
- Don't do that.
- I should introduce myself.
- No, we like you to be natural.
- It's been a while.
- We are meeting casually.
- Our show hates that the most.
- Is that so?
- We hate self-introductions.
- We don't like introductions.
- But still. I must say hi.
- No, no.
- It's not natural.
- I'm sorry about that.
- It looks unnatural.
- Why don't you come this way?
- Cameras aren't here.
- Here...
- Hello, Sae Ho.
- But I see cameras.
- They aren't here?
- Pretend they don't exist.
- Pretend they aren't here.
- This is my agent.
My gosh. Hello.
- He's my junior comedian.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Let's sit down.
- Take a seat.
But why did you wear Eun I's pants?
They aren't Eun I's. They are mine.
- These are Eun I's.
- I wore them to your show once.
- No, they belong to her.
- I...
- Honey.
- Yes?
Your beanie is about to fall off.
- What if this happens?
- It might come off.
- Honey.
What if it comes off?
- What if this happens?
- Coming off.
The microphone.
Honey, we won't be here for long.
Don't put it on you. Just hold it, and talk.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Why don't you sit down?
Stop it, and sit down.
(It's time to have coffee with these warmhearted members.)
They keep calling me.
- Who?
- Who? They called you, right?
But if I tell you, am I violating the rule?
- This wasn't supposed to happen.
- This is good.
If people called him, they probably found out we were coming.
- You told them, didn't you?
- Did you tell them?
Let me tell you the whole story.
- Let's pick someone else.
- You shouldn't have done that.
You shouldn't have told them.
- You told them?
- Hold on a second.
- How can't you not pick on this?
- Wait. I... Hold on.
Let's be frank. You came to see me.
- You can't do that, Sae Ho.
- I told you we were coming.
You weren't supposed to tell them about us.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- When we watch the show later...
- You just ruined the whole episode.
- I ruined the episode?
- Look.
- It's all because of you.
- No, listen.
- It was supposed to be a secret.
You called me when I was enjoying my day off.
- You asked me where I was.
- Sae Ho, you can't say that.
- Sae Ho.
- You should eat some.
What's on your agenda today?
- I'm leaving for Busan at 6pm.
- Why?
- I have a filming.
- For what?
- Well, it's for a commercial.
- For fun?
(Feeling smug)
- You're filming it in Busan?
- Yes, I am.
Should we move to a place where you can do your mission?
- I think we should.
- Sae Ho.
- Wait. We're going somewhere?
- Are you good at...
- Are you good at bowling? Are you?
- My gosh, I am...
- Have you ever bowled before?
Known as Bowling Cho.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- Are you good at bowling?
- Do you know how to bowl?
- Really?
- Yes.
Before we go to a bowling alley,
tell us the date of your birth and the time you were born.
- Even the time he was born?
- Seriously?
The time I was born?
I don't know for sure,
but if my memory serves me right,
I remember it to be between 6am to 8am.
- I see.
- It must've been hard for your mom.
- My mom had a C-section.
- I see.
- It must've been hard.
- It must've been hard for your mom.
Now that I look at you,
I can see that your mom had a C-section.
- Your face is fitting.
- What do you mean?
- It looks like it was a C-section.
- What kind of face would that be?
- I can see that in your face.
- It's not that.
- There's a particular look for it?
- Yes.
Hey, Jong Kook.
- There's a look for C-sections.
- That's insulting.
- I'm serious.
- I'm sorry,
but did I offend you?
- We had a nice talk two days ago.
- Yes, we did.
- I cherish him as my friend.
- Exactly. That's why.
- Why don't we get going first?
- Come with us.
Can I just go like this?
- Yes.
- Of course, you can.
(They head to the bowling alley due to his tight schedule.)
I find myself in this van all of a sudden.
- What?
- I'm suddenly in this van.
- Yes, you are.
- I don't know what's happening.
- That's true.
- I must clarify one thing.
You said...
I borrowed 1,500 dollars from you, but it's not true.
- What?
- I never borrowed any money.
You didn't?
- Really?
Try to remember.
One day, he asked me...
to give some money to someone as a wedding gift for him.
He said he didn't have money at that moment...
and promised he'd pay me back the next day.
But when I arrived at the wedding,
they didn't accept any gifts.
I told Jae Seok that they didn't accept any gifts,
and he told me to return the money to him.
What kind of logic is that?
I was...
No. Honey, think about it.
What did I say?
Let's say I asked you to give them 100 dollars for me.
- And you went to the wedding.
- I did.
- You had 100 dollars, right?
- Yes.
Should you return the money to me or not?
- I should.
- Right?
That's why you owe me 100 dollars.
- Tell me your account number.
- Okay.
Right?
Like I always say,
he would've been a thug had he been good at fighting.
Seriously.
Luckily, he's bad at fighting.
You can't have everything.
No one can have everything.
He's scary.
- You can't have everything.
- No.
Luckily, Jae Seok has cotton fists.
- Right.
- I'm sorry to say this.
I really appreciate that you came today.
But you shouldn't...
- dream of staying here.
- No.
You know me.
- I do.
- I love watching Running Man.
Whenever you invite me,
I have so much fun.
- But...
- But you don't want to stay?
Just stay quiet.
You can leave after the bowling game.
- If...
- Be quiet.
- If we...
- Stop talking.
- From the spring...
- We can...
- Be quiet.
- I didn't mean to...
- Please be quiet.
You're talking too much.
(I can't talk? You guys called me.)
It feels like I'm being arrested.
(Sae Ho is taken to the bowling alley by the friendly guys.)
(Haha and So Min are waiting for Young Eun.)
Let's greet her cheerfully.
(They're ready to welcome her.)
Is she here?
- Hi.
- Look who's here.
- You haven't changed a bit.
My goodness.
(Lee Young Eun)
(She's shown off her charms in many dramas and variety shows.)
(She appeared on a variety show with Haha in 2004.)
I'm so happy to see her. It's amazing.
I can't believe she's here.
I can't believe it either.
She used to be on many variety shows.
That's right.
I used to see you on TV.
- Exactly.
- Really?
My goodness.
What should I do?
- It's embarrassing.
- She was popular among celebrities.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's what I heard too.
I'm joking.
(She's still funny.)
You're done casting a guest.
(Haha and So Min has cast Young Eun.)
She's the best.
There's something we need to check.
(Where does she stand in terms of age?)
- You were born on August 9, 1982.
- Yes.
What time were you born?
We need to know the time.
(As she was born on the same day as Sae Ho, the time is important.)
(They're going to pretend Young Eun was born later.)
(Don't forget you were born at 11:59pm.)
(What time?)
(Say the answer we agreed on.)
(Say you were born at 11:59pm.)
I was born at 12:20am.
(12:20am?)
They were trying to...
- make me say something else.
- We weren't.
Let's do this again. Please say it clearly.
- What time were you born?
- 11:50pm.
12:20am.
- 12:20am?
- No. 11:50pm.
- Young Eun.
- 11:50pm.
- Hold on.
- Really?
Stop shooting.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Sorry.
The thing is...
(The thing is...)
We need you to have been born at that time.
Why?
Because you were.
You were born at 11:50pm.
Really?
But I can't change the time I was born.
- It's okay.
- You're not changing anything.
We've already talked to your mom.
- Your mom...
- Yes.
It's what your family register says.
- I don't know what happened.
- We've checked.
Your guest was born...
on August 9, 1982, at 12:20am...
- No!
Please say it.
She didn't say, "Start."
She didn't.
Say, "Start," and then what time you were born.
1, 2, 3.
Start.
(Innocent)
- 12:20am.
- No.
Start. 12:20am.
No.
(Young Eun was born at 12:20am.)
- I can't lie.
- Gosh.
Ma'am.
(She's stubborn.)
Let me announce the result.
Your guest, Young Eun,
was born on August 9, 1982,
at 12:20am.
Gosh.
(If she's the oldest, they'll fail to win points.)
Among all the guests,
she's the second oldest. Therefore, you win 20 points.
(She's the 2nd oldest?)
Gosh.
(As Young Eun was born a few hours earlier, they win 20 points.)
She was born at 12:20am.
We're not supposed to lie.
- Her mom was right.
- She was born at 12:20am.
- That's right.
Look at this.
- I have goosebumps.
- Young Eun.
- See?
- What's going on?
Justice prevails, and truth is revealed.
- Of course.
- The world is still beautiful.
Of course.
I can't believe she was born at 12:20am.
Bless you.
We'd like to thank your mother.
We thank your mother. Seriously.
(It means Sae Ho is the 3rd oldest.)
The second oldest was...
- It must be us. - born on August 9, 1982.
Lee Young Eun was born at 12:20am.
Young Eun and I are the same age.
The third oldest is Sae Ho, who was born between 6am and 8am.
- Why were you born so late?
- Young Eun was born on August 9?
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook win 10 points.)
- This is...
- I can't believe it.
How is this possible?
Hong Jin Young was born on August 9 too.
Why were you born so late?
(What?)
If you had been born earlier,
- we would have won 20 points.
- Jong Kook, that's...
You're talking about what happened 37 years ago.
How could I have predicted this 37 years ago?
He was born through C-section.
- We lost because of the time.
- Please apologize to my mom.
- We're sorry.
- But if...
- We were rude to his mother.
It was too close.
He's here.
(We now know who the 2nd, 3rd, and 4th oldest guests are.)
Hi.
(Who is the oldest guest?)
(Lee Jong Hyuk)
Actor Lee Jong Hyuk is here.
(He's been in many dramas, variety shows, and musicals.)
(The handsomest, middle-aged actor)
Let me announce the result.
I think I'll be the oldest.
What are you talking about? You're young.
How old are you?
He's just 44 or 45.
Your guest is the oldest.
(Laughing)
You've failed to win points.
I feel offended.
Exactly.
Can I have more ice?
- What's going on?
- It's hot in here.
He's only in his early 40s.
He's in his early 40s.
Shouldn't the oldest guest win more points?
- It's hard to be the oldest.
- It's hard.
- Jung Min...
- Order juice.
- He doesn't drink coffee?
- Please give us another juice.
I'll make sure Jung Min gets the Korean beef set.
(When is he coming?)
He can't? Is it him on that motorbike?
Really?
(A motorbike approaches.)
He's making eye contact with us. Is it him?
Is he coming on a motorbike?
- I don't know.
- Could it really be him?
You should go out. I think it's him.
(Is he just someone the cafe owner knows?)
I think it's Jung Min. Stop him.
- Is it him?
Is it Jung Min?
He came with a motorbike?
- It's him.
- He came with a motorbike.
(A man approaches the cafe.)
(He has the aura of an actor.)
He has blond hair.
(It was you?)
He dresses very casually.
- He came with a motorbike?
- Hi.
Hi.
(Actor Park Jung Min is here.)
(His acting gives you shivers.)
(Park Jung Min is a genius actor who can pull off various roles.)
(Bowing)
We didn't think it was you.
I couldn't park my motorbike there.
(The cafe owner didn't let him park his motorbike there.)
You guys could've talked it out.
He had to...
- park somewhere else.
- This way.
Please put on a microphone.
(Puzzled)
Is this a serious shoot?
You haven't seen each other in a while?
- It's been a while.
- When did we last meet?
(His back is facing the camera.)
- It's been a couple of months.
- A couple of months?
Please come here.
Come this way.
Jung Min doesn't have a lot of experience.
(Please understand.)
(He's not used to variety shows.)
- Have a seat.
What's going on?
- We don't know either.
- We don't know.
Let's hear it.
- I'm not even wearing makeup.
- He hasn't changed a bit.
(I'm wearing no makeup.)
(Jung Min is here, but the team doesn't win any points.)
(Result)
Let me give you a mission.
Your mission is called...
Play, Eat, Shop.
Play, Eat, Shop?
You're going to play, eat, and shop...
the way Young Eun wants.
If you succeed, Young Eun will win a Korean beef set.
(Korean beef?)
Let's do this.
Here is Haha's mission bag.
Thank you.
This is So Min's.
(There is a secret hidden in these bags.)
(Haha and So Min hears about the mission.)
(They're given only 10 dollars...)
(for the Play, Eat, Shop mission.)
(3 activities with 10 dollars?)
On top of that, you have a hidden mission.
You'll get a bag for your mission.
There's a pedometer hidden in the bag.
That darn pedometer.
When the mission is finished,
the total of the 3 pedometers must be less than 10,000 to win.
If it's over 10,000, you fail.
(The amount spent and steps must be less than 10,000.)
You may eat what you'd like.
- We'll treat you to coffee...
- Right now?
- Like we said.
- I'd like iced coffee.
Okay, come with me.
Shall I order it? Would you like to stay?
Shall we bring it to you?
- Would you like to come?
- Sure.
Hello.
One iced Americano, please.
- Hello.
- I'd like water, So Min.
Water with ice.
Please give me a glass of iced water.
I can't sleep well if I drink coffee.
Her heart starts to beat fast.
I feel bad.
- I won't get a drink.
- It's okay.
- We promised you.
- I'm sorry.
- Is it two iced Americano?
- Yes.
- No, it's 1.
- It's 1.
- How much is it?
- It's 3.80 dollars.
- 3.80 dollars?
- Yes.
(They spend 3.80 dollars.)
- Is hot Americano cheaper?
- Is it one cup?
Is hot Americano cheaper? How about a hot drink?
- It's too hot.
- One iced Americano, please.
(When they make a bet, )
(Haha bets on success.)
(You really wrote "success".)
(So Min bets on success.)
(He crosses it out.)
(He quickly crosses out success.)
(Haha bets on failure.)
(So Min bets on success. Haha bets on failure.)
Is it the price of the ice?
- Yes.
- It's 30 cents more expensive.
We'll order iced coffee.
- Thank you.
- I don't usually buy it.
(Only one coffee arrives.)
- Let's share it.
- I'll drink water.
- I don't drink coffee.
- We drank a lot before.
Really? Can I drink it?
- Of course.
- It's really okay.
I prefer water.
What do you want to do today?
Do you like to exercise?
- No.
- You don't?
Taking care of a baby...
can feel suffocating.
- Didn't I tell you?
- How about seeing cherry blossoms?
- What? Cherry blossoms?
- Seeing cherry blossoms?
(Cherry blossoms?)
That sounds amazing.
- Do you mean taking photos?
- Yes.
That's amazing.
We can throw cherry blossoms too.
- We can take portraits.
- Right.
This is popular these days.
I want to go to an amusement park.
Amusement park?
(I want to go to an amusement park.)
(That costs so much.)
I saw this in the playground.
Right, there was a merry-go-round.
There were bars too.
Is it okay for me to say it?
- Pardon? Massage?
- I also want a massage.
- Haha.
- She has a massage license.
- No.
- Seriously.
- I don't mean that.
- It's true.
She's really good at giving massages.
Would you like to buy anything?
I saw a pair of jeans yesterday.
A pair of jeans?
She's wearing jeans.
The color was neon pink.
Neon pink? What did you say? I'm sorry.
(He almost loses his temper.)
(Pink pants are popular.)
I'm sorry. We saw each other after a long time.
I'd like to hear about your everyday life.
I'm sure you have things to do.
- Here it is.
- Go ahead.
My four-year-old child goes to...
- preschool.
- Do you get up early?
- I wake up at 8am.
- 8am?
I get up around then.
- So...
- Do you do laundry every day?
(He shakes the pedometer.)
Don't you clean up every day?
Right, I do everything.
Your children must get up and cry.
- Right, however...
- That's difficult.
Your face hasn't changed much.
Yours didn't either.
- Seriously.
- You look the same.
Let's decide on what to do today.
- We got her a drink.
- That sounds good.
Do you remember?
This mission must be done with 10 dollars.
What did you want to do?
- I want to go to an amusement park.
- Amusement park or...
(Was that the condition?)
I'm sorry to ask,
but could you give me a few drops of coffee in here?
(Speaking of which...)
(He doesn't want to buy one.)
I want to smell it.
(He doesn't have much money.)
Thank you so much.
My goodness.
I can see its color.
Thank you.
(Each drop is precious.)
- You should have told me.
- It's okay.
- I feel too pressured.
- Don't be.
- It tastes like coffee.
- Really?
- Goodness.
- This is amazing.
Yes, it's perfect right now.
Do you want to go to an amusement park?
Let's go to Children's Grand Park.
- Children's Grand Park?
- There are rides...
like the pirate ship ride called The Vikings. I want to ride that.
- That sounds good.
- The Vikings?
Can you afford a ticket to the park?
It's free.
- It's free to enter.
- Yes.
Okay, let's go.
We'll go and make sure you ride The Vikings.
- We'll make sure of it.
- No matter what.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. This is great.
Here's the team mission you'll clear with Jung Min.
It's called 3 Flipping Sets.
(3 Flipping Sets)
(Flipping puck ddakji, paper ddakji, and business card)
If you clear the mission, we'll give a Korean beef gift set to Jung Min.
(Clearing 2 out of 3 missions gives Jung Min a Korean beef gift set.)
You can grill it tonight at home.
It was his birthday recently.
- Consider it as your birthday gift.
- Right.
The first mission is flipping puck ddakji.
(Flipping puck ddakji)
You get only one chance.
You'll play it in a relay. Among 150 pieces of ddakji,
you must flip over 100 to win.
It's been a while, so I lost my sense.
- Flip 100 of 150 pieces.
- Do you mean these?
- Yes.
- This is easy.
Give it a try, Jung Min.
After practicing, choose an order.
Like this?
Are you athletic, Jung Min?
- Yes.
- You're quick, right?
That's good.
Can you do this?
(He practices with the muscles he gained from boxing.)
(There's not much change.)
(This isn't it.)
Wait.
- You're not athletic at all.
- Wait.
Try it again. Think of it as your last chance.
Can we switch him with someone else?
Which year did I say?
Didn't I say 1983 or 1984?
- How can you not do this?
- Wait.
- How about six?
- Why can't I do it?
You didn't flip any.
I'm done with practice.
(I'm done with practice.)
What do you mean? You didn't flip any.
What are you doing?
- Kwang Soo.
- We need to score points.
I'm making it move.
Shall I do it?
Here you go. Try this.
You try it.
(About 120 pieces flip.)
(With a heavy blow, the stack of ddakjis collapses.)
Do it like this.
- Kwang Soo.
- This is it.
You were an expert.
- How did you do it?
- You did it.
You can start. These are 150 pieces. You made it.
May I start right away?
- Say start, and decide the order.
- You go first.
Kwang Soo will start.
- Do you want it lower?
- You should finish it off.
It's pointless. You have to succeed.
Just finish it in one go.
Say start before starting.
- 1, 2, 3, start.
- Start.
(He must flip 100 to win.)
Aim at the top.
(Please flip 120 pieces like you did before.)
(Will he succeed in the beginning?)
(The blow wasn't as heavy as before.)
(He can't believe it.)
Stop playing around. What's wrong with you?
- Is he doing it on purpose?
- What's wrong?
(Did he do it on purpose?)
(We must bet on success no matter what.)
(They both promise to bet on success.)
(Se Chan bets on success.)
(Kwang Soo bets on failure as expected.)
Kwang Soo took his turn. The second player starts.
What have you done?
You give it a try.
- This looks good.
- Blowing diagonally is allowed.
All right.
(He insists on his own rules.)
- What's the point of saying that?
- What?
(He fixes his posture carefully.)
100 pieces?
That's more than two-thirds.
(Please fail.)
(He used to be good at ddakji. Will Se Chan be able to succeed?)
Okay, okay.
Okay.
(What just happened?)
- You flipped a lot.
- I did.
Let's remove them.
There's a lot. I did good, right?
I think we made it.
- I think we got 100.
- We made it.
I think so too. Give them to me. Let me count them.
Let's count. 1, 2, 3, 4...
(His eyes become wider as the numbers go up.)
66, 67, 68, 69.
Okay. You just need 30.
You only need to flip 31.
- You can do it.
- You can do 31.
I'm sure you can do 31.
- I'm sure you can do it.
- Jung Min.
Bring it close.
Blow on the bottom.
Do this, okay?
(Will Jung Min flip 31 of them?)
(He only gets 4.)
What was that?
(He can't hide his sense of relief.)
I got four.
Four?
(It's four.)
You flipped 73 in total.
You failed the first mission.
(They flipped 73 in total, so they fail the 1st mission.)
What did you do? Goodness.
If you fail another mission, this is over,
and Jung Min will go home empty-handed.
I wanted to get the beef gift set for him. I said it a few times.
(Se Chan has to win, and Kwang Soo has to lose. Who will it be?)
There are three rounds...
to the Nice Treasure Hunt.
You must find each member's name tag.
You have three minutes.
One Running Man member...
will hide the treasures,
and one person will find...
the name tags with Jong Hyuk.
Let's get started.
- You can hide the name tags now.
- Okay.
I can hide them wherever I want, right?
(Did Ji Hyo choose to win or lose?)
What does she have?
Is it to win or to lose?
I'm 100-percent sure she wants to lose.
(On their way to the coffee shop while betting for a win or a loss)
(He thought she would choose to lose, )
(and he was right.)
(What did Seok Jin pick?)
(Win)
I'm 100-percent sure she wants to lose.
What am I supposed to do? I'm going to make her get it.
All right. I'll make this ridiculous.
You have one minute left.
She'll find it for sure.
As soon as she comes through here...
Right?
All right.
This is good.
(He sticks it on the cameraman's chest.)
(He wants to win, so he'll hide them in obvious places.)
- He's coming.
- Okay.
I'll put this here.
She has to know.
(He leaves the last one on a chair by the windows.)
All right. She will find them for sure.
(Even if Ji Hyo wants to lose, Jong Hyuk can find them.)
(I trust you, Jong Hyuk.)
2, 1.
We're going now?
- Let's go. We can take our time.
- Hey, run.
No, it's okay.
I think he made them obvious, so we can take our time.
- Of course.
- Do you trust Seok Jin?
Of course, I do.
(It's in their face from the beginning.)
(What do I do?)
I don't trust him.
- It's not this way, right?
- This won't do.
(She tries to sit on it.)
(Why did she just sit down?)
What are you doing?
(He doesn't suspect anything and leaves.)
- You're working hard.
- Why isn't she trying?
My shoe lace got untied.
You want to lose, right?
- No. I want to win.
- Right? You need to lose.
How does he not realize?
He didn't see that while he was coming up?
He didn't see that? This is driving me nuts.
Didn't he see this? It's on your chest.
Goodness. This is driving me nuts. What is wrong with him?
I told you to put them where I can see them.
(How much easier can it get?)
(It even follows you around.)
(I'm here.)
(He passes it.)
Here.
It might be here.
(He's impossible.)
It should be colorful, not white.
(You just have to turn your head...)
(to see it.)
- Hey, Seok Jin.
- Hey.
You should film me. Film me.
(He calls out the cameraman and tries to make it obvious.)
(Will Jong Hyuk notice?)
- Why is this so hard?
- Film me.
(He complains.)
I am really bad at finding things.
Goodness.
I'm really bad at this.
You have to look from far away.
You can't look at the trees. You have to look at the forest.
It's this way, right?
(He looks at it widely from this way.)
I think so.
I'm actually not sure.
I don't know what's going on.
You might think it's weird, but I don't know.
(Winking)
Ji Hyo, you're so shameless.
Jong Hyuk.
(Why is Ji Hyo calling him urgently?)
You can write 1,000 Chinese characters here.
Be quiet.
(I feel like I'm getting smarter with all these books.)
You can write 1,000 Chinese characters.
Who needs that right now?
What is wrong with her?
I think she's here to look around.
I'm not.
I'm trying my best.
(He passes by the cameraman.)
(Will he finally notice?)
(He passes by.)
(He passes by the cameraman and finds one on the cushion.)
One.
(He found one.)
- Where did you find this?
- I found one.
You're really good at this.
- Of course. I have good vision.
- He's so good.
(Of course. I have good vision.)
He's so good.
- This is ridiculous.
- This is so funny.
This is ridiculous.
I guess you didn't see that.
Didn't you see one on your way up?
You have 10 seconds left.
- 10 seconds?
- Yes.
You have 10 seconds, Jong Hyuk.
- 10 seconds.
- 10, 9...
(How is this possible?)
- 6...
- 10 seconds?
- 10 seconds.
- Hold on.
- 4...
- This way.
(He looks around the sofa next to the stairs.)
One. Done.
(He runs out of time right next to the stairs.)
(They fail the mission.)
Goodness.
You have failed the mission.
(You're a rascal.)
- I mean...
- Where did you leave it?
You can't move it.
(There's a name tag.)
Hey.
Seok Jin is a genius.
- Hey, you know what I mean?
- I knew it.
- You finally see it.
- Do you have one?
Goodness. Hey.
How can I make it more obvious?
It's over.
- This is driving me nuts.
- This is funny.
- This is ridiculous.
It was on the stairs...
- on your way up.
- Really?
It was here in the beginning.
She has to lose to win.
- That's why she wanted to go slow.
- She came up...
and sat on it. You said,
"Why are you sitting here?" Then you went sideways.
She wasn't looking for them.
(Thanks to Jong Hyuk, Ji Hyo wins 10 points.)
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook are at a bowling alley.)
I'll tell you the rules to Nice Bowling.
You'll take turns to bowl.
If the total score is over 150, you win.
This won't be easy.
If you are successful, the guest takes the Korean beef gift set.
We have to win.
- We could've had 20 points by now.
- Right.
Can you tell me what this is about?
What's good?
You just have to bowl and go home.
If you try to do more than that,
it'll make things awkward between us.
- I see.
- Sae Ho,
you have your role.
I know.
Honey, you're not in the best condition, so don't talk.
You should just bowl and go home.
When will I be in a better condition?
Never.
- When will I be better?
- I think...
- you're not being very funny.
- Really?
- I'll try to bowl better.
- All right.
- You're in a very bad condition.
- Okay.
- Decide who will go first.
The person who's not as good...
should go first.
- That's right.
- I'll go next.
You're not that good, so you can go first.
I'm bad at this.
Relax.
Sae Ho.
I'll do what I normally do.
Look at the point in the middle. The big one.
- Let's see.
- Let's watch you bowl first.
- Let's watch and see.
- Let's go.
I'm Bowling Cho.
Bowling Cho.
Do it your style.
(He throws a small bowling ball.)
(It goes in the gutter.)
(This isn't it.)
(I know it isn't.)
Hold on.
- No.
- Attention.
(You're in a bad condition to bowl too.)
I told you.
- I already told you. I'm bad.
- I know, but I told you.
- You can't be that bad.
- Come here, honey.
I told you I was bad.
- You should have told us.
- I did.
You said you were good at bowling.
I didn't say that.
I just said Bowling Cho was my nickname.
- Why? Why is it Bowling Cho?
- How can you be so bad then?
I hope my life rolls on like a bowling ball, so I'm Bowling Cho.
You can't do this.
You can get a spare.
- Does one person bowl twice?
- This is unbelievable.
Sae Ho, listen to me.
- Honey, no.
- Hey.
- Hold on.
- Come on.
- You can't do that.
- Your right arm touches your ear.
Sit down.
- Raise your arm to the ear.
- Let's go.
Raise it up in a straight line.
Stop fooling around. Try your best.
- Raise it up in a straight line.
- I can get mad.
Straight line.
- All right. It was straight.
- What happened?
(He has a different facial expression now.)
- All right. It was straight.
- What happened?
Good job.
(He gets a spare.)
(He's triumphant.)
I told you. Straight line.
- Straight line.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
- It's okay.
I just did it.
Good job.
You have to do it straight.
- What happened?
- I don't know either.
- Good job.
- I did it, right?
- How did you bowl?
- I don't know.
Hold on.
Did you want to lose, so you made him do this?
What? Really?
How can you say that?
That's ridiculous. I have to win.
You can't do that.
- Of course not.
- We're in this together.
Of course.
I haven't practiced. I'll start.
(Does he have to lose? Or is Jong Kook insisting?)
Nice.
(Jong Kook bowls for the 2nd frame.)
That wasn't good.
(He gets 9 pins.)
- Nice!
(Nice.)
(I don't think Jae Seok finds it nice.)
- Are you sure?
- You're good.
This is great.
I can bowl like that too.
(Is that good? Or is Jae Seok acting?)
(The ace member's 2nd turn)
It turned.
(He misses a spare unfortunately.)
(Laughing)
I flipped my wrist and...
Sae Ho.
- Why were you so good?
- I don't know.
It wasn't you. I was laughing because of him.
- You laugh after a delay?
- Good job.
- All right. It's my turn.
- Good luck, Jae Seok.
- Let's go.
- I almost had it.
Then...
does that mean I did better than you?
- Yes, for now.
- Right?
Okay.
- I'll show you.
- All right.
I don't know why I flipped my wrist.
I should have thrown it in a straight line.
(Jae Seok stands with a stable form.)
(I'll show you my bowling skills.)
Raise your arm straight up.
It's in the gutter.
(The watermelon heads for the pit.)
(Sighing)
I think he did that on purpose.
I can kind of tell.
No...
- This is not easy.
- It's not.
(Is this difficult for him? Or is he trying to lose?)
(Betting to win or lose)
- We get 10 more points?
- Yes.
(Jae Seok makes a decision to win 10 points.)
This is big.
We do this individually, right?
(Fail)
This is really not easy.
(He has to do something to prevent getting 150 points.)
Are you a weightlifter?
Is this weightlifting?
(Jong Kook doesn't like anything he does.)
I'll aim slightly to the right.
- Okay.
- Stand a little bit to the right.
Look straight ahead.
Do what you normally do. Throw it naturally.
Be natural. Oh, gosh.
(His ball takes a diagonal path.)
Oh, gosh.
(Okay, that was natural.)
(He's in trouble, but this is so funny.)
Come here. Come here.
(Hey, you need to see me.)
- Come.
- I'll bowl better!
(He feels truly sorry.)
- I'll be better.
- This is nonsense.
- This doesn't make sense.
- I'll bowl better!
That was so bad.
I know. I have to win.
You're unbelievable.
I'll clean these.
- Sit down.
- Are you going to be this mad?
Sit down first.
(Jong Kook throws him down.)
I could be bad at it.
You're not that bad.
This is good, Bowling Cho.
(He gets 6 pins.)
(He walks quietly.)
Hold on.
Is bowling supposed to be this scary?
He wants to lose for sure.
(They finish 4 frames in a heavy atmosphere.)
I told you I don't.
Let's go.
(Jong Kook bowls for the 5th frame, and they have 37 points.)
It slipped.
(He's not doing as well as usual.)
(Glaring)
Why?
Why? What?
It's like he brought you when you didn't want to come.
You have to get a spare.
(He's just saying that.)
- I'll do this. I'm doing this.
- Okay.
Let's go. I'm getting a spare.
I'm doing it.
(I'll focus and do it the proper way.)
Good one.
- He'll get it.
- It worked.
(Will he hit the remaining 4 pins and get a spare?)
(He only got two.)
It turned left.
You are worse than me.
(He's frank.)
See? He's not better than me.
Look at the score.
- It slipped.
- Oh, gosh.
- How can you just hit those?
- It slipped.
Really? I think he's worse than me.
Nice.
- Nice?
- I'll be good. Nice.
- Nice.
- I'm going to be watching you.
I'm going to watch "Infinite Challenge" again.
(Jae Seok bowled in it.)
I'll see if you were this bad.
- Don't say "Infinite Challenge".
- Why not?
- Don't mention it.
- I thought you bowled there.
I did.
(That was short but a good time.)
(Cleaning)
Why are you wiping it so much?
You're horrible anyway.
- Give it to me.
- I can't wipe it?
- Give it.
- I'm not horrible.
What are you doing? Just bowl.
(I'll get going first.)
Come here.
- Where are you going?
- I think I should leave.
Goodness.
Hurry up. Stop wiping it.
Stop yelling at me.
Oh, gosh.
This is stress... I mean...
- Strike?
- Let me get a strike.
You keep doubting me.
- So do better.
- I will.
- Don't go for the gutter.
- Okay, I know.
Raise your arm straight up.
Raise your arm up. Go.
(Jae Seok throws the ball with Jong Kook nagging him.)
Up.
- Good shot.
- Goodness.
That's not good.
His hand didn't go up to his head.
(Falling)
(Oh, what?)
Wasn't that good? I think that was good.
(He gets a high score unexpectedly.)
That was good, right?
Why are you not happy?
(You knocked over so many pins.)
- Why are you not happy?
- What do you mean?
I have to get a spare. That's what I was planning.
(He's suspicious.)
I'll get a spare.
(He only has 2 pins left.)
Push it forward. Eyes on the pins. Look far away.
Speak for yourself.
You look down here.
- I don't look down.
- Goodness.
Try it. Do what you did just now.
I'm trying.
- I'll do it.
- Go.
Come back. Where are you going?
Sit down.
Give me your jacket.
(He gets his jacket taken away.)
Is bowling supposed to be this uncomfortable?
- You're supposed to cheer.
- Right?
You keep nagging.
Just go.
Move back a little bit. Don't sit there.
I'm sitting on a chair.
It's fine.
(Jae Seok bowls for the 6th frame, 2nd shot.)
Throw it straight. Relax. Good job.
Oh, my.
Relax.
(Relax. Good job.)
(Oh, my.)
Good luck.
(I should just clap.)
(The score is low like Jae Seok has planned.)
Okay!
(Sae Ho gets ready for the 7th frame.)
(He throws it powerfully.)
Good job.
It keeps going into the gutter.
(He won't turn around.)
(Thanks, Sae Ho.)
It keeps going into the gutter.
(He's glaring at the back of Sae Ho's head.)
(He never turns back.)
(He avoids looking back while grabbing a ball.)
Wipe the ball.
Sae Ho, wipe it once.
Why are you sweating so much?
(He's sweating instead of shedding tears.)
Don't flip your wrist.
(He's terrifying.)
(You scared me.)
- Okay.
- Go straight up.
Don't tell me too many things.
- I'll follow my instincts.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
(This is Sae Ho's 7th frame, 2nd swing.)
Nice.
Your wrist.
You punk!
(What instinct?)
Why would you rotate your wrist outwards?
(I'm just wondering, )
(but why am I getting scolded?)
I told you to do this.
(When did this start going wrong?)
Jong Kook, you look very angry.
Is it so hard to bring your arm up?
- I know.
- You just have to raise it up.
I know the mission is important,
but you didn't even get a spare.
- Come back.
- Where are you going?
Do you have a frozen shoulder? Can't you raise your arm?
(Sae Ho is about to cry.)
You don't have to have a frozen shoulder.
Goodness. Let's not be greedy, Jong Kook.
Let's not be greedy.
(He lets go of his greed and shoots.)
Gosh!
I keep missing the center.
I would be fine if you were good and scolded me.
(Goodness)
(I spoke what was on my mind.)
Why did you do that?
Sorry, I have a headache.
(What did I just do?)
(Was bowling this difficult emotionally?)
Still.
- Good luck.
- Okay, I'll get it.
- Spare.
- Watch.
(This is Jong Kook's 8th frame, 2nd swing.)
Okay. I got it.
(It's a clean shot.)
(Swinging)
(Okay. I got it.)
- Nice.
- I guess...
- you were really nervous.
- Why?
What was this?
(He swung his arm around because he wanted a spare.)
- Nice spin.
- Okay.
It's my turn.
(It's impossible to turn this game around.)
- Oh, gosh.
- He lost.
(And for the remaining 2 frames, )
(Jae Seok tried his best to lose.)
Go.
(Sae Ho's final swing in the 10th frame)
You got it. Oh, gosh.
(It ends up in the gutter.)
I told you 100 times that I am bad at bowling.
I don't bowl much.
(They fail with the score of 76.)
Thus, you failed the mission.
That means Sae Ho won't get the beef gift set.
That's too bad.
- Also...
- Should I leave?
The two of you...
made a bet on whether the mission will be successful or not.
- Gosh.
- Firstly, Jong Kook wrote...
"Success".
- Unfortunately, Jae Seok wrote...
- You can tell us later.
- Look at me.
- "Failure".
(Unfortunately, Jae Seok wrote "Failure".)
Look at me. Hey.
Jae Seok obtains additional points.
Why did you reveal that right now? You could have revealed it later.
Jae Seok, sit down.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
It's easy...
to fail.
It's easy to fail. We can easily force it.
We can only succeed when we bring our hearts together.
You failed on purpose.
Don't you think it's selfish?
- You are having an important talk.
- Let's be honest.
- What do you think?
- I have to go.
- I have somewhere to be.
- Sae Ho.
Thank you for today.
- Sae Ho, go home.
- I will do that.
- You know, - Go on.
- The two of you should talk it out.
- It's not like that.
Sit down. Sit down and listen to me.
- Come on.
- Sit here.
- No.
- Sit down.
Tell me what you think.
- It's not like that.
- You write "Success" or "Failure".
Between success and failure, which one is harder?
The thing is,
I feel really uncomfortable.
(I feel really uncomfortable.)
Tell me.
It was fun to see you and bowl with you.
- However...
- Tell me what you think.
I think I feel uncomfortable.
I can't believe Jae Seok.
I trust people too easily.
(What is he doing when the game is over?)
I trust people too much.
(He takes the correct form...)
(and swings gently.)
He did it.
(He took out the spares perfectly.)
(Shocked)
(Jae Seok's bowling skills are unexpected.)
You are a swindler.
- You know that?
- I am not a swindler.
(The real swindling begins now.)
(Next week)
(The backstabbing race isn't over.)
(Twists and turns of events)
(The grand finale finally unfolds.)
(Don't let your guard down for a second.)
(It's not over until it is.)
(What becomes of the TV rating notice?)
(And)
(So Min and Se Chan's One Year Anniversary Special)
(An outing organized just for them)
(Whatever Se Chan wishes for comes true.)
(Of Se Chan, )
(by Se Chan, )
(and for Se Chan.)
(They even get Twice as the special guest.)
(Se Chan's special day begins.)
Shazam!
(Se Chan's 1 Year Anniversary Special, One Day)