(The refreshing energy of the early summer has dawned.)
- Hey. - Hello. Hi.
- What are you doing? - Hello, Seok Jin.
- Hello. Hi. - Are you Baekgu, the white dog?
- Eternity. - Hey, I get the feeling today...
- that we'll do a partner race. - Partner?
- It's a couple race. What was that? - A partner race.
- A partner race. Why? Why? - My gosh, that's a bit too...
- He might even say, "buddy". - A partner.
Just like you predicted, you will do a couple race today.
(They haven't done a couple race for a while now.)
(That's awesome! It's a couple race today!)
These guys are ridiculous.
You've never become a real couple. Why are you so happy about it?
Even so. You never know.
Young Jin, give me the cologne just in case.
(Young Jin is his personal stylist.)
- I need to spray some cologne too. - Why would you apply it?
Hey, just go with your natural smell.
- My gosh, unbelievable. - "Natural smell"?
- Natural smell? - Your expression is...
- too violent. - Your natural smell.
- What is this? - Why? It smells nice.
- My goodness, come on. - Natural smell.
- You're talking nonsense. - Why would you bring that?
- My gosh, that's so lame. - He's really spraying it.
- Hey, the cologne... - What are you doing?
- My goodness. I can't believe it. - He really sprayed it?
- Hey, what's up with your pants? - Hey, hey. Punk.
- Young Jin. Young Jin. - Hey, hey, hey.
- Hey, come back here. - Hey, Young Jin. Give it back.
- If you want it, pass by. - You little punk. Hey.
If you want it, pass by.
(There's a stream of people.)
- You should've done it in advance. - My goodness.
Stop it!
(He sniffs it all of a sudden.)
(Spraying)
(This is mine.)
- It smells nice. It's nice. - This is nice.
Hey, I like the smell.
Seok Jin is hilarious.
He stuck out his face as if it were a face mist.
Seok Jin doesn't know anything.
He really doesn't.
Let's welcome the guests one by one.
- Okay. - They will come right away.
- Here they come. - Here they come.
Who are they? Gosh, why did they show up first?
- Congratulations. - Okay.
(Their reactions tell you who the first guests are.)
(Ji Hyo and So Min walk forward without sparing a glance.)
- Welcome. - Take your positions.
- Take your positions. - All right.
Hello, So Min.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's nice to meet you. - It's nice to meet you.
(They greet each other dryly.)
Hello, hello.
- I am sure you have been well. - Yes.
Next!
(Haha cuts them off.)
Who is next?
(Is that all?)
Let us talk some more.
The two of you are here, so it's time for the other guests.
- Is that all? - Let's get this started.
(This song is...)
(The real guests of the day make an appearance.)
- AOA! - It's Seol Hyun!
- My goodness. - AOA!
(Seol Hyun and Hye Jeong of AOA)
(AOA is the queen of summer with a new song, "Bingle Bangle".)
(Seol Hyun and Hye Jeong show talents in various fields.)
- My goodness. - It has been a while.
- It's Seol Hyun. - Hye Jeong is here as well.
- It has been a while. - Welcome, Hye Jeong.
It has been a while. It really has been.
- Hello. Hello, Hye Jeong. - My goodness.
- Do you know them? - I know Seol Hyun.
- We are like a family. - Stop it.
- 2, 3. Hello, we are... - Hello, we are...
- Ace of Angels, AOA. - Ace of Angels, AOA.
(They show an explosive reaction.)
Let's fly away!
- Let's fly away! - Come on!
Why did you swat my hands? I'm going to fly away.
- Go away. - All right.
Seol Hyun, you lost so much weight.
I work out these days.
- Really? - You work out.
It's important to work out.
You should be nice to So Min and Ji Hyo as well.
- Seriously. - Be nice to us.
- You haven't seen them in a while. - Show us a smile.
You can't compare with them in the slightest.
(Annoying)
(They prefer the guests over their family.)
Seriously.
Seol Hyun, tell me if you need anything for working out.
- Seriously. - This is incredible.
Hey.
Kwang Soo, why are you acting strangely?
- There he goes again. - He said he was close to Seol Hyun.
- Well, - You aren't close to her.
- we are close. - He said he was very close to her.
Seol Hyun and I had...
- a romantic subplot. - Don't be ridiculous.
(A romantic subplot between Kwang Soo and Seol Hyun?)
- You are wrong. - A romantic subplot?
- No such thing existed. - When she was here last time...
- You are wrong. - Tell them.
- It was between Gary and her. - That's right.
When Gary and I were left, Seol Hyun chose me.
(3 years ago, they had the 2015 Christmas Special.)
(Seol Hyun was Gary's partner, )
(but Kwang Soo confessed to her.)
(What was Seol Hyun's answer?)
(Okay.)
(Kwang Soo beat Gary and became a couple with Seol Hyun.)
(It's a touching memory Kwang Soo will never forget.)
- Seol Hyun, don't you remember? - No.
She doesn't remember.
(Seol Hyun doesn't remember.)
He's a mythomaniac.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
You should stop. She doesn't remember.
- The memory's still very vivid. - Don't demand that she remembers.
- Also... - The rose.
Seol Hyun and Hye Jeong joined us. Let's meet the next guests.
(This song is...)
What?
Hello, hello. It's Momoland.
Joo E, what is wrong with your eye?
Joo E and Da Young!
(Momoland has become popular with songs such as "Bboom Bboom".)
(Joo E has been on commercials thanks to her good cheer.)
(Da Young is a lead vocalist of WJSN who is as cheerful as Joo E.)
(They enter energetically.)
What is that? What is wrong with your eye?
- What is wrong with your eye? - What is wrong with your eye?
- Hello. - What is wrong with your eye?
- All right. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Joo E.
I am sorry,
but what is up with your eye?
I have a sty.
- Do you have a sty? - I am sorry.
Are you cosplaying Gung Ye?
She must be the first idol singer to do that.
She is the first idol singer to wear an eye patch to the shoot.
It's the first in the history of Running Man.
- She is wearing an eye patch. - No one has done that. It's unique.
- I like her character. - She makes us curious.
Will Joo E's partner wear an eye patch as well?
- What? - Will her partner wear...
- an eye patch? - It will be a couple's item.
- I am ready to wear it. - Really?
It's okay.
Joo E says it's okay.
I got rejected from the start.
Isn't it too cruel to reject me so soon?
That happened a bit early.
(Look forward to Joo E's performance today!)
Now,
next to Joo E is...
Dong Yeob.
- Hello. - Dong Yeob.
- Hello. - Hello.
(She is used to it.)
My goodness.
- I wanted to say it. - She looks like Dong Yeob.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Stop it.
Da Young is here with us.
Will we have a couple race with four guests?
- Joo E, Da Young, and the others? - The numbers are perfect.
- The numbers are perfect. - That's right.
There are 6 men and 6 women right now.
- There are two more guests. - Really?
- Really? Why? - Are there more guests?
There are 6 men and 6 women right now.
That means there will be more men.
(At that moment, they hear a familiar song.)
- My goodness. - It's Winner!
It's Winner!
(Winner enters.)
This is great.
It will be fun.
(The gangster of digital music sales, Winner)
(Min Ho and Seung Yoon visit Running Man at the same time.)
- It's Winner! - It's Winner!
(My goodness, it's Winner!)
This is great.
(They show their swag through dancing.)
Seung Yoon.
Min Ho.
(Winner's appearance puts a damper on the male members' moods.)
(I love the atmosphere today.)
- It's Min Ho. - Hello.
- Please come this way. - Their outfits are cool.
They are handsome.
- Goodness. - You should have called.
- So Min. - They are...
- really excited. - We are set! We are set!
(Ji Hyo and So Min find their motivation.)
You can't compare with them in the slightest.
- That's right. - This serves you right!
- We know that. - Your skin is dull.
- Your skin is dull. - We know that.
- We acknowledge that. - You are dingy.
- We know we can't compare. - You know,
we thought we would have 6 men and 6 women for a couple race.
We are getting a headache...
because the two of you joined unexpectedly.
- Why would you get a headache? - I'm having...
- a headache. - Your path is set.
- Your partner is right here. - There will be a male couple.
(Your partner is right here.)
(He can't get away from Seok Jin, his soulmate.)
- Stop it. - I don't like you either.
- Stop it. - Don't be absurd.
- For goodness' sake. - Now...
Hold on.
So Min,
you are smiling from ear to ear.
No, I am not.
- Who is it today? - Who is it today?
- Who is it today? - When you smile brightly,
you look more like Han Min Kwan.
(You can see Han Min Kwan's face in So Min's face.)
I see Kwang Kyu. Kim Kwang Kyu.
- Kim Kwang Kyu. - Is this the Comedian Special?
- I am sorry. - We have Han Min Kwan...
- and Shin Dong Yeob. - Hello.
So Min resembles Kwang Kyu a lot.
- Kwang Kyu. - Kim Kwang Kyu.
Min Ho, you can laugh.
(She suddenly gives him a signal.)
- It must be Min Ho. - So Min is sending him a signal.
Why did you tell him that he could laugh?
He was stifling his laughter.
So Min should have a nice day from time to time.
All right.
- Se Chan, you are sweating a lot. - Yes, I am. I am nervous.
(He is sweating buckets.)
I am nervous for no reason.
I hope one of the women will be my partner.
- All right. - That's why you are nervous.
Why does Se Chan look so small today?
Let's talk...
to the guests who have joined us for today.
Apparently, Min Ho is...
top one in his group when it comes to income.
- Really? - Min Ho is top one.
I guess he gets royalties.
His necklace tells me he spends a lot of money on himself.
It's genuine.
- It's genuine. - Really?
- That's incredible. - It's genuine.
Would you show it to us?
This is what it looks like.
(Embarrassed)
I thought it would be much longer.
That surprised me.
It's so short.
- That's the trend. - Min Ho,
I also thought it would be much longer.
I was surprised because it's so short.
- Long necklaces are tacky. - Short necklaces are in vogue.
- That's the trend. - That's the trend.
- It should be snug. - Long necklaces are tacky.
Aren't your earrings too big?
My ears are about to rip.
Isn't that Moon Hee Jun's style from back in the days?
I am certain Haha will wear those earrings next week.
He will wear bigger ones.
(They can already tell what Haha will wear next week.)
You know,
- about 10 years ago, - Good job.
- he tried to copy G-Dragon. - That's right.
These days, he tries to copy Min Ho.
Doesn't he look like he should be on "High School Rapper"?
(He doesn't even dress like Min Ho.)
- He copies Ha On. - Ha On.
He copies Ha On.
When did I do that?
Ha On is like 30 years younger than him.
Come on!
Why does he copy someone who is 30 years younger than him?
He is unbelievable.
He isn't 30 years younger than me.
(Haha can find his next fashion muse on "Einstein".)
Seung Yoon, how have you been? Winner's new song came out.
- I love it so much. - Tell us about the song.
Shall we watch a movie early in the morning?
Since you visited the show after a long while,
please dance for us.
- Please do that. - Let's see it.
- We have to see this dance. - That's right.
We have to see the Hammer Dance.
- Winner, let's go. - Let's go.
Let's get it!
(Her good cheer explodes.)
- I don't see the end - They'll start now.
(When they dance lightly, their swag explodes.)
(They are relaxed despite the difficult dance moves.)
They are fast.
(Her heart flutters.)
(She becomes a fangirl.)
(Flapping)
Let's go!
(Here comes the Hammer Dance.)
This is it.
(The correct demonstration versus the wrong demonstration)
(Winner doesn't disappoint.)
- They are good. - They are cool.
- That was nice. - They are cool.
- They are cool. - That was nice.
(Thanks to Winner, the atmosphere is lively.)
Now, it's Joo E and Da Young's turn.
(Da Young of WJSN and Joo E of Momoland)
Aren't you very close friends?
- Yes. - That's right.
We met once at a private event, and we became close afterward.
Where did you meet?
- It was in Gangnam. - We had shabu shabu in Gangnam.
- Did you eat shabu shabu? - Yes.
You shouldn't drink during the day already.
(He tries to slander them.)
No, we just turned 20.
"Bboom Bboom" is very popular these days.
Aren't you happy, Joo E?
- I'm very happy. - Right.
- She's very happy. - I wasn't asking you to dance.
(She dances to the song.)
She likes to have fun.
- It's your first time on the show. - You're right.
- I'm very nervous and excited. - Now that you're on the show...
Really? Please answer when I ask.
- When... - She's so anxious.
She can't stay still.
- When I... - She speaks when Jae Seok speaks.
Please answer when I ask.
- I'm too nervous. - She sounds like a broken recorder.
- Are you nervous? - Yes.
You don't seem nervous at all.
- I'm very nervous. - Really?
Joo E and Da Young know each other.
Da Young is also known to be energetic.
- Really? - She seems like it.
- That's right. - She has a special look.
Da Young is originally from Jeju Island.
- Come and visit Jeju Island. - Okay.
(Come and visit Jeju Island.)
Let's go.
(She makes an unrelated comment.)
When was the last time you went to Jeju Island?
I went there to dive recently.
- "To dive"? - Yes.
- Did you dive? - Like a diver.
- Did you go diving? - Yes.
- Really? - I went diving to catch murices.
My mom runs an eel restaurant.
Come to our eel restaurant, everyone.
(Come to our eel restaurant, everyone.)
- There's a lot. - We'll come.
Is this some kind of an official gesture?
I'm sorry, but you shouldn't make advertisements.
- Okay. - All right.
- If you come, shrimp will be free. - Stop it.
- Stop it. What do you mean by that? - Sorry.
- Just come. - Goodness.
They are Hye Jeong and Seol Hyun of AOA.
(Hye Jeong and Seol Hyun)
- Hello, I'm Seol Hyun. - Hello, I'm Hye Jeong.
Seol Hyun often visited our show in the beginning of her career.
She made herself clear back then.
- "I like Joong Ki." - Right.
That's what she told us.
It's sad that Joong Ki got married.
Whose fan are you now?
Now, I'm a fan of someone who isn't Korean.
- Is it a foreigner? - Who is it?
It's the actor in "Thor".
(Her ideal type is Thor.)
(It's understandable.)
- "Thor"? - He's handsome.
Jong Kook is Thor in Running Man.
- He's Thor in Korea. - He's our Thor.
Is he Chris Hemsworth?
Yes, it's Chris Hemsworth.
- I like Thor. - I was startled when...
- she brought up Cream Sam Sauce. - What did you say?
Cream Sam Sauce.
"Cream Sam Sauce"?
- What kind of sauce is it? - Cream Sam Sauce.
- Worth, Chris Hemsworth. - Right.
- Is it silkworm? - It's delicious.
Is there a reason why you like Chris Hemsworth?
I fell in love with him after watching the movie.
- Yes. - It can't be helped.
- You'd fall in love with Kwang Soo. - In "Collective Invention"?
If you watch him in "Collective Invention"...
- Why do you keep mentioning that? - You were a fish.
He was a fish for two hours.
He's without a head or a tail.
- Right. - By the way...
- He was a rockfish. - Was it...
- a rockfish or a carp? - It was a rockfish.
- Wasn't it a halibut? - It was a rockfish.
- Shut it, you all. - Wasn't it a halibut?
- That's not important. - It was another type of fish.
It wasn't a halibut. Halibuts are flat.
- Some called it a Korean bullhead. - "Korean bullhead"?
- What do you mean? It wasn't. - Wasn't it a Korean bullhead?
- No. - It was a monkfish.
- It was a monkfish. - Monkfish are flat.
I love that movie, so stop it!
(They make fun of "Collective Invention" again.)
We also have Hye Jeong with us.
(It's time to meet Hye Jeong.)
She's also modeling for jeans.
She shows them off.
There are ways and poses...
- to make the jeans look good. - Yes.
You can lift up your buttocks a little.
Like this?
Raise one foot slightly.
- Do you lift it a little? - Slightly.
- Do it toward the camera. - But...
It hurts a lot.
- I bet it does. - When you pull it up,
your buttocks can look more voluptuous.
It's a know-how.
- As Hye Jeong said... - Do it toward the camera.
Don't you also do a lot of modeling, Seol Hyun?
- Her full-size posters disappeared. - What?
- What? - "Full-size posters"?
- Full-size posters. - What are they?
They got stolen for a while.
- He means a standing signboard. - "Standing signboard"?
He's a full-size poster.
- Me? - Kwang Soo...
- He's one of them. - Am I a full-size poster?
- He is. - I'm a full-size poster?
They're small and large full-size posters.
- Small and large full-size posters. - Why?
(Small and large full-size posters)
Why are you calling me that? Wait a minute.
- I didn't do anything. - They're large and small.
Why am I a poster?
Goodness.
AOA released a new song recently.
- It's been a long time. - We've been waiting for long.
It took a long time.
- Right. - It's been a year and a half.
Really?
- Why? - We should take a look.
What's the title of your new song?
- The title is "Bingle Bangle". - "Bingle Bangle".
"Bingle Bangle".
Here it comes.
(Shake your bottoms.)
- There it is. - Look at the dance.
(It's already addicting.)
Do you know the song?
They dance well.
Goodness.
They make the same movements again.
(The younger singers are impressed.)
("Bingle Bangle" is a song that will cool down the summer.)
What are you doing?
(Her leg slides.)
(It's perfect to the end.)
That's was so sudden.
I think she just made that up.
- It's the original choreography. - It's original.
(Everyone is in a daze.)
- That looks difficult. - It could be dangerous.
- Why did she do that suddenly? - That was amazing.
(They struggle to copy Seol Hyun.)
- What's wrong, So Min? - What's wrong with them?
- Goodness. - What are you doing?
You're not flexible.
(You'll get used to it after 9 years.)
Today's race has a golden ring on the line.
It's called Zombie Couple Race.
- "Zombie"? - "Zombie"?
- "Zombie Couple Race"? - "Zombie Couple"?
There are two contagious zombies...
who can turn humans into zombies.
There's one vaccinated human...
who can turn zombies into humans.
(There's one vaccinated human.)
If your partner is a contagious zombie, you turn into one as well.
(You become a zombie when your partner is a zombie.)
The winning couple obtains a chance to exchange partners...
and hints about the contagious zombies and the vaccinated human.
The contagious zombies...
and their partners stay as zombies.
If a zombie is partnered with the vaccinated human,
they become a human again, so choose your partners wisely.
What if a contagious zombie is partnered with the vaccinated human?
Nothing happens.
(Nothing happens.)
In the final round, if the vaccinated human...
eliminates both of the contagious zombies, Team Humans wins.
If the contagious zombies eliminate the vaccinated human,
Team Contagious Zombies wins.
If everyone becomes a zombie...
except for the vaccinated human, Team Contagious Zombies wins.
(Identify the contagious zombies before everyone turns into them.)
Before we start the race,
you must choose your partners.
You'll choose your partners by playing Heart Signal.
(Heart Signal)
- "Heart Signal"? - What is it?
A female member comes out with music.
She sends a heart-shaped signal while dancing.
The male members who want to become her partner...
will come out and dance with her.
On the count of three, both of the members...
will make a heart.
The one who makes the same shape as the female becomes her partner.
Thank goodness.
There's a variety of heart shapes.
You can make different kinds.
1 couple will be 2 men.
- Right. - That's a pity.
If you don't want to become partners...
with some of the male members, you can make strange shapes.
- That's right. - You can do that.
Goodness.
(He's nervous.)
It's a mental game.
Why are you pretending to be nervous? It'll be easy for you.
- Really? - Yes.
Why are you being so serious?
Don't be so serious.
We're just partners for the day. That's unnecessary.
(Heart Signal starts.)
All right, everyone. Let's choose our partners.
Hye Jeong will start first.
- Me? - Yes.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Good luck. - I'll start.
It helps if you give us hints.
It won't be confusing.
I won't be pathetic. I'll step out only once.
- Don't be pathetic. - Just once?
- I won't step forward many times. - Me neither.
- I'll go out once. - Me too.
- I'll step out once. - I'm a valuable man.
Please play the music.
(Music starts for the valuable men.)
- Please start. - Why is it so slow?
Right?
(Her dance movements are slower.)
(She makes a heart signal.)
Is that your signal?
- Just once. - Right?
(That's the shape.)
- That's her signal. - Is this it?
That's right.
(She sends her signal directly to Kwang Soo.)
(Did you just pick me?)
Shall I go now?
Men, please go out.
(The men step out.)
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan come forward slowly.)
What's going on? Which heart shape should I make?
Look at them.
(Hye Jeong's signal is mine.)
The flies are out.
- The flies are out. - They are out.
- The flies are out. - It's a fruit fly and a dung fly.
(Buzzing)
(The fly brothers flutter their wings to win her heart.)
- You said you'd try just once. - Let's go.
On the count of three, please make a heart sign.
What should I do? I think she sent me a signal.
- One... - I think she gave you...
- I can make the sign now, right? - a sign.
- One... - Haha is joining.
(After saying he'd step out once, Haha joins the fly brothers.)
(He said he wasn't easy.)
1, 2, 3.
(Everyone makes a heart sign.)
(Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong become a team.)
(That was it?)
Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong are a team.
(Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong become the first team.)
- Let's do well. - Please come here.
- I hope one of them is a zombie. - Next...
(Jealous)
- "I hope one of them is a zombie"? - You said you'd step out only once.
- What are you doing? - Don't say mean things.
- Don't say mean things. - It hurts every time.
- Now, it's So Min's turn. - Okay.
- So Min. - All right. Let's see it.
- So Min. - So Min.
This is just a game. Why are you blushing?
Why am I blushing? It's strange.
I'm just hot.
- Please play some music. - Please join me.
Min Ho should try.
(What's this song?)
What's this song?
Let's go!
(It's So Min's theme song.)
This... We should do this.
We have to do this.
(She gives up.)
(So Min gives up and starts to show off her charms.)
Isn't anyone joining her?
(She signals, but no one comes.)
No one is joining her.
No one wants to go. What should we do?
- Someone please join her. - No one wants to.
(Lonely)
(It's Min Ho.)
(Min Ho joins after watching quietly.)
(Swag)
Min Ho...
He's so cool.
(Min Ho is the best.)
He's amazing.
Will no one else come out?
Is it only me?
No one else? 1, 2...
(They both make a heart sign.)
Three.
(So Min and Min Ho become a team.)
What is this?
Min Ho is an angel.
Let's move on. It's Da Young's turn.
- We should try. - Let's get it.
Da Young... She took her shoes off.
(She takes her shoes off.)
Her shoes...
- Was that really necessary? - She's too much.
- She's too much. - It's Da Young's turn.
I'll try only once. Okay.
What I did with Hye Jeong doesn't count.
(It doesn't count.)
- It doesn't count? - She's sending me a signal.
Please give us some music.
(Da Young's Heart Signal)
- I wanted a song like this one. - She starts right away.
But that song suited you better.
- What is she doing? - I wanted a song like this.
Is that a heart?
- We can't do that. - She's going to do that?
Show us something else.
(There's this one too.)
Hey.
- What is that? - Don't do that!
(Do you want us to do that?)
Haha, it's you.
(Haha, will you join me?)
(Sure, if you want me to.)
Haha is in.
Just let them be a team.
Come on.
Wait.
(Jae Seok does a dirty heart dance.)
(Haha is on the alert.)
She's giving you a sign.
(Whom is she signaling to? Jae Seok or Haha?)
All right. 1, 2...
(Haha and Da Young become a team.)
- Jae Seok got turned down. - It's been a while.
(Jae Seok loses to Haha.)
That was easy.
- I beat Jae Seok. - All right.
This is Haha's Running Man.
I didn't want to join anyway.
It shouldn't count because my heart wasn't moved.
- What are you talking about? - My heart...
- You even lied down. - My heart wasn't in it.
- What are you talking about? - I'll erase it from my memory.
Next up is...
- Seol Hyun! - Seol Hyun.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - Get out of my way.
- It's fierce. - Seol Hyun...
- We all have to try. - We have to.
Please give us some music.
(The competition is already fierce.)
(Crowded)
(Even Min Ho wants to join.)
- That looks cool. - We have to try.
Min Ho, where are you going?
- I want to dance. - Why are you joining?
I just like the song.
Seol Hyun, give us a sign.
- Look at his smile. - That looks so fake.
- It's disgusting. - Seriously.
Please make different kinds of hearts.
- That's the heart. - Oh, that's it.
(That must be it.)
- Give us a sign. - Oh, that must be it.
(It might be this one too.)
- What is it? - Which one is right?
- Which one? - Which one is right?
- This one? - 1, 2, 3.
(I hope we'll make the same sign.)
(Jong Kook and Seol Hyun become a team.)
(The competition was fierce.)
(Happy)
(Exhilarated)
Jong Kook looks so happy.
Seol Hyun is the same.
- She looks too happy to be a team. - So what?
- It shows too much. - I am happy.
- I'm better than the other two. - Don't say that.
- Don't you think? - You never know.
I think it worked out for the best.
(It had to be Jong Kook.)
- I admit it. - I feel so sorry.
(The fierce Heart Signal is over.)
(Couple Matching Result)
Everyone, couples have been formed.
Let me tell you how many zombies there are right now.
At the moment...
(They started out with two contagious zombies.)
(How many zombies are there right now?)
There are four zombies.
(There are two more zombies now.)
That many?
(That means...)
The contagious zombies must have become a team with humans.
- They must have become a team... - Right.
- with humans. - There are four zombies right now.
After changing, we'll start the race.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(The Zombie Couple Race starts.)
Amazing.
Please come here.
(Everyone, check this out.)
(So Min is borrowing Min Ho's golden necklace.)
- Look at this. - Look at that swag.
Stop it, you two.
(Swag, my foot.)
Because So Min got a necklace,
Seol Hyun is regretting her team choice.
(Seol Hyun is regretting.)
No. I'm just borrowing it.
- Seol Hyun must like shiny things. - Shiny things?
- That looks cool. - Don't lose it.
- So Min... - It doesn't look good on her.
Do that again.
(So Min is gesturing.)
- Gosh. We're shooting. - What?
You shouldn't do this.
(Don't make that gesture.)
It suits her.
(Kwang Soo is making it look like So Min made a smoking gesture.)
But So Min does this.
(Haha chips in.)
That's right.
She's caught.
To win hints about the contagious zombies and the vaccinated human...
and to change your partners, you have to win the first mission.
It's called Cosmic Charm Bboom Bboom Every Day Heart Attack.
(Cosmic Charm Bboom Bboom Every Day Heart Attack)
- It's all in there. - Cosmic Charm Bboom Bboom...
Bboom Bboom Heart Attack.
- You're going to... - Hold on.
So Min. I'm sorry but...
- What is it? - Seriously.
During your short conversation, you were doing this so many times.
(She wants to look cute.)
- When you talk to us... - She did it again?
(Earlier, Min Ho was explaining the meaning of the game title.)
(So that's what it meant. I had no idea.)
- You're doing it so many times. - What's with you?
- Stop it. - Stop it.
- It's not like that. - That's how it all starts.
The winner of each round will win points.
The team with the most points will win the race.
- Okay. - First, it's an impression quiz.
(Impression Quiz)
- An impression quiz? - An impression quiz?
- That sounds difficult. - An impression quiz?
The winner will get 10 points. For 60 seconds,
the team members will take turns...
mimicking a person or a thing.
The team that gets more questions right will win.
- I'm not good at it. - So Min is going to win.
- So Min is a professional. - She's amazing.
She can mimic many people. Min Ho, are you good at it?
- I heard he's good. - He's really good.
- He's good? - Yes.
- He's the best in our group. - Really?
- We're the strongest team. - This is going to be fun.
- He's really good. - Who should start?
We want to start.
- So randomly? - He must a zombie.
- He's a zombie. - Why would I be?
- That was so random. - He wants to be a human.
Why do you want to start?
I can do it later.
(If you're going to mock me like this, I'll do it later.)
- Why? - You must have a reason.
- No? - He wants to do it later.
I mean... What?
All right. Let's start from Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong.
(They're allowed to go first.)
- There are two zombie couples. - Ready.
Start.
(Hye Jeong has to mimic An Young Mi.)
- Ready. - They're going to take turns.
(An Young Mi?)
Start.
What's with you? That startled me. What's that?
(That's a very energetic dance.)
- That's... - That's accurate.
- That's very accurate. - That's on point.
- My gosh! - Don't you know this move?
- An Young Mi. Okay. - Right.
(He gets it correct.)
- Okay. - That was spot on.
(It's Han Gi Beom.)
- Come on. - It's just him.
(It's him again?)
(Fine. I'll do his impression.)
(He doesn't need to impersonate him. He looks just like Gi Beom.)
- I can't remember his name. - She doesn't know.
- It's his doppelganger! - She doesn't know.
- No, he isn't! - It's your doppelganger!
- She said they look alike. - They look alike.
- It's his lookalike. - They look alike.
- All right. - You look just like him.
(He looks like the younger version who used to rule the courts.)
- He looks just like that guy. - This is easy.
- It's his lookalike. - You look like him.
- Pass? - Pass, pass.
It's your lookalike.
(She fails since she can't remember his name.)
(The next keyword is pressure rice cooker.)
(Pressure rice cooker? I can handle this.)
Wait, I'm sorry. Hold on.
(He accidentally says the brand.)
- Wait, I'm sorry. Hold on. - What was that?
You can't say the name of the brand.
- What is this? - I'm sorry.
- You can't do that. - I'm sorry. It just came out.
- This isn't fair. - I'm sorry.
- Rice cooker! Rice cooker. - This won't count.
(Since he cheated, it won't count. Their 60 seconds are up.)
We got many of them right.
- That was Han Gi Beom. - That's right!
- He looks just like Gi Beom. - No, I don't. What? No.
- She said they looked alike. - Next up are...
So Min and Min Ho.
- Let's do this. - Let's get it.
- Swag. - It's lovey-dovey couple.
- It's lovey-dovey couple. - Swag.
I can't help but walk like this...
after meeting Min Ho.
- We can do it. - We can do it.
Get ready.
Start.
(So Min will explain first. The keyword is Choi Min Sik.)
- "You. You punk." - Choi Min Sik.
(Choi Min Sik is the right answer.)
"Can you see the bullet wound here?"
Lee Jung Jae.
(I can pull this off too.)
Did you guys prepare this?
This one is difficult.
(So Min's keyword is Song Kang Ho.)
What was that? I can't remember his line.
What was that?
"Hey, I'm number 3. Number 3."
(The actor never said this line.)
- "Hey, this is..." - Song Kang Ho.
(However, he manages to figure it out.)
- He's good. - That wasn't the line.
(How did you answer that?)
- You can flip the page. - He's so good.
(Kang Ho Dong is a comparatively easier keyword.)
"Seung Gi!"
(This one is easy.)
Lee Sang Yeob.
(What? Why is this Sang Yeob?)
(It's incorrect.)
- Sang Yeob? - It's wrong.
- Why would you say Sang Yeob? - What did you say?
- Why? - That came out of nowhere.
My gosh, you two...
(Min Ho's keyword is bidet which is a difficult one.)
- They are really good. - This one is amazing.
(It won't be easy. How will Min Ho describe a bidet?)
(Pressing a button)
(Moaning)
(Why does it look sexual?)
Bidet!
(Bidet is correct.)
- What's happening? - That was really good.
- That was awesome. - My gosh.
- The last impression was good. - I mean...
- He did it with only one move. - They're currently in first place.
It's Min Ho and...
(So Min and Min Ho answers 4 questions.)
I've never been in first place.
Next up are Ji Hyo...
- and Seung Yoon. - Seung Yoon.
- Seung Yoon, you look nice. - We should just have fun.
Get ready.
- Let's just have fun. Okay. - I'll start.
Start.
(Seung Yoon's first keyword is Yang Hyun Suk.)
(It's my label's CEO. I can do this.)
"Well, you know..."
"Our Winner..."
That sounds similar.
(Zoning out)
Song Min Ho.
(She calls out Min Ho's name.)
(It's incorrect.)
- That's Min Ho? - Min Ho?
(She's clueless while Min Ho is speechless.)
- She doesn't know. - She doesn't know.
- She has no idea. - Try to answer it right.
- Why? - That's incorrect.
- She doesn't know him. - That's wrong.
- Pass. - He'll try now.
(Seung Yoon's keyword is Yoo Ah In.)
(It's his famous line from "Veteran", "I can't believe it.")
(This is too easy.)
(Yoo Ah In)
(She doesn't know this one either.)
- Hey, this is... - You should get it right away.
- You should've gotten it already. - How can you not know this?
- I just can't remember it. Wait. - I really can't believe this.
I really can't believe this.
My gosh, this is too easy.
- How could you not know this? - Yoo Ah In.
(She barely manages to figure it out.)
(Ji Hyo's keyword is Lee Byung Hun.)
My gosh, how do I explain this?
(This is hard.)
I can't do this. Give me a second.
(You can do the massage with the prosthetic arm.)
Hey, do this. This.
(It's one of the best scenes from "Inside Men".)
(Byung Hun gives a massage with his prosthetic arm.)
- Hey, do this. This. - There's a lot you can do.
- My gosh, this is... - There's a ton you can do.
(She lifts her arm like this...)
(Is she sawing?)
What? You're sawing, Ji Hyo?
- That's not right. - What was that?
- Why would you saw it? - To be honest...
(We don't know what she's sawing, but she fails to describe him.)
- You're not sawing anything. - That's wrong.
- To be honest, I don't know this. - We'll pass this.
- I don't know. - "Why did you do it?"
(He sings "Instinctively".)
- "Like It". - "Like It".
- It hurts - Right. "Like It".
- I should've sung that. - It hurts
Start.
(Haha and Da Young's first keyword is Park Myung Soo.)
"Let's go."
- Jung Jun Ha. - No.
(What?)
(Incorrect)
That was incorrect.
- "Let's go." - He's flustered.
That was incorrect. That was wrong.
(The next keyword is Gung Ye.)
- She might not know this one. - "I can't see with one of my eyes."
(He puts on an eye patch.)
(Time is up.)
Why? What's wrong?
- Why? Why? - It's over.
(The keyword is Yoon Kye Sang.)
- This is hard. - This is...
"Where are you from?"
- "Where are you from?" - That line!
"Must I know your name too?"
Pass.
The way she passed the question was so cool.
(He's impressed.)
- This is so cool. - "I won't give it up."
(The keyword is Kim Hee Ae.)
Pass.
(She looks the coolest.)
- That was a good impression. - That was good.
- Why am I getting angry? - She doesn't know anything.
If you answer this, it'd be amazing.
(The keyword is window. She makes wiping noises.)
- Window! Okay. - Yes!
- People open and wipe the window. - She opened it.
- She wiped it in the air. - Right.
(It's Seok Jin and Se Chan's turn, but the keyword is Namgung Ok Boon.)
At times, I think of you
- I think of you - Park Haki.
(Incorrect)
Park Haki?
(Only Seok Jin knows this old keyword.)
Hold on a second. Hold on.
- Kim Serena. - Wait a second.
Aren't these historical people?
- Aren't they historical people? - Right now, Joo E...
This is all that I can do.
(Since Se Chan doesn't know them, they answer 0 question.)
This is too much.
- Jong Kook and Seol Hyun are next. - Is it our turn?
- Come on. - Okay.
- I really suck at this. - Come on, come on.
Seol Hyun will start.
Start.
(What's Seol Hyun's first keyword?)
How do I do this impression? I forgot.
You can forget all you want. Keep going. It's okay.
(He's kind only to Seol Hyun.)
"Mister, mister."
(Wait, this is...)
- She did everything. - That's right.
- It's impossible not to know. - This is just a giveaway.
- This is the basic impression. - Everyone does this impression.
- "Mister"? - "Mister, mister".
"Mister"?
(It's Ok Hui from "My Mother and Her Guest".)
- Everyone does this impression. - Right.
(I know what it is.)
It's the one with Ho Dong...
- I don't know this one. - My gosh.
You don't know this one?
(Why don't you know this one?)
- Jong Kook will definitely get it. - What?
(This is Jong Kook's favorite item, the blender.)
- That's right. He has to know. - What?
- Is it a helicopter? - He has to know.
You don't know this one?
(I got it. If it whirs...)
Mosquito. Mosquito, mosquito.
(I got it. If it whirs, it's a mosquito.)
- That's wrong. - Mosquito repellent.
Mosquito?
(He only thinks of mosquitoes since he's teased for his high voice.)
- You only think about mosquitoes. - Mosquito? Mosquito?
It's your best friend.
- You stay with this the longest. - It's Jong Kook's best friend.
- It's your best friend. - Every day.
I see. The blender.
(He finally answers it right.)
(We barely managed.)
You don't have much time.
(Jong Kook and Seol Hyun answer only 1 question right.)
The first mission was Cosmic Charm Bboom Bboom Every Day Heart Attack.
Ji Hyo and Seung Yoon win.
(They win the 2nd round where 20 points were at stake.)
- We turned the table around. - That's true.
- That's amazing. - They had 10 and 20 points.
One of them is about the vaccinated human.
And the other one is about the contagious zombie.
(They get hints about the vaccinated human and the contagious zombies.)
- Both of them... - I see.
(What are the hints they received?)
(Contagious zombies are a pair of mixed genders.)
But we will get to narrow them down a lot.
The 2 of you can choose 1 couple.
You can switch with them.
- Switch, so we know who they are. - Is that so?
(Let's switch.)
- To find out if they're zombies. - They might suspect each other.
- We don't know about each other. - But this is...
- Switch with whom you suspect. - You must switch.
We should put the zombies together. We must pair them up together.
Zombies must be paired up for the humans to be safe.
Why are you being aggressive?
(Kwang Soo. Why are you being aggressive?)
Me?
- Was I being aggressive? - Are you not? What's going on?
Well, if he asks you that, doesn't it mean it's true?
That's right. That's right.
(My gosh... I can't get a word in, can I?)
- The vaccinated human is a man. - Right.
The vaccinated human is a man. Listen.
There are two teams of zombies.
It means each zombie is paired up.
We have to split one of the teams.
(We must split one of the zombie couples.)
(Actually, these two are...)
(This morning before the opening segment)
Kang Seung Yoon is a human.
Okay.
Song Ji Hyo is a human.
Is that so?
(Both of them are human.)
We have to split one of the teams.
The vaccinated human might be either Seok Jin or Se Chan.
(Since the vaccinated human is male, it could be one of them.)
- Do you think so? - Wouldn't it be?
(Let's switch with them.)
Okay.
- The number might change afterward. - That's right.
- No. First of all... - It's hard even with the hints.
- Okay. Have you decided? - We'll...
- switch with Seok Jin and Se Chan. - What?
- Really? - Seriously?
(Why are they switching with them?)
- Why? - Seriously?
Which one of you will pair up with Ji Hyo?
I'll pair up with Seok Jin.
(Ji Hyo will pair up with Seok Jin.)
- Then Se Chan will... - I'll be with Seung Yoon?
(Se Chan and Seung Yoon are a couple.)
- I don't think it's right. - Yes.
You two look alike.
- No. - You thought I wasn't a zombie.
- No, no. It's not that. - Hold on a second.
Does this switch bring any changes?
All right. As of now, there are...
(If the number of zombies increases...)
Were there originally four?
I think there are four.
(It means Seok Jin and Se Chan are zombies.)
- There are four zombies. - I knew it.
(There are still 4 zombies.)
- It remains the same. - To be honest,
even if Se Chan is a zombie, doesn't the number stay four?
- All four of you may be human. - Right.
- That's most likely. - That's most likely as of now.
- Right. - It's most likely that we're human.
Right, all four of them are human.
(Candidates for contagious zombies)
(They're exempted from being candidates.)
(Ji Hyo, Seung Yoon, Seok Jin, and Se Chan)
You'll divide into two teams and go eat.
- Okay, let's get it. - Let's get it.
(Will they identify the contagious zombies?)
We'll probably eat.
Why did Ji Hyo pick us?
(They head to a seafood restaurant.)
I'm suspicious of Jong Kook's couple.
- My team? - Yes.
- I think they're zombies. - Is it either me or her?
- Both of you. - Both of us?
- You guys were also annoying. - Right.
- What do you mean? - Jong Kook is too excited.
In old movies...
about contagious zombies and Dracula,
it's always the beautiful woman.
Men are bewitched by her.
- It could be Seol Hyun. - Doesn't she seem like it?
- They don't give me that role. - Really?
Most spies make that comment.
"They don't give me that role," "I get caught."
They don't ever give him such a role.
They don't, but he always pretends to be it.
- I'm too obvious. - Right.
- He's always misunderstood. - People think it's me.
I prefer to turn into a zombie if Seol Hyun is a contagious zombie.
Zombie?
(His heart flutters.)
I get the impression that she's the vaccinated human.
- Right. - I bet she'll cure others.
(She looks like someone with vaccinations.)
I've noticed for a long time that Seol Hyun never denies anything.
She never denies any compliments.
- She's honest. - She knows how to enjoy them.
She accepts compliments.
She'll say no if we called her a zombie.
By the way,
you're pretending to be cute today.
- Me? - Is it because of Min Ho?
- You aren't usually like this. - She's not being extreme.
So Min isn't usually like this.
So Min definitely reacts when you tease her.
- I'm happy. - That's good.
She's being feminine.
- Why are you looking outside? - She opens and closes the window.
She opens and closes the curtain.
Have you ever been shy, Ji Hyo?
- No. - I see.
- No guest made your heart flutter? - No.
- Did you want to impress any? - No.
- Did you like anyone? - Not at all.
(Not at all.)
There have been 401 episodes so far.
(They've had 401 episodes.)
She's never had a guest whom she liked.
(Ji Hyo never had a crush during the last 8 years.)
(The bus keeps moving.)
- Here we are. - It looks delicious.
It looks delicious.
What's the mission? Will someone not get to eat?
- Of course. - We have to eat.
This mission...
is a group mission. You can win hints and food.
- It's called Huge Drawing. - Drawing is good.
(Huge Drawing)
Determine the order of your seating.
(Sit in a single file.)
The first member reads the given word...
and draws it within five seconds.
The next member copies the drawing in a relay.
If the final member guesses the correct word, you win.
- It sounds good. - It's a team play.
A contagious zombie will try to disturb the group.
If you answer 1 out of 3, you win a hint about the contagious zombies.
The whole group will get to win.
- Let's do it. - Let's go.
It won't be difficult.
- It's a group mission. - Five seconds is short.
- What? - You seem suspicious.
If you make a mistake, you'll be suspected.
If you get it wrong, you're a contagious zombie.
- Seriously. - We won't even need the hint.
In the case of failing, one couple will change partners.
(One couple will change partners if they fail.)
You'll get only half of a meal.
That won't work.
I'm hungry.
(Will they clear the group mission?)
Here's the first question. Only you get to read it.
It's an occupation.
(It's a news anchor.)
Min Ho, this is a group mission.
If you get it wrong, you're a contagious zombie.
- Get ready. - Isn't it okay?
(If you make a wrong drawing, you'll be suspected.)
- We have to win. - One.
- 2, 3, - You have to make it, Min Ho.
- Draw well, or you're suspected. - 4, 5.
(He draws a news anchor and the news.)
- Is it easy this time? - 4, 5.
- Okay. - Is it easy?
- Go. - What is this?
- What did you draw? - I did my best.
- What is this? - Two.
- 5 seconds is short. - 3.
- 1, 2. - What's this?
3, 4, 5. Time's up.
(It's different from the original.)
Five. Time's up.
Wait.
- This is not right. - Get ready.
- Jong Kook is suspicious. - Gosh.
- He's suspicious. - Seriously.
- Two. - This is what I think.
- He should change seats. - 3, 4.
- That's it. - Five.
(This is how a news anchor changed.)
- 4, 5. - That's it.
I'll do it.
(She shows her drawing.)
- I can't believe it. - What's this?
2, 3,
- We have to draw in 5 seconds. - 4, 5.
(What did he draw inside a rectangle?)
Gosh, what's this?
- One. - What is that?
(The last person to draw is Ji Hyo.)
2, 3.
(What kind of drawing is it?)
- She'll guess something strange. - Five.
- No. - Take off the eye patch.
- He drew it like that. - I know that I did.
Min Ho drew it like that.
(A news anchor is projected in a special way.)
(Will So Min guess that it's a news anchor?)
1, 2, 3.
An architect?
(Architect is wrong.)
- What is this? Lift up the boards. - What is it?
What is it?
(What did Min Ho draw?)
- What do you think? - A news anchor?
(So Min guesses it as soon as she sees it.)
- How is that a news anchor? - I recognize it from the drawing.
(I recognize the answer from his drawing.)
This is where it went wrong.
- What? - I drew well.
- What did you draw? - I made the same drawing.
What's that?
- What's that? - How would I've guessed?
Look, this is offensive.
Look at Seol Hyun's drawing.
- Look at mine. - I drew the exact same thing.
- This is obviously a news anchor. - Wait a minute.
- Here's what I think. - This is...
- Jong Kook is suspicious. - That's way off.
(That's way off.)
- Give it to me. - He's suspicious.
- What's this? - Give it to me.
- What's this drawing? - Give it back.
Isn't Jong Kook strange?
It's strange that he drew that.
- It's obviously a news anchor. - Really?
- This is all I saw. - Goodness.
- I'll change seats with Jong Kook. - I'll go first.
- With Jong Kook? - I'll go first.
- This is easy. I'll help us win. - He's suspicious.
- He's being very strange. - Decide after this round.
- He's obviously suspicious. - You smell like a zombie.
Next category is sports.
Look carefully. Here we go.
Start.
1, 2,
3, 4, 5.
(Jong Kook draws without hesitation.)
(What did he draw?)
Here you go.
(The keyword is related to sports.)
1, 2,
- Do you know what it is? - 3, 4, 5. Stop.
(He drew something similar.)
Five. Stop.
- All right. 1, 2, - What is it?
- 3, 4, 5. - It's a sport.
(What kind of sport is it?)
- What is it? I see. - 1, 2.
3, 4, 5. Stop.
(The drawing changed a lot.)
Five. Stop.
- 1, 2, 3, - What is that?
- 4, 5. - Draw well.
(She laughs at her own drawing.)
(What kind of sport is it?)
I'm going to look.
What is that? Is it a squid?
Don't you think it's a jumping board?
- Goodness, is this a sport? - Yes.
What kind of sport has a triangle?
- A triangle? - What kind of sport is it?
What's the answer?
(It has a drawing of a person...)
(and a triangular sign.)
- One. - Is it a sport?
(What was the given word?)
- Yes. - UFC.
(UFC is wrong.)
Isn't a person tangled in something?
Can't you tell from my drawing?
- Is it billiards? - What do you think it is?
- That? - What's that?
(Look at it carefully.)
- That? - Yes.
- Curling? - It's curling.
(That's right.)
(The answer was curling.)
It's curling.
- How is that curling? - It's the Olympics symbol.
- These are the Olympics rings. - It's a Buddhist lamp ceremony.
(Isn't it a lamp ceremony?)
It's a Buddhist lamp ceremony.
(He only sees a lamp.)
I thought it was billiards from Seol Hyun's drawing.
- I thought it was billiards. - This was the last drawing.
How did it change that way?
That's why I drew billiard balls.
(From curling to billiards)
I wondered if I should draw this or not.
- I wondered... - Jong Kook is suspicious.
(Jong Kook is suspicious.)
I know your drawing skills, Jong Kook.
- We know your drawing skills. - How could he draw like that?
I did my best.
- No way. - Seriously.
- You should've focused on the hand. - Exactly.
(They get two questions wrong in a row.)
I have to eat it.
I might not be able to let you win, but I'll let you eat.
- Please. - All right.
- Everyone is sensitive right now. - Whoever the zombies are,
- don't fail on purpose here. - No.
We have to eat.
To win hints and lunch,
you'll play four kinds of games.
(4 Random Games)
- What's that? - What's that?
(4 Random Games?)
Each couple will play 1 of the 4 games.
To accomplish the mission, every team has to succeed.
(They have to succeed within 3 tries.)
That sounds hard.
If you fail on purpose, it'll show.
I know some of you are zombies,
- but let's eat first. - Seriously.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's start from Haha.
- Let's get it. - Haha will start.
Lee Kwang Soo Game.
(They have to say a different syllable than the producer.)
Seafood. "Sea" or "food".
- Food. - Food.
(Seafood)
(Food)
Gosh.
(The first try fails.)
That's it? It's over?
I shouldn't have gotten in the same car as him.
Gosh. I want to eat.
- Let's start from Se Chan. - What are you doing?
You obviously should've said, "sea".
(Isn't it obvious?)
- I wasn't even considering "food". - It's definitely "sea".
- And it's "pus", not "octo". - Hey, zombie.
This is unfair.
- Let's start from Se Chan. - What are you doing?
- This is unfair. - Let's start from Se Chan.
Say it backwards. "South Africa".
Caraf...
(Fail)
Let's just give up. We have two zombies here.
- Let's just give up. - We have two zombies.
There's no way we can eat.
- Can you say it backwards? - Of course.
- "Acirfa Htuos". - Hold on.
Those at the ends are just too bad.
- Can we... - What?
We're bad? Do you want to switch?
- Jae Seok, do you want to switch? - Guys.
- Be confident. - Let's do it in a random order.
My goodness.
Please start from Jae Seok.
All right. Watch us.
- What if I make a mistake? - Let's start.
Okay.
- Song Ji Hyo Game. - Game.
(They have to form a 3-syllable word.)
- Bir. - Th.
(Rate)
Desire.
- He said, "rate". - I meant "rate".
- You said, "birth desire". - No.
- You have a birth desire? - A birth desire?
- You have a desire to give birth? - "Birth desire"?
- I... - It's a desire to give birth?
I messed up. Let me confess.
She said, "rate", and I heard it wrong.
- I'm sorry. She said... - You failed.
It doesn't make sense.
(They fail to win hints.)
Get ready. This time, it's an occupation.
- I'm in trouble. It'll be hard. - Ready.
- Start. - Simplify it as much as you can.
- Simplify it. - 1, 2,
3, 4, 5. Stop.
That was hard. We're in trouble.
(Teacher, blackboard, students)
1, 2,
3, 4, 5.
(Teacher, blackboard, curvy line?)
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3,
- 4, 5. - No one is complaining.
(What's that curvy line?)
(Okay)
1, 2, 3,
4, 5. Stop.
(A square, a person, and a curvy line?)
One...
- Okay. - You got it, right?
(It's less and less like a teacher.)
- 3, 4, - Why do you think I'll fail?
Five. Stop.
- Are you done? - This one...
- Seriously... - He has to get it right.
- If he gets it wrong... - I'll get it perfectly right.
It's a kind of sports, right?
(What do you take me for?)
- No. It's an occupation. - What?
- What is this? - It's an occupation?
- That sounds forced. - He's pretending.
- I can't help but suspect him. - It's an occupation?
- You have to give an answer. - I'm wrong?
- One... - Hold on. Sir.
- Okay. - Sir.
Look at this drawing.
(So Min is the only person who knows the answer.)
Hold on.
(Say it.)
- What did you just say? - Think of an occupation.
- What's the answer? - Hold on.
The drawing...
- Jong Kook. - Hold on.
Sir. Hold on.
- Jong Kook. - Give me a second.
- It's an occupation? - Yes.
- It's "teacher". - It's an occupation?
- 1, 2, 3. - "Teacher".
Teacher.
- Okay. - It was right.
(Jong Kook answers, "teacher" in the end.)
- I was right. It's a blackboard. - It's a blackboard.
I was so sure it was "rhythmic gymnastics".
How can this be...
(It looks like rhythmic gymnastics.)
- Min Ho, you're suspicious. - Min Ho...
- Hold on. - I just copied the drawing...
as best as I could.
(It all went downhill from Min Ho.)
- Min Ho is usually good at drawing. - Doesn't it look the same?
This time, he had enough time...
to analyze the drawing.
- Something's fishy. - Min Ho is suspicious.
I just copied Min Ho's drawing.
(The curvy line haunted Seol Hyun too.)
Isn't this a gymnastic ribbon?
- She didn't do anything wrong. - Look.
(I'll protect you, Seol Hyun.)
She's innocent.
- I did my best... - Seol Hyun, am I wrong?
- You're right. - Right?
- I did my best. - Seol Hyun trusts me.
- You were taking time on purpose. - Seriously.
- Seol Hyun trusts me. - Jong Kook looks stiff.
I said, "teacher" in the end.
Wasn't that to avoid suspicion?
- No. Look. - I'm right, right?
(Is one of them a contagious zombie?)
(What is the other team doing?)
Let's forget about zombies for now.
- Please let two teams eat. - Let half of us eat.
- Okay. - We failed anyway.
We should let two teams eat even if we all fail.
Let's start. You have to succeed three times in a row.
- Who wants to start? - Hye Jeong.
It's too hard.
Song Ji Hyo Game. Go.
- To. - Guy.
- Dried. - Shredded.
- Squid. - Wedding.
- How many times are we doing this? - It's over.
Fail.
(The producer says the next word.)
(Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong fail.)
We told you it's three times.
- After two... - Fail.
- You should have focused. - You'll starve.
- You'll starve. - Why did you do that?
- I'm sorry. - Are you...
- Are you a zombie? - You'll all starve.
- Okay, okay. - I thought it was only two tries.
- She thought they were done. - I thought there were only two.
"Winner". "Win" or "ner". 1, 2, 3.
- Ner. - Ner.
- Kazakhstan. - Tan...
- Indonesia. - Asineido.
Sit down. Get out, you all!
- Get out, you zombies. - It's a mess.
Let us just draw lots.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Let's just play rock-paper-scissors.
Tell me how we can let you eat.
- We'll try Giant Chestnut Bread. - We'll try Giant Chestnut Bread.
- The winners can eat. - Yes. Giant Chestnut Bread.
It's set then. Two winning teams will eat.
Da Young, try it.
- I'll let you eat. - Focus.
Giant Chestnut Bread Game. Say, "shark's fin" five times.
Shark's fin, shark's fin, shark's fin, shark's fin, shark's fin.
(Success)
Say, "thistle" five times.
- Thistle, thistle, thistle... - Okay!
- Okay. - Say, "refund" five times.
Refund, refund, refund...
(She slurs the word.)
(Fail)
Can I try it personally...
regardless of my team?
Let's just stop.
Refund, refund, refund...
Refund...
(Spitting)
- He's a zombie. I caught him. - He's a zombie.
- I'm not a zombie. - You punk...
- Eat charcoal. - Why?
- Zombies don't eat charcoal. - I'm not a zombie.
- One team has been eliminated. - Okay.
(Jae Seok and Joo E are left.)
Giant Chestnut Bread Game. Say this word five times.
"Sticky rice in red bean porridge".
(Sticky rice in red bean porridge)
- Start. - Sticky rice...
(Slurring)
Sticky rice...
(Fail)
That was hilarious.
- "Sticky rice..." - "Sticky rice..."
Sticky rice in red bean porridge... Gosh.
These two teams can eat.
We can eat.
But you won't get any hints. Also, since you've failed,
your partners will be changed. You can eat before that.
- Zombies don't get to eat. - Zombies...
(Let's eat first.)
That looks so tasty.
- The mushrooms smell so good. - It has neungi mushrooms in it.
(Boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms)
The broth tastes so good.
It's boiling. Let me give you some.
That looks so good.
(That looks so tasty.)
(Thirsty)
I want some rice and soup.
It looks delicious.
I'm glad I chose this one.
(Live abalone and octopus)
- It's abalone. - I want some too.
It's delicious.
(It's so chewy.)
- I prefer octopus to chicken. - So do I.
Here is a hint about the contagious zombies.
- It has to be shared. - What if Jong Kook isn't a zombie?
I'm not. You know that.
A hint about the zombies? Let me see.
I'll pass it around.
"The contagious zombies..."
"are over 165cm tall."
That excludes Joo E and Da Young.
(The contagious zombies are over 165cm tall.)
(Joo E and Da Young are excluded.)
We have to switch the couples now.
Decide how you'll switch them.
I'm a little bit suspicious of Kwang Soo.
If you're innocent, you should be able to switch.
He could have done it earlier, but he didn't.
- We have to check him. - How?
We just need to check you.
If you're suspicious of me, you can switch.
- Let's switch him. - Okay.
- What do you think, Seung Yoon? - I think we should try it.
- That's how we'll know. - We can split.
- We have the hint too. - You have to find out.
Then Seung Yoon will be...
- With Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo's partner.
(Se Chan and Seung Yoon switch with Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong.)
Hye Jeong will partner up with Se Chan.
- Yes. - Se Chan.
I'll tell you how many zombies there are.
- You switched, right? - Yes.
As of now, there are...
(Humans Se Chan and Seung Yoon switched with a suspicious couple.)
(How did the number of zombies change?)
As of now, there are...
(Humans Se Chan and Seung Yoon switched with a suspicious couple.)
(How did the number of zombies change?)
There are...
- six zombies. - What?
(There are 6 zombies.)
Wait. What?
- Who switched? - It increased, right?
There's one more zombie.
(Kwang Soo and Hye Jeong had to be a zombie couple.)
- It's everybody but us. - This team...
You switched, and you got infected, right?
What is certain is that us four are zombies.
We're zombies.
(Hold on.)
I didn't know.
(He turns serious.)
You're a crook.
(I didn't think of you that way.)
(Kwang Soo is a zombie now.)
(What is he saying?)
What do you mean?
Kwang Soo, it looks like you were tricked.
Can I have a bottle of soju, please?
(One of them has to be a contagious zombie.)
I didn't do anything.
(Which one of them is it?)
(Strongest candidates for the contagious zombies)
(They arrive at a water park where the last race will be held.)
- What do I do? - It's okay.
(There are many scary rides here. What kind of race will it be?)
The last round of Zombie Couple Race...
is Zombie Run.
(The last round is Zombie Run.)
- Zombie Run. - Zombie Run?
You have 30 minutes to go on the water rides...
and earn hints about the contagious zombies or the vaccinated human.
We have to go on them?
The more extreme the ride is, the better the hints are.
(There are different levels of hints according to the rides.)
(They must go on the extreme rides to get both hints at the same time.)
(If they go for speedy rides, they only get one hint.)
We have to go on the rides.
(We have to ride them to earn the hints.)
I can't do this. I can't go on the scary ones.
If you're a zombie, once you're instructed by a contagious zombie,
a mark will appear on your body.
Until you become a human again, you must walk and act...
like a zombie and obey their orders.
- You have to act like a zombie? - What?
- What is this? - Once you are told to do so.
We have to act like zombies?
(You have to be their avatar and act like a zombie?)
- You have to act? - Yes.
You have to do this all of a sudden?
Like "Train to Busan".
(They need to mimic "Train to Busan".)
Contagious zombies or vaccinated human should be eliminated.
If they're not out in 30 minutes, there will be a trial.
There will be a trial?
There are so many zombies on our side.
Seung Yoon, I,
- Hye Jeong, and Se Chan... - Hye Jeong, and Se Chan.
- are zombies. - We're zombies.
- How do you know? - We confessed.
- There is a contagious zombie here. - There's a big possibility.
- There's a contagious zombie there. - There is.
Can I share the hint I got earlier?
- You can. - Is it up to me?
- You can share it with the zombies. - It doesn't matter.
There are two contagious zombies, right?
It's a male and a female.
- 1 each. - 1 male and 1 female?
- There's one each. - 1 male and 1 female.
You'll move to your designated spots.
- Where are we going? - Designated spots?
(The couples split and move to their designated spots.)
What is this?
(There are weird pictures.)
(Is there a hidden rule?)
What is this?
(Is has full-body characters of everybody.)
(Full-body characters for a zombie race?)
Min Ho looks like a zombie here.
(Min Ho looks like a zombie here.)
(Do you think I'm a contagious zombie?)
(There's something hidden here. What is this board about?)
One. Race starts.
(Zombie Run starts.)
- We have to go on the extreme ones. - Let's do it.
- We should. - Of course.
- What is this? - It's a blob jump.
When you jump on it, you get launched.
- Do you fall into the water? - Yes.
(They decide to try it without hesitating.)
1, 2, 3.
Be careful. Good job.
(Seol Hyun jumps without hesitating.)
- Keep crawling. - She's good.
- You have to sit facing the front. - Face the front.
- Be careful, Seol Hyun. - Okay.
- Do I go? - Two,
one. Jump.
(Rocket Seol Hyun is ready to launch for high-level hints.)
(Flying)
(Seol Hyun is launched.)
(Jong Kook and the lifeguard's weight makes Seol Hyun fly.)
She flew so high.
(Do you really go that high?)
Are you all right?
(This is totally my style.)
How was it, Seol Hyun?
It was fine.
(They get hints about the contagious zombies and vaccinated human.)
All right.
Contagious Zombie B is...
Okay. It's B?
Contagious Zombie B is a female.
(Contagious Zombie B is a female.)
(That makes Contagious Zombie A male.)
The vaccinated human has no brothers.
(Jae Seok, Haha, Min Ho)
(Kwang Soo and Seung Yoon are by the water slide.)
I'll do it for you.
- Do we go up separately? - Yes.
Can't we hold hands?
I thought we were sliding down while holding hands.
- We can't hold hands. - Of course.
(Sighing)
Can you let us hold hands? Can't we do that?
You'll get started at the same time.
- Okay. - Let go. I'll hold onto you.
Slowly.
(Are you ready for a high drop?)
We have to do this.
(He makes a face.)
We're ready.
- Three. - Cross your legs.
(Go!)
(They drop straight down...)
(and jump at the end.)
(He's done this many times before and pinches his nose.)
(Why did I...)
(open my eyes?)
(Screaming)
(He's shocked by the unexpected jump.)
(What am I doing for hints?)
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo and Seung Yoon earn both hints.)
They just threw us in the water.
- It was so sudden. - Kwang Soo.
Contagious Zombie B was...
born in a year that's an odd number.
(So Min was born in 1986.)
(Hye Jeong was born in 1993. Seol Hyun was born in 1995.)
It's an even number, right?
Here's the hint about the vaccinated human.
The vaccinated human has a younger sister.
(Jae Seok and Min Ho are the only candidates.)
- This is so... - Can we...
- not switch teams? - No, you can't.
What are you talking about? What is the problem?
- I want more hints. - What's wrong?
Let's go. I'll do it.
- Really? - Yes, let's go. What do you want?
- Next. - I'll do it.
(Haha and Da Young, Jae Seok and Joo E, )
(and Seok Jin and Ji Hyo are on the Flying Fish.)
(This is a low-level ride, so it should be okay, right?)
- Hold on tightly when turning. - We need a high-level hint.
No, stop.
(Start)
(The angry fish advances at a scary speed.)
(Their faces get distorted like the angry fish.)
(Quick...)
(turn)
(Screaming)
(How is this a low-level ride?)
It hurts. I'm in pain.
- Stop it! - No.
We're going to bump into something.
(They cruise at full-speed...)
(toward the dock and stop right in front of it.)
(Oh, dear.)
(Goodness)
- The driver got soaked. - He got soaked.
(The driver just took a shower.)
This was scary.
The breaking part was awesome.
That was awesome.
(Where's my sanity?)
How was this low-level?
(They get a hint about the contagious zombies.)
- You can write it down or remember. - We'll remember.
Contagious Zombie A...
does not have brothers.
(Contagious Zombie A does not have brothers.)
(Kwang Soo, Min Ho, Jae Seok)
(Contagious Zombie A Candidates: Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, Min Ho)
(Contagious Zombie B Candidates: Seol Hyun, Hye Jeong)
(Vaccinated Human Candidates: Jae Seok, Min Ho)
- Start. - Let's go.
(Hye Jeong and Se Chan must finish the obstacle course in 1 minute.)
I did it. Hurry.
- What do I do? - Hurry, Hye Jeong.
Go. Pass by.
Keep going, Hye Jeong.
(She performs slapstick comedy.)
Keep going.
Go, Hye Jeong.
Hurry, Hye Jeong. Come.
(What's going on?)
(She's an antagonist in a drama who goes down.)
It's cold. The water is so cold.
Go up.
- I'll help you. - I can't climb up.
(Let's just refuse the hint and get away from here.)
(They make everybody laugh and fail.)
We can't do this in one minute. Come here.
I'll help you.
- Give us a hint. - It's about the vaccinated human.
The vaccinated human is the eldest child.
- Vaccinated human is the eldest? - Yes.
We have two hints about Contagious Zombie A.
- Overlapping ones. - We have to pick those out.
- Jae Seok. - I think...
(Here's Zombie Kwang Soo.)
It was like this.
Kwang Soo.
You scared me.
(Why did Zombie Kwang Soo remove Seok Jin's name tag?)
You scared me!
You scared me.
(You scared me.)
I guess you were instructed to do this.
- Someone ordered you. - Really?
(Was he given an order to rip Seok Jin's name tag?)
Kwang Soo and Seung Yoon,
you have been infected.
(They must follow the commands of the contagious zombie.)
- We're infected. - You have been commanded...
by the contagious zombie that infected you.
(They must follow the commands of the contagious zombie.)
Rip Seok Jin's name tag, and turn him into a zombie.
(They are avatars and have to rip Seok Jin's name tag.)
(I'm a zombie.)
(They're zombies, but they're a bit excessive.)
(I did it, Mr. Contagious Zombie.)
You were ordered.
- You were ordered. - Really?
- We had to infect you. - Seok Jin and Ji Hyo...
- are zombies now. - Why?
- He wasn't a zombie. - Because I got my name tag ripped?
Oh, gosh. What's wrong with you?
- I had to do as instructed. - They have been infected too.
(Who is the contagious zombie then?)
(Either Hye Jeong or Kwang Soo was a contagious zombie.)
(Who is the contagious zombie that infected Kwang Soo?)
(Contagious Zombie B is Hye Jeong.)
Today, we'll have a Zombie Couple Race.
You're contagious zombies who can infect humans.
(She heard about her identity alongside Contagious Zombie A.)
(In order to prevent others from getting hints, she had to act.)
(She threw her body around and fulfilled her job too.)
(She was also a great entertainer.)
- What's this? - What's this? Hold on.
What's this?
- What's this? Haha. - What's this?
(Infected zombies, rip Seok Jin's name tag.)
(She infected Kwang Soo, so she made him rip Seok Jin's name tag.)
You scared me. I guess you got instructed to do this.
- You were ordered. - Really?
Hold on.
(I'll infect all human beings in this world.)
- Here are the current numbers. - Okay.
There are eight zombies so far.
- What? - What? No way!
- How many of us are there? - Where is the vaccine?
There are 14 of you. There are 8 zombies.
- 8? - There are 8 zombies?
(If 4 more people get infected, contagious zombies win.)
Eight?
Seok Jin and Ji Hyo got infected too.
- All of a sudden, right? - Yes.
- Were they not zombies before? - They weren't.
- Were they not zombies? - No.
- How did this happen? - Look at this.
He's the eldest child and has no brothers.
The male is...
(Contagious Zombie A has no brothers...)
(and is the eldest child.)
(It's either Jae Seok or Min Ho.)
(Is Jae Seok, who lingered around the board, Contagious Zombie A?)
- What is this? - What's this?
(Or is it Min Ho, who also wandered around the board?)
It's not on the poster.
(Who is Contagious Zombie A?)
(I only did as instructed.)
- All right. - He's the male one.
- I know. - Seok Jin and Ji Hyo...
- have been given orders. - To do what?
(What did the contagious zombie command them to do?)
- Rip Jong Kook's name tag. - What?
- What? - Rip Jong Kook's name tag.
(Rip Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Sniffing)
(He listens right away.)
He was okay until a minute ago.
He has to rip his name tag?
They have to rip my name tag? Those two?
- Really? - Yes.
Like that?
How could you reveal the order when he was right there?
How could you do that to us?
- I can't rip his name tag normally. - It's hard to rip it to begin with.
It's already so hard to rip it.
Can I do anything?
- Do I just keep running away? - Kim Jong Kook.
Can I throw him in the water?
- Is that okay? - Kim Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook. - Come.
I can throw him in here, right?
- Kim Jong Kook. - Hold on.
I don't want to go in the water.
I'm leaving.
- I won't rip his name tag. - Jong Kook.
- I have a microphone on me. - I don't want to go in the water.
- Take his microphone off. - My microphone.
I'm going to throw him in the water. I'll soak him for a bit.
My microphone.
- Take it off. - Ji Hyo.
Watch the corners.
My micro... Where? Where? Here?
(Splatting)
(Zombie Seok Jin gets flung pitifully.)
(Mr. Contagious Zombie, he's too strong.)
Zombie, what about the command?
- Zombie... - Three minutes before trial.
- Three minutes? - Yes.
I don't know. This is confusing.
(Seok Jin failed, so there are still 8 zombies.)
You were infected,
but you have become human beings with the vaccinated human's help.
(You have become human beings with the vaccinated human's help.)
(When one zombie is treated, the couple becomes human.)
- I... - Listen.
I will relieve your burden.
- We're serious. - The two of us...
just became human beings.
- Really? - Yes.
- We got the vaccine. - You're an inhumane person.
I'm human.
- Were you a zombie? - We were.
We were both infected.
- Really? - You were infected?
- Does that mean... - Really?
Stop it. Stop doing that to Hye Jeong.
- Stop it. - Hye Jeong.
(That contagious zombie used me.)
It was true.
It's not me.
Race is over. Let's start the final trial.
The contagious zombies didn't get eliminated in time,
so we're having a trial.
I'm so mad.
You can discuss freely based on the hints you have.
Figure out who the contagious zombies are,
and pick three couples to go on the platforms.
- Three couples? - Okay.
If the contagious zombies are included, Team Humans wins.
Even if the contagious zombies are included,
if a vaccinated human is also on the platform, the zombies win.
That's right.
(If they pick the vaccinated human too, the contagious zombies win.)
Let's figure out who the vaccinated human is first.
Can't they just say it?
Can't they just say that they're the vaccinated human?
- Say it. - All right.
- Say it. - I am the vaccinated human.
(I am the vaccinated human.)
(When Jae Seok confesses that he is the vaccinated human...)
- I am the vaccinated human. - It's me.
(Three more people raise their hands.)
- This is driving me crazy. - I really am the vaccinated human.
- Stop it. - I'm serious. Look at the hints.
- Think about the hints. - I really am the vaccinated human.
Stop it already.
- Think about the hints. - Stop it.
I am the vaccinated human.
- The vaccinated human? - Yes.
- It's me. - Don't be absurd. It's me.
I am the vaccinated human.
Come on. You are a zombie!
Which hints have you received?
The vaccinated human has a sister.
I have a sister named Song Da Na who is a year younger than me.
(He reveals her real name.)
My younger sister's name is Lee Bo Ram.
(He reveals her real name as well.)
- I am the eldest child. - I am the eldest child as well.
I have a hidden sister. I have never talked about her on TV.
(She suddenly makes a confession.)
- My father has... - Be quiet!
I was being serious. Be quiet.
I am telling you the truth.
So Min, the vaccinated human is a man.
Actually, I am...
(She suddenly makes a 2nd confession.)
- What? - The vaccinated human...
What are you doing?
(Min Ho is shocked.)
I am a man. I am a man.
- She is completely crazy. - She is...
- That's our show's psycho. - She is really crazy.
- She is incredible. - She is completely crazy.
- She is incredible. - Right? Isn't she unbelievable?
One thing is certain. I told you that there are...
male and female contagious zombies. The female one is Hye Jeong.
- That's right. - I am certain of it.
Hye Jeong is a wretch.
- That couple should go up. - That's right.
- That couple has to go up. - Right.
Jae Seok and Min Ho...
could either be the vaccinated human or a contagious zombie,
- so we can't choose both of them. - That would be a disaster.
We can't choose both of them. We have to determine what they are.
How about this? Take turns, and convince us...
why you are the vaccinated human.
I wasn't sure about the rules. I am not good at complicated games.
The heavy burden of being the vaccinated human kept me...
- from revealing my identity. - He is honest.
- That was against the rules. - I mean,
I couldn't participate actively. I was under a lot of pressure.
(Min Ho explains.)
I treated Kwang Soo. I did it in the middle of the game.
I thought only one member would become human.
How do you treat a zombie?
This is how you do it. As you saw earlier...
- Don't say it first. - Don't say it.
- You shouldn't say it. - How do you treat a zombie?
- Say it at the same time. - Say it at the same time.
- Shall we say it at the same time? - Say it at the same time.
- Shall we do that? - 1, 2, 3.
(They are both confident, but do they know the answer?)
- Touch. - The character board.
That's right. You touch the character board.
(Touch versus the character board)
You touch the character board.
(This is how the vaccinated human treated a zombie.)
You need to touch the character board.
- That treats a zombie? - Yes.
- The contagious zombies might know. - How?
Do contagious zombies know about touching the character board?
- No, they don't. - I don't know what they know.
How does a contagious zombie infected a human?
- I don't know that. - It must be by touch.
It must be by touch as well!
- It must be by touch as well! - I can't believe you.
(They point fingers at each other.)
- That's how you infect people. - What are you talking about?
Min Ho, did you turn Kwang Soo into a human?
I touched Kwang Soo and made him human again.
However, I didn't know...
Seung Yoon would also become human.
I only treated Kwang Soo.
(Min Ho stands up for himself.)
(He doesn't understand why Seung Yoon became human.)
- That's right. Hold on. - I don't understand.
- I don't know what happened either. - Hold on.
- Why did I become human? - This is what I know.
After I became human, Min Ho came to me and said that...
he made me human.
Jae Seok said until the end,
"You zombie!"
You should know that. It's a fact.
He said it as we came up the stairs when there were no cameras.
- He grabbed my collar and said, - I can explain.
- "You dirty zombie!" - I can explain why I said that.
I didn't treat Kwang Soo.
(It's a big plot twist.)
(Jae Seok confesses that he didn't treat Kwang Soo.)
(It's the complete opposite of Min Ho's claim.)
- Whom did you treat? - I treated Seung Yoon.
(He says he treated Seung Yoon.)
- Are there 2 vaccinated humans? - No, there is only 1.
Gosh, you are really smart.
I am not lying. That's why...
I called Kwang Soo a zombie. I don't know how...
Kwang Soo became human.
Their stories are essentially the same.
(Only the people they treated are different.)
I think it's hilarious how Hye Jeong is staying still...
despite this heated debate.
(Everyone knows she is the female contagious zombie.)
- She acknowledged it. - "Yes, I am a contagious zombie."
She won't even make excuses. She accepted her fate.
I asked Hye Jeong, "Shouldn't you defend yourself?"
She said, "They won't listen."
We are done. We will go up the platform.
I was Hye Jeong's partner. I asked her,
"How could you do this to me?"
She pretended not to hear me. She completely ignored me.
- It's time to make a decision. - Okay.
- Go up. - Hold on. Hold on.
Hye Jeong, tell them that you aren't a contagious zombie.
Go up there already! We don't have much time.
You should still hear what she has to say. Tell them.
- Let's hear it. - Please give...
"Bingle Bangle" by AOA a lot of love.
- Go up there. - I can't believe you!
She gave up. She gave up.
We just need to choose between Jae Seok and Min Ho.
Going up there isn't a problem but...
(Only one of them goes up the platform.)
- We need to choose another couple. - It can be any couple.
Min Ho shouldn't go up the platform.
No, no. It's Jae Seok.
- Go up there. - Go up there.
You never know what will happen. Go up.
- Let's go. - Zombies go up there, right?
- Aren't you the vaccinated human? - This is...
- Go up there. - Joo E.
I am the vaccinated human.
(If he is the vaccinated human, Team Humans lose.)
Jong Kook and Seol Hyun should go since they are humans for sure.
- Seol Hyun... - I am not sure about her.
- That's right. - Me?
- Seol Hyun, let's go up. - Go up.
- Let's go up. - They are humans.
It'd be incredible if there's a twist.
(Between the two of them, who is the contagious zombie?)
The name tags will be removed.
1, 2, 3.
(Contagious zombie)
(Hye Jeong is a contagious zombie.)
- That's right. - We knew it.
- I told you Seol Hyun is human. - What is this?
Don't make Hye Jeong do something like this.
(Contagious Zombie B, Hye Jeong, is apprehended.)
All right.
If Jae Seok is a contagious zombie, Team Humans wins.
- This is the most... - If he is the vaccinated human,
- Team Humans loses. - This is...
(If he is the vaccinated human, Team Humans loses.)
1, 2, 3.
(What is Jae Seok?)
(Jae Seok is a contagious zombie.)
(Team Humans wins.)
I am sorry, Joo E.
- We won! - Remove Min Ho's name tag.
- Good job. - 1, 2, 3.
(Min Ho was the vaccinated human.)
- Min Ho! - Min Ho!
Today, we will have the Zombie Couple Race.
- You are the vaccinated human. - The vaccinated human?
(Before the final race ended, )
(he treated Kwang Soo by touching the character board.)
(He kept his identity hidden and completed the mission.)
Thus, Team Humans wins.
(Team Humans wins.)
Nice!
(It's all thanks to Min Ho's work and the humans' deductions.)
- Hye Jeong. - I was given an important role,
but the rules were too complicated and hard.
When I met Hye Jeong in the morning as a fellow zombie,
I said, "Let's ignore each other." She really ignored me.
(Until the very end)
She didn't even look in my direction.
We should have met up and come up with a plan,
but she didn't even look in my direction.
- Bye. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye.
(For each other, )
(the Running Man members prepare heartfelt presents.)
(The presents give them touching and healing moments.)
- Thank you. - I love it.
(The items they were given...)
(are the only things they can use.)
(How are we supposed to live with only these items?)
(A bottle of water costs...)
(500 dollars.)
(The invisible hand makes the prices skyrocket.)
(I have fire.)
(Ownership is power.)
(How much does it cost to boil water?)
(How much can you offer?)
(The principles of market economy divide the power.)
(A small thing can bring a big amount of power.)
(Between greed and moderation, )
(the members get lost.)
(What is the cruel end of this catastrophe?)
(This high?)
(War of Money)