(Last week)
(Shuddering and Luxury Packages left for their respective countries.)
(It was decided that only 3 people would wing walk.)
(Penalty badges are given after each mission.)
(The number of the badges determines the size of the Pirate Roulette.)
(The 1st 3 people who make the pirate pop up get the penalty.)
(You must win to avoid wing walking.)
(With 8 badges, Kwang Soo has a high chance of wing walking.)
(He's the leading candidate.)
(Luxurious Switzerland)
(Do Everything You Want to Do)
(Select additional tours, and enjoy everything.)
(However, the cost of additional tours...)
(must come from the members.)
(Enjoy the luxuries...)
(and choose who will pay for the expenses.)
(After each tour, an anonymous poll is conducted.)
(If you are on a ballot, you get your name written on the roulette.)
(The member to pay for the scenic tour is...)
(Kim Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook paid 523 dollars.)
No way.
(After the first payment that was tainted with betrayals)
The observatory hotel in Switzerland...
is so popular that even the Swiss find it hard...
to visit in their lifetime.
Only two members...
(Only two members...)
will be able to stay at the hotel and have a stargazing experience.
Experience? Okay.
(The hotel is a remodeled observatory...)
(that lets its guests enjoy the festival of the stars.)
(Only two members are invited to the fantastic night.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- See you tomorrow. - Let's see what happens tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
(Haha and Se Chan are chosen.)
Bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Bye. - Enjoy stargazing.
Bye. Come again.
- Bye. - Bye.
(Don't forget about us.)
- Bye. - Come again.
If the sky clears up,
we will have an experience money can't buy.
You are right.
- That's where we will stargaze. - Over there.
The dome will open.
(When the dome that remains closed during the day opens at night,)
(you can enjoy the paintings space has created.)
Hi. It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you. Welcome.
- Hello. - Hello.
Would you ask her if the hotel has hot water?
- Would you? - Of course it has hot water.
Ask her if the hotel has hot water.
All of these mountains written on the doors are around us.
- This peak must be the highest one. - That's right.
- 4,219m. - Matterhorn is higher.
This is your room.
(The view is amazing.)
You can see Matterhorn.
(They see the Alps outside the window.)
We can take pictures here.
It will feel amazing to wake up to this kind of energy.
- How does it look? - The clouds are gone.
- It's a good day for paragliding. - This is nice.
The weather is pretty nice.
Since we don't have much time, we will explain quickly.
They will only allow three people to paraglide.
- One of you won't get to paraglide. - Okay.
Please choose who will paraglide among yourselves.
(Han Na, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo decide to paraglide.)
(Jin Young decides to sit out since she is afraid of heights.)
- Are you okay? - I am okay.
- Is your heart beating fast? - My heart is beating very fast.
Let's go.
(It's not every day you get to fly over the Alps.)
- Let's go. - Follow me.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Matterhorn, here I come!
I will see the views of Switzerland from the sky.
- Are you okay? - I am okay.
I feel scared now. What should I do?
(She feels scared now that it's time to go.)
I feel scared now.
- I feel scared. - My goodness.
(Her heart beats fast.)
Ji Hyo, how are you feeling at this moment?
Do you feel like you are on a boat?
- My lips are dry. - Do you feel motion sickness?
- Yes. I can't breathe. - You can't breathe?
I will perform a mouth-to-mouth resuscitation.
(A mouth-to-mouth resuscitation)
I can't see well. Where am I?
- Take off your sunglasses. - Should I do that?
(Take off your sunglasses.)
That must be the starting line.
(Let's get ready.)
Do I need to walk? Not now?
(Han Na is the first one to take the runway.)
Okay. Run. Go, go, go, go.
- Run? - Go, go, go.
(She overcomes her nervousness and takes off.)
(She is smiling from ear to ear.)
(My goodness.)
So beautiful!
It's so beautiful.
I now see why people put this...
on their bucket lists. It's beautiful.
We are coming closer to Matterhorn.
(Matterhorn looks like it's within reach.)
(She is happy to see Matterhorn on a clear day.)
I feel like I became a bird.
(She is like a small bird in the grand nature.)
Ji Hyo's in the air.
(Ji Hyo takes off.)
(Screaming)
Mom!
(This dutiful daughter only looks for her mom at times like this.)
(Mom, what's all this?)
Oh, my gosh.
(This out-of-the-world scenery makes her become speechless.)
(I'm on top of the world!)
(The Queen of the Alps might receive her even if she flies too closely.)
Amazing!
- Amazing. - Amazing!
I believe I can fly
I believe I can touch the sky
(This incredible scenery makes his old sentiments come out.)
(They start flying together...)
(while flying along the golden sunset of Matterhorn.)
Ji Hyo!
- Okay. - Ji Hyo!
(Hello, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
Jong Kook.
- Hello! - Hello.
I can see Zermatt under my feet.
(With the same scenery, height, and heart,)
(they finish their picnic in the sky...)
(and glide down.)
My gosh.
(That was really awesome.)
Thank you.
(Bumping)
- Thank you. - Okay.
(She smiles even after landing on her bottom.)
Can I get up?
(Getting teary-eyed)
That was amazing!
My gosh, that was utterly amazing.
(Trotting)
Han Na, how was it?
Wasn't it amazing? Wasn't it incredible?
Ji Hyo is really hyper.
(Her excitement is still evident.)
- Jong Kook, how was it? Amazing? - It was incredible.
- We flew in the sky. - We were really flying.
- Jong Kook, we really flew. - Seriously.
(With the overwhelming feeling of paragliding,)
(they head into the city center in Zermatt to their lodging.)
- Jong Kook, are you happy? - Yes?
Of course.
- You look filthy rich right now. - Me?
(You look filthy rich right now.)
Right now, you look...
- I look rich? - young, rich, tall, and handsome.
- "Young, rich, tall, and handsome"? - You do.
- No one travels with three women. - Rich?
I'm good with looking rich.
- Is it here? - Where?
Here?
(Our lodging is here.)
- "Plaza"? What's that? - My goodness.
(A 5-star, luxurious hotel in Provence style)
- Hold on. Is that a 5-star hotel? - Great. It is a 5-star hotel.
We have to eat breakfast tomorrow.
I'd like that.
We must check out the rooms.
(Humming)
(Unbelievable. I can't believe this is our room!)
- No way. - This is a room?
- Oh, my gosh. - There's a song.
This is amazing.
(It's an antique and luxurious room with 2 floors.)
- Really? This is our room? - I just got goosebumps.
- I mean, Matterhorn... My gosh. - This is beautiful. Wait.
- I'm so shocked. - My gosh, look at this.
(It overlooks Zermatt's city center at a glance.)
- I should check the terrace. - I can hear the birds.
- Come out. You can hear the birds. - My gosh, I love the terrace.
Can you hear the birds chirping?
This is unbelievable.
(Imagine seeing this view and hearing the birds chirping.)
Hey, we could have a cup of coffee while admiring Matterhorn.
- That'd be great. - Tomorrow morning,
- We must. - we must wake up and have coffee...
while looking at Matterhorn.
- That's a must. - This is incredible.
(Night has fallen in this luxurious country, Switzerland.)
- There are stars, right? Please. - There has to be.
This place is amazing. What is this place?
- This is like a secret room. - Goodness, this place is awesome.
What is it? This looks like an attic, doesn't it?
- It's opening. - What's going?
(There's an astronomical telescope, and the ceiling slowly opens up.)
("Mystical Space" is released at the theater closest to the sky.)
(My gosh, it's like we're watching "Transformers".)
Are you doing this just for us?
Really? This is one luxurious package indeed.
- It's a luxurious package. - It is. It is indeed.
(An astronomy professor is invited, and the dome opens just for them.)
(Time to meet the stars that they had been waiting for since Seoul)
(A preliminary briefing with the professor)
(We took that photo from here.)
- Really? - Everything.
(I'll get to engrave the feast of bright lights in my eyes, right?)
Why can't I see the stars? Darn it.
(Why can't I see the stars?)
Haha, nothing is up there.
This is a bust. It's ruined.
Oh, no.
- Tim, there are no stars. - You'll get to see the stars.
When we turn off the lights, we can see them clearly.
- He turned the lights off. - My gosh.
(It's harder to see the stars now.)
But there are no stars.
- Where's the twinkling star? - Where... Where is it?
We can't see them at all.
Tell him not to worry and that my wife's name...
means star in Korean.
(The interpreter is flustered.)
His wife's name means star. She's a singer as well.
Very nice. Do you know what my biggest hobby is? It's singing.
Tim said that his favorite hobby is singing.
(He shares his hobby after hearing Haha's nonsense.)
- He's a singer too. - Can you sing one?
It goes something like this.
(I got an inspiration.)
Home lies behind, and the world is ahead
- My gosh. - My gosh, he's good.
(It's as if watching an opera with Tim's unexpected singing ability.)
(We didn't even ask him, but what's this song about?)
(Why is he singing this song for us?)
(You remind me of this song. It's a song of the hobbits.)
(They feel moved without knowing what the song is about.)
- He's good. - I... I...
That was so romantic. I almost cried.
Whenever the weather is bad, I come here and sing.
- He's so good. - He usually comes here and sings.
I guess he wants to be a singer.
(An encounter of the hobbits and the singer of the hobbits)
- Hold on. - This?
This is it. Hey, come here. Let's pretend that we saw this.
(They do look like they're in the galaxy as they stand there.)
- We must be precise. Move back. - What?
- Wait. Tighter. Bring it closer. - Hold on.
(They even put on the perfect facial expressions.)
("Starry Night")
(This does look pretty real.)
Haha, it looks real.
- This is it. - Our expressions are the same.
- This is good. - This is good. Thank you.
I mean, we did come from far away.
- Exactly. - When...
When would we get to come here during the rest of our lives?
It's a waste. It really is.
It is a shame, but since we can't see them, we'll call it a night.
- I'm not sure... - Tomorrow morning...
if you'll use this clip or not when you edit.
When I came back from the bathroom, I couldn't find Se Chan.
(It was late at night.)
With that view as the backdrop...
(The mountain was his backdrop.)
He was talking to someone on the phone.
He was doing this gesture too.
I'll stop here.
("Yang Se Chan Video Called Someone in Switzerland")
Come on. Why did you say that?
I was wondering where you were going with that.
When I approached him, he suddenly said,
"Get away from here." That's what he said.
- I have my private life too. - This is it. I'll stop here.
I was recording a video. It was great.
He was so affectionate.
(My gosh, this joker...)
You must edit this part out.
You can't air this.
This is all I can say.
(He removes the microphone to avoid leaving comments.)
(You know that you must cut this out, right?)
- You got that, right? - Hey.
- Let's get an exclusive. - No exclusive.
Haha, why did you say such a thing?
Goodnight.
(Ask the stars what really happened.)
(Team Shuddering Package's first night in the UK)
You can wash up first.
Where is it? Da Hee, you can wash up first.
(The reckless sisters are about to wrap up their first night.)
(It looks like she has to wash up first before anyone else.)
My gosh, look at my face.
(Last night, during the crazy mission, Your Silence)
(Whoever made a sound had to wear a disguise for this hard mission.)
(They weren't supposed to laugh, but it was impossible not to.)
(Wait and see. I'll make you laugh even more.)
(The ultimate disguise showed up. Hello, So Min?)
(How was I supposed to beat that face?)
(She trudged back into the dressing room again.)
(This was how this fancy-looking disguise came about.)
My gosh.
I don't have an ounce of energy.
My ankle hurts. It really hurts.
(Her face is still funny now.)
With your hair up, your beard stands out more.
- I look so ugly, don't I? - The beard is too...
Actually, I wasn't going to wash my hair until tomorrow.
I got a blow-dry and curled my hair at the hair salon.
I was going to keep this hair style if the curls were still intact.
But you guys smelled my hair. I shouldn't do that, right?
- We sweated. - We sweated on top of that.
Right. I should wash up.
(Should I give up too? I feel lazy. Should I just sleep?)
(This funniest-looking guy hasn't washed up either.)
What am I going to do?
(Whenever they think about tomorrow, all of their zeal disappears.)
Who will end up wing walking?
(Who will it be?)
Gosh, I'm about to lose my mind.
(Getting up)
I really don't know.
- What are you doing? - I'm testing if I have energy left.
I still have energy.
(What are you doing in the middle of the night?)
- Jae Seok. - So you're going to do it, right?
(You have energy left.)
No, I can't.
(You said you still had energy left.)
Would you do it?
I can't do it.
- I really can't do it. - If you get selected,
- you have to do it. - If I get selected?
Then I'd do it.
You will, right? That's fine.
If I get picked, I'll do it.
I have to do it since it's a promise with the viewers.
(He keeps changing his mind.)
(They're nervous about the penalty.)
Two members are exempted, right?
(They calm down with facial masks.)
Isn't it three?
3 or 4 members have to ride it.
(Let's just sleep.)
What do we do?
- Do your legs touch? - Aren't British people tall?
(This is strange.)
This bed is perfect for my height.
How is this possible?
(Try putting your legs on the pillow.)
By the way,
even if we do wing walk,
(If we do wing walk...)
we still may go to the haunted castle.
We keep talking about the wing walk.
The haunted castle is the hardest.
(It's the final destination of Shuddering Package.)
(It's the haunted Oxford Castle.)
(It's a mysterious place where various journalists visited.)
(An exorcist even heard sounds of ghosts.)
(It's spooky.)
I have no idea what I did wrong.
(He's frustrated.)
I thought a lot about it.
This is wrong.
Let's turn off the lights.
(Let's sleep for now.)
It's impossible to know.
You're right. Let's not think about it.
Let's sleep.
(The lights turn off.)
What's that red thing?
What's that sound?
Is there a red light in the bathroom?
I'm scared.
It's really scary. What's this?
Something touched me. Hey.
What is it?
(They run away.)
- What's wrong? - There's something.
- Is it a light? - Yes.
How do I turn on the light?
(They're cowardly brothers.)
- Turn on the light. Hurry. - What's going on?
My cord startled me.
(Why would you be startled?)
- Which light is it? - What is it?
(What is this red light?)
It's the bathroom light.
(You mean the red light?)
Can we turn it off?
Let's sleep with the light on.
(They spook themselves out while talking about ghosts.)
- Keep the light on. - Shall we keep the window open?
What do you think?
How about the door? Is that scarier?
(Shall we turn off the lights?)
- It's strange. - This is strange.
- It's strange. - What's going on?
This won't work.
(He ponders about what to do.)
I have to go home.
Kwang Soo.
(Okay, Kwang Soo.)
Call a taxi.
Why do I feel nervous with the lights on?
I think it turns off.
(They couldn't sleep all night long.)
(The second day starts in a peaceful mountainous village, Zermatt.)
(What awaits those on the Luxury Package today?)
- Good morning. - Good morning.
- We're going to ride heli-skiing. - Yes.
Hello, heli-skiing.
I hope that the weather will be good for heli-skiing.
I hope that the weather will be beautiful...
and that I won't have to pay.
- Please. - It'll be very expensive.
Let's go heli-skiing.
- Go, go. - Go, go.
Goodness.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Good morning. - Hello.
Did you vote?
(There's a voting box for paragliding.)
- I didn't. - Did you vote?
- I didn't. - You seem like you just voted.
- Did you vote? - Pardon?
- Did you vote? - No, but we will vote now.
Let's do it.
(There's no loyalty or teamwork.)
Shall we vote?
Are we voting already?
(Whom will they vote to pay for the paragliding?)
It's a great morning.
(Jong Kook starts to vote after Ji Hyo and Han Na.)
What?
I'll vote for someone I know.
- Write it. - You can't do this.
(How can you tell me to vote in front of the camera?)
It's secret voting.
- You shouldn't look. - "Secret voting"?
There are no secrets.
- He doesn't have any secrets. - Excuse me.
He's a man without secrets.
What's the point in keeping secrets? You're too quick to notice.
Gosh, stop it.
Why are you following me?
- Leave. - Wait.
I understand.
You're like the boy with a flute.
- I want to keep following you. - Hey.
I got it.
- Are there any bodyguards? - No.
- Are there any guards? - No.
Aren't there guards during votes?
- What are you doing? - It's a close-up.
- Hey... - Don't you know?
- Will you write one of our names? - No.
- It's a man. - Write it.
- Write down the name. - Goodness.
Haha.
(Jong Kook publicly votes for Haha.)
- Does this work? - Yes, thank you.
Now,
- each of us will vote. - You're gangsters.
We're gangsters.
- You're real gangsters. - Voting is over.
- Let's go. - Please go.
(Members at the hotel prepare to ski.)
We won't ever be back here.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I slept very well.
Did you make a video call?
(Reporter Haha is obsessive.)
Come on.
What's wrong with Haha? He's so nosy.
You look funny in a ski suit.
When I came out this morning,
our staff thought that...
I was Ryang Hyun or Ryang Ha.
(I didn't go to school.)
- It looks fancy. - Don't I look like Turbo?
You look like Turbo.
- It's white, it's snowing - It's snowing
- We're here. - We're here.
Everything is perfect.
(They head to summer ski in Switzerland.)
Let's go, summer skiing.
Let's get it.
- You talked a lot in your sleep. - What did I say?
"I'm scared, and I'm a coward."
(I'm scared, and I'm a coward.)
I'm serious. It's true. You don't know, but I do.
- You kept talking in your sleep. - Yesterday, I found out...
- with whom you're having a fling. - Stop lying.
- Stop lying. - Shall I say the name?
You'd better behave.
(They head to ski.)
(Ski rental shop and gondola lift)
Good morning.
Haha, Se Chan.
Ji Hyo.
You look pretty, Ji Hyo.
Hello, you're here.
- Who wants to rent skis? - Me.
One person?
Just one person.
Gosh.
I look the best today in Switzerland.
(He's excited.)
- Let's roll, baby. - Let's go.
(I'll fly over the mountains with this ski board.)
Go, go, go.
Go. Are we taking a helicopter?
Luxury, luxury.
(Alps, I'm coming.)
(Heli-ski: Jong Kook, Haha, Se Chan, Jin Young. Gondola: Ji Hyo, Han Na)
Here we go.
- It's fast. - It's really fast.
- It's going up. - Why is it so fast?
(Why is the gondola lift so fast?)
We get to enjoy the view of Switzerland.
Right, we see it as much as we want.
- Hello. - Hello.
(They ride a taxi to the heliport.)
Captain, you're wearing a tie.
(He's in charge of safety.)
- What's your name? - Matias.
- "Matias"? - "Matias"?
- Matias. - What's your name?
Mr. Yang.
Yang Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - Yang Se Chan?
- Yes. - It's Yang.
- Mr. Yang. - Yang.
What's your name?
- Ha, Haha. - Ha?
Really.
- Double H. - "Double H".
- Ha. - Yes.
How are you?
Are you ready for a helicopter flight?
- It's my first time. - Will helicopter...
- Are you afraid? - I'm a novice.
- I'm nervous. - Me too.
(Did he mean "nervous"?)
Are you sportive?
- What? - "Sportive"?
- Sportsman. - What?
What sports?
- Aren't you a sportsman? - No.
I'm an owner of Korean barbecue restaurant.
- You're Korean... Barbecue... - Barbecue.
I own a restaurant.
- I don't understand. - I'm the owner.
(He cuts and grills meat.)
(He uses body language for communication.)
(They arrive at the heliport.)
Is this the place?
I can't believe it.
Are we riding this?
- Is it the photo? - I'm excited.
You're supposed to ride the helicopter.
Then you jump off on a slope and ski down.
(Some people jump off directly from the helicopter.)
We're not as good,
so we'll ski down after getting off the helicopter.
(They'll ski after getting off.)
I've never ridden a helicopter before.
There's a helicopter.
That's what we'll ride.
- The helicopter is HH. - That's what we see...
- in movies. - It's HH.
- You see it in movies. - Right.
Okay, we're leaving. See you, Jong Kook.
- See you. - Good luck.
- See you soon. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - Let's go.
We'll stay alive.
(They get on the helicopter to ski.)
I'm scared.
It's my first time on a helicopter.
(Don't be afraid.)
(They get ready to take off.)
- I'm nervous. - Me too.
(They're very excited.)
(The propeller starts to turn.)
I'm so nervous.
Did I make a wrong decision?
(They may never get this opportunity again.)
My goodness.
(They're about to take off.)
(Haha and Se Chan look extremely nervous.)
- I'm scared. - Are you ready?
- We're ready. - We're ready.
You're ready?
(The helicopter takes off.)
(As soon as it takes off,)
(it turns around.)
(What's happening?)
Gosh.
(Strong first impression)
- This is scary. - It is.
(The two cowards hold hands.)
My hands are shaking.
(See you in a bit.)
There's a helicopter. It must be ours.
Let's see if it's ours.
It is ours.
It reminds me of the Nevis Swing.
At that time, we jumped from this high.
The Matterhorn is hiding again.
What's that?
(There are dark clouds all over the mountains.)
I'm jealous of them.
(It's a luxury to enjoy skiing in the summer.)
- I'm jealous. - Right?
The sand... Wait. Is this rain?
(Is this rain?)
It's raining. Let's get inside.
(It suddenly starts to rain heavily.)
(The helicopter is met with rain too.)
What's going on?
(Shaking)
(The strong wind makes the helicopter shake.)
Can we really ski here?
(What is going on now?)
(The weather gets worse and worse.)
(The wind is getting stronger.)
(The ski slopes are closed.)
(The staff members hold an emergency meeting.)
It might be dangerous when it rains.
Okay.
Wouldn't it be dangerous for the ski team?
What will happen to the ski team?
(What will happen to Haha and Se Chan?)
(Scared)
(Screaming)
(The cowards are scared.)
(The helicopter hurriedly gets ready to land.)
(His eyes are shaking.)
(Can we even land?)
- I want to get off. - Let's get off.
(The veteran pilot carefully prepares to land.)
(Nervous)
- We've landed. - We have?
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's go!
I'm sweaty.
(The helicopter is unloaded.)
(Staggering)
(The helicopter goes back to pick up Jong Kook and Jin Young.)
Haha, it's so cold here.
(They're met with an extreme situation.)
- It's cold here. - It is.
- How are you? - We're fine.
- We're good. - We're good.
I'm okay.
- It's raining. - Yes.
- Do we have to go back? - It's okay.
Is it okay?
(We've been looking forward to this.)
Gosh, why did it have to rain?
The wind is so strong.
(The local staff tries to find a solution.)
It's pouring down.
(The helicopter is back to pick up Jong Kook and Jin Young.)
(Jong Kook and Jin Young leave for the mountain top.)
What should I do? I'm scared.
I'm scared.
(The helicopter takes off.)
There's nothing to hold onto.
(Screaming)
Gosh.
(As soon as they take off, Jin Young starts to scream.)
What should I do? It's driving me crazy.
(Will my ears be fine?)
This is so scary. What should I do?
What should I do? Jong Kook, please.
- There's a thunderstorm... - What should we do?
Stop talking and focus on flying the helicopter.
(That's bad manners.)
What should we do?
(Don't worry.)
(The helicopter turns around.)
What's happening?
We're turning back.
(Is the helicopter going back?)
There must be something wrong.
(Is there something wrong?)
There is a thunderstorm and lightning...
- There's lightning. - Lightning?
- We can't go there? - No. That's too dangerous.
I don't want to die.
(What about Haha and Se Chan?)
- He says he doesn't want to die. - Right.
The weather is so bad.
(They get ready nevertheless.)
No?
It's canceled?
(The skiing is canceled due to the thunderstorm and lightning.)
- It's dangerous? - It's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Gosh.
Of course. This is who we are.
What a disappointment. What is this?
We're finally in Switzerland.
(We've been looking forward.)
It took us more than 20 hours to get here.
- This is not okay. - I'm so sorry.
No!
(This must be a dream!)
- No! - Let's go.
- Why? - Why?
No!
(It took them 28 hours to get here, but the skiing is canceled.)
(Repeating)
No!
Let us ski!
We're stranded in Antarctica right now.
- Help! - Help!
- Help! - Gosh, it hurts.
- It hurts. - It hurts.
(The sudden hail makes them realize the seriousness of the situation.)
Can a helicopter take off?
(What if no helicopter can come?)
Will we be abandoned?
This is pretty serious.
(Emergency)
(They're trapped on the Alps.)
(What will happen to them?)
This is horrible.
If they can't ski,
they have to wait for a helicopter?
- Yes. - Is it that bad?
(Thunder)
Are they okay?
Is the helicopter team okay?
(Jong Kook and Jin Young who returned immediately are safe,)
(but Haha and Se Chan are trapped.)
(They can't come back without a helicopter.)
This is serious.
How will they come back then?
(There's nothing they can do.)
- They're stranded. - Yes. I'm worried.
(Will they be okay?)
Okay.
(Thunder)
(Is this real?)
I'm scared.
Let's run away.
Help me.
(With the weather getting worse, the staff becomes busy.)
(What will happen to us?)
Help me.
The second helicopter came...
(Emergency meetings are held.)
(The experts gather everyone together.)
- Here. - Haha, come here.
Come and sit down on the ground.
(All they can do is...)
(wait for help.)
Why does the weather have to be this bad?
(They wait and wait.)
A helicopter is coming.
(A helicopter appears like a miracle.)
(The veteran rescue team flies through the bad weather.)
This is better than being rescued.
(We're safe now.)
It feels like we're being rescued. Help me.
(A rescue helicopter arrives.)
(We're safe now, right?)
(They get on the helicopter under the experts' guidance.)
(They take off safely.)
We should laugh.
(They can't believe the situation.)
(Why do things never go our way?)
You're the best.
Thank you!
I'm so disappointed.
(They're forced to give up heli-skiing.)
Haha, look over there. We were just there.
- Where? - Over there. Behind that mountain.
- Behind that mountain? - Yes.
Jin Young, once we go over the mountain,
there's a new world.
- "A new world"? - Yes.
The slope isn't what you see now.
- We dodged thunder three times. - Really?
That's incredible.
(It's an incredible story.)
It's funny, isn't it?
It's supposed to be luxurious.
- It's not. - It's not.
We spent the money anyway, right?
Someone has to pay.
(Someone still has to pay.)
Is the money considered spent?
- We rode the helicopter. - We did.
(It will be unfair for the one who pays.)
Today's weather is beautiful.
- Listen. - Why do I feel so frustrated?
The weather is too beautiful.
Look at the sky.
(The clouds look like cotton candy.)
We're definitely in Europe.
There are horses.
- It's beautiful. - There are horses.
It's so amazing.
Everyone, did you sleep well?
- No. - No.
(Everyone feels the same.)
I woke up every two hours.
Soon, you'll do wing walking as your penalty.
I always ask, but what did we do wrong?
What did I do so wrong in my life?
- What is it? - I keep wondering.
- I keep wondering too. - We're in the UK.
Why are you wearing makeup when we're going to wing walk?
- Don't think that I wear makeup. - I can't believe it.
No one else is wearing makeup including me.
Where did you get your makeup done of all people?
Da Hee did it for me this morning.
- Da Hee? - She did my makeup.
- I did it for him. - Da Hee is good.
(He's very satisfied.)
- Da Hee is talented. - She did a good job.
(He loves it.)
(Let's see.)
Did you do yours, Seok Jin?
(Did you do yours, Seok Jin?)
- Does it look bad? - His makeup looks...
- so obvious. I know. - I put on some BB cream.
I can see that.
I'd like to share some information.
It's about Team Switzerland who's on the Luxury Package.
Due to inclement weather,
their schedule for today got canceled.
- Shouldn't the weather be good? - Wait.
- This is inclement weather too. - Isn't this inclement weather?
Switzerland is known for good weather.
That is true, and here,
- the weather tends to fluctuate. - It rains a lot.
Unluckily, Team Switzerland can't continue their schedule.
However, we're lucky.
- We'll follow the schedule. - Is that good?
- It's not good. - How are we lucky?
Is it true that we're lucky and that they aren't?
Anyway, today's weather in the UK is considered ideal.
It's a very clear day.
- It's interesting. - Why today?
- How is it possible? - Why today?
It rains a lot here, so I brought a raincoat.
- Everyone wears a raincoat. - It's useless.
(This is the usual weather in the UK.)
(Aren't umbrellas expected here?)
It's such a sunny day. It's too sunny.
- The weather is best for traveling. - It's the best.
Since we're here to be penalized, this is considered a disaster.
Are there any issues for the wing walking flight?
- The weather is ideal. - "Ideal"?
- The rest of the people... - Look.
- So Min, you never know. - Listen.
- Stand here, Da Hee. - The three of us should ride it.
Your outfits match each other.
(As they're standing, their outfits match.)
- Let's get it. - They're like a campus couple.
- When So Min was eating breakfast, - That's right.
Sang Yeob came over.
She said, "A young master is coming."
- I called him a prince. - Why is he a prince?
He looks handsome like a prince.
I called So Min to have breakfast together.
I said that everyone was coming.
She said, "I want to sleep more."
"What about Sang Yeob?" "He's coming."
"I'll be there."
(So Min decided to join.)
That's what she said.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- She plays favorites. - Seriously.
- What's wrong with you? - I thought you were tired of him.
- He looks British. - Is that so?
(He has strong features.)
- He looks British with thick lines. - After watching him,
- I know why Sang Yeob stands out. - Why?
- When I look at him, - Look.
- Look. - Sang Yeob is...
- Join us and make him look better. - He's very handsome.
- Kwang Soo. - Come here.
- Come here, Kwang Soo. - I'm not Ki Beom.
- I'm not Ki Beom. - Stop it.
- Look. - He's very handsome.
Da Hee takes care of Kwang Soo.
So Min takes care of Sang Yeob.
Who takes care of me?
I'm okay, but no one takes care of Seok Jin.
Please care about me.
- That's hilarious. - Do you know if I have eaten?
Chun Yoo, Kwon Ryeol. Take care of Seok Jin.
No one cares even if he's lying on the restroom floor.
Don't help Kwang Soo with makeup. Help Seok Jin.
He applied his own makeup.
He wipes off his face with yellow tissue.
(He takes care of himself.)
He says, "Okay."
- I don't know what he uses. - It's yellow.
It's not for pooping, right? What's that?
Can you buy yellow tissue?
- Is there yellow tissue? - No.
It becomes yellow after I wipe my face, you fool.
Take care of me. I barely make it each day.
I walk because my eyes open in the morning.
- It's because my eyes open. - He barely lives.
- Please take care of him. - Goodness.
I take care of him from time to time,
but no one else cares about him.
Check if I'm breathing at night.
Why?
It's getting sadder.
We'll head to the city of Oxford.
Shall we go?
- I don't feel good. - Are we going directly?
- It's better to feel good. - It'll be tiring.
I feel better because I'm less likely to be penalized.
Da Hee takes good care of people.
- Jae Seok takes care of you. - That's right.
I'm the only one who cares about him.
- No one else does. - He helps Seok Jin a lot.
- Is he his assistant? - Yes.
- "I'll sacrifice myself." - "I'll sacrifice myself."
This is the wrong side.
- "I'll sacrifice myself." - This is the wrong side.
That was wrong.
- It's the driver's seat. - Why did you open that door?
- The driver is sitting there. - It's on the right.
- I'm sorry. - You startled him.
The steering wheel is on the other side.
- Why did you open that door? - I'm sorry.
- Hello. - He makes a mistake immediately.
(I'm sorry.)
I forgot that the steering wheel was on the right.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
The flower is still alive.
I've never seen the UK with such great weather.
- Look at the trees. - Everything is beautiful here.
- This looks amazing. - Even the shape...
of the trees is different.
Aren't they tall and grand?
- They're pretty. - This is the campus.
- Really? - Oxford University?
- Is this it? - Really?
I should take photos of Oxford.
(It looks sophisticated for a reason.)
(I should take photos.)
Are you applying to the school?
No, I'm not.
Please drive slowly.
- He can't take photos. - Ivy on the wall.
- "Ivy on the wall"? - Wait a minute.
Seok Jin.
Let me take photos.
I want my child to dream of coming here.
Driver, please slow down.
(He begs the driver to slow down.)
- Slow. - Seok Jin.
I couldn't take any. Hey.
Poor Seok Jin.
All I took was this.
(He's terrible at taking quick photos.)
- I feel bad for him. - What are all these?
That's funny.
I thought about applying to Oxford.
(He talks nonsense.)
- Pardon? - Come on.
I'm free to apply, aren't I?
- I know, but why? - Goodness.
It's a waste of application fee.
That's too harsh.
You're being too harsh.
I'll summarize what's going on.
Before leaving Incheon Airport,
1st and 2nd places get Pirate Roulette Game with 24 slots.
3rd and 4th places get 16 slots.
5th and 6th places get 8 slots.
(The size of Pirate Roulette Game differs by penalty badges.)
1st and 2nd places get 24 slots.
3rd and 4th places get 16 slots.
5th and 6th places get 8 slots.
You'll play in the order of last to first.
(They'll play in the order of last to first.)
The 1st 3 to lose will wing walk.
Da Hee and Kwang Soo are 5th and 6th.
That's right.
They get Pirate Roulette Game with eight slots.
Sang Yeob is in first place.
- He gets 24 slots. - That's amazing.
- 2nd and 3rd have tied scores. - Their scores are tied.
They're So Min and Seok Jin.
Jae Seok placed 4th. He gets 16 slots.
So Min and Seok Jin remain. Are we heading to wing walking?
- We have no time to lose. - We're on our way.
- Let's hurry and play. - Let's decide.
Can't you yield?
- We should compete. - Don't you know how to yield?
- So Min and I talked last night. - About what?
- This is what So Min told me. - What?
(Before going to bed last night)
I'll work hard if I don't get penalized this time.
Have you accepted penalty for someone?
On this show?
You haven't once, right?
Have you, So Min?
- No. - Have you done it for guests...
- or other members? - Come on.
- I'm serious. - Da Hee.
- Gosh. - You're scared of it, aren't you?
- I've never done it. - You haven't, right?
As a member,
you should do it.
- Da Hee. - Do a difficult task for someone.
- Have you sacrificed yourself? - No.
That would be amazing.
Do you want to try it?
You should try it.
She's never sacrificed herself, so she wants to try it this time.
I never said that.
(She's determined.)
Never.
(Is that so?)
Let's go to the site first...
- Shall we do it there? - and decide.
I heard that weather in the UK is terrible, but it's beautiful.
I heard all my life that the weather in the UK is bad.
- All your life? - My friends told me about it.
Who?
His name is Go Pil Seob. Do you know him?
(His name is Go Pil Seob. Do you know him?)
He works at an investment company.
- Why are you getting upset? - Do you know my friend?
- I was just asking. - Do you know Pil Seob?
- You don't know him. - Goodness.
Everyone is so sensitive. It's scary.
(This bus full of sensitive people...)
(drives for a while.)
- It's an open field. - It's so refreshing.
I didn't know the UK could look like this.
Oh, my.
Look at that.
What's that?
- What's that? - It's so pretty.
(There is no end to the blue sky and the green field.)
It's beautiful.
(When things get tough,)
(we sing.)
(They try to forget the reality.)
We must be here.
- Really? - Are we here?
- We are. - We are?
We're making a turn.
Are we really here?
We're here.
We're in trouble.
This is reality.
If we fall, it'll be easy to find us.
(If we fall, it'll be easy to find us.)
So Min.
If we fall, it'll be easy to find us.
(Why do you have to say that?)
- I see a plane. - Really?
Look at that.
- It's a plane. - Look at that chair.
(Coughing)
I'm going to throw up.
- Are we going to sit on that chair? - That's crazy.
(Just by seeing the plane, they become extremely nervous.)
- This is crazy. - What should we do?
(There is a small chair on the plane.)
- We're going to sit on a chair? - There's a chair on the plane.
That's a chair?
(There is a lonely chair on the plane.)
There's nothing else.
(With a maximum speed of 217km per h,)
(the plane can fly as high as 457m.)
(Wing walking is one of the world's most extreme sports.)
(Their amazing experience begins soon.)
- That... - Doesn't it look a bit unstable?
So that's how it looks.
Don't you think the chair will fall off?
- It looks like... - Yes, it looks like that.
I mean...
(They become even more worried.)
I can't believe it. I can't do this.
I can't do this. What should I do?
I really can't do this.
Seriously. What should I do?
So Min.
Seriously.
So Min is doing it again.
She's doing it again.
(Tearful)
I'm so scared.
(To avoid wing walking, they have to survive the game.)
It'll feel so lonely up there.
I have a question.
How long will it go on?
10 minutes.
- 10 minutes? - That's too long.
- 10 minutes... - That's too long.
Are there seat belts?
I hope the chair is not soldered.
Soldered?
What are you talking about?
- I hope it's secure. - I thought I couldn't laugh,
- but that's just absurd. - Soldered?
It's possible.
I hope it's fixed securely.
But...
The weather is perfect for flying.
The weather looks nice.
(Which 3 of them will experience wing walking?)
Gosh, I'm so disappointed.
It's here.
- Go on. - Go on.
- Go on, Jin Young. - Go on.
Hello. Come.
All we've done today is wait.
Don't film. We're alone together.
(Don't film. We're alone together.)
(Matt is still full of energy.)
- He's so cheerful. - Are you married?
Are you married?
(No ring)
No?
I'm so relieved to have him here.
(Cheerful)
She says she's relieved because of you.
(Surprised)
(Out of nowhere, she sings.)
(Laughing)
What are you doing?
- We? - Yes.
Are you a CEO?
(Are you a CEO like Haha?)
Take a guess.
- Take a guess. - Guess what she does.
She's a singer.
- Sing for him. - You're a singer.
It's raining men
(It's raining men)
(Matt looks surprised.)
(Matt is having more fun.)
(Two cheerful people meet.)
(Jin Young's first concert in Switzerland)
(Matt can't take his eyes off of Jin Young.)
(Goodbye, rain)
Remix.
(What do you think?)
- You're amazing. - Thank you.
- Everything about you is amazing. - Thank you so much.
You too.
(Matt's heart melts.)
Sorry.
Why would you say sorry?
- Why? - Nothing.
- So? - He's a singer too.
- You're a singer too? - Yes.
(Matt is on guard.)
All right. 1, 2, 3...
(Jong Kook is suddenly asked to sing.)
(The situation is not the best, but Jong Kook sings his best.)
Your voice is better.
(Suddenly)
(Matt can't get over Jin Young's singing.)
- Thank you. - Sorry.
It's all right.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- My feet are so comfortable. - Right?
- How are you? - I'm fine.
(Matt sits next to Jin Young.)
He seems to be into you.
(Shy)
Sing "Listen" for him.
(She does everything she is asked to do.)
(She puts emotions into the song.)
What is she doing?
(What is she doing?)
(Haha is embarrassed.)
Is this a musical?
(Matt is applauding.)
(Embarrassed.)
- I don't speak Korean yet. - Not at all?
- I can say no words. - No words?
"I love you."
(Jong Kook's Korean class)
- "I". - "I".
- "Love". - "Love".
- "You". - "You".
"I love you."
- "I love you." - Yes.
- "I love you." - "I love you."
Say that to her.
- What does it mean? - It means,
- "I love you." - "I love you."
(Really?)
(Is that what it means?)
His eyebrows...
That was a genuine reaction.
I know the only thing I'll have to know.
Yes.
You're a Casanova.
- Me? - Casanova.
No.
- You're a Casanova. - I'm...
I'm shy.
"I'm shy"?
(He knows how to win a girl's heart.)
The train should leave.
It should leave right now.
- Look at him. - Look at him.
Touch his hand and face.
(Bye, my love, Matt.)
(I love you. I'll never forget you.)
He is so funny.
(They say goodbye through the window.)
Han Na, try putting your hand on the window.
(To test Matt, Han Na gives it a try.)
- Let's see. - He might react.
He won't.
(Will Matt react to Han Na too?)
(He points at Jin Young.)
(He looks determined.)
(Who are you?)
He rejected her.
He rejected Han Na.
Good.
(Good job, Matt.)
- He's so funny. - Han Na got rejected.
He's hilarious.
(Jin Young is satisfied, and Han Na is disappointed.)
She got rejected.
(Thank you for the good memories, Matt!)
(Ji Hyo and Han Na are finally back.)
Are you guys alive?
- Jin Young - Are you alive?
- Guys. - What happened?
- We almost died. - It's...
Is this really the Luxury Package?
- Let's calculate. - This is a debt tour.
It's a debt tour.
You should pay for paragliding, right?
Because of what happened,
- we'll check in early. - Let's go.
Gosh. If it weren't for the rain...
- The view would have been amazing. - It would have been fantastic.
(The hotel is on a mountainside.)
Gosh.
This building has...
very low ceilings.
It's very unique.
(They're guided to a place.)
We climbed a hill...
- What's that? - What's that?
(Surprised)
(What is this place?)
- Hi. - It looks amazing.
(They say hi to the mysterious man.)
Is this...
- What is this? - Will someone cook for us?
Does this living room only belong to us?
Really?
The whole place belongs to us?
- It seems so. - It does?
The whole place is yours.
(The whole place is yours.)
There are four more floors.
Take a look around.
- Amazing. - I got goosebumps.
(I got goosebumps.)
(The hotel is located in Zermatt's best spot.)
I love this.
- Look. - My goodness.
(It's an exclusive hotel that is rented as a whole.)
This is so luxurious.
This is what we've been waiting for.
It's amazing.
(When you go downstairs,)
(more luxury unfolds.)
- The rooms look amazing too. - Each room has a different theme.
This place is so luxurious.
It's fantastic.
Let's look around.
This is so luxurious.
- This room looks amazing. - It looks fantastic.
It looks so great.
- I love the atmosphere. - Seriously.
- Is there more? - What's that?
(This floor looks a bit different.)
- There's a gym. - There's a gym.
There's a sauna too.
- There's a pool. - A sauna.
This is amazing.
(Enjoy the pool and the spa while looking over Zermatt.)
What is this place?
Guys. Seriously?
This place is so luxurious.
- I love this. - It's incredible.
(He is the butler.)
This is amazing.
Can we drink the stuff in the fridge?
- It's included. - Right?
This is why it's called Luxury Package.
Everyone, thank you for today.
The rain has stopped.
- Yes. - The sky has become clear.
- It's so sunny. - We could ski now.
- The weather is unpredictable. - It's a shame.
You should pay for...
yesterday's paragliding.
(It must be expensive.)
How much was it?
It cost...
810 dollars in total.
- 270 dollars per person. - That's expensive.
- But it was worth it. - Really?
Let's see the vote result.
Did everyone vote?
Yes, everyone did.
- Everyone? - But...
In the first round, they plotted against me.
No way. You can't say that.
(Cold)
Look at her smile.
- She's so nasty. - She's so mean to Se Chan.
What did I do? Let's do this.
First...
(This is the first vote to decide who'll pay for paragliding.)
The paragliding cost 810 dollars.
(Who'll have the honor of taking the first vote?)
They wrote it down on this paper.
- Yang Se Chan. - Hold on.
(Se Chan gets one vote.)
Hold on. The paper is ripped in half.
You ripped it.
(This morning, they checked out from the hotel.)
(We're one.)
(Can I have a piece of the paper?)
(They got paper from the staff...)
(and had half each.)
Han Na.
(He said "Han Na"...)
(and wrote down Se Chan's name.)
(It gets found out because of the voting paper.)
I saw you rip it. Haha.
Didn't you have a good time stargazing?
(I'm sorry.)
It's the same paper. Haha.
(This is the second vote.)
(How dare you...)
It's the same paper.
(Se Chan wrote Haha's name as well.)
(Everybody's the same in Running Man.)
- I knew this would happen. - It was obvious but still.
Next. Ha Dong Hoon.
Who's that?
We don't know who that is.
- Can you tell from the writing? - Next.
It's Haha.
- Okay, good. - It's me this time.
I told you we should be on the same side.
You guys planned it together.
It's me again. Look, it's me.
All right. Next is...
Kim Jong Kook.
- Who? - Who wrote my name again?
- They betrayed you. - You didn't write your own name.
- You wrote my name again? - I know. These three teamed up.
Last one.
- It's Hong Jin Young. - What?
(Last vote is for Jin Young?)
From the three friends,
- No way. - one person betrayed you.
- That's not true. - Really?
- See? - Who is it? You?
- No way, Ji Hyo. - Han Na.
- Is it you? - I'm disappointed.
- I swear. - Was it Haha?
You swear?
- It's her then. - Is it Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo. - You wrote Jong Kook's name then.
(She tells the truth.)
(They finally figure out the culprit.)
(It came from Han Na's conviction.)
Ji Hyo, that was good.
- You're a great actress. - Goodness.
Jin Young is not smiling properly.
- I see. Okay. - Jin Young.
- Okay. - She looked at me.
- This is war. - That's not why.
- This is war. - I told you.
Betray them. I didn't like you three hanging out together.
That's not why. It looked like Jong Kook had a lot of money.
- I thought he could pay it all. - She's so direct.
- Good job. - Yes, this is war. Okay.
I'll let it go because your pants are so shiny.
We'll decide who'll pay through Ghost Leg.
(They'll decide who'll pay through Ghost Leg.)
There are numbers 1 through 6. You'll select multiple numbers...
according to the number of votes you received, and it'll decide who pays.
Haha, you have three votes.
Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Jin Young has one each.
- You never know. - Han Na.
We did good.
(They go ahead with the lottery.)
This is Haha,
- and this is Se Chan. - Okay.
(Se Chan is on the left, and Haha is on the right.)
- I'll open them at the same time. - I did good so far.
- If I get picked, I'll be so sad. - We're going at the same time.
- I'm going. - One.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(Who will be the nice one to pay?)
- I'm going. - One.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- 2, 3. - 2, 3.
(Who will be the nice one to pay?)
Se Chan!
(Se Chan gets selected.)
- Why didn't I go? - Se Chan,
thank you for the paragliding.
- Thank you for the paragliding. - I beat the odds.
That was unbelievable.
I didn't even go paragliding.
- So Se Chan will pay. - He didn't even go.
I didn't even get to see the parachute.
Paragliding was great.
Haha didn't get picked?
(This is not the end. Who'll pay for the helicopter?)
This is unbelievable. We're here in the UK to do this.
I didn't know we'd actually come.
I'll be good.
(There is a daily limit, so only 3 people can ride it.)
You're here for wing walking. Do you see the plane behind you?
- I did. - We know already.
I'm too terrified to look.
I don't even want to look at it.
I can't digest right now.
(They'll have to decide on who'll go.)
These two have such big differences.
- This is... - 24 or 16 is a big difference.
Kwang Soo's is this small. Look at his.
- That's true. It's so small. - Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- Seok Jin... - Yes.
- and So Min, come here. - Come here.
You 2 have to decide. 1 of you get the 24 spaces,
- and the other one gets 16 spaces. - Right.
- So three of us have to go? - Right.
- Hurry. Can we decide quickly? - Go ahead and decide.
- Use this. - Shall we use this?
- Use this. - Can we use this?
- Yes, you can. - If you lose, you get this one.
- Seok Jin, do rock-paper-scissors. - Let's go.
- This is the match of the century. - You can go first.
The loser goes first. Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin loses, so he goes first.)
She won.
(He gets nervous.)
"She won."
This is the first one. It won't pop out.
(Seok Jin gets 1 in.)
I think it'll pop out.
Please, please.
Seok Jin has no intentions of being nice.
He's cold-hearted.
- "Cold-hearted"? - Let's go.
- I think it'll pop out. - Here.
(The loser will get one step closer to wing walking.)
(Seok Jin is cursing her and wishing she'd lose.)
(I don't know anymore.)
(It pops out.)
(So Min gets the pirate roulette with 16 spaces.)
(He's truly happy that he won.)
(This can't be true.)
That was her second try.
At least we didn't come to this.
Imagine if this was the main game.
So Min, how could this happen?
We have a chance. We have enough chances.
I'm getting anxious now too. Look at her.
We have to get through seven turns.
This one's not good. It'll pop out in three tries.
This one's mine.
It came out.
(There are 24 spaces, and it came out in 1 try.)
- That took 1 try. - I stuck 1 in.
- I stuck 1 in. - You never know.
You never know. Nobody knows.
You never know. You really don't.
(Da Hee and Kwang Soo start to get hopeful.)
(She's losing it.)
This is not how it's supposed to work.
This is unbelievable.
I'm getting nervous already.
This is a lottery. You never know what'll happen.
This is...
This is insane.
Pirate Roulette Death Match will decide...
the three people who'll receive the penalty.
(Pirate Roulette Death Match will decide the 3 people.)
Let me be the other half.
We'll start with the person who has the most number of badges.
The person whose pirate pops out has to go wing walking.
(Kwang Soo goes first, and they'll take turns inserting a sword.)
We'll start with last place.
Let's start Pirate Roulette Death Match.
Kwang Soo is in sixth place, so he goes first.
- Don't touch your head. - Go ahead.
Kwang Soo.
- I think it'll pop out at once. - Show them, Kwang Soo.
I think it will too.
- Kwang Soo, let's finish this. - Show them.
(Kwang Soo, show us the miracle again.)
Look at his face.
- Three people, right? - Yes.
Kwang Soo, show them.
(Trembling)
It'll pop out.
It's so small.
It's over. Hurry up.
If you fake it, your mom will scold you.
- No? - He inserted it.
- He's fine. - Put it in fully.
Push it in. Push it in fully.
(Ticking)
(Kwang Soo survives the 1st round.)
(Screaming)
I only need three people.
(If 3 people lose, Kwang Soo gets exempt.)
- I only need three people. - I'm getting nervous.
- I'm getting scared. - Three people. Please!
I'm getting nervous watching.
I'm so nervous.
Da Hee.
(Next is Da Hee, also with 8 spaces.)
Please lose.
(As long as it's not me)
(They all hope the pirate pops out.)
(It pops out.)
Please lose.
(Da Hee gets the penalty.)
(What happened?)
- 1 died. - We have 1 loser.
- Hold on. - Yes!
(Okay, one person lost.)
(Yes, one died.)
Stop it. Don't say one person died.
One person lost. My bad.
- I'm sorry. - Hold on.
Can I go one more time?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- No. - Just one time.
Move over!
(Stop with that nonsense.)
- Move over. - Go away!
This is business.
- I came this far. - Kwang Soo.
You can't do this to me.
- This is not possible. - Da Hee gets the penalty.
- Jae Seok. - Please, not now. Not now.
It'll pop out. I'm sure.
(Jae Seok has 16 spaces. Will he survive?)
Please, please.
(There is so much tension.)
It'll be quick.
- I know. - Okay.
- This is too awful to look. - Please.
(Jae Seok survives the 1st round.)
Jae Seok survived too?
(Thank you, Pirate.)
- Jae Seok. - Why didn't it work for me?
We have 1 person, so we only need 2 more.
I don't want to look at their faces.
We only need two more people.
- So Min, do you want to go with me? - Please.
(No.)
(She's about to cry.)
So Min, what's going on with you?
- What is wrong with you? - Gosh.
Gosh, I'm so mad.
- So Min is getting started. - I can't do this.
- Why are you crying? - Calm down.
- I'm so mad. I was in first place. - Why are you crying?
- So Min. - You can win.
- I have eight spaces. - I didn't have any badges.
So Min, your snot came out.
(Really?)
Please. Let's do this.
- You don't know yet, So Min. - Seriously.
- You don't know yet. - Please.
- All right. - You don't know yet.
- My hand is shaking. - You don't know yet.
I don't think that's it, So Min.
(Will So Min survive?)
- What? - You're fine.
(I got it?)
You were crying, and you're laughing now.
(What is she doing?)
I'm going to check if you're okay.
(Should Da Hee check?)
There's nothing.
Please pop out.
I want Seok Jin's to pop out.
If these two lose, it's over.
I hope Seok Jin and Sang Yeob lose so that it'll be over.
I hope they lose so that this will end.
Are you allowed to do that?
- It's coming. - Okay.
(Seok Jin survives the 1st round.)
- I have many spaces, - Why is he so good?
so I'll just go.
I'll pick a random spot. Goodness.
- That scared me. - Hey, hey.
Kwang Soo, it's you.
(Is it already my turn again?)
Wasn't that quick?
(It's Kwang Soo's turn again. He has 7 spaces left.)
I have acid reflux.
I have a heartburn.
(What's Kwang Soo going to do?)
You have one-seventh of a chance.
Kwang Soo's is smaller than this one's head.
(His chance of survival is that small too.)
Da Hee?
You're done.
(He finds something.)
- Why is she here again? - You're done. What are you doing?
(He's serious.)
I can't do this. What should I do?
- It's too small. - It is.
I keep looking at it, and it's too small.
Please let me pass one more round.
(If he survives this round, he really has a chance.)
- That's not it. - I have a bad feeling.
Kwang Soo, that's not it.
(He carefully inserts it.)
- Insert it. - I have a bad feeling.
- Hurry up. - Goodness.
Are you allowed to take it out?
(He already inserted it.)
Hurry up.
(It pops out.)
(Kwang Soo gets to go wing walking.)
(The pirate is here.)
Hey, you can't do that.
Yes.
(The pirate did his job.)
Wait, so it's 1 out of us 4.
He knew the pirate would pop out,
so he was shaking his hand.
(Am I the only one who heard the click?)
(Shaking)
Why did you pick this space?
I told you that wasn't it.
(Kwang Soo gets to go wing walking.)
There's one space left.
Please, Jae Seok. Please.
I already said I don't have to get married. What should I bet now?
I don't have to move next year, so please.
I won't get a car.
(Please.)
Pop out.
(Even people with 24 spaces are not safe now.)
(This game has So Min's new house and car on the line.)
(Clicking)
(Jae Seok survives.)
- He's so good. - This is so nerve-wrecking.
- So Min. - Which one should I pick?
I have 1 out of 24 chances, and I'm still nervous.
I know. Me too.
(These two are done for.)
So Min.
(She's in a desperate situation.)
That's not it.
(Clicking)
(So Min survives.)
You survived.
- It's okay, right? - What happened?
- Did you insert it fully? - Yes, I did.
(So Min survives, and the remaining two are not relaxed anymore.)
Seok Jin keeps on checking.
- Please pop out. Pop out. - Let's finish this.
- Pop out. - Let's finish this with Seok Jin.
- Pop out. - Finish this.
(If he loses here, it'll be really funny.)
Pop out.
No, please.
(Will this be dramatic?)
(Clicking)
When it comes to something decisive,
- he never loses. - My heart.
I'm so relaxed. Let's get it.
Sang Yeob, make it pop out.
(Flinching)
(Clicking)
(Sang Yeob looked scared, but he gets lucky and survives.)
Jae Seok, it's you.
This is going fast now. It's going fast.
The faster we do this, Jae Seok and So Min...
(The chances of Jae Seok and So Min's losing increase.)
Jae Seok.
(The staff suddenly laughs.)
(Why are the members and the staff laughing?)
(Come here.)
(Brother, you need to rest.)
Who do you think it'll be?
Who do you think will join you?
(What do you guys think?)
It's him.
(The Grim Reapers of Wing Walking thinks it'll be Jae Seok.)
He'll lose this turn.
Accept it.
(Excuse me. Let's go.)
(There is one-fourteenth of a chance of losing. Will Jae Seok survive?)
(Clicking)
(Jae Seok survives.)
Did you insert it fully?
So Min.
(She can feel the vibe.)
(So Min, go on the plane with us.)
(It's not scary at all. I heard it's a lot of fun.)
Go! Go away, both of you.
(She's mad.)
(She yelled at the Grim Reapers. Will she be okay?)
So Min, be bold.
- How many spaces did you use up? - Should I try the front one?
(So Min, join us.)
(There are 14 spaces left. Will she beat the odds?)
Let me try this one.
(Clicking)
She survived.
(So Min survives.)
(So Min survived again. It's Seok Jin's turn.)
I feel like once the red swords run out, my life will too.
(He has a bad feeling.)
I have two left.
I feel like I'll be gone.
Go.
(Seok Jin goes all-in with the red swords.)
I don't have to go on it.
(I trust the red swords.)
(Ringing)
- I have a bad feeling. - I feel weird.
- He got a call. - It's for him.
Seok Jin, get ready. Oh, dear.
(Clicking)
Why is Seok Jin not losing?
It's my turn.
- Sang Yeob. - Let's get it.
(He survives easily.)
I'm still calm.
(It's Jae Seok's turn once again.)
How many does he have left?
- Don't waste your time. Hurry up. - Don't do that.
You never know.
He has 12 left. One-twelfth of a chance.
He has one-twelfth of a chance of losing.
- Please. - My heart is pounding.
(He's cautious.)
(Goodness)
I have a bad feeling.
(Why was Jae Seok surprised?)
- I think it'll pop out. What now? - He can feel it. It'll pop out.
(If Jae Seok loses, the 3 people will be decided.)
(Join us.)
I think it'll pop out. What now?
Please insert it fully.
(Will he survive? Or will he be the last person to go wing walking?)
(It pops out.)
Yes!
(Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Da Hee will go wing walking.)
(We survived!)
(Why did you come so late?)
(Crying)
(Seok Jin, So Min, and Sang Yeob are automatically exempted.)
(The UK is the best.)
According to the results of Pirate Roulette Death Match,
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Da Hee will go wing walking.
(Jae Seok gets to go wing walking.)
(Jae Seok, Da Hee, and Kwang Soo have been selected.)
- However... - What?
What? Is there something else?
(Is there something else?)
- What do you mean? - What is it?
- What is it? - Why are you saying that?
Please tell me now.
- Why is there always a "however"? - Tell me.
However, wing walking's speed is 128km per h...
at an altitude of 457m.
It also involves vertical descent and twists and lasts for 10 minutes.
(The original wing walking is at an altitude of 457m. It has twists...)
(and vertical descent. In total, it lasts 10 minutes.)
- 10 minutes is too long. - What's a twist?
- Doesn't it go like this? - Like this.
It goes like this.
That won't do.
Since you're all faint-hearted,
we divided up wing walking into three levels.
(They divided the original wing walking into 3 levels.)
Level one, flying at an altitude of 457m for 5 minutes.
- You just fly. - It's just upright?
That one's okay.
- You're just at the altitude. - I can do that.
Level two, all of the above with twists in addition.
- As long as it doesn't drop. - And...
level three, experiencing all of the above for 10 minutes.
There are twists and the vertical descent.
I'm scared of that. I can't do the vertical descent.
- These are the three levels. - I didn't know that existed.
(They'll pick an envelope each.)
Who will like to go first? You can do rock-paper-scissors.
- Should a lady go first? - Yes.
- No. - It's up to you.
- I don't want to do that. - What?
(He refuses sternly.)
- Kwang Soo. - To be honest,
Da Hee got chosen first. That means she finished last.
That means she finished last.
You son... How could you...
(What?)
- That was a swear word. - She used a swear word.
- That was a swear word. - Da Hee used a swear word.
Not even my mom says that to me.
I've never heard such a word from my mom either.
- She used a swear word. - Seriously.
I meant to say that you are an individualist,
but the word came out wrong.
- I didn't use a swear word. - It can't be helped.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - You lack consideration.
- The winner decides the order. - That's right.
(The winner decides the order.)
You are a coward.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Da Hee loses.)
(The winner decides the order.)
Kwang Soo, it would be better if you don't choose the envelope.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo loses.)
(Please let me pick first.)
Stop that.
Kwang Soo, it would be better if you don't choose the envelope.
- Da Hee, go first. - Okay.
I will go after Da Hee.
(Da Hee picks first.)
You get whichever one you touch.
Da Hee, please open the envelope and reveal the level.
- Please let it be level 1. - I really hope she gets level 1.
(She wants to avoid the vertical descent of level 3.)
(Which level does Da Hee have?)
Which level do you have?
(Da Hee gets level 2.)
It's level two.
(Level 2 is out of the picture.)
(10 minutes of flying and twists)
- Why is this happening to me? - It's either level 1 or level 3.
Even among them, the competition is fierce.
Of course it is. Everyone wants the standard flying.
- The standard flying. - The competition is fierce.
- It's either level 1 or level 3. - You know,
those levels are very different.
- Level 3 lasts twice as long. - He's right.
Who wants to pick first?
I get to decide, right?
Tell Kwang Soo to pick. He is unlucky.
- Tell Kwang Soo to pick. - Please let me get the leftover.
Pick first.
(In that case, pick first.)
Kwang Soo, pick the one on the right.
- Pick the one on the right. - I'll choose last.
It's the one on the right. Pick it.
Please don't let him...
Pick the one on the right.
Kwang Soo, think carefully. You don't want the vertical descent.
Level three has the dive.
- I have a gut feeling. - No. That one is level three.
- Pick the one on the right. - Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo ignores So Min and goes for the left.)
Now...
(Don't say I didn't tell you.)
- Open them at the same time. - Is that mine?
Open them at the same time.
(Here, Jae Seok.)
You shouldn't have touched it!
The result will be bad since Kwang Soo touched it.
- I... - Hey!
- I only touched the tip. - You shouldn't have touched it.
Kwang Soo's touch will change the result drastically.
When you touch the envelope, the content changes to level three!
- No, it doesn't. - Yes, it does.
- I was startled too. - You are unlucky.
I saw Kwang Soo touch the envelope and thought, "He shouldn't do that."
I only delivered it to you.
On the count of three, open the envelopes.
1 will fly for 5 minutes at the standard altitude.
The other will fly for 10 minutes with twists and vertical descent.
One.
(5 minutes of flying at the standard altitude...)
(versus 10 minutes of twists and vertical descent)
Two.
(What are their fates?)
Three.
(Kwang Soo gets level 3.)
Jae Seok has level one.
(Level 3 is the worst stage of the worst penalty.)
I told you to make Kwang Soo pick first.
- You should have listened to me. - It doesn't make sense to be happy.
I told you so.
It doesn't make sense to be happy.
What's the point? I have to wing walk anyway.
- I told you to make him pick first. - Kwang Soo worried...
about getting chosen for wing walking last night.
A man's mind is fickle.
I am so happy about picking level one.
That means you will go first.
(Jae Seok, Da Hee, Kwang Soo)
You will go first.
I will now introduce the pilot who will fly the aircraft.
- He looks dependable. - He looks cool.
(Mike Dennis, wing walking pilot)
(Over 30 years, 3,000 wing walkers have ridden his plane.)
- It's nice to meet you. - What a handsome man!
- Hello. - Hi.
Who is going to be riding on the wing of my plane?
- 3 people. - 3 people.
- These people here? - Yes.
Who is level 1? Who is level 2?
- Level 1, level 2, and level 3. - Level 1, level 2, and level 3.
- And you are level three? - Yes.
(Sighing)
(He shakes his head.)
He seems to know that Kwang Soo is hopeless.
- What does that mean? - He took one look and sighed.
- He seems to know. - Congratulations on level three.
- Level 1? - Yes. Level 1.
- It's fine. - It's fine?
Level 2? It's a little bit...
- Level 3. - Level 3?
(It gives me a headache.)
(Why does it give you a headache?)
Actually, it's fine. You will be fine.
You will all enjoy it. It's lovely.
- It's a beautiful day. - Yes.
- What is not to enjoy? - It's true. It's a beautiful day.
However, I am faint-hearted.
Tell him that they are cowards.
Three of them are cowards.
Tell him that I wet my bed until I was in ninth grade.
Okay. Fine.
He needs to have a change of clothes...
because I don't want the damp on my seat.
How about he ride it without any pants on?
(In that case...)
So Min, you...
You changed a lot in 10 minutes.
- Of course he can't wear it. - It's heavy.
Yes, I can. If you give it to me, I will demonstrate.
I knew it would be impossible.
So if you put this on your head...
(Are you watching, Se Chan?)
It suits you.
Okay.
When we fly at 140km per h,
the wind...
The wind.
(The wind pushes the mask.)
Is the wind that strong?
Was the demonstration necessary?
(I doubt the demonstration was necessary.)
- Seriously. - He almost fell backward.
- I understood. - Did you see his face...
when he was pushed back?
Please tell him that we understand some English.
- You will go like this. - I see. I see.
- His neck will break. - I understand.
All right. Please give a big hand...
- to the pilot. - Thank you.
- Please take good care of us. - Thank you.
- See you in a minute. - Yes. See you.
(It's not dangerous. Don't worry.)
Don't worry. Let me check.
(His pants are still dry.)
Please take good care of me.
(The wing walking experience is just around the corner.)
I can see that you are very scared,
but this is an extreme sport many European women enjoy.
- It's not dangerous. - Like I said,
they actually wanted to do this.
We are doing this for a penalty. There is a big difference.
So I can't have drug-induced sleep, can I?
No.
The employees keep telling us there is no need for this fuss.
There is no need for this fuss?
Tell them that they don't know anything about me.
Since Jae Seok is going first,
he will recount his experience when he comes back.
Gosh, Jae Seok is going now.
- Jae Seok. - Good luck.
Jae Seok, let's go.
(For the safe wing walking experience,)
(the pilot flies the aircraft first without a passenger.)
(Warming up)
(This is really happening.)
They should make sure there is enough gas for three people.
(Come to think of it...)
(Annoyed)
- I am serious. - Stop it.
If we include the test flight, the plane will fly four time.
- They know what they are doing. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
Stop it.
The gas tank looks small.
I am worried about your safety.
- It took off. - It took off in an instant.
- It took off. - I will be on the wing.
- It's in the air. - It's in the air.
I can see it.
This is no joke.
(Since this is a test flight, the plane takes off gently.)
It's really high.
(It looks pretty okay.) (My goodness.)
(It suddenly makes a twist.)
(Leaning)
Are they doing that?
(Are we doing that?)
Look at that. It's scary.
Was that a twist?
- No. - It wasn't a twist.
- Apparently, it was nothing. - It wasn't a twist?
To change direction...
It was a twist.
If that's not a twist, what is?
- It's landing. - It's descending.
It's landing.
Jae Seok, it's time to put on your gear.
Goggles.
(Jae Seok puts on the safety gear.)
(Here are your goggles.)
You look cool.
(You look cool.)
- Hold on. - Don't be ridiculous!
He doesn't look cool.
Do you take us for fools?
Who said that?
Him...
- and him... - Do you think this looks cool?
Do you think this looks cool?
It's not much different from the grasshopper mask.
(Kwang Soo fastens the helmet straps.)
- For goodness' sake! - I am sorry.
(He gets pinched.)
You were warned.
- Don't pinch him. - I didn't know.
I didn't know. I thought it was my finger.
- They can't even do this right. - The goggles...
I will be back.
Don't worry about me.
(He is confident.)
Let's go.
I can do this! I can do this! I can do this!
(He collapses.)
(That's a lie.)
Kwang Soo.
I can't do this.
(I can't do this.)
Kwang Soo.
(Even if he can't, he must.)
(Jae Seok gets on the plane first.)
See you soon, Jae Seok.
(Hesitant)
(Worried)
(With heavy feet,)
(he arrives at the plane.)
- You can follow me so far. - Okay.
(He finally sets foot on the plane.)
(He is incredibly nervous.)
He will actually do it.
- He is on the wing. - My goodness.
(With the staff's help, he carefully climbs on top.)
Hold this through the next step.
Put your left foot sideways.
- Stand up when you are done. - My goodness.
(My goodness.)
(He can't help but sigh.)
I am so scared.
(I am so scared.)
- That's it. - Darn it. It's scary even up here.
Come here.
(He's merely on the wing, but he's already far away from the ground.)
- Take your seat. - This is so scary.
He's in big trouble. What will he do?
- He must be really scared. - He's really scared.
- Right. It looks like it. - Jae Seok is...
(They're worried because he easily gets scared to begin with.)
Okay. Sit, and make yourself comfortable.
I'm seriously scared.
It's scary to be up here.
(Jae Seok boards the plane.)
(Everything is ready.)
Take that again. It looks good. Have fun.
(How's the level 1 wing walking?)
The weather is great today, but why must I get this penalty?
I'm so scared.
(Jae Seok has asked that question way too many times.)
(Captain Mike gets into the cockpit.)
(Are you ready for the level 1?)
Jae Seok, Mike got in.
- Jae Seok, he got in. - Jae Seok.
Good luck. It's just starting.
Why is the weather so good?
(It's very sunny.)
He's about to start the engine.
Take off.
(He's ready and starts the engine.)
(The propeller starts spinning at last.)
(He can feel the vibrations with his entire body.)
- Here it goes. It's spinning. - He's surprised.
- He's surprised. Oh, my. My gosh. - He's surprised.
Gosh, this is crazy. Goodness. This is so scary.
(Screaming)
(After warming up the engine,)
(he finally takes off.)
It's shaking a lot.
(The plane begins to move to the take-off point.)
It's shaking too much.
(His entire body can feel the vibrations.)
I'm going to die now.
Since it's a penalty, it's not like I can't get out of this.
The weather is amazing today.
(The plane races in a stretched-out runway.)
(It arrives at the take-off point.)
My gosh, I haven't been as nervous as I am now.
This is really happening.
I think he's going to fly now. It got windy all of a sudden.
- Why did it get so windy suddenly? - The wind is suddenly blowing.
I'm a bit worried about him.
(I can't get off now.)
I can't get off now. What should I do?
(Without having the chance to get off,)
(the plane begins to accelerate.)
(Clenching his teeth tightly)
Here it comes. Here it comes.
(They're completely fixated on him.)
(The wheels are off the ground.)
It's flying. It's flying.
(After racing at an incredibly fast speed,)
(the plane successfully takes off.)
- It's in the air. - It's flying. It's in the air.
- He's sitting there. - Oh, no.
(As soon as it takes off,)
(the plane soars higher and higher.)
(Flinching)
- Look at his hand. - He's waving at us.
(Look over there. He's waving at us.)
(Jae Seok, come back safely.)
(The plane changes direction.)
- Jae Seok is doing that. - My gosh.
Goodness, he looks so cool.
(No, he doesn't sound cool at all.)
(At about an altitude of 450m,)
(Jae Seok is enduring the speed of 120km per h without any gear.)
It's so scary. It's so scary.
(You're scared? We didn't even start yet.)
(He suddenly changes direction.)
(What's happening?)
(It flies to the open plains after switching its course.)
- It's high. It's really high. - Jae Seok is on top of the plane.
- It's different from earlier. - Jae Seok, you're so cool.
- The plane doesn't waver at all. - Right, right.
Will it feel shaky on top of the plane?
(Shaky, my foot. The vibrations are fiery.)
My nose is runny.
(Gosh, my nose is runny.)
My nose is running, and I'm drooling.
Hey, by the way, the view is so beautiful.
This is so beautiful. It's scary,
but it's really beautiful.
(The scenery makes him forget about his fears for a short while.)
It's really beautiful.
It's really scary, but it's really beautiful.
(This must be why...)
(I'm going through with this penalty.)
It's really scary, but...
(The plane shoots out the steams.)
(A line of a beautiful cloud is drawn over the amazing scenery.)
- What's that? - What is it?
(They're amazed. Gosh, that's very beautiful.)
It's really scary, but it's really beautiful.
(He barely opens his eyes and enjoys the beautiful view of England.)
Freedom! Freedom!
(He shouts, "freedom".)
Freedom.
(His Freedom Cheer is full of sentiments of a middle-aged man.)
- He's raising his hands. Yes. - He's doing that with his hands.
- He feels at ease. He's relaxed. - Right.
He's doing something with his hands.
I'm about to throw up.
(Relaxed? As if! His nervousness is at its peak.)
(If level 1 is this scary, how scary is level 3?)
I want to return!
(He does Seol Kyung Gu's impression in the middle of the penalty.)
I want to go home now.
(Let's stop wing walking now.)
- Jae Seok endured it. - Here he comes.
He got off.
- My gosh, it's over. - He's coming here. It's over.
(Fluttering)
(He returns like a paper doll after riding it for 5 minutes.)
(The plane lands safely.)
(Tears of relief)
(Welcome. We're proud of you, Jae Seok.)
(He's worried about level 3.)
That was amazing.
Jae Seok, are you okay?
Let's go back and talk.
(Sighing)
(Sniffling)
Kwang Soo, let's go back and talk.
Did you cry?
I have a lot to talk about. Let's go back.
- Did you cry, Jae Seok? - You must be curious.
- Did you cry? - Let's go back to our spots.
- He must've really cried. - I think he really cried.
Why did he cry? Why did Jae Seok cry?
- Why did he cry? - Everyone came for him.
This...
(He begins sharing his experience.)
It's a long story.
Snot from my nose... And my mouth...
(The attack of the wind)
(He couldn't close his mouth due to the attack of the wind.)
The wind?
- It was fast. How fast was it? - Poor Jae Seok.
- Poor you. Are you serious? - Da Hee.
But by the way, it was beautiful.
Did you see?
- No, I didn't. - Then...
- He's making it up. - Why are you lying?
Be quiet. I could feel that it must've been beautiful.
You had your eyes closed when you took off. How would you know?
But at that instant... Everyone.
I wouldn't have had regrets if I died then.
- It was that good? - Really?
- You'd think that once. - Just once?
- That's when you must be careful. - What?
That's when you must get a grip. You might lose your mind then.
- That's when it'd go either way. - I did it. I got myself together.
- You must be careful. - In the middle, you did this.
- At that time, it got higher. - That's what I thought you did.
- You spread out your arms. - I was determined to do that.
- It'd be a photo of my lifetime. - "A photo of my lifetime".
But from down here, it didn't look that cool.
(A photo of your lifetime? It didn't look that cool.)
It looked like you fainted and was fluttering in the wind.
(You were fluttering.)
- It wasn't what you imagined. - What's wrong with you?
Things are different up there. It's a battle against yourself up there.
You're closer to the sky than to the ground.
- What? What did you say? - What's up with him?
What are you saying?
The moment you lose your mind, it's over.
- Why would I lose my mind? - You brat!
- What? - I came back from the dead!
- What do you know? - Listen.
- Goodness. - Next up is Da Hee.
All right. Da Hee will try level two.
- She's going to do that? - That will include a twist.
(It's just getting started.)
(A flight at a different level will begin.)
(It's even hard to watch.)
(Higher and faster)
(The ultimate flight will come.)
(And...)
(a night with the ghosts will be the grand finale of their trip.)
(Strange phenomena unfolds at the haunted castle.)
(They shouldn't have entered.)
(The members aren't invited.)
(What will happen to them?)
(They'll enjoy their luxurious trip in Switzerland to the fullest.)
(A Michelin chef will cook the meals himself.)
(This is the epitome of luxury.)
(However,)
(it's not over until it is.)
(The longest suspension bridge appears in sight before them.)
(What will happen to the members on top of the bridge?)
(My gosh, if this clip doesn't air for a long time,)
(Grand Final)