- Hello. - Hello.
Running Man aired a few days ago.
- Yes. - Yes.
Right afterward,
the Running Man homepage changed.
The profiles on D web portal changed.
- Did they change? - If you look up...
"Running Man Haha", you will see your changed profile.
So I type in my name after "Running Man", right?
Look at Jong Kook's picture!
I am surprised that he looks nice.
Why did you use this picture for my profile?
It's a nice picture of you.
(Haha, Identity laundering)
- This is too... - Look at my picture.
Jae Seok looks too handsome.
The picture suits him.
- Se Chan looks really pretty. - Let me see it.
You look really pretty. It's a picture I took.
Se Chan is Kim Jong Kook's fan. He dressed up as a girl.
- It's from the TV rating. - It's a good look for him.
You actually have a fan who looks like him.
- I bet I do. - I know you do.
- Seok Jin's picture is hilarious. - I thought he was...
Kim Young Hee.
- He looks like Kim Young Hee. - This picture was taken...
- when I was in 11th grade. - You look better in the picture.
- 11th grade? - Then why do you look so old?
- When was your picture taken? - It was taken in high school.
- You look really young. - It was taken in high school.
- You look like a baby. - What?
You look like a baby. I thought it was taken in middle school.
Why am I Joong Ki's Friend?
- Joong Ki's Friend? - Why am I Song Joong Ki's Friend?
You do well in dramas.
(The profiles now reflect Jong Kook's tastes.)
(Please enjoy the Running Man profiles.)
(Today, )
(Running Man goes on a vacation with the charming ladies.)
(A vacation is a must in summer.)
(However, )
(this vacation seems to be a bit off.)
(It's a strange vacation.)
(Let's see what kind of a race unfolds today!)
(L Game Park in Jung-gu, Seoul)
This place is incredible.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - Seok Jin,
you don't have a lot of people to greet, do you?
I said hello to Chan Hee!
You should have said so.
The young staff members were surprised.
- Are you teasing him already? - I know.
I don't want the staff members to be uncomfortable.
You should have said, "Hello, Chan Hee."
Have you ever been beaten up in the morning?
(Do you want a taste?)
I don't eat sweets in the morning.
(I refuse to take your Honey Punch.)
Seok Jin has Honey Punch. You don't eat sweets in the morning.
Seok Jin turned red.
- Seok Jin turned red. - That was a good one.
I didn't expect that reply.
You didn't, did you?
What is this?
- Are you wearing this today? - We're on a vacation, right?
- Are you wearing this today? - Doesn't it scream vacation?
- Aren't you going to change? - What? This is my outfit.
I saw the same outfit in "Mom's Diary".
- The shoes changed. - It's a look for a vacation.
- He is wearing a hat. - Don't people dress like me?
Your outfit is the most out of place.
You can't tell from the front. From the side,
the outfit is quite revealing.
- Seriously. - The viewers can't see it, but...
Don't you know Jong Kook does that? One time, I felt like...
his muscles were staring at me.
I have a fear of edges.
Jong Kook, Yoo Seok is wearing a much better outfit today.
(Jong Kook, Yoo Seok is wearing a much better outfit today.)
(This is how nice I look.)
Yoo Seok looks like a celebrity.
- He looks neat. - He has blonde hair, too.
(Let's dress more like a celebrity next time.)
- Today... - Are we going somewhere?
- It's hot these days, right? - Yes.
It's more than just hot.
It's so hot that there are no mosquitoes.
Today, we will comfort your tired bodies and minds...
- with a vacation. - Okay!
- A vacation is a must in summer. - We will get to play.
We should go somewhere cool.
However, the decisions will be made by the unlucky members...
in Unlucky Vacation.
Unlucky Vacation?
(Running Man has an amazing history of unluckiness.)
(Today, everything about the unlucky members is revealed.)
(Let's see what happens in the end.)
Does that mean this is Lee Kwang Soo Special?
You are in no place to say that.
Seriously. You are in no place to say that.
- Someone else should say that. - For goodness' sake.
For goodness' sake.
The unlucky members of Running Man will be divided into two teams.
The winning team of each round wins a point...
and the right to pick a penalty for the losing team...
that fights fire with fire.
- It's a team competition. - However,
both teams will spin a roulette. One person from the losing team...
- will be exempt from the penalty. - Exempt?
One person from the winning team...
will carry out the penalty.
This is hardcore.
Not many people will be exempt. Wouldn't it be too hard...
to fight for one spot? Even in a winning team,
the unlucky members will end up getting picked for the penalty.
- The competition will be fierce. - It will be.
Before the race begins, you will pick your partners.
I need to be in a good team.
(The box of fate decides the unlucky and lucky members.)
(An unlucky member and a lucky member get matched.)
If you think you are unlucky, move to the left.
If you think you are lucky, move to the right.
I can't lie about this.
(He admits that he is an unlucky member.)
- Why? Why am I unlucky? - Hey, hey.
- Come here. - Come here.
(I am not unlucky.)
- Go. - All right.
Let's do this objectively.
Who went to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?
Go.
- Who went to Australia? - Crocodiles.
Who went wing walking? Come here.
- We need to be objective... - Ji Hyo!
- about this. - We are set.
I won't be picky. I will pick the rope in front of me.
(The lucky member pulls the rope to choose the unlucky member.)
- Are you going to choose that? - I will choose the yellow rope.
- Ji Hyo, let's partner up. - I don't want Se Chan.
We will be couples now.
- Ji Hyo or Jong Kook. - You should go first.
(Ji Hyo picks the unlucky member.)
- Come on, Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo, let's partner up.
Pull.
- It'd be nice to be with Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- Hey, Jae Seok. - Jae Seok.
- Ji Hyo. - Is it me?
What are you doing?
- What do you mean? - Come on.
- The line was loose. - What do you mean?
- You were miming. - I do mime these days.
- You were miming. - I do mime now.
- Your acting got better. - She's pulling. Here she goes.
(Which unlucky member has Ji Hyo chosen?)
It's me!
(It's Kwang Soo.)
Okay.
- Hey, he's pretending to be happy. - No, I'm happy. I'm happy.
- She hit you. Kwang Soo... - Listen.
- does this when he's faking it. - No, no.
- Jong Kook's next. - No, I never thought I'd get her.
- Let's pair up, Jong Kook. - Hey, on a day like this,
- I want Haha or Jong Kook. - My hands are lucky.
(Which unlucky member will pair up with Haha?)
(It's Seok Jin.)
Oh, no. What will we do?
(The first thing he says after pairing up is...)
(Oh, no. What will we do?)
This isn't that bad. It's not.
Sure.
- I don't think you're that happy. - Let's pretend.
- You were pretending, right? - They haven't paired up before.
- Hey, I know you're pretending. - Keep pretending.
Then two of you should pull at the same time.
- Okay. - Please! Please.
- One of them will be lucky. - Hey.
- Jong Kook, pull mine. - What did you say?
- Look at him. - We should pair up today.
- Wait, it's been a while. - It's because...
You know about So Min, right? You know whom she wants, right?
- Who is it? - It's Se Chan.
Do you want me or him? Who is it?
No, I want Jong Kook.
- Of course, I want Jong Kook. - He's uncomfortable.
- Wait. - All right.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
Okay, I got you, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan form Protruding Mouth Brothers.)
So Min is pairing up Jong Kook.
(This means...)
- Great! - She's faking it.
- She's acting. - Why are you acting?
Both of them were acting.
But you know what?
- I'm at ease. - For today's outfits,
you can either wear a cool, sailor outfit...
or animal pajamas.
- I know the animal pajamas. - They are really hot.
(It'd be a disaster if we get the pajamas.)
The first unlucky member,
Kwang Soo, will choose the outfit for his couple.
Whatever he chooses,
- I'm sure he'll get the pajamas. - It's D.
(Will he be able to dodge the animal pajamas?)
He resembles cutlassfish a lot.
(Since you're a fish, get cutlassfish pajamas.)
Come on, I have to carefully choose my outfit.
I'll go with C. I choose C.
(He chooses C without giving it much thought.)
Hold on, Kwang Soo. Are you sure that's what you want?
- I'm sure. Trust me just this once. - Really?
- Wait. - Lucky members.
Trust this unlucky one.
- Sure. - Let him go.
(This lucky member is doubtful, and this unlucky member is certain.)
- Get the pajamas. - Get elephant pajamas.
(With their fates tied together, they are in the same boat.)
(What has Kwang Soo chosen this time?)
- Okay! - He got the animal pajamas.
(He just screams first.)
Nice job, Kwang Soo.
(I knew it.)
This was expected. This was an obvious one.
How can you do this? How can you pick only bad ones?
- What is that? - Gosh, they'll be hot.
That's a panda.
- What's next to the panda? A bear? - This is so fascinating.
What is this?
(Is that a polite joey that's making a right-angle bow?)
- This startled me. - It startled me.
What is this? This completely startled me.
- I was so startled. - It startled me too.
- What is this? - It could've been bad. Lift it.
- Hey. - Lift this thing here.
- When you lift this... - That's not the point.
- This is a kangaroo. - Lift this.
Gosh, I was so startled.
It's so hot in here. My face is turning red.
- Stay out of this. - It surprised me.
I was so startled.
I thought that was the back, but I saw the tail on the back.
(The front and back sides are both adorable.)
(Unlucky Kwang Soo ends up choosing cute pajamas.)
Kwang Soo, how could you get that?
- So Min will go second. - Wait.
She'll go next?
- For her, what animal pajamas... - So Min.
- So Min, don't be nervous. - You have no choice. Take that one.
Jong Kook keeps telling me that it'd be fine,
but why do I feel like it wouldn't be?
Today, I picked you. Nothing can top that.
(Just do whatever you want.)
- He doesn't mean it. - There you go.
- Take that. - D, D. No, not that one.
(4 members in the same outfits will form a team.)
- Go for it. Do whatever you want. - D.
(If she chooses pajamas, they'll pair up with Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo.)
(So Min chooses A.)
(Will So Min and Jong Kook be able to avoid wearing the pajamas?)
(Jackpot! She gets short-sleeved, sailor outfits.)
(That's it! What a nice choice!)
Did they get the summer outfit?
Good job.
(Jong Kook and So Min pick the sailor outfit.)
- Are you that happy? - Yes.
- Okay. - What a relief.
Okay! This is awesome.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin will open the lockers at the same time.
- Jae Seok, get D. Choose D. - What?
- D. I want D. Let me take D. - No, I'll choose D.
(Lucky Se Chan recommends choosing D.)
- Play rock-paper-scissors for it. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok will take D as he wins the rock-paper-scissors.)
Okay, you won.
So Min was between A and D.
- Let him slap you to play again. - Okay!
(Don't give up just yet.)
- Let him slap you to play one more. - Stop it, you punk.
- You little runt. - Okay, okay.
Do you think I won't do that?
- Seok Jin might really do it. - Do you think I won't do it?
- Hey, hey. - He will really do it.
Seok Jin will follow on it.
- Hey, stop that. Stop it. - You think I won't do it?
I'll switch.
- Okay. I'll switch with yours. - Okay.
He desperately wants that one. I'm confident about my choice.
Are you sure? Gosh, I think he should've gone with D.
- It's this locker. - Please!
- 1, 2, - My instincts told me.
- Three. - Please!
(Which one of these teams will end up wearing the animal pajamas?)
(Whatever happens, we can't wear the animal pajamas.)
- Okay! - Yes!
- Three. - Please!
(Seok Jin and Haha get the sailor outfit.)
Just as I expected.
(It was a nice choice.)
I told you to go with D.
- I should've just gone with that. - Exactly.
I changed at the last minute.
(Sailor outfit: Haha, Seok Jin, So Min, and Jong Kook)
(Animal pajamas: Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
- By the way, you look cute. - It's cute.
- You wear these then. - Do you want to switch?
- It's beyond your imagination. - It's really hot.
We have invited guests...
who will join you on your unlucky vacation.
They are two beautiful ladies that everyone wants to...
go on vacation with.
- Two guests? - Beautiful ladies?
- Beautiful ladies? - Come on!
The first beautiful lady will come out now.
Ta-da.
(Who's this lady that came out with cute entrance sounds?)
(The prettiest, unlucky member, Jennie of BLACKPINK)
- My gosh, Jennie! - Jennie!
Jennie!
(Whenever she made a decision, it was always a dud.)
(As she was unluckier than Kwang Soo, she wrote a new history.)
(Pretty, unlucky gem of variety shows whom Running Man discovered)
(To join the meeting of unlucky members, she visits again.)
Jennie is back again.
- Jennie. - What a surprise.
- Jennie. My gosh, Jennie. - Hello.
- You look so pretty as usual. - Jennie.
- Oh, my goodness. - Hello.
(Blocking any possible contacts)
(That won't work. How dare you?)
This is amazing.
(He's boiling with anger. What's wrong with Jae Seok?)
- You look so pretty. - This is amazing.
(They haven't changed.)
(Jennie's entrance is enough to get things heated on the set.)
Tell you what. Jennie...
- and Kwang Soo went into the room. - That's right.
- It went viral. People became fans. - The whole country became her fans.
(Jennie's visit to the horror room stirred up a sensation in Korea.)
(This is scary! There's a person in here!)
(In the beginning, she said she'd take the lead and acted all tough, )
(but she stayed in the back and ended up crying that day.)
(A bigger coward than Kwang Soo had been introduced.)
- Honestly, I easily get scared. - Right.
But I wasn't as bad as she was.
- It was really scary. - I had no time to get scared.
When I was about to get scared, she started screaming.
I was about to get scared.
- My gosh. - Goodness, Jennie.
- I didn't know that I got... - Is that so?
- scared that easily. - You didn't know?
I was...
(Screaming)
(All of a sudden, he quietly approaches her...)
(and scares her.)
- What's wrong with him? - What are you doing?
- Have you gone mad? - What was that?
- Jennie, are you all right? - He must've lost it.
- He scared me out of my wits. - Have you gone mad?
- Viewers want to see this. - Seok Jin. Your face turned red.
- Remember it was all me, viewers. - Your face turned red.
Viewers, I did it.
- You went too far. - What's up with this guy?
I was about to do a knee strike.
My goodness, he's unbelievable.
(Feeling embarrassed)
We'll introduce the second beautiful lady.
Is there one more?
(Who is it? Come on out, beautiful lady!)
It's Jin Ki Joo.
(The second beautiful lady shyly shows herself.)
(A multi-talented, beautiful lady, Actress Jin Ki Joo)
(She's sweeping the screens as she claims a crown for romance dramas.)
("Jin Ki Joo with a Cute Smile Rules the Wed-Thurs Drama")
("Jin Ki Joo Gets a Wide Array of Offers for Different Genres")
(She's planning to rule Running Man with her aura that brings luck.)
You're joining us today, Ki Joo.
- It's nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Hi, Ki Joo. - Hello.
- Gosh, today, - Hi.
- we have great guests. - My gosh.
This is your first time on a variety show.
- Introduce yourself to the viewers. - Right.
I've never been in front of so many cameras like this.
- I bet. - It's my first time.
But all these cameras aren't filming you.
(Don't you worry.)
(Just be yourself.)
- Why did you say that? - She might get the wrong idea.
- They're not all filming you. - They're filming her.
Okay. Let me start again. Hi, my name is Jin Ki Joo.
I don't know what to do since it's my first time here.
But I'll just have fun here today.
- She's charming. - She's charming.
She's perfect to go on a vacation with.
Why did you give us pajamas on a day like this?
- Jennie is famously unlucky. - She's "famously unlucky".
But is she also known for that?
Ki Joo is known to get very lucky.
I knew that about her.
Every time she takes a test,
- she always passes. - Really?
It all started with...
- her test with Samsung. - Samsung?
- She passed and was hired. - My gosh.
She worked at the company for three years.
But did you resign from that company?
Yes.
- Why did you do that? - She quit the company.
- She quit the company. - She quit?
- After that, - Really?
She passed the test to become a reporter.
She worked as a reporter for three months.
That's a short career.
If she worked for three months, isn't it more like a part-time job?
- She quit that job too. - Why? Why did you quit?
- She applied to be a supermodel. - No way.
- Really? - A supermodel out of nowhere?
(Strangely, she passed every test.)
And she came in third place at the supermodel competition.
- She came in 3rd place? - You were in 3rd place?
- You came in third place? - She was a supermodel.
(She has a close tie with the number 3.)
- And then she became an actress. - What?
She is lucky,
but she can't stay at one place for a long time.
(She is a vagrant.)
- Exactly. - She wanders around.
- Kind of. - She wanders around.
Next year, if I look for an apartment,
she might be the realtor.
(What will her next job be?)
Hold on.
- How can you... - You're not leaving...
around lunch time today, are you?
She might leave after three hours.
Ki Joo. It was 3 years, 3 months, and 3 days. Is it 3 hours this time?
- That'd make sense. - Three hours.
It's 2018 now.
- She's been acting for 3 years. - Really?
Are you retiring soon?
- That's interesting. - I'm not.
Why did you suddenly become an actress?
That was random.
As I'm a bit older now,
I finally had the courage.
(I finally had the courage to pursue my dream.)
- But... - But...
do you have any regrets about becoming an actress?
No.
All her dramas have been successful so far.
That's right.
She is lucky.
She's only been in famous dramas.
Ki Joo is...
incredible.
She is definitely lucky.
Not everyone can pass all those exams.
Jennie became a new member...
of the unlucky club.
- She thinks it's Kwang Soo's fault. - I'm sure.
You've never thought you're unlucky...
in your life?
I'm very lucky.
She's so shameless. She keeps saying that.
All unlucky people think...
they're lucky.
Seriously.
I win at rock-paper-scissors every time.
- I'm the luckiest in our team. - Really?
Why don't you two play rock-paper-scissors?
- Try it. - With Ki Joo.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jennie loses.)
- See? - Is this your first time?
You just lost for the first time, right?
- Jennie. - This is my first time.
- It's like she's possessed. - You're right.
Kwang Soo is dangerous.
- It's not my fault. - It lasts long too.
How can she be rescued? Is there a way?
She'll stay this way forever.
My goodness.
That's a problem.
The guests will pick a team too.
- In each box is... - I see.
Either a sailor outfit or animal pajamas.
Jennie will make a choice first.
You can choose whichever you want.
I'll choose this one to be on this team.
Ki Joo's eyes have been on this one.
(The other box becomes Ki Joo's.)
All right, Ki Joo.
- Please. - Jennie...
- One... - Let's see.
(They'll open the boxes at the same time.)
- Two. - Please.
Three.
(Who will be sweating all day...)
(along with Jae Seok, Se Chan, Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo?)
(Animal pajamas or a sailor outfit?)
(Who will be wearing what?)
Gosh.
(Jennie chooses animal pajamas, and Ki Joo, the sailor outfit.)
- Hold on. - It's unbelievable.
- Jennie is incredible. - How can this be possible?
You're unbelievable.
Never blame me again.
You really are lucky.
- You're lucky. - Never blame me again.
(The teams are decided.)
Let's start the game after they change.
(Sailor outfit: Haha, Seok Jin, Ki Joo, So Min, and Jong Kook)
(Animal pajamas: Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Jennie, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
(The guests change into shark pajamas and a sailor outfit.)
I look like a baby shark.
She's so cute.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
Jennie looks so cute in the pajamas.
These pajamas are for someone like Jennie.
(Dancing)
- You look very cute. - She looks so cute.
Kwang Soo, why are you standing next to her?
- Why are you standing next to her? - Hey!
- I can't believe you. - Jennie stood next to me.
She stood next to me.
Cut it out. Come here.
- Go away. - Why are you in the middle?
- Exactly. Since when? - Why are you doing this?
He's never stood in the middle.
- He wants to be in the middle. - It's okay.
Go to the end.
He told me to go to the end.
(He is pushed away.)
- Are you okay? - Yes.
All right, the first mission,
Game of Unlucky Thrones﻿, will begin now.
- Game of Unlucky Thrones﻿. - Game of Unlucky Thrones﻿.
The first game is called Unlucky Couple Touch.
Unlucky Couple Touch?
In 1 of these 2 boxes is...
a specially-made, couple t-shirt.
In the other box is a normal t-shirt.
You'll choose a box randomly...
and wear the t-shirt in the box while playing the game.
The team with the highest score wins.
(The team with the highest score will win.)
(To win, you have to avoid the couple t-shirt.)
One person from each team...
- will pick a box. - Jennie will do it.
Jennie is unlucky too, right?
Then...
So Min, you pick a box.
So Min has been doing well.
I'm at least luckier than Jennie.
- That's right. - You can beat her.
- Right. - Jennie is...
Jennie will be unlucky this time too.
I choose this one.
This one?
- Me? - You can choose one first.
- You want this one? - I want this.
- I think this one is a good one. - Really?
She changed her mind.
- She changed her mind. - Then I'll choose this one.
Jennie chose this one.
1, 2, 3.
Jennie wanted this one.
(One is a normal t-shirt, the other one is a couple t-shirt.)
- They look the same. - That one looks thicker.
You never know. Unfold it.
(Who is unluckier?)
That one is thicker.
- Yes! - I can't believe it.
- Jennie is so unlucky. - How can this happen?
(Then...)
How can this be possible?
- Jennie... - Seriously...
I can't believe it.
You found the perfect guest.
She's even stubborn.
I'm losing my confidence.
Kwang Soo, do you want to be Jennie's partner?
- Go. - What am I supposed to do?
- You two... - You look so happy.
(Why are you smiling?)
He smiled, saying, "What am I supposed to do?"
- I can't let him do this. - No.
- He looks too happy. - No!
- I can't stand it. - I just...
- I can't stand it. - What are you talking about?
- Ji Hyo should do it. - What did I do?
- Ji Hyo should do it instead. - Because of you...
- It was so annoying. - Why?
He should have been honest.
"Me?"
- But he was like, "Me?" - It's not okay.
- It was so annoying. - No!
Kwang Soo, do you want to be Jennie's partner?
What am I supposed to do?
(He pretends to be indifferent.)
It was so annoying.
- Ki Joo, right? - Yes.
(Determined)
- See? - Ki Joo too?
Just a bit.
- A bit, right? - A bit.
I'll give you another chance.
- You hid your feelings, right? - Do a good job.
Kind of.
- Kind of? - Yes.
I'll give you another chance.
Well... Kwang Soo, do you want to play?
- Me? - Yes.
(Indifferent)
Kwang Soo, do you want to play?
(Me?)
- Hey! - What? Wasn't it natural?
- Wasn't it natural? - What did you think, Jennie?
Jennie agrees.
- It was annoying, right? - A bit.
- What are you talking about? - It was so fake.
- Just be happy. - Be real.
I just want you to be natural.
- You should have done this. - Yes.
- You should've been... - You expect me to dance?
Just be natural. This is your last chance.
- This is your last chance. - Okay.
(This is his last chance.)
Kwang Soo, be Jennie's partner.
(Do you want to be Jennie's partner?)
- Okay! - There you go.
- This is it. - Okay!
(Is this miracle really happening to me?)
- This is it. - It was natural.
(Come here, Jennie!)
(His reaction finally feels natural.)
- It's so natural. - He threw the kangaroo.
- It's a lot more natural. - It's natural, right?
- Yes! - It's so natural.
- This is it. - This is it.
- Now we can move on. - It was nice.
This is it. Ki Joo, was it okay this time?
- Yes, I approve. - You approve?
I can see that she used to be a reporter.
- Exactly. - Hold on.
What would you write about Kwang Soo's reaction?
(She was a reporter for 3 months.)
"Fake"?
(Reporter Jin's exclusive and simple summary)
- It was annoying, right? - Yes.
("Is Kwang Soo's Fake Reaction Really Okay?")
Who will play against them?
Ki Joo should go.
Yes. Let's do that.
(Reporter Jin versus Unlucky Jenny)
(Ki Joo is happy to be wearing a normal t-shirt.)
What should I do?
Kwang Soo.
- Should you get in first? - Put your arm in.
(She puts on the t-shirt.)
- The height difference is so big. - Jennie is...
a good dancer, so I think she'll be good at it.
- I think I'll be good at it. - Right?
- Put your arm through the hole. - My arm?
(That's where Kwang Soo's head is supposed to go.)
- Her arm is supposed to go there? - You can...
- put your head through here. - What is this?
Put your head through here.
- This is where my arm should go. - What are you doing?
(Jennie's masked fan is arrested.)
- What is this? - Stay there.
This is not the right way.
(Screaming)
You can stay there.
- I can't see anything. - It doesn't matter.
- As long as we can see Jennie. - I need to see.
We just want to see her.
- I think he can see. - I can't see anything.
- You can see, can't you? - We just need to see her.
I actually can see.
All right.
(Will they be able to play the game in this t-shirt?)
Put your head through here.
- You should lock arms. - I'm in trouble.
- Take my arm. - Don't hold hands.
- Hold on. Don't take his arm. - Don't hold hands.
Don't take his arm.
It was the staff's decision.
- Put your hand behind your back. - Why?
(Screaming)
Put your hand behind your back.
- It's just a rule. - You can't hook arms.
- Put your hand behind your back. - Put your hand behind your back.
Jennie, what do you want to do?
- Do you want to hold hands or not? - Why would they hold hands?
I want to put my hand behind my back.
(Determined)
That's what I want too.
(Let's do this.)
"I want to put my hand behind my back."
(I'm just happy we're partners.)
(They're putting their hands behind their backs.)
- Kwang Soo, you can do this! - Okay.
We might have an advantage.
(They have to overcome their disadvantage with teamwork.)
Kwang Soo, use your legs too.
- Like this? - Yes.
Here it comes.
(To win, they have to burst more candies than the other team.)
No!
(Screaming)
(Clumsy)
My goodness. We're doomed.
- It's over. - I can already see the comments.
Focus, Kwang Soo!
No!
(Kwang Soo doesn't care about his partner.)
Kwang Soo, cooperate with your partner.
- Gosh. - Jennie.
You go first.
Consider Jennie more than yourself.
(Team Ki Joo is guaranteed to win.)
Your team won't win.
- All right. Jennie. - We got it.
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - Break the pumpkin.
You have to score a lot now.
Break the pumpkin.
(They go crazy during their last chance.)
(Their mood changes all of a sudden.)
- Okay. - If...
(Their last chance is up.)
- It's 300. - They scored over 300.
They're in 10th place.
(Sadly, they score only 424 points.)
Why did you concentrate on Jennie, Kwang Soo?
You should concentrate on the game. Why did you keep looking at her?
Jennie, what happened?
It's because of Kwang Soo.
What? What do you mean?
- "It's because of Kwang Soo." - I broke all of them.
Jennie, tell us. Didn't you explode the bombs too?
- He pushed and pulled me. - Is that so?
It wasn't Jennie. It's because he pulled her.
She blames others so much.
It's extreme.
She gives a lot of excuses.
I hope Jennie won't call Kwang Soo by his name anymore.
I hope she calls him "mister".
- Just call him Mr. Lee. - Call them mister.
- Don't call him Kwang Soo. - Call him Mr. Lee Kwang Soo.
He isn't her senior.
- This is Mr. Yang. - Me?
- I'm sensitive about that. - "Mr. Yang"?
(She's sensitive about the name Mr. Yang.)
You feel sensitive?
Thank goodness. I'm safe since you feel sensitive about Mr. Yang.
- She's sensitive about Mr. Yang. - I'm thankful to him.
- Yang. - Yang.
(Jennie and Kwang Soo score 424 points.)
- Complete it. - Do it.
You can do it, Jin Ki Joo.
Go, go, go. Work harder.
- That's right. - Use both hands.
- She's good. - She is.
Do it faster. Go to both sides. Left and right.
That's good. It's over there.
Using both hands is good.
- Come on. - Hurry.
- Go lower. - This is so funny.
(All the candies disappear like magic.)
- That's right. - She's good.
- Hurry and break more. - Break that pumpkin.
Do it faster.
(Ki Joo shows her fancy skills as a single player.)
It's over.
(The score is announced.)
(If she scores higher than 424 points, Team Ki Joo wins.)
(What is swordswoman Ki Joo's score?)
She will win.
(She wins with a score of 770 points.)
Great job, Ki Joo.
- She did well. - She did a good job.
Okay, I agree. You did well.
- I think... - Did I do well?
Did I?
(Team Ki Joo gains 1 point.)
- Here's the second game. - Move back a little.
- Okay. - We should move back a little.
- Step back, Kwang Soo. - How far?
Step back until where?
Where? What's going on?
- There's no space. - We're shooting Running Man.
There's no space. Goodness.
The second mission is called 1-to-1 Unlucky Archer.
- I see. - Behind one wall,
there's a proper bow for playing games.
Behind another is a toy bow.
(Each team chooses randomly. The team to score the highest wins.)
(It's difficult to shoot with a toy bow.)
Okay.
- Jong Kook is good. - I'm good at archery.
Right, you're good at archery.
- Yes. - She says that she's good.
- Jennie says that she's good. - Are you really good?
I'm quite good at archery.
She's never said that she's bad at anything.
She always says that. I bet she'll do well.
She has all the qualities of an unlucky person.
- Give it a try, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- How about... Okay. - Shall I go?
It's a match between two unlucky people.
It's about who's unluckier.
I'll definitely defeat Kwang Soo. You pick first.
I pick number two.
I pick number one.
Please move the divider.
Which number do you think it is?
- All right. - Number one?
- Will it be true? - One.
Move the divider in 1, 2, 3.
(Which bow is which?)
- 3. - Jennie says it's number 1.
Okay.
(Number 2 that Kwang Soo picked is the real bow.)
- Kwang Soo. Okay. - Really?
(Everyone, I did it.)
- I must win this. - You must win.
(Is it really true?)
(We're doomed.)
- We won. - Jennie said...
- it'd be number one. - Jennie was wrong.
- She said that it was number one. - How?
Jong Kook should shoot the arrow.
- Okay. - Jong Kook should do it.
Jennie is the best on our team.
- We trust you, Jennie - We'll give her a chance.
- What do I do? - Yes.
- It's your last chance, Jennie. - All right.
I'll win this.
- Let's go, Jong Kook. - It's a knife versus a toothpick.
- We'll count. - Our team will play first.
- You get only 2 shots. - 2 shots?
Yes.
(Jennie, who claims to be good at it, shoots first.)
(This is a chance for her to regain her honor.)
(She shoots.)
Only two seconds remain.
(Jennie shoots in a stable position.)
(Will it turn the tables around?)
(It lands on the 8-point zone.)
- That was good. - She scored eight points.
That was great.
(She jumps in happiness.)
Eight points.
(Jennie's first shoot scores higher than expected.)
- That was great. - Good job, Jennie.
- You did well. - You really did it.
(Unbelievable)
- That was great. - Jong Kook.
- You can do it. - It won't be easy for Jong Kook.
- Let's go, Jong Kook. - It won't be easy.
It won't fly.
- It'll be amazing if you win. - Okay.
That's real talent.
(He feels ambitious about shooting with a toy bow.)
(It won't even fly to the target.)
(She tries to disturb him.)
(He aims his bow in silence.)
(He shoots.)
(How much will he score...)
(with his toy bow?)
(Did it land on the 8-point zone?)
He scored eight points.
- Okay. - He scored eight points.
(Jong Kook's 20 years of workout made it possible.)
- Goodness. - Did you figure out how to do it?
- Do you shoot like this? - He's so talented.
(Impressed)
(Flustered)
- My goodness. - Jennie.
- That's amazing. You must focus. - Wait.
- Score 10 points. - Let's go.
You must score 10 points.
You can't do it, Jennie. It won't work.
- Shoot a little higher than before. - It won't work.
- A little higher. - That's good.
(It's Jennie's last arrow.)
Shoot a little higher.
(Is Jennie really good at archery?)
- Shoot a little higher. - That's good.
- Okay! - Okay!
(Jennie is an ace after all.)
Nine points!
(She becomes the ace of archery by scoring 9 points.)
Nine points.
(We're proud of you, Jennie.)
- We made it. - We'll win.
- We'll definitely win. - We won.
- Stop it. - We won.
(Stop it.)
(I'm just so proud of her.)
- I'm proud. - My goodness.
- As long as he doesn't score 10. - Please.
(Team Jennie is very excited.)
(A man smiles bitterly alone.)
(How can Jennie score 9 points?)
Goodness.
You can do it.
(It's another impossible mission.)
(I believe in Jong Kook.)
- As long as he doesn't score 10. - Please.
You have a lot of time. Move it up a little.
No.
(If he scores lower than 8, Team Jennie wins.)
(It's Jong Kook's last shoot.)
(What will be his score?)
(It lands very low.)
(He scores 4 points.)
No.
(Team Jennie wins with a score of 17.)
(Did he really score 4 points?)
(Laughing)
(He's speechless.)
(Somehow, Jennie turns the tables.)
(They exaggerate their celebration.)
(They won't have another chance to enjoy sweet victory.)
We won.
(I can't believe I lost to Jennie.)
It stopped too short.
(They play the third mission.)
The third mission is called Unlucky Soccer Player.
- Okay. - It's soccer.
- Don't worry. - I'm most confident about soccer.
- We're good at soccer. - We're good.
The opposing team has two soccer balls.
We have to choose.
One of them is a real ball. The other is a heavy ball.
(One of them is filled with water.)
(Two members from each team pick a ball and play against the other.)
You can't hold them.
- Pick one, Kwang Soo. - I pick this one.
Do a heading.
(A loud thud)
(He picks a ball carelessly.)
(He falls out of frame.)
(The original, unlucky person is different.)
You must pick well.
- It's not obvious. - There's a lot of water in it.
There's a lot of water in it.
- I saw you. - It could break your ankle.
- Be careful. Shall we start? - Yes.
- Kwang Soo and I'll play. - Okay.
See who's acting.
They're nasty when they play.
- Turn around. - Turn around?
- Okay. - It's definitely not Kwang Soo's.
- 1, 2, 3. - I'm 100 percent certain.
It's not Kwang Soo's.
Do you have to hold it at that height?
- Hold it up higher. - Hey.
- Hold it up. - Which one looks heavier?
Hold it up higher.
(Which one looks heavier?)
Which one of them is acting?
- Kwang Soo. - He's pretending that it's heavy.
It must be Jae Seok's since Kwang Soo's seems heavy.
Kwang Soo's seems heavier.
(He picks Kwang Soo.)
Okay, cover us.
- Okay. - What?
- What are they doing? - I have no idea.
Wait a minute. Don't let them go.
- I'm putting it down. - Just put it down.
- The camera will film us. - Tell Jae Seok to come out.
- No. - Get away.
I'm leaving. Goodness.
I'm leaving.
- Is that allowed? - What did I do?
- Did you not do anything? - Of course not.
- You didn't do anything? - No.
You didn't?
- You have to kick this ball. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - I think that's the right one.
- I'm 100 percent sure. - It looks heavy.
It looks heavy.
(Is it filled with water or not?)
Kick hard.
I knew it.
(Kwang Soo's ball was filled with water.)
(I knew it wasn't the right ball.)
(Twitching)
(There is a sad secret behind it.)
(They were suspecting the balls got switched.)
(They were actually switched.)
(The twist of fates hits Seok Jin's ankle hard.)
The game hasn't even started yet.
- His ankle is destroyed. - His ankle...
His ankle is smashed.
- Bring my ankle back! - His ankle is completely destroyed.
Is it still there?
- Seok Jin's stylist, - Is it still there?
Please bring a new ankle!
- Seok Jin needs a new ankle. - Bring a new ankle, please.
(That's strange. It looked like the right ball.)
- Let's not cheat. - Let's not cheat.
(It was a good idea to switch the balls.)
- Let's do this. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Staring)
(Let me see.)
This is not okay.
(Jong Kook smells something fishy.)
- It's... - This is not okay.
Turn off the cameras.
(I can't stand it anymore.)
Turn them back on!
- Never turn off the cameras! - Turn them back on!
- I can't believe you. - We're shooting right now.
Don't get out of frame. Stay inside.
Go out of the frame, and you're doomed.
I can't believe you guys.
Gosh.
The score is 0 to 0 now.
This time...
- Kwang Soo. - All we need is one goal.
One goal is enough.
Does it show?
(Haha and Jong Kook show their balls.)
- Jong Kook is pretending. - It shows too much.
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
- Me? - Yes.
- Okay. - We won't see it.
I think it's Jong Kook too.
(This is their chance.)
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is bad at pretending.)
- I'll succeed. - Gosh.
What is it?
(Kwang Soo is sure.)
(What? Why is this ball bouncing?)
You wanted to let him know?
I wanted to let him know.
(Haha is worried about Kwang Soo's ankle.)
(Jong Kook's ball is filled with water.)
I want you to know before you kick the ball.
Kick the ball.
Kick it.
- Just succeed. - You can't do this.
Just succeed.
I'll just succeed.
- Just succeed. - I will.
Succeed, and you'll become a hero.
(Will Kwang Soo succeed with the ball filled with water?)
(Thump)
(The ball just rolls.)
I feel so sorry for him.
Poor Kwang Soo.
It must hurt a lot.
- Is it that hard? - We can't get the ball in the net?
- It's the last round. - Jennie, if you succeed now...
- I have to kick the ball? - Yes.
So Min and Seok Jin...
(Jong Kook is the last player on Ki Joo's team.)
(How will their second match end?)
- Seok Jin's ball looks light. - Isn't that cheating?
Before...
But it shows.
- Jennie, what's your choice? - Just follow your gut.
- My gut? - Yes.
(What is her gut feeling telling her?)
Just follow your gut.
Just follow your gut. You can't tell anyway.
That one.
- So Min's? - That one.
So Min's ball.
Jennie, this is the last round.
(Is it filled with water or not?)
- She's our last player. - Please.
- You can do this. - Let's do this.
(The team's fate depends on Jennie again.)
(You're our ace.)
(Let me kick it real hard.)
(What did Jennie choose?)
(It's the right ball?)
(Will she score a goal too?)
- Goal! - Goal!
(She reminds you of Hong Myung Bo back in 2002.)
(Jennie did it again.)
(She gets lucky at crucial moments.)
- Jennie! - Jennie!
Gosh.
- In the last round... - In the last round...
- Oh, my. - Jennie.
What's with that goalkeeper?
- He must recognize Jennie. - What's wrong?
- What's wrong with him? - He recognized Jennie.
- It's our turn now. - Jong Kook, please succeed.
Let's get extra time.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I don't think I'll succeed.
The goalkeeper must see our faces.
(Jennie's team is doing their best.)
They should show us the balls.
We can't tell whether it's a bowling ball or a soccer ball.
Let's go!
5, 4... Jong Kook.
- I'll kick Kwang Soo's ball. - Okay.
- Jong Kook. - I'll kick Kwang Soo's ball.
(Jong Kook thinks Kwang Soo's ball is the right one.)
I think it's empty.
- It's empty. - Are you sure?
I'm sure.
- The shape... - You have to succeed.
All right.
- Okay! - Let's go.
Let's do this.
(I don't know.)
(Jong Kook faced a humiliating defeat in the archery match.)
(Will he save his face this time?)
(The ball is filled with water.)
The camera got smashed.
(Instead of scoring a goal, he breaks a camera.)
We win!
(Jennie's team wins the first mission.)
(After being teased for being unlucky, Jennie surprises everyone.)
Even Jong Kook failed.
(Jong Kook loses to Jennie for the 2nd time.)
- We did it! - Good job!
As long as it ends well, it's okay.
That's right.
Is the camera okay?
Jennie succeeded, and Jong Kook failed.
The winning team should write down a penalty.
- Eat Hot Chicken Flavored Noodles﻿. - Hot Chicken Flavored Noodles.
- That sounds good. - That sounds good.
Wearing a duck-down jacket...
- With chopped chili pepper. - It sounds terrible.
- With chopped chili pepper... - Wearing a duck-down jacket...
- Hot Chicken Flavored Noodles... - With chili pepper.
- With chili pepper. - That's it.
What's that?
We're dividing up?
We must be choosing a car.
It's hot, right?
- Yes. - Definitely.
To move to our vacation place,
- you'll choose cars first. - No.
- This is so important. - This is really important.
- This is... - Please.
There are five cars.
Three of them have a lot of space and air conditioners.
(3 cars have a lot of space and air conditioners.)
They also have drivers.
In the other two cars,
you're not allowed to use the AC.
(They're not allowed to use the AC.)
(5 people have to squeeze in with no air conditioner.)
I don't believe it.
(They're horrified.)
- On a day like this... - You'd die.
It's not going to happen to me, so...
(I'm lucky.)
- You're confident. - We're not worried either.
Jae Seok is so confident.
It's going to be fun.
One unlucky member from each team...
will choose a key.
You'll move in the car you choose.
- So Min, you should do it. - You should deal with Jae Seok.
I don't think she should do it.
(Jae Seok will play against So Min.)
I should choose the opposite of what I want.
- The opposite? - I want the one in the middle.
Then you should choose the opposite?
So Min, avoid the one in the middle.
I choose number six.
(They make a choice.)
(They always choose the same thing.)
It's 1 of the 3.
Unlucky people...
Choose that one.
It's not this one.
Not this one.
(They both choose one on the other side.)
(Thinking)
(I don't think that's a good one.)
Please, So Min.
(Jae Seok changes his mind again.)
So Min, please. We have to win.
- We have to win. - That's a bad one.
- That's a bad one. - So Min, I chose it.
(So Min ends up with the one she chose at first.)
- Open the box and press the button. - I'll wait in front of the van.
Your car will light up.
(Who is the surprisingly lucky one?)
You can do this.
- It looks like a good one. - We'd die in this outfit.
Press it. You never know.
It doesn't look like a van key.
(I hope the key will open a van's doors.)
(Ki Joo's team chooses a small car.)
(The heat and disappointment make her flop down.)
- Which one is it? - The one with no air conditioner.
It's 1 in 4 now.
(It was 2 out of 5. I must be really unlucky.)
- I told you. - It's okay.
- Now, Jennie's team. - We might choose the other car.
You might choose the bad car.
When it beeps, let's get in the car right away.
It's 1 in 4 now.
(They're so ready to get in a van.)
(It's 1 bad car versus 3 good cars. Did Jae Seok make the right choice?)
- Please. - 1, 2, 3.
Did you press it?
- It's that one! - Okay!
(They choose a bad car.)
(Is this for real?)
- This is it. - It's that one.
(Did both teams really choose bad cars?)
- This is it. - What did you do?
So Min tricked us, right?
No. Try it again.
You chose the car next to ours.
- Can we check the other keys? - Go ahead.
It was this one.
- How could you choose those? - You chose the car next to ours.
(It's almost scary.)
It's unbelievable.
(It's unbelievable how unlucky they are.)
I'm so frustrated.
- You guys are so unlucky. - It's incredible.
Please get in the cars. Let's go.
Seriously?
(They move to the vacation place with no air conditioners.)
It's so stuffy in here.
- Gosh. - It's so stuffy.
(Steaming hot)
We're in the underground parking lot right now.
- Once we go out... - The sun...
- It's going to be awful. - This is not okay.
- Gosh. - Why did we end up like this?
What? It's all Jae Seok's fault.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay. We're a team.
How could So Min choose a bad car too?
How could you both choose bad cars out of five?
Gosh.
- I can't even open my eyes. - It's so hot.
- It's so hot. - Gosh.
It's so hot!
Turn on the air conditioner!
Ji Hyo, I can't.
You understand me, right?
It's so stuffy here. Jennie, go away.
- Go away! It's so stuffy. - Come on!
- Here we go! - Here we go!
Stay away from me!
Gosh, it's so hot.
(Team Ki Joo has no air conditioner either.)
It's nice to be closer to each other.
We'll become close friends today.
You would know.
As I always say, it's hot because it's the summer.
He's positive.
Jong Kook is positive.
Who is the handsomest in person?
Today?
- Today. - Among the members today.
Who looks better in person?
"In person"?
(My answer is...)
Jae Seok.
- He looks better in person? - Yes.
(Ki Joo picks Jae Seok.)
(He can't understand.)
How bad does he look on TV?
Jae Seok looks better in person?
His mouth protrudes less than on TV.
- His mouth? - Really?
See him without glasses later.
The screen makes you look 1.5 times bigger.
His teeth protrude 1.5 times more.
- Is that so? - It's like that on screen.
(What's going on with Jae Seok?)
It's so hot.
It's extreme.
Isn't it crazy?
- It's really hot. - Do you hear me?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Do you hear me? - Yes.
Is something going on?
For those who are suffering,
here's a mission where you can win a chance to use the air conditioner.
- Okay. - That's good.
You can win a chance to use the air conditioner.
- What? - A chance to use the AC.
What do we have to do?
There are five songs related to the keywords I'll give you.
"Keywords"?
Sing 1 verse from each song consecutively.
- We have to do well. - Per member in relay.
The keyword is "summer".
(Summer)
Start.
(Summer, summer)
(He starts with "Seagull in the Heat".)
(I beg you, summer)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo succeed.)
(Their fate depends on tone-deaf Ji Hyo.)
(Ice coffee is perfect for the summer)
- Is it from a commercial? - I think so.
Is that not allowed?
- Wait, are commercial songs okay? - It's still a song.
- Right? - It's acceptable.
It's acceptable.
(Sunny summer)
It's by GFriend.
(It's an idol singer-like answer.)
Okay. What's the last song?
(Naengmyeon, naengmyeon, naengmyeon)
(He sings "Naengmyeon" energetically.)
You cleared the mission.
(They win a chance to use the air conditioner.)
- Keep it on until you arrive. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank goodness.
(They remember the lyrics.)
It's so obvious.
Goodness.
Summer is included in the lyrics.
- It's so hot. - Your hand is so hot.
This is too much.
Let's see.
Read the consonants from the song lyrics.
Name the title of the song to win.
- What is it? - Wait.
(After reading the consonants, they must name the song title.)
(These are the consonants of the first verse.)
Are these the lyrics?
- It's the first verse of the song. - "It's time to say goodbye".
- No, it's not. - "Yesterday"...
- "Yesterday". - You'll start now.
Start.
Pardon?
- "It's time to say goodbye". - "It's raining".
- "Today". - "Okay"?
(Shall I start from the last word?)
- "Again". - "Again"?
(He guesses "again".)
"Now". I think it's now, right?
- Now. - Now...
- "Today"... - "Now and today".
(He makes a guess with "now" and "again".)
Isn't it "Now it's time to smile, smile again"?
That's right.
(Now it's time to smile, smile again)
(Is Jong Kook's answer correct?)
- That's right. - Right.
(Now it's time to smile, smile again)
- Right. - It's time to smile, smile again
What's the song title?
- It's "Festival" by Uhm Jung Hwa. - It's by Uhm Jung Hwa.
- "Festival" by Uhm Jung Hwa. - "Festival".
That's correct.
- Yes! - Let's turn on the air conditioner.
- Okay. - That was amazing.
- That was amazing. - Take them off, Ki Joo.
How did you know?
(Here comes the cold wind.)
- That was amazing. - It's time to smile.
- Turn on the air conditioner. - Really?
- Now it's time to smile - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Smile again now that the air conditioner is on.)
Right, this is it.
(It's a happy day because it's cool.)
- We were correct. - Open up the chest
(They head to the next destination with the air conditioner on.)
It's so cool. This is great.
It's great.
Look at the sky and enjoy the view.
Look how blue it is. The mountains look great too.
Chicken soup sounds good on a day like this.
- That would be great. - I want naengmyeon.
I'd love to eat with my feet in a stream.
No, I don't want to put my feet in a stream.
(He's starting again.)
How about a mountain stream instead?
- That's right. - Doesn't that sound good?
- Mountain streams are great. - Aren't they the same?
- No, they're different. - There should be a lot of water.
How about eating chicken soup with your feet in the stream?
- It doesn't sound good. - How about a mountain stream?
(Everyone teases Kwang Soo.)
- She prefers the mountain stream. - How far will you go?
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay.
We just don't like Kwang Soo.
We oppose everything that Kwang Soo says.
Mention something delicious. Ask Jennie if it sounds delicious.
Bibim noodles.
I don't want to eat bibim noodles right now.
(Okay, let's do it.)
How about iced coffee?
- Iced coffee? - Yes.
- You like iced coffee. - I want mixed grains drink.
- That sounds perfect. - Right?
(She agrees with Se Chan immediately.)
Doesn't mixed grains drink sound good?
That's impressive.
- Jennie sounded so natural. - I know.
- This is great. - She says her likes and dislikes.
- That's good. - She's cool.
I'm happy that I can be honest.
You're happy that you can be honest?
That's good.
Come on.
- Come on. - Come on.
Okay.
You'll be penalized even if our team wins.
We're opposed to everything that Kwang Soo says.
Okay, that sounds good.
(The car enters Yangju.)
We're finally here.
(They arrive at the house where they'll enjoy the vacation.)
You traveled far to come here.
- Did you make acrostic poems? - Did you?
Ki Joo didn't say much, but the two of them did.
They made one with my name.
(What kind of poem did they make?)
- Are you good at anything? - Do you write good acrostic poems?
I want to make an acrostic poem with Jin Ki Joo.
- What? - Give me the letters.
- "Jin". - Seriously.
- "Ki". - You're so cute.
- "Joo". - That it kills me.
(She's impressed by So Min.)
- "Kim". - Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
May I call you by your name now?
(Of course.)
- Really? - Of course.
- "Jong". - It's been awkward all day.
- That was smooth. - It was very smooth.
"Kook".
Kook.
(Kook?)
(Kook? You're cute, Ki Joo.)
- Goodness. - That's terrible.
- "Jin". - Jin Ki Joo.
- "Ki". - Stop acting cute.
- "Joo". - I'll kill you.
(Haha interrupts her.)
(That's how it ended.)
It's too difficult.
- Wasn't it good? - It was all right.
Jennie, make an acrostic poem. It's been a while.
- Jennie makes cute poems. - She's good.
She was cute.
She made one with "Lee Kwang Soo".
"Will you have a drink with me?"
(He remembers it clearly.)
(Lee)
(Now it's time that President Yang Hyun Seok will allow me.)
(Kwang Soo)
(Will you have a drink with me?)
(His heart pounds.)
I still remembered it the next day. "Did she really mean it?"
You made him misunderstand.
Be careful what you say.
- Make another one for us. - Really?
I'll make one with "Lee Kwang Soo".
Again?
- Is it his name again? - He'll misunderstand.
She's playing hard to get.
- He looks so happy. - He's happy.
- He's so happy. - He's blushing.
(He stands next to her.)
"Lee".
Now that it happened...
What?
(What is she going to say?)
- "Now that it happened". - "Now that it happened".
My goodness.
"Kwang".
- Kwang Soo. - What?
She called his name.
- "Now that it happened"... - "Soo".
(He's full of excitement.)
"Soo".
Are you free on Wednesday?
(His heart stops.)
- Aren't you busy that day? - No.
- No! - I'm completely free on Wednesday!
No way.
We'll shoot on Wednesday!
- We'll shoot on Wednesday. - Stop them.
- No. - It can't happen.
- It can't happen. - Jennie, this isn't right.
- Wait. - This is wrong.
What are you doing on Wednesday?
I have work in Japan.
(She remembers her busy schedule.)
(You're not in Korea?)
That's fine.
Cancel the shoot.
(The shoot is canceled thanks to Jennie.)
- I knew it. - That's nice.
- I knew it. - I'm not free.
She was just asking.
On Wednesday,
she needed you to run an errand for her.
I'm busy too.
- Kwang Soo might go with her. - I have things to do too.
(Let's focus on work instead.)
The second mission is called Unlucky Diggi Bang.
(Unlucky Diggi Bang)
(It's Haha's "Dang Diggi Bang".)
- That's it. - Is that it?
This mission is made up of three rounds.
The first game is called Between Hand and Face.
(Between Hand and Face)
One member from each team will cover their eyes.
Touch five members of the opposing team.
The team to guess more within three minutes wins.
We prepared various items for disguise.
We should cover ourselves.
(Wigs and mustaches are ready.)
Jennie will go.
- Okay. - Let's have Ki Joo do it.
Let's play Game of Wits to determine the order.
- Okay. - The losing team goes later.
- Okay. - Let's start.
Ready, set, go.
- 1. - 2.
Three.
(Flinching)
Four.
- 5. - 6.
- 7. - 7.
(Jong Kook, Seok Jin, and Se Chan fail at 7.)
Was it two people?
Was it 2 or 1?
- Was it 2 or 1? - Both of them. Let's try again.
We did it at the same time.
You should sit down on purpose this time.
I was looking for the right timing.
You're doing this to look clueless. It looks unnatural.
I'm not doing that. You win in this game...
if you wait until the end.
If there are over 10 people, you win for sure.
- 10 people? - 10 people.
- Let's go again. - I'm going first.
Okay. Ready, set, go.
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 7.
(There are 10 people playing.)
("You win if you wait until the end.")
- 8. - 9.
(He lost.)
(He waits until the end, and he's the only one left.)
Hey.
Seok Jin did this.
- You were doing this. - You wanted to survive.
- I shouldn't have waited. - You said you'd just wait.
They told me to. I'm so upset.
Can't I do what I want?
- Fine, let's go again. - Why can't I?
Why did you tell me to do this? I'm mad now.
I'll do what I want. What's wrong?
- Let's try again. - Why are you telling me what to do?
You said I do this to look clueless.
Why would you make me feel uncomfortable?
Seok Jin only cares about how he looks on TV.
He doesn't care if his team wins.
I didn't know this was part of the act.
- Oh, gosh. - I wanted to win.
(Team Ki Joo lost, so they dress up first.)
Seok Jin is a bit too much.
They're going that far.
Gosh, Jong Kook.
Details.
(He puts something in his mouth.)
Great attention to detail. I like the passion.
It'll be confusing between So Min and Ki Joo.
You just need to guess So Min and Ki Joo.
I think it'll be difficult.
You all look so different though.
Get ready. Ready...
(She starts exploring.)
What's this?
(So Min distracts her by biting her.)
(Something is trying to bite me.)
Hold on. I can't tell if you're male or female.
I think you're male. I don't like this.
(Coward Jennie is back.)
You bit me. Stop it.
(Hitting)
(She's a coward.)
Okay, I'm done with you.
What's this? This is not a good feeling.
(What is this curly thing?)
(Screaming)
(She doesn't feel good about what she's touching.)
(She freezes.)
(It's a person's face, Jennie.)
She's good.
(Did I make you feel bad?)
What's this? You're built.
Okay, okay.
She's good.
This is female.
Hold on. How can I tell?
It's female. She has soft ears.
How... I'll go with my gut feeling.
Here.
(He makes his cheeks skinny.)
Wait. You're making your cheeks hollow, right? This is weird.
(It's weird, )
(so she puts her fingers into his nose.)
(She's detailed. Good job.)
(She blocks his nostrils with a nasal endoscopy.)
(Happy)
(He can't breathe.)
Hold on.
Okay.
(She saves him and moves onto Haha.)
This is weird. What is this?
Why does it feel like something weird?
What's this?
You have one minute left.
(She blocks his nostrils too.)
Who are you?
She always puts her fingers in the noses.
It feels rough. What? Haha?
Hold on. You have hair.
(Pulling)
(She starts plucking hair after the endoscopy.)
I'm done.
(Jennie is done observing the 5 people.)
- Okay. - Please guess the first person.
Hold on.
Wait, I'm so confused.
(She's confused. What's her answer?)
Please guess the first person.
Hold on.
Wait, I'm so confused.
(She's confused. What's her answer?)
Please guess the first person.
(She was confused with So Min. What is Jennie's answer?)
Seok Jin?
(What?)
(How?)
Seok Jin, Jong Kook...
(She's so unlucky.)
And So Min.
(This isn't good.)
Ki Joo is here.
(She fails to guess his gender.)
How did I do?
So Haha, Ki Joo, So Min,
Jong Kook, and Seok Jin.
It's a mess.
Take the blindfold off.
(What's a mess?)
What happened?
It's a mess.
(Did I just touch that?)
- She's bad at this game. - Hey.
- Hey. - She's so bad.
How can you get Seok Jin and So Min confused?
- Jennie. - You're so unlucky.
- You're unlucky. - You touched So Min's face.
How could that be Seok Jin?
I'm so disappointed in you.
- I feel bad. - Did you think I'd bite?
She touched Seok Jin's face and said it was Ki Joo.
Why did she put her fingers into his nose?
Oh, gosh.
I'm so sorry. I couldn't see, so I lost my senses.
Did you see when she touched Jong Kook's face?
"This is not a good feeling."
Did I make you feel bad?
No. When you can't see, you lose your senses.
What now?
(It's Ki Joo's turn to guess.)
Is this how you put it on? Is this right?
(Is his how you put this on?)
- Even with the disguise, - He's laughing at himself.
- You look fine. - you still look cute.
(They're drawn to her.)
Good for you.
(They fall for her.)
She was born like that.
(Give me the mirror.)
I look like I'm doing comedy.
(Let me see my face.)
(What's this?)
- You look like a criminal. - Kwang Soo.
I looked at myself and ignored it. I didn't think it was me.
(What's that?)
(She's terrified.)
Why are you screaming? Jennie, that's not nice.
She collapsed. She looked at Kwang Soo's face.
I've seen somebody like that.
Me too. I know somebody like that.
(Somebody must look like this.)
I've seen somebody like that too.
- Get ready. - Doesn't he look...
kind of like Bbaek Ga?
- That's true. - Bbaek Ga from a while back.
Please get ready.
You have three minutes. You have to guess within that time.
Are you ready?
What's this? There were wigs too.
I can't tell if it's female or male then.
(She can't even tell the gender.)
(She's thorough. She touches his ear.)
It's male.
(Good job, Ki Joo.)
Okay. I'm okay with this person.
- Next. - Yes, that's next.
(I hope she doesn't get it right.)
(She tries to put her hand in the mouth.)
She thinks something is inside.
Your teeth...
(She has a feeling.)
I got it. Okay.
(Are we that obvious?)
Remember the order.
Goodness, this is so obvious. She's so small.
(She's good at this. She knows all of them.)
Next.
This person is trying to cover this up.
- I got it. - She knows.
This is the remaining person. I just have to confirm. Nicely?
Okay.
(She still has time, but she's done.)
First person is Kwang Soo.
Se Chan is next.
Jennie is the third person. Jae Seok is next,
and Ji Hyo. It's Ji Hyo.
(She guesses all 5 people right.)
(Team Ki Joo wins.)
We almost had it.
- You got everything? You did. - How did you get Kwang Soo?
I knew it was Jennie in one second.
Team Ki Joo wins the first round.
Second round is a team game.
- We have to win this time. - We have to win to make it a tie.
Second round is a team game. It's called Between the Cheeks.
(Second mission: Between the Cheeks)
- Between the Cheeks? - Three people...
go upstairs and present the question.
Two people stay here and try to guess the right answer.
Two people downstairs have to put blindfolds on...
and pick 1 person out of the 3 who are holding fishing rods...
with different items attached to it.
You have to feel the item between your cheeks...
and guess what it is within the time limit.
Please select who will do what.
- Okay. - We already know.
Jennie and Ji Hyo.
Jennie will go insane.
- She'll faint. - I know.
- She will. - It's scary.
- This game is for her. - We'll go with her.
(Team Jennie goes first.)
Do we pick one person and guess what their item is?
I'll let you choose.
Okay.
What are these?
- What's this? - Nose pack?
You can pick one fishing rod each.
This is hard to guess.
This is hard. How are you supposed to guess?
I don't think they'll choose me.
I'll pick the pig skin.
Okay.
(He probably won't get picked, so he chooses the pig skin.)
I don't think they'll pick me.
- They might pick you. - There's a good chance.
This one's easy.
- Is this better? - It is.
Is this easier to guess? Okay.
- Did you make your mind? - Yes.
All right. Please pick one person.
(Ji Hyo and Jennie have to pick one person.)
Oh, no.
- Oh, my goodness. - Jennie will go nuts.
I'm scared.
Number 1, 2, or 3.
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, or Se Chan.
Who shall I pick, Jennie?
(You can choose.)
(Please avoid Kwang Soo with the pig skin.)
- Who shall I pick, Jennie? - 1, 2, 3.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
(She's unlucky again.)
1, 2, 3.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
(She chooses the most difficult one without hesitation.)
Kwang Soo.
Goodness. What now?
(You said they won't pick you.)
(I know.)
(This is the unlucky synergy effect.)
She picked the worst one.
You have three minutes.
Ready,
- Hold on. When is it coming? - set...
- Tell us when it's coming. - Tell us.
(Between the Cheeks starts.)
It's coming down.
(Here comes the pig skin.)
Tell me.
Tell me when it's coming.
Hey, hey.
- Try again. - Goodness.
- How gross. - Hey, hey.
- You have to aim. - Hey, hey.
- Where is it? - No.
It's behind.
(Shrieking)
- Was that it? - It brushed past my lips.
- Here? - What will you do?
Goodness.
Hit their noses.
(It's not that bad.)
(She moves a little.)
(Screaming)
(She's about to faint.)
Jennie!
- Ji Hyo. - I can't do this.
This isn't supposed to be like that.
I can't do anything else.
- I have no choice. - Guess.
Hold on. Where is it?
(I'll put it in my mouth.)
(Shrieking)
(She'll sing better after this.)
(You scared me more.)
- Ji Hyo. - Jennie.
(It touches her slightly.)
(Wailing)
- What's this? - Ji Hyo.
Their reaction is different.
(This isn't that bad.)
Hey.
Guess.
Hold on. It's here.
That's one minute.
(They wasted 1 minute by screaming. They have to guess now.)
(They're bolder.)
(They're paying attention now. Will they get it?)
- It's sharp. Take it out. - That's one minute.
- Take it out. - Hey.
(They're paying attention now. Will they get it?)
(Licking)
What was that?
(She shakes powerfully.)
What is that by the way?
(This is not scary. They won't even get close to guessing.)
Is it a shoe insert?
(Not at all.)
- Where is it? - Oh, no.
(She reacts in 2 languages.)
(Kissing)
(They can't guess, but their cheeks touch.)
Goodness.
(What are they doing?)
No, no.
Do better. Make them guess.
- It's here. - Ji Hyo.
There.
You have 30 seconds left.
- Ji Hyo. - What's this?
- You can't put it in your mouth. - What is she doing?
- Doesn't it smell like feet? - Five,
- Is it food? - four...
- Ji Hyo and Jennie. - Please guess.
Two.
(3 minutes has passed.)
This is too hard.
- What's your answer? - This is hard.
Hold on.
My teeth are about to fall out.
Squid?
- Buttered squid? - What's this?
- Grease. - It's greasy.
Did they put grease on a shoe insert?
You're so sharp.
- Please. - Please.
It's so hard though.
- I think it's a shoe insert. - Hold on.
It might be food. Fish cake?
Fried fish cake? Fish cake.
Fish cake.
- Fish cake? It's not. - Squid?
- I have no clue. - What's your answer?
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- Fried fish cake. - Fried fish cake.
(Fried fish cake is incorrect.)
- What was it? - What was it?
- Pig skin. - It was pig skin.
(What did you say?)
(She's shocked.)
Jennie, are you all right?
- I've never had it before. - Really?
- It was her first time trying it. - Jennie reaction was intense.
- I couldn't have imagined it. - Me neither.
(Team Jennie fails.)
I'm nervous about this.
Me too.
This.
Oh, dear.
(So Min and Ki Joo will be guessing Jong Kook's item.)
(What do they have to guess?)
You won't get this.
- You'll never get this. - This is...
(They're slightly scared. What is it?)
- What is it? - Ready...
It's coming.
- Stay still. - Stay still.
Set...
(If they guess right, they get to fill the penalty list.)
If you stay still, it'll come down. Stay still.
Is it here yet?
(It's a sponge.)
- What's this? - Did something drop?
- Feel it. - Feel it.
It's on my head.
What's this?
- What's this? - Get off!
- What's this? - It feels weird.
(They're so thrilled that they do a techno dance.)
(They're such good dancers.)
You're good dancers. Ki Joo dances well.
- I can't see. - Where are you, So Min?
- Where are you? You're here. - Ki Joo.
- This item... - It feels rough.
(They hold hands together, and it starts.)
(The prickly, sponge tango)
It's your hair.
(There's no time for dancing.)
- This... - You have 15 seconds.
Do you know where it is?
- You have 15 seconds. - It's here. What's this?
A sponge?
- Is it a sponge? - It's kind of...
I think it's a sponge.
(How did she know?)
- I think it's a sponge. - Seven,
- How do you know? - six,
- A sponge. - five,
- 4, 3, - It's kind of big, right?
- I think it's a sponge. - 2, 1.
(3 minutes has passed.)
(It is a sponge.)
- What's your answer? - What do you think it was?
Don't you think it's a sponge?
(Nodding)
I think it's circular and big.
Why are you nodding when she can't see you?
(Ki Joo, why are you nodding when she can't see you?)
Oh, right. Sorry.
- What's your answer? - 1, 2, 3.
- A sponge. - A sponge.
(So Min and Ki Joo's answer is a sponge.)
Really?
- Yes. - Really?
(Sponge is correct.)
(Team Ki Joo wins round 2 as well. They win the mission.)
- So Min is good. - You're the best.
Team Ki Joo wins round two as well.
(They get to fill out the penalty list.)
Please fill out the penalty list.
What should we write?
Put the heater on and eat in the car.
Eat jjamppong.
Do what?
Put the heater on and eat jjamppong in the car.
- Don't you like jjamppong? - I do,
- but not the heater. - Turn the heater on...
Put the heater on and eat jjamppong in the car.
(Let's make sure we win the next mission.)
(Unlucky Vacation penalties)
The weather is insane.
- The weather is insane. - Hurry up.
What's wrong with this weather?
(They go to the swimming pool for the last mission.)
I'm dizzy.
Please let me go in the water.
If you put meat on the ground, it'll get cooked.
I'm going to melt.
Everybody, are you hot?
- Yes. - Yes.
This is the last mission of Unlucky Vacation.
It's Battle of Unlucky Round.
(The last mission is Battle of Unlucky Round.)
- What is it? - It sounds fun.
Each team has two people who are bombs.
Through a tube stealing game, the team with more bombs left win.
(There are 2 less tubes than the number of people.)
The bombs have to survive?
- They do. - What's a tube stealing game?
Each team will be dancing to the music...
and at the whistle, get on a tube.
If you can't get on the tube, you're out.
If both bombs are out, your team loses.
- This is clean. - We have Jong Kook.
- We have to avoid him. - Okay.
- There are two bombs in the hats. - What kind of hats are these?
Don't flip it.
- What kind of hats are these? - There are bombs inside.
- You do it. - I'll take one.
- Should I take one? - You should.
Okay, I will.
They might stick to me.
(Team Ki Joo's 1st bomb is Jong Kook.)
Ki Joo, take the other one.
I'll take one.
What if I die?
Is it okay if I get eliminated early?
You have to have some strength to get on the tubes.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes, Kwang Soo.
I'll protect you the best way I can.
- Ji Hyo or Jennie can take one. - Jennie.
- I think I'll get eliminated. - It's okay.
- We'll protect them. - The three of us.
(The bombs are Ki Joo, Jong Kook, Jennie, and Kwang Soo.)
This is the 1st round. There are 10 people...
and eight tubes.
Music start.
- Cue. - Start.
(You have to put your bombs on the tubes and not the other team's.)
(This is my song. Let's go, "Dang Diggi Bang".)
(This is fun.)
(He's energetic, and he's going crazy.)
(Hello, this is Haha of rookie group RPR.)
What are you doing?
(Promoting his song is 100 times more important than the mission.)
He doesn't dance like that. Why is he trying so hard?
(So Min joins him.)
So Min.
- Here she is. - So Min joined.
Let's play.
(This is the highlight.)
(Is this Jamaican?)
(He's out of breath.)
(The pool is heating up with the reggae party.)
(The game starts.)
(They gather around the tubes on opposite ends.)
(Is that Jong Kook?)
(I'm going to run away.)
(All 4 people sit down peacefully where Jong Kook is.)
No, no.
(Chaos breaks out at the tube without Jong Kook.)
No. No.
No, no.
Move out of the way.
(Ki Joo falls into the water.)
- I am going to climb up. - There is no space.
- Hey! - 30 seconds remain.
(So Min and Ki Joo are at a danger of being eliminated.)
So Min, get Jennie!
(So Min charges towards Jennie at the other tube.)
What should I do?
- You need to hang in there! - My goodness.
So Min is scary!
(The tiger moth is determined.)
Jennie!
(Jennie can't be eliminated since she is a bomb.)
Ki Joo, come here!
Ki Joo, come and sit here.
Hey, So Min.
(Meanwhile, Ki Joo fights hard...)
(by herself.)
Hey, Ki Joo!
(She drags the tube with four men.)
No!
Hey, Ki Joo.
(Ki Joo is about to get eliminated.)
Ki Joo, come here! Come here!
Ki Joo, come and sit here.
Hey, So Min.
(Let's pluck Jennie out of the tube.)
- No! - So Min.
- In 4, 3, - Come on, Jennie.
- two, - No!
- one. - Okay.
She did it!
(Jennie manages to keep her spot.)
Jeon So Min and Jin Ki Joo are out.
(Jeon So Min and Jin Ki Joo are out.)
You need to play harder!
Why is my team so foolish?
- Seok Jin, did you survive? - Yes, I did.
- The two women are out. - Why didn't you give her your seat?
What?
(Even when Ki Joo was close to getting eliminated, )
(Seok was busy securing his seat.)
(While the others used their bodies, he used his mouth.)
(I survived.)
We will reveal the identities of the two eliminated members.
- Okay. - It's okay.
(She is depressed.)
Ki Joo is out.
(We have one bomb.)
- We need to get one more. - How could you let this happen?
You fools!
I didn't think about that.
- Reveal her identity. - They focused on saving themselves.
I didn't think about...
- who the bomb is. - Instead of saving the bomb,
they focused on saving themselves.
Jong Kook is really angry.
You should remind me at every mealtime.
In their team,
(I am forgetful.)
- Jennie is a bomb. - For sure.
(He is sharp.)
Ji Hyo offered to give up her seat.
- Really? - Why didn't our team do that?
There are 8 people and 6 seats now.
Music, please.
(My team loses if I get eliminated in this round.)
(The song is...)
("Ddu-du Ddu-du" by BLACKPINK.)
BLACKPINK!
(When Jennie shoots, )
(the fans shoot together.)
(The atmosphere is heated up.)
(She suddenly shows a high-quality body roll.)
(As everyone falls for BLACKPINK's swag, )
(Round 2 starts.)
(Jong Kook the bomb gets the tubes.)
(Haha and Seok Jin attack Jennie.)
All right. Keep her away from the tubes.
Come on.
Jennie must be a bomb.
Come here, Jennie.
(Jennie, here are empty tubes.)
(Jennie escapes from the battlefield...)
(and Haha gets a tube.)
- All right. - Get your head into the tube.
Jennie, get into the tube.
Hurry up, Jennie.
Hurry up and come on in.
- Okay. - Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo, come here.)
In 5, 4,
- three, - Come on.
- two, - All right.
One.
(Ji Hyo sacrifices herself to save Se Chan.)
- Se Chan. - Good job.
Song Ji Hyo and Yu Jae Seok are out.
It's a tie now.
Good job.
What is wrong with you?
(Haha runs out of energy.)
(What is wrong with him?)
What is wrong with him?
Please play "Dang Diggi Bang" one more time.
"Dang Diggi Bang".
That's right.
(Only "Dang Diggi Bang" can save Haha.)
(Running...)
(and bumping into people...)
(are exhausting for Haha.)
(Promoting "Dang Diggi Bang" is his medicine.)
It's "Dang Diggi Bang"!
(Staggering)
(He suddenly changes.)
(His energy gets restored when "Dang Diggi Bang" comes on.)
(The other team is moved by his undying passion.)
I don't think this song has a dance routine.
I think it does.
(Of course there is a dance routine.)
(Even though it's made-up, it's addictive.)
It's coming!
Move out of the way!
That's it!
(His passion never goes away.)
Let's go! Let's go!
(His energy goes away when his song gets turned off.)
Now, there are six people...
and four tubes.
(A bloody battle for the 4 tubes starts.)
Here he comes.
No!
This is driving me crazy.
(Haha gets eliminated with Se Chan.)
What?
(Dry heaving)
(Are you tired? When you are dry heaving...)
Please play "Dang Diggi Bang".
Let's have a concert.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(It's time for everyone to restore their energy.)
Let's go!
(He transforms.)
(Shake it, shake it.)
(He is a reggae zombie.)
Haha!
(They say singers' lives follow their songs.)
(Haha jumps until his blood sugar level drops.)
(Reggae zombie is exhausted.)
There are four people...
and two tubes.
This may be the last round.
All right. Play the music.
(With 2 tubes, this may be the last round.)
Go to the right!
Go to the left!
(They move from side to side like they are at a festival.)
(Everyone looks cute and cheerful.)
Go to the right!
(It's the whistle sound.)
(The fight for tubes starts.)
(Landing)
Come on.
Jong Kook, hang in there!
- Flip it. There you go, Jennie. - Jong Kook!
(They try to flip Jong Kook's tube.)
Be careful. Look behind you.
Get on the tube.
- Come on. - Did Kwang Soo give up?
That's right. Get Jennie on the tube.
In 7, 6,
- Flip the tube! - five...
(Kwang Soo succeeds to flip the tube the 2nd time.)
(Everyone falls into the water.)
- Get on the tube. - Get on, Jennie.
- Get on the tube. - You need to get on, Jennie.
- Get on. - What is wrong with him?
He is holding the tube!
Get on quickly.
I am not on the tube yet.
(He is frightening.)
- I don't know what to do. - What is going on?
2, 1.
(Battle of Unlucky Round 4 is over.)
It's over.
That's good.
The winner of this round...
could be the final winner.
The score is 1 to 1.
- Jong Kook, I am not worried. - Let's go.
Music, start.
(The last round starts.)
(It's "Twist King" by Turbo.)
(While everyone has a dance party, )
(Kwang Soo approaches the tube.)
That's good.
Go to the tube.
(After "Twist King", the match to be the king begins.)
(Hitting)
(Even when a tiger tackles him, )
(Kwang Soo calmly enters a tube.)
That's good. That's good.
Kwang Soo, you got this.
You are inside the tube.
Kwang Soo.
30 seconds remain.
My goodness.
Kwang Soo!
In 3, 2, 1.
(Both of them are inside the tube.)
- What? - One.
You did well.
Kwang Soo held on.
Kwang Soo, you did well.
- Hey. - I am anxious.
- Kwang Soo, hang in there. - Mom.
(Mom)
(Mom, he is picking on me.)
Mom.
Kwang Soo.
(He looks pitiful.)
Do they have to go again?
This is too much.
Kwang Soo, you did a good job.
Hang in there.
(Coach Jae Seok is expectant.)
- You can win. - Hang in there.
- You are almost there. - All right.
You can do this. Drink some water.
(Let's show them a groundbreaking result.)
I feel bad.
(Kwang Soo has a timeout.)
(Do you need a towel?)
- Let's take this off. - Hold on.
I can't do this.
(I can't do this.)
(He withdraws.)
I lost.
(Running over)
(Throwing)
I lost.
(I am giving back the towel.)
You can't do that.
Play the music.
(The very last round begins.)
(Red Velvet sings "Red Flavor" for a bloody battle.)
I am curious, honey!
(Cute)
Jennie is good at this.
(She shows her refreshing charms.)
She is good.
Please distract Jong Kook.
(Jennie goes to seduce Jong Kook.)
Hey!
Come on.
Distract Jong Kook.
- Okay. - Go.
Jennie, you are doing well.
(He is distracted.)
You are doing well.
(Here I come.)
(So Min's lethal seduction)
There goes So Min.
So Min.
(Throwing)
(You are only an annoyance.)
That's good. That's good.
(You're so clingy.)
Jennie, hold onto Jong Kook.
Hold onto him.
(Please get lost!)
Hey.
(Whistling)
- He picked it up. - He got it.
(When he's distracted by Jennie, Kwang Soo gets the tube.)
(If he can last in the tube, it will be Kwang Soo's win.)
(The tiger approaches him as he takes his time.)
(It's just like the previous round. Then the perfect method is...)
(forcing himself inside the tube just like the previous round.)
- No. Not this time. - 5, 4,
3...
(I can't let him beat me again. I must hold out!)
- Kwang Soo, a bit more! - Four,
- No. - three...
- 3, 2, - He did it.
(He minimizes the space inside the tube.)
- Yes! - Two...
(Team Jennie wins the Battle of Unlucky Round.)
- Kwang Soo did it! - Kwang Soo did it!
- Kwang Soo did it. - No, it was all Jennie.
- Jennie did it. - It was all Jennie.
Jennie helped us win.
The third round goes to Team Jennie!
(Team Jennie wins the whole race of the Unlucky Vacation.)
We have to wrap it up.
- Come out now. - Come on out, Haha.
(There will be a celebratory show according to the order.)
(Spouting)
(Let me put on the show for the 4th time.)
You look so cool!
(Are you ready to jump?)
Let's go!
(This reggae zombie dance is back again.)
Let's go.
(Is he shaking his bottom?)
(Mr. Lee is a zealous supporter.)
(They do a celebratory gesture for winning the game.)
(This 40-year-old singer uses up his energy when it's 40°C today.)
Go for it.
(His passionate celebratory performance is over.)
The winning team should write down the final penalty.
- All right. - No one knows who it will be.
Let's finish up.
- The last one will be the campfire. - This is crazy.
Bring in the roulettes now. These are the final roulettes.
We'll begin with drawing a member who will be...
- exempted from Team Ki Joo. - Ki Joo, you should spin it.
- My gosh. - Spin it hard.
The member who will be chosen by the roulette...
won't face the penalty today.
- Anyway... - One,
- 2, 3. - Spin it hard.
Please.
(Which lucky member will get to avoid the scorching hot penalty?)
It's me. My name is getting close.
It's Ki Joo.
(Congratulations! Ki Joo is exempted from the penalty.)
This person is exempted.
- It's Ki Joo. - Ki Joo won't face the penalty.
- Ki Joo is amazing. - She is lucky indeed.
By the way, there are three penalties today.
- My gosh. - How is this possible?
- Number three is her lucky number. - Exactly.
- This is incredible. - You're really lucky.
- That's amazing. - Oh, no. I feel bad.
- My gosh. - All right.
- This person is the unluckiest. - The worst luck.
Jennie, spin it hard. 1, 2, 3.
(Which 1 of these members will be the unluckiest?)
It's Jae Seok! It's Yu Jae Seok!
- It's Jae Seok! - My gosh.
- It's Jae Seok. - You're so unlucky.
- I expected this to happen. - Hey.
It unfolded just like how we talked about in the car.
- He's something else. - You're truly the unluckiest.
Jae Seok will have to carry out the penalty...
- with Team Ki Joo. - Come here.
- I'm so sick of these penalties. - My gosh.
- Why do I always get the penalty? - So Min surely chose a great one.
- Hey, Jong Kook. - Yes?
It's been a while since your last penalty.
- Exactly. - It's been a while for you.
- It's nice that you're joining us. - Who wants a cup of citrus tea?
- Me. - I want one, Haha.
Everyone has to drink one.
(It's boiling hot citrus tea, good for a sore throat.)
It's steaming.
Let's clink our glasses.
- Let's make this the last time. - Hey.
Let's think that it's December right now.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- We're so unlucky. - My gosh.
(As if!)
- This is too much. - We're boxers who are training...
for matches.
(2nd way of self-hypnosis)
- Why? - What?
We'll weigh ourselves an hour later.
- We must try to lose weight. - I want to fail the weight test.
- Try to pretend you're a boxer. - I'm sweating buckets.
Gosh, it's hot.
(Gosh, it's hot.)
(What was that? You said you were a boxer.)
- You looked like one of us. - It's hot.
I've never seen you like this ever since you've been on the show.
- This is annoying. Why is it hot? - That was funny.
I guess you can feel it when something is hot.
- Of course. I hate hot things. - He looked like one of us.
- I thought his skin was iron. - My gosh.
- I hate hot stuff. - "Jong Kook Was a Human After All".
- This is so hot. - Gosh, this is delicious.
My gosh, I finished mine.
- I finished mine. - Me too.
(Their summer vacation was burning hot.)
(The members of Running Man are invited to a mysterious place.)
(The moment they set foot inside, )
(they have been trapped.)
(Someone has mapped out the whole set-up.)
(A mysterious stranger is observing everything.)
(All of a sudden, the members start to disappear.)
(If you want to survive, find the architect.)
(The trap is slowly closing in on them.)
(They must find the architect to end this whole race.)
(They struggle in order to end this long race.)
(Who is the architect that planned this whole race?)
That was it.
(What's 2 plus 1?)
(It's 3.)
What is this?
(Rock and roll!)
Peace!
(Suspicious Race)