(One day in August)
(Sampe Jigu, Han River)
(A special race awaits the members.)
(Knocking)
(He is already on his guard.)
(Before the shoot begins,)
What is it?
(Jae Seok gets a questionnaire.)
- Please fill it out. - What?
Please fill it out.
What is this?
(He is on his guard.)
Kwang Soo, here you go.
(All the members receive the same questionnaire as well.)
"The Secret That Can't Be Told"?
(What is this?)
- "The Secret that Can't Be Told". - "The Secret that Can't Be Told".
"Write down the secrets you know about the members."
(You are prohibited from telling the others.)
- The members' secrets? - Yes.
(Thinking)
They are secrets for a reason.
Why would I reveal them?
You want me to tell the secrets that are true, right?
They have to be true.
If I do that, a few of them will have to retire.
What should I do? Those who will have to retire are...
Seok Jin, Kwang Soo,
So Min, and Se Chan. I can end their careers.
I won't reveal Jong Kook's secrets because he is my business partner.
(His business partner's secrets are safe.)
It's for my sake.
Gosh, how much should I reveal about Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo...)
About three days ago,
So Min...
I don't know if I should reveal it since it really happened.
(He reveals So Min's secret he witnessed 3 days ago.)
What did you write about me?
- I couldn't write anything. - What did you write about me?
- I couldn't write anything. - I protected you.
I protected you.
- Seriously, - Did you write anything down?
I wrote down a secret that can be told.
Although the questionnaire was named The Secret that Can't Be Told,
I didn't want to force you to retire.
I will make this episode...
your last episode.
Thank you for your hard work, So Min.
The female celebrity's name was...
(He reveals other members' secrets without taking a breather.)
I can write down another one, right?
Let's go down together.
(They even report real secrets that exceed expectations.)
(What is the purpose of writing down these secrets?)
- Hello. - Hello.
Please take a shot of So Min's new hairstyle.
- She got a bob cut. - A bob cut.
It's unstylish.
Seok Jin kept asking me if I couldn't wear a wig.
- I had no choice. - It suits you.
She got a haircut to play the role of an unstylish woman.
I don't see why it was necessary since she was already unstylish.
She reminds me of the countryside.
Doesn't she have many lookalikes with that new haircut?
- Who? - You know,
Kim Byung Ok in "Lady Vengeance".
- She resembles him a bit. - She does.
- She resembles Byung Ok. - She resembles him a bit.
- She does. - She does, right?
- I am so scared. - Right?
(I can contain my anger.)
- She does. - Isn't that Choi Yang Rak's hair?
(It looks familiar.)
- You are right. - "Alkkagi".
He had that hair in "Alkkagi".
- It's Yang Rak's hairstyle. - By the way...
It's Yang Rak's hairstyle.
Seok Jin leads fashion.
He is wearing Heung Bu's pants today.
(Heung Bu's pants)
(He leads fashion with Heung Bu's pants.)
- Heung Bu's pants. - That's hilarious.
I can't believe Jae Seok noticed them.
Seok Jin, show them the back of your pants as well.
(The back is worse.)
There is a patch on the back of the knee.
Seriously.
A swallow might show up today like it did in the fairy tale.
- A swallow. - A swallow might show up.
A swallow will be able to break your legs.
(Heung Bu's pants make his legs look skinnier.)
Stop it already.
This is the hobo look.
I will forgive you since it was funny.
What are we doing today?
- What are we doing today? - Yes.
You know.
- What? - You know.
(Does Jae Seok know about the race of the day?)
Is it a secret mission?
Does Jae Seok know?
Today, we will have a race Jae Seok prepared.
Did Jae Seok prepare the race?
Did you prepare the race?
Jae Seok is so mean. How could he feign ignorance...
and ask what we are doing today?
He feigned ignorance and asked, "What are we doing today?"
Hold on. The race I prepared today is...
- Tell us. - You know,
I got the idea...
from watching a movie.
"Truth or Dare".
("Truth or Dare")
- What does mean? - Don't roll your tongue.
- Isn't it a scary movie? - Yes, it is.
- I watched "Truth or Dare". - You did, right?
- It shows a strange-looking face. - You either tell the truth...
- or perform a dare. - That's right.
(You either tell the truth or perform a dare.)
That's right.
Truth or Dare.
You either tell the truth or perform a dare.
If you don't want to tell the truth, you simply have to perform a dare.
- Telling the truth will be easier. - That's right. Everyone,
do you agree to participate in this game?
(Do you agree to participate in this game?)
- Yes. - Of course. This is a shoot.
Everyone,
do you agree to participate in Truth or Dare?
1, 2, 3.
- Yes. - Yes.
- 1, 2, 3. - Yes.
(All the members agree to participate in Truth or Dare.)
That's good. Everyone agreed to participate in the game.
Why are you trying to look so cool? What are you doing?
(What are you doing?)
- Are you launching a new program? - It'll start now.
What happens if I don't agree?
- What? - What happens if I don't agree?
Then you can go home.
- Go home. - I agree to participate.
- You can go home. - No, I agree to participate.
Okay.
Truth or Dare.
Where are we going?
A moment ago,
all of you agreed to participate in Truth or Dare.
We had no choice if we didn't want to go home.
We will now begin the first game.
- Are we starting right away? - We are in a bus.
(Are we starting right away in this bus?)
- Right now? It's so soon. - In a bus?
Yes.
The first question goes to Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin's decision)
Okay.
Truth or Dare?
(Truth or Dare?)
Go for dare.
- Dare. - Then he has to perform a dare.
I choose dare.
(The first player, Seok Jin, chooses dare.)
(A dare envelope is handed to him.)
What does it say? Can you tell us?
- Can we take a look together? - "Is Your Nose Big?"
(The name of the dare is "Is Your Nose Big?")
"Put a 10-cent coin in your nose for 3 seconds to succeed."
- You can easily do that. - A 10-cent coin?
- It's easy. - It's easy.
- It's not too bad. - It's easy.
- It's easy. - It's a reasonable dare.
While Seok Jin has a big nose,
his has small nostrils.
How does the size differ?
(He practices before he begins.)
What? I don't think it's going in.
- Put it sideways. - He got a nose surgery.
It's not going in.
(He faces an unexpected challenge.)
Gosh, it's not going in.
- Hold on. - I told you. His nose is big,
but his nostrils are small.
- This is a disaster. - Get ready.
Go.
- It will be hard. - My goodness.
- It hurts. - Is it not going in?
- Is it not going in? - It's not going in.
- Seok Jin doesn't have a big nose. - Five,
- 4, 3, - For goodness' sake.
- 2, 1. - He is trying so hard.
- One. - Time's up.
It's not going in. Do you want to try it?
- Time's up. - Are you serious?
Seok Jin is out.
(Time's over.)
- What? - Out?
- Out? - Out?
(A failure to put a coin in his nostril...)
(gets him eliminated.)
(They are only 15 minutes into the shoot.)
- He said Seok Jin is out. - What?
- Already? - What is going on?
- Out? - Please pull over.
(Please pull over, Mr. Driver.)
- He asked the driver to pull over. - Are you serious?
- What? - What are you doing?
- Are you sending him home? - We just began.
(Seok Jin breaks the record of going home the earliest.)
- We just began. - Gosh, that startled me.
(They see something.)
(After the sudden announcement of Seok Jin's elimination,)
(masked strangers enter the bus.)
Gosh, that startled me.
- Is this the end for him? - Is he going home early?
- Is he leaving? - Heung Bu!
Heung Bu! Come back!
Like the song title goes, "Heung Bu Is Shocked".
"Heung Bu Is Shocked".
Seok Jin is shocked
- He really left. - Really?
- Is he out? - Hold on.
We are leaving.
You received an invitation.
What is this?
(What is this invitation?)
- What is this? - It's an invitation.
"Dangerous Choice, Truth or Dare."
"You have been invited to the Truth or Dare Game."
"You are out if you tell a lie or fail to perform a dare."
"When three members are out, the timer starts."
"If you don't figure out a way..."
"to end the game until the time is up,"
- "everyone is out." - It looks like...
we need to figure out a way to end the game.
Whether we choose Truth or Dare,
we must succeed in receiving a hint to end the game.
It's the same in the movie.
- Really? - Yes.
- Then we can escape. - That's right.
The person who asked the first question was...
- Jae Seok. - What?
- What is happening? - Is this an individual race?
Are we on our own?
(This morning, two hours before the shoot,)
(the mysterious man visited Jae Seok who came before the other members.)
(You startled me. Who are you?)
What is this all of a sudden?
Truth or Dare.
Choose one, please.
(I did suggest this idea, but this is so sudden.)
Unbelievable.
(This is his catch-22. Will he choose Truth or Dare?)
I choose dare.
- You chose dare. - Okay.
(The first challenger is Jae Seok.)
What is this?
"Truth or Dare".
"You chose dare."
"Make all of the members participate in this game."
"If they don't, you will be eliminated."
(He will be eliminated if they don't participate in it.)
I'll be eliminated if I fail?
(He must get everyone to play the game.)
(That's why Jae Seok pretended to be a cool host.)
(He tried multiple times. He screamed at the members...)
(and pretended to be serious.)
1, 2, 3.
(Before they realized it, everyone agreed to play.)
(You heard them, right? Everyone said they'd play.)
(Jae Seok's one-sided hosting led him to the first success.)
- That's why he asked us... - I see.
- My goodness. - all those questions.
I'm in the same boat with you all.
I have to choose between Truth and Dare.
The man came to my car and asked me that.
Since Jae Seok succeeded his first dare,
- we will give him a hint. - My gosh.
(Jae Seok gets the first hint since he successfully did his dare.)
- You should give me the hint. - Will he read it by himself?
We all have to work together.
- We need hints to figure this out. - Exactly.
- How does this qualify as a hint? - This is a team mission.
"Only Jae Seok takes care of Seok Jin."
(First hint: Only Jae Seok takes care of Seok Jin.)
- That's the hint? - How is this a hint?
- This can't be a hint. - Something is going on here.
Think about it. Seok Jin was eliminated right away.
My guess is that it has to do with this.
We have to figure out how we can end this game...
- by gathering hints like this one. - That's our first step.
- Remember the forms you filled out? - Yes.
We will use the true stories from the forms.
You will select the ones we wrote down?
We're all on the same team. You didn't take it too far, right?
- Of course not. - No, I didn't.
(The bigger the secrets are, the more unfavorable it gets.)
Kwang Soo.
You didn't see this coming when you filled it out, right?
I had no idea.
(I'm doomed.)
- Hey. - I had no idea we'd be a team.
- What is it? What? - I thought the harsher,
- the better. - Gosh, you're unbelievable.
- What are you saying now? - Listen.
But I... I only wrote down the facts.
- Hey. - What's worse is that Haha...
- Never mind. - I didn't...
I didn't write one for Haha...
because I thought he'd end up in big trouble.
- I'm serious. - Let's go all the way.
Where are we going by the way?
I wonder what Seok Jin is doing now.
(The bus with dangerous secrets travels deep into some place.)
(In no time, they arrive at their destination.)
- Let's go. Let's get it! - What is this place?
(They get off the bus since they have arrived.)
- Hey. - Where are we?
Where are we?
(The gate gives off an eerie vibe.)
Isn't that... Isn't that a real warehouse?
We'll go in there? What's that place?
(What is the secret hidden in this place?)
What's going on?
(7 members except Seok Jin enter the mysterious warehouse.)
(This place is spacious. What is this place?)
What's that?
- Cell 1, Cell 2... - Hey, guys!
- Hey, guys! - Seok Jin!
- Seok Jin is locked up. - What's happening here?
(Wait, but he's surrounded by massage boards.)
Don't you think this is too harsh?
- These are massage boards. - Hey.
- Help me. - What's happening?
- There's a lock here. - What is this?
(Where is Seok Jin locked up at?)
(Welcome to Truth or Dare House.)
I see a bucket of water in this one.
If we don't do chin-ups, we'll fall into the water?
- One cell has a treadmill. - I guess we have to keep running.
We can neither sit nor stand in that cell.
(And Seok Jin is locked up inside.)
- That must be really hard. - I think it gets worse.
- You're right. - Hey.
- Gosh, I hate this. - Darn it!
Gosh, this hurts!
(But at that time...)
(Clinking)
- No, someone is locking the doors. - What's going on?
- Open up! - No, no!
(It gets worse. Someone is locking the doors.)
(They hurriedly run to the door but to no avail.)
- What just happened? - Oh, no!
- They locked us in here. - They really locked us in.
They even used a lock.
(Without the faintest idea of what's happening to them...)
- We can't go out. - They locked the doors.
(They locked up their only exit.)
- Hold on. Is this really happening? - Wait.
- Is there a restroom here? - They really locked it.
Hey, they locked the doors from outside.
- Hey. - They locked the doors.
What is this place now?
- What's going on here? - This is getting crazy.
(Truth or Dare, which only ends with the hidden secret, begins.)
The member who will receive the question is...
(The third member after Jae Seok and Seok Jin is...)
- Lee Kwang Soo. - My gosh.
(Kwang Soo is the third member who will get the question.)
(It's Kwang Soo, the weakest member's turn.)
Kwang Soo, choose truth.
- You just need to tell the truth. - Go with truth.
Remember that Cell Two has a treadmill.
Kwang Soo, you'll sweat buckets in there.
- Why is it my turn? - Just go with truth.
Truth or Dare.
- Kwang Soo, don't go with dare. - Kwang Soo, go with truth.
- He should choose truth. - Of course.
Truth... All I have to do is tell the truth.
- I might fail to do my dare. - That's right.
- But I can just tell the truth. - You can do that.
- Right. I can't fail with truth. - Hey.
- You should tell that. - Tell what?
The truth. Tell the truth.
(He pretends as if it's not a big deal.)
What are you saying?
- What was that? - Tell that.
- Sorry? - You can just tell the truth.
- What is he saying? - That'll be better.
- You just need to tell the truth. - Okay.
Just tell the truth.
It's scary that he can't know the question before choosing.
That's a true dare.
(Will he choose Truth or Dare which his career is at stake?)
- Truth. - Okay!
(I have nothing to be scared of!)
I can just answer truthfully.
- What is it? What's the question? - What is it?
I can answer every question.
They're my family.
- Viewers... - What is it?
Read it. Kwang Soo, read it for us.
Let me see. What is it?
(He freezes as soon as he reads.)
He froze.
(What is the question?)
"Tell Kwang Soo's embarrassing..."
"Tell your embarrassing stories that Jae Seok knows about."
(Kwang Soo's embarrassing stories with women)
Poor him. This is bad.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo, just tell them.)
Come on, tell them.
- What's wrong with that? - Just tell them.
You must tell the truth for us to get the hints.
- Kwang Soo, just don't lie. - That's right.
Just be honest.
You guys are so annoying right now.
- "Just don't lie"? - This is...
(This game is fun as long as it's not about me.)
But Jae Seok knows a lot of my stories.
Tell embarrassing stories with women that Jae Seok knows about.
- I bet this one is funny. - It's probably this one.
Probably? Okay. Go ahead.
I asked Jae Seok...
for advice about the troubles I had.
(He asked Jae Seok for advice regarding women.)
It was at night.
- It was about your dating life? - Right.
- Yes. - Don't leave out details.
I had a feeling...
that she was interested in me.
- And I was interested in her too. - There was a fling.
Yes. I went to Jae Seok's house.
The two of us talked in the car.
- It was the two of you in the car. - You went to Apgujeong?
Jae Seok said,
"Kwang Soo."
"If you don't tell her..."
- Was it a green light? - "about your feelings now,"
"you might lose her for good."
(This dating coach gave Kwang Soo a sharp advice.)
(Everyone sighs.)
- Right now. - "This is the time."
Okay.
- That's right. - The story is embarrassing me.
The next day...
(He followed Jae Seok's advice and texted her the next day.)
- You did it right away. - "I think..."
"I like you."
- You texted her? - Yes.
- Great. That was great. - I did.
Can I tell the whole story?
- You did well. - Okay.
I said,
"Do you want to date me?"
(Do you want to date me?)
- Kwang Soo. - Well done.
- This... - No.
- Seriously. - Okay.
- I'm getting hot. - This is more...
- romantic than a romance movie. - Right?
So what happened?
- She answered... - My heart is fluttering.
my text message.
"Kwang Soo."
(Was the dating coach's advice spot on?)
("Kwang Soo...")
"You might've gotten the wrong idea."
("You might've gotten the wrong idea.")
(He's known for his misunderstandings.)
How humiliating.
(This happens all the time to guys with little experience.)
"I don't see you like that."
I...
- "We're just colleagues." - You'd have my vote.
That guy...
(Enraged)
destroyed...
my precious tie with her.
This is so humiliating.
Whenever I think about her...
She wouldn't have known this if you didn't confess.
You...
- "We're colleagues." - You have my vote.
Kwang Soo, did this happen only once?
- You know the number of times? - Pardon?
- Did that happen only once? - What do you mean?
I guess there's another one.
- What? - Did you get dumped only once?
(This dating coach has an urgent sense to make reports.)
Is that the only celebrity?
How much did you tell them?
- You should've told only one story. - Kwang Soo, tell the truth.
- Just tell the truth. - You should've written down one.
If we can help it, we shouldn't choose truth.
There are so many.
Is this what he said? The lady...
who was having a fling with me.
This is another lady now.
She had a love scandal with someone else.
Is that what you told him?
(She had a love scandal with someone else. Is this it?)
- That's not it. - What is it then?
Tell me what you told him so I can talk about that!
- I didn't tell him that. - I mean...
- I told him no such stories. - Tell me what you told him...
- so I can tell that story. - I didn't say that.
- Why would you bring that up now? - Listen to me.
I told him no such stories.
If you tell me about how many times you confessed your feelings,
- How many times? - we'll accept your answer.
It's about your confessions.
The criteria for confessions might be a bit tricky.
I'll count similar experiences.
- I did that about 4 times. - 4 times?
(If Jae Seok wrote down a higher number than 4,)
(Kwang Soo will go to the cell with the treadmill since he lied.)
You really got dumped four times?
His number is lower than mine.
(He got dumped about 3 times.)
I wrote you got dumped 3 times, but you said 4 times.
Who is the last one?
Gosh, that's right.
But you told the truth.
That's true.
- He asked me for advice thrice. - Look at his face.
- Thank you for your sacrifice. - Seriously.
You did that for our team.
He did that for our team.
Anyway, they weren't meant to be.
- That's why it didn't happen. - That's right.
- Right. - But at that time...
I called Jae Seok.
I said, "Jae Seok, she texted me back."
I told him what she wrote.
- As soon as I told him that... - What did he say?
(Laughing)
- He's such a rascal. - Hey.
Jae Seok, you're such a rascal.
- Listen. - Did you do that on purpose?
He wanted you to get popular.
- Hey. - That's right.
He was bored at home. This was a nice distraction.
You fell for it.
- He wanted to make funny stories. - No.
- To make funny stories? - I...
- I... - He wanted to make it funny.
It's great if things work out after he confesses his feelings.
- What if he gets dumped? - Even if it doesn't work out,
as you just said, I was a bit bored that day.
- It made you laugh. - It...
(It made Jae Seok's boring day more interesting.)
It made you laugh.
It was like a welcoming rain.
(Kwang Soo wins a hint by sacrificing himself. What is it?)
(The second hint: 100 versus 100)
Hold on.
(100 versus 100?)
I think I know.
We once filmed an episode called "100 versus 100".
That's right.
- Some judo players came and... - That's right.
Could it be about people we know? Our acquaintances?
I think we need 2 or 3 more hints.
I think so too. It's still unclear.
(What could be the solution?)
Now I'll ask all of you a question.
Truth or Dare?
Let's choose dare.
- Let's choose dare. - I can't do this.
- Let's choose dare. - Let's choose dare.
We should choose dare.
Let's choose dare.
- Hold on. - I can't do this.
You said we should choose truth.
- Let's choose dare. - Let's choose dare.
- You said we should choose truth. - Let's choose dare.
It's for everyone.
We're good at group games.
1, 2, 3.
- Dare! - Dare!
(Kwang Soo is forced to choose dare.)
- We all chose dare. - Truth.
(Why are you doing this to me?)
Dare. You're too late.
- What does it say? - A Sweet Life?
(Their group mission is called A Sweet Life.)
Each of us will get a bag of 10 candies.
Each round, we have to submit...
some of our candies.
After three rounds, if we have submitted...
more than 30 candies, we succeed.
It means we all need to submit a certain number of candies.
- But... - At the end...
Let's say after three rounds,
we have submitted more than 30 candies.
The one who has the least candies left...
- will be out. - So...
(The one who has the least candies left will be out.)
It's a mind game.
Let's not think too much.
(Loyalty is their weakest point.)
- Let's all submit at least five. - Should we?
- Then it's 35 in total. - If anyone submits less...
Hold on.
Let me...
announce the blacklist.
- You're on the list. - You.
Why would you announce that?
Who gives you the right?
- Seriously. - Okay.
- Five candies, okay? - Okay.
Promise?
- Trust me. - You better submit five.
- You. - I'll submit five.
- Submit 5. - I took out 5.
You better submit five.
(So Min is ready to submit five.)
I hate it when she does this.
It's too obvious.
She already took out five.
- I took out five. - She's suspicious.
Seriously. There's no reason to lie.
These two are the same.
(Kwang Soo takes out 5 too.)
- What? - Stop it.
I shouldn't do this?
Just trust him.
Otherwise, he'll get mean.
(Will they be all right?)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to decide the order.
Let's just play Race of Wits.
- Okay. - Again?
(It might become their official game.)
Ready.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 3.
- 4. - 5.
Six.
(Haha loses.)
Seven.
- Gosh. - You go first.
(Haha will submit his candies first.)
Haha goes first.
Close your eyes.
Please turn around.
- Okay. - Trust me.
My image...
(Should I keep my promise?)
(They all promised to submit at least 5 candies.)
It's simple. I don't even have to think.
(Haha submits 5 candies as promised.)
(I kept my promise.)
- I'm done. - I...
I always keep my promise.
You can submit more than five if you want.
- I'll submit just five. - That'd be simple.
Okay.
I really submitted five.
(Jong Kook submits 5 candies.)
- I'll submit my candies. - Go ahead.
I trust you.
Think after you submit your candies.
I can't wait to find out...
how many he submitted.
(Let me see.)
Haha.
- Haha. - Yes?
You shouldn't look.
(This 40-year-old guy is very curious.)
What's taking you so long?
There's no reason to take so long.
(How many candies did Jae Seok submit?)
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Really?
(Will she submit 5 candies as she normally would?)
I'm sure she'll be reasonable.
(Okay. I've made up my mind.)
(What? Just 1?)
(She breaks her promise and submits just 1 candy.)
But...
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
I don't hear any rustle.
(Is he not submitting any?)
(Se Chan deliberately makes a rustling sound.)
Don't think too much.
Let's just trust each other.
Let's at least win a hint...
- if we're doing this anyway. - Submit five first,
and think later.
We shouldn't...
I'm done.
(In the end, Se Chan submits only 2.)
Let me announce the result of Round One.
- It's supposed to be over 30. - Yes.
- It's supposed to be 35. - I submitted a lot.
We're supposed to be finished now.
It has to be 35.
The number of the candies you submitted is...
(After Round 1)
17.
(It's less than half of their goal.)
- You jerks... - You guys...
- Also, - I...
what we have here is 17 candies...
and one microphone cover.
(17 candies and 1 microphone cover)
A microphone cover? Kwang Soo, do you have yours?
(It must be Kwang Soo.)
Haha, where is yours?
- What happened? - It's not me!
Gosh!
- It's really not me. - What did you do?
- Where's your microphone cover? - It's not me, I swear.
- Hey! - When did this happen?
Are you serious?
(It's fun to watch them fight.)
Stop doing this.
(Haha looks frustrated. What really happened?)
(A few minutes ago, Jae Seok was submitting candies.)
(Haha dropped his microphone cover while trying to peek.)
(Haha himself wasn't aware of it.)
(Kwang Soo approaches.)
(Kwang Soo picks up Haha's microphone cover.)
(Is mine still here?)
We just need to submit 30.
(He submits only Haha's microphone cover.)
I submitted some, I swear.
Your bag is still full.
I submitted some.
Did he take others' candies too?
He probably didn't know the director would mention it.
(Why did you mention it?)
Gosh.
- You took off the cover? - You're not telling us the numbers?
You're unbelievable.
You'll find out how many I submitted.
You took the cover off and submitted it?
(It's funny, right?)
It is funny though.
So we've submitted 17 so far.
Let's think about it.
- Who grabbed my neck? - We need to submit 13 more.
- Submit some. - Okay.
Hold on.
(Jong Kook makes you answer automatically.)
Hold on. Jae Seok.
- Submit some. - He got caught.
- Submit some. - He answered, "Okay."
- Submit some. - Think about it.
If there are 17 candies...
You're suddenly talking. You must have submitted less than five.
Make up for it now.
- I mean... - If she'd submitted five,
she'd be driving us crazy right now.
"Why didn't you submit five?"
But she's just smiling. She definitely didn't submit enough.
- For me, - I'm sure.
I already submitted five. I can't submit anymore.
Cut it out.
Those who submitted five don't have to submit more, right?
Guys, are you having fun?
(Don't leave me out.)
(He paid extra attention to his outfit today,)
(but he's been watching the other members from behind the whole time.)
(Are you guys having fun?)
- Are you having fun? - Seok Jin.
Pay attention to me.
We're doing something important here. Please keep quiet.
It's important for me too.
- There are two more rounds. - It's your last chance.
- Okay. - Let's start Round Two.
- Let me start. - Haha will go first.
(Haha starts Round 2.)
(Thank you for your microphone cover.)
That microphone cover thing was very interesting.
I...
already submitted five, so I won't submit any.
(As Haha submitted 5 in Round 1, he submits none this time.)
I'm so angry.
I really am.
I trusted at least three of them.
(Were we too selfish?)
Gosh, they're all the same. Okay.
Who else submitted five?
Let me...
You want to go first?
(Shameless)
- Come here. - Stop pretending.
I wanted to let it go,
- What? - but I've had enough.
- Stop now. - You're going too far.
- You want to see my bag? - You go.
Seriously? Can I show them my bag?
- Are you sure? - Can I?
- You go. - You can't show them.
- No? - You can't.
- Did you hide some here? - No.
I could show you my bag.
You sound so confident. You must be hiding some somewhere.
You shouldn't search his body while shooting.
Seriously...
Are you a detective or something?
I mean...
Gosh.
Why do I have to put up with this?
Do you seriously think I'm hiding candies there?
(Even I wouldn't do that.)
What are you doing?
Is he hiding some in his shoes?
Let's just trust him.
Gosh.
I can't believe this.
(He has to submit something now.)
I'm not even surprised.
(Everyone is suspecting and criticizing me.)
- This is your last chance. - Okay.
I'll do it.
(This time, I have to submit something.)
(I'm submitting just the wrapper.)
I can't do this.
(I can't believe myself.)
(As Jong Kook submitted 5, he submits nothing this time.)
I pass.
(Rustling)
I submitted some, I swear.
(Se Chan submits 1 candy.)
(Ji Hyo pretends to submit a lot...)
(but submits just 1 in the end.)
(Jae Seok submits 2.)
It has to be over 30 this time.
Let's put an end to this.
- After Round Two, - I'm sure we're done.
the number of candies submitted is...
- 22. - Gosh.
(It's only 5 more.)
(Whose fault is it?)
- I can't believe it. - I can't believe it.
Is it just three more?
I can't...
- It's five more? - Seriously...
Someone must have submitted nothing.
- Why would you do that? - I mean...
How can someone submit nothing two times in a row?
- How can you do that? - I submitted some.
- Why are you doing this? - I submitted some.
- What's with you? - I submitted some.
We have to go over 30.
Let's at least win a hint.
- Everyone should submit four. - Let's do that.
Let's submit four each. Do it now.
- The thing is... - I'll take...
- that... - I'll take the penalty!
(Jong Kook is angry.)
Submit four!
So we can win a hint.
- I will. - You should've said so sooner.
Why won't you listen to me?
(It's fun today.)
So Min, please turn around. Please turn around.
(Kwang Soo managed to survive.)
(He is submitting only 1, not 4?)
Kwang Soo didn't submit four.
(I can see everything.)
- Seok Jin. - He didn't submit four!
I'm not done yet.
I saw it.
- What's with him? - He didn't submit four.
- I'm not done yet. - What are you doing?
- I'm not done. - He submitted only 1 or 2.
Good job.
(He turns in 1 additional piece.)
- He turned in one. - What?
He turned in one.
- My goodness. - Goodness.
- What's wrong with him? - He turned in one.
- What are you doing? - How many did I turn in?
- Kwang Soo. - I turned them in.
(Kwang Soo turns in another one.)
(If it wasn't for Seok Jin...)
It's fine as long as you aren't last. Turn in four.
- It's not difficult. - Look at the front.
It's fun to get clues.
Jae Seok should turn in at least three pieces.
(He grabs a lot.)
(What is he doing?)
(He keeps them in his cap.)
(Bulging)
(He only turns in one piece.)
If we turned in five pieces,
the rest of them should give at least four.
You can tell based on how much remains in the pocket.
- That's... - The total should be 30.
Jae Seok, your cap is bulging out.
(Stop lying, Jae Seok.)
Your cap is bulging out too much.
- Wait a minute. - What is that?
What's that?
- Gosh. - What's in your cap?
- Stop. - Your head is uneven.
What's that inside?
- Wait a minute. - How many do you have?
You're annoying.
I turned in a lot. I really did.
How many pieces are in his cap?
(Ji Hyo gives 2 pieces.)
I'll give two pieces.
We have to win anyway.
Yes.
(Jong Kook gives nothing.)
I'm done.
Turn in yours, So Min.
- What? - Do it. I'm watching you.
(They succeed if someone turns in 2 pieces.)
(How many did So Min turn in?)
Se Chan.
(Se Chan and Haha remain.)
(Did someone hide it in here?)
Hand them in. Hand more in.
(Did So Min, Se Chan, and Haha turn in a total of 2 pieces?)
It's over.
I'll announce the final result.
- It has to be 30 pieces. - Goodness.
- Are there over 30 pieces? - Result of Round 3.
The total amount of candy is...
(Is it 30 pieces?)
(They promised to turn in 5 pieces each.)
(They agree to turn in at least 4 pieces.)
(It turns into a violent mess. Did they turn in over 30 pieces?)
- It's 29 pieces. - Goodness.
(With 29 pieces, they fail.)
Really?
(The member with the least number of candies goes to jail.)
Who is it?
Tell us how many we have.
- I'll announce first place. - The first place?
(He announces the one who turned in the least.)
Why would you announce that?
Who placed first?
- Why would you announce it? - I'm not first place.
- The first place is... - Isn't that too harsh?
There's a first place.
- 2 people placed first. - 2 people?
- Why would you announce it? - Wait.
- Two people placed first? - I turned mine in.
With seven pieces, they placed first.
- 7 pieces? - 7 pieces?
- I knew it. - They turned in one per round.
- That's harsh. - I know.
The two people are...
- Jae Seok and Kwang Soo. - Wait.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo)
(Two familiar faces)
- That was obvious. - Kwang Soo.
- I knew it. - How could you?
If you had turned in one more...
Both So Min and Se Chan have six.
- That's right. You too, So Min? - Yes.
- I'm conscientious. - Jong Kook told us to turn in four.
What do you mean conscientious?
Ji Hyo is great.
- I turned in five pieces. - Jong Kook, Haha,
and Ji Hyo turned in 5 each. 1 of you...
- will go to jail. - Yellow one's going to jail?
- I don't know anymore. - I'll definitely do it next time.
Forget it.
- I'll turn it in next round. - One.
Open up like this. 1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook goes to jail.)
It's Jong Kook. It ended up being him.
He loves to exercise, and he gets to do it here.
He usually does it at the gym.
- It must be fate. - Right.
(I don't have to go to the gym today.)
- Okay. - He got it.
(He goes to Cell 2.)
Can I walk faster?
He enters jail.
Next question is for Ji Hyo.
Truth or Dare?
You should pick truth. If you pick dare...
Dare.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
- Wait a minute. - Give us a minute.
- If you tell the truth... - No.
- Then we can't win. - I don't want to pick truth.
- Ji Hyo. - I don't want to pick truth.
- I know how you feel. - I saw Kwang Soo torn into pieces.
I don't want to do it. Dare.
(What is Ji Hyo's mission?)
- Do you shake? - We don't know what's inside.
(As If You're Insane)
- Ji Hyo will do well. - "Shake only the head."
- Goodness. In 20 seconds? - That's amazing.
- Will they come out? - It'll be hard.
Take all of them out?
(It's full of candies.)
Does she flip them?
- No. - Leave them like this?
How will they come out?
I told you to choose truth.
If you fail this time, the countdown will start.
- There's room for three. - No.
No, I can do it.
- You can do it. - If you fail, the countdown begins.
- She has to do it in a cruel way. - Get ready.
Start.
(Ji Hyo's mission starts.)
- That's right. That's good. - They're coming out?
- They come out 1 by 1. - They're coming out, Ji Hyo.
- One on the left isn't coming out. - Hurry up. Do it faster.
- That's good. - Do it faster.
- That's right. - Right.
You're insane.
(Ji Hyo is doing well.)
- That's good. - You're almost done.
Keep going. You're almost done.
You almost got it.
(Dare is better than truth, right?)
(She wants to save everyone by winning clues.)
(Her banging of her head is noble.)
(They're almost empty.)
- A little more. - There's only one left.
- You have 1 left. - 1 is left.
- Done! - Success.
(She gets rid of all the candies.)
You got it.
(They're empty.)
19.77 seconds.
- I'm so dizzy. - That was impressive.
She was really insane.
- I can't see well. - That was really surprising.
Dare can be successful.
- Wait, let's see the clue. - 100 to 100.
- "Being out"? - "Being out can save your friend."
Someone has to be eliminated to save all of us.
- Is that what it means? - One has to be out.
You have to sacrifice yourself.
(Which member will be eliminated?)
Read the chance mission that we prepared.
- Okay, is there a chance? - There's a chance.
- We need one of these. - Right.
- Do we play once more? - What is it?
- Seok Jin. - What?
- What is it? - Find a Lying Member.
(It can save 1 of the 2.)
"Eliminated and surviving members..."
"choose one member to save."
"When both teams choose the same member, he'll be saved."
"One more clue is given."
If they choose different members,
one of you will be punished as well.
(Additional member is sent to jail.)
- We have to... - We must choose the same.
- choose the same member. - Let's choose the same member.
If we pick different members...
There's nothing to be funny about.
Okay, I got it.
6 of us must choose the same members as 2 of you.
- Okay. - Okay.
Whom shall we pick?
If we consider consistency,
- it should be Jong Kook. - We should pick Jong Kook.
I don't think he'll yield.
Jong Kook is very comfortable in there.
He looks like he's working out at a good gym.
He keeps throwing punches.
- Jong Kook, go easy on me. - Okay.
- Okay. - May I be released, Jong Kook?
If you get a chance, you should. Do you prefer getting out?
- Let me get out. - Getting out is better.
- How can I stay? - Getting out is good.
- You're working out. - Still...
- You're exercising. - I'm hot in here.
I'm about to lose my mind the longer I stay here.
- Let me get out. - Have you made up your mind?
- Let me get out. - What?
We're arguing right now.
They're arguing. He said, "Getting out is better."
Shall we change our decision?
He wants to stay in.
Jong Kook said that he's hot.
Have you decided?
- We agreed. - Are you ready?
(They agree on who gets out.)
If we fail, one more goes in.
- It's over once you go in. - I know.
Please, guys.
- Yes? - We made an agreement.
1, 2, 3.
(What did they agree on?)
(Whom did Jong Kook and Seok Jin choose?)
(Their choices agree.)
(Seok Jin finally gets released and stands before the camera.)
I'm finally getting out.
- Jong Kook is doing well inside. - Right.
- Jong Kook is very well. - I'll get another chance.
- Thank you. - Do your feet hurt a lot?
They hurt a lot.
- I'm impressed by your loyalty. - Thank you.
- We get a hint. - We're loyal.
- Jong Kook, hang in there. - Okay, Seok Jin.
Show it to us.
"Game Is over When Everyone Stays in Their Places." What?
(Fourth clue)
Everyone stays in their places.
- Let me see the last 1. - "100 to 100".
- We shot 100 to 100 before. - Wait.
- "Only Jae Seok"... - "Takes care of Seok Jin".
- "Being out can"... - "Being out can save your friend."
"Game is over when everyone stays in their places."
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- We have to do something. - What's this?
- What does it mean? - Where is our place?
Stand in the order of your age.
- Doesn't it mean our age? - I don't think so.
Does anyone become 100 years old when you add something?
- 100 to 100. - 100 years old?
- It's 100 years old each. - Our total age is over 100.
There are about 5 100-year-olds.
- It's 100 to 100. - It's 2 by 2.
Our total age is over 100.
We need more clues.
The game is done when we're in our places?
Jong Kook, hang in there. We'll save you.
(What do the clues mean?)
It's time for another question.
- Next up is Se Chan. - Is it me?
It's Se Chan.
- Truth or Dare? - Pick truth.
- Pick truth. - Pick truth.
- I'll choose... - You should pick truth.
- Dare will be hard. - I don't think I can do it.
Truth.
Se Chan is honest.
He has nothing to hide.
(Pick another member whom you'll answer truthfully with.)
(If everyone tells the truth, they win a hint.)
Pick someone honest.
Seok Jin is very honest.
I just got out.
- I choose Seok Jin. - Just tell the truth.
- I choose Seok Jin. - Tell the truth.
- I choose Seok Jin. - No!
Just tell the truth.
- You just have to tell the truth. - I can't!
I just got out.
Just tell the truth.
- Gosh. - You don't have to go back in.
Okay.
Okay. Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin has to tell the truth.)
You're amazing.
It'd be so funny if he has to lie.
Let me see the question first.
His nose is big,
but his nostrils are small.
(His nose is big, but his nostrils are small.)
- Heung Bu. - Okay.
I just need to tell the truth, right?
I'll tell the truth.
- That's right. - Take off your glasses.
If you lie,
- I'm nervous. - whipped cream will be splashed...
- and... - I'll be out.
you'll go to the cell with ice water and a chin-up bar.
(He'll be splashed and sent to the cell with ice water.)
(I'll tell the truth.)
This show cares so much...
about Seok Jin's health.
They make him stand on the massage board and...
- He can just tell the truth. - Yes.
A cold shower is very good for you too.
I'll definitely tell the truth.
It was so painful to be in the cell.
This question is about...
a secret Haha knows.
(It's a secret Haha knows about Seok Jin.)
It's about Seok Jin.
What do you know about me?
- I didn't write anything serious. - Really?
Okay. I'm going to tell the truth.
(I'm a bit worried.)
About four weeks ago,
you were waiting for a Running Man shoot.
You said something that shocked the other members...
and made your stylist cry. What was it?
(I think I know.)
I know.
What is it?
What did I say?
Yes, that's the one.
- That's the one? - Yes.
That's right.
- What? - I remember it.
He said...
he wanted to be on a certain show.
(Seok Jin said he wanted to be on a certain show.)
We all said, "What?"
"Are you serious?"
Gosh.
Hey!
Haha!
- It's up to you. - Seriously...
Seriously... It must be so hard to decide.
I haven't been sleeping well since that day.
I was so shocked.
(What shocked Kwang Soo so much?)
Are you going to tell the truth?
Tell the truth,
or you'll be penalized.
Of course, it was just a joke.
It was.
(Why did I make such a joke?)
When Seok Jin goes home,
his wife will say, "Seok Jin, you're out."
(Seok Jin's wife will say he's out.)
- "You're out." - That's possible.
He'll be out either at home or here.
(Seok Jin faces a dilemma.)
Tell the truth within five seconds, or you'll be penalized.
- It's okay. She'll understand. - Five...
What should I do? I just got out.
- Gosh. - All right.
(He might have to go into the ice water bucket.)
(I'm sorry.)
(Okay. I'll tell the truth.)
I said,
"Gosh..."
(Exclaiming)
You have to think.
You have to think a lot.
"Oh, there's a show I want to do."
(Will he tell the shocking truth?)
Which show?
"Gosh..."
(Exclaiming)
"I want to be on 'Flaming Youth'."
(I want to be on "Flaming Youth".)
("Flaming Youth" airs at 11:10pm on SBS every Tuesday.)
I was just joking.
(It's a show where middle-aged singles make friends.)
(He actually said it!)
I was just joking!
- Su Jeong, I was just joking! - Turn off the sound!
- I was just joking! - Turn off the sound!
(You should probably sleep here tonight.)
- I mean... - That's too bad.
It was really a joke.
- "Flaming Youth". - He told the truth.
He did.
Those cells are awful.
- It's terrible. - He told the truth.
- Now we can win a hint. - Seriously...
(Thank you for your sacrifice.)
Let's just choose dare from now on.
The truth hurts too much.
It does.
- Se Chan. - Yes.
If you tell the truth, we can win a hint.
Here we go, Se Chan.
I can tell the truth.
While Se Chan answers the question, can we have Jong Kook's door open?
What?
- Is it about Jong Kook? - What is it?
Okay.
It feels much better with the door open.
Se Chan's question must be related to you.
- Really? - Can you hear us well?
Yes.
- Here we go. - What is it?
What could it be?
- It's a secret Kwang Soo knows... - Me?
about Se Chan.
What is it?
(Oh, it's that one.)
You always take screenshots of the shows Jong Kook is on...
and send them.
He is the president of my celebrity fan club.
When Kwang Soo asked you if it was fun,
what did you answer?
(What did he answer to the question, "Was it fun?")
I don't want to be here.
(Haha is scared.)
(You texted me this.)
(I can't say that.)
(When I asked him how he could watch all Jong Kook's shows...)
I can't say that.
- Not this. - You're so mean.
- I think I know. - No.
I don't think I can say it.
We need a hint.
We have to get out of here.
I even mentioned "Flaming Youth".
I didn't want to tell anyone, but...
(If I tell the truth, that monster will come after me.)
(Between the truth and survival, what will Se Chan choose?)
"I can watch his shows because I like him so much."
(How can he be so shameless?)
- It's no problem. - You must want to survive.
(He is penalized for his lie.)
(Here, both lies and truths hurt.)
It hurt.
- The wind hurt. - The thing is,
the cream completely melted.
It must have been something you couldn't say.
(For Se Chan's safety, we'll protect the secret.)
Se Chan.
Se Chan, you're out.
(Se Chan is sent to jail.)
(You know...)
(how I always want to be close to you, right?)
It's so cold.
Se Chan.
He must feel so uncomfortable right now.
Let me ask all of you.
Truth or Dare?
- Dare! - Dare!
1, 2, 3.
- Never choose truth. - Who would choose truth?
We can't do this.
Our friendship got hurt.
- Let's not choose truth. - We have to choose dare.
- We have to choose dare. - Definitely.
We can't say anything more.
Blowing Eggs.
"All surviving members have to participate."
"Within 100 seconds, you'll take turns."
"Blow eggs upside down."
(Blow 10 eggs upside down.)
It's hard.
Practice.
(They start practicing.)
That's not how you do it.
(Blowing)
- I feel dizzy. - Gosh.
Move your head.
So Min!
That's not how you do it.
- Hey! - I can't do this.
Blow here.
(The egg hits Seok Jin's nose.)
(My nose hurts.)
(The egg hits Kwang Soo's nose too.)
(Those with big noses might get hurt.)
It keeps hitting my nose.
Gosh.
Guys, you should move your head.
(Jae Seok figures out the right way.)
Move your head.
When?
(Will Jae Seok's tip help Kwang Soo succeed?)
(The egg breaks.)
(The raw egg gets all over Kwang Soo's face.)
Gosh.
(He blows hard enough, but he moves too slowly.)
What are you doing?
Was it raw?
Were they raw eggs?
(The practice is over.)
Ready.
(Blow 10 eggs upside down within 100 seconds.)
(Haha starts.)
(1 is done.)
(It's not going well.)
(I should step in.)
Jae Seok, go.
(Jae Seok takes over.)
(He knows how to succeed.)
(During the practice)
(Blow and move!)
(Blowing 9 eggs upside down would be no problem.)
- Gosh. - Move on.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
Two.
- Gosh. - What's with you?
Why are you blowing so hard?
Gosh.
Hey.
What is this?
(The landing and the sound are impeccable.)
How many are you going to break?
- What are you doing? - How many are they?
(2 are done.)
- There you go. - Two are done.
Look at the mess they make!
(Seok Jin is the 3rd player.)
(His nose gets in the way, and he doesn't blow hard enough.)
What are you doing?
Okay.
Hurry up!
We don't have much time.
Hurry up! We don't have much time.
Yes!
(He gets the 3rd egg upside down.)
All right.
Ji Hyo.
Good.
Keep going.
(Ji Hyo gets the 4th egg upside down right away.)
Ji Hyo is good at it.
(She gets the 5th egg upside down too.)
- Yes! - Keep going.
(Blowing)
Gosh.
(He gets the 7th egg upside down by chance.)
- I did it! - Good.
Hurry up.
Just two more.
- Good! - Hurry up.
- One more. - Hurry up!
Hurry up!
(Two more to go...)
(until 10)
Just one more.
(Let me show you.)
(There's 25 seconds left.)
Hurry up!
(It's not going well.)
Here.
(Seok Jin tries again.)
Hurry up!
Put it down.
Gosh.
My goodness.
(He breaks another egg.)
(I have to do this.)
Okay!
You did it.
(With 11 seconds left, there's 1 more egg to go.)
(Will Kwang Soo succeed?)
Gosh.
(He gets splashed again.)
What did you do?
Hey.
(While Kwang Soo makes a mistake, Haha makes a quick attempt.)
(Will they succeed?)
- What are you doing? - I got it.
(Haha succeeds.)
(They win a clue.)
It was a success.
You got all 10.
(I also did my best.)
We got it.
Many of them bounced off.
Take your hint.
- What? - "Bird that flies high sees far"?
(What does it mean?)
"Bird that flies high sees far".
"100 versus 100".
(How is it related to the previous hints?)
"Bird that flies high sees far".
(Wait a minute.)
(Is there something high up?)
"Bird that flies high sees far".
(Something might be hidden up there.)
- Is there anything up there? - Let's look.
(Let's go upstairs first.)
Is there a hint outside?
(Only Jae Seok takes care of Seok Jin.)
(100 versus 100)
Do we have to be high up?
This is scary.
- "Being out..." - "Being out saves your friend."
"saves your friend."
(Looking around)
(What's this?)
- What is it? - What is it?
- What's this? - It's a scale.
It's a scale.
- Right, it's a scale. - That's right.
There are three.
(There's a drawing of a scale on the floor.)
There are 3 R Stickers. There are 2 on this side.
(They're on top of the scale.)
(There are 3 and 2 R Stickers.)
- It's a scale. - 3 and 2 people should stand.
3 and 2.
There are three R Stickers.
It's 100 to 100.
- It's our weight. - 100 to 100.
100 to 100.
What's "100 to 100"?
We have to stay in our places.
- Right. - This must be the place.
- There are 3 and 2. - 3 and 2.
(Will they figure out how to escape?)
Wait, look.
Look.
2 and 3 people go to each side. Make it 100 to 100.
- Do you mean 100kg? - Yes, 100kg.
That's...
(Three people's weight can't equal 100kg.)
100kg isn't possible.
Shall we make our total age 100?
- Shall we make our total age 100? - Age?
We can make our total age 100.
"Only Jae Seok takes care of Seok Jin."
(That's it.)
- Our total age equals 100. - You and I work.
Is it 100? How old are you?
- I'm 47 years old. - It's 100.
- You're 53. - Hey.
- Wait. - The total is 100.
It must be our age.
(They have figured it out.)
I told you before.
I'm 40 years old.
I'm 33.
- I'm 34. - 3 people should stand here.
- Wait. - This is for three people.
- 34 plus... - 33.
(34 plus 33)
- It's me, So Min, and Se Chan! - Se Chan!
Me, So Min, and Se Chan make 100.
We need to release him.
(Se Chan should be released.)
- He can't come out. - We must take him out.
- That's right. - Our total age is 100.
- Really? - We need three people.
He must be released.
- That's right. - He can't come out.
We need him.
Someone has to switch places with him.
We must save him.
("Being out saves your friend," is an important clue.)
(Will they figure out the secret to this game?)
Was it "Being out saves your friend"?
- You should get eliminated now. - No, I must stay here.
(He must stay with Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok must stay on the scale.)
(Jae Seok shouldn't go to jail.)
I should be eliminated.
(Haha must go to jail.)
- Haha. - I must be out.
That's his place.
Two of us must stay here.
My place wasn't here. It was over there.
That means...
(Ji Hyo, Haha, and Jong Kook must stay in jail.)
Haha, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo must be in jail.
- That's right. - Right.
That's why it's three.
Haha and Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook plus Ji Hyo)
The total age of Haha, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo is 121 years.
(Their total age is 121 years.)
Really?
That's right.
It's 121 years.
(The answer was age.)
It was our age.
It's resident registration number. Men are 1, and women are 2.
(Ji Hyo goes to jail number 2.)
- That's right. - Right?
Look at that.
I must switch with Jong Kook.
We got everything.
- Right. - That's right.
- I got goose bumps. - This is amazing.
(How will they open Cell One?)
- Seriously. - By the way,
how will we get Jong Kook out and put Ji Hyo inside?
- Should we play Truth or Dare? - We must lose.
Our failure won't release Jong Kook.
This is how we can escape this room. Wasn't there a secret?
(Do you remember what was written on the invitation?)
"Dangerous Choice, Truth or Dare."
"When three members are out, the timer starts."
"If you don't figure out a way..."
"to end the game until the time is up, everyone is out."
- All cells must be occupied. - That's right.
- They should be occupied. - Let's do that.
I'll go inside.
They must be full.
We figured out everything.
Summer before marriage.
Last summer?
I was...
Choi Soo Jong.
(He says a blatant lie.)
(This is how the big picture becomes reality.)
We got it.
(Haha goes to jail intentionally.)
Many things happened during the summer before marriage.
Now, three cells are occupied.
We must do it now.
(All 3 cells are occupied.)
Let's find our places.
(The time limit is 10 minutes.)
What's going on?
That startled me.
(The time limit is 10 minutes.)
(The timer is on for 10 minutes.)
The game has started!
(The countdown starts.)
Where's the key?
- How can he get out? - Can you open the door?
Can you open the door?
- How can we save him? - There's something else.
What's this?
- What's this? - It's a seesaw.
(It's a real seesaw.)
- What is this for? - Is it a real seesaw?
It doesn't measure our age. Is it our weight?
Is it our weight?
(What does a seesaw have to do with opening the cell?)
It's your last mission.
(Their last mission is given.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Bring it. - Take a look.
"Balance the Seesaw".
"All surviving members get on."
"Balance the seesaw and maintain it over three seconds."
"Then the cell doors open."
The cell doors should open.
- Then switch places. - Right.
- We have to balance it. - I weigh about 62kg.
- I weigh about 76kg. - 76kg?
I weigh 72kg.
I weigh 49kg.
Kwang Soo and Seok Jin should go over there.
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin are on one side.)
- Right. - We'll stand here.
Let's balance it with the distance.
Get off, So Min.
I'll get on first.
Sit in the back.
(Finding the balance quickly is key.)
Let's see. Get on.
- Hurry up. - I will...
(Time keeps passing.)
Let's see.
We got it.
- Wait a minute. - Keep it for three seconds.
- One. - Wait a minute.
- Wait. - Wait.
Come forward, Seok Jin.
- Wait. - Kwang Soo, go forward.
- So Min. - Come forward, Seok Jin.
Are we heavier?
Hold still.
That won't work.
(Finding the balance isn't easy.)
Go back, Ji Hyo.
If I do this, we're too heavy.
Go forward, Kwang Soo.
Ji Hyo, come forward.
- Come as much as possible. - Shall I go?
- Yes. - Go forward, So Min.
(He floats.)
Wait a minute.
(Jae Seok got startled.)
- Wait. - Why didn't you warn him?
You should have warned him.
(Keep your manners.)
How much do you weigh, So Min?
- I weigh... - Put your feet up.
- 55kg? - I weigh 54kg.
(Hesitant)
- You said you weigh 49kg. - What?
You said you weigh 49kg.
I weigh 54kg.
You said your weight was 49kg.
Wait a minute.
Hold it.
- We got it. - Don't be tense.
- Relax. - Don't be tense, Kwang Soo.
- Go forward a little. - Relax.
Go back.
(Will they make it in 3.5 minutes?)
Go back a little. You got it.
1, 2, 3.
(They successfully balance the seesaw.)
We got it!
It was a success.
Success.
Switch places.
Good job.
Everyone, go to your places.
(Everyone takes their places.)
Keep your places.
Go to your places.
(Ji Hyo goes to Cell 2. Jong Kook goes to Cell 1.)
So that's what the numbers are.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Haha take their proper cells.)
The total age is 121 years, right?
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok versus Kwang Soo, So Min, Se Chan)
(What will be the result?)
Everyone, go to your places.
(Everyone takes their places.)
Keep your places.
Go to your places.
(Ji Hyo goes to Cell 2. Jong Kook goes to Cell 1.)
So that's what the numbers are.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Haha take their proper cells.)
The total age is 121 years, right?
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok versus Kwang Soo, So Min, Se Chan)
(What will be the result?)
(Truth or Dare is a success.)
(They're gold medalists at the moment.)
You're not good enough for us.
All right!
- All right. - We did it.
- This feels great. - All right.
This feels nice.
Our teamwork is amazing.
We never fail things like this.
I found out today. We're 321 years old altogether.
- That's right. - I got goose bumps from something.
- Our age... - You are 100 years old together.
(It's a century with these two together.)
- These two together. - That's what shocked me.
- Okay. - It's only true this year.
That's true.
(And a week later)
(Dangerous Choice follows Truth or Dare.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Today, it'll be a couple race...
where eight teams will compete.
(Actress Lee Elijah, Actress E Xi A)
(Actress Lee Ju Yeon, Singer Sun Mi, Comedian Kim Ji Min)
(Bobby of iKON, Seung Ri of Big Bang, B.I of iKON)
(This is a couple race with the 8 hottest stars.)
In a moment, Running Man members will look at the items...
and choose one that they like. You become a couple...
with the member who chooses the same item.
All right. Please choose an item each...
and fill out the cards.
(They think about the Running Man members they like and choose.)
I...
(They also fill out the card that'll be placed next to the item.)
It's raining.
Today, it's a couple race where you'll be partnered up...
with the guests who are the hottest stars.
You'll select your partners first.
- Already? - The guests...
have already chosen a couple item.
They have?
This is what we used to do during blind dates.
The couples will be decided according to what you pick.
As you know, there are five women...
and three men here today.
If there are three men, there'll be a male couple.
- There are three men. - Not me. I pick Sun Mi.
- Sun Mi has been here before. - Yes, that's right.
- She was here with Elijah. - Elijah.
- Elijah was my partner. - That's right.
And Ju Yeon is a good friend of So Min.
- We're from the same school. - Really?
Class of 2005 at Dongduk Women's University.
People say this.
You hang out with people who have similar tendencies as you.
That's not true.
- I heard she's not ordinary either. - We're different.
- Are they similar? - We...
We had drinks together a few times. She's not ordinary at all.
From what I hear, she's 1 of the top 5 psychos...
in the music industry.
That's true.
- Right? - Yes.
- Is she the Five Psychos? - Yes, Five Psychos.
- Five Psychos. She's a member. - Here.
So Min is 1 of the top 5 psychos in the acting industry.
- I can't imagine it. - I know. I can't tell.
In front of you are the cards that they wrote.
- They wrote us letters. - Letters.
- There are letters. - This is a guy.
(They guess whose item each one is from the writing and the content.)
This has to be Seung Ri 100 percent.
"I'm going to count to 3, and you can come get the bag. 1, 2, 3."
("I'm going to count to 3, and you can come get the bag. 1, 2, 3.")
- It's obvious he's promoting. - This has to be Seung Ri.
- The bag is Seung Ri's. - This is Ju Yeon.
- "I only drink dewdrops." - It's Ju Yeon.
"Let's drink together." This is 100 percent, right?
She's not ordinary. Her brain is not ordinary.
- Check all of them. - Hey!
- This is a guy. - This has to be Seung Ri.
- "I'm going to count to three..." - We already mentioned it.
- I already said that. - When?
(I said that 2 minutes ago.)
- When? - I said that.
- Why are you stealing it from me? - When did you say that?
- I said it earlier. - Why did you whisper?
I didn't. I said it loud and clear.
- He said it clearly. - When was it?
- Earlier. - This is driving me nuts.
- Seok Jin. - I feel like a loner.
(He's very sad.)
What do you mean? It's more like you are bullying us.
Why did you whisper? You excluded me.
- Everybody heard it. - He said it to everybody.
- It's a one-way street. - I know.
How are you picking who's going first?
Let's play Race of Wits.
He won't skip games. He won't let it slide.
I'm going to get witty. We played this so many times.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 3.
- Does the loser pick 1st? - 4.
Yes, the loser picks first.
- 5. - 6.
(Seok Jin stands alone.)
(The game is finished in a blind of an eye.)
(Six...)
Do you guys practice?
Does he pick last?
Seok Jin is going last.
- For this round, we jump. - Do we jump?
Yes. Start.
- 1. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
(He was moving up and down, and he's in 7th place.)
- This... - It's hard to jump.
Jumping is hard.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 3.
- Okay. - Haha and Jae Seok.
- Goodness. - Face up or down
(The bottom half is decided. It's time for the top half.)
Okay. You're gone.
- This time... - I'm nervous for some reason.
Slap each other and the person who doesn't laugh wins.
(This time)
(Slapping)
(All of a sudden?)
- Hey. - Didn't we start?
- We did. You're out. - Didn't we?
- You're out. - Why?
- You're out. You made a sound. - Why?
You made a sound. You're out.
- You're out. - I didn't make a sound.
Do rock-paper-scissors.
(The person who gets to choose 1st is...)
- Good. - So Min goes first.
- So Min has many options. - So Min.
I knew it. She's good with couple races.
- Right? - For some reason,
- I'm drawn to this heart. - Good.
- Really? - It's Seung Ri.
- It might not be. - That's true.
- They might have switched them. - That's true.
No, I don't think so. It can't be.
- It might be fake. - It might be a trick.
I like this one. This heart is the biggest.
(So Min chooses the heart bag.)
- Next is... - Me.
I think... This...
(He's drawn to this item.)
- Are those socks? - Yes.
It says, "Kwang Soo". This is either good or bad.
- I don't want him to have this. - That's good.
They were looking for Kwang Soo, and you took it.
That's good.
- You never know. - Good job, Se Chan.
- Okay. - Who's next?
- I think this letter... - The music one?
sounds the most sincere.
- But... - Kwang Soo likes music.
I thought this looked like a guy's writing.
(Ji Hyo chooses the scarf.)
It says, "Haha", so I have to take it.
- Haha is mine... - Aren't you disgusted?
on Running Man.
(The others have no chance.)
- Haha. - And my wife...
understands too.
I find that so interesting.
That's a relief.
- Okay, this. - Okay.
- What's that? - A fan.
- Okay. - All right.
- This one is for you. - Okay.
(They all choose their items.)
We'll first invite...
- the guest... - Me.
- who chose the headphones. - I'm curious.
- He looks excited. - I'm curious too.
- Who will it be? - He's into this.
It's hard to be excited every time to be honest.
It's coming up. They pressed the button.
Please. They're coming.
(This person makes Kwang Soo's facial muscles twitch.)
(This person probably gets emotional when they listen to music.)
(They are coming now.)
- It's a woman. - It is.
Who is it?
- Is it Sun Mi? - She's pretty.
- She's hiding. - Is it Sun Mi?
(Who is the partner with the headphones?)
I think it's Lee Elijah.
- It's Elijah. - Elijah.
It's Elijah.
Elijah.
(Let's talk about Elijah.)
(She's a great actress, looks beautiful, and is funny.)
(She'll dominate Running Man again with her talents.)
Are we a couple? Yes.
- Elijah. - Hello.
I'm sorry, but what was this?
(You know what it is.)
She's so weird from the beginning.
- You don't look that happy. - No, I am.
- Are you in the same agency? - We are.
- Yes. - You work in the same company.
They became partners,
and they're both not that happy.
She didn't say anything to me yet.
(This is what happens when you are partnered with your family.)
- Did you see Kwang Soo? - He might be shy.
This is funny.
- Yes! - Yes!
(Let's try our best.)
All right. It's so awkward between you two.
- What's wrong? - This is suffocating.
(Following the suffocating couple...)
Next is the couple cushion.
- Okay. - The couple cushion.
Do you think...
- this is a guy? - It's a guy.
It's a guy. The excessive ones are all guys.
Who stamps the paper with their lips?
This person doesn't know moderation.
They either have too much experience on variety shows...
They're here.
- They're here. - They're here.
(The person is here.)
- It's a woman. - It is.
It's a woman.
(Jae Seok's cushion partner is...)
Xi A. It's Xi A.
It's E Xi A.
(E Xi A is a new, popular actress.)
(She steals the men's hearts and catches attention with her acting.)
(She's the scene-stealer who gets everybody's attention.)
I said this earlier.
She either has too much experience on variety shows...
- or not at all. - Right.
This is "Match Made from Above" style.
I watched it a lot.
You can watch her later.
- What? - She's a former girl group member.
- Really? - You didn't know, right?
- She's from a girl group? - Which one?
Really?
- She's incredible. - Really?
(She has unexpected charms. How will she do today?)
Next is the headband.
- The headband? - It's Jong Kook.
- Come here. - What? Me? Okay.
In amusement parks, there are people...
- who only work in the summer. - During the busy seasons?
Yes. This is where I put my money.
This is where you collect money.
You're the boss.
- They're coming up. - They're here.
Who is it?
- I think it's Sun Mi. - Is it a guy or a girl?
It's Ji Min.
- What? - It's a woman.
It's a woman.
(The Heart Man's partner is...)
It's Ju Yeon.
(Lee Ju Yeon is the original beauty face and a great entertainer.)
(She started off as After School and is now an actress.)
(She can dance, sing, and act. She transforms all the time.)
(1 of the top 5 psychos is here.)
She's here! Jong Kook, she's here!
Jong Kook...
(She twists her ankle.)
(It looks like she's full of pride, but she flounders.)
Look! Look at her. Look at her strut.
She's unique.
- She's 1 of the top 5 psychos. - Top 5 psychos.
Goodness. Jong Kook.
(Why is he embarrassed for her?)
- She's 1 of the top 5. - Top 5 psychos.
- She's one of them. - Where do I stand?
Here.
(I'm partners with Jong Kook.)
- Gosh. - Lucky you.
She's indeed in the top five.
We're from the same school. Hey.
- Did you take the sock? - There's only Sun Mi left.
- What? - The sock?
I was going to pick the sock.
Really? Why didn't you?
I thought it'd be him.
I'm happy I don't have you either.
Okay.
What's going on? There's something going on between you two.
With her? No, not at all.
- We're close. We're friends. - We're friends.
- Not at all. - She got his name wrong.
She called him "Chan Young".
(Why is he Chan Young?)
What? Why?
I don't know. She says I'm Jung Chan Young.
They met and drank all day. When they were going home,
she said, "It was nice meeting you, Chan Young."
(That's what happened.)
- What are you doing? - I was so mad.
I was angry. She didn't even get my last name right.
Who's Jung Chan Young?
Who did you get him confused with?
He's the husband of an After School member.
- Then why... - I have no idea.
That's so scary.
- She's a psycho, right? - She's no joke.
There's no basis for her to say that.
She might be in the top three.
(She proves her class as 1 of the top 5 psychos.)
- Next is the bag. - They're the same.
The bag?
I'm getting anxious. Whose is this?
They're here.
(It looks like a man's silhouette.)
We're right.
It's a man, So Min. It's B.I.
(Is it Seung Ri like the card hinted or is it someone else?)
(Who is the one behind the heart?)
(It's The Great Seung Ri.)
(He went from Big Bang's youngest member to a person of influence.)
(He's CEO Lee who owns global businesses.)
(He writes history every day.)
It's obviously Seung Ri.
(This is suffocating to watch.)
Look at his dress shoes.
It's obviously him.
Why did he turn so unctuous?
(He starts promoting his song out of nowhere.)
(He's on fire as soon as he comes out.)
What's this?
- This is old style. - Is it not like this anymore?
- No, it's changed. - Over there.
- That's your partner. - Here's your partner.
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to...
Who is this cute lady?
(He does a skit all of a sudden.)
(Who is this guy?)
Are you a gangster or something?
- Is he a gangster or something? - What's this?
Why is he doing that?
- What's that? - No...
No, today...
- Why are you talking like a thug? - I'm dressed for the role.
- Turn it into romance. - Didn't I get it right?
- No. - It's romance.
This is good.
From what I hear,
Seung Ri is the only member who's active, right?
- This is your prime. - That's right.
- This is the happiest time. - That's right.
People who didn't know me know me now.
It took 13 years.
This is his prime since he started as Big Bang.
- That's right. - That's great.
You two look so good together.
(We expect great chemistry between them.)
Who's next?
Next is the sock.
- Me? Wait. - The sock.
There are three people left, right? Ji Min...
- Four people. - They're running out of options.
- They're coming. - Who is it?
(There are 2 female and 2 male guests left.)
They're here.
(There's a 50-percent chance he'll be partnered with a female.)
Please let it be a guy.
(Who chose the sock and will be partners with Se Chan?)
(It's B.I of iKON, who is popular among children.)
(He plays the leading role in "Love Scenario".)
(He's the irreplaceable leader of iKON.)
(I'm here, girls.)
B.I and Se Chan are...
- are kind of awkward. - Right.
- It's awkward. They're awkward. - B.I looks so handsome.
I'm a big fan of his.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank you. Let's have fun today.
- I'm a big fan of yours too. - And...
he has a stage name.
He's Jung Chan Young.
(He's not Yang Se Chan.)
Am I Jung Chan Young?
What did you do to me?
(Sorry, Chan Young. I mean, Se Chan.)
Next is the bracelet.
Okay!
They're coming up.
- Is it a woman? - Wait. I'm not sure.
Okay!
It's Sun Mi. It's Sun Mi, Seok Jin.
(You can slightly see her silhouette.)
I avoided a man.
(It's not a man. She's small.)
It's Ji Min.
(Kim Ji Min is a beautiful comedian.)
(Sighing)
Go get your father.
Get your father.
Bow to him, Ji Min.
(She's so polite.)
- She's polite. - Who is it? Is it you?
- It's me. - Why?
I'm still happy.
(It's strictly a senior-junior relationship.)
How did this happen?
Let's go, Sun Mi.
Let's go, Bobby.
They're here.
- It's Sun Mi. - Who is it?
It's Sun Mi and Bobby.
We don't know who their partners are.
They're both coming up. It depends on where they go.
(Would it be male-male and female-female couples?)
- Come out. - Sun Mi and Bobby.
(Or would it be male-female couples?)
(What will the last result be?)
- They're so... - He's wearing a scarf.
(Bobby is Ji Hyo's partner, and Sun Mi is Haha's partner.)
It's Bobby and Ji Hyo.
(He smiles with his eyes, but he has a manly side.)
(He's the hip hop champion who stole the ladies' hearts.)
(24 hours is not enough for this charming woman.)
(She flipped Korea upside down with her unrivaled performance.)
- Hello. - They look good together.
- They look good together. - Those two look good together.
That's true.
What if these 2 and those 2 are couples?
- They look good together. - Let's do that.
They look good together.
(The couple selection is over with Haha and Sun Mi, Ji Hyo and Bobby.)
(Couples)
We have incredible people here today.
Please give them a round of applause.
I'm so excited.
They're incredible.
This is great.
Let's talk to Sun Mi first.
She's awesome.
How have you been?
- I've been well. - She swept all the festivals.
That's what I was about to say.
There are performances that dominated the college festivals.
People go insane.
The video went viral too.
There was a festival where all the sexy ladies were invited to.
She came out and swept it all.
- No way. - I'm serious.
- No. - I'm serious.
Sun Mi, can you show us the performance?
But the thing is,
it went popular because I was soaked.
We can't pour water on you.
Is this water for me by any chance?
(We can't pour water on her.)
Sun Mi.
Do you think we got this to see your performance?
(It's obviously drinking water.)
That's not right.
(She's not ordinary.)
(She's just as bad as me.)
Show us how it's like.
There were muscular men standing behind her.
Can you stand behind her?
Who? Me?
No, it's okay.
Kwang Soo, stand behind her.
- Should I stand behind... - Should we stand behind her?
- We'll stand behind her. - Do we just stand?
It looks awful with the two of them standing there.
(That's true.)
(It's better not to have them there.)
(She pulls herself together and starts dancing to "Gashina".)
(Grabbing)
(What was that for?)
(His heart drops.)
(Mom...)
(It goes wrong from the start.)
(His heart is about to drop from the slightest contact.)
It's part of the choreography.
- Do we do it together? How? - Yes.
You have to hug her.
You have to hug her from the back. That's right.
(Let me borrow your body.)
(Turning)
That's right.
(What's this?)
You should have told us first.
She did it by herself.
The guys turn around.
(The song is reaching its climax.)
(Swirling)
- This is next. - "No".
Do it now.
(Why are you leaving the pretty me here?)
- Do I shoot? - Shoot.
(Shoot now.)
(They all shoot.)
(They dominate the stage.)
- Great job. - Shoot your guns.
- Good. - Good job.
(He approves as well.)
(He was going down nicely...)
(How far are you going?)
Good job.
Hey.
(This is an old, comedic dance.)
(Dancer Kwang Soo's solo time)
What?
(She's shocked.)
- That's not it. - That's not it.
Hey, what's this?
- It's part of the performance. - Oh, gosh.
What's this?
There's the choreography that comes before this.
- That was awesome. - That was.
- She's different. - She's good.
They're all great dancers.
I don't have to mention Ju Yeon.
- Ji Min is good too. - She is.
- I guess. - She's good.
Xi A is good too.
- Elijah is good too. - Elijah...
I've seen her do the traditional mask dance.
It's ballet.
(She did the traditional mask dance.)
- Ballet? - Oh, it was ballet.
Oh, right.
- She does ballet. - What?
She does ballet. That's right.
Does anybody want to challenge that?
Do you want us to do "Gashina"?
- "Gashina"? - Sure, go ahead.
You know "Gashina", right?
- I don't really know it. - You don't?
- Do it while you have a chance. - Sorry? Hold on.
(A chance?)
Hurry up.
- You will lose your chance. - What are you saying?
Why do you say such mean things?
Since this is her first time on Running Man...
He is picking on the guest. Isn't he picking on the guest?
- Who are you to give her a chance? - Isn't he picking on the guest?
- Who are you to give her a chance? - It's not like that.
A chance like this...
- Does the dance go like this? - Who are you to give her a chance?
If she refuses to do it, she won't get screen time.
I just feel bad. I just feel bad.
SBS is giving you a lot of chances.
I hope I succeed.
(Speak for yourself.)
- I hope I succeed. - You need to do well.
(The world of variety shows is a scary place.)
- I need to do well. - You need to do well.
I received another chance today.
That's right. You need to do well.
Seriously.
Ju Yeon was incredible in her heyday.
- She is incredible. - That's right.
She is still incredible.
She was in After School.
- That's right. - There was this dance move.
- What is that? - After School's dance move.
- There is no such dance move. - No?
- There is no such dance move. - That's Psy's dance move.
What is that?
There is that dance move.
I knew it. There is that dance move.
(She puts her hand on Jong Kook's shoulder.)
- After School. - You know,
this kind of behavior amazes me.
- She didn't even ask. - Although she met Jong Kook today,
she put her hand on his shoulder like this.
- She didn't even ask. - She is the best.
(She is 1 of the top 5 psycho.)
She is the best.
She isn't aware of her surroundings.
I told you she is 1 of the top 5 psycho.
She is one of them.
I can't balance myself.
You did a good job.
His muscles are really firm.
(She is childlike.)
(She isn't aware of what she has done,)
(but everyone else is incredulous.)
That's good. That's good. Jong Kook is flustered.
Jong Kook is flustered.
(It looks like Jong Kook met his match today.)
Do Sun Mi's signature dance move of turning around...
in turns.
- Would you do that? - I can't wait to see it.
- Shall B.I go first? - B.I.
You can do this, B.I.
- What am I doing? - Touch your hair.
Let's see.
- Am I dancing by myself? - That's right.
- I see. - You are dancing by yourself.
Go ahead.
Show us your version.
(He gathers his energy.)
(He turns around innocently.)
(Did you call for me?)
(The original singer gets knocked out.)
That was good.
Sun Mi is so happy.
Seriously. It wasn't that funny.
(He shoots shyly.)
Shake your hips more, B.I. There you go.
There you go.
(He becomes absorbed in the dance.)
(I can dance to "Gashina".)
Look at the way he shakes his hips.
That was cute.
(B.I's languid movements are impressive.)
That was amazing. You moved like this.
All right. Ji Min, you are up next.
Me?
I really can't dance.
(Let's see how Ji Min does in her uncertainty.)
There you go.
That's good.
(She captivates the audience with her disheveled hair.)
(I am the queen of disheveled hair.)
(It looks amazing.)
(After doing the turn,)
(she twists her neck.)
(She can't be controlled.)
Stop it.
Turn off the music.
(That's new.)
Pass. Pass.
(We applaud her explosive energy.)
Ji Min, that was...
When you twisted your neck, you lost your balance.
- No, I didn't. - No?
It was intentional.
She is good.
Up next is Chi Chi.
A girl group, Chi Chi.
You can do this.
- What should I do? - Xi A.
You had that role of Lee Byung Hun's mother.
Please forget about that.
(What should I do?)
I will be at the yard.
(She is the most loving mother in "Mister Sunshine".)
Xi A.
(She takes the stage.)
(It's time to see the shy mother's dance skills.)
- Turn around. - Turn around.
(She is graceful and ladylike.)
(She transforms.)
(She twists her waist and blows a kiss.)
(A mother's splendid transformation)
She is good.
(Swaying)
(She even shakes her hips seductively.)
(Excuse me, ma'am.)
Excuse me.
(She can't be controlled once she lets herself go.)
(Is she the person who was hesitant before?)
Xi A.
Did I go too far?
You should have stopped after the turn.
Why did you shake your hips?
It was painful to watch.
When was Chi Chi active?
Go back to your place.
For goodness' sake.
Up next is Seung Ri.
I can't wait to see his version.
Here comes the CEO.
After more than 10 years, he became the center of Big Bang.
- That's right. - He is standing tall.
- He is receiving everyone's love. - That's right.
(It's time to see Seung Ri's version of "Gashina".)
(Turning)
(What is this?)
(After turning around in a cool way,)
(he shoots everywhere.)
(You are watching "Gashina" by Seung Ri,)
He is good.
(the dancing machine of YG Entertainment.)
(I am letting myself go.)
(His movements are shocking.)
- He is good. - He is cool.
(Am I doing a good job?)
Hold on.
Seung Ri. Seung Ri.
Seung Ri.
- I am sorry, but... - There are no members here.
Listen.
It's strange because you are so different...
when you are here without G-Dragon.
Seriously.
- He is so cool. - I am finally showing the talent...
that was inside of me.
(Seung Ri shows his talent after 10 years.)
It has been dormant for 10 years. It has been aged.
I have never taken it out before.
It has been aged.
- Is that so? - Back in the days,
you glanced over at G-Dragon after the dance.
- That's right. - He didn't like you acting up.
When I looked at him after showing my specialty,
he went, "Stop being so flippant."
(Grating his teeth)
(The leader is very strict with Seung Ri.)
Did G-Dragon do that?
That's right.
I couldn't read his mouth properly, but he went...
(Stop being so flippant.)
- He did it with a smile. - Yes, it was like that.
All right. We talked briefly.
We are now done with Sun Mi's interview.
- Really? - Yes.
Didn't we go over everyone?
- Didn't we go over everyone? - No, we haven't.
We are only done with Sun Mi's interview.
Sun Mi.
I don't even need a lot of screen time.
Can we stop?
You should take a nap from time to time...
in the upright position.
(The guests' interviews are precious.)
We have Bobby with us.
(The rapper of iKON, Bobby)
We finally meet.
You have heard of "Love Scenario" by iKON, right?
("Love Scenario" is a hit song by iKON.)
It's popular among elementary school students.
- That's right. - It's like the national anthem.
Who composed the music and wrote the lyrics?
I did.
(My partner is really awesome.)
He is really cool.
You might feel uncomfortable with revealing the actual numbers,
but how much did you make with royalties?
- The song topped the charts... - That's right.
for many months.
To be honest, I received the royalty...
three days ago.
Did it get processed only three days ago?
No, it was the second payment.
- The 2nd payment. - The 1st payment...
was about 7,800,000 dollars.
13,000,000 dollars.
The world isn't that easy.
(He is beginning to learn more about the world.)
That was good.
(I promise to work harder.)
I love B.I...
and "Killing Me" so much.
Please give us a performance.
I love it.
I love "Killing Me" so much.
(I really want to see it.)
("Killing Me" by iKON)
(They are energetic from the start.)
This is it!
- They are incredible. - This is it.
This is killing me.
(Check out my sexiness.)
(Their vein-popping dance is a treat to the eyes.)
They are good.
I can't even copy them.
(We are iKON.)
(This is the class of YG Entertainment.)
My goodness.
- Aren't they cool? - They are so cool.
When Bobby stood next to me,
he kept his eyes half-closed.
When he took the stage, he did this.
(I am telling you, he did this.)
I am serious.
- Ji Hyo. - It was no joke.
Are you sure he did this?
Did I do it wrong?
- For goodness' sake. - They are so cool.
- They are so cool. - Hold on.
They surprised me.
- Seung Ri danced with us earlier. - That's right.
Did the three of you dance?
Seung Ri, can you dance with them?
- Let's go. - Seung Ri, dance with them.
Now that he is...
the only member left from Big Bang, he does everything.
Let's do this.
(Let's do everything.)
(Seung Ri and iKON decide to perform "Killing Me".)
White Skull, are you watching this?
Yigija Unit, are you watching this?
(Are you watching this?)
(I see that he has a lot of pent-up anger.)
- What was that about? - What?
- Are you really okay? - Yes.
- Are you okay? - Yes, I am.
G-Dragon and the others won't be in the army forever.
Okay.
(He decides to worry about it later.)
Whatever, I don't care. I'll just do it.
(He brings out his instinct as a dancer.)
("Killing Me" by Seung Ri and iKON)
(Dancing in sync)
(He spreads out his wings.)
(Seung Ri soon falls out of sync.)
- Hold on. - Hold on. This is...
- Jae Seok. - Seung Ri.
He is trying to show off.
- I have something to say. - He is trying to show off.
You dance to stand out, not harmonize.
- He wants to stand out. - You know,
Bobby and B.I danced in harmony.
You tried so hard to stand out.
Because I didn't want to be outshined by iKON,
- Really? - so I asked my stylist...
if she had anything. She gave me this.
Is that so?
You should be careful of lightning.
It will destroy your back.
- Okay. - You should be careful today.
Stainless steel can be dangerous.
Seung Ri doesn't usually reveal what's inside his heart,
but I hope he would discuss this today.
He joined YG Entertainment as a dancer.
- He is a good dancer. - Tell us about Big Bang's dance.
- To be honest, - He is a really good dancer.
there are many idol groups like BTS, Wanna One,
and iKON. When you see their dance moves,
- they move like this. - That's right.
Big Bang did everything.
We practiced with famous dancers and such.
However, all of Big Bang's dances turned out this way.
(Swaying)
(It's incredibly simple.)
Why did we learn all these moves to begin with?
- Why did we learn these? - Let me sum up.
- You're not happy with them. - Exactly.
Can you dance to one of...
your songs with your own additional dance moves?
- Sure. - You can do this, right?
- Of course. - Which song will it be?
- All right. - "Lies"?
- Play "Bang Bang Bang", please. - "Bang Bang Bang".
- "Bang Bang Bang". - "Bang Bang Bang". Gosh.
Did he gain weight? I keep thinking that.
(But did Seung Ri gain weight too?)
- Hey, that was random. - Excuse me.
- I'm sorry. My apologies. - Can you at least whisper?
Everyone keeps asking if you gained weight.
- Everyone is curious. - Turn off your microphones then.
- I can hear everything. - That's enough. Stop it now.
I gained weight. Yes, yes, yes.
(Fine. I'll admit it.)
(He gains his freedom and weight.)
- Fine. I gained weight. - I'm sorry. You're about to dance.
- I got it. - He's cool now.
I can't wait to see this.
(He's the most determined.)
(His eyes undergo a change as soon as the song is played.)
(Powerful dance moves)
(But what is he doing?)
(Flapping)
- Isn't the original one better? - That looks weird.
- Hey. - Look.
(It does look different, but the moves look avant-garde.)
- Hey, that looks weird! - Wait a second.
- What is that? - The original is better.
- Hold on. The original is better. - What was that?
- This is from the ancient times. - Isn't this "Warrior's Descendant"?
- This is Seo Tai Ji's dance. - It's his dance move.
- White Skull... It's... - Listen.
(His inferiority complex is activated once again.)
He behaves worse than Seok Jin when he's drunk.
What's up with you?
(Next week, more of Seung Ri's awesomeness will air.)
(This is just the beginning.)
(Chaotic Race...)
(that will win over everyone begins in earnest.)
(Their excitement is out of this world.)
(These bubbly partners' special talents are beyond this world.)
(What's wrong with them?)
(And...)
Why does that cost nine dollars?
(This suspicious secret brings them into deeper confusion.)
(These couples are shocked.)
(They have the strangest battles to unravel the secret.)
(They desperately try in order to get out of the chaos.)
(What is the result these partners will face?)
(I salute to White Skull.)
(Are you watching this, G-Dragon?)
(Dangerous Choice Part 2)