(Last week)
(Couple Race with the special guests heated up the atmosphere.)
(The 8 guests and 8 members were paired up.)
(Ji Hyo and Bobby, Kwang Soo and Elijah, Seok Jin and Ji Min,)
(Jae Seok and Xi A, Haha and Sun Mi, Jong Kook and Ju Yeon,)
(Se Chan and B.I, and So Min and Seung Ri)
(The guests showed their charms and lengthened the opening.)
(They plan to show their charms for real this week.)
(White Skull Infantry Division, are you watching this?)
(The show that doesn't hold back begins now.)
(The hot guests deserve a lengthy introduction.)
It's Lee Elijah's turn next.
- It's finally her turn. - It's finally her turn.
(She is like a part of the Running Man family.)
Elijah, you got paired up with Kwang Soo.
What does the agency think of Kwang Soo?
(Laughing)
- Please be honest. - That's right.
Tell us.
- What is it? - Prince.
- Prince? - Prince of Asia?
Does the agency think of him as the Prince of Asia?
I don't know him very well.
(She gives up on giving a statement.)
You should make something up!
Don't get angry.
- I mean... - You two aren't close.
- You're really not. - I mean...
Not even strangers would do that.
- She should make something up. - Seriously.
They're worse than strangers.
What is Elijah's image within the agency?
- Please be honest, Kwang Soo. - That's right.
- What did you hear? - What is it?
Even before I met Elijah on Running Man,
(How does a fellow celebrity in her agency see Elijah?)
I heard that she is really crazy.
- That can't be true. - I heard that she is really unique.
You heard that she is unique. Is it wrong, Elijah?
- Of course it is. - Both So Min and Ju Yeon...
- are crazy. - Crazy people are unaware.
- That's right. - How am I crazy?
Everyone else knows...
- except for them. - I am really not crazy.
Up next is E Xi A.
I can't wait.
- I can't wait. - Like I told you before,
Xi A was a member of a girl group in 2012.
- As a member of Chi Chi, - Right.
she worked mostly in Japan.
What does Chi Chi mean?
It was an acronym for creative electronic house idol.
In Japanese, Chi Chi means chest.
(However...)
- Really? - Yes. It was embarrassing.
Her words made me solemn.
We don't know how to react to that.
- It just happened that way. - Yes.
- You must have been shocked. - Yes.
- How did that happen? - We used to have...
a member called Gary. Gary means diarrhea...
in Japanese.
(Diarrhea is our friend.)
Something like that can happen...
- Seriously? - by pure chance.
- In that case, - Let's see Chi Chi's performance.
show us Chi Chi's performance.
- Let's go. - The dance is really cute.
I am too old for this.
She is cute.
Let's see Chi Chi's performance.
(She takes the stage as a member of Chi Chi.)
(She transforms.)
(She turns on the switch for a girl group member's face.)
(She is confident.)
She is incredible.
- Do you know this song? - Yes, I do. I remember it.
(There is no way this isn't the crazy girl special.)
- Do you know this song? - I know this song.
I remember it.
(Without hesitation, she gives a professional performance.)
She is good.
- Her body remembers. - Give her a round of applause.
Isn't she great?
(After shaking her body,)
(she goes back to her place.)
- She is good. - She is good.
- She can dance well. - She is cool.
- You were surprised, right? - I got goosebumps.
- Forget about "Mr. Sunshine". - She's completely different.
- She is a different person. - She really is a different person.
Sexy!
He keeps going, "Sexy!"
- "Sexy!" - I thought I was hearing things.
Even when Seung Ri danced, he shouted, "Sexy!"
He keeps going, "Sexy!"
(Even when Seung Ri danced...)
(Sexy!)
(Even when So Min danced...)
(B.I's automatic reaction involves shouting, "Sexy!")
- He keeps going, "Sexy!" - Are you trying to make it a thing?
- Are you trying to make it a thing? - No, I am not.
- They are sexy. - Sexy.
In an interview, you said that Running Man was a program...
- you'd want to be in. - That's right.
Really? Although we haven't gotten started in earnest,
how does it feel to be here? Is it nerve-wracking?
- It's really fun. - What was the most fun?
Because Kwang Soo looks exactly like my brother,
I can't help but laugh every time I see him.
- Does your brother look like him? - Yes.
He looks exactly like my brother.
- Really? - Yes.
- Does your brother look like him? - Really?
How can a man with a sister like her look like him?
There is a resemblance. Their mouths look similar.
Does your brother have a nickname?
Kwang Soo.
(Her brother's nickname is Kwang Soo.)
Does your brother like the nickname?
- No, he doesn't. - He doesn't.
(He doesn't like the nickname.)
What is going on? I was just standing here.
- I was just standing here. - They look the same.
- So... - She is laughing at my face.
- What is your brother's name? - They look the same.
- His name is E Jang Gi. - Jang Gi?
Jang Gi?
- Jang Gi? - E Jang Gi.
- E Jang Gi. - Jang Gi?
- Jang Gi? - Is his name Jang Gi?
- What a coincidence! - Jang Gi?
- This is uncanny. - I am curious about him.
- You should remember this. - What?
You will die if you see your doppelganger.
I doubt we look the same.
- You will die. - I mean...
You shouldn't look at his picture if it comes up in this episode.
- Why not? - He already saw his doppelganger.
- He saw Han Gi Beom. - He already saw his doppelganger.
He will die soon.
Park Se Ri says it's really hard to avoid running into you.
(That must be the reason why she won't visit Running Man.)
I am sure I will see her someday.
They resemble each other.
The last guest is Ju Yeon. Like I said before,
Ju Yeon is So Min's best friend and a former member of After School.
After School had...
a lot of hit songs.
Why don't you show us After School's performance?
We need to see "Diva".
We have to see this.
We have to see that.
When she goes to a karaoke, she plays her song and dances.
- Really? - Yes.
(She has an abundant love for herself.)
You danced in front of a convenience store.
- What? - She was drinking beer...
in front of a convenience store when she turned on the music.
She really did that.
(A drunk performance of "Diva")
- She did that at dawn. - There was a garbage truck.
- She really did that. - Really?
- The sun was rising. - She is incredible.
Ju Yeon, give us a performance of "Diva".
- Show us your charisma. - Show us.
(Here it comes.)
That's it.
(Everyone in this country knows.)
This is great.
(I am your)
(Diva, diva, di, di, di, diva)
(Practicing in front of the convenience store was effective.)
(Ji Hyo is turning into a diva too.)
(Ju Yeon is being normal for the first time on this show.)
(She was my idol when I was in the military.)
(The song brings back memories.)
That was amazing.
We haven't heard this song in a while.
- It's very fun, right? - I love it.
I like it. It brings back memories.
Anyone could follow the dance moves.
It'd be so fun to dance with the audience.
- Should we all try? - What?
Let's try dancing all together.
(Suddenly?)
I'm sorry. She's like this.
She's like this.
- All together? - Yes.
Sure.
Ju Yeon, stand in the center.
You should all do it.
We don't know when we'll get to see...
After School again.
You won't.
(Determined)
You don't have to...
You'll have to see them on "Saturday, Saturday Is a Singer".
Will we...
- But that show... - Oh, it's over too.
We don't know what will happen.
Jae Seok.
(Will "Saturday, Saturday Is a Singer" be able to air?)
It's complicated.
We need "Saturday, Saturday Is a Singer" to see After School.
Haha!
- Haha! - Get up.
Haha.
(How are you doing, Myung Soo and Jun Ha?)
- He's crying. - Stop it.
Change the subject.
- Yes. - Change the subject.
Okay!
I can hold it back. I'm not going to cry.
(I'm okay.)
Shall we start?
Okay. Should we dance together?
Since it's been so long,
all the staff members...
should shout it together.
Give energy to Ju Yeon.
Dear citizens, I beg you.
Please shout the chorus!
Let's start from the cameramen.
Start.
(Why are we doing this?)
Camera directors, start.
Chan Hee, come on!
- Lighting director, start. - Start.
(He must have been waiting.)
Good.
We're one.
- We're one. - Pronounce it correctly.
(The whole staff miraculously comes together.)
Let's go!
5, 6...
(Tonight, tomorrow night, I can't stop thinking of you)
(I'm your)
(Diva, diva, di, di, diva!)
(Try it at home and at work.)
(Diva, diva, di, di, diva)
It's been so long.
I love it.
Sexy.
- Sexy. - Sexy.
- It brings back memories. - It's amazing.
(Satisfied)
Before we start the race,
please change into your team uniforms...
and fill in the couple registration from.
"Before we start the race"?
We've already been shooting for four hours.
I thought we were doing a talking race today.
We're just done introducing ourselves.
Seung Ri isn't saying anything.
- He was overzealous... - He's exhausted.
in the beginning.
(It's finally time to show off your charms. The real race starts now.)
- Come here. - Hi.
- Have a seat. - There are some refreshments.
There's so much.
"Couple registration form".
We have to fill it in?
(Every couple has to fill in a registration form.)
Specialty?
I've never lost in 3, 6, 9 my entire life.
- He's good at it. - I've never lost.
I'm really good at multiplication tables.
That's why I could start school early.
Gosh, really?
- Because you were good? - Yes.
Is that possible?
That's strange.
You can start school early if you're good at multiplication tables?
I didn't start school early because of my birthday.
- It was multiplication tables. - Seriously?
- Yes. - Is that possible?
Do you have mythomania?
- It's true. - No matter how good you are...
She just wants to say that she was very good even as a kid.
Are you still good though?
I don't know because I haven't tried.
Then it doesn't count.
It doesn't matter if you were good as a kid.
Should I give it a try?
(Se Chan and B.I are the only male couple.)
First of all,
why don't we write that our specialty is dance?
- That sounds great. - Is there any song...
you want?
Well...
- Let's take a look first. - I...
personally...
think we should play your song.
Then we'll get a chance.
Let's see.
Let's start from here.
What do you think?
Do you know this song?
I do.
If we play this, Haha will go like this.
But Haha might...
steal attention from us.
- You think so? Okay. - Pass.
(The next song is...)
("Untitled" by G-Dragon.)
I can do an impression of him.
Try it.
Even just once
Isn't that just B.I?
- If I could see you - If I could see you
(All guests today are very self-confident.)
Let's try another song.
- Do you know what this is? - What is it?
(Haha and Sun Mi take pictures for the registration form.)
(Haha does his best to look cute.)
(Pressing)
Is it a selfie stick?
(They look surprisingly cute together.)
Let's do a sexy version.
(We're sexy.)
I'm going to copy you.
(Narcissistic)
(What are you guys doing?)
The pictures look amazing.
(They're done filling in the registration forms.)
(But these registration forms have a secret.)
(The eight couples are gathered for the mission.)
You guys look so awkward together.
He is tying a shoelace around me, saying it's in fashion.
Is that from your underwear?
It's a shoelace. It's apparently in fashion.
(Se Chan is wearing a trendy item.)
- Are you judges? - No.
(I don't care about the fashion.)
I thought they were judges too.
No.
They look the same.
Do you have your couple registration forms with you?
- Yes. - Yes.
(All the couples filled in the couple registration forms.)
There's a secret...
behind today's race.
What is it? Are there spies again?
I knew it.
I knew there would be spies.
Some people must have come earlier.
Will you take the stickers off your registration forms?
(They didn't even know there was a sticker.)
"Couple IOU"?
What is this?
(Couple IOU)
Couple IOU?
(It's a couple IOU.)
What is this?
"We will..."
You deceived us.
I hate to owe someone.
Are you in debt?
- Why did you do that? - I didn't do anything.
(When did we get into debt?)
(What are these signed couple IOUs?)
All of you are...
in debt right now.
- Why? - Why?
All the couple items,
couple bags,
and refreshments you took...
have been taken into calculation.
Even the macarons and jellies?
- What? - That's ridiculous.
(Even the jellies?)
- Gosh. - You...
That's just ridiculous.
The debt is per individual, right?
You share your debt with your partner.
(The debt is shared between partners.)
Elijah even packed some food.
- I was hungry. - She did?
- She packed some food. - She did?
(Her greed left her in debt.)
You have to work together with your partner...
to pay off your debts.
The race is called Eternal Love.
(Eternal Love)
- Eternal Love. - Eternal Love.
After every mission, the winners will win prize money.
And that amount will be written off from their debts.
If you fail to pay off your debts,
you'll be penalized...
according to the amount left.
Let me tell you how much each of you owe right now.
Our debt might not be that big.
First, Seok Jin and Ji Min.
- I don't think we owe a lot. - Couple bracelets, 50 dollars.
- These? - These?
(Couple bracelets, 50 dollars)
Nice.
What?
They're worth 50 dollars?
- These are worth 50 dollars? - These?
No way.
My skin is reacting.
- Where did you get these? - These are worth 50 dollars?
Couple bracelets, 50 dollars.
- It makes my skin itch. - They're ripping us off.
A bottle of water, four cookies and candies,
and five macarons.
Why did you eat so much?
(5 macarons?)
Why is he so obsessed with macarons?
I'm the only one who ate them.
- You didn't eat any. - He ate so much.
And a pen.
It's 73 dollars in total.
That's a lot.
We're doomed.
(Seok Jin has never earned that much from his stock investments.)
Kwang Soo and Elijah.
You'll be surprised.
Couple headphones, 50 dollars.
Oh, my.
(Couple headphones, 50 dollars)
(Shocked)
I...
didn't even want the headphones. I just liked the note.
1 fruit, 3 macarons,
a cup of coffee, a bottle of water,
- and four cookies and candies. - They ate so much.
I didn't eat any. It's what Elijah packed.
(I didn't get to have any.)
Two pens and a box of wet wipes.
(How much do they owe?)
It's 81 dollars in total.
(It's a new record.)
Okay. It's over 80 dollars!
- We owe just 70 dollars. - We can do this.
I mean...
Se Chan and B.I. Couple socks,
- 20 dollars. They're the cheapest. - Okay.
1 pudding, 2 cookies and candies, and 2 pens.
It's 30 dollars in total. It's the lowest amount.
Gosh.
We can do this.
(Debt Amounts)
The first mission to pay off your debts is...
Specialty Pawnshop.
(Specialty Pawnshop)
Oh, that.
(Running Man Pawnshop is here to buy specialties.)
- We have to buy something? - Specialties.
All the couples wrote down their specialties in the forms,
and we're going to verify them.
If you succeed, the pawnshop will determine the price...
and buy your specialty.
(The pawnshop will determine the price of the specialty.)
The first specialty is...
- impressions. - Who wrote it?
- Me. - Me.
- Ji Min... - Did you write it too?
(Ji Min and Sun Mi's specialties are impressions.)
Sun Mi wrote it too.
Ji Min, what are you going to do?
To warm up,
- I'll mimic Dooly's mom. - Dooly's mom.
You know who she is, right?
You have to know Dooly to understand this.
You know Dooly, right?
Look carefully. It's Dooly's mom.
Dooly.
(Dooly)
(It's Dooly's mom.)
That's how she sounds.
Dooly.
That's exactly how she sounds.
Where is he?
Right. That's how she sounds.
I had completely forgotten, but I remember it now.
It's from my memory.
- "Where is he?" - It's from the cartoon.
So Min wants to mix things up.
She wants to mimic Dooly's mom...
in Joo Hyun's voice.
Okay.
In Joo Hyun's voice.
Dooly's mom?
(So Min wants to try it in the only voice she can mimic.)
Gosh, Dooly.
(Gosh, Dooly.)
(Isn't that just Joo Hyun?)
(The reaction is lukewarm.)
Gosh, Dooly, that punk. Where is he?
(So Min becomes desperate.)
(She ruins the childhood memories.)
(She becomes desperate and makes Dooly's mom swear.)
Since you just mimicked an animal...
Xi A is going to surprise you.
- Can she do it? - She can...
mimic dogs perfectly.
When she barks, all the dogs in her neighborhood bark back.
(Shouldn't she go on "How is that Possible?")
- That's how good she is? - Yes.
She's a native speaker.
What kind of dog?
- I'll do both big and small. - Both big and small.
Let's start with a big dog.
(A big dog)
(A small dog)
See?
(It's nothing special.)
- She's good. - B.I can do it too.
(Barking)
It's a seal.
- Is that a seal or a dog? - It's a countryside dog.
(That's not how you do it.)
(What?)
(It suddenly turns into a dog fight.)
(A Maltese puppy jumps in.)
(Xi A did say she could make all dogs bark.)
(She is making all the dogs here bark.)
It's turned into a dog fight.
It's a dog fight.
Stop barking!
(A neighbor gets angry.)
We'll have to do...
a barking competition. You just saw it, right?
Xi A can both bark normally...
and fight. She can fight too.
We can do a countryside dog.
Xi A can fight with a countryside dog too.
Bring it on. Go on. If you laugh, you lose.
(B.I is warming up.)
(Suddenly, she changes.)
- He lost. - You lost.
- B.I lost. - They were fighting.
What kind of game is this? What is this?
How do you know who wins?
B.I did lower his tail.
- Right? - I did expose my belly.
Good.
You win.
- Bring it on. - I win.
If you're a dog, we'll try a cat.
- Okay. - A cat and a dog can fight too.
Come on in. Come here.
Good.
(Calm)
(Despite Xi A's attack,)
(Sun Mi remains calm.)
(She might soon bite Sun Mi.)
(Sun Mi explodes.)
Hold on.
Good.
She did well, right? It gave me goosebumps.
How do you know who wins?
- What is this? - What...
What is this?
- What kind of game is this? - Who just won?
Who won?
- I want to try a cat. - Ju Yeon wants to try a cat.
- Ju Yeon will try a cat. - Ju Yeon and...
- Sun Mi should compete. - Try.
- A cat? - Yes.
Sun Mi, you're doing great.
Are you ready?
(Cute)
(They start cute.)
(But soon they reveal their true colors.)
(Be quiet!)
What is this? If you do this, do you win?
(No one knows the criteria,)
(but somehow you can determine who wins.)
What is this? Why did she do that?
Is the cat's fur standing on end?
- Yes, exactly. - It's the cat's fur standing up.
(There are mean cats in this world.)
Good job.
- Good job. - I won.
- We can do a chimpanzee. - Okay.
- A chimpanzee. - A chimpanzee.
(A chimpanzee escapes.)
(Here comes a chimpanzee.)
Make some sounds.
(So Min always looks clumsy, but she is actually pretty good.)
You're supposed to mimic the sounds.
Make some sounds!
So Min, make some sounds!
(It's a competition where you have to mimic sounds.)
If I make a sound, I can't look like a chimpanzee.
(Dilemma)
(She forces herself to make sounds.)
(So Min fails because she doesn't sound very much like a chimpanzee.)
Good.
Very good.
She just looks like one.
If no one... You want to try?
- Sun Mi can mimic Kim Hye Soo. - Kim Hye Soo.
- Kim Hye Soo? - Listen carefully.
- It's from "Tazza". - Kim Hye Soo.
- Seriously? - Listen carefully.
Stop right there!
I can shoot you!
She sounds exactly like her.
(This is the original version.)
(I can shoot you!)
Leave the money right there. I'll shoot you.
No!
Stop!
- I can shoot you, Sun Mi! - I can shoot you!
(Your specialty can get stolen.)
Why did you have to do that?
Fail.
(Se Chan steals Sun Mi's specialty.)
Ju Yeon, can you do something?
It's okay to do something very small too.
- Really? - You don't have to be good.
- Don't worry. - Gosh. Don't skip meals.
- Who is that? - Explain first.
(No one has heard it before.)
- Who is that? - Who is that?
Your dad?
Yes, it's my dad.
(How did you know?)
Your dad?
How can you mimic your own dad?
Please do it again.
Gosh. Don't skip meals.
- Is that what he always tells you? - Yes.
Let me try.
Get out, you punk!
(Get out, you punk!)
It's my dad. My dad.
Let me mimic my mom.
This disgusting Ha family.
(This disgusting Ha family.)
(What happened to Haha's mom?)
I win, right? It happened just yesterday.
- It happened yesterday. - Let us win!
(They even mimic their own families.)
(The pawnshop is judging their specialties carefully.)
The next specialty is "body".
- Okay! Bring it on. - Okay!
- Okay! - Sun Mi.
We're confident.
You have to twist your body parts, right?
Let's start from the person who wrote it...
and move onto others.
Xi A will start.
Okay.
My tongue can reach my elbow.
Look.
It's not supposed to?
(It's very difficult.)
(Her tongue reaches her elbow easily.)
See?
- How do you do it? - Her tongue touches her elbow.
Here?
(I think I can do it too.)
Where exactly?
(They all try,)
(but it doesn't work.)
Elijah.
She can't.
(Forcing)
(Kwang Soo forcefully brings her elbow to her tongue.)
- Gosh. - It worked.
- Seriously. - You're lying.
You can't, right?
(No one apart from Xi A can do it.)
- Ji Min should win. - That's right.
(Everyone, Ji Min should win.)
(Ji Min should win?)
- Look at her. - Ji Min...
(Her tongue reaches her elbow so easily.)
There you go.
(She is even faster...)
(than Xi A.)
- Her tongue is so long. - Her tongue is so long.
- Look at Ji Min. - Ji Min...
She can lick all over her arm.
(She can lick all over her arm.)
She really can.
(Ji Min steals Xi A's specialty.)
No one can beat Ji Min.
She can lick all over her arm.
I won't be able to get married because of Running Man.
Can anyone do something else?
Can I try walking on my hands?
She can walk on her hands.
What's that?
(She is flexible from yoga training.)
(Ju Yeon is going to walk on her hands.)
Hold on. It seems like I can only swing.
(It seems like I can only swing.)
Ju Yeon.
Who can't do that?
Who can't swing like that?
I can swing.
I can swing on my hands.
Ju Yeon, please stop.
You keep disappointing me with small things.
(It's not a big disappointment.)
It's nothing big, but...
Ju Yeon.
(Ju Yeon keeps disappointing us.)
It's fine, but...
So Min, what are you doing?
It's a cobra.
(Isn't it incredible?)
Do it at home instead.
(He cuts her off.)
It's not appropriate for the show.
It's not good enough.
Go back.
So Min showed the cobra to Seok Jin.
"Oh, it's a cobra."
(What do you think?)
(A moment ago)
(It's a cobra. You don't know?)
(Oh, it's a cobra.)
(He's not interested.)
I just wanted her to stop.
(I'm sorry, So Min.)
(The body specialty competition is over.)
Let me go over the things you wrote.
(So Min and Seung Ri wrote the next one.)
So Min and Seung Ri wrote, "dance".
We can dance to any kind of music.
- That sounds fun. - That's right.
- To any kind of music. - Any kind?
Any kind.
- We can dance to anything. - That's impossible.
If it's true, it really is a specialty.
- I can dance to anything. - Really?
- Even to the nature sounds? - Yes.
Okay. Give us some music.
(His specialty will be verified. What's the first music?)
(Shark family)
(Seung Ri is ready.)
(He starts to dance right away.)
There you go.
(It's a grown-up shark.)
- He's mimicking a shark. - It's a shark.
He's very creative.
(The grown-up shark is getting ready to swim.)
He's good.
(He suddenly lowers his fins.)
- He's good. - He's good.
(How can he dance like this to this song?)
It's getting fun.
(Are you ready to jump with the grown-up shark?)
(Excited)
(Cute)
(This grown-up shark seems old. He's definitely not a baby shark.)
He's cute.
How cute.
- The song changed. - Hey.
- That has a nice vibe. - That's the sound of a valley.
(Can he dance to the sound of water?)
Can he dance to this?
He's pondering.
(He's dancing!)
(His wavy dance move conveys the sound of the water as it is.)
- That looks like water. - He's expressing the valley.
(She acknowledges his expression.)
- He's very expressive. - It really resembles water.
(All of a sudden, the scene turns into a valley.)
He did definitely earn his spot with his dancing.
- He's pretty good. - He gained a lot of weight.
(He's dancing pretty well, but he gained a lot of weight.)
It looks just like the flow of the water.
(His movement is light, albeit his weight gain.)
- He can make this work. - I mean...
He really did. Look at his bottom.
(The song changes once again. What is this familiar song?)
(It's the news theme song that notifies the 8pm news.)
He's flustered a bit.
(News? All of a sudden?)
(I danced to the sound of water. This is a piece of cake.)
(She's amazed. He can dance to this song well too.)
(He's expressing that the news is on.)
That's the TV.
- That's the TV. - That's the screen.
Something is airing. Something is airing.
- The news is airing. - He's pretty good.
- He's expressing the TV. - It's airing.
- That's the TV. - It's the 8pm news.
- He's expressing the TV. - The 8pm news.
- That's the TV. - He's expressing the 8pm news.
- It's 8pm. 8pm. - 8pm.
- Let's give it up for him. - He's so good.
Who wants to try dancing to the water sound and the 8pm news?
I'll accept challengers for these two songs.
(Anyone can challenge him.)
Okay. Should I try it?
- You should. - B.I.
B.I!
You'll dance to the water sound and the news theme song.
Do the trendy moves like this.
- B.I. - He might be good at this.
(The sound of water plays first.)
- This isn't easy. - My gosh.
It's not easy to dance to this.
(He wriggles his body as soon as the song begins.)
(I can see the water.)
Keep going. Even your microphone is helping too.
- That's right. - It looks like the flowing water.
He's pretty good.
(Sometimes, I dance to the water sound.)
It looks like the flowing water.
(He's flexible and expressive. B.I's water dance is a threat.)
Express the water flowing down. Go for it, B.I. That's it.
That's it. The water is flowing down.
His movement does look like water flowing down. Seriously.
Dance to the 8pm news song.
- 8pm news? - That was great.
Get into the rhythm.
You must look serious.
- This isn't easy to pull off. - His dance looks hopeful.
- His dance looks hopeful. - It's not easy.
(His gestures and footwork suddenly look drastically old.)
(Hold on. I'm not done yet.)
(Something seems off.)
- It's getting hard. - It's hard.
I think his steps got all jumbled up.
He's doing the same dance moves.
He danced well to the water sound, but he messed up with the news song.
He used the same hand and foot at the same time like this.
Before he realized it, this was what happened to him.
- At this point... - Stop that.
I'm sorry. He's the leader of iKON, but this is what he did.
- B.I was good, - This must be hard.
but Seung Ri was better.
You must express that something was going to air.
It's because he didn't prepare the choreography in advance.
Elijah, do you want to try this?
- Go for it if you want to. Great. - My gosh.
Here's the thing. You never know what will happen.
- Exactly. - You really don't know.
She learned dancing for three years.
Here it is.
(She starts differently from the others by turning.)
(Exuding her sexiness)
(What? That doesn't look sexy.)
What is that?
- What a twist! - What is that?
(We thought the dance was going to look sexy,)
(but she awkwardly moves her body.)
(She unexpectedly moves her body as if it's getting dislocated.)
(Strangely, this awkward movement goes well with the theme song.)
- That's so fitting. It works. - Great. Great.
- What a twist. - She's doing well.
- My goodness. - Well done.
My goodness. That was great. The last one was great.
- The last one was great. - The song ended.
(She reinterpreted the theme song with her awkward movement.)
This one. The last one was great. It was awesome.
- Her dance had depth. - Right now...
- That was great. - Exactly.
- Right now... - Even Seung Ri recognized that.
- That was great. - I never knew the song was upbeat.
- Well done. - It was really good.
- You ought to try it too. - You must.
- You must dance. - Go for it.
- What am I going to do? - I think she's going to do well.
I'm not that good at dancing.
- Xi A, take it easy. - Okay.
Xi A is up. She'll dance to the water sound first.
(What? She suddenly shakes off her body.)
Great, great. That was awesome, Xi A.
Xi A. You're doing well.
- She looked uninterested at first. - She's so serious.
- She was uninterested at first. - That was great just now.
- She's good. - My gosh.
Xi A, it's going to be the 8pm news. The 8pm news theme song.
- The 8pm news song. She's good. - 8pm news.
(Bouncing off)
(I'll start cheerfully. The 8pm news will begin!)
(She vigorously shakes her body.)
(Just like the breaking news, it's brief and simple.)
She dances like my mother.
She sort of dances like me.
- Here it comes. - She has to go for it now.
(For some reason...)
- Here it is. - That's the shuffle.
(Something looks off.)
(She does the shuffle which is an old dance move.)
(And she dances the hammer dance which is trending now.)
- What is this? - Why did she mix those?
- No way. - She did this dance instead.
- Xi A, I liked everything. - She should've done this instead.
What was this?
(She fails to overcome the theme song.)
That was great. It was great.
Xi A's dance was good,
- but it's Elijah versus Seung Ri. - That's right. Yes.
The final match is between Elijah and Seung Ri.
The scores are being tallied up at the pawnshop.
- They're doing that now. - The process is thorough.
All right. We'll choose a different song for the last match.
- A new song? - Yes, we'll pick a different song.
- We'll play the song now. - Okay.
(What is the last song that will decide the last match?)
(It's the theme song of a Saturday show, "Unanswered Questions".)
- It's for "Unanswered Questions". - This is a hard one.
- They must dance to this song. - They'll dance to this?
(To this song?)
- Seung Ri. He's Kim Sang Joong. - He's getting ready.
- It's his facial expression. - It looks like Kim Sang Joong's.
(He resembles Kim Sang Joong, but what kind of dance will he show us?)
(Turning)
(He dominates the atmosphere with a serious turn.)
(Dancing)
(Everyone is laughing at his playful movements.)
(She's the only one who can't seem to laugh.)
(She's practicing in a serious manner.)
- She's ready to do hers now. - She's getting into the rhythm.
- She wants to win. She's trying. - She's getting into the rhythm.
(Looking silly)
(But here's the thing.)
- Great! - Elijah is joining him.
(Elijah, who finishes practicing, sets out.)
- Elijah. - They look good together.
(Thus began the unexpected pair dance of "Unanswered Questions".)
My goodness.
(For some reason, their dances seem similar.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Their dances look similar.
(These two master dancers' gestures and facial expressions are similar.)
Elijah is great.
We watched Seung Ri dance. I really liked this one.
- That was great. I liked it too. - It was.
- It was good, right? - It was connected.
But Elijah isn't an easy match.
(Swinging)
(It's my turn now.)
- She's "Tomb Raider". - It fits the music.
- What about the highlight? - It's coming up.
- She looks really serious too. - Four,
3, 2, 1.
(Lightly shaking)
(She does her signature dance move again.)
Hey, her dance suits the song.
(Her dance move reminds them of the dance from the 90s.)
(Her old dance suits the song again.)
- That's Fin.K.L's dance. - It's the same dance.
Hey, that looks like S.E.S' dance.
- It's S.E.S' dance. - Wasn't that the dance move?
- She's using them well. - All of a sudden, it changed.
That was great.
(Elijah reinterpreted the theme song of "Unanswered Questions".)
I couldn't breathe.
- It was. - That was sudden.
(It was like Deux's "In Summer".)
I had no idea that she'd do this to the theme song of that show.
I'm very curious how this challenge will affect these two.
- You should give her more points. - Please be generous.
- Next one is B.I. - B.I.
- He wrote, "writing poems". - What?
- Poems? - Writing poems?
Usually, I write lyrics a lot.
I titled this to "Running Man".
- Let me recite a brief poem. - Great.
- The title, "Running Man". - "Running Man".
"A small version of our society, Running Man."
(I'm already getting into the poem.)
"My mom once told me..."
"that airtime leads to my pay, and I must take care of my airtime."
"You must swim against the popular opinion to be on TV."
(These personalities on variety shows totally agree.)
"When everyone says 1 word, say 10 to be on TV."
(That's why I talked so much.)
"Show your right cheek when they slap your left."
"That's how people will see that you even got slapped."
(Only one clip aired.)
(Running Man is the hub of personalities on variety shows.)
- That was great. It's amazing. - My goodness, that example.
(B.I's theory of "Two Slaps on Variety Shows" moves them.)
- That example. It touched my heart. - It's amazing.
I can relate.
"I will try to become a fox to survive..."
"in this animal kingdom that's swarming with wild beasts."
"Lee Kwang Soo. I only have one target."
(Lee Kwang Soo. I only have one target.)
(Why me? All of a sudden? Why on earth would that be me?)
- Why... - Come on.
(Even the end of B.I's "Running Man" is neat.)
- His expressions were great. - I wrote this in a hurry yesterday.
- In a way, you could say that... - He wore that famous song too.
- it's the reality of variety shows. - That's right.
"Show your right cheek..."
- "when they slap your left." - "When they slap your left."
- "Only a slap will air on TV." - "Only a slap will air on TV."
Gosh, your poem definitely struck a chord with us.
Let's give him a big hand.
It was amazing.
It was so touching.
This is why he writes so many good songs.
Lastly, Elijah's specialty is...
- her sense of balance. - I see.
She learned ballet too.
1 player will spin 10 times...
and pour the water into the cup over their partner's head...
within five seconds. Pour the most water into the cup to win.
(Spin and pour the water into your partner's cup.)
- Let us try first. - Okay.
Bobby and Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes.
It'd be fun to see Bobby get splashed with water.
Ready.
- Let's go. - Ready.
(Ji Hyo has to spin 10 times and pour the water into Bobby's cup.)
- Ready. - Hold on.
Go.
- 1... - 1...
(She has to try to pour as much water as possible into the cup.)
- 4, - 4,
- 5, 6... - 5, 6...
(Ji Hyo is doing great.)
(Ji Hyo has spun 7 times.)
(She has to grab the basket.)
Grab it.
(Unstable)
(She grabs the basket.)
Go.
(Now she has to pour the water into the cup.)
(Running)
(She splashes the water over Bobby.)
(No water goes into the cup.)
(I feel dizzy. Let me lie down for a moment.)
She wasn't planning on pouring the water into the cup.
My goodness.
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
- She's a spy. - Ji Hyo.
- No one pays attention to Bobby. - Ji Hyo.
Everyone is focused on Ji Hyo.
You should control your body well.
You shouldn't just splash the water like Ji Hyo did.
You can never get to your partner.
As soon as you grab the basket...
Sun Mi will try.
What should I do?
I can't see anything right now.
That's good. That might help.
Dancers know how to spin without getting dizzy.
That's right.
- Let's start. - Okay.
Ready.
- Go. - You can do this.
- 1, 2. - Good. She's fast.
- What's with her? - Three.
What is she doing?
(Are you already feeling dizzy?)
- Already? - You have to bend over.
- 5, 6. - 5, 6.
(She screamed from the beginning. Will she be able to walk?)
- Grab the basket! - Go!
Gosh.
Hold on.
(Will she show off a dance singer's sense of balance?)
(Let me grab the bowl.)
(She falls.)
(Just like Ji Hyo,)
(let me lie down for a moment.)
- Are you okay? - Sun Mi!
Are you okay?
- Is this real? - Is your head okay?
- Sun Mi! - Are you okay?
- Is your head okay? - Are you okay?
Hey.
(At a moment like this...)
"Siren"!
Call an ambulance!
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
- She couldn't even grab the bowl. - Are you okay?
This is the funniest thing you've ever done on variety shows.
Ever since her debut,
how could she fall so naturally?
- Now Se Chan and... - B.I.
B.I will try.
Let's go.
They might be better. They're both guys.
- Ready. - Let's do this.
Go.
(Se Chan and B.I start.)
(Se Chan is holding the cup, and B.I is spinning.)
(They seem to be serious about the mission.)
He's getting dizzy. Eight.
Nine.
Let's do this.
(They're going to make use of their speed and athletic abilities.)
- 9. - 9.
- 10. - 10.
(He approaches the bowl.)
(He rolls.)
(When someone lies down during a mission,)
(you should play their new song.)
This is too much.
(This is the perfect moment to promote "Killing Me".)
(Good job, B.I.)
Look at him.
Gosh.
What is this?
Some people feel dizzy very easily.
Gosh.
Did I get some in?
- You spilled everything. - I'm sorry.
His cochlea...
Sit down and rest.
- Take a break. - Take a break.
Let us try.
- Today... - Okay.
- Let's win. - Well...
Ji Min is going to compete...
in a show this fall.
Start.
(She spins very quickly.)
She's fast.
- 4, 5... - 4, 5...
(You're doing great.)
- Where is my cup? - 7, 8...
(Seok Jin forgot his cup.)
Give me a cup! I forgot my cup.
- Give me a cup! - Just continue!
(They're not allowed to stop once they start.)
- I forgot my cup. - Grab the bowl!
(Ji Min keeps spinning without realizing what's going on.)
- Grab the bowl! - Give me a cup!
(She has to grab the bowl.)
5, 4...
Give me a cup!
(I need a cup to hold the water.)
(The other members keep track of time.)
(What?)
(You have no cup?)
(Why don't you?)
(Ji Min splashes the water on Seok Jin's face.)
- I don't have a cup! - Why don't you have a cup?
(He makes everyone laugh by forgetting his cup.)
He has no cup.
Here's your cup.
I don't need it anymore.
(Angry)
Just do something with it. Put your booger in it or something.
Did your booger come out?
You should get your cup yourself.
It's Seok Jin's fault.
- You should get your cup. - Think about it.
Seok Jin is playing the game. Who else would get him the cup?
(The nation's favorite host wipes the floor.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
Someone might slip.
(He's so thoughtful.)
He's so thoughtful.
(Is that why he's so popular?)
(I don't want my colleagues to get hurt.)
Don't air this.
(Seok Jin feels grumpy.)
- What are you doing? - It's part of my contract.
Something like this has to be included...
- in every episode. - It has to air?
- Yes. - That's a good idea.
You being kind?
- They have to show your kindness? - Yes.
- It's part of the contract. - They have to air it.
Don't air it. I don't want him to look good.
It'd make him look too nice.
Ready.
Go.
- Ju Yeon has never done this. - 1, 2...
- Three. - You're doing great.
(You're doing great, Ju Yeon.)
- 7, 8... - 7, 8...
(She is fast and stable.)
Go. Hurry up. 5, 4...
Come here.
Just come here.
Here we go.
Let's do this!
- Hold him. - 5, 4, 3...
Here we go!
(Pouring)
(Ju Yeon disappears.)
She poured a lot.
(Incredible)
She did pour some into the cup.
(The cup is almost half full.)
(After pouring the water into the cup,)
(Ju Yeon disappeared.)
(She falls.)
Hold on.
(She is forced to take a break in the corner.)
Are you okay?
- She poured some into the cup. - Ju Yeon.
Here we go!
(At a moment like this, your own song is the best medicine.)
(This will give her energy.)
(I'm your diva, diva, di, di, diva)
I mean...
You did a good job.
Are we in first place?
(Jong Kook and Ju Yeon are far ahead of the others.)
Seung Ri and So Min.
Please mimic G-Dragon.
(The impression vending machine is on.)
(If I could see you)
(Are you watching from the White Skull Infantry Division?)
He's good.
(Even if I lose everything)
(It's okay)
(It's funny every time.)
G-Dragon must be so annoyed watching this on TV.
- The White Skull Infantry Division? - Where's the camera?
White Skull Infantry Division. Salute.
I apologize. I'm sorry.
(White Skull Infantry Division, I apologize.)
- What did you just say? - What did he say?
I apologized to the White Skull Infantry Division.
You apologized?
Please put subtitles.
"White Skull Infantry Division, I apologize."
(After the video message, So Min and Seung Ri start.)
(That's quite a bit of water.)
That's Haha.
That's Identity Change.
(So Min turns into Identity Change.)
(Jae Seok and Xi A try.)
- She's done. - She's good.
She's very good.
She's so calm.
(She spills almost no water.)
This is incredible. Aren't you dizzy?
Not really.
(Jong Kook, Ju Yeon, Jae Seok, and Xi A are leading.)
As this is Elijah's specialty, she should be the best.
Start.
- 1, 2, 3... - She's fast.
(Will she be able to protect her pride?)
- 6, 7... - 6, 7...
(Show us your skills!)
- She's doing great. - Nine.
(She's done spinning 10 times.)
- Behind you. - One...
(She grabs the bowl.)
Pour it into the cup!
(She just has to pour it.)
Pour it!
(Will Elijah beat Xi A and Ju Yeon?)
4, 5.
(She approaches Kwang Soo...)
(and pours the water on him.)
(You're spilling a lot.)
She poured a lot into the cup.
How much water...
(She spilled a lot too.)
It's quite a lot.
(But she managed to pour quite a lot into the cup.)
(Did she pour more into the cup than Xi A and Ju Yeon did?)
What's the result?
(Kwang Soo and Elijah clearly win.)
- Elijah wins. - Okay!
(Your sense of balance is immaculate!)
Gosh.
(We did well too.)
I finally won in something.
(Kwang Soo and Elijah win the balance competition.)
(The pawnshop is closed.)
Are you ready? Let's see the result.
(What's the pawnshop's verdict?)
(Jae Seok and Xi A can pay off 30 dollars.)
- Haha and Sun Mi... - Sun Mi, we won 16 dollars.
- Okay! - So Min and Seung Ri, nine dollars.
Why did we win just nine dollars?
We won the dance battle.
Why did we win just nine dollars? We won.
- We won. - We won the dance battle.
Has the amount been written off?
Thank you.
(We're in 1st place.)
- Say it. - Beg them.
(No problem. Good luck with your next mission.)
- I'm excited. - There's only 20 dollars left.
(They divide into two groups and go for lunch.)
(Debt Amounts)
- It looks so tasty. - It smells so good.
This place looks so good.
- Sit here, Ji Min. - Okay.
- Smell that. - It smells so good.
This mission involves opportunities...
to write off debt and receive free meal cards.
(It's 1 shot, 2 kills.)
We must win.
It's called Couple Survey: Love Scenario.
(Couple Survey: Love Scenario)
"Love Scenario"? I love it.
The love experts are...
- Kwang Soo and So Min. - Yes,
- I'm confident. - Me too.
There are two survey questions that unmarried men and women...
- in their 20s and 30s answered. - 20s and 30s?
You win if you rank 1 to 5 correctly.
- Is that right? - You'll be awarded...
according to which answers you get right.
I have to get them right.
This is awesome.
If you answer the question wrong,
the couple next to you will doodle nicely on your face.
(If you answer wrong, the couple next to you will draw on your face.)
Nice.
No way.
Here's the first question.
"What did you lie about the most to your lover?"
- A lie? - That's okay too.
"I love you."
(Whispering)
I don't think so.
Answer... Answer.
If it's wrong, we'll draw on your face.
- Go ahead. - "You're the first."
(Seung Ri's answer: "You're the first.")
- He's right. - It's there.
Correct.
Really?
- You dated many women. - It was...
number two.
- Yes. - Number two?
(Number 2: "You're the first.")
- That's four dollars. - Yes!
How did you know?
Don't people say this a lot?
- Did you say it a lot? - No.
I guess it wasn't your first.
I've never said this before.
There's no point mentioning about the past.
Rather than that,
I thought it was saying you've never been to a place when you have.
- That's right. - That's possible.
That's how some people watch the same movie twice.
Like it's the first time.
Like watching old movies?
- Answer. - Mention that one.
(She's confident.)
- This is number 1. - Number 1.
- "I love you." - It has to be there.
(Ji Min's answer: "I love you.")
- That's a lie? - How's that a lie?
Xi A mentioned this too, but I said it wasn't right.
It's there, right?
Number one, "I love you."
(She's correct.)
- Really? - Yes!
(Number 1: "I love you.")
I've heard that a lot. "I love you."
Nice. It's a lie.
Did they all lie to me then?
Men usually say it...
when they do something wrong.
- It's a lie. - Right.
- You're an expert. - I'm a love expert.
I've heard that so many times.
Answer.
- Answer? - Answer.
"I was busy."
- This isn't it. - She'll get the penalty.
(She has a feeling.)
- Why? - She's getting the penalty.
Because...
- So Min. - Why? Why isn't it there?
- It'll be simple. - "I'm home."
Stop it.
Let's see.
"I'm home."
It suits her.
(It's simple.)
(The love expert has a spot on her face.)
It suits her.
Our turn. Answer.
- Go ahead. - Answer.
"You're the prettiest person in the world."
- It has to be there. - It is.
"You're the most handsome."
Okay.
(Xi A's answer: "You're the prettiest person in the world.")
I knew it. I think it's number three.
All right.
- Really? - I feel...
- a little sad about this answer. - I know.
- They all lied to me. - How could they lie?
This hurts.
"I'm tired of this."
Answer. "I'm sorry."
(So Min's answer: "I'm sorry.")
I don't think so.
Why? Why?
(Am I wrong again?)
Why not?
Come here.
Answer.
(I'll step up.)
You scared me.
- What? - What is that?
- I'm going to get her glasses. - I see.
- I only got her one lens. - Okay.
I'll get her glasses.
You'll get it soon.
"Your food is the best."
- That's not it. - That's not.
- It's not there. - He...
doesn't know anything.
(This isn't it?)
He doesn't know.
I'm confused because they're in their 20s and 30s.
During our time, it's like "My manager's father passed away."
(What did his manager's father do?)
I know that one.
But I'm not sure about those in their 20s and 30s.
There are so many things.
Don't stick your tongue out.
Answer.
He must be so cold.
That's so scary.
- What's this? - It's pretty, Kwang Soo.
- It's Ms. Kwang Soo. - We have the answer.
Answer.
"I'll be home early today."
(Xi A's answer: "I'll be home early today.")
That's after you move in together.
Doodle on her face.
(She never got doodled on her face before.)
I don't think she's ever done this before.
I've never seen that done to a woman.
That's too much.
Isn't this too much?
- So Min. - Hey.
(She clenches her teeth.)
- She looks like a witch. - This is too much.
Her nostrils look that big.
- What's wrong with your lips? - My lips?
- Why? - What's wrong with them?
(Kwang Soo, So Min, and Xi A get penalties.)
Answer.
It has to be right.
"I went to bed early."
(Ji Min's answer: "I went to bed early.")
(Incorrect)
(The love expert surrenders.)
- "I miss you." - Hold on.
Blackheads on his nose.
"You're the only one."
I already had that.
(They look funnier over time.)
Number 4 and 5 are usually hard to guess.
- Answer. - Answer?
"I don't have any money."
(Kwang Soo's answer: "I don't have any money.")
(Incorrect)
You don't know people in their 20s and 30s at all.
- I said that a lot when I was 20. - Aren't you in your 30s?
These people are in their 20s and 30s.
So Min, is Kwang Soo going to be in a cartoon?
What are you doing to me?
Is he going to be in a cartoon?
Kwang Soo, you look very angry.
I'm mad.
- Answer. - Answer?
"Let's get married in the future."
(So Min's answer: "Let's get married in the future.")
I don't think so.
Really?
(She's correct.)
It's 20s and 30s. You say that a lot when you're young.
- "Let's get married." - It's number four.
(Number 4: "I'm going to marry you.")
- You're a love expert. - Because...
I married 3 guys in my 20s.
(There's only number 5 left.)
- Answer. - Answer. I went first.
Men say this a lot.
"I have time."
(This is his answer.)
(What do you mean?)
Goodness. You're so old. You're so old.
"I have time."
- You're so old. - "I have time"?
(Concentrating)
Your nose hairs are sticking out.
They're sticking out too much.
(His nose hairs stick out.)
You should erase it when we eat. I'll lose my appetite.
You should erase it when we start eating.
Gosh, you guys.
Answer.
"What's wrong? She's just a friend."
- People in their 40s? - "She's a female friend."
- "She's a female friend." - People in their 30s and 40s.
(Incorrect)
Seok Jin,
- you can't even pay money for this. - What is it?
You have glasses now.
- Doesn't it look good? - It suits him.
It's not bad.
- It's not bad at all. - Doesn't it suit him?
- It suits him. - Seok Jin,
you should do this at home.
- I need eyebrows. Thank you. - You don't need any makeup.
This one's kind of hard.
- Let me give you a hint. - Okay.
This is what an older man says a lot to a younger woman.
- Answer. - Me!
This one's kind of hard.
- Let me give you a hint. - Okay.
This is what an older man says a lot to a younger woman.
- Answer. - Me!
Answer. "Do you trust me?"
(Jae Seok's answer: "Do you trust me?")
- All right. - That's what I had too.
(Correct)
Good job.
- "Do you trust me?" - Me too.
(Number 5: "Trust me.")
This is a close match.
We didn't get any right.
- We'll write off our debt. - This is so hard.
We're in first place.
(So Min and Seung Ri lead with 6 dollars.)
You must be hungry.
This mission is called Couple Telepathy: 1, 2, 3.
(Couple Telepathy: 1, 2, 3)
"Couple Telepathy".
What's that?
The couples stand on three boards...
and must produce the same gesture according to the given word.
If you don't match, one board gets removed.
You get graded payments according to the order you survive.
We must win.
If your arms are in the opposite directions, it's wrong.
- Okay. - Really?
- Let's use our right hands. - Okay.
Don't use your legs. Only use your arms.
Let's get started.
(First word)
"Heart". 1, 2, 3.
(First word: "heart")
(Looking around)
They're using different arms.
(He tells the producer.)
- What's that? - What?
- Isn't that wrong? - Hold on.
- You're using your right hand. - I'm right.
- That's wrong. - It's wrong. Let's take one out.
Look. How's this not a heart?
Step away from each other.
- Is that the heart? - Those two are different.
Your arms are different.
- How more couple-like can we get? - This is not fair.
I'm disappointed.
- That's part of the game. - All right.
- This is not fair. - Here's the second question.
"Sun Mi". 1, 2, 3.
(Second word: "Sun Mi")
(It has to be the gun dance.)
(What gestures will they do?)
(Oh, dear.)
- This is perfect. - We got it right.
Why?
What's wrong with this?
She's wrong. You have to be accurate.
She's wrong. We'll take one out.
Doesn't Sun Mi use one hand?
What happened with them?
(We're saved.)
Don't old people use two hands?
Hey, she's the only one who did that.
(She's an oldie.)
Let's get started again.
"Selfie pose". 1, 2, 3.
(Next word: "selfie pose")
This is perfect.
- We did it. - Ju Yeon,
you were late, and the hand gestures are totally different.
Haha, what's that? That's an old phone.
- Haha. - Why?
Haha is wrong too.
Come on, Ju Yeon. Hold on. 1, 2, 3.
(Hopping)
Hey, she's like a feather.
(He's carrying her on his back.)
You're the bomb.
(She's happy.)
"Bomb"? Stop it.
- Stop it. - You sound old.
- Don't say that. - Can we move on?
He's the bomb.
Why am I getting nervous?
Right hand.
Ready...
"Acting cute". 1, 2, 3.
(Next word: "acting cute")
(They only have one board left. They have to get this right.)
(They matched.)
- This is awesome, Sun Mi. - I'm sorry.
- B.I... - This is awesome, Sun Mi.
- This is awesome. - I'm getting goosebumps.
(How are you matching?)
This is acting cute.
(We're acting cute.)
- This is cute. - We're acting cute.
Didn't they plan this ahead of time?
- No way. - What are you talking about?
Do "acting cute". 1, 2, 3.
(Isn't this acting cute?)
- How's that cute? - How is that it?
You can look up "acting cute". This isn't there.
- This is right. - This is cute in Northern Europe.
(He went too far.)
He says that's cute in Northern Europe.
This is a warning. If you do this again,
- you'll get a board taken away. - All right.
Here's the second question.
"The worst thing to say to turn down a blind date."
- "Turn down"? - "Turn down."
- "Turn down"? - Answer.
(I'll get it right this time.)
(She gets ready to draw on his face.)
"I'm sorry. I'm married already."
- What? - That's the worst.
- You're the worst right now. - No, wait.
(This is what he gets for it.)
You got a nosebleed. Hey, wipe your nose.
Am I getting a nosebleed?
(It makes him sad.)
Answer. "You're not my type."
(Seung Ri's answer: "You're not my type.")
- It's there. - Really?
(Correct)
- Really? - That's being honest.
"You're a great person, but you're not my type."
(Number 3: "You're a great person, but you're not my style.")
- It's along that line. - Right.
- Answer. - Let's go, Ji Min.
"I'm sorry. I don't carry my phone around, so I replied late."
That's not turning them down.
- The title is different. - You're not turning them down.
- Really? - Is she right?
(Correct)
- That's an answer? - It's number one.
- It's number one. - Really?
- Really? - Yes.
You were right on it.
(Number 1: "I don't usually look at my phone.")
Ji Min is awesome.
- Turning down... - Answer!
(They shout out at the same time.)
I have an answer. What should we do?
So Min first.
"This is too much for me." It has to be there.
It is.
- Why? - It's not. Come here.
(Incorrect)
- Hold on. - They said that a lot.
Right? "This is too much for me to handle."
This is strange. Are they not from our time?
What's that? Is that snot?
Is that squid ink?
She has a lot of nose hair.
Answer. "I'm sorry, but I'd rather be alone."
You don't want to date. "I'd rather be alone."
- "I'd rather be alone." - I'll take that.
I was going to do that.
(Correct)
- It's number two. - It is?
I knew it. I was going to do that.
You're not ready to date anybody.
Nice.
(Seung Ri did it.)
I was going to do that.
Answer.
(I'll get this one.)
"I'm not..." Well, how should I put it?
Jae Seok, please cut your nose hairs before you speak.
(Please cut your nose hairs before you speak.)
- It's fine to be serious. - Stop it.
- I mean... - I'm talking right now.
- Sorry. - "I'm..."
"busy right now."
- I think it's there. - "I'm sorry, but I'm busy."
- Is it not right? - "I'm kind of busy."
- I'll take that. - Really?
(Correct)
- That's right. - I'm excited.
- "I'm busy." - This one's very similar too.
Number five is very close to this.
Answer!
(Okay, I got it.)
(Jae Seok again?)
"I'm busy because of a business trip."
- What do you mean? - Answer!
Go ahead.
(Smiling)
You tore your lips.
He's smiling too widely.
You're Joker from "Batman".
(He has big nose hairs unlike the charismatic Joker.)
Answer.
Get ready.
"I have so much on my plate."
(Jae Seok's answer: "I have so much on my plate.")
- You're out of your mind. - You should get it together.
- What? Xi A. - He has a lot on his plate.
You keep making me say it.
Hey, she doesn't want to get her face dirty.
Answer. I'll go. Let me see this first.
- Are your eyes open or closed? - His eyes are open.
Me.
"I'm too busy at work."
(Seok Jin's answer: "I'm too busy at work.")
- "I'm too busy at work." - That's the same thing.
- You said it's similar. - Why did he say that?
- You said it's similar. - Come here.
He needs to get a stronger penalty.
(He's an interesting guy.)
(He gets a makeover.)
- What's this? - This finally looks complete.
- Isn't it great? - Yes.
This is driving me nuts.
(Toothless and homeless king, Big Nose)
- "I have a dinner meeting." - "I have somewhere to be."
"I have somewhere to be."
(She says an answer fast.)
This is it.
(Correct)
(Yes, I got it.)
- I'm excited. - You can say it differently.
(Couple Survey is over.)
Xi A is good.
(Seung Ri and So Min won 13 dollars.)
I almost had it.
All right. Let's start.
"Seduction". 1, 2, 3.
(Word: "seduction")
(I'm seducing you.)
(Nice, we matched.)
We're wrong.
- Are we wrong? - We're wrong.
- Haha, how's that seduction? - What?
- How's that seduction? - Try it.
- That doesn't make any sense. - Do it.
What's wrong? What's wrong with her?
- Sun Mi failed. - I'm sorry.
Try it. Don't get seduced.
- Try it. 1, 2, 3. - What's that?
(Tapping)
1, 2, 3.
- Okay. - Do you approve?
I approve.
That's seduction.
I approve of it.
(They each have 1 board left.)
This is fun.
"Cheerleader". 1, 2, 3.
(Decisive word: "cheerleader")
(Se Chan and B.I match. Haha and Sun Mi match.)
(Ji Hyo and Bobby match as well.)
(However...)
This is not right.
Jong Kook and Ju Yeon are out.
(Their hands don't match.)
Are you sure about that?
Sun Mi, are you sure that's cheerleading?
- Show them. - How?
You're making us mad. Isn't this cheerleading?
It is.
- She's a cheerleader. - You're absolutely right.
She is a cheerleader.
(Only Jong Kook and Ju Yeon are out.)
"iKON". 1, 2, 3.
(Next word: "iKON")
(Like this?)
2, 3.
They're wrong.
He covered his mouth, and he covered his chin.
- My mouth is protruding. - You're wrong.
No, my mouth is protruding. Jong Kook.
- You're wrong. - Jong Kook, my mouth is protruding.
They're wrong, and they're wrong as well.
- No. - Haha and Sun Mi win.
All right.
We'll decide 2nd and 3rd place teams.
(2nd and 3rd place teams will be decided.)
(Only 1st and 2nd teams can get free meals.)
You have to do something that requires little space.
Hold on. Isn't this smaller?
We have to cross our legs.
- Like this. - You have to be quick.
- Haha recommended this. - I recommended it.
Ready.
(The word is...)
"Acting cute in Eastern Europe".
(Phrase: "acting cute in Eastern Europe")
(5 minutes ago when the word was "acting cute")
(Team Yellow insisted this was "acting cute in Northern Europe".)
(It's "acting cute in Eastern Europe" this time.)
(Good)
This was Northern Europe earlier.
This was Northern Europe.
Wasn't it?
Look.
(Is it Northern or Eastern?)
Northern and Eastern Europe can't be the same.
Time out.
We're right.
- Northern Europe? - Europe is one.
(He's shameless all the way.)
(Ji Hyo and Bobby win at the end.)
(Debt Amounts)
(Final location: gymnasium)
They made...
- a curling rink. - All right.
(It's much bigger than the previous one.)
I love this game.
This is really nice.
I hope I get a good one.
- Let's get an exemption. - This won't be easy.
There's "exemption".
(The rubber basins are curling stones, and there are targets.)
(What is the last mission for writing off debt?)
This is the final race.
Goodness.
How much debt do we have?
(Current debt status after lunch)
(Current debt status)
(We're in last place.)
By the way,
I thought Seung Ri...
was Soo Yong.
- Why do you have dark circles? - They keep getting worse.
- He's completely... - It's really bad.
- Well... - "It's really bad."
That was too blunt.
Let's wrap this up. He has to get some IV fluid.
You should eat some salmon. You have a lot of money.
Don't you think I tried?
(Goodness)
(Seung Ri finally explodes.)
- Don't you think I tried? - You have?
Did you get a health award?
(I care about you.)
I'm just worried.
He ignored it the whole time, and he exploded at the end.
- He's mad. - You should understand.
Here's the final mission.
It's Human Curling.
- Okay. - It's curling.
There are two rounds in total.
Two pairs become a team,
and you earn the amount...
- that the basin stops on. - I see.
Two pairs become a team,
and you split the total amount.
(If you can't write off your debt, you get a penalty at the end.)
1 and 2, 3 and 4, and 5 and 6 are the teams.
We have to pair up with those with little debt.
(They're in last place with 75 dollars of debt.)
- Kwang Soo is worst. - He has too much debt.
Please pick one.
I just hope I don't get Kwang Soo.
I hope I don't get him.
All right.
Please.
- That's good. - You're not showing me?
Xi A. I won't show you.
Go first, Seung Ri.
So Min and I picked...
four.
- Four. - What?
Then...
(Haha and Sun Mi have 3.)
- How much do you have? - This is good.
- How much do you have? - 15 dollars.
(They might win 1st and 2nd places today.)
For real?
(They're watching this celebration.)
They'll have so much money.
(1st and 2nd places are together, so what are we supposed to do?)
- No way. - 12 dollars.
The rich get richer, and the poor get poorer.
(They're jealous. This is dirty.)
You can't do anything about it.
- Next. - Us.
B.I?
- We have 8. - Who's 7?
Seven.
What a relief.
(Jong Kook and Ju Yeon are in 3rd place.)
- How much debt do you have? - We have little.
We have the same.
- How much do you have? - 27 dollars?
- 24 dollars. - That's not bad.
- We're in the middle. - We're good.
(The ants watch the merger and acquisitions of the riches.)
Why didn't Kwang Soo go yet?
(Why can't we be one of them?)
This is driving me nuts.
- I'm so anxious. - We have 35 dollars.
He should be over there.
- He didn't go yet. - Why...
We're always left behind.
What number is Kwang Soo? Let's see his number first.
1, 2, 3. This is Kwang Soo.
- We're 2. - They're with 1.
- It's 1. - In 1...
We didn't see ours, right?
(It's not us.)
Does nobody have number one?
- I think it's them. - Why are you hiding it? Who is it?
- I think it's them. - Who is it?
- I think it's them. - Who has number one?
Who is it?
(We have...)
(number 1.)
(Losers meet losers. They're in extreme poverty.)
(They have 40 dollars and 75 dollars of debt.)
(We dodged the bomb.)
- We did it. - I'm relieved.
- We just need... - We have to get "exemption".
We just need "exemption".
That's the only way. Go for it.
We have over 100 dollars of debt.
- Let's do it. - "Exemption".
- We need it. - We have no other way.
(Pairs and Teams)
- The order is important. - It is.
If you go later, you can push the team that was there before.
So let's decide the order...
with Race of Wits.
(Let's decide with Race of Wits.)
- Stop playing that game! - Let's do that.
- Come here. - Why does he...
love this game so much all of a sudden?
Why all of a sudden?
How many times do we play this a day?
He's a late bloomer.
Why do you like it so much?
- It's Race of Wits. - Do you have no wits at all?
What is it?
(The losers have to throw the stone first.)
Let's get started.
Set, go.
One.
(Sitting)
- What are you doing? - It's separate.
- They're out. - You have to play.
You have to say, "two".
- I sat down. - You have to say it.
- I sat down. - Seung Ri.
- You have to say, "two". - You do.
- It's separate. - I have to say, "two"?
He was so cute when he sat down.
(Seung Ri is so cute.)
Do I have to say, "two"?
We're separate.
- We play on our own? I didn't know. - He did this.
So Min said, "one",
and he was so happy. He sat down.
(He was so happy, and he sat down as well.)
(Let's check.)
(Yes, I'm saved.)
- I didn't know. - It's over.
- I had no idea. - I'm sorry.
- Seung Ri. - I didn't know.
- It's over. - We're sorry.
- You're supposed to tell me. - Take a break.
(Seung Ri is not witty, so they get to go 1st.)
Here's the next round.
- Set, go. - Set.
One.
(B.I gets 1.)
- 2. - 3.
(We're witty, right?)
- 4. - 5.
(Team Green is safe.)
- 6. - 7.
- 8. - 9.
10.
11.
(Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Seok Jin)
(The game is almost over. How will this 3-way race end?)
- 12. - 13.
14.
(He was looking around, and he was too late.)
(When you think it's late, it's late no matter how quick you are.)
- Did you see him? - I didn't expect that.
- Did you see his face at the end? - I didn't know.
I thought they were playing.
Go ahead.
Gosh, Jong Kook.
That was the fastest "14" I've ever heard in my life.
It's fun to play with so many people.
- It is. - Right?
- We didn't say it together. - Right?
Goodness.
(They're 1st and 2nd places for having no wits.)
Let's start sitting this time.
(Round 3 starts sitting down.)
(Bobby and Ji Hyo, and Sun Mi and Haha lose.)
- 1. - 2.
(B.I and Se Chan, and Jae Seok and Xi A lose.)
We did it. We're going last.
(Curling Order)
- Ready. - Go back a bit.
Try going back and forth.
Okay.
Straighten out the wheels.
- Two. - This is so funny.
- It's too strong. - It's good.
- It's strong. - No, it's good.
It's strong.
(He approaches the center.)
It's good.
It is.
It's the right direction.
(Will he get "exemption"?)
He's passing it.
(He goes outside of the target.)
It's out.
(Play again next time.)
(They're too strong. It's an out-of-the-park homer.)
- It's out. - This is great.
This is great.
- This is... - It's difficult.
(He's by himself.)
If you're going first, you have to be near the target.
That wasn't bad.
- We have to block the path. - Okay.
(Let's block the path so that other people can't be in target.)
Let's block it. We'll be good.
- Let's go. - Hold on.
- Point left. - Second team.
- Point left? - No.
- No, this way. - This way?
- If you block the path... - Yes.
The direction...
It's not strong enough.
(It's gentle and accurate like a curling stone on the ice rink.)
He's there.
(The direction looks right. Will his plan work?)
Let's block the path.
(He keeps on going.)
How much is it?
- It's 0 dollars. - 0 dollars.
(Nice play)
- Is it zero? - It's okay.
People might bump into us.
(They get nothing exempt.)
Number three is Haha and Sun Mi.
Let's go.
(They have 32 dollars of debt.)
(Here's our team's strategy.)
(They saw So Min and Seung Ri going out.)
I think it's better...
to aim for the front even if it's a bad spot.
(They're going to hit lightly.)
(Push lightly, Sun Mi.)
- It's good. - It's strong.
He's going left.
(Where are you going?)
- It's strong. - You can't!
(No,)
(you can't. Turn.)
- He's gone. - Haha.
(She jumps up and down after doing a groove.)
I'm sorry.
(You promised we'd pay off the debt, but you're leaving.)
- It's okay. - That was good.
They're out.
(They get nothing exempt.)
They all got zero dollars.
(None of them got anything exempt yet.)
Ji Hyo is good at games like this.
(It's Ji Hyo and Bobby's turn.)
She's good.
(It's a soft delivery.)
That's not it.
(He's going towards the middle.)
This is not a defending tactic.
(All right. Keep going.)
(He's going to the middle. Where will he stop?)
- 30 dollars? 10 dollars. - 30 dollars.
(He lands on "20 dollars".)
- Ji Hyo, that's not bad. - 20 dollars?
That's good.
- 20 dollars. - Is it 20 dollars?
- 20 dollars. - I should have gotten 50 dollars.
Se Chan and B.I are up next.
Okay, let's go.
You have to put me...
between Jong Kook and Bobby.
That would be the best.
You should come here and block the path.
Put me between them.
Come in through here.
Do well.
Watch the wheels.
He might get blocked.
It's not half bad.
- Let's go. - No, no.
Take out Bobby.
Let's go.
That's good.
(I have a good feeling about this.)
Come in through here.
Come on!
It's okay. Use your body.
My goodness.
(He stops.)
You should have used your body.
It's okay.
It's a good defense.
How are we supposed to play?
- You blocked the path well. - You did a good job, B.I.
(They come up with the perfect defensive strategy.)
In which direction should I push?
Push straight.
(Let's walk the straight and narrow path...)
(and get an exemption.)
We shouldn't push Se Chan.
Give Se Chan a push...
so that he can stop on 20 dollars.
(Let's avoid Se Chan and pay off 41 dollars at once.)
(She pushes him hard.)
(Jae Seok moves straight.)
(Let's see if he can pass through as he planned.)
(Bumping)
30 dollars!
(Jong Kook lands on 30 dollars.)
(He gets 30 dollars from the accident.)
(Gosh, thank you.)
(They get 30 dollars unexpectedly.)
I hope no one bumps into me now.
(Jae Seok gets 10 dollars off and Jong Kook gets 30 dollars off.)
We can't push all three of them.
There is nothing I can do because of Se Chan.
- You can go that way. - Gosh,
why is he over there?
If it weren't for Se Chan, we could have gone in between them.
- That's right. - I am a player, too.
(This is my strategy.)
- If it weren't for him, - You should push him away.
things would have been perfect.
They keep complaining about me.
(Try to penetrate if you can.)
Se Chan is like that.
Let's push Se Chan...
so that he can push Bobby and Jae Seok.
Right?
This should be the angle.
- Okay. - Let's get Jae Seok.
- Let's go. - Here we go.
You can do it.
(Their plan is to turn the obstacle into a tool of victory.)
Push hard.
That's good. That's good.
(Seok Jin glides at the speed of light.)
(Let's see if his strategy comes to life.)
That's good. That's good.
Good job.
(He falls before he reaches the exemption.)
(He pushes the others away but fails to stop at the exemption.)
- What is this? - My goodness.
- You're out. - Seok Jin.
It doesn't count if you fall down, does it?
- Let's get him up. - Get him up where he is.
- Do that. - Get him up where he is.
Don't move him.
- How much did he get? - Zero dollars.
- No, it's 30 dollars. - It's 0 dollars.
(He goes from exemption to 0 dollars.)
Let's go.
We need to hit Seok Jin.
Hit Seok Jin's right side.
That way, both you and he will live.
(Ji Min wants to put Seok Jin on the exemption.)
(Kwang Soo's sacrifice can save Team Blue.)
1, 2.
- That's too... - No.
(Throw towards Seok Jin.)
What is this?
- Let's go. - That's good.
(Kwang Soo heads towards Bobby, not Seok Jin.)
(Bumping)
- It's "exemption"! - It is!
(Bobby gets the exemption.)
(Kwang Soo ends up giving Bobby the exemption.)
It is!
(This isn't what I had in mind.)
Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo, thank you for the exemption.)
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo.
You got the exemption.
- I'm so happy. - You got the exemption.
(They help the other team and get 0 dollars.)
That's good.
I love it.
Kwang Soo.
Thank you.
- That was amazing. - I am so annoyed.
- I am so annoyed. - That was amazing.
(Ji Hyo's team gets an exemption,)
(and Jong Kook's gets 30 dollars off.)
(Bobby and Ji Hyo and Jae Seok and Xi A get an exemption.)
(Se Chan and B.I and Jong Kook and Ju Yeon get 30 dollars off.)
(The rest get 0 dollars off.)
This game makes me root for the others.
(The 2nd round of Human Curling starts.)
That's good.
- So Min, lean to the left. - That's good.
- 10 dollars. - 10 dollars.
10 dollars.
(Jong Kook and Ju Yeon have 23 dollars of debt.)
- Okay. - That's good.
- That's good. - It was a nice landing.
Good job, Ju Yeon.
This is good for us.
Why is she going that way?
(She is outside the target area.)
Gosh, why didn't it go that way?
Come on, Haha.
- Haha. - I feel bad for Sun Mi.
I know how you feel.
I am sorry.
It was incredible.
It's like that.
In which direction should I push?
They would be in the Human Curling national team.
- Seriously. - I think I should push...
- in this direction. - I agree.
They are like professional athletes.
- Can you do it? - Of course.
(They get ready for the throw.)
- This is the last moment. - Hold on.
There she goes.
Look at that.
(She moves towards the center like the master of Human Curling.)
- They are good. - They are good.
- She is in the target area. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo controls the direction before she stops.)
Don't move more.
(She lands on 30 dollars.)
30 dollars?
- 30 dollars? - They are incredible.
30 dollars.
You should go between Ju Yeon and Ji Hyo.
(Aim for the exemption between Ju Yeon and Ji Hyo.)
Okay.
(You simply need to go straight.)
It will be okay, Se Chan.
My goodness.
- Good job. - Ju Yeon, go back.
Ju Yeon, go back.
That's right. Don't move.
(Ju Yeon gets pushed towards the exemption.)
(If she stops, Team Black gets the exemption.)
(That's right, Ju Yeon. Stop right there.)
That's right. Don't move.
(Sliding)
That was too strong.
- 30 dollars. Don't move. - That's good.
Don't move.
30 dollars.
(She lands on 30 dollars.)
- Did I land on 30 dollars? - That's good.
- Don't move. - 30 dollars?
(B.I is exhilarated.)
(The coaching staff gives him a thumbs up.)
Don't move.
(It looks like we did it.)
- We did it. - Don't move.
(Ju Yeon and B.I get 35 dollars off for Team Black.)
She is moving to the left.
- She will hit B.I. - No.
- B.I. - Xi A.
She will hit our team members.
Hold on. Hold on.
- Don't move. - Five dollars.
- That's good. - Okay.
This is confusing.
- Is this it? - The last pair remains.
We need to do this.
Let's go in between them.
- Seok Jin, send her in. - Right.
Send her in.
It will be hard.
All right.
Aim for the right.
(Now that he has the direction, he just needs to throw gently.)
- No! - I am going too fast.
(Charging)
- I am scared! - I am going too fast.
(Say goodbye to paying off your debt.)
I am going too fast.
(Ji Min pushes Ju Yeon off 30 dollars.)
Jong Kook!
She was like a rocket.
(Seok Jin and Ji Min get 0 dollars off.)
This is the last pair.
(Kwang Soo and Elijah)
Don't push in this direction.
- Watch your hands. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They refuse to miss the last chance.)
Let's get the exemption.
(Let's get the exemption.)
That's your only chance.
- Get ready. - Okay.
(Exemption, wait for us.)
That's good.
- That's good. - He did it.
He did it.
(Let's see if the reduced speed puts her on the exemption.)
(That's it! Stop right there!)
(Can Kwang Soo and Elijah turn the tables?)
(Never mind.)
- Where are you going? - No!
(With a graceful, ballet-like turn, she loses her chance.)
(Elijah, come here.)
Hold on. No!
No, Elijah!
- Welcome. - Elijah!
We are on the same team.
That was close.
- That was really close. - That's shocking.
You aimed perfectly.
I came to see you, Ji Min.
(The final result)
(Bobby and Ji Hyo and Jae Seok and Xi A get exempt.)
(Other pairs have debts.)
(Whipped cream bomb gets 50 dollars off.)
(Spanking gets 30 dollars off.)
(Forehead flick gets 10 dollars off.)
Seung Ri and So Min, Haha and Sun Mi.
You are 27 dollars in debt.
- That's a lot. - That's a lot.
- Get ready. - I will go first.
(Race of Wits)
- Start. - One!
(Seung Ri wins alone.)
Seung Ri won.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Ju Yeon wins.)
Did I win?
(Se Chan and B.I get 17 dollars' worth of penalties.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin and Ji Min get exempt.)
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo and Elijah get 115 dollars' worth of penalties.)
(Whipped cream bomb gets 50 dollars off.)
(Spanking gets 30 dollars off.)
(Haha gets 1 spanking.)
(B.I gets 1 spanking.)
(Kwang Soo gets 1 whipped cream bomb and 2 spankings.)
- Spank reasonably. - Haha will get one spanking.
Haha, come.
Please go easy on him.
It breaks my heart...
that he bundled up his t-shirt around his butt.
This much is his t-shirt.
I feel bad for him.
(Jae Seok lands a blow without hesitation.)
(A t-shirt can't stop the electrifying sensation.)
Are you okay?
(It's important to pay off your debt on time.)
It wasn't a hard blow. It just made a big sound.
It just made a big sound.
- Seung Ri will deliver the blow. - It just made a big sound.
Okay.
B.I acted up in front of Seung Ri today.
Yes, he definitely did. Why do you look so serious?
Why do you look so determined?
- Here I go. - You'll be fine.
(Gasping)
Hold on.
I want iKON's stylists to go somewhere else.
(Don't gasp there.)
- All of you, iKON's stylists! - Stop that.
- What are you doing? - What's going on with you?
- They gasped over there. - This is just a penalty.
- "Is he really going to do that?" - He must've been holding grudges.
- It's only a penalty. Stop that. - Get out of the set!
(How hard will he hit B.I?)
- Hurry up. - Okay.
(Trembling with fear)
All right. Good luck, iKON.
(This is the love of a senior singer.)
(Hitting gently)
(Gosh, he went easy on B.I.)
- Come on, this isn't right. - Do you think it's a joke?
- Seung Ri should get the spanking. - That was terrible.
- That was an insult to us. - Right.
He went too easy on B.I.
- Since he went too easy on B.I... - Seung Ri, listen.
- Seung Ri's stylist and agent... - Leave.
should come and watch.
(He might be awful to you later.)
(The penalty is at its best when watching with everyone.)
- Yes, this is how it ought to be. - I agree.
This is how things are done on SBS.
(Clapping)
(This is how the national host starts the penalty.)
Hold on. Wait.
- Wait a second. Wait. - This is how it's done.
- He'll spank you without a warning. - Hold on.
Get down.
(He even gets them to cheer.)
(Here's the finale.)
(Or so you thought.)
(When everyone seems to like it, do it one more time.)
Wait.
Hold on. I'm not like an offering. This isn't right.
(They cooperate at times like this.)
(When things are heated up...)
(Spanking)
(Good luck, Seung Ri.)
- It doesn't hurt, right? - You're okay, right?
- It doesn't hurt, right? - It probably hurts.
(His body experiences the real deal of variety shows.)
- Are you all right? - You're fine.
- I'm sure that doesn't hurt. - You're fine, right?
- You're fine. - How is it?
It felt refreshing.
(Thank you for your lesson.)
- That was so cool of you. - Great. Well done.
- Next. - That was great.
(Kwang Soo's penalty of 115 dollars remains.)
- Get the stick 1st. - I'll get that 1st.
- This one? - Everyone, it'll splash on you too.
- Move back, please. - We have to move back.
- Kwang Soo. Get your cream first. - Yes.
(Let's make this quick and smooth for you.)
(Getting splashed and spanked)
Get ready. Here it goes.
Get down. Get down over here.
(Go get your spanking.)
- Come here. - Get down.
Let's go. You need to get the spanking.
Hurry. Stay right there.
(Pale-looking Kwang Soo is dragged.)
(The system operates like a smooth wheel.)
(That's the look of a master of variety shows.)
My goodness, this is incredible. This is amazing.
- First spanking. - My goodness.
(The first spanking sounds clear.)
My goodness.
(He finishes getting both of his spankings.)
(Today is a festival for penalties.)
Go home. Go home now.
(Kwang Soo places first during such festivals.)
- Xi A, go home. Go home, Ju Yeon. - Okay.
It's 4 to 3. 4 to 3.
(That was random.)
What? 4 to 3?
- Okay! - Yes!
(Everyone's focus is on the soccer match right before the shoot ends.)
- We did it. - Hey, we scored a goal.
- It's 4 to 3. - Are you serious?
- What is this? - Yes! Go, Korea!
(Cheering)
(He cheers with them for Korea though.)
This is awesome.
(We thank Elijah, E Xi A, Lee Ju Yeon, Sun Mi, Kim Ji Min,)
(Seung Ri, Bobby, and B.I for running with us.)
(A mysterious briefcase arrives for the members.)
(Deliver the briefcase within the time limit.)
(They shouldn't have accepted the offer.)
(The moment they accepted the offer, everything began.)
(Mysterious movements loom over them.)
(They can't give up even if they want to.)
(They can't escape until they accomplish the mission.)
(And...)
(guests, who puzzle the members even more, show up.)
(GOT7, idol singers who bring the best episodes)
J-black.
(J-black and Mmary, dancing couple, Yu Seung Ok, the healthiest woman)
(The battle is strange, but it's even more dangerous.)
(Only victory can complete their delivery.)
This is hard. It's hard.
(Will the members be able to escape from the fiery pits of delivery?)
Gosh, that startled me.
(Dangerous Delivery)