Don't walk. Run. Running Man.
Hello, viewers.
- Great.- That's nice.
Let me hit you just once, please.
New face.
Running Man's Fan-Meet:Nine Years of Running Man.
Fan-meet?
(Opening song by all 8 members)
(They'll sing a song together toexpress their love for their fans.)
(Each member shows offhis or her charms.)
(Each performance will be unique.)
(Apink, Nucksal, Code Kunst,SORAN, Gummy)
(Collaborationwith brilliant artists)
(Group dance performance will bethe highlight of the event.)
(The group dance)
(And Running Man's first theme song)
(The fan-meet starts now.)
(5 hours before the fan-meet)
More than my body,
my mind is exhausted.
I think we will feel emptytomorrow morning.
It's bound to happen.
It will be embarrassingonce this airs.
- We will feel empty.- When this episode airs,
I will be outside.
(Jae Suk is outsideat this moment.)
This is so embarrassing.My wife wanted to come,
but I told her to stay at home.
(He didn't want his wifeto come and support him.)
- This is embarrassing.- This is so embarrassing.
- Knock, knock. Good work, everyone.- Naeun.
(The woman with a sweet voicevisits the tired members.)
What did you bring?
- Naeun.- Good work, everyone.
- My goodness.- Thank you, Naeun.
- This is a protein drink.- You should get some protein.
Dancing is an exercise,
so you need protein.
(1 hour before the fan-meet,the audience begins to enter.)
(They get a T-shirtthe members worked on...)
(and enter the venue excitedly.)
(2,400 people in total)
(The audience took outtheir precious time for the event.)
(They await...)
(the eight members of Running Man.)
My voice keeps getting hoarse.
I don't like feeling nervousbefore an event.
- I know.- What time is it now?
It's about time.
It will start at 7 p.m, right?
Do we have 20 minutes left?
(Four teams of artists arein another waiting room.)
(They wouldn't have felt so nervousif had this been their concert.)
(They feel a sense of responsibilityfor the members.)
(10 seconds before the start)
- Oh, my goodness.- 10 seconds.
- Let's do this.- Let's go.
(The members' present unfolds now.)
(The first performance ofRunning Man's Fan-Meet starts.)
("Only One for Me"by all Running Man members)
(Yoo Jae Suk)
- Scream!- Let's go. Scream.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.- Hello.
Thank you.
Special project for Running Man'sninth year anniversary.
To those who were with usduring Running Man's Fan-Meet,
I'd like to thank you againwith all my heart.
- Thank you.- Thank you.
Many of you are here...
to be with us on our fan-meet.
As I told you before,
please exert energy with usuntil you sweat.
Everyone, are you ready?
- Yes.- Yes.
With your expectations and support,we'll start the performance.
Suk Jin will...
announce the start.
(We can't believe thatwe'll hear this live.)
All right. Race.
- Starts.- Starts.
(The real performance starts now.)
("Dang Diggi Bang"by RGP: Haha, Skull, and M. Tyson)
Running Man!
- Everyone.- Yes, sir!
- Get up!- Okay.
- Put your hands up and clap!- Clap now!
Raise them higher!
- Keep going!- Let's go.
1, 2. 1, 2.
One more time.
- Let's go.- Everyone.
Put your hands up
- Raise.- It's the last.
- Clap.- Put your hands up.
Clap your hands.
- Let's go.- Clap, clap.
Let's go. Let's go.
1, 2. 1, 2.
Scream, everyone!
We're a new group.
(Stang, digi, digi, ding,dang, digi, bang, bang)
(Digi, digi, dang, digi,dang, digi, bang)
Hello, we're a new group.I'm Skull of RGP.
- I'm Haha. Yes!- Yes!
Yes!
All right. We'll bringin the next performer to the stage.
The big brotherof Running Man, Suk Jin.
Although she's about to turn 40,she's still adorable.
It's the joint performanceby Ji Hyo and Suk Jin.
- Go!- Yes!
("Don't Give It to Me"by Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
(Song Van)
Thank you!
You see...
We prepared so much for this,but we were so anxious back there.
I'm not sure if we did a good job.
The next performance will be givenby the youngest members.
They're the youngest.
Our three babies have prepareda song...
that you will definitely love.
Let's give it up for them!
(Please welcome themwith applause!)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo finisheverything without any mistakes.)
(Yoo Jae Suk)
("Woman on the Beach"by Kwang Soo, So Min, and Se Chan)
(Running Man9th Anniversary Fan-Meet)
(Foolish So Min)
Make some noise!
- Gosh, I'm so embarrassed.- Hello, everyone.
- It's good to see you.- Hi.
Let us properly say hello.
- So we should introduce who's next.- That's right.
I see that a few thingshave been set up.
- Four chairs.- There are four chairs.
Those indicate a grand performance.
- Right,- Yes.
but less than four people areperforming next from what I know.
I know it as just one person.
One person? Could it be him?
Running Man's Sparta-Kook.
The man with the muscles.It's his turn.
- So let's introduce him up here.- Sure.
Please put it togetherfor Kim Jong Kook.
Thank you!
("Speechless" by Kim Jong Kook)
He's amazing.
- Yes!- I see.
I was so nervous.
Thank you.
This wasthe last individual performance...
we prepared.
Jae Suk and Haha...
prepared an amazing performance.
Are you excited?
- Yes!- Yes!
Please enjoy.
See you in a bit.
("Hollywood" by Super-X)
(Yoo Jae Suk)
- Make some noise!- Let's go!
Let's go! Super-X.
5, 6.
Come on.
Super-X.
(Collaboration performanceswith artists)
(Pink Nose Light, Hyo Chan Park)
(Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk,F-Killer)
(Apink)
(Ji Suk Jin)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Pink Nose Light,Running Man 9th Anniversary Project)
- Hello.- Hello.
This is the kind of songwe would never have received.
- Are you satisfied with the song?- Do you think it's good?
- I did my best.- Right? It's really nice.
- I hope we can pull this off.- I know.
You might become disappointed today.
- We'll do our best.- You might become disappointed.
Nang only gives compliments.
- Really?- Yes.
He does that even if you are bad.
I have low expectations.
I take what I canin a short amount of time.
Did you compliment us in the pastto take what you could?
I didn't mean that.
I complimented you in the pastbecause you did a good job.
- I am glad we met a good teacher.- Seriously.
I want to say thatplease do not give up on us.
I will make it work.
- If the notes become mushy...- "Mushy"?
(His tongue gets twisted already.)
(You'll tune our recordingwith the computer, right?)
He is the repair shopof the music industry.
(Don't worry because Nang isa veteran composer.)
- Should we decide on a team name?- That's right.
- The others already made theirs.- That's right.
What should we use?
Since our last namesare Lee and Jee,
we go by LeeJee Brothers.
Then we could be Pink LeeJee.
(Then we could be Pink LeeJee.)
- Pink LeeJee.- Pink LeeJee.
It's cute.
Pink Nosebleed.
- Pink Nosebleed?- Pink Nosebleed?
You are "Pink",he is "Nose", and I am "Bleed"?
You don't want that name.
(If not Pink LeeJeeor Pink Nosebleed...)
I think Pink Nose Lightwould be good.
- Pink Nose Light.- Pink Nose Light.
- "Kwang" means "Light".- Pink Nose Light.
- Pink Nose Light.- It's a good one.
- Pink Nose Light is cute.- It's a good one.
- We are Pink Nose Light.- Pink Nose Light.
(They decided on Pink Nose Light.)
- Shall we listen to the song?- Yes.
(We are going to party)
(I like that)
(He sings passionately.)
(I like that.)
It suits him.
(He is good.)
It sounds like he is singingthe guide track.
(He gets more excited.)
We should record the song now.
(Humming)
(He's still better than expected.)
- He is so good.- It's your part.
Gather around right now
(Gather around! Right now!)
(That's incredible.)
(Suk Jin and Kwang Soo are good.)
(The enthusiastic responsegives them confidence.)
- The song is really nice.- I know.
- It's refreshing.- It's refreshing.
- You are good.- Until the sun rises
(The compliments excite them.)
Eun Ji, warm up your throat first.
Okay.
(The main vocalist of Apink,Eun Ji warms up her throat.)
(When the sun sets)
(When the stars rise)
(Baby, baby, right here)
(Impressed)
- My goodness.- Her voice suits the song.
- Her voice suits the song.- Gosh, it's so nice.
- He always does that.- That's right.
- That's his style.- Nang.
(Nang's complimentmakes Eun Ji embarrassed.)
- It was okay, right?- It was really nice.
(Baby, baby, right here)
- That's good. We are set.- Are we set?
- That's good.- Goodness.
(Eun Ji's recordinggoes without a hitch.)
- It's nice. It's nice, but...- Okay.
He says "It's nice" first.That's how he always starts off.
It seemed like he was angry.
"It's nice, but..."
It's not like that.
Good!
Gosh, it's nice.
(It means he likes it so muchthat he is going crazy.)
- Nang.- That's his style.
- I am gaining confidence.- I know.
- Seeing Nang gives me confidence.- I know.
- Kwang Soo. I feel nervous in here.- Yes?
- Please sing comfortably.- Good luck.
- It's Suk Jin's turn.- I can't wait.
(He pulled off the intro perfectlya moment ago.)
(We are going to party)
(That...)
(He missed the beat.)
Let's start over.
(They burst out laughing.)
It's nice. It's nice.It's very nice.
He will lose his confidence.
- It's nice.- When that happens,
his back becomes hunched.
He will soon sing like this.
(He did a good job earlier.)
I am nervous.
- Good luck.- Please sing comfortably.
(With Apink's support,his 2nd attempt begins.)
(I like that)
I am less nervous now.
Oh, yes.
Your vocalization became freer.
(How about this?)
(That's incredible!)
That's incredible.
I don't know if we're complimentingor making fun of him.
- We're complimenting him, right?- Yes.
- Let's warm up your throat first.- Okay.
(Until todaybecomes tomorrow morning)
(My goodness!)
(They cheer loudly.)
- It wasn't half bad.- Bravo.
He is happy. He is happy.
He is happy.
Stop it!
If we tease him too much,he will catch on.
It's nice.
- It's nice, right?- Yes.
(Pink Nose Lightsings "Party" together.)
(The song that will welcomethe refreshing breeze of fall...)
(will be revealed soon.)
(Pink Nose Light practices dance3 weeks before the fan-meet.)
(Jo Ah Ra, Choreographer of "Party")
(A dance battle betweenKwang Soo and Suk Jin...)
(is the key point ofthe choreography.)
(Naeun, Eun Ji, Bomi,and Kwang Soo...)
(versus Hayoung, Namjoo,Chorong, and Suk Jin)
(When the two of them have a fight,)
(Bomi does a random danceand wraps up the situation.)
Here is the important thing.
You shouldn't dance to the beat.
Don't dance to the beat.Dance however you want.
It will be better that way.
(Bomi's offbeatand random dance begins.)
(Laughing)
(How about this dance?)
(The vending machineof random dances begins to work.)
(Bomi showed a new danceat every practice.)
(What kind of random dancewill she perform on stage?)
- Shall we begin?- All the best. Let's begin.
Kwang Soo. Do you know the part...
- you have to go to the back?- Yes.
Please look forward as the camerawill focus on you at that time.
Okay.
Okay. Let's go.
(Their rehearsalcum final practice begins.)
(The practice goes smoothlyuntil Kwang Soo's part.)
(All he has to do is look forwardwhen he goes to the back!)
(He bumped into someone else.)
(He immediately carries her.)
(I'm doomed.)
(That is howtheir final practice ended.)
Are you okay?
(Their final rehearsal endedon a shaky note.)
(In the midst of this anxiety)
(Two men get readyfor their performance.)
("Party" by Pink Nose Light)
Thank you very much.
- Are you okay, Kwang Soo?- I'm fine.
Please give Kwang Sooa round of applause.
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo's parentsare proud of him.)
I practiced so much, but I madea mistake during our performance.
I was very nervous.
I was supposed to do this,but I danced like this instead.
(He suddenly did the hula dance.)
That was how I danced.Everybody, We are...
- Pink.- Pink.
- Nose.- Nose.
- Light.- Light.
I'm sorry.
(He immediately gives upand apologizes.)
(Pink Nose Light, the group that'sbetter at performing than singing.)
(But it's okay.)
We tried our bestto not cause any trouble...
- for Apink.- Don't say that.
But I'm not sure if I did well.
I was worried. How was it?
For the past eight years,
I have been the oldest memberof my team.
It's my first timeto not be the oldest after 8 years.
- I see.- That made me happy.
It's not easy to have someonehis age as the oldest member.
- Obviously.- Yes, that's right.
The first timewe were announced as one team,
I was even preparedto carry him while I dance.
You are farfrom being the oldest member...
- since I am part of this team.- Thank you.
Thank you very much.We will now introduce the next team.
- Se Chan is now a hip hop artist.- Yes, he is.
(DJ Ssaebssaeb is readyto take the stage.)
The next team membersare Song Ji Hyo, Yang Se Chan,
and Nucksal!
(Next up are Ji Hyo, Se Chan,and Nucksal.)
As well as Code Kunst.
(Next up are Ji Hyo, Se Chan,Nucksal and Code Kunst.)
I heard a rumor that...
someone great will be joining them.They have a hidden card.
- They have a hidden card?- Look forward to their performance.
(Who is their hidden card?)
Everybody!
Are you ready to have fun?
Yes!
Make some noise!
We, Pink Nose Light,will now leave the stage.
- Let's do it for the last time.- Okay.
We'll say goodbye for now.We are...
- Pink.- Pink.
- Nose.- Nose.
- Light.- Light.
- Thank you.- Thank you.
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Yang Se Chan)
(Hyo Chan Park,Running Man 9th Anniversary Project)
We'll soon begin our recording.
(They are nervous as they're aboutto start recording their song.)
My gosh.
(A deep sigh)
I think you're just pretendingto be nervous although you're not.
Why would you be nervous?
Okay. Let's see.
Before we begin our recording,you should listen to the guide...
- and then you can start.- Okay.
Our main director for todayis Dr. Co.
I am very picky.
Please be more mindfulsince he's very picky.
No matter how good you are,you'll at least do it thrice.
(He's warning them in advance.)
(They are trembling in fear.)
I should mess upthe first three tries then.
(Se Chan plansto mess up the first three trials.)
(You plan to mess it up?)
(He's singing nonsense.)
Okay. If you do that...
(Hyo Chan Parkwill be disbanded right away.)
- Okay. Please leave.- No. I won't do that.
Let's start recording.
- Se Chan, you may go in.- Okay.
You may go in, Se Chan.
(Se Chanwill start recording first.)
Okay.
(He warms up his voice firstand starts immediately.)
Increase the volume. Tension...Why is this beeping?
(He's askingwhy is the headset beeping.)
What's wrong with that?It happened last time too.
Am I being arrogant? Should I justcontinue despite the beeping sound?
- You're right.- I'll just do it. I'm sorry.
No. You're right.
The microphonemight be rejecting you.
You might get electrocuted.
(Dr. Co is being strictwhile Nucksal is teasing him.)
I have to be careful.
(He believes in what they said.)
He's the type who needslots of attention.
He's starting to get on my nerves.
(Dr. Co is being strictwhile Nucksal is teasing him again.)
(She starts overand begins recording again.)
(He looks serious.)
(They are no longer smilingand looks stiff.)
Her voice is too shaky. Was it okay?Let's listen to it again.
- Let's do it a few more times.- Okay.
(Ji Hyo has to repeat her partover and over again.)
- Everything is good, Ji Hyo.- Do I just do as I'm doing now?
Your voice is shakybecause you're nervous.
Do you want to sit down?
- People also record while sitting.- No. It's better for me...
to do it while standing.
- Okay. If that's the case...- I'll give it a shot.
- Just take your time.- Okay.
You're doing fine.
Don't worry, Ji Hyo. Just relax.
We have a lot of time.
(Will she be able to overcomeher nervousness on stage?)
("Bonjour, Hi" by Hyo Chan Park)
Hyo Chan Park. Hyo Chan Park.
Song Ji Hyo, Yang Se Chan,and Code Kunst.
Make some noise!
Yoon Mi Rae!
- A shout-out to Yoon Mi Rae!- What's up.
Running Man!
(SORAN)
(Jeon So Min)
(Yoo Jae Suk)
(Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk,Running Man 9th Anniversary Project)
(17 days before the fan meeting.)
So, today...
is the day we will berecording our song.
Goodness.
We meet again.
Everything is good.
But the lyrics... How do I say this?
(What's wrong with the lyrics?)
I am disappointedas I couldn't join you...
during the lyrics-writing session.
I had another shooting on that day.
You could've chosena different day but both of you...
(You could've chosen another dayto write the lyrics.)
I gave it a thoughton why you decided...
to do it on that day.
I think SORAN and Jeon So Min...
are planning to use meas your puppet.
(He thinks they only want himas their puppet.)
I think you just want meto join you on stage.
- Not at all.- That's what crossed my mind.
- That's not true.- It isn't?
- We didn't plan that to happen.- Not at all.
So, I came up with a team namethat's perfect for this situation.
It's "Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk".
(Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk)
Don't say that, Jae Suk.
Jeon SORAN.
(Jeon So Min and SORANfeaturing Yoo Jae Suk.)
In my opinion,
the five of you...
will be working togetheras a band soon.
- You love that, don't you, So Min?- I love it.
(I'd love that.)
(That's how they decided on"Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk".)
I'll tell you the reasonI am scared of the lyrics.
- You know the reason, don't you?- What is it?
Her past love storywhich she told me about...
is described in the lyrics.
(The lyrics are aboutSo Min's love story.)
I mean...
I am not merely enjoying the song.
But it feels like I am relayinga message to someone...
on So Min's behalf.
(That is what the lyrics are about.)
I understand what you're saying,
but if you put that aside...
and just read the lyrics,
you'll see that So Min is a genius.
People around me are hyped upabout it.
I understand thatand share the same thoughts...
about the lyrics in general.
But must we include,"Do you want to kiss me"?
(It's overly explicit.)
I want this songto be played in all stores...
and make sure that he has no choicebut to confess to me.
(She wants the song to become a hit,and he has to confess to her.)
(You have our support, So Min.)
(Her parents are shocked again.)
(So Min wrote,"Do you want to kiss me"?)
(Their daughter's love life isbolder than they thought.)
- He'll be so bothered by this.- So Min.
He'll be so bothered by this...
- and has no choice but to confess.- "You can just speak up."
- That's right.- "Or you can just..."
What do you think of the lyrics?
The lyrics are not fictional...
and are full of sincerity.So, I like it a lot.
- You like it, don't you?- But...
imagine that you are the man...
whom she is talking aboutin this song.
I will feel very uncomfortable.
(I will feel very uncomfortable.)
(Her direct lyricswill make him feel uncomfortable.)
Right? Yes!That's what I'm talking about.
- So Min.- Yes.
- Let's begin recording our song.- Okay.
- You can do this, Jae Suk.- You can do this.
- He's a good singer.- No, I'm not.
- I'll try my best. Okay.- Let's begin.
(After their guest artist'senergetic recording...)
(Before this song ends)
Give it a shot.
(She's too emotional.)
(The lyrics are aboutSo Min's true love story.)
(Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk's"Confess Already".)
Race starts.
(The performancewill be revealed right now.)
("Confess Already"by Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk)
All right!
Make some noise!
(Yoo Jae Suk)
Let's go!
Come on!
All right!
Jump!
- Scream!- Jump!
Thank you.
Yoo Jae Suk!
(Yoo Jae Suk)
The last collaborationperformance awaits you.
(Team Gummy, the best singing team)
The member that stands outin this team is Haha.
- Of course.- He's with two talented singers.
(Ant is between talented singers,Gummy and Mosquito)
I don't know how it will turn out.
Let's meet the next group.
This was Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk.Thank you!
- Thank you!- Thank you!
(This was Jeon SORANand Yoo Jae Suk.)
(Jeon SORANand Yoo Jae Suk are the best!)
(Gummy)
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Haha)
(F-Killer, Running Man9th Anniversary Project)
- Okay.- Why are you clapping?
(Everyone gives a standing ovation.)
Why?
- Gosh, I feel pressured.- We got her.
- Great, we have high hopes.- I feel very pressured.
There's no way thatyou won't be amazing.
- Jong Kook.- You know what I mean?
(She sounds amazingeven as she warms up.)
(She's ready.)
Okay, thank you.
All right, shall we practice?
Okay.
(It's the only collaboration teamthat sings ballad songs.)
(She becomes a professional whenshe enters the recording studio.)
(I remember your sparkling eyes)
I'll do it again.
(She's Gummy indeed.)
That's good, that's good.
You can sing with strength,"I listen to your voice."
But it's better that you singthe later part with emotions.
It'll be great if you singthe first part powerfully.
I also prefer that you singthe first part powerfully.
Hold on!
(He intercepts.)
(Hold on.)
- When you sing, "sparkling",- Be quiet.
sing "sparkling" twice, understand?
(He adds an extra word.)
Try singing, "I remember yoursparkling, sparkling eyes."
I rememberI got it. I'll do it again.
I rememberCan you sing it like this?
It's less boring.I remember
I rememberLike this?
I'll do this at every phrase.
Let's end it.
(He has nothing to sayas Gummy accepts everything.)
Let's end it because I feel so bad.
I ruined the atmosphere.
Your sparkling, sparkling eyes
(She does what she's told.)
(I remember)
Can we record it like this once?
I'll keep it to myself.
- Really?- Yes.
- I'm being serious.- Okay.
(Friendly Gummy agrees again.)
(Your sparkling, sparkling eyes)
(She's very serious.)
(I remember)
(Wow, Gummy did it for me!)
What do you think, Producer Haha?
Okay, that was good.
Let's listen to it and move on.
(We hope thatit cured his broken heart.)
(Next is Haha's turn.)
(He's quite serious.)
(He gets emotionaland calmly sings phrase by phrase.)
(He's singing well.)
- Haha, you sound great.- Okay.
I'm sorry, but we havea specific team name.
- Yes?- We have to call him Mr. Blowfly.
(I see.)
- Excuse me, Mr. Blowfly.- Yes?
(Excuse me, Mr. Blowfly?)
- That's right.- Is the person...
who spoke Mr. Mosquito?
Yes.Listen to your voice
When you say "voice"...
- Could you sing that part again?- Voice
Voice, voice
Do it like this.
Your teeth on top shouldtouch the lower lip. "Voice".
- Voice- I listen to your voice
- You got it.- Okay.
Okay.
(After practicing,)
(he pronouncesthe letter V correctly.)
That's good.
(That's right. He's doing well.)
He pronounced "voice".
(Fan Killer number 1,Mr. Mosquito also records.)
- That's amazing.- That lump...
(On the day of the rehearsal)
Don't be discouraged.
You can do it!
Sing well.
Mosquito, Gummy, and Ant, let's go!
(It's a team of insects.)
- Am I an ant?- You're an ant.
Let's start.
Don't be discouraged, Haha.
- You can do it!- Don't beat Jong Kook or Gummy.
(With other members' cheering,they start their rehearsal.)
(After Jong Kook'smellow singing part,)
(it's Gummy's turn.)
(Someone in the corner takesour attention away.)
(In the end, he makes a gesture.)
(He destroys the emotion.)
(Laughing)
(What is he doing?)
(He's expressing with his body,"I am also here.")
(He definitely has a presence.)
(It's a performance of2 ballad singers and 1 dancer.)
- Good job!- Great!
(Haha doesn't have to bediscouraged.)
Mosquito, Gummy, and Ant are great.
We're with you.
(Haha sings a balladfor the first time.)
(It's a collaboration performancewith Jong Kook and Gummy.)
("Raise Your Voice" by F-Killer)
(Running Man)
(Group Dance Project)
Okay, shall we do it?
It's a big single file.
Haha is in the front.
Se Chan will come out to the left.
- This way?- In front of his chest,
do this movement.
1, 2, stop, stop, stop, stop. Okay.
- Raise it higher.- Higher?
- It's about this high.- Higher? Okay.
One and okay.
(Jong Kook bursts out laughing.)
- That was excellent.- We'll start.
Shouldn't we only show the arms?
We can't show our heads.
Shouldn't we only show the arms?We can't show our heads.
- We keep making eye contact.- Ma'am.
We shouldn't show our head.
He's tall for nothing.
It seemed odd.
It looks like Kwang Soo's headwith legs like a centipede.
- That's true.- Right?
- You're right.- We're an insect.
Kwang Soo, bend your knees.
Okay, 5, 6, 7, 8.
(They continue their practice.)
1 and 2 and 3 and 4 and...
5 and 6 and 7.
(She's observant.)
- Suk Jin.- Wake up, Suk Jin!
- Please!- Act your age!
I was wrong only once so far.
- Act your age.- Let's act our age.
Let's go, we can do it.We aren't fools.
Shut your mouthwhen we're practicing!
(They're strict with Suk Jin.)
- Shut it and concentrate!- That's right.
- I'm a huge fan.- Me too.
As you move the left foot,pull on the right and left.
Then do this twice.
(It's important to bouncethe pelvis powerfully.)
This is Jang Do Yeon's dance.
If you bend your kneesand move only the pelvis,
it's similar to a movementin hip hop.
Yes, It's hip hop.
Is that hip hop?
(This is hip hop!)
- Right.- Is that hip hop?
- What?- Look, don't do that.
You don't twist the knees.
Do it like this.
(He doesn't understand.)
Hey, please.
Kwang Soo, remember to smile.
(He realizes that he has to smile.)
Smile.
(Peaceful)
(His smile spreads happinessto everyone.)
(Is it okaysince everyone is laughing?)
He's driving me crazy.
It's terrible.
What? I'm not a fool.
- Okay.- It's the individual dance.
You'll start. My group did a wave,
but people hope to seeyour individual dance.
- Each person does a freestyle?- Dance as you'd like.
However, you have to keep itconnected.
If I send it with my chin...
(It's important to connectthe dance between individuals.)
(If sent by the chin,receive with the chin.)
The next person receiveswith the chin.
- Goodness.- That's correct.
(They suddenly receivewith their chin.)
(They work well as a teamfor things like this.)
This is fun.
(They toss it to Lia.)
Lia received it.
(She receives it.)
(Lia is the best.)
This is what we do.If I throw it with my shoulder,
someone receives itwith their shoulder.
With which part are you throwing it?
I'll dance for a long time.
Try and throw it.
I'll dance for around a minute.
- That sounds good.- For one minute.
- With which part will you give?- When will you give?
With which part will he give?He took it back.
- Will you give?- Will you give?
Are you going up?
He spat it out.
(Haha receives it with his mouthand sends it with his bottom.)
(Se Chan receives itwith his bottom.)
(What is he doing?)
- Hey!- Hey!
(Everyone raises their voiceas he uses his pelvis.)
This is hip hop.
Isn't it hip hop?
You said that it's hip hop.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Decide with which partyou'll toss it.
You decide for yourself.
- I received it.- Go down and up again.
- Toss.- Se Chan.
- Toss.- His face. That's right.
Receive it with your face.
- He tossed it with his face.- It goes through the shoulder.
Then I toss it.
- It's the shoulder.- I receive it and it goes up.
What's wrong with you?
(Spitting)
(Are you spitting at me now?)
- It's what I wanted to do.- That's the end.
- Do it.- Receive it like this.
Receive itand toss it with the pelvis.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Will you kick?- Move like you got kicked.
Do it like you're collapsing.
- That's basic.- That's right.
(I know how to dance.)
- You're doing well.- You're doing well.
(He receives with his legs...)
(and tosses with his chest.)
(He receives with his chest.)
- What's next? Turn.- I receive it.
That's good.
- Yes, do it like that.- It looks like a driving dance.
(They finish practicingtheir individual dance.)
Let's go!
Boom, boom. Come up and boom, boom.
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Put your hands together.
You worked very hard until now.
Make today's last performanceamazing.
(We hope that they performwithout mistakes.)
1, 2, 3.
- Let's go!- Let's go!
(How will their group dance turn outafter 3 months of practice?)
("Boom and Just Blow"by all Running Man members)
(The start is strong.)
(Everyone gapes.)
(Without bumping into Kwang Soo,he moves successfully.)
(They move in sync.)
(It's Suk Jin's turn this time.)
(People watch Suk Jin in a daze.)
(This is really amazing.)
They're in sync.
(The change in the song makesthe atmosphere cheerful.)
(It's Jong Kook's lifting of So Minthat they were worried about.)
(They do it without mistakes.)
That was great.
(They've been working togetherfor 9 years.)
(They show it off on stage.)
(It's time for Ji Hyo and So Min.)
(The audience shouts.)
(Never seen before on Running Man)
(It's a captivating sceneof the two.)
(They move quicklyto a single file.)
(They startthe individual dance part.)
(She finishes withthe steering wheel dance.)
(Everyone gets excited.)
(It's an amazing finishthat matches the fan-meet.)
(The members stay in their positionafter their group dance.)
(The audience shouts endlesslyfor the amazing performance.)
(It was really amazing!)
Bravo.
Ji Hyo is a good dancer.
Ji Hyo's facial expression wasprofessional.
I bet they'll get tearyafter such a performance.
Isn't it moving?
Right? Isn't it touching?
(The members on stage smileafter a long time.)
(Everyone doubted thatthey could do it.)
(The 8 Running Man members performedbeyond expectations.)
(They encourage and cheerone another.)
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.- As always,
we thank you,and we won't forget it.
As I said before, we hope thatyou'll be healthy and happy.
This is our last song.
It's Running Man's theme songthat we made after nine years.
The song was written byJung Joon Il.
It's a great song.
- That's right.- It's quite good.
You're right.
(Running Man's theme songfor the fan-meet)
(Experienced singer-songwriterto write this special theme song)
(Composer Jung Joon Il)
(Members write the lyricsto the theme song.)
(Despite the lack of singing skills,they try their best and record.)
(Their first theme songwith 9 years of emotions)
(How did it turn out?)
("I Like You" by Running Man)
(Song Van)
(Now I will be on your side)
(I can't understand everything)
(But I will lean closer to you)
(Because I like you)
(A difficult today and tomorrow)
(It's okay, stay strong)
(I will run with you)
(That's how we became one)
(Now I will be on your side)
(I can't understand everything)
(But I will lean closer to you)
(Because I like you)
(A difficult today and tomorrow)
(It's okay, stay strong)
(I will run with you)
(Believe me, don't believe me)
(Times when I misunderstood you)
(That's why we shone much brighter)
(Remember us)
(I'll give it to you)
(My clumsy heart)
(I love you this much)
(On the day)
(On the day we stop this walk)
(Thank you so much)
(Thank you so much, I was you)
(The day when we crieduntil our eyes hurt)
(The day we could laugheven though it rained)
(They never expressed their truefeelings over the last 9 years.)
(All the days)
(All the days are soft and dry)
(I like you)
(The first song they singto each other after 9 years)
- We love you!- Thank you!
- Thank you!- Thank you!
- Thank you!- Kwang Soo, pay up.
Thank you!
- Thank you!- Thank you for coming from far.
- Thank you.- Thank you.