Running Man
Episode 248
[There hasn't been any
penalties as harsh as this.]
[Only those who show their
persistence will live.]
[Polar opposites]
[The Running Man Penalty Race.]
[Underneath the spring sky.]
[A small car is parked.]
- Why are they doing this to us?
- We can't get off?
- They told us not to get off yet.
- What's this?
- There are two red carpets...
- they come from there, and us from here.
- There's guests.
- That's crazy.
- How did you get in?
Ji Hyo is out of breath.
- Ji Hyo, why are you stuck?
- Isn't Ji Hyo supposed to be on top?
Jong Kook is too big.
My hip hurts!
Where's Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo isn't here.
- There's no Kwang Soo.
- I didn't know.
- It's a limo!
It's a limo!
Is it coming here?
- I thought they were going to be squished.
- It's not fair!
This is the polar opposite.
[They can feel it in their bones.]
- Is Kwang Soo there?
- Why Kwang Soo?
- It can't be...
- I forgot about Kwang Soo.
- Why is Kwang Soo there!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- What is he?
- It doesn't make sense.
What are you a Hallyu star?
[Arrogant.]
[I'm Asia's prince.]
- Look at his pinky.
Hello everyone!
Running Man!
[Displeased.]
He sucks at emceeing.
What do you mean he sucks?
I will introduce you to the guests.
No matter how much time has passed,
he is a powerful presence!
[The cryogenic patient
who enjoys his renaissance!]
g.o.d.!
- Jun!
- Park Jun Hyung!
[g.o.d's big brother, Park Jun Hyung]
It's Jun Hyung!
- Park Jun Hyung!
[His extreme fashion sense.]
Congratulations on your wedding!
[The cryogenic patient who didn't age.]
Such old moves.
Old dance.
Congratulations on your wedding!
[Running man outing before his wedding.]
- What's up?
It's been a while.
It smells weird in the car.
There are five guys in this small car.
It's like the smell of bean sprouts.
[Bizarre expression.]
What are you saying?
He's weird.
From Thailand's prince to a man.
[From the Pacific to the Atlantic...]
Is he emceeing in front
of 2 million people?
- 2PM!
[2PM is coming!]
Nichkhun!
[His beauty fills the screen..]
[Thailand's prince, Nichkhun.]
Are we doing something good today?
[Straight away to the members.]
[His fan service is great.]
- Save us.
The American Jun Hyung, American,
and Nichkhun is from Thailand?
The unstoppable is here!
Capturing both males and
females' attention!
Dangel... dangerous lady!
- You're spitting so much!
- What are you talking about?
- [Wait a moment, Jun.
- When you said 'Thailand', too...]
- No, no...
[Let me continue.]
From F(x)... Amber!
[The hottest icon, Amber!]
[Unique idol, f(x) Amber.]
[Cheering.]
[All of a sudden, a fan meeting.]
[Be prepared to see her boyish charm.]
Hello, I'm Amber from f(x).
[Amber, an American appears!]
- He's a variety idol!
Super Junior M!
Henry!
[Prince Nobleman, Henry.]
[A very talented musician]
- It's Henry.
He has Formosan background.
[Henry, Canadian.]
- It's the last guest.
Good at talk shows and slapstick.
He makes the audience's head
turn with his timing!
A fitting character for variety shows.
M.I.B's Kangnam!
[M.I.B.'s Kangnam, from another world.]
He's like an old man.
[He's randomly punching in the air.]
[What's wrong with him?]
[He keeps performing his dances.]
[Is he still dancing?]
His legs look so short.
[At last!]
[He goes out of the screen.]
[Where are you going, Kangnam?]
- But he's always like that.
[Energetic from the start.]
Hello, everyone!
Guests who are energetic like
that, gets tired quickly.
Let me introduce the next guest.
Running Man members, come out!
[That's it?]
- Us?
Call us out one by one.
Hurry up, we don't have much time.
Please come out, Running Man!
[They escape the small car.]
[Sore]
- Hello!
[The guests are welcoming the RM members.]
Henry!
Jun Hyung! Congratulations on
your wedding!
- Next month.
- Congratulations!
Yo! Thank you very munch.
I used to say that in elementary school!
- Thank you very munch!
- Munch.
Even I did that when I was a kid.
I really thought... what do I say...
I'll do it again, oh my gosh!
What are you doing?
He prepared a lot of things to say!
I think Running man starts too early.
I'll do it again.
What do you mean, you'll do it again?
I'm so happy.
That was hard?
[That's what he prepared?]
You look like General MacArthur.
[General MacArthur Jun's
Running Landing!]
The bottoms look like
he's ready for a farming activity.
For Henry, he doesn't really
know Ha Ha.
You said you didn't know Jong Kook?
No, I've met him a lot at the gym.
People meet him often at the gym
more than as a singer.
So you don't know anyone here?
- Jae Suk.
- You know me, right?
- It's Henry, not Helry.
- What about him?
- Hi.
- This is the first time meeting him today.
He doesn't know.
He doesn't watch TV.
- Henry, do you know her?
- Hello.
Hello. You've met me at the airport?
Oh right, we saw each
other on the airplane.
The woman he met on the airplane.
The guy he met at the gym.
The guys he doesn't know.
[I know them all now.]
Nichkhun has been on the
show so many times.
How many times is it now?
But every time Nichkhun came on
the show, it was very hard.
When Nichkhun comes, it's
physically draining.
Is it hard today?
This race, is the Polar Opposites Race.
The teams will do missions,
and according to the missions
three teams will get to
enjoy the experience.
Meanwhile, the rest of the teams
will experience the worst.
The three lower-ranked teams will get
a penalty ball with your names
written on it.
A penalty?
In the final mission, the teams
with penalty balls will draw and
the final team will get
the extreme penalty.
Just two.
Our youngest PD went to
test the extreme penalty.
He has already done it.
You're showing it to us now?
What penalty is it?
Does it come on screen?
Everyone will shake with
fear together watching it.
[Huh?]
[What is this?]
[Oh heavens.]
[Automatically taking a step back.]
[No way...]
[An uneasy feeling...]
[Arising to the top...]
- It's okay with the breeze?
- It's fine.
[50 meters high]
[20 story apartment.]
[This visual is bungee jumping?]
[His shaky hands.]
[Is he going to jump at that distance?]
One, two, three!
- Jump, we're ready to go.
[It seems a little unusual.]
Three, two, one, jump!
[The cord...]
[is unlatched!]
Jump!
[What is this?]
[This unreal situation.]
[Everyone's surprised.]
Wow!
There's no cord!
[This is the final penalty?]
Jump!
[There is no cord!]
[The height of 50 meters!]
[Vertical drop!]
[Then straight down into the net.]
[There's no time to scream.]
[The cordless bungee jumping
in Inje, Kangwon Province.]
[Now it's your turn.]
You really need to be brave!
Honestly!
If you betray me...
I'm serious about this today.
[He's guilty.]
Out of everyone, it will only be two.
Only two will go.
One from this team,
another from this team.
Okay?
I have a busy schedule.
Like really busy.
I have a tight schedule.
Starting with Henry, pick a member
you'd like to be partners with.
Running man members can reject.
- Henry
- I hope no one gets hurt.
We won't get hurt!
The fact that you said you didn't
know me was the biggest scar.
[Sorry...]
Come on!
Henry's choice, one, two, three!
- Jae Suk!
- Okay!
[His foreign-like expression.]
Henry's a good athlete.
[Amber, with her entire body is saying no.]
Oh, you worked out.
- I'm better!
- I'm better than before!
- No, I'm better!
- No, it's me.
[All of a sudden a push-up contest.]
Why are you doing this, guys?
This is like foreign style.
Now, the next is Kangnam.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay!
He's the most sly foreigner
I've ever seen.
I think we'd be good partners...
Ha Ha.
[Extreme adrenaline couple.]
Nichkhun!
- Me?
- Me!
- Gary.
- Yes!
[Gary looks stronger then the rest.]
Nichkhun, you must not
want to go to Inje.
We can't lose today!
[Now only Big Nose and Blank Ji are left.]
[Jun Hyung is in dilemma.]
What am I supposed to do?
[Choosing Big-nose
is better for the variety show.]
Come here, Suk Jin.
I refuse it!
I refuse it.
[Humiliating!]
[The first man who
was refused by Big-nose!]
I only picked you
because you look pitiful!
Combine our ages, it's almost 100!
- Is that so?
- Almost a hundred?
Okay, I'll take care of you.
- Oh, okay.
- Not if you don't want it!
[The second humiliation.]
[The almost-hundred couple is paired up.]
- We'll lose the game?
- Yes, we will.
I think we'll be going to Inje.
Let's hope not.
[The worst penalty
in Running Man history!]
[If you want to avoid
this extreme penalty...]
[stay in the top three
for every mission!]
Don't think about anything else!
- Just think about victory.
- Just victory!
No matter what, we need to win.
- Fight, Amber!
- Fight, Ha Ha!
Do you know
what 'yapsap' (sly) means?
Yapsap?
Yaps...
Biyul!
(Cunning)
Biyul, you mean this?
[That is Biyum. (rhinitis)]
I think this might be by luck.
You're physically strong, but not smart?
What are you talking about?
I'm smart!
Hurry up!
We need to get there quickly!
What were you doing?
I didn't go to the bathroom
this morning.
- The filming started too early!
- I know.
Many people are competitive.
They're no match for you.
You're the best!
I feel so relieved to be with you.
Where did you learn all that?
Where did you?
People call it 'abu' (flattery).
Abu?
Abu Dhabi?
Not Abu Dhabi, a praise in an
exaggerated way that is not sincere.
That's what 'abu' means.
But I really meant it.
Is it okay?
It's okay if you mean it.
I really feel like everything
will be okay with you.
I hope we don't have to
go to Inje together.
No, we won't.
I'll do my best today.
[This team doesn't seem so strong...]
I think Ha Ha and Amber are
very possible.
Let's do our best, Ji Hyo!
What's that?
What?
What is that for?
They've installed the camera.
I think that's for us!
Let's hurry!
That's for us?
- Yes?
- Is that our mission?
[High hi!]
[What in the world is that?]
[It's set at the sixth floor.]
This is...
something that we use
when there's a fire.
[It feels really bad.]
What's wrong?
Why are you standing there?
What is that?
Why is it there?
Why, what?
What?
What are they doing?
Are they crazy?
Why did you set out the penalty?
What is it?
- What's going on?
- Just tell us what it is.
We need to talk to the manager.
What is going on?
This upsets me!
- What are you doing?
- What is this?
The first mission is 'Plot Twist Quiz.'
Before I announce the mission
I'll let you know the reward and
the penalty for the first mission.
[We must be dreaming...]
I can't express myself enough!
You didn't eat, did you?
No.
- Aren't you hungry?
- Yes.
Why are you asking us that?
We've prepared a special
breakfast for you.
For the top three teams
you'll eat a high-class course meal
at a cozy and warm sky lounge.
I think we'll going
to eat on the crane.
- Did you just say we?
[Are you volunteering?]
I mean... the lower-ranked teams...
The three lower-ranked teams will
will eat on the crane
facing each other.
If you successfully eat on the crane...
Do you really think we can eat?
You'll receive one penalty ball.
Just one penalty ball for each team.
But if you give it up and get down
you will receive ten penalty balls.
Ten balls are too much!
Either doing it and lower
the possibility for the final penalty
or giving it up and
make the possibility higher.
We're late!
- What's that?
- We're late!
Are we supposed to clean the window?
No, you'll eat there if you're
ranked 4th, 5th, and 6th...
- Eating outside?
- On that crane.
That's for us?
[Out of his mind]
If we lose at the quiz game,
we'll eat there.
For the quiz game, get inside
and make up some questions
for your partner.
Quiz?
He's not very good at Korean!
We're in trouble.
You're not good
at understanding Korean!
[But why is this the 'Plot Twist Quiz'?]
What would Kangnam know?
Kangnam... Kangnam...
M.I.B., Kangnam...
Japan...
I need to make the questions
that Khun can get.
'Where's the capital of Thailand?'
It's too easy, right?
[But, does Gary know that?]
I don't want to get the penalty balls.
Eggs, you know what the eggs
of sharks are called, right?
It's caviar, you know.
[The questions are for Jong Kook,
why caviar?]
'However, ' I really wanted
to use such a word.
Doesn't that sound so mature?
'However.'
[A mature person
must use a conjunction.]
It's all good.
[Everybody's done with their questions.]
- Let's go.
- I think you will get this.
- Maybe it's too easy.
[We have really easy questions.]
I'm afraid it'll be this simple.
Questions are easy,
do you think it's that simple?
[That's right.
It's 'Plot Twist Quiz.']
Please submit your questions.
It can't be that simple.
I think they will mix up the questions.
We'll be answering your own quiz.
Like I said,
It's the 'Plot Twist Quiz.'
The questions you made up
will be asked to the other
team members.
Everyone will solve them together.
We'll give you a cell phone.
The phone is for...
we'll give you a phone
number for each question.
Only the first one who's connected
can answer the question.
Do not call if you
don't know the answer.
Each team will have ten
running balls.
Until the quiz is over, you
need to use up the balls.
For example,
if Yoo Jae Suk's question is
answered by other team's member...
Then their ball will be added
to Yoo Jae Suk's team.
On the contrary...
If Henry answers Yoo Jae Suk's question
you can take one of your balls
and give it to the others.
The first one to give out a question is
Henry.
Henry!
This question is...
- Did you press '010'?
- What's wrong with you?
Do not press '010' in advance.
Let's not do that.
Then, I'll just press '01' only.
Don't press any of the numbers.
- Didn't you press the numbers?
- No, I didn't.
I'm not that kind of a person.
Ask the question!
Are you ready?
One, two, three!
If you tap, tap, tap the Canadian tree,
what comes out?
[Tap the Canadian tree,
and something comes out?]
[What is he talking about?]
- Okay, okay.
- Tell us the number to call.
The number is here!
Tap, tap, tap!
[This is very easy, isn't it?]
- What does that mean?
[They call the number anyway.]
I'm so late.
I pressed the wrong...
- I'm connected!
I'm connected, too!
The line is busy.
What was that?
Jae Suk!
It's busy!
- Hello.
- I'm connected!
Please give me the answer.
If you tap the tree!
She doesn't even know.
Really?
If you tap the Canadian tree?
[Do you really know the answer?]
- Three, two...
- Santa Claus!
Santa Claus!
- Why?
- All of a sudden?
What is she talking about?
It's a different number now.
Erase the history.
- What comes out?
- Okay!
Am I connected?
- Are you connected?
- Nichkhun is connected!
- Wow!
- Hello.
Mine is connected, too.
I'm sorry, I've got the wrong number.
He's got the wrong number.
- I don't want to get a penalty!
- Maple syrup!
[Maple syrup]
Does it count if he speaks in English?
[Correct!]
[Nichkhun got the first question.]
- Maple, maple.
- Did you know it?
Of course I knew it.
Canadian trees are maple trees.
The leaf on the Canadian flag
is the maple leaf.
- But it comes out?
- Let me explain it.
You know what Thor has?
If you tap the tree with a hammer,
the syrup comes out.
- I can't get connected.
- You need to press it fast.
I don't know the answer.
One ball from Nichkhun and Gary
was added to Jae Suk
and Henry's basket.
That was a wise move!
Let's give it to the one team!
Let's all give it to them!
Let's do it!
[The second person is Kangnam.]
The eggs of sharks are called caviar.
However!
What do you call the eggs of dolphins?
[The name of dolphins' eggs?]
Reveal the phone number!
It's different number, again.
It's not in the history.
- I'm late.
- I pressed it wrong again!
[Who will be connected this time?]
- Hello.
- Yeah!
It's difficult.
What's the answer?
Dolphins' eggs...
- don't exist.
- Correct!
[Big-nose broke the trick!]
Dolphins breed.
- You didn't know that.
- I know it. They're mammals!
Actually, I was thinking about
a giant pickled pollack roe.
[A pollack would have been
shocked to hear it.]
You know, a giant roe you can hug.
A dolphin's egg is
a giant pickled pollack roe.
That's so funny.
Kim Jong Kook.
Is it me?
I'm sure people from
foreign countries don't know it.
Japanese and Korean people know it.
What if I know it?
- I'll give you all my property.
- Really?
I hope Henry gets it.
[It'll be a jackpot reward.]
Are you ignoring us?
The question can't be difficult.
What's the name of the
Japanese street snack with octopus?
Revealing phone number
[What is it?]
- It'll be me!
[Who will be connected this time?]
- Hello.
- Is that you?
Yoo Jae Suk.
He's connected for the first time.
[Will we answer one, finally?]
[Was the question too easy?]
It's economy-yaki.
[Eco... nomy... what?]
[What is economy-yaki?]
[Combination of economy-class
and Okonomiyaki?]
Did he say 'Okonomiyaki'?
- Is that a Korean dish?
- I didn't know that.
[Everyone is panicking.]
That's like a seat on a plane.
You won't be able to find the answer.
[The next one is...]
- Is it me?
- It's me!
I thought 'Okonomiyaki' was
the answer but...
[Did he say it and get it wrong?]
Economy-yaki?
[Economy-yaki?]
[The cheap snack food
must be economy-yaki.]
They confuse me, too!
I didn't know this was
a difficult question.
I have a strong feeling.
Please, sit down.
It's already connected.
Hello!
The answer is Tako-yaki!
That's right!
Economy-yaki?
- I don't know it.
- I've never had it, though.
Kangnam is from Japan.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Good Luck!
I think the question will be easy.
He's a candidate for the penalty.
No, he's not a candidate
for the penalty.
What did Song Ji Hyo give as a gift
when Lee Kwang Soo moved?
Ready, and the number is!
The number is gone!
Why am I so slow?
I pressed it wrong.
[Who's connected?]
The line is busy!
It's always busy!
It's me!
[Blank Ji is connected!]
It's me.
The answer is an electronic fan!
Correct!
[They've successfully answered
their own question.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Song Ji Hyo!
Congratulations!
[Where would he put the penalty ball?]
Nichkhun and Gary have another ball.
[He feels betrayed again.]
I made a mistake.
Then fix it quickly!
Can I change it?
No, you can't do it again.
You can't do it again.
[He's acting as if it were
a real mistake.]
I see how it is.
Gary is serious!
- I see how it is.
- No, Kwang Soo was...
I'm serious today!
I see how it is.
It was a mistake.
I see it now.
I'm really serious today.
[Giraffe... you little!]
Kang Gary!
- You're disqualified!
[You've betrayed me every time.]
I've been frustrated by you!
[You've been always betrayed me.]
If you betray me...
I'm serious about this today.
Why?
[Giraffe, I'm watching you...]
[Frightened]
[Everybody is being sensitive because...]
[The worst penalty for
the three lower-ranked teams...]
[Eating at a high elevation!]
The next one to give
a question is Park Jun Hyung.
I don't have to call...
[Suk Jin and Jun Hyung, Gary and Nichkhun,
Jae Suk and Henry's teams have 11 balls.]
[We'll get the last question.]
Question...
[The last question of
'The Plot Twist Quiz.']
Suk Jin, when did I made my
debut as g.o.d.?
The phone number is...
[The phone race start!]
What year?
I'm late.
- What is this?
- Please!
I know this one.
Same day?
You know, the line is busy!
Jae Suk, quickly!
Who calls this fast?
Hello?
Yes!
Hello!
Lee Kwang Soo. We need
to give him a different phone.
1998!
Wrong!
[Please play again.]
[He doesn't have a quick mind.]
Reveal the number!
I'm late!
Okay, I got it.
Please!
[The three team members are nervous.]
- Hello!
[Is Big nose connected?]
- It's connected!
- It's me.
- It's Yoo Jae Suk.
Yes.
You don't know the answer.
I don't think you know it.
- Only I know it.
- Suk Jin, Grasshopper knows it.
He doesn't know it.
[The third team will be
decided by Jae Suk's answer.]
[Which team will be the
last upper ranked team?]
I was with them when they debuted.
Then, he must know it.
1999, at the 'Declaration of Saturday.'
[Jae Suk and Henry get third place.]
[g.o.d. debuted at the music show
Jae Suk emceed.]
- The 'Declaration of Saturday.'
- Yes!
- Grasshopper was there!
- Yeah!
Move one of your balls to
Park Jun Hyung and Ji Suk Jin's bowl.
Why did I hug him?
Why did I?
- Yeah!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[Depressed]
Three lower-ranked teams can
go up on the crane for your meal.
Congratulations!
Penalty?
It's going to be penthouse style.
- Are we going to stay indoors and eat?
- Yeah.
Don't you know it's more expensive
to get an outside seat in a higher spot?
You don't even know that's how it is.
[Experiencing the polar opposites, start!]
This is for the top three teams.
We're going to be in trouble
if you can't make it in the top three.
This place is beautiful!
You didn't have to prepare this much!
- This is amazing!
- Thank you so much!
Gary...
won't be talking to Kwang Soo
for a while.
Who am I supposed to attack, then?
We shouldn't get hurt
for this kind of stuff.
I picked him because Gary and
Jong Kook always avoided penalties.
Gary didn't receive any penalties?
Think about when we went to Taiwan.
I went to Taiwan.
These people went there, remember?
That's right.
We went all the way
to Taiwan for a penalty.
There are people who avoid
big penalties all the time!
She didn't go to Taiwan.
Don't shake hands with her.
Until the other teams finish eating...
you should stay, then you'll
get one penalty ball.
If you want to get down,
you'll get ten penalty balls.
Let's just give it up.
I can't stand the height.
- I'm really sorry.
- No, Suk Jin!
[It'll be great if you give it up.]
If we give it up, we will have to
take ten penalty balls.
Why don't you say something?
[Depressed Gae]
We won't take ten balls!
- Don't give up!
- I see.
[Big-nose gets on the crane.]
How are we supposed to do it?
It's very shaky.
It doesn't even make sense!
- Seriously...
[Who am I and where am I?]
Everyone, today...
I'll do my best.
Kangnam, here's the food.
What are we eating?
We're going to eat this?
['Ra' to the 'Men.'
Ramen!]
Enjoy the food.
We will lift you up.
How can we eat ramen without hot water?
I don't even eat ramen.
It's like a spaghetti,
just mix with sauce.
- It's ramen!
- They're having ramen.
Eating ramen is the worst penalty
for Jong Kook.
Let's go!
[We'll take off!]
[Their hearts start pounding.]
[I'm not going to look down.]
What's with this angle?
It's tilted!
Where are we going?
Wait, wait!
Wait a moment!
This is crazy!
- It's too high!
[They're still far from 25 meters.]
The food is dropping, man!
Isn't this too high?
Don't look down.
With my luck, I think I'll bounce
out of the safety air cushion.
Stop lifting up!
I want to get down!
I'll take the ten penalty
balls and get down!
- We're not going down!
- Hurry up and eat!
Didn't you tell me you're winning
a lot these days earlier?
This is different.
This is really scary...
[Not a rising trend, just rising.]
They're crazy.
Stop!
Stop complaining and eat it!
Should I eat or should I sleep?
This ramen is so soggy!
Do you want some more kimbap?
I'm fine.
Yours has more sauce than mine.
[The teams on the crane gondola
feel camaraderie, too.]
Let's just eat.
[The crane has stopped.]
- Then, Ha Ha will propose a toast.
[The crane has reached the target spot.]
- Forget all the bad feelings from earlier.
[They're having a luxurious wine party.]
- Our friendship will be high!
- High!
- Our love will be deep!
- Deep!
- Our glasses will be equal!
- Equal!
- For Running Man!
For your happiness!
For your safe return!
[Think about us, too...]
We don't know what will
happen to us.
Let's just enjoy this moment.
Who knows if we will be there next time.
Suk Jin is calling.
Hello.
- Is this Jae Suk?
- Yes.
Hurry up and finish eating!
I'm sorry we're recording now.
What? We're recording, too!
Jae Suk...
- Please eat quickly!
- Yoo Ja Sik! (You little)
- Thank you for the food.
This is luxurious!
[Tomato carpaccio soup
and salmon salad.]
- Is it good?
- Yes, it is.
Hurry up!
Hurry up and finish eating!
We have to stay here
until they're done eating?
- Hurry up!
[If it wasn't for Lee Kwang Soo...]
[They want to eat fast,
but this is a full course dinner.]
[The entree is Korean beef
tenderloin steak.]
This steak is very good.
It's really good!
Ji Hyo, hurry up.
We're going to go crazy.
We're eating meat, so it takes time.
I'm sorry.
Just chew it up and swallow it!
Just chew it up!
Gary looks very gloomy.
He's serious.
[Do not touch me!]
He won't make eye contact with me.
He actually avoided it.
- I'm going to write something for Gary.
- Like what?
I think he's playing.
Gary is smiling now!
Let me just show it to him.
I think this is good enough.
- Go, go, go!
[I hope he realizes my true feelings.]
- I don't have a selfie stick now.
[It's against the light.]
We can't see it.
[Do you see this, Gary?]
[This is how I feel about you.]
[Gary, I love you.]
[We're almost done eating.]
[Gaze]
[If you realize how I feel,
please smile at me once.]
I can't even curse now.
This drives me crazy.
[His heart is crashed.]
Kwang Soo, he thinks
you're making fun of him.
Kwang Soo is shocked.
I'm just saying I love him.
He totally misunderstood you.
He can't see this letter.
[Gae and Kwang's crisis...
How will it end?]
Let's just all get down.
Two gondolas together.
- If we do that...
- Jun, it's okay.
Inje is going to be worse
than this.
- Just be patient.
- It's like if you fall from here.
We don't know what's going on.
Let's just take some selfies.
Are you okay?
Everyone, one, two, three!
[Up in the sky.jpg]
[Mood in the cloud.jpg]
[We are gondola brothers.jpg]
Look, there's an airplane!
That makes it more scary.
We're parallel with the airplane.
I hope we can meet each other
after the next game.
I hope we stay the same.
We're done eating.
- Are you done?
- They said they're done.
- They're done!
[We're free!]
Getting down is even scarier.
[Having a meal at the high altitude
is completed.]
We're back!
If you had given it up, you
could have collected ten balls.
But everyone stayed until the end,
so each team will get one ball.
It will raise the possibility of getting
picked for the final penalty.
They're not getting this ball?
For the next game...
we need to put them in
the lower ranks.
We need to help each other.
That way, each team
will have one ball in there.
[Crane Gondola Brothers have formed.]
- One, two, three, fighting!
We are a team!
I thought it was going to be
physical games, that's why I chose him.
They might have something physical later.
Please put the
penalty balls in this box.
Can I just pick a ball from the box?
Just to test their luck.
[Why does he make so much fuss?]
[Suk Jin and Jun Hyung]
[That's bad luck.
Why did you pick my team?]
- They're killing us.
- This drives me crazy.
[Suk Jin and Jun Hyung again!]
[Who will be picked for the
final penalty in the real game?]
[The present possession
of the penalty balls.]
[The second mission site,
the waterfront of the Han River.]
[The Han River is full of spring air.]
[What kind of polar opposites
will they experience here?]
[What awaits the six teams is...]
[the six special sunflowers.]
[And a number attached
to each sunflower.]
I think if you get something wrong,
it will drop water.
What's that for?
What could it be?
[Those sunflowers look unlucky.]
This is the second, and the last mission.
- It's already the last mission?
- Excuse me...
do we really have to go to Inje?
Just one team will go.
One team out of all.
For now, Yoo Jae Suk
won't have to go.
You don't have
any penalty balls in there.
I know you're anxious, if you
think you will lose this game...
- You know what to do?
- We're a team!
[A member of Team Lounge intrudes.]
- Go away!
You know, we're Team Gondola.
[For some reason,
everyone wants to join the group.]
- Gondola!
[Quietly]
This is frustrating!
According to the results
of the mission...
The top three teams will...
be on a high-class yacht.
You can enjoy some snacks
and go on a cruise.
That sounds nice.
Just hang out on the yacht.
What will happen to
the three bottom teams?
The three bottom teams will...
wear diver suits
and swim across the
Han River.
- What?
- Are you serious?
[The finish line is already
set up at the opposite site.]
Are you for real?
[Is... this... true?]
- This suit makes you float on water.
[2013. 12. 29]
[The first time crossing the Han River.]
[They made paper boats,
and crossed the Han River.]
[2014. 3. 2]
[The second time crossing the Han River.]
[With 7 College students, they made
boats out of 7 different materials.]
[However...]
[This time, without a boat?]
These suits will make you float.
This Han River idea is so old!
You need to ask our permission!
Maybe it was sensational
in 1976, but not now!
Isn't it fun to swim?
[Another person is excited to swim.]
Isn't the water cool?
We've made a boat before,
but it's on our own this time?
Sir...
I can't swim.
Even if you can't swim, this
suit will make you float.
And we give you flippers, too.
If you cross the river within 30 minutes,
you will be given one running ball.
If you give up in the middle,
you will receive ten balls.
This is insane.
There are six shower booths.
If water falls from the shower,
when you turn on the water
you'll be dropped out from
the game.
You can choose a number you want.
We'll chose the number by
throwing a dart at the board.
The dart board is divided
by color in front.
But it has the numbers at the back.
Meaning you'll be choosing the number.
It sounds unfair for some reason.
It's vague!
Let's just do something physical!
Can't we just grab people
and throw them away?
You guys are older, complain
or something!
- This is not my territory.
- I'm not good at quarreling in Korean.
This isn't about capability, but luck.
So it's supposed to be fair
for everyone.
But it's upsetting for some reason.
Let's go swimming!
What's your favorite number?
- Amber!
- Ha Ha!
Let's pick six since it's June.
[Everyone followed their feeling
and chose their numbers.]
Don't worry about it!
- This is 50:50.
- That's right.
They're saying we have to
cross that river?
- We'll cross the Han River?
- It doesn't make sense!
By swimming?
Look at that river!
[Half of you will be facing it soon.]
You mean, we will cross the river?
That's what they mean?
The Han River?
Who's going to throw the dart?
Let Amber do it!
- Are you okay?
- How far is the distance?
- What's the width of the river?
- About 1.5 Km.
Go, Amber, go!
How come the Gondola Brothers
are gathered here?
[The Gondola Brothers
are at numbers 4, 5, and 6.]
It's upsetting!
- Please, please, please!
- Amber!
[Their life is in her hand!]
Amber, I really hate to
receive penalties!
[He's laying more burden on Amber.]
Good luck, Amber!
This is all about luck!
You're the youngest and you can swim!
Pick yourself!
Get ready!
Rotate the board!
[Amber throws the dart without hesitation.]
[The dart is on yellow color.]
It's on yellow!
- We're wearing yellow!
- I think it's you!
We don't know the number yet.
Please, please help us!
[This makes the chance
of going to Inje higher!]
If you want to change
your number, do it now!
Let's switch!
Please switch the number with us!
- Please!
- Should we?
- Should we switch with them?
- No, just stay.
Gary!
- Do you want to switch with us, Gary?
- No!
Stop talking!
Don't talk to me!
Let's switch, Gary!
Gary, come on!
I'm not switching!
No!
- Let's switch!
- Just stay!
Let's just stay like this.
Jun Hyung!
Two!
[Who will be the first team
to across the Han River?]
[Winner!]
[Gary and Nichkhun are chosen.]
[We survived!]
[Devastated]
[The yellow was number six.]
You know why I wanted
to switch spots, Gary?
[He can't hear anything.]
[Gary and Nichkhun receive
two penalties in a row!]
- Kwang Soo is toying with Gary.
- What are you saying?
[Crossing the Han River is one thing,
but they're stepping toward Inje.]
I wanted to switch for you.
[Anyway, Gary and Nichkhun are chosen.]
We'll pick the next number.
This board has five numbers.
We're choosing another number?
[This time, Nichkhun
is going to pick a number.]
[Each team is deciding on a number.]
[Ha Ha and Amber pick number two.]
- Do you want to choose number five?
- Yes, I have a feeling.
You do?
Then I choose three.
- What's wrong?
- It's okay.
I'm nervous!
It's up to you, Nichkhun!
- Come on!
- Please, Nichkhun!
I really wanted to switch for Gary.
- I love Nichkhun!
- Yeah, 2PM!
- Pick number 2 for 2PM!
- I'll throw it!
Please!
I really hate to swim!
[Nichkhun throws it lightly.]
[It's on the red.]
[What number will it be?]
Does anyone want to switch?
- We will!
- Just stay here.
- Let's switch!
- No, we won't.
- You don't want to switch?
- No.
Please aim for their heads.
Teams, hug each other.
Please!
Three!
Two!
- I can't cross the Han River!
- One!
Please! Not this time!
[Winner!]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are chosen.]
[We survived again!]
[Is that from the shower
or are they crying?]
[The red was number one.]
We almost switched with Kwang Soo!
[They're teasing him like kids.]
[The dart has answered Gary's wish.]
[The second team to receive
the penalty is chosen.]
[Giraffe's bad luck overpowers
the Goddess of fortune.]
[There's only one team left.]
Let's just go to the spot that's
left at the end.
[Ha Ha and Amber pick number one.]
They picked number one, because
they think it won't happen again.
It's fine.
We've been lucky with leftovers.
Leftovers are good!
We pick number three!
Please let us survive once!
Please give us a round of applause!
This is the last time!
[Ji Hyo will throw the dart.]
Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo predicts number two.]
- Don't do that, Ji Hyo!
Number two, number two!
Number four, number four!
Number four is good, too.
- Number four is good, too?
Kwang Soo, why?
If I get to swim across with you,
you won't be able to cross it!
Why are you being so scary?
Wait and see!
I think I could carry out this one,
but not the final penalty...
- Ji Hyo!
[The last team's fate is in Ji Hyo's hand.]
- Anything except number one!
- Ji Hyo!
The last team will be...
Rotate the board!
Just one more time!
If we can pass this time!
Ji Hyo!
It's on yellow!
Yellow, yellow!
Kangnam's hair is very yellow!
[What number will it be?]
- Do you love me?
- Of course!
Let's go!
Just one more time!
Oh no!
Please!
Do you want to switch with us?
- Was it from the shower?
- No, it wasn't.
- It's wasn't?
[Then, where did the water come from?]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[I'm sorry.]
[He's a funny guy.]
[They feel relieved.]
- It's not us!
We'll count down with everyone.
Three! Two! One!
[The dart is thrown!]
[The number of yellow...]
[is the last warriors
to cross the Han River.]
[Who will be the last team?]
Two, one!
[Winner!]
[Ha Ha and Amber are the
last members.]
[We survived!]
[I understand how you feel.]
[The yellow was number one.]
- How did you know?
- It felt really weird.
You two are exempt.
The three bottom teams will have
to swim across the Han River.
If you cross the river within 30 minutes,
you will be given one running ball.
If you give up in the middle,
you will receive ten balls.
The rest of you will go
to get on the yacht.
Please get ready for swimming.
[We knew it wouldn't be easy to
swim across the Han River...]
[but we never knew it would be this hard!]
Everyone's crazy!
[The penalties of the polar opposites!]
[It begins!]
[The three teams are getting ready.]
We're wearing these.
[The final weapons are given.]
- It's upsetting!
- Don't be upset!
It's frustrating!
We were picked at the last round.
- Henry!
- Yes, Jae Suk!
[Why me?]
[On the contrary,
the teams on the yacht...]
Nants ingonyama bagithi Baba!
('Circle of Life')
I never knew this day would come!
I'm really bad at pot luck!
[The group photo time!]
[2015. May
The yacht is awesome!]
This is first time out of five years!
Henry, you're such a lucky guy.
I love you, Jae Suk.
Jun, it's all thanks to you!
[They are giving each other a hug.]
Let's have some food, everyone!
Yeah!
Come on, baby!
This is very comfortable.
Thank you.
One, two, cheers!
Thank you very munch!
For our safety, not to go to Inje!
I love Running Man!
I just hope I don't have to
go to Inje.
You don't have to worry too much.
We'll be near you in full gear.
- Just take it easy.
- Okay.
[Who are we?
Why are we here?]
If you're ready,
you will start swimming!
This drives me nuts!
[Step by step in flippers.]
- It's cold.
- It is!
[Dives without a hitch.]
It's cold!
[Nichkhun starts swimming immediately.]
[Two young men threw
themselves into the Han River.]
On your back, and keep kicking.
[They follow Amber's advice.]
Keep kicking, Ha Ha.
[Crossing the Han River, start!]
Did they start swimming?
They're swimming!
They've started!
[They're swimming right next to the yacht.]
Kwang Soo, turn your body.
You're a good swimmer!
Kwang Soo!
Catch some abalone, since
you're in the water.
- What?
- Abalone!
Stop talking nonsense!
- You can't get abalones here.
- Oh, this is a river.
They live in the ocean.
Amber is just like a dolphin.
Amber!
[From backstroke to freestyle,
she looks like she's in a water park.]
[And she's fast!]
Who's leading at the front?
[In front of the yacht,
someone is leading everyone.]
- Who is it?
- Where is Nichkhun?
[Nichkhun is here.]
- That was Nichkhun!
How is it possible?
He's good at everything!
Cheer up!
He sings well, he's handsome
and he's even good at swimming.
He's really good.
But he's crossing the river,
and we're on the yacht.
[Gary, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo
couldn't get further than the yacht.]
Kang Gary!
I want to give up!
I'd rather get ten balls!
You'll get ten penalty balls!
- No, we're not giving it up!
- I want to stop here!
- No!
[Kwang Soo, you will put us in danger?]
Everyone is crazy!
[It's very peaceful here.]
Gwon Ryul, can you believe this?
It's hard to believe we could avoid that.
We've always taken those penalties.
Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, and I
are really unlucky.
Kwang Soo couldn't stop
the chain of bad luck.
You're totally free
from the final penalty...
I'm afraid if I have to go to Inje.
I can't believe it.
I hope it's not me.
I should cancel what I've just said.
[By the way...]
[Nichkun starts speeding up again.]
[He keeps swimming
across the Han River.]
[In the middle of swimming,
he's still very handsome.]
Nichkun reached the halfway point.
Nichkun is really fast.
He's already passing it.
He's swimming over there!
[People might think
he's enjoying his vacation.]
[Relaxed.]
[Amber is swimming in second.]
[Powerful swimming.]
Go faster!
Hurry up, come on!
Come on!
[Helping Ha Ha and
swimming at the same time.]
I feel sorry for you.
You're almost there!
She's amazing!
Ha Ha, you're almost there!
- 2PM!
- Nichkun crossed it.
- Yo, Nichkhun!
- You're awesome!
[Nichkun is awesome!]
[He's making a landing.]
[Nichkun has arrived.]
[Nichkun is exhausted.]
They're here.
Ha Ha is arriving, too.
They're fast at the end.
[Welcome.]
[Amber and Ha Ha arrive.]
[The strength drained out
from his legs.]
I will never do it again.
You've worked so hard!
- Amber is amazing!
- She is!
She could have swam faster,
but she was taking care of me.
Nichkun is a good swimmer.
[While they're praising each other...]
[Gary, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo
are still swimming.]
[Grabs]
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[Is he helping her?
Or is he relying on her?]
[Gary grabs Kwang Soo.]
Gary!
I'm sorry, it's my bad!
[Gary is pulling everyone in the front.]
[Swimming itself is tiring,
why would they add more trouble?]
You're almost here!
[Miraculously, they're near the land.]
[They're swimming at full speed.]
Come on!
Good job!
Fighting, Gary!
- Fighting, Song Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Fighting, Lee Kwang Soo!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
Lee Kwang Soo!
Gary is cursing!
Song Ji Hyo!
You're almost here!
[Everyone arrives.]
You're here!
[As soon as they arrive...]
Pull a trick on me!
[All six members have arrived.]
I had a cramp on my leg once.
It's going to happen to me now.
- We did it!
- We're awesome!
You did it!
- Gary!
- Drink some water.
You've worked so hard!
Are you okay?
The important thing is...
it'll be okay if you can
avoid going to Inje.
Let me announce the results.
Everyone has succeeded.
No one gave it up.
[Kwang Soo was the last one.
He did it in 29 minutes.]
[Emotion explosion]
[He must really hate going to Inje.]
I thought I would stay in the water,
if I failed.
I thought about staying
in the water forever!
Be careful!
Gary kept cursing at me
in the water.
I feel much better now.
[He kept cursing in my ear.]
[The final penalty is...]
[the cordless bungee jump!]
[Who will have the misfortune
of carrying out the last penalty?]
You've worked so hard
crossing the Han River.
[A round of applause for them.]
[More than anything,
no one gave up in the middle.]
No one gave it up!
Amber kept belching
while she was swimming.
[Amber let out a big burp.]
- Then we will start.
- Hope everyone is lucky.
- You must be so relaxed.
- What a day for me!
It doesn't even make sense!
Henry said he's lucky
and it was true.
I expected to receive the final penalty
but it turned out this way.
Jae Suk should have had
five balls at least.
This is Suk Jin and Jun Hyung.
Lee Kwang Soo and Song Ji Hyo.
Kangnam and Jong Kook.
Ha Ha and Amber.
One of each!
Nichkun and Gary have two balls.
[Oh, no!]
- You never know.
- That's right, this is nothing.
We've done this before.
Five balls have won over one ball.
Then it's totally by luck!
I want to pee!
[Starting the draw!]
[The die of hell has been thrown!]
Inje... I can't...
[Everyone is nervous.]
- Don't worry, it won't be us.
- I feel a tingling on my spine.
[Out of six balls, only
one ball will be drawn!]
One, two...
- Who is it?
- Don't look!
[Who will receive the final penalty?]
[You will experience an adrenaline rush!]
[The cordless bungee jump!]
[Watching it makes our knees
knock together!]
- Don't look!
- Let's not look at it!
[I... really want to avoid this.]
Don't look!
[Finally!]
- Is it out?
Is the ball out?
[Blocking for a spoiler!]
Don't be afraid!
It won't be us!
- Please!
- Don't look!
[Kwang Soo gets close to Gary...]
It's my team?
Is it my team?
- Did you see if it's us?
- I didn't see it.
I'm holding it.
- I think it's us.
- Why?
My nostrils are itchy.
- Please!
[No one has seen it yet!]
Gary is crying!
The final penalty goes to...
- One!
- Please!
[Suk Jin and Jun Hyung!]
[Frozen]
[The rest are celebrating.]
[We avoided it!]
We did it!
[Gloomy Gary is smiling now.]
[Some in heaven...]
[and some in hell...]
[It will test the courage
of this groom-to-be..]
[Flailing his swimming trunks...]
[The most impressive moment
ever since the world cup in 2002.]
[Dreams come true!]
[This must be a dream.]
I'm so happy!
[We are the world.]
[She looks more excited than
when her song hit number one.]
[Gary is about to pass out.]
[You did it, Gary!]
I'll pay for everyone's dinner!
[Except Big-nose, let's celebrate!]
At least, I feel better
that they've made up.
They've gotten closer now.
Kwang Soo, I love you.
Gary, it's my fault!
[The best happy ending.]
Gary is laughing now.
Gary looks younger now.
[We've just made up.]
- In a long time, he's Peaceful Gary.
[Forever Peaceful Gary!]
- You've worked so hard, Nichkhun.
I've always thought...
how would it feel to
cross the river by swimming.
I've thought about it.
It's tiring.
I don't think you wouldn't have said it
if you received the penalty.
Everyone is happy.
Suk Jin told me that
he'd have good luck today.
[Everyone is happy, that's a good thing.]
Let's just think this will
get rid of devils for a year.
Combining our ages... it's almost 100.
[Will they be able to do
the cordless bungee?]
You know I'm getting married
in exactly one month.
I almost forgot about it.
I want to meet Little Park Jun Hyung
in the future.
- Should we go up first?
- Let's go up.
How can we do this?
Seriously!
Should I go up with him?
Wait a moment.
It's good to go first.
Should we go up?
We'll go up now.
Cordless bungee...
Suk Jin!
I looked down...
I was a little brave before...
I thought I could do it...
but now it's not even funny.
[Panic]
[50 meters high]
[20 story apartment.]
- Sit down.
- Me?
I'm not going to do it now.
- Just lie down.
- I'm not ready.
- Wait a moment.
- We're not doing it now.
Don't make me nervous!
This is not a joke.
Brother, please...
I think I'm younger than you.
Brother is whom I can rely on.
I'll make it as quick as possible.
You can't make it too quick.
We're filming.
Honestly, people gave up on it before.
Right?
- One out of 1,000.
- I'm that one person.
I can't do normal bungee jumping!
And this is cordless jumping!
[20 minutes have passed.]
My shoulders.
Just lie down.
Wait!
My bottom is out!
It's supposed to be like that!
I'm not kidding!
No, not yet!
Please lift me up.
Not yet, not yet!
- I'll tell you.
- Please, don't!
What are you going to do?
[Panic]
- I'm going crazy!
Seriously!
Three, two...
Let's go, Suk Jin!
Jump!
[That was a practice for Suk Jin.]
[It's real this time!]
- Jump!
[Vertical drop]
[Eyes are popped!]
[I want to go back!]
[The net is shaking.]
[Now, it's my turn.]
Oh, my father!
Why did I come up?
I need to get down and go up again.
Yoo Jae Suk!
I'm alive!
- Sit down.
- Don't shake it.
I'll do it nicely!
- Lie down.
- My bottoms are out of it.
It's supposed to be like that.
This is insane!
Did I really do it?
This is... I don't know.
I love you!
My mom! I love you, Mom,
Sister, Brother, Niece!
Everybody, I love you, man!
One, two, three, go!
Three, two, one!
Jump!
[Jump!]
[Scream]
[High-speed drop!]
[Always smiling]
[That is fun!]
My jaws are locked!
My nostrils became parachutes!
[Bounce, bounce!]
I should have said something fun, too.
I couldn't think of anything
at the moment!
[The almost 100 duo]
[They have succeeded
at the final penalty.]
I think it is safe.
But I won't do it again.
- Anyway, Jun Hyung!
- Suk Jin!
We're the dropping team!
- We have succeeded at it!
- We did it, yo!
Good luck Running Man!
- Congratulations on your wedding!
- Thank you!
[Congratulations,
Groom-to-be Jun Hyung!]
I love black bean sauce noodles!
[There are various kinds of
black bean sauce noodles.]
[Please call me Kim Jjajang!]
[Between black bean noodle
and seafood noodle soup!]
She's playing hard to get!
[Enter the mysterious, the True house!]
[What's the best recipe
for black bean sauce noodles?]
[Put everything you have!]
Do you think I'm a nice
guy because I'm fat?
[A battle as rich as soy bean paste]
[and as chewy as noodles!]
One dot for black bean noodle
another for seafood noodle soup.
It's memento.
[The blacklist of True House.]
Subtitles by DramaFever