Subtitles by DramaFever
[Escape the desert island!]
[Merciless missions that
make them lose their temper!]
[And there is something
secretive here!]
[What will their destiny be?]
[6:30 a.m.]
[Yeongheung Island Dock, Incheon]
[MC Yoo gets the guest list.]
[These people are coming?]
Wow, today...
Hello!
- Why, why?
- Good morning!
Hello!
Are you going sky diving?
[Giraffe's backpack
really stands out.]
[Is there a parachute inside?]
What are you taking about?
They told us to bring
some toiletries, too.
- I was surprised to see the guest list.
- Who is it?
Please move over a little bit.
It's a female guest!
Seeing how he's behaving,
it's a female guest!
Can I have high hopes today?
- Me, too.
- Yeah, Gary and I.
Isn't it a little too late for you?
- Excuse me?
- You and Soo Hong, both.
How are we the same?
Our ages are different!
At least Soo Hong
knows how to have fun.
He goes to clubs, too!
- Where?
- A health club.
[Stop it!]
His girlfriend's name is Protein.
- Proteina.
- Proteina?
[Mr. Capable's girlfriend,
Proteina.]
When you see them...
I can't believe they're really coming.
- Really?
- They need to gather together.
The one who always placed
first in school.
He won the Minister award at Math
Olympiad when he was in high school.
And placed in first
among high school mathletes.
The God of Math in the world of idols.
- Math?
- There's such a person?
- Super Junior's Gyu Hyun!
- Oh my, really?
[The hidden talent
of Super Junior.]
[Super Junior, Gyu Hyun]
[With his math DNA,
he conquered the whole school.]
[He kept his score in the top 10% rank.]
[Graduated from Kyunghee University.]
[I will complete the mission
like the God of Math today!]
[The presence of an intellectual.]
Seriously?
[He looks different...]
Is he good at mental calculation?
Everyone looks at you
differently, now.
It said you got the Minister award
at the Math Olympiad.
But that was 12 years ago...
- I'm a little...
- But look at this!
His father said this
in an interview.
'He may not be a genius,
but he has a brilliant mind.'
[Embarrassed]
He didn't get in with special admission
but he entered Kyunghee University
with his SAT score.
- Yes, I did.
- Wow, that's incredible!
The Minister award!
We need to applaud!
Have you ever received
a Minister award?
There's such a person in the business?
Okay, next.
Wow, this person
is also incredible.
'I de-stress by studying.'
- Which member?
- There's such a human being?
She's never lost first place in school,
even with her tight schedule.
- I know this fact.
- Is it a sitcom?
Wonder Girls' Ye Eun!
[Wonder Girls, Ye Eun]
[A real master of study,
armed with diligence.]
[Wonder Girls Ye Eun,
reveals her report card.]
[Bookworm Ye Eun,
studies in the car.]
[Entered Kyunghee University.]
[De-stressing by studying
instead of sleep!]
[I will show you what
a smart idol is like!]
- Hello!
- Hi!
Hello.
[I didn't know Ye Eun
was that smart.]
Gyu Hyun is smart, too.
- It's famous that Ye Eun is smart.
- Not at all.
She used to study in the car
while 'Tell Me' was famous.
She really likes studying.
- Is it fun to study?
- I'm not good at math.
You guys should go out, then.
[The God of Math is embarrassed.]
[He's upset at their superior DNA.]
Why are you being sarcastic?
This is her report card in her
second year of high school.
First place of 41 people
during midterms.
She placed ninth out of 605
people during finals.
She's really good.
And she got in Kyunghee University
with her SAT score.
You guys are a campus couple!
He was year ahead of me in school.
- Oh, you went to school together.
- I cherish her as a classmate.
Ye Eun and Gyu Hyun
are intellectuals.
I can listen up to this point.
- But the next...
- Who is it?
He has an IQ of 138
and is an economics major
at Northwestern University.
One of the top schools in America.
Starting from entering in the
top ten on America's idol.
- Who is it?
- 'Kwang Soo-like Eyes'?
Lastly, we have the
Blue-chip entertainer.
- John Park!
- John Park... really?
Park!
Kwang Soo!
[The intellectual from overseas,
John Park.]
[On American's largest
audition program]
['American Idol']
My name is John Park
I am a student, but I could be
the next American Idol.
Welcome to the top 24.
[Attending
Northwestern University.]
[Kim Tae Hee: 'I want to study
English with John Park.']
[The true golden boy in this era.]
[Intelligent and qualified,
The Golden Boy is here!]
Hello!
John Park is very smart.
I heard it's easy to get into
University in the States.
Graduating is hard!
- Did you graduate?
- I'm on a leave of absence.
See, graduating is hard!
You have to graduate
to prove that you're smart.
In Korea, we get a direct
call from school saying
- 'it's better to dropout...'
- To see if you really want to study.
Just to explain a little bit
his IQ is 138.
There are a few who are higher.
It's not really special.
You should at least be in Mensa...
Take care of your
bare skin (mensal).
[What's wrong with my skin...]
- Take good care.
- I'll take care of it for you.
- Northwestern, economics major?
- Yes.
- Wow, really?
- That's unexpected.
I actually got into University through
an audition with singing.
Economics major
with singing?
You could do a double major
with economics and music.
It was a five year program.
But since I got in with singing
I think they let me off the hook
with my GPA.
[So does that mean
he didn't really study?]
Didn't you mis-cast him?
But anyway,
we have John Park here.
[Who's the last intellectual?]
I never knew, but this guest
has so many accomplishments...
[Who is it?]
I was so surprised.
A monster who kept their top
one percent rank in the Nation.
His IQ is 148.
Is there a real
monster coming out?
His IQ is 148!
A language genius that mastered
English and Japanese.
This era's hottest
and sexiest brain!
Rap Monster from Bangtan Boys.
Hello!
[BTS, Rap Monster]
[Rap Monster's SAT score ranked
in the top one percent.]
[Brain Monster... sexiest brain.]
[I'm here to conquer 'Running Man'!]
- Hello!
- Rap Mon!
He looks so different, now!
Now that I look at him!
Rap Mon looks so smart!
- Is your IQ really 148?
- I only scored that once, in high school.
That's enough!
We can't get 148!
We won't get that number even
if we take the same test twice.
That's almost my height!
Even if you show us the answer,
we still won't get 148.
- Even if you show us...
- Is it really 148?
He maintained in the top 1.3 percent in
language, math, foreign language, society.
Wow!
He got a score of 850 on TOEIC
in middle school by studying on his own.
That little...
That little?
Please be careful what you say!
[Ha Ha gets upset with
his qualifications.]
- Why are you angry?
- What's wrong with you?
Please introduce yourself,
in English.
[Dumbfounded]
Introduce yourself!
[He's asking the language genius,
with his elementary level English.]
We need to confirm if
he really speaks English!
Then confirm by
asking him in English!
- Rap Mon!
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
His pronunciation is amazing.
He studied hard.
Please give a round of
applause to the four guests.
[The smartest brains.
Fantastic Four.]
This is amazing!
I will give you the mission you'll
be doing with the smartest idols.
It's a survival race.
Escape from the desert island.
[Escape from the desert island?]
[Escape out of the desert island!]
Wow, do we have to use our brains?
I should get ready
to start farming there.
Just give Gary a tent
so he can sleep there.
John Park might not make it out.
[Please, don't say that.]
Just like it is called, you need to
escape from the island first.
[Escape the island with
the given missions.]
[In the extreme environment,
the survival mission is starting!]
[I want to get out of here so badly!]
[If you want to survive, move!]
[Will they be able
to escape safely?]
Who has a schedule
tomorrow morning?
Are we staying until the morning?
If you can't escape, you will have to
leave the island early in the morning.
[Early in the morning?]
If you have a schedule,
please adjust now.
Oh, we have to adjust our schedule?
Before you go, here is an item that
you need to survive on an island.
- A bottle of water.
- What is this?
Now you will do a test with
the production crew rep
- PD Lee Hwan Jin.
- You need to do an IQ test on him!
[He has a golden brain!]
You will need to do an IQ test
on the desk behind you.
How are we going to do an IQ test?
I didn't even sleep.
- I've got the brain of an anteater.
- A sloth, for me.
We're a sloth and an anteater.
You need to get a higher score than
the PD to get a bottle of water.
I will hand out a few cards.
You need to guess the order
and re-organize the cards.
She takes the basket... and chooses...
The second is a vocabulary test.
Write the definitions as quickly
and simply as possible.
This tests you on your
understanding and expression.
I will show you a
picture for the third test.
You need to arrange the
blocks to make it the same.
- This is hard.
- My head hurts.
In Korea, the average adult
drank 32 glasses of coffee in a month.
Then how many glasses does
one person drink in a year?
It's wrong!
[Rap Monster writes down the
answer as soon as he hears it.]
This is the last question.
Wasn't the last question number seven?
- It's seven, now.
- Yes this is the last question.
I think I skipped lines!
- Wait...
- I think I missed two questions.
Then what do I do?
[The bottle of water depends
on their test results!]
[What will their results be?]
Nice work, good job.
This is no fun!
I hope I don't get a low rank.
Let's go!
I failed that question...
The people that I call out have
a higher IQ than PD Lee Hwan Jin.
If I don't get called...
It's only three people!
[Only three people will
get the bottle of water!]
One of the four failed!
[Worried]
[Who is the first one to
get the bottle of water?]
- John Park.
- Really?
[This is great!]
Seriously?
[How did this happen?]
It doesn't make sense!
[The IQ test result]
He's quick-witted.
He has a flexible mindset.
And he is very sociable.
- Sociability?
- How does the test show it?
He has a lot of potential.
The next person is
Gyu Hyun!
- That's not even weird.
- Go over there.
You're lucky, Gyu Hyun!
Gyu Hyun has really good concentration.
He also has great numeracy.
He has good abilities
for natural science field.
- He's cold.
- He has no affection.
[You're mistaken!]
And the last person!
Rap Monster!
Ye Eun, it's because
you didn't get any sleep.
- Yes, I am not a genius.
- It's because you got no sleep.
More than anything,
his language ability is excellent.
He's amazing.
Out of the eight of you
I'll name one the people
who got the highest IQ.
The highest person is
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Me?
He struggled, a lot.
Suk Jin is really disappointed.
All categories
were well balanced.
His focus ability was the best.
Then doesn't he lack
in every category?
[What?]
You sugarcoated it.
He's so-so.
- You only like him.
- You're generous to him.
We will give a bottle of water
each to those who scored higher.
You can't buy water there.
All the intellectuals are there.
[Let's still do our best...]
[It's my pleasure.]
We will now get on the boat
for the desert survival.
[It's finally time for battle.]
[If failure, they must take the
boat early in the morning.]
[Escape out of the island, today.]
Let go!
To the unknown island!
[The 11 brains are
heading to the boat.]
Ye Eun, come here.
And Park John.
Gyu Hyun, hurry up!
How many staff are with you?
- What are you doing?
- Film this!
How many staff are with you?
They can't even wear sunscreen,
yet they're applying it on him!
[Super Junior's face is worth it.]
If it's this size,
you won't get seasick.
[They got on board safely.]
[Finally, to the final location!
To the island!]
[What kinds of things will happen?]
Make sure to hold on to
your bottle of water.
I should have had some
water before I came.
I'm thirsty now that I
think I can't drink any.
Do you tell us the missions
when we get there?
We don't even have name tags.
- You're right!
- That's true!
- This is the first time.
- Why, Ye Eun?
I just thought of
'The Hunger Games' all of a sudden.
The survivors disappearing
one by one?
Isn't that a little too much?
[Escaping the island makes me
think of all sorts of things...]
Could you tell us the
three lowest ranked people?
[I am curious, though.]
- Can I really say it?
- Yes.
Just tell us the surnames.
Lee.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Am I the only one with that name?
Our surnames are all different.
The only one who has
Lee is Kwang Soo.
- This is another surname.
- Yes.
- Kang.
- Gary!
[Gary got selected.]
What's the point of surnames, then?
It's Lee Kang.
The last one.
Ha.
[Ha Ha got selected.]
[He asked for them...]
Lee, Kang, Ha!
[Lee Kang Ha trio]
[We are brothers.]
How did you all sit together?
Should we ask about the lowest?
I'm so curious!
They're more curious.
I don't have pride.
I joked around during the test.
- The lowest?
- Yes.
Don't get shocked.
We've done it a lot before!
[The lowest ranked IQ?]
- Ha!
- Yay!
[Running Man's official no-brainer]
Kang, Lee, Ha!
[Happy vs. sad]
I'm the highest out of the three!
[I hope there isn't anything
to do using our brains...]
[The boat heads
further into the island...]
Is this really the order?
But is it really true that we
might not leave the island?
It's like I've told you before.
You either come out today or tomorrow.
It's one or the other.
I bet it's going to be tougher later,
seeing how we're comfortable now.
[Are we really leaving
tomorrow morning?]
Everyone's face...
I have to finish recording my album,
I have to come out today!
You really need to get out.
I will give it my all.
[Will they be able to
safely leave the island?]
[That is how]
[they spent an hour on the boat.]
[Gets up]
It's actually a deserted island!
[Nervous]
- Are there any people?
- Guys!
There are people over there
but there's nothing there.
It's just empty.
Is it really a deserted island?
It's my first time here.
I wouldn't come here.
In my entire life.
[What will happen to them?]
[They arrived at the island.]
From today, a human being
will start living here.
[As if it's hiding the
events yet to come]
[it's the calm before the storm...]
Do you come to
deserted islands often?
It's our first time.
It's a real tent!
[Is that where the disqualified
person will sleep tonight?]
Everyone's already tired.
[They're already so tired,
and the only thing]
[greeting them are... life jackets?]
I think our name tags are on that.
[There aren't any names on the tags!]
Aren't those life jackets?
[When are we using that?]
- It's already scary.
- It's so hot.
- Everyone's here, right?
- Water!
- Please!
- I'm so thirsty.
Like I said before, it's a survival
mission on the deserted island.
There are life jackets beside you.
There's one for every person,
and there aren't any name tags.
If you complete your
name on the life jacket
you can escape.
[You cannot escape unless
you have your entire name.]
The current time is 11:44 a.m.
Starting now...
we are going to collect your
phones and watches.
[Even our watches?]
If you put your bag down,
we will also take it for now.
Listen carefully.
Six p.m. is when there's a high tide,
and it'll be hard to sail.
So we will send the last
boat out at 5 p.m.
If you don't get out by 5 p.m.
you need to sleep here and
leave early in the morning.
And just to let you know,
your name tag isn't just one piece.
You have to find all the vowels
and consonants in your name.
For example, for Yoo Jae Suk.
Y, OO, J, and then
'AE' is together.
Then, 'S, U, and K.'
You must find all of them
and stick it on your life jacket.
Then, you will wear it and escape.
There are some people
who have nicknames.
You must find the letters
of your real name.
Ha Ha is Ha Dong Hoon.
Gary is Kang Hee Gun.
John Park is Park Sung Gyu.
Gyu Hyun is Cho Gyu Hyun.
Ye Eun is Park Ye Eun.
Rap Monster will be
Kim Nam Joon.
The current time is 11:48 a.m.
I will give you
exactly 30 minutes.
There are vowels and consonants
hidden just around you.
You may be able to get out.
I will give you 30 minutes, exactly.
- Is there only one per person?
- We need to search separately.
Where, where?
Which way is it?
- We need to find it!
- How do we find them?
- Oh, no...
- I need to find them!
[How are they going
to find such small]
[letters in this large space?]
Aren't there any rules?
We just start looking?
[Just like this!]
[Huh?
That is?]
[Giraffe finds a bag.]
[The letter inside is]
['K']
Okay!
I'm going to get out for sure!
[They get them so easily.]
[Kkuk got 'J.']
I saw this tiny thing from
all the way over there.
I am so desperate right now.
[Ji Hyo got 'O.']
[He found two at once.]
[One is 'A' and the other is 'U.']
I should trade later.
What's up with me today?
I found 'K.'
Wow!
An enormous jellyfish!
[I'm getting a tan, go away.]
[Meanwhile]
Gary!
A, Y, G, R.
I'll give them all to you.
- Please give me some in Park Sung Gyu.
- Okay!
- Did you find them?
- Not yet.
- You'll give them to me later?
- Let's share later on.
- Ye Eun!
- First, have some water.
If we find some of each other's,
let's exchange.
But our letters coincide.
Then we'll keep those
and give the ones we don't need.
We're trading, okay?
- You can drink water whenever you want.
- Thanks.
- Just keep it.
- No!
- We have to trade, okay?
- Okay!
I think I can just take it easy.
[Gyu Hyun finds the bag first.]
- I found it!
- Wait, I found it first!
[Gyu got it first.]
[Gyu Hyun gets all of them
right in front of Kwang Soo.]
Listen to me, first!
- Yes!
- Wait, Gyu Hyun!
- Just check first!
- There are so many!
- Yes!
- Where is it?
I'm going crazy!
[Kwang Soo's about to cry.]
- There are so many!
- Gyu Hyun!
This is so annoying!
The letter is 'J'!
Oh Yay!
[They search, and search]
[and slowly build their names.]
[There's not much time left.]
[The 11 people are trying their
best until their last breath.]
[The 30 minute time limit is over!]
- Rap Mon found the most!
- He found nine!
Mine erased!
[Gary's letter disappeared.]
How can this be, it's impossible!
- It actually erased!
- It really erased...
Please give me a 'G.'
I'll dance!
You're really desperate.
[I really need to get out today.]
Everyone, including me,
is very desperate.
- We're all desperate.
- What do you have tomorrow?
- To be honest, I have nothing.
- Then just stay here.
Just stay here.
What about you Ye Eun?
- I have a performance in Busan.
- What time?
I don't know what time,
but I have to leave early!
- Pass, pass.
- In Busan!
It might be faster to take
the boat here, to Busan.
I can call YP later,
because we're close.
- Do you have anything tomorrow?
- A meeting.
It's an athletic meeting, right?
Go over there.
How about you, Monster Rap?
Monster Rap!
What do you mean Monster Rap?
I'm a little crazy right now.
- Mon Rap.
- I miss my mother.
You can see her tomorrow.
- My mother's birthday is today.
- Really?
We're having pizza at nine.
Happy Birthday to you!
He can't come today!
Dear, Gyu Hyun's mother.
Happy Birthday to you!
Please live a healthy life!
Recording.
I need to complete my album!
- Do you have to do it tomorrow?
- I have to finish tomorrow!
- Really?
- I don't have any other time.
What are you doing...
[Kiss]
- I'm very desperate.
- I think Gary's actually desperate.
[Whisper, whisper]
- What, what?
- She's so honest.
She needs to get skincare.
She's very honest.
We need to understand.
- I booked an appointment...
- It's really important!
I'll give you first and second.
- Skincare counts?
- Why?
- She's so honest!
- I need to get an insulin shot!
I actually have to go
to a charity bazaar!
- Let's exchange one.
- Then, he's done!
- He has a lot left.
- Which one do you need?
- I need two.
- Let's trade later.
I just need 'WA.'
Wow, this is nice.
[The current name tag situation.]
[Seeing now...]
Ji Hyo, you only need' H'!
[She collected
everything except 'H.']
It's currently 13 minutes before 1 p.m.
Time really passes slowly...
In about three and
a half to four hours
everything will be over
and whoever is left will stay.
Everyone can escape.
We have a bonus game
that could help.
It's called 'Guess the time.'
At any hour
you need to shout out the time with your
arms pointing like the needles in a clock.
Whoever guesses the correct time can
receive a letter of their choice.
This is why we took your
phones and watches.
The girl who can't say good bye.
The boy... this is 30 seconds.
[Human timer]
The two of us are no longer in love
So no no no no no no.
- I'll just keep doing this?
- Gary's so desperate!
The two of us are no longer in love.
It's been a minute.
So no no no no no no.
[You're trying so hard...]
Dear Gods!
[Have we ever seen Gary
this desperate before...]
Gary really needs to go out!
Now, let's do the next mission!
This is a chance.
Whoever does this mission well
will receive any letter
of their choice.
- Okay!
- That's good!
You can obtain
a vowel or consonant
through a 'Telepathy Image Game'
with a citizen.
In Mokdong, Seoul, there are
miniatures of you and the island.
- It is everyone's miniature.
- Oh, yes.
Their order and your order
have to be the same.
Only one person will
get a letter of choice.
- But how do we guess?
- It's hard!
This is the first topic.
From smartest to stupidest,
determine the ranking.
Number goes up as it gets stupider?
Dong Hun!
Hello!
- Hello!
- They're on the screen.
Nice to meet you!
Where are you?
- We're in front of SBS.
- In Mok-dong?
Thank you for your cooperation!
Thank you!
Who's your favorite celebrity?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Me, too.
Most of all...
thank you for your time.
Please determine the ranking
for being smart including
Running Man members.
From first to eleventh.
So, the stupidest person
will be ranked eleventh.
They know Rap Monster.
[The Image Game, begins!]
[How will they determine?]
Let's be rational.
They know Rap Monster.
- Rap Mon, Ye Eun, then Gyu Hyun...
- They don't know Gyu Hyun.
- Are you decided?
- No, no.
- Gary.
- I'll be the last person.
But people in their 20s like you.
Even the people who like Gary
don't like Gary for being smart.
I think Jae Suk will rank high.
- I won't rank first, though.
- Didn't you say you will rank fourth?
I think we'll be disappointed.
- You won't rank ninth.
- No one wants to be number 11.
I'll take it.
- No, Gary should take seven.
- Kwang Soo!
[Upset]
I graduated from a university, too!
Switch with someone
if you don't like it.
Gary might rank high, though.
No, they watch Running Man.
You can't change it.
It's determined.
We'll reveal the rank now.
One, two, three!
Who's number one?
Rap Monster!
[Correct]
That's reasonable.
Wow, I rank second?
Wow, Jae Suk rank second!
He's not that smart!
I'm not very smart.
The third...
is Song Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo ranks third?
[Ji Hyo ranks
a lot higher than ninth.]
- Oh my god!
- It doesn't make sense!
[They thought he'll be the last.]
It doesn't even make any sense!
Who ranks fifth?
[You look smart to me.]
John Park, he's correct!
He ranks fifth!
You scored, John Park.
- Who's next?
- Gary!
- I told you!
- We were going to switch!
See, you rank pretty high.
[And the sixth is Big-nose!]
If we have had switched!
Then, Ye Eun and Gyu Hyun...
My name is still not on the list!
[Gyu Hyun is the eighth.]
[The ninth is Ye Eun.]
Ye Eun ranks ninth.
They don't know about
Gyu Hyun and Ye Eun.
They don't know they're smart.
Kim Jong Kook ranks tenth.
I told you to stay!
Ha Ha is the eleventh.
I have nothing in my brain!
Why did you change it?
Many people know Rap Mon is smart
because of BTS show.
Rap Monster, we'll give you
a vowel or a consonant.
- I want an N for Nam.
- An N?
The ranking doesn't matter,
but I need to be correct.
- What do you want, John?
- I want a P for Park.
The next topic is...
The one will be able to survive without
a problem even on a desert island.
That's a given.
[Mr. Capable is number one?]
Come forward, Kim Jong Kook
and Song Ji Hyo.
Kwang Soo, you too.
Hello!
- Hello!
- He might not know me.
Nice to meet you.
We're on a desert island.
I'm a big fan of Song Ji Hyo!
You'll rank high.
From the strongest survivor
on a desert island to the weakest.
Please determine the ranking.
Think about the personas
of Running Man.
Then, start deciding.
I will rank low.
Jong Kook, you rank first.
Our images...
I think Ji Hyo will rank
either first or second.
Just go, you don't have to
give a little.
She might rank
higher than Jong Kook.
- I would be third?
- You'll rank third.
Jae Suk could rank second.
Jae Suk, get the third.
But he might put
Gary next to Ji Hyo.
Let's fix it.
- Are you decided?
- Yes, we are.
- Jong Kook is the first?
- Ji Hyo is the second.
- Wow, I've got it!
- Gary ranks first?
Because you're Monday Couple
with Ji Hyo.
He's a fan of Monday Couple.
This is unbelievable!
[Mr. Capable ranks third.]
The fourth is Ha Ha?
You're the fourth?
How?
How could I rank fourth?
[The fifth: Yoo Jae Suk]
[The sixth: John Park]
I think the seventh is Kwang Soo.
No, it's Gyu Hyun.
He's ranked pretty high.
The eighth is Ye Eun.
She's correct!
- Kwang Soo.
- Why am I ranked ninth?
The tenth...
[Rap Monster]
- Why do I rank tenth?
- Suk Jin scored it.
[The last person is Big-nosed Brother!]
Thank you so much!
Am I supposed to be happy?
You're lucky.
Song Ji Hyo, here's H for Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo escapes!
- She's incredible!
She's lucky every time!
I envy her.
Gary...
- You rank pretty high.
- That feels nice...
but I didn't win any letter.
Still, your image is good.
I can escape now!
I was close...
Ji Hyo is really leaving!
Goodbye, Ji Hyo!
Share your luck with me.
[I'm going back to land!]
The weather is really hot.
I'm not joking.
[But I'm free!]
Why is she so lucky?
There are lucky people.
[Bye, Lucky Blank Ji!]
Phew.
It feels really good.
But I feel a little lonely
without the members.
More than anything, I'm excited
that Gary doesn't know anything.
[What is she talking about?]
[Is there something Gary doesn't know?]
I'm sorry, Gary!
[Let's meet now.
Right now!]
[What did you plan
behind my back?]
Isn't it nice that you can bring
laughter to so many people?
[What did they plan
without letting Gary know?]
[Five hours ago...]
[Since the opening in the morning]
Who has a schedule
tomorrow morning?
Are we staying until the morning?
If you can't escape, you will have to
leave the island early in the morning.
[Serious face]
[Gary said he has to finish
recording for his new album.]
[11:50 a.m.]
We'll give you 30 minutes.
[He was more enthusiastic than ever...]
[The first mission,
'Finding the Lucky Bag']
[The producer secretly
summoned Jae Suk]
[while he was searching
for lucky bags.]
synced by riri13
What's the matter?
Don't show that we're talking.
- Do you want to escape from here?
- Of course.
I really want to escape from here.
A few years ago around this time
we had a special theme.
Do you remember?
- I don't remember.
- It was a Thanksgiving special.
TruGary Show...
[TruGary Show?]
[It was Thanksgiving special in 2011.]
[It was four years ago...]
You're the spy today.
[For the first time, Gary was
assigned as a spy.]
[But, the whole thing was a
hidden camera for Gary.]
[They've seen every single
act of Gary.]
[TruGary Show!]
[Gary's poor acting skill
made everyone laugh.].
[After that, he couldn't be
a spy for a long time.]
[But Why did you bring up
the TruGary Show again?]
- Do you want to escape?
- Yes.
I really want to escape.
[Today's real mission]
[TruGary Show Returns]
Are you serious?
When you escape, we'll take you
to the other side of this island.
We've prepared
a resting place over there.
You can play as if
you're on the beach.
Your mission will be completed
If Gary is left alone,
and everyone else is gathered there.
After 30 minutes of searching, you and
Jae Suk need to spread the rule.
If we let them know at once,
that might be too burdensome.
What should I do?
Gary said he'll really do his best.
He told me he must get out.
He only thinks about one thing.
He doesn't think twice.
We're in trouble.
This is going to be hard.
Uh-uh, there's Kang Hee Gun.
[He had worked harder
than ever before.]
[I must...]
[escape this island!]
[on the other side of the island...]
[Jae Suk passes the TruGary
Show mission on to Ha Ha.]
- Do you remember TruGary show?
- Yes.
Just pretend it's nothing special.
- We need to leave Gary on the island.
- Says who?
When we escape, there's a place
where we can take a rest.
It's nonsense!
- It's nonsense!
- I'm serious!
- Where?
- They told me and Jong Kook first.
Don't lie to me!
- Don't say it to Gary.
- Is it for real?
[During the lunch break]
[When Gary walks around...]
[Let's carry out the plan!]
Ji Hyo.
Where's Gary?
Is he far from us?
- Kim Jong Gook!
- Jong Kook!
[Wait, Gary is still too close.]
Today, our mission is TruGary Show.
[Really?]
Did you know?
In a nut shell
Gary has to be the last one
on this island.
It's actually Gary's hidden camera.
We can't let Gary escape.
He has to stay here till the end.
This is hidden camera.
We need to leave Gary here.
[Gary comes back at that moment!]
Gary's coming.
[He didn't hear us, did he?]
[The rules are passed on to everyone.]
This is a simple game.
It's the 'Telepathic Image Game
with the Citizen.'
[Wink]
[Okay]
I think Gary has to be the third.
[Everyone's pushing him
near the top.]
Gary ranks seventh.
[They push him for
the opposite image of Gary.]
Gary will rank higher.
[They successfully interrupt Gary.]
[I'm sorry, Gary.]
[For the second question...]
[everyone expects
Mr. Capable as number one.]
- I would be third?
- You'll rank third.
[They push him for a
higher rank again.]
[But, Gary ranked first.]
[They could have been failed if they
pushed him for the first place.]
Wow, this is unbelievable.
[In the meantime,
Ji Hyo escapes first.]
[And the other members are acting.]
- She's really leaving.
- Bye!
Running Man is a reality show!
Bye bye!
[He says bye seriously.]
I saw the look on Gary's face
was getting long.
I don't think me, Gary, and John Park
will escape from here.
Bye!
Wait, stop the boat!
I just need to find one more!
[He's acting.]
[Will I be able to release the album?]
Under the scorching sun...
Bye, see you!
Bye, Kang Gary!
See you later!
It's time to say goodbye.
From now on
we have group of games,
that might let you leave at once.
We need 15 to 20 minutes
to prepare them.
Should we rest?
You can take rest, or search for bags.
- I'll search for it.
- Where should I go?
- East, west, north, or south?
- Wait, Gary...
[Desperate]
I need to go find it.
I'm in a hurry.
[I feel so bad...]
He really needs to go.
[But we will win
only if you stay here.]
I'll leave first, so let me know
which direction.
The name tags are hidden as before.
You can leave now,
and you'll hear a siren in 20 minutes.
- Did you hide some more?
- Give me an O if anyone finds it.
They've hid them again?
['TruGary Show in desert island'
begins now!]
Did you find another one?
[Uneasy Gary moves
faster than anyone.]
[Gary's current situation]
[Ang, and n out of
Kang Hee Gun]
[What should I do
about my album?]
Well, we'll all escape except Gary.
[Giraffe found a lucky bag.]
Oh, if Gary had found this one.
[It's H for Hee.]
Kwang Soo, give me one.
I have none.
[Ha Ha also needs an 'H.']
Do you have a D?
- What about an H?
- Do you have any?
You don't need these.
[Is that so?]
Who needs an O?
Can you give me one sticker?
Suk, give me anything you don't need.
- Give me the leftovers.
- Suk Jin...
- Do you have a J?
- No.
[Let's share it.]
Ji Suk Jin, we're not against each other.
[He gets an I from him.]
[Jae Suk gives Ye Eun a K for Park.]
Great!
We need to help each other.
[Is that nice to be together?]
[I work alone.]
[Giraffe, the human search engine
runs about everywhere.]
[It's a delivery.]
- Uh!
- Did you find one?
- What's that?
- Is that 'WA'?
[Lonely]
[Gary finds a lucky bag.]
- How many do you need?
- I just found one.
It's a K.
I thought you had an H,
so I gave it to Dong Hun.
Who needs an O?
- Do you have an O?
- I have everything.
[Suk Jin gets another I
from Gyu Hyun.]
- I need to find U.
- I'll give it to you, if I find it.
Where could it be?
[John Park was looking
from a distance and concluded...]
It's a nice view.
[20 minutes passed.]
[Lucky bag searching is over.]
Did you find any?
I found one bag.
- What did you find?
- K.
[He should not find them.]
Gary, what do you need?
I need H and...
[and care]
[TruGary Show in desert island]
[Will they be able to leave
him on the island?]
We don't have much time left.
You have about two hours and a half.
[Nervous]
- What do you need?
- O!
Ye Eun, you only need a K.
I have K, too.
Jae Suk gave me this earlier.
[Ye Eun can escape the island!]
- Ye Eun is done.
- You have K and O?
Then, complete your name
on the jacket.
Does anyone have 'WA'?
[Only Kwang Soo's name has 'WA.']
- I don't think it's easy to find.
- I haven't find any.
What happened to Gary?
I still need four more.
[Come to paradise, Ye Eun!]
[Park Ye Eun]
Congratulations, Ye Eun!
You can wear the life jacket
and leave the island.
- Thank you!
- Who needs an H?
Me!
[I want it!]
- I need one.
- Where?
Kang Hee Gun.
H for Hee.
- Ah...
- You found an H.
[What's going on?]
- Do you need it?
- I'm done.
I need it!
[If he gets that H,
only three vowels will be blank.]
[He might leave before five o'clock.]
[Do something about it.]
Use it to trade,
if someone has what you need.
- I only need a U.
- Switch with me, then.
Do you have it?
You don't have it.
[What are you doing, stupid?]
[I didn't know that.]
I only need a U.
[He's the stupidest of all...]
You found all except one?
When did he collect them all?
[Will we be able to
trick Gary till the end?]
I'm finally leaving.
Cheer up, Gary!
Good luck!
[I wish you good luck,
Kang Hee Gun!]
I have the simplest game.
- Stick a match?
- Draw a match?
[The mission is revealed.]
- Guess the numbers on the match!
- No.
Ignite in one strike.
We'll give you what you want.
- In one strike?
- Yes.
- That's not that easy.
- That's easy.
It's hard for some people.
Matches break If you strike too hard,
or don't ignite if you strike too weak.
- And it's windy, too.
- We'll count one, two, three.
- Ha Ha's bad at this.
- I'll go first.
[He want to do it first.]
Gary will be the first runner?
He's desperate!
[We should be careful.]
Ready!
- How many does he need?
- Four.
[I'll do it this time!]
[Nervous]
- Count to three, everyone.
- It's windy all of a sudden.
It's so windy.
- Did they bring a fan?
- Isn't this almost like a storm?
- I'll do it now!
- One, two, three!
One, two...
[Burn it up, I need to go home...]
[Help us, wind.
We want to go home first.]
One, two... th...
It was three seconds!
[The counting was buffering at 98%.]
[He looks at them,
but no one's on Gary's side.]
But he still got fire.
You should have done it now.
[I think they paused...]
[We're lucky that we
have to trick Gary.]
It's strange it was windy
when you tried.
Get ready.
[He comes forward to block the wind.]
One, two, three!
[Ha Ha succeeds at it
with windbreak.]
It was good!
That's enough!
[He's upset!]
It's already passed three seconds.
We need to play other games, too.
We don't have much time.
[He's giving him an 'H.']
I'm sorry.
Dong Hun, I'm sorry...
[No, we're sorry...]
[He wouldn't doubt any longer.]
[John Park's attempt]
- Two, three!
- That was easy.
Anyone can do it.
[Kkuk easily succeeds at it.]
Everyone's succeeding at it.
[Idol Gyu Hyun]
[Giraffe and Rap Monster succeeded.]
Only Gary couldn't do it.
[Bitter]
Why did you want to try first?
You've never lit a match before?
- The generation of match!
- Turn your back, it's windy.
I can go home, after I strike it.
- Isn't it?
- Let's leave together.
Me, too.
You missed your chance!
No, this was...
[He used his chance to divide wind.]
You missed it.
I didn't strike it yet!
I lost my energy all of a sudden.
- This was a big swing and miss.
- Jae Suk is scary.
[Grasshopper, how could you...]
[Jae Suk can go to the paradise,
if he gets an 'AE.']
It's good timing!
Go!
One, two...
[Die off!]
[Omnidirectional cooling system]
[What the heck?]
I sneezed.
You just blew it off!
- I sneezed.
- It was clearly sneezing.
That was a sneeze?
Gyu Hyun, was that a sneeze?
He was sweaty but all of a sudden
it's windy.
[Absurd]
- Rap Mon, was that a sneeze?
- I think it sounded natural.
[They need Jae Suk for
tricking Gary till the end.]
That's unfair!
Those of you who did it,
tell me the letter you want.
I want an 'O.'
[He finishes Kim Jong Kook.]
[Kim Jong Kook escapes the island.]
- Can I put this one now?
- Yes.
Why did you blow it off, Suk Jin?
[He need three more letters.]
Ha Ha needs to get one more.
- No, I'm leaving now.
- You are?
Are you leaving, too, Rap Mon?
Should we wear it
before we get on the boat?
- Many people helped me.
- Everyone's leaving.
- Are you leaving, Kwang Soo?
- I'm leaving.
Who's staying?
Jae Suk, Gary... four of you?
[John Park, Big-nose,
Gary and Jae Suk?]
- Are you leaving, Gyu Hyun?
- Yes.
[Gyu Hyun completes his name.]
- John Park, I, Gary...
- It's ripped.
[One letter is ripped.]
Well, if that's ripped, it's over.
[Lee K...ng Soo]
[He wanted to get 'WA' so much,
but he ripped it apart.]
Let me have a marker.
This is unfair!
He blew out my match.
[Things happens in life.]
I earned this!
Step back for now.
I'll clear the situation,
please go back.
[It's Giraffe's mistake.
What will be the solution?]
The letter 'WA...'
We made two of them.
We kept one for giving you out.
The other one is hidden somewhere.
[Huh, how is it possible to find it?]
If you can't find it,
you have to stay here.
I just need to correct
it with a marker.
He kicked away a good fortune.
[But don't fail the mission
because of this!]
- Three o'clock!
- Not yet.
I think it's 10 minutes away.
2:48 p.m?
They say it's 2:50.
- 10 minutes away.
- Even this doesn't work.
[Depressed]
I'll try this in 10 minutes.
[I'm depressed, too.]
I need to finish the recording.
Let's hurry...
- Four of you can leave now.
- Thank you!
Kim Jong Kook, why are you leaving?
What's wrong with that?
[Who will stop Gary with me?]
Kwang Soo might not
be able to leave here.
- Kwang Soo ruined it.
- He might be left with Gary.
If Kwang Soo can't find it.
Then, it's over.
That's right.
Didn't Gary succeed at the match game?
But we need to leave
Gary here alone, right?
That's right.
- In the end, we need to.
- I gave him an 'H.'
Good job.
[Recording, recording]
- Is he staying?
- Yes, he's staying.
I'm sorry, but we can't
give you what you want
even if you win this game.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Ask for 'o' and 'a' to
make the 'WA' sound.
'O' and 'A' instead of 'WA.'
- How about that?
- So, two instead of one?
- You don't have 'WA'?
- I have to find it.
I've searched for hours,
but I couldn't find 'WA.'
[Island, waa...]
I'll win 'O' and 'A.'
This is decibel meter.
You will scream in front of the meter
and one person with
the highest number will win.
When you become castaway,
you should scream loud.
There was a reason behind the games.
[The first runner is John Park.]
Should I start now?
- Ah!
- That's too weak.
- It's 98.4.
- You need to have more than 100.
I'm getting nervous.
[The second runner of
Ring My Decibel is Big-nose.]
[He has the highest number.]
124.7!
Ikay!
What do you mean by 'ikay'?
[Damn it.]
Suk Jin is talking non-sense.
He said 'ikay' instead of 'okay.'
[I'm not myself.]
[He's holding the microphone
with two hands.]
I can't read the meter.
I'm in a hurry...
Calm down!
- Gary, calm down.
- I'll do anything.
I need to release my album on time.
- I understand that...
- Just let me...
[Gary... since when did you
start moving so fast?]
[Oh, my throat that usually work
for slow raps, please help me.]
[Rock spirit!]
[What was the sound?]
That was loud.
130.
[I'm burned out.]
[To stop Gary from getting a letter
someone has to get a higher number.]
[The fourth runner of
Ring My Decibel is Giraffe.]
[I'm going to do my best
to make Gary stay.]
[I'll complete the TruGary Show.]
Start!
[Side attack!]
[That's my persona!]
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say sorry.
92.4.
[The lowest number]
I'm in a hurry.
[The foul king]
[The last runner of
Ring My Decibel, Grasshopper]
Sorry, I'm desperate.
[Desperate Gary at the back]
[Betrayal Giraffe at the side]
You can start any moment you're ready.
I'm not ready yet.
Ready, set...
go!
[His whole body is shaking.]
Gary won this.
[Gary wins at Ring My Decibel.]
[Gary gets 'EE.']
Isn't that unfair?
- This is the worst piece!
- They had 'EE'?
I still have two more to get.
Wasn't that too much?
[Time to focus on the TruGary Show.]
This is not a clean game.
Gary needs two, I need one,
and Kwang Soo needs two.
Do I really need two?
- Sung Gyu?
- I need two.
- I need one more.
- Me, too.
Let's just help each other
and leave together.
We'll escape together!
This is a battle between
production crews and us!
[Two hours left until
five o'clock.]
[They have to collect
about two letters.]
We need to help the ones
with less letters first.
[What will be the final result?]
I feel bad for Gary.
[On the other side of the island,
members who escaped are taking a rest.]
Gary has no idea
that we're relaxing like this.
Can you throw me a banana?
Have a baguette with condensed milk.
I feel sorry for them.
It's so delicious.
Can we just enjoy this?
What if Kwang Soo can't escape?
He has to find a piece, 'WA.'
It's impossible.
By the way... why do I feel
like I'm in detention?
It feels really bad.
Why did we even take the IQ test?
It's the same usual members!
Gary, Suk Jin...
[They're Dumb and Dumber Avengers.]
Is this a detention of life?
- You need to hold the both ends.
- Do we tie a knot?
You should tie a knot while you
hold each end with your hand.
- You can do it.
- What are you talking about?
- Just one knot?
- Yes, go somewhere and practice.
- Anyone who can do it can try first?
- Yes.
Is this possible?
I'm going to do it, no matter what!
Three o'clock!
[Tying a knot is too difficult!]
[I want to guess the time
and leave this island...]
It's not.
Three o'clock!
[He tries right after
Grasshopper fails.]
- John Park!
- Really?
[John Park succeeds
at three o'clock mission.]
You're right.
What letter do you want?
Is it three o'clock?
And I was wrong?
- You were wrong.
- What time was it?
You shouted 12 seconds before 3.
What do you want, John Park?
I want an 'S.'
It was so close.
[Gary is struggling with the rope.]
If you're not going to challenge,
please go away from the table.
We'll give you a letter for two people.
[I need to win second place!]
Park, you need to be good.
[Gary needs two letters
and the rest needs one letter.]
This drives me nuts.
I'll leave first.
I'm sorry.
[Big-nose will leave?]
[Do you even know how to play it?]
You need to twist it.
[He knows something.]
[Will he be able to tie a knot?]
[I'll copy what he does.]
I'll escape now and
leave him with you.
He doesn't know how to do it.
He's playing jump rope.
I'll try now.
[He's in a hurry.]
[He puts the rope through his body .]
[It's back to square.]
Wait, wait!
I'm not done yet.
Wait, I...
[Is he a performance artist?]
Wait, wait.
I haven't touched the rope
with my hands.
I haven't touched it.
Wait.
[It's like marching in place.]
You saw I didn't touch it, right?
So, I just need to tie a knot, right?
[Now, I just need to put it down.]
[Putting it up again]
Wait for me!
- Gary, how long are you...
- Wait!
Wait and watch!
Gary, I think you failed.
Did you do it?
What?
Did he tie a knot?
[His strong wish made a miracle...]
- I don't think you tied it.
- Yes, I did it.
Put it one more time will do.
He's really passionate.
He's going to do it!
I've never seen him doing
anything so hard.
[He figured it out!
What's the result?]
[Please, please, please!]
- Gary, what are you doing?
- How long are you going to do that?
Don't we need to have a time limit?
- Gary, I don't think you can...
- I'm doing it.
I just need to take it out!
[Empty]
[He's so naive.]
[Dizzy, dizzy]
Can we watch him?
He keeps saying he knows the answer.
I know the answer.
But the arm is the problem.
- It doesn't make sense.
- It's impossible.
[Big-nose knows the secret?]
I'll do it.
I need to get on the boat.
What is he doing?
It doesn't make sense.
Look at Suk Jin.
Yeah!
[Success!]
[He twisted his arms first and did it.]
[He tied a knot!]
[Culture shock]
[I still don't understand...]
- Did you see that?
- Ji Suk Jin succeeded.
Let me try!
[Jae Suk saw what
Big-nose was doing.]
Does this really work?
[He's still tries
with his whole body.]
[Carefully]
He's going to fail.
I did it!
[Grasshopper succeeds at it.]
I can leave now!
[Big-nose and Grasshopper can escape!]
This is how you do it?
That's how you do it.
Stop it!
Just stop it!
How did you figure it out?
I've seen it in a book.
- We did it!
- Wear the jacket and leave.
- Okay!
What do we do if Jae Suk leaves?
[Will the TruGary Show be able to go
on as planned with Giraffe and John Park?]
I can give you a deal.
Only three of you are left.
The last game I suggest
is guessing due north.
Make a straight line
that you think points due north.
We'll put a compass.
We'll give you the letter you want,
if you're correct.
Let's do it.
Otherwise, you can go search the island.
It's up to you.
[Runs]
[He'd rather find 'WA' at once,
than play two missions.]
I've searched almost everywhere.
Where do I find 'AO...'
This drives me crazy.
Gary needs one more after that mission.
West...
If that's the west
then this is the east.
I remember that line.
This is the west, that is east.
[He's mobilizing his whole sense
to guess the direction.]
When we arrived here at noon...
[You don't look like Gary...]
[Will his sense of urgency
wake up his potential?]
I think this is the direct north.
I'm decided.
It's slightly different.
[Two lines are similar
but different, who's the winner?]
Please, be correct!
- How many letters do you need?
- One.
- Two.
Gary is correct.
[Garry guessed it right.]
It was correct!
Check it out, it's correct!
How did you guess that right?
Gary needs to collect one.
[He needs a 'U.']
[All three of them need one letter.]
[It's the last chance
to search and find!]
[Where are you, 'U'?]
You need a herbalist from Joseon Era.
[John Park is searching for 'K.']
[It's become a heated
triangular contest!]
[Seriously, where is it?]
Please...
[Giraffe is focused on the area
that he hasn't been to.]
[John Park finds a bag
in between rocks.]
[But it's 'D.']
[The coastline is long,
but it's still a piece of land.]
[John Park finds another bag.]
I found K!
[He finishes Park Sung Gyu.]
[John Park escapes
from the desert island!]
[Desperate Gary and Passionate Giraffe
are the only ones left!]
[Success or Fail?
It's in their hands now!]
[Will Gary win and finish the race?]
[Or will Giraffe win and
finish the TruGary Show?]
Wow!
[Eureka!]
[Did he find the 'WA'?]
What's going on?
Why is he running?
Kwang Soo!
[Did you find it, Kwang Soo?]
Wa!
[He found 'WA.']
- Did you find yours?
- Yes, I found a' K.'
[Carefully]
[I can't rip it
apart again!]
[He's treating it like
a national treasure.]
[It would have been a lot easier]
[if his name was
'Kang Soo' or 'Kong Soo.']
[Giraffe completes 'Lee Kwang Soo.']
[Everyone except Gary escapes
from the desert island.]
[Gary searches alone.]
[Please, stop the time for me!]
[We've completed our mission, bye!]
[Everyone left like that...]
[Deserted]
[I put so much effort into
this album for more than a year...]
[I couldn't finish recording
because I'm stuck on the island.]
[Sigh]
[Time is up!]
[Gary fails the mission.]
- Did Sung Gyu leave?
- Yes.
[I'm all alone...]
[I'll have to sleep on
this island by myself.]
Are you okay?
[Nod, nod]
Then, we'll take you to the tent
by boat.
[Devastated]
[Goodbye studio session!]
[I've worked so hard
to escape all day long...]
[I'm stuck out here for a long while.]
[Oh, my album...]
[I worked for a year and a half.]
My album will have nine tracks.
I tried to make ten tracks...
I'm sorry.
I have bad luck this year.
It'll be nine tracks.
I've recorded it for a year and a half.
Today...
I want to believe this
is a hidden camera.
Didn't you plan a hidden camera for me?
[If you said that earlier,
the TruGary Show would have failed...]
[They're having a party.]
We've succeeded!
We did it.
This is the paradise!
You're enjoying your time here?
The title song of the album is
'Get Some Air.'
I guess that song is for me.
I'm going there to get some air!
[Where this boat takes me...]
[is where I spend the night.]
I wish this was a hidden camera for me.
- Welcome!
- Kang Gary!
Gary!
[Where this boat lands...]
[we wait for you.]
Why are they all waiting there?
[Am I the only one staying?]
What's going on?
What is it?
Kang Gary!
[Are you surprised?]
What is it?
What's going on?
We had so much fun!
He thought he was staying the night here.
Yes.
I was disheartened...
- What is all this?
- Eat some.
September fourth, a few years ago
we had the 'TruGary Show.'
The 'TruGary Show' has returned!
[The TruGary Show returns
in desert island!]
Thank you so much!
I can go home?
Gary was desperate.
Gary was the most desperate one.
You had a 'K.'
Tell me.
Me?
He had a 'K' but he
didn't give it to me.
- Did you have one?
- Yes.
I thought he was going
to trade it later.
Then, he left the island.
I asked Jong Kook before I left.
If it wasn't for hidden camera,
I would have felt really bad!
Do you know what I was thinking?
'It must have been an H.'
Rap Monster wouldn't...
[It's good that it's a happy ending.]
So, today you've succeeded
at the 'TruGary Show.'
The boat is here!
- We can leave!
- Let's go!
[Finally, they can
escape from the island.]
- It was the TruGary Show!
- Thank you!
[Thank you, Gary.]
[After Gary got some air
he was able to finish the work.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Happy Korean Thanksgiving!]
[The rest stop on a blocked highway
is like an oasis in the desert.]
[Rest Stop Food Race with Hong Jin Young,
Eun Hyuk and Im Joo Hwan]
[From stone pot bibimbap
to Korean beef steak]
Isn't Kyungpo Beach nice?
[A heated fight for a
Thanksgiving gift set!]
[The men who threw away their pride vs.
The women who threw away their image.]
[Who will win the
'Thanksgiving gift set'?]
Next week, 'Running Man'
'Happy Thanksgiving Race.'