['K' Golf Course in Gyeonggi Province.]
Today, it's a couple race.
A couple race?
[They're highly motivated
from the beginning.]
- Is it an idol special?
- This day has come again!
[Six male members,
six gift boxes.]
Six beautifully wrapped gift boxes
are waiting for you.
Your wrists are attached
to the strings, right?
I will call a name
and another person will appear
as they lift their hand up.
Those two are a team.
We will start with our lover boy, Gary.
- Oh!
- What is it?
- This is making me really nervous.
- Is it Ji Hyo?
- Who will it be?
- It must be Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo!
- It's not Ji Hyo!
- It's been a while.
Please reveal Gary's partner!
[Hand lift.]
- Hi!
- It's Ji Hyo!
[He drew Blank Ji.]
[Congratulations, it's Monday Couple!]
- It's Blank Ji Hyo.
- I should be happy about it.
It's Ji Hyo!
I'm slightly nervous to be
partnered with Gary for a while.
- Are you nervous?
- Your heart's fluttering?
Ji Hyo even put on perfume!
Hold hands so we don't get
confused with the non-couples.
- This is nothing.
- Please show us today!
- Can we lock hands?
- He wants to lock hands.
It's a habit.
Next is Ha Ha.
[The big reveal!]
Please reveal Ha Ha's partner!
[Everyone's talking about
couples and lovers.]
[The definition of couple is...]
Honey!
[Ha Ha's wife, Byul.]
[The first time hearing
'honey' on Running Man.]
[Everyone's shocked.]
[Were you surprised?]
Is Jae Suk's wife coming, too?
What are you saying?
- Hello!
- Hi, Byul!
- This is a first!
This is a little awkward.
- You don't seem happy.
- No, no.
- What are you doing?
- Why are you so shy?
I'm really shy, too.
Ha Ha can't do anything today.
He can't do much.
She's visiting her husband's workplace.
Do you know what he said to me
when Ha Ha's wife appeared?
- He looks nervous.
- No.
'That really sucks for him.'
She hasn't had an outing in a while.
What if your wife comes?
Is his wife coming today?
- That's impossible.
- Ryu Su Jung.
I didn't know Byul was coming today.
I will show you what a real couple is.
Are these all real couples?
Next is Yoo Jae Suk.
Na Kyung Eun!
- Na Kyung Eun might come.
- Kyung Eun.
No way.
After the helicopter passes.
- She might come.
- Is she on the helicopter?
Who is it?
I'm really curious.
If Byul came today...
you never know.
Please reveal...
Yoo Jae Suk's partner!
[Did she really... come?]
Please reveal
Yoo Jae Suk's partner!
I'm so curious.
[Lift.]
[What the heck?]
- Really?
- For real?
[Puzzled]
Me?
- Me and him?
- Me?
Me?
[Bravo.]
- Nice!
- Me?
What are you doing?
[Is this real?]
[Be happy together.]
- It's 'Love and War.'
- It fits perfectly.
We can't do a couple race together!
Suk Jin!
We're good to go!
There are a lot of boxes left!
- Come here Kwang Soo.
- This is crazy.
- Is it the easy brothers today?
- Go over there!
- There are still some left.
- Come this way.
- Don't tell me what to do!
- Come here!
[Let's be happy, Honey.]
What are you doing
with Jong Kook and I?
- I have a bad feeling.
- Ryu Su Jung!
- No.
[It can't happen...]
Please reveal Ji Suk Jin's partner!
[Big-nose Couple Reveal!]
His arm is going up!
Don't put pressure on it!
- I saw it, don't resist!
- It already went up a lot.
No, not at all.
This is disappointing!
[Big-nose and Giraffe couple.]
There are so many boxes left!
- There are four boxes left!
- But why?
[Huh?]
[Two people at once?]
[Another real couple's entrance.]
[Wow.]
It's Son Jun Ho!
[Musical Prince Son Jun Ho.]
[Super diva and Alpha Mom,
Kim So Hyun.]
- Hello!
- Welcome!
You're a real couple!
Where's Ju An?
[They met as a couple in
'Phantom of the Opera']
[and became a real couple.]
[They are masters at both
child-rearing and love!]
Let's give our guests some applause!
[They were on 'Oh My Baby'
and now they're on Running Man!]
You're both handsome and beautiful.
Isn't your father a doctor?
[Shocked at the sudden question.]
- What did you ask?
- Isn't her father a doctor?
- And you're older than him, right?
- Yes.
- What are you saying?
- I just said what I knew.
These are the couples.
First, the official Monday couple...
Gary and Ji Hyo.
Korea's 'Brangelina' Ha Ha and Byul.
[Bran... what?]
Why are there so many Brangelinas?
[We never said anything...]
Forever in a love-hate relationship,
Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
- It's a couple race today!
- Don't complain!
- I don't like it either.
- Just focus on the game today!
Don't talk, play the game and leave!
Somewhere between alliance and betrayal,
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.
- We were never attracted to each other!
- No.
Lastly, we have the musical star couple,
Son Jun Ho and Kim So Hyun.
Today, the race is called
'The Love and War Race.'
- We're just war!
- We're also war.
[There's already a war.]
- What is it?
- If you see here
There are rings that are
numbered from 1 to 32.
Three teams who have
won the interim missions
will have the chance
to get rid of the rings.
Get as many chances as you can
and the team that gets
rid of the most rings
will do the final mission.
It's good.
[By the way...]
[There are people watching them.]
I'm warmer because I'm wearing black!
I'm hot because of you!
Don't the couples have to hold hands?
Can I grab him by the collar?
Grab whatever.
[Grab.]
[Let's also grab whatever.]
We claim war!
We claim love!
[Although it's blurry,
we can see a handsome figure.]
- I'm feeling a little nervous today.
- Don't lie!
[They are entering the filming set!]
- You're so weird today!
- Coffee delivery!
[Coff... what?]
- What?
[A precious friend who came
to visit with a load of gifts.]
[Song Joong Ki!]
[Is it really Joong Ki?]
[And Jo In Sung!]
[Yahoo!]
[We're lucky today!]
[And finally Im Joo Hwan.]
[A sudden attack of
the three flower boys.]
[Are you Kwang Soo's stylist?]
[Oh my god!]
Joong Ki!
[Joong Ki's sudden visit.]
[In Sung and Ju Hwan
accompanied Joong Ki today.]
[It became a greeting session.]
[I want to go closer.]
- Hello.
He said hi to me.
Go hug him!
[The greeting session
seems to be done...]
[It became a meet and greet.]
[A lucky encounter
thanks to her husband.]
- What are you guys doing?
- When did you get here?
[Greeting the staff as well.]
- Don't do that! He's uncomfortable!
- What's going on today?
[So Hyun got courage.]
Can I just get one photo?
[She became a teenage girl.]
[All thanks to 'Running Man.']
[Uncomfortable.]
Look at his face!
[Pretending to be cool about it.]
She's my wife.
Joong Ki got discharged
from the army last May.
Give him some applause.
[He's still taking a selfie.]
What are you doing?
- Stop it!
- Okay!
This is my personal life!
Wait!
Why are you all coming here?
She really likes them.
[I want to...]
Take some photos!
[see them up close.]
She liked them more
than her husband for a second.
I'm serious, I saw it!
Coming today was the best decision.
Your body's gotten more muscular!
- He worked out a lot.
- Joong Ki...
left experiencing all the
difficult stuff at the beginning.
[All the precious memories
with Joong Ki.]
I was born in '85, the year of the ox.
I'm 26.
[The young boy we knew]
[has returned as an actor
to represent Korea.]
You brought him, but only
Kwang Soo became popular!
[The biggest beneficiary, Giraffe.]
I kept thinking of 'Running Man'
while I was in the army.
I came because I wanted to see you guys.
But I don't know if I'm a bother.
- What do you mean bother?
- We missed Joong Ki.
But In Sung and Joo Hwan came as well!
He's my favorite stylist.
[The stylist is more handsome
than the actual celebrity.]
In Sung, why are you
close with Kwang Soo?
He follows me.
[Satisfying.]
- He follows him.
- He has a good personality.
How long has it been, Joo Hwan?
- We met at Jeju Island.
- We went fishing back then.
- Oh, right we went fishing.
- Yeah.
We were eating dinner yesterday.
Joong Ki wanted to say hi
after the discharge
but he didn't have much time
due to his drama and what not.
What do you mean get lost!
I want to hear them
but you keep talking!
[Slap.]
- I got slapped!
- Good job!
[Why are you being a nuisance?]
Good job, In Sung!
[He did it for everyone.]
Hit me once, too!
Were you this kind of a person?
Anyway, Joong Ki came to say
hi after he got discharged
and he's going to get busier
so he probably wouldn't
have been able to come
but he wanted to say hi
so he came all the way.
And In Sung and Joo Hwan are close
with Joong Ki so they came.
Thank you so much for coming today.
Give them an applause!
Next time, you should be
on the show as a guest.
No, my schedule's full.
You have nothing to do.
Let's just make a game, right now.
If we were in the water,
I would take his pants off.
[This man!]
Please say something to the audience.
Hello, this is Song Joong Ki.
It's been a while.
This is like...
my second home.
And it's been a while since
I've seen the staff and directors.
I just came to say hi today
and next time, I'll come with
In Sung since he's not busy.
- We'll just bring In Sung.
- We'll go to his house.
Please kidnap us.
I know his house password.
[All of a sudden!]
Our writer is a fan, so...
[Signing]
[I didn't expect that!]
What's your name?
It's Ji Eun, right?
[He's blocking her for the flower boys.]
[He's the best.]
Here, Ji Eun.
Be happy.
She always asked me for my signature
and I never had the time,
but I finally did it today.
Anyway, let's hear from In Sung.
It's In Sung's turn to say something.
In Sung, please say something.
Hello, nice to meet you.
He's not a person...
I've been on SBS a few times
because of dramas
but it's been a long time
since I was on a variety show
thanks to Joong Ki and Kwang Soo.
I'm grateful that I could come today.
Even if In Sung's schedule
doesn't allow it...
we'll just bring him
when we bring Joong Ki.
I can make him faint for three seconds.
I'm going to call the police.
We should hear from Joo Hwan, too.
Hello, I've been here once and
this is my second time here.
It was a very sudden visit.
The bag really suits you.
What is this bag?
- Coffee and some snacks.
- Really?
- You brought all these?
- When you usually go out
is it the four of you?
And also Ki Bang.
- Ki Bang, too?
- Oh, we forgot to call Ki Bang!
[It's a secret.]
- Ki Bang will be hurt.
- Ki Bang might get sad.
We'll go on a separate
outing with Ki Bang.
Thanks so much for coming,
even if it was short.
And since Joong Ki's back,
I hope he can say hello elsewhere, too.
Thanks to In Sung and Joo Hwan again.
Hopefully we can see each other soon.
We'll come get you.
[Race start.]
You never kissed!
How do you know?
[Is it real or fake?]
[A war-like couple race.]
[Thirty two rings in total!]
[Challenge the final mission
by eliminating the rings!]
How long has it been since
you've been married?
- Almost five years for us.
- Five years?
Almost three years.
If your wife likes another celebrity
do you get jealous?
- I like a lot of celebrities.
- Me? Were you asking me?
Your question's wrong because
you're not married yet.
- What do you mean?
- You can't ask like that!
This single man!
You need love to get jealous.
You can't answer
that question so easily.
Just because there's a camera here,
it doesn't mean
we're done filming.
We're going home together.
Round two starts after that!
- He doesn't know!
- It was my mistake...
But do you get jealous?
I'm curious now.
No, I don't get jealous.
- Do you get jealous?
- No, I don't.
- Really?
- Because they're celebrities.
- Has she ever liked anyone?
- Yeah.
Kyung Eun likes Joong Ki.
- She likes Joong Ki?
- Yeah, she does.
It keeps changing,
but yeah she likes him.
She likes whoever appears on a drama.
Yeah, that's so true.
After you get married the
jealousy goes away, right?
But I think if you married,
you'd be jealous all the time.
I'm not like that!
You're pretty narrow-minded.
- Narrow-minded?
- Narrow-minded!
Who do you like, Jun Ho?
Because So Hyun liked In Sung.
- Girls Generation!
- Yes, I like Girls Generation.
- Who in Girls Generation?
- I like them all.
- Pick one.
- I like...
It's really hard.
He has someone in mind for sure!
He's just saying that he doesn't.
It's for sure!
We're laughing now.
But on the way back,
she's going to ask, 'but who is it?'
with a smile, calmly.
Jun Ho could truthfully answer
but he's going to say,
'But didn't you like In Sung?'
[So accurate.]
- It's so true.
- Of course!
When I'm watching a drama, he tells me
to go inside and stop watching it.
- Really?
- He does that?
[Love and War race, first mission site.]
[What is this?]
[A pugil stick covered
in bubble wrap.]
- What is that?
- It's a good thing we're a team.
What do you mean, good?
What is this?
What are we doing?
- What is all this?
- What are we doing?
Are we fighting with this?
I want to take this home!
[What is happening here...]
This is the first mission,
'The styrofoam love fight.'
One person from each couple goes up
Then, they use the punch stick
to eliminate the other opponent.
Jong Kook's team is at an advantage.
No, I'm injured.
- My ankle hurts.
- Jong Kook's good at everything.
We are at an advantage.
Why aren't you supporting me?
But we are at an advantage.
You're secretly boasting.
Each person will compete,
then if someone falls
their partner can fight their opponent.
Then you can qualify in the next round.
Can I win today?
I always lose at the last second.
One team will win by default.
I wish it were us...
The choice of the order
will be with a pre-mission.
Locking the hands of love.
You've all probably done it before.
Kim Jong Kook, please come forward.
Lie down on your back.
Yoo Jae Suk, please come forward.
[Unhappy.]
- Oh this?
- Do the airplane.
- Do the airplane, with your feet.
- With my feet?
Should I take my shoes off?
- Keep them on.
- Keep them on? On your stomach?
- Is it okay?
- You should take them off.
You said it was okay!
I have a white shirt.
I laid down on the floor!
[They bicker about everything.]
Even his bandages are tiger patterned!
[Roar.]
It's hot... your feet are hot.
- What?
- Cool your feet down!
Then what do I do?
It's hot!
- Even if it's a female, it's bad.
- They're hot for each other!
I broke up once because of hot feet.
- Jae Suk, lift your legs off the ground.
- Oh I lift them?
You have to balance with your hands.
It's very stable.
After 30 seconds,
bend your arms like push ups.
You have to bend your legs.
- He likes to work out.
- It's too easy for Jong Kook.
Who is this game designed for?
- We're definitely going to win this.
- For sure.
[It's designed for us,
what are you going to do?]
[Gloomy.]
Let's reverse!
The girl goes on the bottom.
You can do that!
- She's going on the bottom, too!
- What?
How am I going to hold you up?
What are you saying?
[Your humor is... classy.]
He's using honorifics, too.
It's scary.
[Who will be the last team
to win the pre-mission?]
Lower your partner on the first whistle.
Lift them back up on the second one.
Suk Jin, you should do it!
I will, I will!
It's not hard!
How much do you weigh?
Is this the only game you can think of?
Ready, set...
Everyone's ready, right?
Ready, set!
[Locking the hands of love, start!]
[Lift.]
Oh my goodness...
Did you eat today?
You're like a feather!
So light!
Very nice!
Thirty seconds needed to pass.
You made such a weird game.
- You made such a weird game.
- Lower.
[The time of torture.]
Honey!
Honey!!
[The sound that wakes you up, 'honey']
[The men with their women are
showing off their virile beauty.]
[Just feeling heavy
vs. the power of love.]
I did it!
Ji Suk Jin, please lift him up.
- Yes, like that.
- Hey! It hurts!
Just hold it in for a second.
[Illegal parking.]
[Risky couple.]
[I give up.]
[They couldn't stand the pain.]
[The fighting spirit of the couples.]
Honey, I'm sorry!
[Elimination due to his
wife's heavy love.]
Three teams are left.
[Monday couple, real couple survived.]
Ha Ha's a little different today!
[The lifting of a man.]
Can't you see what's going on?
Go easy!
He wants us to go easy.
Ji Hyo, don't laugh!
I'm getting tired!
[Three minutes passed.]
It's hard to judge right now.
[Number 1, Ha Byul couple.]
[I'm going to try my best
until the last moment.]
[Number 2, Monday couple.]
[I waited five years...
I can wait until we win this...]
[Number 3, Kkuk and Hopper.]
[Although we bicker, together,
we can overcome anything...]
Get off!
[There's no reason to overcome this!]
Agh!
Move!
[He's calm even after a butt attack.]
What are you doing?
Monday couple vs. the real couple.
Gary!
You're a man today!
I can't give up today!
He's a man to Ji Hyo today!
- Gary! I'll treat you to dinner.
- No!
You're fake anyway!
This is a chance for me!
[One man is doing it for his family]
[another one is doing it
to start a family.]
Ha Ha's different because
Byul's here today.
- He's different from usual.
- He's showing us what a man is.
But more than anything...
Jun Ho's probably awkward right now.
I didn't know.
We're not really a couple,
so it doesn't matter.
[The most embarrassing moment.]
Song Ji Hyo!
You can't date even if you win!
You don't know when you'll break up!
[What goes around comes around.]
[Energy up!]
- I'm going all the way today.
- So am I.
[Intense.]
I want to be lying down, too.
- You're awesome.
- It's really hard to judge.
[Will the four years of love...]
[beat the five years of
Gary's one-sided love?]
[Lift up!]
Honey... it came...
[Tremble, tremble.]
Gary, what are you doing this for?
I can't give up!
That fake couple!
That business couple!
Do you know business?
He just wants to film commercials!
Song! Ji!
Hyo!
Kang! Ga!
Ry!
[I like you.]
This is like the actual mission.
This is the real mission for us!
We know Ha Ha really well,
and he looks so cool today.
It's a first to see him like this.
- He usually doesn't try this hard.
- You guys haven't even kissed yet!
Hey!
What do you know?
You never know!
Nice!
Good job.
[Up again.]
Let's go!
Starting now, it will be
three times in a row.
One, two, three!
Now we will go five times in a row!
Start!
Dream... Dream's daddy!
- One, two...
- Dream's daddy!
Three, four!
[Gary and Ji Hyo succeeds!]
[What about Dream's daddy?]
Three, four!
Last one!
Ha Ha!
You can do it!
Let's go! Let's go!
Oh my gosh.
[I've never been this
fired up about winning...]
[I've never been strong...]
[But I want to be the
strongest in front of you.]
[Because I am the head of the family...]
[He did it!]
Honey, not there!
Isn't that too long of a break?
Now, we will do it five times.
But the person who
does it first will win.
The one who does it first.
Ready, set!
This will be the final round!
One, two, three, four, five!
[Ha Ha and Byul won by a millisecond.]
[You did well, Dream's dad.]
- Did we win?
- Yes!
Wow, that's amazing.
[Ha Ha... you're different today.]
Ha Ha's a man!
[A father... is always full of
energy in front of his family.]
Usually, when the
husband's a little tired
the wife says 'you can stop now.'
But she kept saying
'think of Dream, you can do it!'
[You've got to keep your men strong.]
That's the difference
between real and fake.
Gary's amazing, too.
[I hope my sincerity reached Ji Hyo.]
[Ha Ha and Byul can
decide the order now.]
Go Byul!
Byul, I love you!
- I cheered you on a lot!
- I'm your fan!
Everyone, pick where you want to go.
- How about...
- Be!
Tray!
Get lost!
[How does a person change...]
- Can you do an acrostic poem right now?
- Of course.
- Ha!
- Ha Ha?
- Ha Ha!
- Byul (star)!
- Stars shine bright, just like you!
[Mr. Capable...
is good at anything...]
It'll be Suk Jin!
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook
vs. Easy Brothers]
[The Styrofoam love fight]
[Suk Jin vs.. Jae Suk]
Please step on the form rolls.
Wait!
I'll cheer you on forever!
Good luck, Ji Suk Jin!
[Satisfied]
[What about me?]
Do it properly, okay?
- It's a cheer, right?
- Of course, it is.
It's not easy to balance.
[The battle of herbivores]
[Who's the weakest?]
[The winner of the semi-finals,
Big-nose]
[I will win this time!]
[I won't let you!]
[The most agile man, Yoo Hyuk]
[I'm the king of a herbivores!]
[He keeps throwing straight punches.]
[I hit him!]
[But he counterattacks
with a left hook.]
They're neck and neck!
What's going on?
[Very intense battle.]
[What's with these people?]
[Goodbye, Big-nose!]
[Goodbye!
I'll let you leave.]
[Big-nose drops out.]
- Good job!
- Can I do it again?
[What a feeling!]
This is upsetting!
Let's say this was a practice round.
I guess it's hard to
keep balance.
That was satisfying!
[The Styrofoam love fight]
[Kwang Soo vs. Jae Suk]
Ready, set, go!
[Giraffe with long arms and legs
vs. Grasshopper with a powerful punch.]
[Masters of avoiding.]
[Take that!]
[Do you think it's going to work?]
[Hit... and hit...]
Are you actually trying?
[This beater loves me.]
- Are you trying to avoid it?
- That's nice.
Very good!
Good job!
[This is humiliating...]
[Angry counterattack.]
Good job!
Be careful and hit him!
Hit him!
[Deep bow.]
That's right!
Watch out!
[Who told you to hit my head?]
Push him, push him!
[It's your turn.]
Very good!
Good, Kwang Soo!
[He held out.]
Very good!
[Bull's eye!]
[Kwang Soo loses.]
[Sad]
[Happy]
[He defeated them all by himself.]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook wins.]
We were close.
[The Styrofoam love fight]
[Gary vs. Jun Ho]
- It's Gary and Jun Ho.
- Fight!
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
[They have high hopes for this match.]
Start!
Show him, Gary!
[Gary used to do boxing...]
[Huh? What's going on?]
[Absurd.]
[It ended in five seconds.]
He's knocked down!
Are we allowed to hit
each other's jaw?
[It was 'at one blow,' literally.]
I thought I was watching a UFC fight.
He's got the counter!
I'm seeing stars.
Oh, Byul (star)?
Can you edit it well for me?
This is embarrassing.
- Gary, it was something else.
- My jaw got hit.
[The Styrofoam love fight]
[Jun Ho vs. Ha Ha]
I'm already tired.
This is tiring.
- His legs are shaking.
- Ha Ha was doing the bicycle before.
In short, Ha Ha's lower
body is crumbled.
Gary's face is crumbled too.
Because of an upper cut.
[The real couple's rivalry, starts!]
Ha Ha looks different today.
[Haroro is attacking while sitting.]
Ha Ha needs a counterattack.
- That's right!
- Honey!
Just push him.
That's right.
You need to break his balance.
[Extraordinary.]
[Ju An's Daddy vs. Dream's Daddy]
[I need to survive.]
[He's one of those fathers...]
Honey!
He's still alive.
He's hanging on.
[Let me finish it!]
[What is he holding?]
[A link between you and me]
Ha Ha's still alive!
Push him!
[The situation is reversed.]
[In par terre position!]
- Wives!
- Honey!
- Dream's Daddy!
- Watch out, honey!
- Honey.
- Dream is watching you!
Are you going to get
scolded if you lose?
I don't want to get married!
This is amazing!
[A man can lose,
but a family head can't!]
Ha Ha wins!
[Jun Ho touched the floor first.]
Are you tied to your wife's aprons?
This is the marriage life!
This is the reality.
[Dream's parents make it to the finals.]
[Jong Kook vs. Ha Ha]
It's not easy to keep your balance.
- Be careful.
- Ha Ha is different today.
[Very charismatic.]
Dong Hun, you look stronger.
It maybe true but...
I think he reached his limit.
[My Partner, Grasshopper!]
I cheer for you, Dong Hun!
I'm just saying people have limit.
[Mr. Capable vs. Dream's father]
[Head shot.]
Wait!
- What?
- His wife is watching!
I was striking a cool pose!
You should start with a jab,
how can you start with an uppercut?
Dong Hun, think about all the
sadness for the past five years!
Oh, no!
Keep talking, honey.
No!
[Should I go easy on him?]
[Scattered.]
Oh, my Buddhist rosary!
You're done.
You broke his Buddhist rosary!
It was his great grandmother's!
It's something you
can't buy with money.
It's a family heirloom!
You shouldn't have touched it!
It's been handed down
for three generations!
And it's broken by Ha Ha!
Jong Kook, you should fight
for your great grand mother.
[The enemy of my great grandmother!]
Ha Ha, your wife is watching you.
This broke!
It became nun-chucks!
The beating stick has a joint now.
It's over.
It's off-balance!
[Let's finish up, Ha Ha...]
Then, just walk over to that side...
[Here we go!]
[Forget the Haroro that you know of!]
[I will create new history!]
[Bye!]
[Thrown.]
[Goodnight, Dream's Daddy.]
Jong Kook wins!
I can tell how hard his work is.
Be nice to me.
I will, from now on.
[Jong Kook lost to Byul.]
We were very close but...
this is a game.
[The finals.]
[Grasshopper vs. Byul]
You look different...
I'm scared.
Jae Suk is not going to go easy on you.
[Let's see who's the strongest.]
[Trespassing!]
Attack!
Now!
[She shuts her eyes tight
and gives everything she has.]
[The die is cast!]
[It's not going to end like this...]
[but it did!]
[Grasshopper is exterminated.]
- Honey!
- What are you doing?
The base turned upside down.
What were you doing?
Honey, we won!
[The Styrofoam love fight]
Ha Ha and Byul wins!
Winners, please come forward.
[What privilege will they have?]
You see...
there are 32 rings.
Since you're the first winners,
take out ten numbers.
[The first winners can
eliminate ten numbers.]
[Byul's debut song]
December 32nd!
- Take it out.
- Can we say it out loud?
It doesn't matter.
[How will it effect the final mission?]
[They eliminated ten numbers.]
- We're the second place winners.
- How many can we pick?
Second place can
eliminate seven numbers.
Seven numbers, it's not bad.
Seven numbers?
[They eliminated seven numbers.]
It's perfect.
Five numbers for third place.
- Just random numbers?
- Sure.
[The musical couple
eliminated five numbers.]
[The current state of love rings]
Ha Ha is competitive today.
- Dong Hun, why are you doing that?
- He's a real man.
You look totally different today.
Actually, I know he is a strong man...
On TV...
Are you assisting your husband?
He's always weak on TV.
He's weak, so I couldn't
understand him.
I feel like I'm a
tour guide for couples.
It's fun.
[The second mission site.]
[Yongin Boat Race Course.]
[Next to the peaceful lake...]
[A group of super-sized
water bombs are installed!]
I don't know what it is, but I like it!
Kwang Soo, let's do it!
[The couples are highly motivated.]
We need to sit one by one.
The first winner can sit here
and then the second...
- Where is your place?
- I was the third winner.
Seeing the water above...
- I guess it's from the lake.
- Look at the color.
- This is the moment...
- Just sit down.
Since we have musical stars
we need to greet them.
This is the moment...
When all I've done.
[He summed up the situation.]
See?
You know what Jun Ho
said during the break?
Did I act too lightly?
I didn't think so.
- He's cute.
- That's what we do on variety shows.
- This is the moment.
- When all I've done.
- It's fine.
- She likes it!
I just like the song.
I love this number.
When all I've done!
Why don't you like it?
[The little husband scolds
his wife for her taste in music.]
Ha Ha is the model Korean husband.
I hope they will have
their own show together.
During this game...
the couples can check the truth
and their hearts for each other.
Is it like The Telepathic Quiz?
It's 'Talk Bingo.'
Fill up your bingo table with the
words under the category we suggest
You'll take turns being a caller.
The first one who completes
two rows will make the team win.
The rest of the couples
will get water bombed.
That's harsh!
The category for
the first round is...
'The dating spot I've been to.'
Where do you think he's been to?
He probably didn't have
the chance to date.
What are you talking about?
You mean the dating spots
that we've been together?
It's only good
for the real couples!
Or with someone else?
Why would you want to do that?
- Can we talk to each other?
- No, you can't.
Honey, come to your senses!
[Embarrassed.]
[The dating spot I've been to.]
[Their bingo board is filled in.]
[The Talk Bingo, first round start!]
The dating spot I've been to is...
Night club!
What?
[Jae Suk doesn't have it.]
[Who has it?]
- You're the only one?
- Do any of you have it?
[No one has it.]
Is it good if no one else has it?
Why would you go to a night club
when you date?
Who would date at a club?
Have you gone to
a night club for a date?
Of course!
I have!
- You met someone there?
- No.
- I went there on a date.
- Because you performed together?
- No.
- Oh, to perform together?
I went there with my date
when I was in high school.
- My girlfriend in high school.
- You were a high school student?
That's illegal!
Can't we arrest him now?
It's Byul's turn.
I don't think anyone has it.
A postnatal care center!
[Ha Ha doesn't have it.]
What is that?
[No one else has it.]
- Nice, you're the only one.
- We had a good time there.
I have good memories.
You call it a date?
It's pretty nice.
I recommend it.
It's my turn, right?
Yes, I can see how much
you hate being water bombed.
The dating spot I've been to...
you know before we got married
Spicy rice cake place!
I don't have it.
What do we do, isn't that too specific?
- Snack bar?
- Restaurant?
Restaurant should be fine.
Didn't you hear the rules?
You're not supposed to
write anywhere too specific.
- How can you not write 'restaurant'?
- I couldn't think of it.
Why didn't you write it, honey?
It's Jun Ho's turn.
'The dating spot I've been to' is...
church!
[So Hyun has church, too.]
[The rest are silent.]
At a church?
So Hyun kissed me at
the church for the first time.
- Really?
- At that holy place?
I did it too, with
a daughter of a pastor!
Gary, what are you talking about?
That was my first kiss!
At her church?
Jun Ho, you said So Hyun kissed you?
We were talking in the car
at the parking lot of the church.
In the car, then all of a sudden...
At the time, I kept saying I liked her,
but she didn't accept me.
I said I like her again,
then all of a sudden...
- Oh, no!
- Really?
[Why are you talking about this?]
Why did you change your mind?
It's not that I kissed him but...
He kept hinting?
I tried to avoid him,
but it was the wrong direction.
- You couldn't resist.
- No, I avoided in the wrong direction.
She tried to resist, but couldn't.
God, please allow me!
Oh, So Hyun!
Wow, he's good.
He's good.
He's a rising star.
[He's a new variety star
at 33 years old.]
It's Gary's turn.
'The dating spot I've been to' is...
I'm sure Ji Hyo has it.
- Han River!
- Okay!
Han River!
[Ji Hyo doesn't have it.]
Isn't river enough?
You don't have it?
- Just river is okay?
- But the Han River is different.
Han River and just river
are totally different things.
I'll accept any river for this one.
- Yes!
- Han River has cruise.
Han River is one of
the mandatory places.
Some people camp close to Han River.
Did any of you go to Han River...
and see other celebrities on a date?
- I have.
- Me too.
Honestly, I have, about three times.
I went easy on them.
I've only stayed in the car.
- Why?
- You're nasty!
I was just listening to music
while watching the river.
I've seen you.
- Should I say it?
- Say it.
Should I say it in front of your wife?
What are you doing?
Tell me.
I was just joking.
'The dating spot I've been to' is...
I hope he doesn't say an
old place like Gyeongbok Palace.
Old palace.
He actually said it.
[Careful for what you wish for.]
[No one has it.]
I'm the only one, right?
I never knew.
Did you really go there?
- Yes, I did.
- Actually, it's really nice.
It's really nice at night.
My blind date was at Changgyeong Palace.
The cherry blossoms at
Changgyeong Palace are wonderful.
It's So Hyun's turn.
'The dating spot I've been to' is...
My husband´s grandfather's house!
[Her husband doesn't have it...]
[who else might have it?]
Your answers never match.
I'm sorry, honey.
The day before our wedding photo shoot
we went to my husband's
grandfather's house and took a walk.
Did you kiss there again?
We're always passionate.
They are lovebirds.
He's boastful.
[Embarrassed.]
You told me to do my best...
I'm sorry, I'll be careful.
No, I have to tease you for the show.
- Just keep trying.
- I understand.
So Hyun thinks Jun Ho is cute.
Next, it's Jong Kook's turn.
Jong Kook, call whatever you want.
- It's not 'my house', right?
- This might be common for celebrities.
One, two, three!
Practice room!
I knew it, because
they're musical singers.
[But your partner doesn't have it.]
Practice room?
Is karaoke included?
[He's cute.]
Were you dating a celebrity?
When I was in Turbo.
I know who she is.
I know who his date was.
Shut up.
Then, she must be a singer.
No, she wasn't.
She's not a singer.
Why would you practice
together if she's not a singer?
She just visited my practice room.
I stayed at the practice room
most of the time.
It's Ha Ha's turn.
I think everyone has this.
Just say it.
[Worried.]
- Anything is fine, Honey.
- Namsan!
- A mountain?
- Is mountain okay?
- Han River included all rivers.
Any mountains?
[One row is done.]
How about 'mountain road'?
Mountain.
I don't have it.
- I climbed up a mountain once.
- Which mountain?
- Chunggye mountain.
- Together?
- Yes.
- I went jogging at 2 a.m. once.
- Which mountain?
- Namsan.
Oh, at Namsan mountain?
It's my turn.
Are you ready?
Give us a good one.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Convenience store.
- How about 'supermarket'?
- No.
[Only Jun Ho has it.]
How could you go on a date
at a convenience store?
It doesn't make any sense!
It was really out of the way.
I'm serious.
- It was a tiny store.
- They had chairs?
The guy didn't recognize us.
We could talk for a while.
- I've done it.
- Convenience store.
- Are you talking about your wife?
- Yes.
- And the Chunggye mountain, too?
- Yes, that was with my wife.
- He can't talk about other women.
- Of course not.
You're going too far.
['Talk Bingo' is dangerous.]
[Only one more to go.]
That's good.
[It's Jong Kook's turn.]
'The dating spot I've been to' is...
How have you been?
The U.S.!
[He finishes two diagonals.]
The US?
[The water bomb goes off.]
Oh no!
[Splash!]
[The powerful water bomb
washes away the summer heat.]
[These two stay dry.]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook come in first.]
You're amazing.
[He must train the
muscles in his brain.]
- So fast?
- How did he make it so fast?
- That couple is amazing.
- You need to meet a good partner.
That's right.
[Their improvised song and dance.]
That's why you call him Mr. Capable.
The topic for the second round is
'Disappointing gifts you've received.'
Honey, just include the ones
you received before you met me.
I don't care, okay?
Let's just win.
You need to write the gifts that
you actually received and be specific.
['The gift that disappointed you.']
[The finished boards.]
['Talk Bingo', second round begins.]
I...
think many of you have this.
- No, don't call it.
- If it's in a good position.
It's in a good position.
If it's too common,
sometimes people forget.
It's better to wait,
because other people might say it.
- What do you want me to do?
- Just call it.
- We don't really get along.
- Isn't that weird?
[But they placed first.]
Then I'll call this one.
I think many people wrote this.
A bad gift that made me feel crappy...
Crappy?
That made me feel bad... is
- a letter!
- Great!
[Ha Ha has it.]
[As she expected, a few people have it.]
- It's common.
- A letter, why?
Do postcards count?
How about diary exchanges?
In fact, I...
and other women have
a romantic image about snail mails.
When Ha Ha wrote me a letter...
on my birthday
he asked me what I
wanted for my birthday
and I said nothing else but a letter.
So he wrote me a letter.
But he wrote me a swear word.
- Huh?
- Why did I do that?
Some of you already
know that Ha Ha...
is loving and caring,
but too shy to express it.
He's too embarrassed
to express himself romantically.
He wrote
'Happy birthday.'
'Sorry for not being
able to be with you.'
'I love you.'
Then he wrote a swear word.
- I know what you're talking about.
- He's a macho man.
It was right before the marriage.
- I'm sorry.
- I thought I saw it wrong.
That's great.
On your tenth anniversary,
you should read it back to him
in his ears.
Next is So Hyun's turn.
A credit card with a lowered limit.
You didn't like that credit card?
How much was the limit?
It was when we just started dating.
He made a credit card and gave it to me.
He told me to use it all I want
and I was really happy.
It means he thinks of me
more than just a girlfriend.
He thinks of you as a family.
I was so happy that I
couldn't use the credit card.
Later, I found out about the
credit limit and it surprised me.
Was it because the limit was too little?
No, it's because it's really
impressive when you receive it.
But when you find out about the limit,
it feels like a betrayal.
It feels like that's how
much he can trust me.
She wasn't going to
go over the limit at all...
Let me explain.
- Was it a joke?
- No, I met her at my debut musical.
I was a student right before the time.
Three hundred thousand won
was all I had and I gave her that.
- He gave his everything.
- But he made a credit card for her.
He didn't have much
but he still did it.
I still have the note he
put on the credit card.
What did he write?
Put away your credit card,
and use this card.
He's romantic.
He was going to increase the limit then!
I hate it the most.
This romantic situation,
I really don't know what to do.
I can't stand it when a
romantic scene comes on TV.
- I like it.
- Are you trying to become like Sean?
Sean or Cha In Pyo?
That's amazing.
He's amazing.
Son Jun Ho is the new model husband now.
- The title moves.
- I'm not romantic.
He cursed...
It's Ji Suk Jin.
One of the most disappointing
gifts I received was...
a bamboo wife!
(A long bamboo bolster)
A bamboo wife!
[After the 'old palace, '
no one else wrote it.]
If you want to use a bamboo wife,
make sure to wear your pj's.
- Did you get marks?
- It's not smooth.
- Don't they leave marks?
- Yes.
Next is Ji Hyo.
A gift that I don't
want to receive is...
a song.
- A song?
- A love song?
- Are you talking to Gary?
- A song recorded on a cassette tape!
- That counts, too.
- Yes.
Oh, when a guy sings
while looking at your eyes?
What should I do?
I fell in love with her.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I love you.
Please let me love you.
[She can't stand it.]
Ji Hyo is so pretty.
[Putting her name in
the song is the worst.]
Ji Hyo is my woman.
- Hyo...
- Stop it!
It's unctuous!
Stop it!
How about you?
Do you sing to each other?
I haven't, but Jun Ho did.
I sang many times.
I played piano and sang for her.
- What did you sing?
- Ji Hyo hates it.
At home, she was upset because of me.
So, I casually started to sing...
I'm the only man to you.
Excuse me, you do that at home?
- You do it at home?
- How does your wife react?
I think she might start singing too.
I actually like this kind of stuff.
He says romantic stuff.
- What does he say?
- You know, when I'm upset...
[What could it be?]
When she's sullen, I say,
'Please look at me.'
'I know you have a
beautiful profile, but still...'
- That's not too bad.
- But he's not shallow.
He's very romantic.
He actually uses the lines from a drama.
- They're a match made in heaven.
- That's right.
It's almost done.
Let's just play until
we have the third place.
One of the gifts that I don't want is...
- flower!
- I knew it.
- I made it!
- You did?
- Song Ji Hyo!
- They've got the second place.
[Ji Hyo and Gary placed the second.]
You still have a chance for third place.
Third place.
Honey, are you okay?
You need to meet a good partner.
By the way, I thought
women like flowers.
Women don't like flowers,
don't give them something like that.
They like it if you give her
a big bunch of Baby's breath
when they're with all their girlfriends.
Why don't you do it?
Just do it!
You always hold dumbbells, not flowers.
Next is Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, just call one
more item for me.
[What will be Kwang Soo's word?]
A purple sock!
Socks!
Okay!
- Who has it?
- Me!
I have it, too.
[She completes two lines.]
Socks!
I made it!
Ha Ha and Byul made it to third place!
Thank you, Kwang Soo!
[The rest of the couples
gets the water bomb again.]
It's so cold!
Thank you, Kwang Soo!
Thank you for your work!
[The second mission is over.]
The couple who placed first,
please come forward.
- Jong Kook!
- Yes.
- The first place.
- Let's pick this one.
Another one.
Three.
[They have eliminated 15 rings so far.]
Pick the numbers, Gary.
[They get to eliminate seven numbers.]
[They are being careful.]
[They have 25 rings left.]
Third place can
eliminate five numbers.
- So Hyun, did you win?
- We placed third once.
[17 rings left,
chasing after the first team.]
[Their crazy mode didn't stop here.]
Your third mission is
'The couples name tag war.'
Find the key of love and
unlock your handcuffs.
As soon as you unlock them
you can eliminate other
couples' name tags.
Unless you unlock the handcuffs,
you can't attack.
You will have to run away from others.
These handcuffs are such obstacles.
[Even after Ha Ha was eliminated]
[She was hiding and ousted Kwang Soo!]
How do you feel being
betrayed, Kwang Soo?
[Thanks to Ha Ha's competitive wife,
they placed second.]
[A total of 22 rings were eliminated!]
[Ha Ha was in a crazy mode
from the beginning.]
[He won the pre-game.]
[Then his wife Byul
kept winning the first game.]
This is a chance!
[They eliminated ten rings!]
[During the second mission...]
[they worked in perfect harmony]
[and made it to third place again.]
[They eliminated five more rings.]
[And won second place at the last game.]
Ha Ha and Byul, please come forward.
In the beginning, I announced that only
the first winner can enter the finals.
Ha Ha and Byul qualified
for the final mission.
The last team
[32-story condo in Sungnam]
Go Eun, you will be doing it first.
Did you think you would win today?
What is it?
- Oh my god.
- They covered my eyes again.
- What is it?
- What are you doing?
Why do they have to do this?
[32 numbers and 32 story building.
What kind of a mission will it be?]
[Five people on the 15th floor.]
What is it?
[Five people on the 16th floor.]
[Cameras are installed
from the 1st to 32nd floor.]
- What are those?
- What's going on?
[What are the cameras for?]
The final mission is...
'The Telepathy Elevator.'
Like I said, only the first winner
can challenge the final mission.
Ha Ha and Byul can challenge
the final mission.
The couple has to pick a number
out of all the numbers they have.
- One number.
- Just one?
Each of you
will take a different elevator and
go to the floor of your choice.
You will win if you can
communicate telepathically
and meet each other on the same floor.
That's why it's better
to have less numbers.
- Do they have only one chance to try?
- Yes.
- How is it possible?
- I have a few numbers on my mind.
Anyway, you have ten numbers now.
This is a lot easier
for the real couples.
That's right.
- It's not that easy.
- They can pick a special number.
I thought I had to memorize
all the numbers.
We all thought so at first.
Just in case, we kept
more than five special numbers.
More than five?
Her birthday, my birthday...
our anniversary
and my son's birthday.
Ha Ha will pick a number
and go to that floor.
You will go to the lobby and choose.
Then go to that floor.
Good luck!
- You never know.
- Good luck!
Ha Ha left a few special numbers,
I hope he picks the right one.
It's easier that they
have an anniversary date.
Yes, it is.
I think it's possible.
[Will they be able to
read each other's mind?]
Good luck!
- Isn't that the song?
- I think so, too.
- I hope it's what I'm thinking.
- December?
- That should be the date.
- It's the date.
I think they will play
'Mai piu cosi lontano.'
They can do it.
Because they're married...
[Out of ten numbers...]
[But there's only one answer
for the two hearts!]
[Nervous, anxious, and burdensome.]
This drives me nuts.
[They came to pick a number.]
[The same location,
but different times.]
But the possibility went up.
Let's see.
Number 20.
This is my birthday.
August 20th.
Ha Ha's birthday is August 20th.
Number 22.
Byul was born in October 22nd in 1983.
My birthday is October 22nd.
And...
30 is our wedding anniversary.
The last number is
our wedding anniversary, 30th.
You know the story
about the couple
who crossed dramatically.
On Christmas day,
the wife cuts and sells her hair....
and buys a wristband for her husband.
Her husband sells his watch
to buy his wife a comb.
It's a beautiful story,
but we might do the same.
If we go to the floors for
each other's birthday...
If I pick my husband's birthday
and he picks my birthday...
then we will fail.
After what we've done
today to win this race...
[The couple's last crisis...]
I've decided.
Go Eun, I'm trying to communicate
with you telepathically.
I hope you heard me.
Honey...
I need to speak through telepathy.
[Can you hear my mind?]
[I think he might have
picked this number.]
I think they will succeed.
I think so and I hope so.
What number did you eliminate?
I only got rid of five numbers.
- We took out random numbers.
- Me too.
We just got rid of one to five.
Because we didn't think about it.
- So I think we would win if I picked 6.
- I thought about it, too.
No, Suk Jin might pick 'lucky seven!'
[No way...]
Seven?
[He is very predictable.]
But you stopped at five,
so Kwang Soo would pick six.
I'd pick 31.
- Is it a special day?
- No, it's a random number.
I think it's a special day.
What day is it?
What number would you pick?
- I... would pick 31.
- Why?
So Hyun told me by telepathy.
- For real.
- That she picked 31?
[Ha Ha is on the way to the elevator.]
This is crazy.
He's on the elevator.
He's going.
I really hope they will meet.
I'm nervous.
This is the moment...
This is the day.
- Wow, this is...
- Very nervous.
[This moment...]
[Go Eun, see you up there!]
I hope Ha Ha meets Byul, really.
I have only one chance, right?
[They have only one chance.]
Ha Ha picks the floor now?
[They have to pick the same number.]
My heart is pounding.
It's very romantic.
[Ha Ha gets off the elevator.]
He's right there!
He got off!
[Kkuk put his hands together.]
How would he feel?
I'm so nervous.
What should I do?
[After Ha Ha goes up,
Byul takes the elevator.]
[Sigh.]
I can't watch.
[Blank Ji and So Hyun's
hearts are fluttering.]
- What would Ha Ha be thinking?
- She went up!
She's coming, she's coming!
The second floor...
She's coming, coming, coming!
What should I do?
This is a bit touching...
It is touching.
It's moving.
- If it takes a while.
- She's still going up.
- She's going up pretty high.
- I think they will meet.
[I hope my heart was conveyed to you.]
[Do you remember the day of
our marriage registration?]
[I proposed to you at the city hall.]
Marry me.
Please be my last love.
[They started their second
life as a couple.]
[And they had to face
the telepathy elevator.]
- His birthday.
- Her birthday.
The 30th is our wedding anniversary.
[There might be bumps]
[and the path might be rough.]
[In the end, if we are together...]
[that is...]
[the love.]
Honey!
[Ha Ha and Byul read
each other's minds.]
[Congratulations!]
[It's very touching!]
- I have goose bumps!
- Me too!
They met!
[Heartwarming.]
It feels really nice.
We lost the race,
but it's a nice ending.
- It feels weird.
- It is weird!
- Kiss her.
- Kiss her!
[Hug.]
[They picked their wedding anniversary.]
[The miracle of love.]
- My leg were giving out.
- I thought you might go to 22nd floor.
- I...
- We did it!
[Ha Ha and Byul win the final mission.]
November 30.
It's our wedding anniversary.
I picked our wedding anniversary.
[Ha Ha and Byul's love and war
has a happy ending.]
- I knew that you would pick 2 or 32.
- Jae Suk said you would pick 7.
[I envy them.]
- Was it your wedding anniversary?
- I almost changed my mind.
- It was confusing.
- We were worried, too.
This is the prize for the race,
and it happens to be star-shaped.
I should have won this ring.
[Gary doesn't give up.]
- That's wonderful.
- It feels so nice!
Gary said fake couples have limits.
We were done a long time ago.
I could see the ending early.
- Why did you pick 31?
- She doesn't answer.
- What day is it?
- Our first kiss.
[Oh, at the church?]
They remember the date?
That's amazing!
[Live happily with Ju An.]
Congratulations!
[Hope you can always
communicate telepathically!]
Subtitles by DramaFever