[A dangerous invitation
to the Running Man cast!]
[Shall we start the game?]
[The Running Man members
are locked up in a giant maze.]
[The mysterious hunters
strangle the Running Man!]
[The maze with a great
secret opens now!]
["S" restaurant, Goyang, Gyeonggi-do]
This marinated crab is really good!
Marinated crab and
dried yellow corvina....
[What a nice feast!]
This dried yellow corvina
is so delicious!
I love this marinated crab!
Is the marinated crab good?
Yes, it's not very salty.
The bell-flower root is amazing.
This must be fresh bell-flower root.
- This is a feast...
- That's what I'm saying.
Why are they filming us eating?
Is there something?
[What's this strange feeling...]
Are we in the middle of something?
Is this a mission?
[Look of suspicion]
Why are they staring
at us so pitifully?
What are we doing today?
We finished our meal.
[Their anxiety grows...]
[Someone gets out of the car,
with their face hidden.]
[The mysterious mask.]
[He's holding an
invitation in his hands.]
You know when you sell your cows...
you feed them a lot right before
they go to the slaughter house.
You've never raised cows, have you?
I just heard that from someone else...
[Where did you hear that?]
That surprised me!
That's scared me!
[A mysterious man walks
in and bows politely.]
[He hands over the
invitation without a word...]
[Confused]
[What is that?]
Read it!
You are invited!
Did you have a good meal?
We've prepared a
small party for you.
[A party just for
Running Man members...]
Please ride the limousine
waiting outside.
I hope to see you, soon.
What is it?
Is there something
inside the limo?
- They said it's a party.
- It's party time!
[That's how the party began.]
[An unfamiliar space...]
[and a mysterious invitation...]
I was scared, but it's nothing.
[Ha Dong Hun is entering
the banquet hall.]
[Flinch]
[The floor isn't going
to give out, right?]
[There's a chill in the air.]
Wait a minute.
This sofa is not going
to shoot out, right?
[Anxious]
[Who invited Running Man here?]
Hello!
[You're the host?]
Welcome to the mission town!
This mission town is full of
activities that will keep
my guests entertained.
[Excited]
First of all, can you answer
this simple question?
Yes.
Who do you like more?
Michael Jordan?
Or Bob Marley?
[Ha Ha is in a sticky situation.]
That's too difficult!
This isn't fair.
It's like asking me to choose
between my mom and dad.
Which nickname do you like more?
Big-nose or Race Starter?
[It's a source of trouble.]
Which song do you like more?
"Ballerino"
or "Get Some Air"?
[Oh, my god.]
Wait a minute.
Would you do 30 sit-ups
or 30 push-ups?
That's really...
Would you avenge or betray
your fellow members?
What's this?
Jae Suk!
Which do you like better?
To chit-chat or to dance?
I love to do both of them.
I like to do both of them
but I just ate, so it's not
good to hop around.
I'd like to chit-chat now
because I just ate.
Which do you like better?
Sleeping in or taking a nap?
I love to do both...
I'd love to sleep in
and then take a nap.
[What is the meaning
of these questions?]
I guess I love the newest song now.
I like Big-nose better.
I'll do 30 push-ups.
I choose sleeping in.
I'd love to chit-chat.
I choose Bob Marley.
I see.
If that's the case
please go inside the room on the right.
I see.
Won't you show me your face?
Who could it be?
I guess you're very rich.
[Who's the man behind the mask?]
[He's walking toward the
room on the right.]
What?
Why is everything so big?
What a huge sofa!
This must be Brobdingnag!
(Enormous land in "Gulliver's Travels ")
This is somewhat scary.
[The big room]
Is this Brobdingnag?
It must be.
The sofa is enormous!
Is this coffee table?
This must be where a
Brobdingnagian lives.
Seoul, Paris, New York,
London, Shanghai?
[A mysterious world clock on the wall!]
[What secret could be
hidden at this place?]
[After the greeting session]
Who are you, by the way?
Excuse me?
It makes me curious.
I'm going in.
[Full of curiosity]
[The small room]
Why is everything so small?
What's wrong with this place?
This is fun!
I love doing things like this!
[A tiny world that's different
from our daily life]
They've made something new.
This must be Lilliput.
What am I supposed to do here?
They've prepared a lot.
I'm getting excited.
Hurry up, I'm excited, too.
[Where are we?]
Come in.
- Maybe the other room is big.
- I think so, look at the garbage can.
[Fascinated]
Garbage can!
We're cultured men.
Sit on a chair.
[The sound of youthful innocence.]
This...
[Squeak]
- That must be the big room.
- A big room and a small room.
Ji Hyo?
Ha Ha, what is this place?
[Blank Ji enters the big room.]
It's really big.
Look at the sofa.
Look at the table.
A Brobdingnagian must be living here.
- It's scary.
- Isn't it?
Guess.
What could it be?
I can't even guess.
The big room.
Who invited us here and why?
It's not possible to guess,
because there's a weird thing.
New York, Paris...
Could this be
"the Gulliver's Travels Race"?
Well...
[There's got to be something...]
Someone is playing with us.
Someone is...
- Jigsaw killer?
- Yes, Jigsaw.
[Where is Jae Suk going?]
What's this?
[Grasshopper enters the small room.]
Come in, it's the small room.
[What is this place?]
- This is tiring.
- Have a seat on the sofa.
- That's for three people.
- I just ate...
You never know,
so we were memorizing that.
- 9:00 in Seoul, 1:30 in Paris.
- This doesn't make any sense though.
Look.
The minutes have to match.
- That's right.
- But it's all different.
You don't need to memorize it.
- The large hand has to be in the middle.
- There's nothing.
It's nothing important.
Look, how could it be not important?
Then, why would it be
hanging over there?
I don't know!
[Look at him...]
This is a chat room.
Why did they put it up there?
This is not a chat room,
it's Big-nose's room.
[Lastly, where is Kwang Soo entering?]
[Giraffe enters the small room.]
- Kwang Soo!
- What is this?
Sit on the sofa.
That's a sofa?
It's the small room.
Everything is small here.
[Kwang Soo has to bend at 90 degrees.]
This is pretty comfortable.
It's too hard to move around here.
Do you like the mission town
that you're invited?
We have plenty of time,
so please enjoy.
But to leave this place,
you need to complete missions.
[The small room's mission -
Roll the red ball]
[and push all the blue balls
out of the circle.]
- 60 seconds?
- We have a time limit.
- Where are the blue balls?
- They're over there!
Quickly bring them over there!
[The big room's mission:
Roll the red ball]
[and push all the blue balls
out of the circle.]
[And their own balls inside the circle.]
It's like curling!
Let's do it!
The ball is... over there!
It's easier to do with smaller balls.
[It's unfair!]
It would be a lot easier
to do this in the small room.
What do we do?
It's easier to be in the small room.
[Apart from the ridiculous mission]
[Who would be the person
behind the mask?]
[And what he is up to?]
[Small Room]
We need to put five.
- With red balls...
- The balls are that small?
[The tiny-sized BB bullet]
Because we're in the small room.
[Squeak]
That's so noisy!
This is so stuffy.
[Their stress level goes up.]
[The first runner is Lee Kwang Soo.]
Challenge!
Suk Jin!
[You broke my concentration.]
Put the ball carefully.
[The mission starts!]
Your balls are flying in the air.
- Try it in the right direction.
- I don't think he can.
He lost his chance.
Doing it fast won't work.
- Okay!
- I'm going to put it for him.
[He keeps missing them.]
You should have done it already.
[Stress goes up!]
It's frustrating.
Just watching makes me frustrated.
Okay!
The last one!
[Just one more!]
Please!
Do it quickly!
Five more seconds!
Five, four!
Three, two, one!
[Lee Kwang Soo fails.]
Wait a minute.
What are you two doing?
Do I have to put the bullets?
You're the youngest out of three.
Then, I have to do this?
You're the youngest out of us!
If I put it over here...
- Someone else needs to collect them.
- I need to straighten things up.
Straighten what up?
Just straighten these up.
I need to rank everyone by age.
I guess people get mad
when they're in a tiny room.
[It was interesting at first,
but it's frustrating as time goes by.]
[The first runner, Jae Suk attempts.]
It's not even close!
I just pushed one ball.
Everyone is being sensitive.
Okay!
[One shot, three kills!]
Hit the left one just like bowling.
[Squeak]
What's with the sound?
Just sit on the floor!
It's too uncomfortable for me.
Okay!
- The last one!
- Do it quickly!
Put all five over there
and hit them continuously.
Just like kicking a soccer ball!
- Six, five...
- I'm not going to do it!
[Blow that for a lark!]
This is upsetting!
- So upsetting!
- Move away!
[Stress goes up!]
Look at this!
[Squeak]
- We don't have enough time.
- It's too noisy!
[At last, everyone's anger
exploded in the small room!]
Put them carefully.
Put them all together.
- Should I go first?
- Yes.
[The first runner, Gary begins.]
Wow, that's great!
But it needs to go a little further.
[They will success if Ji Hyo and
Ha Ha's balls go inside the circle.]
That was too powerful.
That's right!
[It crashes with Gary's ball.]
You need to push it harder at first.
So, the ball has to stay at the back.
This was your fault,
because the ball was too close.
You're going to start nagging?
I'll push it harder this time.
Like I said before
the ball has to stay at the back,
so the next ball can go inside.
I wanted to do that!
- Let's just leave it.
- I made it, though.
You're too damn bad...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's bet a forehead slap.
Let's do that!
Why are you bringing that up again?
It's all over.
I tend to hold grudges.
[Kwang Soo is still
struggling with BB bullets.]
Do you have rotten fingers?
[How can you say such a harsh thing?]
It's not that.
I'm so irritated, I'm going to go crazy.
You need to flip it!
Why did you shake that?
Take a break!
- Don't we have any elastic bands?
- Focus!
Concentrate!
[He's going to nag for the whole day.]
He's not talented.
[That hurts my pride.]
Don't get up!
Get down!
- Get down!
- I can't do this any longer.
[Upset]
You know how much I swore
Suk Jin in my mind?
[They've been in the room for an hour,
and have become extremely sensitive.]
You're not talented.
You're not talented at this!
He said I'm not talented.
You know what I was thinking?
I don't want to be blamed by them.
My arm is dead.
[Aw, my joint!]
Why did you do that?
What's wrong with your arm?
- I feel numb.
- Are you okay?
I'll sit up and do it.
There's nothing you can't do,
when you concentrate.
This is harder than I thought.
Let's just calm down.
Okay.
One, two, three!
[Calm down and shoot!]
I pushed it harder.
- Good, good!
- That looks good!
This is perfect!
We have no excuse,
if we fail this time.
- I'm slightly roll it.
- It's too far.
[The second runner is Blank Ji.]
- Slightly!
- Perfect, that's beautiful!
[After a while,
Blank Ji succeeded at it.]
- It's up to you, Ha Ha.
- Do it gently.
This is perfect.
It's bouncy.
[Success,
but it bounced back?]
[Please...]
This is a success.
If not, the host is too...
I didn't even push it,
but it went in the circle.
[Will it be accepted as a success?]
Honestly, it's a success.
[Congratulations,
you've succeeded at the mission.]
- Huh, what's that?
- Wait.
[Only one member can escape
the room for each mission.]
[Decide who will escape.]
[It was hard to finish the mission,
but only one can escape?]
Decide who will escape,
and pick a door to exit.
[Why are they doing this to us?]
[What's up his sleeve?]
- I'll go out first.
- No, you can't.
What are you talking about?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Or we can roll the ball
and play a game.
Let's do the Cola, Cider game.
The ball has to reach this line.
The ball staying inside the line will
win over the ball out of the line.
I'll roll the ball.
[Blank Ji rolls it!]
Good, good!
- Ji Hyo...
- That's too bad.
[Super focused]
[Gary who wanted to escape first...]
[It's not even close.]
I rolled it wrong.
I made a mistake.
Let me roll it again.
[Ha Ha rolls it confidently!]
I'm going out first!
Bye!
[The fist escapee is Ha Ha.]
[He has to choose
between the two doors.]
Go that way.
Left or right?
I chose the right before.
I'll choose the right door again!
See you soon!
He's making me upset.
There are many other games.
I see, hurry up and go.
[What is waiting for Ha Ha
outside the door on the right?]
What is this?
There are so many doors!
[The two rooms are nothing!]
[This is the real beginning!]
[Ha Ha chose the door before him.]
[What?]
[Half of the wall is blocked?]
[No way...]
[Am I supposed to go in here?]
Are you serious?
[It does look like a maze...]
[He needs to put his head down
and bend on his knees.]
How is it possible to get in here?
Are you serious or joking?
[To escape, you need to crawl.]
Oh, I'm supposed to crawl on the floor?
[Section 1 - Crawling maze]
Crawling under the net?
[Ha Ha, starting to crawl
through the maze.]
What's wrong with this?
[He can't even get up to find a route.]
Where should I go?
[Suffocated...]
[At a loss...]
[Will Ha Ha be able to escape
from the crawling maze?]
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin succeeded.]
[Only Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are left.]
Don't try to do it fast.
Just focus.
If you can't do this,
you'll become a failure.
Okay, okay.
If you can't succeed at it this time...
If you want your new movie
"Sashimi Boy" to be successful
[He's making fun of him being]
[a fish in the movie
"Collective Invention"]
It's a rockfish, not a halibut.
I think the film will
draw ten million
but Bo Young, Chun Hee
will have the honor for the success.
[Anger is the source of my strength!]
[He succeeded at pushing the ball out.]
You're dead meat.
Get ready.
[If Kkuk fails at it,
they need to start over.]
[Stubborn]
[Noisy]
[Kkuk succeeds at it!]
[Worthy of the name, Mr. Capable]
Only one member can escape
the room for each mission.
- We're not leaving this room together?
- We did this mission together.
What are you talking about?
Why do we have to follow this rule?
- Because this is a mission.
- Oh, that's right.
You can go home, if you
don't want to follow the rule.
[Embarrassed]
You don't have to be on Running Man.
[Even a chair is upset
at his weird comment.]
- Suk Jin is disqualified!
- Seriously!
[Squeak]
Let's play the hand flip
and pick one person.
I'll escape the room this time!
[Who will be the first
escapee of the small room?]
[Big-nose!]
[Envy]
See you.
Let him escape the room first.
[Big-nose doesn't even look back.]
[The air of the room becomes combative.]
I did it so well,
I should have gone first.
I'll throw rock.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I'm sorry, Gary.
- Ji Hyo...
- I'm sorry.
We played the game fairly.
Gary, I'm sorry.
I'll leave first.
[Ji Hyo chose the door
that Ha Ha didn't choose.]
[What will be behind
the door on the left?]
[A dizzy-looking giant maze!]
[Section 2 - Normal maze]
[Big-nosed brother
enters the maze, too.]
It's fun.
It's really interesting today.
Where am I supposed to go?
[The path is blocked?]
[It's not a wall, but a door?]
[This maze only has doors.]
[Section 3 - Door maze]
[Blank Ji is at the maze.]
[She walks carefully.]
[She looks everywhere,
but all the walls look the same.]
[Thud]
You scared me!
The way...
wait!
This is a maze.
[Even looking at the door
maze makes us stuffy.]
[The route changes every
time he opens a door.]
There's no way out.
This is amazing!
[Ji Hyo is still wandering in the maze.]
[It looks all the same...]
[Surprised]
[Woman's intuition]
[I'm sure there's something!]
[Scream]
What was that?
Isn't this where I started?
Where am I supposed to go?
This way...
I think it's this way.
Is this the right way?
There's no exit.
Why, why?
What?
Why?
[One by one, they are disappearing...]
[Jae Suk is entering the door maze.]
What?
Is this a maze?
[Jae Suk's location]
Gwon Yeol, where are you?
[Even the VJ is lost at the maze.]
What's this?
This is...
this is a real maze!
I think I came the wrong way.
It's a dead end!
[Total panic]
This door is blocked!
Gwon Yeol!
[The VJ is still lost.]
I'm back to where I was!
I can't get out of this maze!
What are we doing today?
[While Yoo Hyuk is roaming,
someone is approaching.]
Where are you going?
Jae Suk!
[Gary seems like he's not far.]
What, what, what is this?
Why are doing this to me?
[Everything is going as I planned...]
[Paper toss]
Start!
Just throw it.
This is sticky.
[But it's...]
- It's difficult.
- It's not easy, it's giving me tears.
I thought it's going to be easy,
but I was wrong.
Whoever gets it in first
will escape the room first.
No, I don't want it.
I think we'll be able to do it soon.
[Focus and throw]
[Goal in!]
Hurry up!
Get it in!
Throw it at the direction.
Face your hand at the
direction of the bin.
That's right!
[He's nagging again!]
[There isn't much time left,
but he keeps failing.]
[They've succeeded at it!]
[He's more surprised.]
Success!
[Tiger and Giraffe completed it.]
We need to decide who'll get out.
Like you said, I tossed it in first.
[He said he doesn't want it,
but he's changed his mind.]
[Bickering]
What are you talking about?
Once you decided to go out,
I guess that's what will happen.
But it's unfair.
You said "whoever gets it in first
will escape the room first."
And I put it in first.
Of course, I have to escape first.
According to what you said.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Will you play?
Let's try that.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Kkuk - scissors]
[Giraffe - paper]
[Clearly, it's Kkuk's victory]
[Being grumpy]
[Kwang Soo can't control his anger.]
It'll match with your sweater!
[Was he going to pour on him?]
[I hate you!]
You wanted to play rock-paper-scissors!
You said who gets in first
will leave here first.
Then you wanted to play
rock-paper-scissors, so we did.
Right?
Just get out of my face!
[He's about to explode!]
Get out!
Get out of my house!
Cameras, get out you, too!
I'll leave.
It was fun.
I could do it
because I was with you.
Should I play a game by myself?
What's that?
It's a maze!
No exit?
[He starts exploring the maze.]
When you're inside the maze,
don't go to the easy path.
If it looks like an exit,
it turns out that it's not.
The floor isn't going to sink
or something like that.
[Will Mr. Capable be able to exit?]
[At that moment, a mysterious
shade is approaching.]
What's that?
[Who are they?]
Why are you doing this?
[They eliminated Mr. Capable's
name tag in a flash!]
[They're hunters!]
[Where are the hunters
taking the members?]
[After four hours of missions,
Kim Jong Kook is ousted.]
[What will the jail look like
hidden inside the maze?]
It's Jong Kook.
[Mr. Capable was captured, too?]
[Where are we?]
What is this?
- This is a desert island.
- Is that?
Roll the two dice, and escape
when you have matching numbers.
If you get two different numbers,
you need to wait 10 minutes.
We're waiting now.
I really want to get out of here!
- I want to get out.
- I'll get out this time.
[Giraffe who was captured quickly
came to the desert island, too.]
So, this is like a jail?
Jae Suk, we've thought about it.
And we think there's a Jigsaw among us.
(From the movie "Saw.")
- Really?
- Then, it mustn't be Ji Hyo.
She keeps saying it.
[One of us made this maze?]
Suk Jin isn't Jigsaw, but Jig-goo.
(Honest and straight)
- Next up!
- If it's 10 or under...
Under 10, under 5, or under 4...
It went on the wrong side.
Kick it.
Kick it?
[You must be in a hurry.]
[Suk Jin tries next.]
I did it!
[They match.]
Wait.
This drives me crazy.
[Ha Ha attempts to escape.]
Four.
You did it.
Okay!
I could tell he was going to make it.
I couldn't escape from here once.
Ha Ha keeps escaping from here.
What will happen if
I walk out from this door?
What's that?
I'm scared.
[The hunters are watching him
at a close distance!]
[Anxious]
[Scream]
Don't go that way,
he got caught here.
[Ha Ha escapes through the other door.]
[Running fast]
I'll roll the dice!
[He moves quickly,
avoiding the hunters.]
[But where is the exit anyway?]
[Did he finally find the exit?]
Isn't this the big room?
I need to get out.
What?
I was just checking the room.
I just came to check to see
if everything was okay.
Don't do this to me.
[There's already a mission for Ha Ha.]
No!
[This must be a dream!]
[Please tell me this is not reality.]
I was here four hours ago.
Do you know how long I've
been rolling the dice?
What kind of return is this?
[Domino Toppling]
[Pop a ball by playing domino toppling
with the books in the bookshelf.]
[If you want to escape,
complete the mission!]
[Blow]
[He sets the target!]
[What he needs now is speed!]
[Why did I look for trouble?]
Three, four, five, six!
[He needs to put 10 books
and pop the balloon!]
I'm too short for this!
It'll begin when I drop this book!
[Domino toppling begins!]
[Will his effort get him a good result?]
[Balloon, please pop!]
[He fails at the mission.]
[What kind of a balloon are you?]
[Will you resist
if I do this?]
[This is extremely frustrating!]
[Carried away]
The balloon resisted!
[Nothing is working out.]
Maybe you should have
gone the other way.
- That's where the rooms are.
- That way?
[The rest of the members
escaped the island together.]
I'll carry you on my shoulders.
- That's good.
- Look and find where they are.
Can you see them?
There are doors there, there, and there.
There's an exit.
[So, there's an exit.]
Two of them are coming this way!
[Warnings, warnings!]
- Go to that way.
- Come this way!
[Should I see where they are?]
[He was discovered!]
[Evacuate!]
[Kwang Soo and Gary escape
through the crawling maze.]
They're behind us!
[The hunters are dashing
to the entrance of the maze.]
- Gary!
- Kwang Soo!
Be careful!
Wait for me, Gary!
[That was close.]
[the hunters are approaching again.]
[There they are.]
[They're about to be found!]
[Are they gone?]
[Let's run away!]
[They run toward the
crawling maze, too.]
What is it today?
[Why do we have to be chased away?]
My knees hurt!
Kwang Soo!
Gary!
What the heck!
What is this race about?
The hunters are right in front of us.
Should I go up and check?
[Where are you, hunters?]
They're on this side.
[Walking around]
- Let's go!
- Should we run?
One, two, three!
Let's go!
[Running toward the exit]
[Ha Ha is still wandering
after escaping from the big room.]
[Careful, careful]
[The hunters are attacking!]
[Oh my god!]
[They can't get out of
the clutches of the hunters.]
[Yoo Jae Suk, to the desert island!]
Wait a minute, wait!
I just came out!
I came out from the room just now!
I said I just came out!
[Ha Ha, to the desert island!]
Why are you doing this, all of a sudden?
[The hunters make Mr. Capable give in!]
Why are you doing this to me?
[Kim Jong Kook, to the desert island!]
[The hunters of the maze appear!]
Run, run!
[Running away with
every ounce of their energy]
Please!
[Scream]
[They've encountered the hunters!]
[I need to protect Ji Hyo..]
[The final resistance]
How are we supposed to escape?
[Gary and Ji Hyo,
to the desert island!]
[All the Running Man members
go back to the desert island.]
[Where is the end of this maze?]
[The members are back
at the desert island.]
What on earth is happening?
What's today's race about?
The man with the mask...
He's a psycho.
I tried to find the smallest hole.
How do we get out?
What is this all about?
Let's put one of the dice on "escape."
We'll roll the other die,
and escape when we get "escape."
[Big-nosed brother
starts rolling first.]
[Kick]
[A free-swing eagle shot!]
[Moreover, it fails.]
[Get over here!]
[Jae Suk's eagle shoot
blow their stress away.]
[Thanks to Big-nose and Jae Suk,
the desert island is fun again.]
- Did you plan all of this?
- No, I didn't.
I wanted to kick it over the wall.
I feel so bad.
[This time, Kkuk attempts to escape.]
It's really frustrating.
[He's even good
with rolling the dice.]
I'll leave after this.
[The legendary cack-handed,
Giraffe's attempt!]
Okay, escape!
- Are you escaping?
- Yes.
- Let's go together.
- I'll be leaving in a moment.
Let's go together.
It's good to go out with bait.
Where do we...
[The maze stretches out
when they step out of the island.]
[Peek]
- I don't see any hunters.
- Keep looking since you're tall.
They'll come out from the side soon.
There's no exit.
Maybe there's something at the end.
[Ha Ha is trying to escape
from the desert island.]
[It hit Yoo Hyuk's foot
and landed on "frustration."]
[Big-nosed brother's re-try.]
[Hitting consecutive home runs]
[He hits an out-of-the-park homer!]
[Dumbfounded]
You passed me the die.
You passed me.
[While they're struggling to escape]
[the maze is crawling with hunters.]
They're everywhere.
[Even Mr. Capable is holding
his breath and walk quietly.]
[The hunters are still ruling the maze.]
The exit is over there.
We need to go out.
[We can go to the next stage,
but only if we pass the hunters.]
[Kwang Soo is roaming about
the maze by himself.]
Where are you, Jong Kook?
Where are you?
[Oh no, it's the hunter!]
[Passing by]
[What?]
[No way...]
[Kwang Soo was left alone
in the small room.]
This is frustrating!
[What in the world is happening?]
It's fun.
[It's fun...]
[One week before filming Running Man]
[SBS, Mok-dong]
[Knock, knock]
Please, come in.
[The door opens slowly.]
[Kwang Soo is here!]
Hello!
[He doesn't have anything to film,
what bring him here?]
You called me all of a sudden...
Thank you and sorry.
What brings you here?
[Why did he come to see the PD?]
You know the hidden camera,
"Happy Kwang Soo Day"
personally, I'm a big
fan of the episode.
Personally, I think it was
a really funny episode.
One of the best episodes of Running Man.
[But, he's holding his grudges!]
[They dropped in
without letting him know]
[checked his underwear,
and occupied his bed room!]
[They even invited
Kwang Soo's father to trick him.]
[A blockbuster hidden camera!]
Don't let him know until he watches TV.
[And he found out that
he was tricked by live on TV!]
I will take revenge no matter what!
I will take revenge in person,
if you don't let me on Running Man.
[He swore revenge.]
I guess you have built up a lot.
You know...
I could talk about it forever.
Personally...
the most hurtful thing is
making fun of my appearance!
[Making fun of his appearance]
Talking about appearances here...
Forget it.
It's not worth to talk about.
It's just nonsense.
I'll tell you the things
that made me feel bad, in a nut shell.
First of all, Jong Kook...
he said I look older than my age.
"I think he registered his birth
when he was three years old."
Honestly, Ha Ha is worse
than Jong Kook.
What did he say?
"He looks like about
13 years older than his age."
"You look like a squid today."
"You're really ugly."
"Doesn't Kwang Soo
look really ugly today?"
[What made him angry wasn't just
about making fun of his appearance!]
Do I still have to say
that I'm one of the members?
Isn't this ridiculous
that I have to mention this?
What did Jong Kook say before?
"I mean, you should
stay somewhere dark."
"Hey, don't say hi to me!"
"Just go home, I'll call you later."
More than anything,
they were heartfelt comments!
And occasionally, when I'm
the main character of an episode
every time...
"You've always ruined this
kind of huge project."
"The worst thing here is
that you're the main character!"
"That's the worst fact!"
Countless times, I was hurt
angry, I was in trouble!
Because of all those things,
I hatched a plan to get my revenge.
Submit to your fate!
So, how can we help you?
First of all, the framework
of this project is
a maze.
[Maze]
There are many kinds of mazes.
Listen.
This is amazing!
[Running Man's stage installation site]
[The maze is getting built
in an out-sized hall.]
- Hello.
- He's the set designer.
[Han Jung Hun]
[Running Man's stage designer]
This is enormous!
Thank you for the hard work!
Here's the door maze.
There are many kinds of mazes.
I hope there's a door maze.
When you open a door,
there's another door.
And opening it will
lead to another door.
You can't see the path at all.
Some of them are not opening.
This is frustrating!
I feel stuffy already.
[He came to check the maze,
but he's lost.]
[Even the designer is lost.]
- You don't know the path, do you?
- I know.
You just tried to open the door
that won't open.
[Satisfied]
[They're still building
the "upside down room."]
[Admiration]
Thank you so much!
This is wonderful!
Many of our members
don't like to be in a small space.
The small room
It'll be suffocating
just by looking at it.
The big room
and a low maze.
I want them to have to hang their heads
down to crawl it through.
I hope to have that.
But, there should be a door for me.
So, you want us to make a door
that you can get out?
A secret path that only I can use.
Also, I'd like to have
a monitor room with cameras.
That's all I want.
Like I said before, there's
one problem to be solved.
There should be a way
for the members to win the race.
If you get caught, or...
there should be a way
for them to win the race.
So, it makes a fair
game for the members.
This has to be a confrontation anyway.
I'll follow the rules
that you think it's fair.
I see, then we'll review it later.
Let me suggest one thing.
The winning condition is
to bring the six members
except you to the last room.
That's your winning condition.
I see.
If they don't go to the room
or if the indicator such as an armband
or an ankle band is revealed.
Then, I'll admit it as I'm defeated.
We're not responsible for that.
Don't worry it.
I'm very confident.
[Don't worry about me!
I'll win!]
It shouldn't look like me.
You will film only the
upper part, right?
[For a perfect revenge,
he's acting as a masked-man.]
- You'll change my voice, too.
- Yes.
Like the movie, "Saw."
Yes, I like that.
Do I look like me?
I shouldn't look like me.
People say it still look like me,
when I'm wearing a fish mask.
It is obvious?
[Finally, it's d-day!]
[They're waiting to enter the hall.]
It's strange, see?
Are you a spy?
It's just beginning.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Why is Kwang Soo last one to enter?
Why did you put me at the end?
Of course, they think it's strange
because we never do that.
[At the crucial moment]
[he chose "revenge."]
[Grin]
[When he chose revenge,
an armband is given to him.]
[He's wearing it on his arm.]
[In the small room]
Are you the one?
Are you Jigsaw?
Are you Jigsaw from the movie "Saw"?
What are you talking about?
I don't really know...
His acting was pretty natural this time.
[The room escape missions were going on]
[and the members were getting stressed.]
We did it!
[Bickering]
[The stress goes up!]
You guys are sensitive!
[Good, this is exactly what I planned!]
[He made them suffer]
[and sent them to
the maze one by one...]
[The designer is left alone.]
What's this nonsense?
[He starting to overact.]
So frustrating!
[Then, he moves
to the corner of the room.]
[And escapes through the secret path.]
[He opens the secret door,
and it's the outside of the maze.]
This is fun.
They're working so hard.
In such a small room,
they must have felt stuffy.
It's a lot of trouble.
[While the rest of the members
are struggling in the maze]
[Kwang Soo is very relaxed.]
[Quick steps]
[The place he walked
at a quick pace is...]
[the monitor room.]
[And the password is]
Asia Prince!
[Inside, there's high-tech equipment
that he can see the whole maze!]
[A comfortable chair
and some refreshments]
What is that we're doing today?
[He's watching the members while
enjoying the refreshment.]
This drives me crazy!
I think the crawling maze is the worst.
Good riddance!
Now, I can sleep at night.
[Kwang Soo is expressing his spite.]
Such a hard work!
They've been wandering
in the maze for hours.
And they still couldn't
finish the mission.
Why does no one think it's strange?
Are they all stupid?
Why did you go there?
It's on your left, you fool!
[While he enjoys the joy of
designing the maze to the fullest...]
There's no exit!
[The members are flat on their back
while the hunters attack.]
[The members were
captured by the hunters.]
[and went to the deserted
island one by one.]
Do they even know what they're doing?
Try rolling the dice
as much as you want.
There's nothing you can do.
I think I'll have a good
night's sleep for years.
I'm too immersed in.
[He's low on sugar.]
[He starts eating snacks immediately.]
Why am I sweating so much?
[What a dreamy moment!]
[The rest of the members are
gathered on the island one by one.]
I'm going to go check
at the desert island.
[He casually drinks his drinks.]
[Scream]
[He's acting like he was
just attacked by the hunters.]
I need someone to drag me there.
[He wants to look like he was
captured by a hunter.]
[He runs the shortest distance]
[through the giant maze
everyone wandered about.]
[Crossing the small room
that's getting ready for filming]
[he arrives at the
desert island in a burst.]
Where are the hunters?
They're over there!
This is designed for my height,
so I can see them from here.
Come over here.
Be gentle!
Ahhh!
What's this?
[He puts his heart and soul
to act like he's ousted.]
What's going on?
[As he's getting near
the desert island]
Dong Hun!
[he's restraining
his facial expressions.]
Did they rip your name tag?
[And going back to the
maze he designed.]
[Welcome to Kwang Soo's maze!]
Don't you think the
designer is among us?
I know who it is.
[He knows who the designer is?]
[Ha Ha, it's you!]
I'm tired of this!
[It wasn't me.]
[His legs gave way
with nervous tension.]
It's not me!
I don't know who he is,
but he's stupid.
He must be a psycho.
[He's putting it bluntly out of stress.]
[Wait and see,
you'll see what real stress is!]
[Rule - Roll the dice and escape,
when you get "escape."
Okay, escape!
Escape!
The probability is only one sixth.
[Escape]
[They escape the deserted
island one by one.]
- Ji Hyo, hurry and escape.
- See you, Jae Suk.
[Entering the maze again]
What's this?
Gwon Yeol, this maze is so frustrating.
[The maze is still full of hunters.]
Think about it, there's
got to be something.
Like a clue or something.
Just wandering in the maze
won't solve anything.
Jong Kook.
[Can you release me?]
Maybe we need to eliminate
someone's name tag.
Hunter's name tag?
- Should we try?
- Let's try that.
Let's do that and see what happens.
- Then what?
- There could be a hint.
Jae Suk is coming.
- Hunter's name tag...
- There are so many hunters still.
We should try and fight against hunters.
- They have name tags.
- There might be clues.
Let's pick one person.
You'll lose if you don't throw,
rock-paper-scissors!
Rick-paper-scissors!
[Everyone else throws scissors,
Kwang Soo throws paper.]
Okay, it's you, Kwang Soo.
[His bad luck is something
we need to memorialize.]
[Kwang Soo is obliged to
eliminate the hunters' name tag.]
It's better for you to hold,
so Jong Kook can rip it.
[Peek]
[It's the hunter!]
[What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
You need to rip his name tag!]
[While Kwang Soo is hesitating]
[Running Man and
the hunters' all-out war!]
Kwang Soo, rip his name tag!
I'm holding him.
Rip his name tag!
[Kwang Soo keeps touching his name tag.]
It seems there's something!
It's suspicious.
Take it off, Gary!
They're resisting!
[And finally, Ace Blank Ji
comes forward.]
[She rips his name tag.]
There is!
There really is a hint!
[What is that?]
Like I said before,
there's one problem to be solved.
There should be a way
for the members to win the race.
If you get caught, or...
[So it's a fair game.]
This has to be a confrontation.
I'll follow the rules,
that you think it's fair.
[So the production crew
set a very fair rule.]
[Mok]
["Lee," "Kwang," "Soo," "Pal,"
and "Mok"] (Palmok means wrist)
[The game is over as
soon as he gets caught.]
[Do they think this is fair?]
[They are excited
to find a new hint.]
Let's go attack them.
This is no time for us to remain idle.
Let's go fight them back!
[What should I do?]
- Hunters can be eliminated!
- Hunters are running away!
[The hunters are avoiding
the Running Man for now.]
They went under the net.
The net is shaking.
- It's the big room.
- No, it's not.
Don't go in!
It's the big room!
[He's entered already.]
Good job!
What is this?
[Jae Suk enters the big room.]
[Welcome to the big room.]
This room also has the same thing.
[There are the same clocks?]
[Ha Ha was wondering around
and locked up in the small room.]
[You were here, Ha Ha.]
I need to finish this mission.
- Why did you go in?
- My name tag was eliminated.
Really?
[Kwang Soo forcibly entered the room.]
[And Big-nose joins them!]
Seriously!
Three of us again?
[It's Easy Brothers!]
What is it?
Is there something else?
We ripped a hunter's name tag,
and there was a hint.
- The hint says "mok."
- What does it mean?
- This "mok"?
- Yes, that "mok."
It could be "mok yoil."
(Thursday)
[The hint is not very clear.]
[What a relief!]
Seoul, Paris, New York,
London, and Shanghai...
- Seo-pa-new-lon-shang...
- Isn't that suspicious?
[His eye shift fast
as soon as they start guessing.]
What time is it now?
- It's...
- That's 9:30...
[The clocks look more
and more suspicious.]
I'll accept if you make a condition
for me to be defeated.
[The second, very fair rule
that production crews prepared.]
[Each room in the maze has a hint that
indicates the designer of the maze.]
[K, S]
[Kwang Soo]
[Light Room]
[Light Kwang]
[Soo]
Really, there's something
about the clock?
Were there the clocks
in the small room?
Yes, and they're the same.
They're suspicious.
[Thinking]
[Will the clue be upside down]
[There must be something...
What is it?]
The time difference between
Seoul and Shanghai is one hour.
[With wrong time difference]
But the minutes don't match.
Look at the eight o'clock.
Doesn't it look like seven o'clock?
The clock for Shanghai.
It's eight o'clock.
The large hand doesn't...
Huh, is that seven?
That's weird, too.
Maybe this is not about time.
- Maybe it's a direction.
- The way we can escape the maze?
Jong Kook, I don't think that's it.
I think the hint "mok" was for
an animal with a long neck. (mok)
If you look at the clocks.
Only Seoul and Shanghai
could be read as K and S.
They're in Asia.
Kwang Soo?
Maybe I'm too stuck with this idea
that it could be Kwang Soo but...
[Mr. Random Capable's keen reasoning]
This game cannot be designed
without a spy.
Clearly, this is to trick us.
I think that's K and S.
Kwang Soo, can we rip his name tag?
Seriously, could it be his revenge
for the hidden camera?
But he's been ripped a lot of times.
Balmok, sonmok... (ankle, wrist)
I've also thought about
an armband and an ankle band.
Don't we need to be in one spot?
Jae Suk, let's do the mission
and get out of the room.
[Mission - organize the giant book
in alphabetical order.]
[The four people are working together.]
[And they completed
the mission in no time.]
- We did it.
- Is that a success?
One person will go out and wait.
It has to be at least three,
so we can attack.
Why don't you go out first?
Okay, I'll be waiting outside,
so hurry up and come out.
We need three people at least.
[They're doing the mission
in the small room, too.]
Hook it on the dress!
That's right!
Lift it!
- Bravo!
- Only one can leave.
54 seconds.
[Let me get out first!]
I'm already out!
I knew that's going to happen.
[This is not the right time
to be locked up.]
[On the other side]
[Finally, Jae Suk
escapes from the big room.]
- No one from the small room escaped?
- I called out, but no one answered.
Let's think, Jae Suk.
- Let's think carefully.
- This is crazy.
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook
start solving the mystery.]
Seoul...
I looked at the letters, too.
[At that moment,
the hunters are out in force.]
[They're ready for combat!]
[Crowded]
So many of you came.
You're too many!
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook
stick to the corner.]
Good.
Move to the side.
Come to the corner!
[Action!]
[The hunters are struggling against
Mr. Capable and Yoo-ruce Willis.]
[At that moment!]
[A hunter suddenly
attacks from up on the wall.]
[But!]
[Jump!]
[Rip]
It's "soo."
[Mr. Capable rips the
hunter's name tag off.]
This time, it's "soo."
I think we need to rip all of them.
From Monday to Sunday!
[You said it's "soo"?]
Then it's Kwang Soo!
Mok (Thursday), and soo (Wednesday)...
- Seriously, it's Kwang Soo.
- Do you think so?
Wol, hwa, soo, mok, geum, to, il.
(Days of the week)
That's a fake.
Think, the clock of
the cities in Asia...
[Wait, that's right!]
[K and S in the cities in Asia.]
[And all the titles of the giant books
contain "prince."]
[The Frog Prince],
[The Little Prince], [The Happy Prince]
[The Swan Prince],
[The Prince and the Pauper]
[Asia, and prince...]
Asia Prince!
[Asia Prince]
[The Asia Prince
among Running Man members is]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Gary solves the mystery perfectly.]
With a long "mok" (neck)
"soo" is from his name Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo with a long neck?
[Kwang Soo with a long neck?]
[That Kwang Soo with a long neck
is listening behind the door.]
[Mental breakdown]
[In a hurry]
[The arm band for the "designer"]
[he's wearing it tightly
in case someone checks.]
[Then he goes straight to the
monitor room through the secret path.]
What happened?
[Emergency!]
Are there any more hunters?
Is that it?
[All the hunters are called out.]
Over there.
Where can we reach the last room?
The winning condition is
to bring the six members
except you to the last room.
If they don't go to the room
or if the indicator such as an armband
or an ankle band is revealed.
Then I'll take it
as I am defeated.
[There's no time!]
[Before my identity is revealed, I need
to put the members in the last room.]
- Kwang Soo!
Did you escape?
- Let's stick together.
- Is Kwang Soo out?
[He joins the members hastily.]
Come over here, Kwang Soo.
Bring Kwang Soo over here.
What were you doing, Kwang Soo?
How did you escape the room?
[He's suspicious.]
[They're surrounding Kwang Soo
from the both sides.]
Search Kwang Soo's neck.
I have no idea.
[That's the spot]
[that he tied the armband.]
[If he's caught, the game is over.]
[He isn't wearing anything?]
Check his wrist and ankle.
[But they're still doubting.]
[I need to bring them to the last room.]
I think that's the last room.
What's that?
What does "fin" mean?
[That's the last room for the mission.]
Don't we need to go to the room?
There's no way.
[The members are walking
toward the last room.]
There's a way, but...
The winning condition is
to bring the six members
except you to the last room.
[Walk along with them and
put them in the last room first.]
[At this rate, I can win...]
- This side is open.
- But, that's not connected.
- We need to go through here.
- There's a way!
- Is that connected?
- It is!
[Ha Ha found the exit.]
It's open!
[Finally, they arrive at the last room.]
Let's get in!
[Kwang Soo will win if he lets
them enter the room first.]
- What's this?
- There are seven seats.
Isn't that a prison?
[They're entering doubtlessly.]
Are you sure there are seven seats?
[Everyone, please enter the room.]
Let's get inside.
- Are we supposed to get in?
- I don't know.
- What are you doing?
- I don't want to get in.
Kwang Soo, why are you resisting?
- Kwang Soo opened his mouth.
- Kwang Soo did?
- Something happened to Kwang Soo?
- No, he was resisting.
I want to go check that room.
I went inside.
Three of you were outside, right?
[Kwang Soo is acting suspicious.]
[Let's put him inside!]
[Kwang Soo is resisting death.]
[No, I almost won the race!]
[Kwang Soo becomes
super strong all of a sudden.]
What's going on?
[I can't end it like this!]
I will take revenge no matter what!
I will take revenge in person,
if you don't let me on Running Man.
It's a maze.
It's a maze, right at this place.
I will have my revenge today.
Everything is all set!
Be strong, everyone!
One, two, three, fight!
That's very good!
[From designing the maze
to educating the hunters]
[Everything went as I planned]
[and I could have won the race...]
This is really close to
what I wanted to achieve.
Good riddance!
[Why am I doing this here?]
I'll go inside the room!
Why is he resisting?
[It's a weird situation
for the people who]
[don't know Kwang Soo's
winning condition.]
[They don't know the rules]
[but they join forces
and move Kwang Soo together.]
Yes, he's inside.
Why did you resist?
[Kwang Soo loses.]
There was something!
I had a feeling.
What is it?
He's so strong!
There's no other reason that
he would resist this much.
The clocks for the Asia, K and S.
[Kwang Soo's revenge fails.]
Asia Prince.
- What was written on the clock?
- K and S.
[Everyone is completely exhausted
from the maze.]
I kept saying it's Kwang Soo,
ever since I saw the letter "mok."
- What about "soo"?
- Kwang "Soo."
Oh, Kwang "Soo."
I thought it's really suspicious,
so I told him to get inside.
Then, he resisted so hard.
[Even at the last moment,
Kwang Soo was caught by Gary.]
See, he has it.
[The armband for the "designer."]
The designer?
So the "mok" means...
"son-mok" and "bal-mok"
(wrist and ankle)
Where did you hide this?
I checked his arms, too.
- But I couldn't feel it.
- I was wearing it really tight.
Since I was so close to winning the race,
I couldn't control my face.
I saw his mouth opened.
So we lose, if we all came in?
All inside the room but me.
[If it wasn't for Gary,
Kwang Soo could have won easily.]
This is frustrating!
He was resisting
and changed his attitude.
[We won!]
My goal was to make everyone stressed.
That was my only goal.
We were really stressed.
- It was really stressful.
- Then, that's enough.
- So, what happens now?
- Kwang Soo's plan failed.
- You can decide a punishment for him.
- You never told me that before.
- Getting a forehead slap from Jae Suk.
- We didn't talk about it.
- Forehead slap.
- How about this?
He will go through the crawling maze,
and he gets a slap when he gets up.
This is better. That forehead
slap will replace the clapper.
The last clapper?
Why slap my forehead
for the clap sound?
Say "we'll clap the slate!"
right before the slap.
You don't have to go that way.
- Come this way.
- Oh, we can?
You know the way.
Where's your room?
[They're walking on
Kwang Soo's personal path.]
You were resisting too hard.
I didn't think Gary could have
known what's going on.
I just thought he's not here.
Gary noticed really early.
- Since when did you doubt me?
- From the beginning.
This is my monitor room.
Why do you knock?
It's your room.
- I need to say the password.
- Password, please.
Asia...
Asia Prince.
This is not what I set.
I'm not lying.
They told me the password.
That's too much!
- I didn't set the password.
- So, this is it?
He was eating snacks.
[This is it!]
He ate some pastries.
Just by looking at the maze,
I feel stuffy.
[But why is everyone here?]
I thought I solved the maze.
[This is giving me stress.]
[They arrive at the crawling maze.]
This is so frustrating!
This is frustrating!
I was going crazy when
I was at a dead end.
[Everybody's talking
about how bad it is.]
This one's really terrible.
- It's a dead end.
- Dead end.
Do you know how stressful it is
when you arrive to a dead end?
This is the low maze.
You can't go through
without putting your face down.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Please, give me another chance!
- Left turn!
- That's enough!
Say sorry to us!
Turn right!
How did you do this?
It was really tiring!
[Saying the same thing
at the same time]
When I was doing this...
It was actually really stressful.
- We'll clap the slate board.
- Sit here.
Come over here.
- Kwang Soo.
- Count to three yourself.
[Act like a man...]
- I can't do it!
- Just say it!
From right to left.
We'll clap the slate!
One, t...
[Kapow!]
[Off-beat swing]
[The first forehead slap slate
on variety shows!]
[From designing the maze
to failing the mission]
[thank you for making us laugh,
Kwang Soo!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ssireum (Korean folk wrestling),
Kim Ki Tae]
[Judo, Lee Won Hee]
[Action, Jung Doo Hong]
[Taekwondo, Tae Mi]
[Pro wrestling, No Ji Sim]
[The strongest opponents
in Running Man history!]
[Be prepared for the big battle!]
[Complete 100 Running Man!]
[Broadcasters from
every field are here.]
[Charge up the sensibility
before the combat.]
[And some slightly tough warm-ups]
[100 Running Man Festival]
[An unavoidable battle]
[The biggest show-down
in Running Man history]
[Next week, Running Man]
[100 vs. 100]