Subtitles by DramaFever
[2016 Luck battle]
Ji Suk Jin, you're born as stone
out of the five elements.
- Stone.
- That suits him!
You are loyal
and have a strong sense of pride.
- You're a devoted husband.
- What?
[Are you serious?]
In 2016, Ji Suk Jin should...
- You want to do a lot, right?
- Yes, so much.
You shouldn't do anything in 2016.
[Oh no.]
Gary, you shouldn't
do anything in 2016 either.
[Jae Suk's second child.]
[Kim Jong Kook's marriage.]
[2016 Luck battle]
[2015 Running Man and
X-man collaboration.]
[The comeback of the legends:
Andy, Jong Soo]
[Chae Yeon, Stephanie,
Ji Hyeon, Jung Nam.]
[And the hottest Seol Hyun, Bobby,
B.I, Jimin's challenge.]
[Their will for victory grows.]
- You're dating Song Ji Hyo, right?
- Of course!
You're a squid, right?
[Take notice of these people.]
[X-man suspect number one:
Kim Jong Kook.]
[Mr. Capable's always the best.]
[He lost to Seol Hyun in Go?]
[X-man suspect number two:
Seol Hyun]
[She was eliminated with
no will to fight back.]
[Seol Hyun became the most
suspicious for X-man.]
[X-man suspect number three:
Andy.]
[He's known to be pretty strong...]
[He was out without even getting
the chance to use his strength?]
[Who is X-man of 2015?]
[And selecting a partner
for the couple game.]
[She rejected Big-nose.]
[B.I and Bobby]
[are women's ideal type!]
[They couldn't resist their charm.]
[B.I, Ji Hyo and
Bobby, Jimin are a couple.]
[And a love triangle that
sprouted with Seol Hyun's charm.]
Seol Hyun,
let's play games together.
[What is Seol Hyun's answer?]
[Starting now.]
[Kang Gary's confession.]
Seol Hyun, let's play games together.
[What's Seol Hyun's answer?]
One, two...
three!
Yes!
[How can this be?]
[Gary and Seol Hyun are a couple.]
It's okay, Kwang Soo.
- Tell her.
- You still have a chance left.
[I'm going to confess now.]
Three!
Seol Hyun!
[Seol Hyun, I'm here...]
[Earnest]
You have to do something.
Go kneel in front of her.
[Kwang Soo kneeled.]
[Will his sincerity reach her heart?]
[A man who wants to protect love.]
[And a man who's trying
to acquire it.]
[Kwang Soo vs. Gary]
[What will Seol Hyun's decision be?]
Yes.
[Twist]
[This can't be real.]
What's going on?
[Touched]
[Kwang Soo knelt down,
and I felt bad.]
This is a twist!
Their heights match perfectly.
No wonder, she threw the
red scarf at Kwang Soo.
[Gary and Suk Jin are a couple.]
Now, it's the original X-man team.
Just looking at all of you
reminds me of a long time ago.
Not a lot has changed
although time has passed.
- They're still the same.
- Yes, I agree.
We'll start with Kim Jong Kook.
Is there someone here that you would
like to become a couple with?
Please pick someone that you like.
[Who captured his heart?]
I'm sorry but I'm not going to be picky.
[If anything changed,
it's Kkuk's mind.]
I can't be picky.
Please don't ask questions like that.
[It's Kkuk's time to
show off his charm.]
It's so karaoke-like.
["Just the Way You Are" by Bruno Mars.]
[The performance of the
best male singer in 2005.]
Her eyes, her eyes make the stars
look like they're not shining.
Her hair, her hair falls
perfectly without her trying.
[His voice doesn't change...]
[People's hearts still flutter.]
When I see your face
there's not a thing
that I would change.
[It's like a dream...]
Just the way you are...
[Me, too...]
And when you smile.
The whole world stops
and stares for a while.
[Move]
[I want to listen closely.]
[It's the wrong time to be
arguing over their spots.]
[Jong Kook, Jin Sook is here...]
[Jin Sook, I'm still in
your heart right?]
[He's singing a
serenade after ten years.]
[Will they respond?]
When I see your face.
When does this song end?
- Turn it off!
- He's too much!
- Stop it!
- Why?
- Is this a concert?
- Now, everybody!
Just the way you are.
[The pride of the Triple Crowned Singer]
You sing really well.
You're good but...
- I need to do something.
- Why do you add high notes and stuff?
Your
I always do that!
It makes me so angry!
You should have done that in 2005!
If you did, there would have been
100 more episodes of X-man!
I saved it for today.
[There's so much
pressure for the rest.]
How are the rest of the
people going to sing?
Please give him a round of applause!
Next up is Andy!
[Next person to show off
their charm is Andy.]
Did you prepare something?
I thought it wouldn't be
enough by myself.
So I've brought UP10TION with me.
This is old-school, too.
[I remember the old days.]
- We're not choosing UP10TION, are we?
- No, you're not.
If you pick me, we're all a team.
[That's the best strategy
to win their hearts.]
[He's dancing to a cute carol.]
[Oh my god.]
[My kid would like this.]
[Have you seen a cute 35 year old?]
[Should we go closer?]
[They advance together
to get their attention.]
[This is fun!]
[He's trying to win their
hearts with a cute dance.]
[This song is?]
[One of the best hits "Wild Eyes."]
[I am Andy of Shinhwa!]
[He transforms into a DJ.]
[Andy's funny sketch.]
[In step with DJ Andy]
[they're doing the retro dance.]
[Here's my heart!]
[The heart dance is back.]
[It's so addicting.]
[Andy hasn't changed
even after ten years.]
[He finishes with a cool ending!]
[What do we do.]
[Andy and UP10TION's
performance is over!]
He prepared a lot!
That's amazing.
You're supposed to
prepare for these things?
Good job!
[You're awesome!]
He has changed into a suit.
- Guest fashion.
- Wedding hall!
When I was asked to be on X-man,
I asked who the female guests were.
There's someone here that stole my
heart ten years ago and even now.
[Out of these people?]
Now that I think about it
my heart has always belonged
to her ever since I met her.
- Who thinks it's them?
- It's not me, for sure!
I've never been on X-man with him.
- What about you?
- I don't think so...
- And Ji Hyeon?
- I don't think so, either...
Who is it?
Maybe they're just in my heart.
Okay then, Jong Soo.
Please pour your heart into it.
Please turn the music on!
[This song is?]
"Lovers in Paris"!
[2004 drama "Lovers in Paris" OST.]
[Who is Jong Soo's woman?]
[Manly and serious Eagle Eye!]
[He starts walking
in rhythm to the music.]
Is it me?
[Yes Jin Sook, it's you.]
[Chae Yeon has been picked!]
[His confession after ten years.]
[It's not ordinary.]
[Why me?]
[He's busy trying to sing and
bring people to the stage.]
[He puts his arm over her shoulder?]
[Are you ready for this Jin Sook?]
[Flustered, flustered]
[Change of attitude]
Get your hands off!
I told you to get your hands off her!
[This is?]
[A famous line in "Lovers of Paris."]
Get your hands off!
I told you to get your hands off her!
[He reenacted it perfectly!]
[Surprised]
You can't win!
If you didn't win for 33 years,
you won't win until you're 60!
I would break your arm!
But I'm not going to
in front of my woman!
Make sure you never run
into me again, you got it?
What are you, stupid?
You can't tell him
to take his hands off?
"He's my man."
"He's my boyfriend."
Why can't you say it!
"He's my man."
"He's my boyfriend."
Why can't you say it!
[Eagle Eye's acting is on fire.]
[Why can't you say it!]
[And then he goes back
to singing, casually.]
[An unexpected performance.]
[He sings again for now.]
[Jin Sook, it's not over yet!]
Can't you see me?
Can't you?
[Pardon?]
Is she moved?
You're in my heart.
[Summer of 2004,
Lee Dong Gun's famous line.]
[Who knew we would
hear it again in 2015?]
[This is crazy.]
[He plays a double role.]
You're in my heart.
[This is so cheesy.]
[And then he goes back to singing.]
[Was he trying to be funny?]
[Jong Soo's ten years of love.]
[Jong Soo's performance
was like a musical.]
Wow!
Jin Sook's touched!
[Calm]
Wow!
I was so absorbed!
This reminds me of "Lovers of Paris."
What's Jung Nam going to do?
What's he going to do?
We'll see Kim Jung Nam's performance!
[Lastly, it's Kim Jung Nam's turn!]
[He starts with a Turbo song.]
What is it?
It's Animation Crew!
They're the Animation Crew, right?
[Kim Jung Nam and
Animation Crew's performance.]
[What kind of performance will
the original dancing machine show?]
[They warm up a little.]
[And slowly take their positions.]
[And then the real
performance starts!]
[The original dancing machine
is in full dance mode.]
[Charismatic]
[He's in perfect sync with
the Animation Crew.]
[He's so cool!]
[Poppin']
[A surprise]
[People are screaming
here and there.]
[Kim Jung Nam had this kind of charm?]
[Give me the rose.]
[It's not over yet!]
[He goes straight
into his confession.]
[He goes to Ji Hyeon.]
[What will she say?]
[She receives the rose from Jung Nam
but sends a heart to Andy.]
[Shocked]
[Give me the rose!]
[Throws away]
[The original dancing
machine is angry.]
[When thou leavest
cloyed by my visage]
[Without a word let me myself
manage to send thee dearly.]
[Be pleased to have thy feet tenderly]
[lay, trodden on those
flowers bestrewed.]
It's a real rose.
I went to the fish market
this morning!
Wait, not fish market...
[His memory is bad.]
Why did you go to the fish market
to get a rose?
[Sorry, I have someone.]
We've seen the men's charms.
Ji Hyeon, shall we start by
showing off your charm?
Please give us music!
[The music starts and
she moves forward!]
[Where are you going?]
[She heads for Andy.]
[A shy dance of temptation.]
[Yoo Hyuk's burdensome dance.]
[2005's hottest idols
are a perfect sync.]
[I only look at Andy.]
[She only dances in front of Andy.]
[I'm here, too...]
[you know how I feel, right?]
[She only shows her charm to Andy.]
[She finishes off with
an arrow of love.]
Did you only go to Andy?
Back in the day, we were
both very active as idols
but we didn't get to interact a lot.
What happens if he rejects you?
What if he does?
You didn't even go to anyone else.
[I believe that Andy
wouldn't do that.]
What a situation.
[Bluff]
Following Ji Hyeon
next up is Stephanie!
[The Queen of charm, Stephanie!]
[Stephanie is known for her moves.]
[Her signature powerful dance.]
[Fascinating]
[It's time to open up
Stephanie's heart!]
[Oh yeah!]
[He likes it too much!]
[She passes Jong Soo
and goes to Ha Ha.]
[I'm out.]
[She passes Ji Hyeon's love Andy, too.]
[And she lures Team Leader Kim.]
[I see you.]
[Stephanie's performance is over!]
[In awe]
You're the best!
Lastly, Chae Yeon!
Please give us music!
[That's like the variety show expert.]
[She starts off by
warming the crowd up.]
[Everyone's dancing together.]
[This is fun!]
[This song is?]
["Heart attack" by AOA.]
[Are you watching, Seol Hyun?]
[The guys react right away]
[with her movements.]
[The original sexy diva.]
[Sexy and charismatic.]
[Seol Hyun joins.]
[I'll help you.]
[The two sexy divas meet.]
[Huh?]
[What is she doing?]
Did you see her face?
[She's upset,
but they're in perfect sync.]
[It's okay!
Go back now!]
[Seohyun leaves in a hurry.]
[It's "Up and down."]
[She starts luring them in.]
[Is he okay?]
[She lures Eagle Eye in rhythm
to "Bang bang bang."]
[Nobody move]
[He's on fire.]
[Her bullets of love.]
[Heart attack]
[Bravo, Chae Yeon]
[Sexy Queen, Chae Yeon!]
Lee Jong Soo's eyes...
[His eyes were on fire.]
And Seol Hyun came up to help
but her face...
[Upset]
[Thanks, Seol Hyun.]
[You're the best, Chae Yeon!]
That was impressive.
[His shoelaces are untied.]
[Your laces are untied.]
That doesn't matter right now!
This is so nice!
It's been a while!
- Thank you.
- Please, a round of applause.
That's amazing.
So, last but not least
its time to make a decision.
I don't know who
will become a couple
but let's start with Kim Jong Kook!
I've never been
in this position before.
It's been ten years.
I'll give you five seconds.
Five, four, three...
Two, one.
[Who will be Jong Kook's partner?]
Stephanie,
let's play games together.
[Jong Kook's woman, Stephanie.]
One, two... one, two.
Three!
Yes.
[Jong Kook and Stephanie
are a couple.]
Next up is Andy!
One, two...
[Ji Hyeon showed her
affection to Andy.]
- Three!
- Ji Hyeon...
Would you like to
play games together?
Yes.
[Upset]
You couldn't really see them
together back in the day.
Now, Ha Ha!
Your head must be
pretty complicated.
I wasn't expecting this.
I'll call you, confidently.
- Jin Sook!
- If it were ten years ago
I would have said no
- And called someone else?
- Yes.
But I'm going to let him go.
[Goodbye...]
Yeah, just let go.
But I'm still rejecting you.
[I'm still rejecting you.]
[That was a quick rejection.]
[I won't forget.]
[Sorry.]
Jong Soo!
One...
- Two.
- It's been ten years.
If it doesn't work out today,
maybe in another ten years.
[Wow, romantic.]
- I will call out her name.
- One, two, three!
Chae Yeon, let's play games together.
[She accepted him in a heartbeat.]
[Jong Soo and Chae Yeon are a couple.]
Congratulations!
[I know how you feel.]
[All the couples have been decided!]
Now, we will start the couple game.
It's only one round.
It's simple, you need to
decorate the Christmas tree.
You need to put the ornaments in between
your cheeks and go hang them.
The team that can get the most
ornaments in three minutes will win.
The most important thing here
is that it's the best game
to figure who the X-man is.
- I forgot there was an X-man!
- I forgot.
I'm sure you forgot about it.
It is the best game
to figure out who it is.
Since it's a collaboration with
Running Man, there's an R-man.
[Before the Go Fight]
Only me?
[Kwang Soo was heading
to somewhere alone.]
Because we're holding an
X-man special on Running Man
we will be giving you
a special mission.
You are not X-man.
However, you are R-man.
You can pretend you're X-man.
You will be helping so that
X-man's team loses.
You will protect X-man
with different tactics.
If X-man doesn't get
caught until the end
it will be X-man
and R-man's victory.
X-man will know that there's R-man
but they won't know who it is.
How can I let X-man know
that I'm R-man?
I think it's either Andy of Bobby.
You, as R-man received a message
from X-man for help.
[He got a secret command
before the couple game.]
Make an intentional
error in the game
and do something that
can arouse suspicion.
[That's my specialty.]
[But who could the X-man be?]
Ready!
Three minute time limit!
Please watch out for X-man.
And there's also R-man.
It would be obvious in this game.
Ready!
[B.I and Ji Hyo are moving with the
ornament between their cheeks.]
[Jung Nam and Ha Ha
daringly go for the mouth.]
- They're good!
- They're playing it well.
Go slowly!
[B.I and Ji Hyo succeeded.]
Okay, next!
[Jung Nam and Ha Ha are clear.]
Okay, next couple!
[Next is Suk Jin and Gary.]
[Suk Jin and Gary failed so easily?]
[Jimin and Bobby are fixing the
ornament between their cheeks.]
[Jong Kook and Stephanie are speedy!]
[It's a close game.]
Okay, next!
Hurry!
[Andy and Ji Hyeo vs.
Kwang Soo and Seol Hyun.]
Make an intentional
error in the game
and make an action that
can arouse suspicion.
[Alright, I'll show you
the skill of R-man.]
[Everyone can see that
it was so awkward.]
- What are you doing?
- No, that's not it!
He's suspicious!
Kwang Soo's a little weird.
[Well I did something
to arouse suspicion...]
Please watch for X-man.
[The game continues.]
[The score is 3:3.]
[It's Jong Soo and Chae Yeon's turn.]
[Jong Soo's mistake.]
[Very suspicious]
[He's not upset even after
making a mistake?]
[Bobby and Jimin move full speed.]
[They succeeded in a flash!]
[Jung Nam and Ha Ha are
using their lips again!]
[The current score is 4:4.]
[Jong Kook and Stephanie
are on the move.]
[Watching carefully]
Up, up, up.
You can't make it?
[Why is he putting it on the higher
string when there's a lower one?]
[He succeeded]
[but it's a little suspicious.]
If you make the same mistake,
you're X-man and R-man.
They're probably R-man and X-man.
[Seol Hyun is a little suspicious...]
Go slowly!
[Kwang Soo and Seol Hyun
reach the tree.]
[And all they have left is to hang it.]
- Why are you putting it there?
- Put it on the side!
[Seol Hyun leans her cheek
forward and they failed.]
[That's so weird.]
- They're so suspicious!
- Kwang Soo's weird!
[Is Seol Hyun really X-man?]
[The current score is 6:6.]
[Jong Soo and Chae Yeon are as
suspicious as Kwang Soo and Seol Hyun.]
[Turn]
[Why are you turning all of a sudden?]
[They failed again
with Jong Soo's turn.]
[Eagle Eye is making
so many mistakes.]
[What is this?
Is Jong Soo the X-man?]
[Both male couples are up.]
[Jung Nam, Ha Ha and Suk Jin, Gary
are doing their best.]
[And it's Kwang Soo and
Seol Hyun's turn again.]
[Everyone's keeping
an eye on them.]
If you don't hang it
this time, it's you!
Hurry up!
Don't rush!
Just hang it!
- There's one minute left!
- They're going to win!
[We need to succeed this time.]
[They both succeeded.]
[Kwang Soo and Seol Hyun's
suspicion decreased a little.]
[Jong Soo and Chae Yeon
are getting more suspicious.]
[They failed again
because of Jong Soo.]
He's weird!
He's X-man!
[Is Jong Soo X-man?]
- It worked.
- Okay!
[It's Kwang Soo and Seol Hyun's turn.]
We won, we won.
They won't hang it, look.
[The current score is 12:11.]
[While they struggle]
[it's Jong Soo and
Chae Yeon's turn again.]
[Just then]
[They failed again.]
Hurry up!
[This is our chance.]
[I don't know if Seol Hyun's the X-man]
[but we need to succeed
and dispel our suspicion.]
[They succeeded.]
[Time out]
We won!
Team Ji won with a score of 13 vs. 11!
X-man must be on that team.
There is someone
suspicious here though.
[Jong Soo is the main suspect as X-man.]
[If Jong Soo's really X-man,
that's dangerous...]
He kept blowing in my ear.
[Did Jong Soo really make a mistake]
[of is he X-man?]
The original X-man members
know how to play it!
I love them!
Now, the only thing we have
is the final vote.
Is that real?
Will you be able to
find out who X-man is?
But so many people look suspicious.
2015, X-man and Running Man
collaboration!
We'll leave for the final site now!
[In a moment]
[2016, Luck Battle]
[How will Running Man's
luck be in 2016?]
[Their fortunes aren't ordinary!]
[And the twist at the end!]
[There's a person with
the best luck in 2016?]
[Who will it be?]
Originally, we used to vote
for the person we think at the end.
This time, it's the
collaboration project.
It's the collaboration.
We'll do the last vote
in Running Man style.
It's simple.
Inside the SBS building,
16 laptops are prepared for voting.
We have 16 people today.
You can find the laptop,
and vote on it.
[Out of many computers in the building,
they have to find the right laptops!]
The laptops will have an R sticker.
And you can vote more than once.
R-man and X-man could vote, too.
When a players gets a majority vote
I'll announce the name.
You will win if you eliminate
the person, and it says X-man.
You have three chances
and you have 10 minutes to
eliminate the name tag.
[The first round begins.]
There's none on 15th floor.
You don't give us any hint?
Whose name should I write?
Seol Hyun was the most suspicious though.
- Oh, X-man!
- I'm not X-man.
You're not X-man for sure?
- I think it's you.
- I'm not!
Seol Hyun, watch out for your name tag!
I won't go easy on you!
But, I'm not X-man...
Seol Hyun looks suspicious.
When we were moving the ornament
she was able to hang it
only once.
So, I think it's her.
[They slowly narrow
it down to Seol Hyun.]
If you win the race
if X-man wins, we'll donate 17 million
won under X-man and R-man's name.
If you catch X-man,
you will donate under your name.
I wonder if I'm not good
at finding laptops.
Maybe they found it over there?
[Seol Hyun meets Eagle Eye.]
Did you find it?
[I can feel it.]
- Seol Hyun...
- It's not me.
- You're not?
- I'm telling you the truth.
Please believe me,
I'm not X-man.
[Eagle Eye's eyes flare up.]
Look at my eyes.
[Like this...
I can look at you with honesty.]
[If you look at me liket that...]
You're not.
[With Seol Hyun's innocent look,
his eyes cool down.]
She's not X-man.
[By the way, R-man Kwang Soo
has to help X-man.]
I hope Seol Hyun was X-man.
[What a sweet thought.]
If it's Seol Hyun
maybe it's our fate.
This building's too big!
[R-man Kwang Soo finds the laptop.]
Who should I write?
Jong Kook or B.I?
Jong Soo?
Someone strong...
The least suspicious person...
I have no choice!
[To disturb the voting result]
[B.I gets one vote.]
If Seol Hyun is really X-man,
it's too easy.
[B.I: one]
B.I?
[Did Kwang Soo's plan worked?]
Finally!
Seol Hyun gets one vote.
It's right there!
Seol Hyun!
Two votes for Seol Hyun.
I'm 100 percent sure it's Seol Hyun,
but we need a majority of people.
If I misspell her name
like this, does it count?
Seol Hyung...
[Seol Hyun gets four votes.]
[Everyone's voting for Seol Hyun.]
She has four votes.
What if she's not X-man?
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, you have my vote!
Kwang Soo has two votes.
Again, it's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is catching up.
He's always on the list.
Seol Hyun has five votes,
Kwang Soo has four.
B.I has one vote.
Kwang Soo's catching up.
Laptop...
It's right here.
Write down the name of X-man.
[Seol Hyun]
I think...
[Seol Hyun gets six.]
Here's another one!
[He keeps finding the laptops.]
It's too easy.
[Seol Hyun has seven votes.]
[He finds the laptop.]
I kept putting Seol Hyun's name.
Should I write someone else?
[Seol Hyun]
[Seol Hyun gets 8 out of 16!]
[They have a majority vote.]
We'll finish voting right now.
I think it'll be me.
In 10 minutes,
you need to eliminate the name tag of...
Seol Hyun who gained eight votes.
Find Seol Hyun and eliminate
her name tag in 10 minutes.
I'm not X-man!
[I'll see you soon!]
[Everyone's searching for Seol Hyun.]
If Seol Hyun is X-man.
Where are you Seol Hyun?
Seol Hyun who gained eight votes.
[R-man Lee Kwang Soo
is in a state of emergency.]
What if Seol Hyun is X-man?
It'll be really weird.
[I have nowhere to hide!]
Seol Hyun!
[R-man will protect you!]
[The rest of the members are searching.]
Where are you coming from?
Seol Hyun!
[At that time, Eagle Eye rushes!]
[She hides behind the pole.]
[The emcee Jae Suk
arrives at the scene.]
I'm not!
[She's over there!]
Seol Hyun...
[Eagle Eye is trying to beseige her.]
What are you doing?
All of a sudden, you...
disappeared with her,
so I was surprised.
- I'm not X-man!
- I see.
I understand!
I'm not X-man,
tell them I am not.
Do you remember you met me earlier?
When I asked if you were
X-man, you looked at me.
She's not?
Ji Min!
[Hold it, right there!]
Seol Hyun is here, hurry up!
That's amazing!
[She takes her down right away.]
I'm not X-man,
I worked hard!
Hold still!
[He eliminates Seol Hyun's name tag.]
Hold, it should be written on her back.
Could you show me your back?
- It's on her back.
- You'll regret this.
Seol Hyun!
[Is she X-man?]
Let's see if Seol Hyun was X-man.
[Ever since she fails during Go Fight]
[everyone was suspicious of Seol Hyun.]
[Most of the members point to Seol Hyun.]
She collapsed as she was passing.
She wasn't playing to win.
[Is she really innocent?
Or is she acting?]
[She doesn't have the mark.]
She's not.
I told you!
[Mental break!]
I said I'm not!
Seol Hyun wasn't X-man.
I didn't write your name.
You failed to find X-man
in the first round.
Let's start the second round.
[If Seol Hyun is not, then who is X-man?]
[The first round, they failed
to apprehend X-man.]
Seol Hyun wasn't X-man.
You failed the first round.
It's already over?
It wasn't Seol Hyun?
Someone already ripped her name tag?
Seol Hyun wasn't X-man.
Seol Hyun wasn't?
She's not that type of person.
So, she actually chose me.
[The suspect for the
second round was Andy]
[but he wasn't X-man, either!]
If you can't find it during the
third round, it'll be over.
The third round begins now!
[The laptops are in different locations]
Excuse me, let me vote for a second.
Kim Jung Nam.
Chae Yeon.
The vote differs.
This is a bad sign.
This is the last round!
Just one more round and it's over!
What's that?
The members move ahead of R-man.
[He doesn't even know who X-man is,
how can he help him?]
[When he was given the mission]
You're R-man.
[he was told to help him
by confusing other members.]
[And protect X-man until the end.]
It'll be good If I get
out during the third round.
I need to write my name.
Who's the least suspicious?
This is the last round.
If they eliminate me, X-man will win.
I'll write my name.
[The ultimate step to protect X-man]
[R-man's suicide!]
- Kwang Soo!
- He's not!
I don't think it's Kwang Soo.
If Kwang Soo gets one more vote,
it'll be over.
Wait, Jung Nam!
Don't write anything.
Everyone's suspicious of you.
- But, I'm not!
- Let me write it.
- I'm not going to write your name.
- I'll hold Jung Nam.
Write it.
Why are you writing your name?
You're R-man!
[I got caught!]
You're R-man, right?
You're X-man, aren't you?
I think Kwang Soo's R-man.
[The sudden R-man's harassing
tactic confuses everyone.]
[Did the stubborn R-man
successfully write his name?]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[The final result]
It's over.
For the last round
the person you chose...
is Lee Kwang Soo.
[The third round's target
is Lee Kwang Soo.]
Kwang Soo is not X-man!
He's really not X-man.
Watch it turn out to be Kwang Soo.
X-man, I don't know who you are.
I really missed you.
[See you soon, my destiny!]
[Jae Suk goes up to the
10th floor where Kwang Soo is.]
Are you X-man, Kwang Soo?
[Hesitate]
Are you?
- I'm not.
- You're R-man, aren't you?
[You finally figured it out!]
I think my tactic was brilliant.
Why?
Are you really R-man?
When you see it on TV, you'll want
to be on my team from now on.
[He's proud of his sacrificing tactic.]
- Even I'm surprised.
- Then, you need to be eliminated.
Yes, either way.
Isn't is worth the Nobel prize?
Nobel prize?
What Nobel prize?
You don't know what
the Nobel prize is for?
Are you talking about
the Nobel Prize in Literature?
Is that Jong Kook?
I don't want to be eliminated by him.
[Tiger finds his target.]
What's wrong with you?
Why are you blocking me?
I was on the 10th floor!
Jong Kook, this is the last chance.
If Kwang Soo's not X-man
it means you failed arresting X-man.
[The members don't know
Kwang Soo's R-man.]
[I've already won.]
One, two, three!
[We failed!]
I trusted you, Kwang Soo!
R-man!
[I did it!]
Who's X-man?
I'm going to marry X-man!
- Wow, X-man!
- You've failed to arrest X-man today.
X-man, you're my destiny!
Let's get downstairs!
I'm so sorry.
I wrote my name.
I think it's Chae Yeon.
[Out of the 13 members left,
who's the real X-man?]
You chose Seol Hyun
during the first round
and she wasn't X-man.
And Andy for the second round,
but he wasn't.
Then, Kwang Soo for the third round.
He was R-man, not X-man.
Because you couldn't find X-man.
The winner is X-man.
That's right.
[X-man and R-man win.]
Who is it?
From now on,
let's see who X-man is.
He's right here.
Me?
What are you talking about?
[All of a sudden, they
all point at Jong Kook.]
He was weird during the Go Fight.
He wasn't really trying
during "Of Course."
Will Kim Jong Kook really be X-man?
He's right.
I feel betrayed!
Will he be X-man?
[Trained for the past five years]
[The mysterious X-man
hasn't been revealed yet.]
[Will Jong Kook be the real X-man?]
One, two...
He is!
[The one who tricked
Running Man members]
[X-man members and R-man is...]
[Kim Jong Kook.]
[Six hours ago, during "Go fight"]
[he was acting like he's too shy.]
Just push her if you're
not going to date her.
[And toward Seol Hyun's weak attack]
[he tripped himself]
[and fell.]
He's X-man!
[He pretended he was shy
in front of Seol Hyun.]
[The second fight with Bobby.]
[Mr. Capable lost again?]
[Everyone was suspicious
that he lost on purpose.]
[Are you kidding?]
[He can't make it too obvious.]
[He sent a message to R-man.]
[Make a mistake,
and draw people's attention.]
[He receives the mission.]
[Without knowing who X-man is,
Kwang Soo carries out the mission.]
[Could he be X-man?]
[Could Kwang Soo be R-man?]
[Indicating X]
[Avoid others' eyes, and indicate X.]
[I'm X-man!]
Seol Hyun wasn't X-man.
You know I'm X-man,
why are you telling me?
You are...
- X-man.
- Why are you doing this to me?
[2015 Running Man
and X-man collaboration]
[X-man Kim Jong Kook]
I was doing an X behind you.
[We were totally tricked.]
I know why.
Because Jong Kook is both X-man
and Running Man member.
Why did you tell me
Kim Jong Kook was X-man?
- He didn't know it.
- I didn't think he was X-man.
[How can you not recognize
your partner in front of you?]
- They didn't know each other?
- They didn't.
He didn't know?
I thought he knew it.
Anyway, the final winners are.
X-man and R-man,
Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo!
[Even after 10 years,
it hasn't changed a bit...]
[Our memory is alive within us,
even after 10 years.]
[2016 Luck Battle]
We've just finished X-man.
We're here again.
Thank you for welcoming X-man,
and enjoying the show.
Thank you so much!
For the new year, 2016.
For you and myself...
aren't you curious about
your luck for the next year?
It's the year of red monkey.
(It sounds like a slang for "idiot.")
I think he's saying it on purpose.
Anyway, we'll have to run hard again.
So, I've prepared something special.
It's the "Ladder of Fate."
Like an exorcism,
to avoid bad luck in the new year.
Behind you, there're
numbers one to seven.
We'll tell you the luck numbers
according to Tojung's book of fortune.
We'll use the numbers for the latter?
[They will choose their
lucky number and color.]
[They'll read their fortune for 2016
by tarot card, face and palm reading.]
[And complete the ladder of fortune!]
[Who will be the only one
for the exorcism event?]
We'll see our luck by
"Tojung's Book of Fortune."
[According to each person's
birth date and time]
[the yin yang and five elements
are calculated to tell fortunes.]
He's really famous!
He's an idol in the
world of fortune telling.
[Fortune teller, Park Sung Jun]
[19 years of experience]
Today, I'll announce
the rankings of the best
luck in the year of 2016.
I hope I'm in the
middle of the rankings.
I'll tell your fortunes
from Ji Suk Jin.
Sit in front of him.
- I'm nervous.
- I'm not used to this.
[This is for fun,
why do you get so nervous?]
Ji Suk Jin, you were born as stone
out of the five elements.
[In eastern philosophy, the five elements
wood, fire, earth, metal and water]
[are the fundamental
components of the Universe.]
Like a solid stone, you're faithful.
What?
You said he's faithful?
- He's faithful.
- And he's easily influenced by others.
[Totally agree!]
- When other say something...
- I'm influenced, right.
- He's influenced, but also stubborn.
- How did you know that?
He's absolutely right.
He and I went to ten used car dealers.
"Why don't you buy one
if you like any of them?"
On the way home,
he bought a new car near his house.
After visiting ten used car dealers,
he bought a car from the new car dealer.
The book is absolutely right!
You want to do lots of things.
He does!
You want do start a lot of things,
and do the things others do, too.
In 2016, don't do anything.
[In 2016, don't do anything.]
What should Suk Jin do?
[Burst of laughter]
He's planning to start a few things!
The keyword from the book
for Suk Jin is "don't do anything!"
This is the best thing I've ever heard!
Just don't do anything.
[Shattered]
Just do what you're good at.
The long and short of it.
It's even more shocking than
"the outcome won't be good."
Don't wander around
but stick to what you've been doing.
And stay quietly.
This is that kind of time for you.
I'll tell your lucky numbers and colors.
Your lucky colors are yellow and white.
He has yellow underwear!
Those colors can make
your fortune better.
Your lucky numbers are O and Sa.
(Five and four)
- O and Sa?
- O Sa!
O Sua!
[It sounds like Big-nosed Brother's
catch phrase "Woo Sua."]
You're really accurate!
[Lucky numbers: 5,4]
[Lucky colors: yellow, white]
Gary's personality is you can't stand
when someone tries to control you.
- That's right!
- You want to be free.
Like a bohemian.
Because you're lack of something
that holds you.
That controls you.
You hate when someone tries control you.
You feel uneasy when that happens.
There's only one person
who can control you.
- Isn't that Ha Ha?
- That person can lead you.
Someone who'll be able
to help each other.
He needs to choose this person
when we need a partner.
He's Kim Jong Kook.
You should be nice to me!
They talk to each other
even for serious matters.
Gary might feel a little stressed
but your relationship is good
especially for Kim Jong Kook.
Because of Gary, you can make more money
and extend your field of activity.
Because of me, Jong Kook's luck rises?
Not Gary, but Jong Kook's luck rises.
Kang Gary is my pot of gold.
You always have too many
things to think about.
You want to do many things.
And also want to expand your business.
In the year of red monkey, 2016
with Ji Suk Jin,
don't do anything.
Can you please calculate again for me?
[You, too, stay still
for the next year.]
I feel so bad for Gary!
I've already started a lot!
Stop it now!
It's too late to stop.
Should I not invest any more?
Now is...
time to take a break.
[It's just your luck,
you can change it with your will.]
[Lucky numbers: 5,4]
[Lucky colors: yellow, white]
You'll be stable for your work and love.
I have good luck with love?
- B.I?
- She likes him a lot.
[The Monday Boyfriend is unhappy.]
You're always surrounded by a lot men.
Look, they're all men.
But, they're not decent men.
[No one seems decent here...]
Are you talking about us?
Well, we're all weird.
From 2016 until you turn 37,
you might be able to meet a good man.
- Will these start dating?
- You have good luck for two years, too.
You're about the age.
Think about it.
[Will the perfect person
come to Blank Ji next year?]
[Lucky numbers: 6,3]
[Lucky colors: black, blue]
Ha Ha is good-natured.
He is nice guy.
But you're stubborn.
It's not very obvious
but you're usually satisfied
when you do things your way.
Since 2015, your luck is on upturn.
In the year of 2016, you'll be able to
start new things.
He must be happy!
I envy him, I kind of hate him.
Why?
What's wrong with me?
You can even do a lot of things, too.
But, they won't turn out good.
[The result won't be good...]
This is even worse!
[Oh, no...]
Gary's luck is better.
[Doing nothing is better than failing.]
Sit up!
[Lucky numbers: 1,6]
[Lucky colors: white, black]
Yoo Jae Suk is a fire
who was born in the summer.
But the fire is not very strong.
But, the year 2016 has a big fire.
It'll be a good luck for you again.
Again?
[What's wrong with him?]
He's talking about my fortune.
What's with you?
If he's good, it's good for us, too.
It's always bright for him.
During the year of red monkey,
your luck can lead you to grow.
Is that true?
You want to make money,
and gain honor, too.
He's greedy!
He wants to have it all.
You have a big mouth,
it means you're ambitious.
Your luck with children
is good this year.
He's planning for it!
He told me he plans to
have another child.
One thing you need to be careful of...
is Gary.
Try avoiding Gary.
[His luck overall is good,
but Gary is the problem.]
That's so funny!
This is stressful!
There's a man who's well
suited with Yoo Jae Suk.
Please, please, please!
That's our hope!
- It's Lee Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo?
[They're holding their hands tightly.]
Lee Kwang Soo is like
firewood to Yoo Jae Suk.
I'll give you firewood!
I'm your firewood!
Watch out!
I'll put the fire out!
[They still need to avoid Kang Gary.]
You, you're my firewood!
I'll burn the fire furiously!
2016, the year of red monkey
your luck is in second place.
In second place?
[If Jae Suk's luck is in second,
who has the best luck?]
[Lucky numbers: 3,7]
[Lucky colors: blue, red]
Lastly, I'll explain Kim Jong Kook
Lee Kwang Soo's luck together.
Lee Kwang Soo was born as a big tree.
For a tree to grow, you need water.
You have enough water,
and rooted well in on the earth.
You have everything!
But, there's no sun.
[No sun, no photosynthesis.]
You have desire to grow high
but you feel like you're
lacking in something.
So, you want to fill up emotionally.
That's right!
Absolutely true!
He's tall and handsome,
but his hip is flat.
How does it relate to this?
He feels lonely a lot.
He calls me early in the morning.
You're a tree who
was born in the summer
but you're lacking in warmth.
- You have a hot temper.
- You're right!
You want to see results quickly.
Even with relationships,
you're lacking in means.
Oh my goodness!
- How do you know that?
- He's always dumped.
- He's in a hurry for that, too.
- Exactly!
He surprised all of them.
They say "why are you doing
that all of a sudden?"
He always confess his
feelings at the wrong timing.
- Jae Suk told me to confess!
- You're my firewood!
He told me to do that!
I was put to shame!
It's accurate.
Kim Jong Kook has good technique
to analyze things well and make money.
Analyze!
You're good at analyzing
and apprehending.
Even with relationships
- you try to analyze.
- He does that!
- So true!
- You need to open your heart!
I'm not that young any more.
You have a frame for the ideal type.
True, true!
Try to forget those frame,
but open your heart.
That's how it is.
From 2017, your luck goes up.
There's possibility for you
to meet a good woman.
That's the year after next.
He will use that as an excuse next year.
I was thinking about getting
married the year after next.
One of you has the best luck next year.
- Who is it?
- The man is...
[Giraffe Lee Kwang Soo]
[vs. Tiger Kim Jong Kook]
[Who has the best luck in
the year of red monkey?]
Lee Kwang Soo!
- Is this a good thing?
- Of course it is!
- Thank you so much!
- We knew it!
[Fortune telling for
the members are over!]
[Kim Jong Kook's lucky numbers: 3,7]
[Lucky colors: blue, red]
[Lee Kwang Soo's lucky numbers: 2,5]
[Lucky colors: red, yellow]
You can pick a color
and put it on the number you like.
Put your name on top of it.
We'll let the least luckiest
person pick first.
What do you want?
I'll pick white.
- What number?
- Number four.
[He picks one of his lucky numbers.]
[Four: Gary]
The mixture of white and black is gray.
And I pick number one.
[Suk Jin picks yellow and five.]
[Ji Hyo picks blue and six.]
[Jong Kook picks red and three.]
[Jae Suk picks green and seven.]
[Lee Kwang Soo picks orange and two.]
We all picked the numbers!
For the lines on the ladder,
we invited a tarot reader.
Hello!
[Surprised]
We can tell she's a tarot reader
with her costume.
[Tarot Master Quinny]
[Tarot reading: Out of 78 tarot cards]
[you pick to see the answers
to the problems you have.]
I've never done this before.
Me, too!
[Who's the best partner
for Running Man games?]
Do you want to start, Kwang Soo?
He has the best luck in 2016.
Except love, he's all good.
You can pick now.
I don't know how to do it.
Is it your first time?
For tarot reading, it's good to pick
a specific subject you want to look.
We'll see who's your best partner.
Oh, it's for the game partner?
[Who's the best partner
for the doubles they'll play next?]
It's not about overall luck.
It's fascinating.
You get to pick a card.
Think about one person.
- And pick three cards.
- Three cards?
Maybe it's past, present and future.
You can't blame anyone about it,
because you're the one picking the cards.
She doesn't pick the cards for us.
It's my pick with my will.
Even the picture looks mysterious.
With this person, it's
easy in the beginning
but the end result won't be that good.
That's true!
It's good in the beginning,
there's always trouble in the middle.
- It's Ha Ha!
- It won't be easy to end well.
- Who did you think about?
- I thought about Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha]
They get along so well in the beginning.
But, at the end...
they always fight.
We cursed at each other
so many times!
[It's amazingly correct?]
- Can you check another partner?
- Think about the second person.
That's incredible!
[What are the meanings of the cards?]
- You have lots to learn.
- It's Jae Suk.
[A member he can learn lots of things?]
- Is it me?
- Yes.
Yes, but it doesn't spark up
like when fire flares up.
You're supporting him
as firewood!
You're my fuel, you know.
[Bitter]
Don't try to take it from me.
- How come you didn't pick me?
- I was going to pick you last.
You always call me at night.
Lastly.
[How will their compatibility be?]
[From the end]
Why did you pick the one at the end?
[He picked a special card,
what's the result?]
- It's really good!
- It's good?
[The best compatibility!]
What did I tell you?
- I finally found my partner!
- I give you, and you take it.
You might feel a little pressure, but...
it's joyful and happy.
Like you're cuddled by mother.
It means you're strongly united.
- It's so true.
- They're the strongest partners.
[It's Kkuk's turn.]
[He has someone in mind and picks.]
We pick the cards,
according to our fortune.
It's really fascinating.
You hurt each other emotionally.
Emotionally?
Who is it?
It's hard to lead that person.
Even if the result is good,
you might still feel hurt.
- You little...
- It's me?
I've always felt hurt!
Not one time, I was unhurt!
[He's the best partner for Kwang Soo...]
Did I really do that?
Jong Kook is a good partner
for Kwang Soo, but...
Kwang Soo's not a good
partner for Jong Kook.
[I need him to win at games...]
This is only for the games,
not for the whole life.
Just for the games.
Let's just think about today.
It's really good with this person.
- Perfect!
- It is?
For you, he's a really good partner.
I thought about Gary.
You did?
Even the Tojung's book
said you too are good.
- He said it's good if I control him.
- You need to invest!
[It's about games, not investments.]
[After Tojung's fortune telling, tarot
reading says they're good partners.]
We didn't know you two
are good partners.
Are you thirsty, Suk Jin?
Can we let Suk Jin go home?
I have plans for two things,
but my fortune tells me it's a bad idea.
You have one more person.
It'll be me!
You'll see thunder.
For both of us.
[The history of Running Man]
[is the history of the two rivals.]
[Ttuk and Kkuk conflict with each other
at every single thing they do.]
[How will be the result
of the tarot reading?]
With this person...
you'll have hard times.
You're better off with me!
I told you I'm better partner for you!
Yes, it's really tiring.
It's been tiring for me, too.
On top of that, you need to wear a mask.
You're tired, but you need to
pretend you're not.
This is how our relationship is anyway!
Jong Kook is wearing a mask now!
[It seems they're perfect partners!]
I started from there, but ended up here.
[It's Jae Suk's turn.]
It's interesting!
We're more and more serious.
With this person, it's
neither good nor bad.
Today, you get good result,
tomorow you get bad result.
Who is it?
Lee Kwang Soo.
[I knew it!]
I always worry he'd betray me!
He's on the other team tomorrow!
I'm on your side!
This is so accurate!
He change his sides all the time!
Among all, this person is
the best partner for you.
Gary!
I can do anything for you!
We have a high winning rate together!
- Gary told me that before.
- It's true.
Jae Suk is actually
okay with any members.
No one has bad compatibility with you.
Lastly...
with this person,
I think it's the worst.
You never know.
With this person, you'll have
the short end of the stick.
[Amazing!]
- For real?
- It's so weird!
[They're bad influence for each other.]
[It's just for games,
so, we won't be partners for games.]
I feel better now!
- Don't feel bad!
- I don't!
[Gary's still in panic from
the classic fortune telling.]
With this person, it might be stressful
- but as a result, you'll be happy.
- That's Jong Kook!
[Jong Kook]
Really?
It's the same for each other.
[A new Monday Couple for 2016?]
This person's good, too.
As a new partner,
you'll have good synergy.
Is that Ji Hyo?
I was thinking about Jae Suk.
- It's funny!
- I can give you all!
Let me borrow your name!
Don't mix up with your life!
It's just for games!
I'm talking about the name tag.
[Time to pick partners for the double.]
I want to play with Jong Kook.
If it doesn't work...
- Let's try it!
- Ji Hyo!
I wanted be Ji Hyo's partner.
Wait, he's testing his
life with this game.
- Let me yield...
- It's okay, it doesn't matter.
- Just play with Ji Hyo.
- Thank you.
[She doesn't hesitate
to be Ha Ha's partner.]
Front or back!
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are partners.]
This drives me crazy.
Isn't this amazing?
Come out, Yoo Suk.
[Suk Jin's VJ.]
[Ping pong unity]
[The luck battle game]
You can play ping pong with your head.
[Modification of "Headies"]
[They will get lines to put on
their ladder by the result.]
Let's see if our luck for partner
are actually true with this game.
[Will the tarot reading
for partner be right?]
For the third and fourth winners.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo vs.
Suk Jin and Yoo Suk]
Let's begin the game now.
[Their luck is not very good.]
[Will they be able to turn their luck?]
Let's begin now.
[Drawing a horizontal
line with his toss?]
[His head shape is a
bad luck for Ji Suk?]
- Are you X-man?
- He has a pointy head.
One to zero.
Okay!
It's two to zero.
Dong Hoon is good at it.
It's harder than ping pong.
Hit it harder.
[Its weird.
It's not supposed to be this funny.]
Were you throwing up?
I was going to tap your back.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo vs. Suk
Jin and Yoo Suk] [3:0]
[Ji Hyo gets the hang of it.]
[With Ha Ha's mistake, it's 3:1.]
Good!
[It was tight... but]
[Flounder, flounder]
[His slapstick gets
funnier and funnier.]
What's wrong with you?
Is that a bullfight?
Are we in Spain?
- It's like a bullfight!
- I'm upset!
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo vs.
Suk Jin and Yoo Suk 4:1]
Good!
At least, we didn't get last place.
We have the best luck by Tojung's book.
Jong Kook and Gary are the
best partners by tarot.
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
have the best luck.
[Who's side is the goddess of luck?]
[I was careless!]
[It's so funny!]
Never mind.
I was thinking about the
rules of table tennis.
It's their trick.
[They missed it again!]
You were thinking about
table tennis, right?
It's really fun!
It has different rules.
Let's win with this upturn.
It's three to zero.
No, it's two to one.
[The rally continues in fast speed.]
We did it!
[It went on the net!]
Three to one!
I thought it's out.
They're really lucky.
It's good!
[Neck and neck]
[Jong Kook and Gary vs.
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo]
[2:3]
[One point is critical.]
[Jong Kook's attack worked!]
I almost kicked your face.
[They're tied.]
[Do you want to dig the ground?]
[What are you doing?]
What good will it do
to look at the bottom of the ball?
Why did I do that?
[This serve will decide the game!]
[The fierce serve!]
That's right!
[Receive and toss!]
[Gary saves it!]
[Grab]
[Gary's attack succeeded!]
[Puzzled]
[Gary threw his whole body.]
We were doing so well...
I knew we would win together!
[The first winner gets three lines,
second wiinter gets two.]
[The third winners gets one line.]
I'm going to put it in the middle.
I need to stick right
next to you, Jae Suk.
[He didn't get any lines.]
I'm put a line toward Jong Kook.
I'll move one line toward Ji Suk Jin.
[Only one member will get the penalty.]
[Their lucks are changing by the lines.]
I'll see my fortune with this.
[The ladder of fortune is completed.]
My line goes back to my number.
[2016 Luck Battle]
Lastly, we'll invite Face Reader.
No one has actually
done this before, right?
[Hermit Boeun Kang Min Won]
With Yoo Jae Suk.
Please, make an objective observation.
This is about looking at the shape.
You have bulging cheek bones.
Cheek bones...
If you were born 200 years ago
you would be living in wealth.
If I were born in the past?
I have to talk about your mouth.
Bulging mouth...
The more you talk,
the more money you make.
It's really precious.
You job is perfect for you.
I love my job!
Yoo Jae Suk is the
second best out of all.
You, too have bulging cheek bones, too.
You're competitive.
He is really competitive.
- Looking at your eyes, are they big?
- No, they're small.
It's a shape of a snake eye.
It's poisonous!
It doesn't mean it's bad.
It's the eye of a leader.
Therefore, he's good at leading things.
From the point of view as a face reader
you're pretty lucky.
You have the best luck out of all.
You have a broad forehead.
Broad forehead means
you're smart.
She's smart.
The shape of your eye brows
are like crescent.
That's the best shape
of eye brows for woman.
You have well-formed features.
You eye brows says, you
will be successful.
You shouldn't cover your eye brows.
[He's fourth in his luck.]
We call this kind of nose as Big-nose.
Big-nose, nose shows
your pride and wealth.
It shaped well at the bottom,
it's for your old age.
If you keep it well,
it'll be good for generations.
For generations?
Ji Suk Jin has very good
luck with your spouse.
Tail of your eyes shows it.
- It's really good.
- His wife is a really good.
I wouldn't know because I never
lived with another woman.
If you say things like that,
the luck with your nose won't work.
You'll be in trouble.
[The result of the face reading]
We picked the color and numbers.
We'll see who will get
the penalty today.
Who do you think?
If I get it, it'll be complete.
[He still has no line.]
Our fortune changes like this.
My line goes somewhere else again.
- Mine, too.
- I want to get penalty.
[It's your will to change your luck.]
Let's not read it now.
- Come forward.
- We'll take it as an exorcism.
[Finally]
[it's time to change their luck.]
[The penalty will drive
away the bad luck.]
[But it will be only one!]
Whose microphone will be taken?
- This is the critical moment.
- Who will take a shower today?
You didn't change anything, right?
We didn't.
We left it as it was.
Who do you want to start?
Let's open it by order.
Should I take off the microphone?
Everyone has to.
- Let's take off the shoes.
- I'm usually lucky.
I'm usually unlucky.
- Me, too.
- And Kwang Soo.
I have a bad luck with this.
- If you get the penalty, you'll get it.
- Then, it's good!
I'll take it!
[Who will be the luck person
who will get the golden prize?]
Let's get inside.
[Entering the room of exorcism]
We don't know until they open.
I don't think it's me.
I have a good luck!
Don't touch the top.
It will come down if you touch it.
[Just one unlucky member
will have muddy shower.]
[This isn't funny...]
[The members will decide
who will start first.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Let's begin with Lee Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
- We'll start from Lee Kwang Soo!
- Why me?
Please!
That was my line!
[It ended at the first line.]
[Will he greet the new
year with a smile?]
[He passed.]
[Mixed feelings]
It was my spot!
That was my spot!
You can pick a member, Kwang Soo.
Next up is...
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Why me?
I hope it's him.
Kwang Soo!
Why did you pick me?
Please!
Not me!
No!
[Jong Kook's luck was good.]
[Will it end nicely?]
Wow!
[His legs gave way.]
[Five members are left.]
[About to cry]
It's so nervous.
[It's hard to stand up.]
This is insane.
Kim Jong Kook...
please pick one.
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Of course, he picks Jae Suk.]
It's getting even more nervous.
I have bad luck with this kind of stuff!
[Please]
[Nervous]
Please!
Please, forgive me!
[It's a long journey.]
Why is it so long?
Where is it going?
It's heading to Suk Jin's line!
[Big-nose's line?]
[His luck was really bad all day.]
[Will it be okay?]
[Of couse!]
[Oh my god!]
[The mud shower looks so refreshing.]
[It will take away all
the bad luck he has.]
[We hope everyone is happy in 2016!]
[On top of muddy water,
he gets feathers, too.]
[That makes me so happy,
because it didn't happen to me.]
It's so funny,
my stomach hurts!
[The terrible ending
of the unlucky man.]
It's insane!
His bad luck has gone now.
[It's okay.]
[I'll be happy with the lucky clover.]
This happens all the time,
not even one exception!
This means I have really
good luck in 2016.
We'll do our best to make
everyone laugh in 2016.
Please look forward to see us!
Happy new year!
Today, it's "the Reply Avatar Race."
[We'll post the mission on SNS.]
(Social media)
[They have to follow
the viewers' commands.]
[From the method to the members]
[communicate with the
viewer in real time!]
[And...]
[What will be the ending of the
secret name tag elimination?]
[They can trust no one!]
[SNS Reply Race]
Subtitles by DramaFever