[Strong like a storm,
and fierce like a wave!]
[Kim Woo Bin, Kang Ha Neul, Junho.]
[The unstoppable three young men!]
[They will start running!]
- I like the music.
- It's exciting!
[Come dressed in what you
wore when you were 20.]
- I couldn't say that I love you.
- That's Seo Taeji!
[Gary is wearing a dreadlock wig.]
- Gary actually looked like that.
- Yes, I looked like this.
When I was a VJ, I wore this
and stayed in the back.
- I used to wear these earrings.
- Those huge earrings!
- People wore cotton pants!
- Yes, those chinos!
[Hip hop style back in the Turbo days.]
- The sneakers used to be big.
- Yes, size 300.
I actually used to wear long coats.
- I copied Chow Yun Fat's style.
- With a muffler?
People used to chew on a match, too.
This style is my generation.
He's supposed to wear bell bottoms.
It was straight cut!
What bell bottoms?
[Big-nose,
second year high school student.]
It wasn't the 70's.
What are you?
- That shouldn't be his fashion!
- How old are you?
I used to wear clothes like this
when I was 20.
The denim fashion made
a comeback many times.
- Did he fake his age?
- What are you talking about?
[The handsome young men are here.]
[Three flower boys.]
Honestly, we can... they're here!
- Junho and Kim Woo Bin.
- They're coming!
[A cool boy, Junho]
[A pure young man, Ha Neul.]
[20 year-old Woo Bin]
What's with your pants?
[Combination of the two flower boys.]
- He's Papillion!
[20 year-old Woo Bin]
I can't believe this!
- He's Papillion.
- Who wears those kinds of clothes?
Who wears this?
- What is it?
[Only Woo Bin can pull it off.]
Hello, I'm 2PM's Junho.
It's nice to be here.
It's been a while.
- Hello, I'm Kang Ha Neul.
- It's his second time here.
[Ha Neul did rock climbing
and went up the 63 building.]
- He went up the 63 Building, too.
- He, did!
- You went up the 63 building?
- By foot!
Hello, I'm Kim Woo Bin.
Nice to see you again.
[Running Man family member,
Actor Kim Woo Bin.]
- Were you overseas?
- Where in the world was it?
Actually, it wasn't that different
from what people wear now.
Ah, I see.
- Did you play with this?
- Of course, we always played it.
Punching machine is to...
Guys become competitive
when they play this.
- Woo Bin!
[Show us, Woo Bin!]
I think he's a good fighter.
I saw him in 'Friends 2.'
I think he'll hit 1,000.
Tall guys are usually strong.
[Powerful punch]
- That's right! The sound tells it all.
I think he scored pretty high.
- It's 837!
- Wow, 837!
[Goal celebration]
- I know he exercises.
- Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
- Why don't you try?
- Do it, Jong Kook!
- Mr. Capable is pressured.
He should score 500 at least.
He looks like a gangster from LA.
- He's scary.
- It's like a fighting game in real life.
[He looks like a final boss in games.]
This is not so...
- It sounded different.
- It bounced back.
- I'm not good at it.
- 667!
[Mr. Capable is humiliated.]
[Mr. Capable lost against Woo Bin.]
He only looks like he's strong.
I'll announce the rules for today.
It's on the scroll at the back.
- What is it?
- It made me jump!
[Winner! Big-nose scored 100!]
- Me?
- Big-nose has the main role?
- What is this?
- Thank you.
[An announcement of the winner?]
Congratulations!
I think you're the leading
character today.
Big-nose scored 100.
Big-nose, please take the winning prize.
- Me?
- Winning prize, now?
[There are ten gold bars
that are 3.75 grams each.]
Is today Suk Jin's last day
on Running Man?
No, I think this is the future and
we have to let it happen or something?
Maybe the future came first.
Today, the winner had been
nominated and that's Ji Suk Jin.
If Suk Jin scores 100 and
becomes the winner
all of you will win, too.
We have to help him, then.
Nine members will need to have a
strategy to help Suk Jin win the race.
- You should do worse than me.
- What?
- It's not an easy task.
- It's too difficult!
Ji Suk Jin has to have 100 points at
the end and that's how you can win.
Please help Ji Suk Jin today.
We might get competitive
and win over him.
- We can do it.
- Let's do it!
I'll do worse if you make me feel bad.
Then I'll have to return the gold.
You should check carefully,
they might be switched to fake gold.
[Will they be able to make Big-nose win?]
- Pocket your pride!
- Look, how he talks!
[How will this race end?]
I have to win, so we all win.
[For Big-nose's win, let's go!]
- Do we all go together?
- In one car?
[They need to go to
their first mission site.]
- Oh, I forgot to bring it.
- What?
- Do you mean, the gold?
- I'll bring it.
You can't forget what we play for.
[Big-nose lost the gold.]
- Huh? I'm in trouble.
[Not in the waiting room.]
- How can you lose that?
- He looks embarrassed.
You kept it?
I thought I lost it.
Okay.
Ten of them!
He's here.
Five, four, three, two, one!
[Move!]
[Where are you going?]
- Hey!
[Big-nosed brother, wake up!]
We need to give Suk Jin some tension.
Hey!
[You can't make
these kind of mistakes!]
He needs some training.
Do it one more time.
[Don't go!]
[Site of big-nose's training.]
He doesn't exercise at all.
[They care about their eldest brother.]
Run faster!
- Do some exercise.
- We trained you.
You'll only be able to take this
when I win, you know?
- I want to talk to Woo Bin.
- Me?
- It's been a year already.
- Right.
- What is?
- Since we went to Australia with Woo Bin.
- It was that long ago?
- We didn't let Woo Bin sleep.
- The ocean was so beautiful.
- The coastline, too!
I still remember the sight.
- By the way, Suk Jin has to...
- I have to win but...
what games will they be?
It's not just about winning
because they mentioned '100 points'.
We have to get that score.
Work harder, Suk Jin.
It'll be more difficult
than just winning.
[What awaits them...]
It's a pool.
- There are towels.
- What is that? It's a team game.
It's for two teams?
It's the first round of
'Make Big-nose the winner.'
It's not easy.
Everyone says it's too difficult.
This is the most difficult game
in RM history.
Everybody said it's too hard.
The first game will be
'Oh, shiny 20's quiz.'
- What's that?
- A quiz game?
You'll be in two teams.
One with Ji Suk Jin, and one without.
You'll see why it matters in the game.
Which is better...
Oh, we can decide the
team members?
People who are good
with quizzes should come here.
You should come to my team, Jae Suk.
Why did you move, Woo Bin?
- It's okay, Woo Bin.
[He volunteers to go.]
Wow, Woo Bin just volunteered to go.
- This is perfect.
- I'll do my best.
Some of my team members are...
Junho wears the mask of 2PM but...
You're kind of risky.
I think Junho missed the timing.
[Accidentally, he became a member
who's good at quizzes.]
While I wasn't paying attention,
everyone already moved.
Did you decide the teams?
Don't forget. I have to win,
so you can win.
You know we're actually
the same team.
We'll say the correct answer,
if you bother us.
I lose my temper sometimes.
Don't offend them.
- We could clear this round!
- Should we clear it?
- Good job.
- Just remember.
We have to make you win.
You're not going to win.
- I should do well, too.
[Their teamwork doesn't seem so strong.]
[Ten water bombs are installed in the pool.]
- Look at the water.
- This is going to be hard.
Won't they guess right
just to avoid getting wet?
I'll tell you the rules now.
- Each member will solve a quiz.
- And?
If all the team members get it right,
each member will score 30 points.
'Team Ji Suk Jin' will solve
short-answer questions.
- And 'Team Not Suk Jin' will solve...
- Multiple choice questions?
Dichotomous questions.
Dichotomous questions,
choose between the two.
When the answer is wrong,
the whole team will be water bombed.
I told you one smart person
should be there.
- They need smart people.
- Why is that?
They might ask difficult questions.
You actually need to know to be wrong.
That's why I came to this team.
[Trust me, I'm the brain.]
You're the black hole!
- What's wrong with your eyes?
- Why?
Some of you have glassy looks.
Before tests, people do.
- Not all, but some of them...
- Don't make them mad!
- They have glassy looks!
- I'll guess the right answer, then!
It's better if we go first.
They can see our score
and control their score.
We're in the same team!
- Don't forget we're one.
- Remember and work hard!
- Let's do our best.
- Guessing them correct isn't that easy.
- Pocket your pride.
- I see, I see!
First question is
for Kang Ha Neul.
- It's important to have good roots.
- He looks smart.
- He's been acting as smart characters.
- He's always acted as an elite man.
- Like a prosecutor.
- That's just the role!
Let's see.
- I'll count on you.
- Let's check.
- Mother!
- Yes.
- Hope you all get a jackpot!
[His mom's doppelganger.]
- He looks exactly like his mom.
- I know that.
You look like her, especially today.
His hair is long now,
so he's more like his mom now.
- Especially when he smiles.
- He does.
I'll give Ha Neul the first question.
Male hormones are called androgens
and they are a factor into
causing 'this'.
'This' is also called a symbol of youth.
You know it, right?
What is 'this'?
You don't know?
- You should have asked my team.
- You know it, right?
I'll repeat the question.
Male hormones are called androgens, and
are a factor in causing a symbol of youth.
A symbol of youth?
- Say it confidently.
- Just say it!
Wait!
It's a pimple!
He's right.
- Yeah!
[Correct.]
[He must have been under
a lot of pressure going first.]
Kwang Soo said, 'it's a hair.'
[A symbol of youth, a hair?]
- He's so weird!
Only four members are left.
Fighting!
The second question.
This is what you ate when
you were 20.
You can see this in snack bars.
It is named after its chewy texture.
What is it?
- What's that?
- It's too easy.
- Are you ignoring us?
- Snack bars!
- It represents snack food.
- I liked it a lot.
Girls like it.
- The answer is jjolmyun
(Spicy cold chewy noodle)!
- Right answer.
[Correct answer]
[He continues their sweeping upturn.]
- I don't like jjolmyun.
- I thought it was spicy fried ramen.
- Why is he so happy at getting jjolmyun?
- I was confused with spicy fried ramen.
- Don't forget. I have to win!
- We're doing okay so far.
It's for you, Jong Kook.
Dates back to old times,
a person before a test
Wait, okay.
never eats 'it' thinking they might
'Nakje (fail)' because of its name.
Because of the name?
What is this?
- Not the texture but the name.
- The name?
Name?
What name?
This one is difficult.
- 'Nakji (small octopus)'.
- The name makes you fail!
- Wow, you're amazing!
- That's the answer?
[Is Woo Bin right?]
I'll give you five seconds.
Five, four...
Nakji!
You're right, Jong Kook!
[Correct.]
[Three questions in a row!]
I'll win today!
- I thought it was seaweed.
- No, that one is for the texture.
This question is for Yoo Jae Suk.
'80% of what brought me up for
twenty-three years is this.'
'The world is just shameful
the more I look.'
This is Seo Jung Joo's
famous poem 'Self-portrait.'
What is this?
- Can you repeat the question?
- Isn't this too hard all of a sudden?
This is a very famous poem.
'80% of what brought me up for
twenty-three years is this.'
'The world is just shameful
the more I look.'
What is this?
I have one word on my mind.
What brought me up...
Si-ryun (ordeal)!
Hey, take your time.
- I don't know.
- Think about it.
- I can't think of anything else!
- He didn't say, 'It is'.
He said 'what brought me up.'
It's a two letter word.
It is 'Si-ryun (ordeal)!
I don't know.
[Wrong answer.]
[Suk Jin's team fails.]
- The water is so cold!
- That was too difficult!
The correct answer is
'Ba-ram (wind).'
- The wind brought me up?
- That's too difficult.
We're going to choose between two.
We just need to be wrong.
But we should know what's wrong.
Please be wrong.
Let our team win, okay?
Since it's the first question,
I'll answer it correctly.
No, we never know.
Just be wrong.
- What if we all get it right?
- We should know what's wrong.
In modern society, some men feel pressured
and depressed about their image.
This obsessive behavior is
originated from...
This question is designed for Gary.
the character in Greek mythology.
This beautiful young man
became an anemone after he died.
What is this?
Number one, Narcissism.
Number two, Adonis Complex.
What will be the answer?
Number one or number two.
Does he have to be right or wrong?
They have to be wrong.
I don't know.
I have to make a guess.
I've heard of narcissism before.
- It's not Narsha!
- It is number 2, Adonis complex.
- That's the right answer.
- What if it's right?
[Correct answer]
- Am I right?
- I said that's the right answer.
- That was the right answer!
- I was right?
- Narcissism means excessive self-love.
- It's not easy to be wrong.
- Narcissism means self-love.
He couldn't be wrong
even if he wanted to.
- The questions are hard.
- We're in trouble.
Dichotomous questions are harder!
- You need to pick the wrong answer.
- That's what I did.
[He's a time bomb at quizzes.]
- Give us really difficult questions.
The second question is...
Many young people get 'Byun-bi
(constipation)' from dieting too severely.
In the word 'Byun-bi (constipation)'
what does 'bi' mean?
'Bi' from 'Byun-bi'.
What's the meaning of the 'bi'?
Number one, to hide.
Number two, to be blocked.
- What was number one?
- Secret, bi.
Constipation...
means it's blocked, right?
What if it means to hide?
Please, answer it now.
To hide or to be blocked.
- Just solve it.
- Follow your feeling.
- Won't he look dumb if he's wrong?
- It's to hide!
That's right.
You picked the wrong answer.
You know, constipation
means it's blocked...
- What?
- Really?
[A bolt out of the blue!]
- What? It's not to be blocked?
- Is that a trick?
- That's a trick question!
- You should think it over.
Why would you hide it?
You might end up getting
them all!
This is a battle between
us and the producers.
It's really hard.
Next question.
The year 1985 was when
Ji Suk Jin was 20 years old.
- It's when we were born.
- I wasn't even born yet.
Didn't you go to night clubs
at the time?
What happened in 1985?
Number one,
'Back to the Future 1' was released.
I can't believe it!
Number two,
'Terminator 1' was released.
- I don't know.
- Terminator in 1985?
I think I remember watching it.
You were born in 1985.
Wasn't 'Back to the Future'
released before?
No, the correct answer
is 'Back to the Future.'
- So, he has to choose 'Terminator.'
- I'm confused, too.
Choosing Terminator
will be good for us.
- Woo Bin!
- Yes.
- You should pick the wrong answer.
- Answer it wrong!
I can't give you more time.
You have five more seconds.
It's number two, Terminator one.
- He's right.
- If it's wrong, then...
We needs to be wrong, right?
[When they're wrong
they'll be water bombed.]
[Wrong answer!]
[Team Not Suk Jin fails.]
[It's Team Ji Suk Jin's turn.]
[Thanks to Woo Bin,
Big-nose revived.]
Let's just get the right answers!
- It's so cold!
- It's cold!
They will increase the amount of water.
There's more water now.
- Let's go!
- Let's do it!
Start from Kang Ha Neul.
Young men like you play
billiards, right?
Yes, we do.
Billiard balls used to be made
out of 'this'.
We also call universities as 'this' tower.
What is this?
You know it, Ha Neul.
Did you just say universities?
Billiard balls were made out of 'this'.
We also refer to universities as
'this' tower.
What is this?
- Isn't it ivory?
- Ivory, yes.
[Even Kwang Soo seems like he knows.]
- You know that.
- You must know.
Is that it?
- Is that it? What if it's not?
- Ha Neul, you're right.
The answer is plaster!
[Plaster?]
[Are you kidding?]
The ivory tower!
That's right!
[Answer: ivory]
- Are universities plaster towers?
- I'm sorry!
I was confused!
What is a plaster tower?
I kept showing you with my mouth.
- You should come over here.
- You should switch your team.
Can I swap members?
The plaster tower,
it was very funny though.
No, I actually know the word.
'The plaster tower' will be next
to your name in search engines.
- People will remember the plaster tower.
- I really know it.
It will accompany your name forever.
It's too late.
[I said, I play intelligent characters.]
They tricked us.
They are playing with us!
Kwang Soo, try guessing it right.
Should I do that?
Don't try to be wrong.
Here's the question.
Not only young men but everyone
loves beef.
Especially this part...
Number one!
[Correct answer.]
[He's got it right.]
[He guessed it right without
listening to the question.]
- I didn't think I would get it.
- You should listen!
- I thought I wouldn't know.
- What are you doing?
The part is along the inside ribs
and it looks like a thin cylinder.
One cow has very small amount of this.
1. Neck chain. 2. blade steak
Number one is the correct answer.
I don't know anyway.
- You shouldn't give the right answer!
- You'll win at this rate.
- We won't be able to get any gold.
- Be careful!
Woo Bin, please!
Woo Bin has to stop this.
The next person is Gary.
A very popular dish
for a young couple's date is
spaghetti carbonara.
In italian, 'carbonara' means
'this' maker. What is this?
Number one, firewood.
Number two, charcoal.
- This is too much!
- Number one!
Number two!
- Wait!
- I think it's firewood.
That's why I picked number one.
We're supposed to be wrong.
[Wrong answer.]
[Team Not Suk Jin fails
at the second try.]
What a relief!
Woo Bin saved us again.
They would have won,
if it wasn't for Woo Bin.
I knew the answer,
so I picked the wrong answer.
- Let's switch seats.
- I hate being the first to go.
Switch with me Ha Neul.
This is a good chance, Ha Neul.
Why are you always giving me
the burden?
In my opinion...
it's all up to... Ha Neul.
I knew the word, the ivory tower.
I'll give you the question, Suk Jin.
Age of 40 is
called 'Bulhok', and 50 is?
I'm not sure.
It's 'Jichunmyung.'
Then what's the name for
the age of 20?
- It's too easy.
- Do you know it?
I know! I know it!
- He just said it's an 'adult.'
- We celebrate the coming of age day!
- An adult?
- Why? That's not it?
I hope I'm right.
Is that, right?
The sounds same
as 'provision' in a contract.
My answer for the 20 year old is
- 'Yakkwan!'
- That's right.
- Did you know that, Ha Neul?
- I know it.
The next question is for Junho.
This is a word to call a hideout
and we use the word
for a gathering place.
Don't you have a place, too?
- We do have it.
- What is it?
I think that's right, Junho.
Okay, the correct answer is...
- Agit (from agitating point)!
- That's right.
[Correct answer.]
[Two correct answers in a row!]
- If we can continue until Ha Neul!
- It's a good change!
It's easy word but I was
confused with 'base.'
Kim Jong Kook, Korea has 'hanbok'
(Korean traditional dress).
China has 'Qipao'
Then, what is the name of the
Vietnamese traditional dress?
- That's hard.
- It's confusing.
- We wore it when we were in Vietnam.
- Ao!
[They wore them when
they were shooting in Vietnam.]
- Do I look okay in this dress?
[It's 'Ao Dai.']
You wore them when you
were in Vietnam.
- Jong Kook, you know it, right?
- Ao!
Please move your hand
away from your mouth.
- The Vietnamese dress?
- You know, usually women wear them.
- It's a tight dress.
- I think I remember.
- Ao dai?
- Right, right.
[Correct answer.]
[They barely passed the third crisis.]
- This was difficult.
- I was confused with 'Januzaj.'
- The soccer player, Januzaj.
[The burden increases.]
We're here, Ha Neul.
- That's amazing.
- I'm worried about Ha Neul.
It's Jae Suk's turn.
This is used as a reflection of
the living standard.
It's the proportion of income
spent on food.
Young men like you guys usually
have a high number of this.
The correct answer is Engel's coefficient.
Yeah! He's right.
[Correct answer.]
[Four Correct answers in a row.]
[Only Ha Neul is left.]
- Ha Neul!
- It's a good chance!
- You're the last!
It's Ha Neul's turn.
Kang Ha Neul.
The rainbow colors are
red, orange, yellow, green,
blue, indigo, and violet.
Colors will be reversed in a
secondary rainbow.
Say the colors' reversed order
in three seconds.
Three, two...
[Big-nose can win if he
gets this question right.]
- one!
- Violet, indigo, blue, blue, oh bother!
[Dear God...]
[Team Ji Suk Jin fails at the
last question.]
I'm sorry.
Don't you know Violet, indigo,
blue, green, yellow, orange, red?
And why did you fall?
[He made us laugh with his words
and made us laugh again with his body.]
What are you doing?
I was so shocked.
I'm sorry.
Why did we put him at the end?
He looks like Kwang Soo now.
- I think the first one is easiest.
- Go back to your seat.
I feel sorry for him.
- It was funny.
- He likes variety shows and he's funny.
Violet, indigo, blue, blue, oh bother!
I'll give you a question, Ha Neul.
'This' is Michael Jackson's signature move.
It was popular among young men at the time.
The dancer moves backwards
while appearing to walk forwards.
What is it?
- You really don't know?
- Just kidding.
The correct answer is Moonwalk.
[Correct Answer]
We've gone over the big mountain!
Junho.
In the 90's, there were returned
students who lived in luxury and pleasure.
They were called by 'this' tribe.
It's also a name of a fruit
with lots of vitamin C...
The answer is orange tribe!
[Correct answer.]
[They passed two.]
- We'll pass this time around!
- Good, good!
We'll get them all!
This alcoholic beverage is described
as stars in a pale golden color.
This is usually used at celebrations.
What is this?
It's that one?
- Yes, it's that one.
- Champagne!
[Correct answer.]
- We're almost done!
- We're going to finish it!
It's time to finish it.
- Don't miss it.
- I won't.
In swimming, there's
a stroke called 'dolphin.'
- What does it look like?
- Butterfly!
[Correct answer.]
I thought it was a frog.
- You're the last one.
- The last one!
[I have to win, so we can all win.]
If you solve this problem, you and
your team members will get 30 points.
And it'll be very helpful for you
to win with the score of 100.
Old in age...
but full of a young spirit.
What's the word for it?
Green old age?
Isn't that the answer?
No way...
Green old age?
What is it?
Full of a young spirit?
The last question is tough.
Even in old age,
a full of young spirit...
Do we use the word often?
[It is a matter of the winning at stake.]
- Okay, I'll answer now.
- I think he's right. Trust him.
Count three for me.
One, two, three!
Green old age!
- That's right.
- Isn't that right?
[Correct answer.]
[Team Ji Suk Jin wins the first round!]
[They made it happen all together!]
It was my answer!
It was me!
[Team Not Suk Jin members
did their best to be wrong.]
Team Ji Suk Jin members
score 30 points each.
[Big-nose gets close to winning.]
- I thought it was not the answer.
- Me, too.
Because Ha Neul said it,
I thought it was wrong.
- Ha Neul got it right.
- I thought he tried to be funny.
Maybe it's not that difficult
to make me win.
I think it's easy.
- I think there's something else.
- That's a given.
The fact you have to score 100...
is a bit suspicious.
By the way,
Ha Neul sings really well.
No, I'm not that good.
Please sing 'Wedding Cake' for me.
I don't remember the lyrics.
[He has such a sweet voice!]
He has a good voice.
He only sang one measure
and it's like the movie.
Continue!
[He continues singing 'Wedding Cake.']
Are you singing the duet part?
[He has a nostalgic voice.]
You sound exactly
the same as the movie.
You sound like Yoon Hyung Joo
when he was young.
You do sound like him.
His voice is very nice.
Wedding cake...
It's depressing.
It's different from when
Ha Neul sings it, right?
[They can't sing in duet.]
[But their next mission is...]
[Props for a congregate dining?]
- It's karaoke!
- It's a karaoke machine!
- Do we have to make him score 100?
- Do I have to score 100?
The second game is
'the youth singing room.'
You can make your own
teams again.
Make five teams, each team
with two members.
- I want to go with Ha Dong Hoon.
- I agree.
We had a concert
in the states together.
Did you see the interview?
I didn't speak at all.
How do you think it would look?
It will be great 'cause you know
we just want to make our fans happy...
[Did he take a vow of silence?]
[It's okay. Singers can speak
through songs.]
[The teams for 'youth singing room'
are decided.]
This is how you play
'The youth singing room.'
Each of you will wear
pace counters and sing.
We'll add up the singing score
and the numbers on the pace counters.
The team that gets the closest number
to 600 is the winner.
If the number is less than
600, it's invalid.
Then Suk Jin should start.
Around 610 is a good number, then.
If you win the first place,
your score will be 80.
Wow, it's close to 100.
Please wear the pace counters
on your waist.
- Let's sing that song.
- What song?
Insooni's 'Every night.'
Make sure you score more than 600!
[Insooni-Every night]
Faster, faster!
We've got to run.
[Let's finish it at once...]
[They don't miss the break.]
[As if they would climb up
the altitude of 600 meters.]
[He's rapidly losing his energy.]
You can't be tired already!
You can't stop!
[Ha Ha helps recharging.]
Jump, jump!
- You can't make it like this!
- I don't think he reached 600.
[What will their score be?]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
scored 89.]
[The score isn't bad.]
Give me your pace counter.
Why are we nervous?
You can go back.
Don't use your energy at once.
- I think I saw 25.
- No way, it must be 250.
You scored 89.
Ji Suk Jin's number is...
256!
[89+256=345]
Song Ji Hyo's number is...
- 260.
- Yes, 260 is good.
Song Ji Hyo's number is 341!
Thank you, Ji Hyo.
We have to score higher than that.
[They have to score more than
Suk Jin's team to let him win.]
- It has to be more than 600.
- But it's too much more!
Ji Suk Jin and Song Ji Hyo
scored 686.
Why is it so high?
That's right.
You have to score more than that.
What are we going to do?
This song has a long intro.
Kwang Soo can do it.
Sing a 2PM song!
- Again and again.
- 10 out of 10!
- How can we do it on bended knees?
- Let's do this.
[The sound of a heartbeat...
is that the song?]
[The song with the most
powerful dance?]
Kwang Soo is weird.
[2PM - Heartbeat]
This is not my part.
[He gathers all the strength...]
[His pace counter might break.]
[Very appealing.]
[It won't be easy scoring
more than 686.]
[It's the climax!]
[Their heartbeat is pumping.]
[Was this song this long?]
- Jump!
Still not enough!
Get up!
[Good night!]
[They give CPR with their cheers.]
You can do it!
You should hold it out!
[The song is over.]
- It was pretty long.
[Kwang Soo and Junho scored 97.]
[Totally amazing!
The result of their youth and vigor.]
Just watching them was enough
to tire me out.
I bet your heart feels like it's
about to burst out of your chest.
- You scored a total of 97 points.
- Yes.
- If you guys were to sing another song...
- No.
- [Why would you even say such a thing?]
- [I'm sure our score was enough.]
- I'm sorry.
- You're not breathing like that on purpose?
[The rare cardio exercise that he just got
results in him making all sorts of noises.]
[Anyway... what did we score
on our pedometers?]
353.
[Kwang Soo of Team Kwang Soo and Junho-
97 + 353 = A total of 450 points.]
[In order for Team Suk Jin to win, Junho
must've scored 236 points or higher.]
Junho's total count is 382.
[Team Kwang Soo and Junho-
450 + 382 = A total of 832 points.]
[With the fiery strength of youth,
Team Suk Jin is allowed to maintain the lead.]
- We're going to sing a ballad.
- Cue the music!
[Huh?
What the heck is this?]
[Never before seen dance moves
to a soft ballad song.]
[It seems they may have surpassed
the 600 point mark already.]
- He's so scary!
- Are you a ghoul or something?
[Haven't you ever heard of the
urban legend singing style?]
I can't even bear to listen
to his singing.
[Jong Kook ends his portion of the song
with an eerie lingering note.]
[And this one picks up with
a reggae beat.]
[Gets carried away with his bounce moves.]
[Why did you choose a ballad
if you were going to act like this?]
[Is he even mixing in
some light salsa moves?]
I really can't even stand
looking at him!
[Everybody, join in!]
[The song is coming to an end, but the
dance party is just getting started.]
Wow, this is a really long song.
[The song is coming to an end,
and it's time to say their goodbyes.]
[One final shake for the road.]
- You totally passed your points.
[What of their singing score?]
[Team Jong Kook and Ha Ha
scores 84 points.]
Ha Ha... your pedometer scored
a total of 332 points.
[84 + 332 = 416 points.]
- Kim Jong Kook... 410 points.
- Yes?
[416 + 410 = 826 points.]
You have scored a total of 826 points.
Okay, we got it.
[Team Suk Jin and Ji Hyo still maintain
their lead with 686 points.]
[Team Jae Suk and Gary is eliminated
from the running with 832 points.]
Woo Bin, do you want to take your turn?
- Let's go with that song you like.
- Yeah, that's a great song.
[Which song will these two sing?]
[Kang Ha Neul gave a perfect portrayal
of Yoon Hyung Joo in his movie.]
[But how will the pedometer
affect his singing skills?]
We're going to sing the song,
'Expression of our love'.
[Slowing revving up the RMP.]
[Here we go!]
[The moves of two men who have
been holding back for too long.]
- Stay strong, Woo Bin!
- You can do this, Woo Bin!
[Ha Neul is to sing the song, and
Woo Bin is to focus on the pedometer.]
- Kang Ha Neul!
- Wow, he's a great singer.
[Their never-ending supply of energy-
We are the superstars of youth!]
[Ha Neul's energy keeps on going
all the way to the end.]
He's a really good singer.
[Ha Neul and Woo Bin make
a great team.]
[Team Woo Bin and Ha Neul's
song comes to an end.]
Encore!
[Please don't say such harsh words...]
How did he sing so well
while running around like that?
88 points!
- You totally put up a good fight!
- That was great.
[What did this dynamic duo score
on their pedometers?]
- Their lung sizes are just different.
- It's 'Lung capacity'.
- Kim Woo Bin... 332 points.
- Yes?
- Okay, they're going to be fine.
[88 + 332 = 420 points.]
I think they're going to be fine.
- But Kang Ha Neul is the problem.
- Why?
- Why is Ha Neul the problem?
- I will reveal his results.
- Ha Neul did a good job.
- He jumped around a lot.
- What is it?
- Is it over 400?
- 128? Is that for real?
- 128?
[Just how in the world did
this happen?]
I bet we pressed down on the button.
I bet we accidentally did
something wrong.
They had a total score of 548.
[Rule- Less than 600 points doesn't count.
Must remake their attempt.]
We're going to just add in
your new singing score.
We won't do the pedometer portion again,
and you must score a total of 138 points.
- Then Team Suk Jin will maintain the lead.
- Okay.
[Their two combined scores must be over
138 points for Team Suk Jin to win.]
- What are you going to sing?
- Emerald Castle's 'Footsteps'.
- Kwang Soo loves that song.
- I totally love that song!
- That's totally Kwang Soo's style.
- That's a real man's song.
- What do you think you're doing?
- You'd better knock it off.
This song is really popular with women.
[The song that stirs up the emotions
in a woman's heart.]
[How will Ha Neul do with the song?]
[Kang Ha Neul's singing voice is like
taking a stroll in Haneul (heaven).]
- What is the matter with you?
- I really love this song!
[His sweet voice and the longing stare
makes for a killer combo.]
[Explosion of lip-synching performance.]
[Slowing building up to the climax.]
[Just get away from each other!]
[Our Ha Neul is awesome!]
[Too overly empathetic.]
[There's the angelic voice.]
- Kang Ha Neul is the best!
- Great job.
Let's see what he scored.
[A very high score is being
expected by everyone.]
[Please show us what Ha Neul scored.]
- Seventy...
- What!
- What?
- What did he score?
[What did he score?]
[No way!]
- Woo Bin, I think it's up to you.
- How did he only score 71 points?
- You should've sang some backup.
- I can't do this anymore.
I think I'm spent.
- What is their score so far?
- The current score is...
Their current total is 619 points.
At least 67 points are needed...
[Woo Bin needs to score at least 67 points
in order for Team Suk Jin to win.]
- Woo Bin holds the key to Suk Jin's fate.
- You just need to score 68 points!
Please take care of me, Woo Bin!
Fighting!
[Time to reveal Woo Bin's singing skills.]
- It's all in your hands!
[67 points? I will blow that
out of the water with this song.]
[Everyone is jumping into the spirit
to cheer Woo Bin on.]
[Shall we get this party started?]
[Keeping up the nice beat]
[A man who knows his beat, and a
man who knows his trot- Kim Woo Bin.]
[Please score at least 67 points!]
[The fate of this mission hangs
on Kim Woo Bin's mic!]
'Like another fool in the day...'
[The vigor of youth-
Locked and loaded!]
[Fire!]
[Woo Bin's song will decide the
fate of their mission!]
[Woo Bin's song comes to an end
in the midst of all the chaos.]
- The machine said it wasn't bad.
- That has to be at least 80 points.
But didn't the machine also say
that he needs to work harder?
- I bet it's around 80 points.
- We've got the score.
- What's the score?
- We've put all our heart and soul into it.
We really gave it our best.
We worked together as one!
- Please...
- That was at least 80 points.
Here's Kim Woo Bin's score.
[What did Woo Bin score?]
[Did he... surpass his goal of 67 points?]
[Woo Bin scores a total of 82 points!]
[Woo Bin's song is a huge success!]
Why are we going through all this
trouble just for Suk Jin?
It's for the sake of all our victory!
- My win also means your end.
- Great job!
[Suk Jin still continues to maintain his
lead even after this mission.]
Kim Woo Bin, and Kang Ha Neul are now
in second place with a total of 701 points.
[Woo Bin and Ha Neul each earn 40 points
for having come in at second place.]
[Team Suk Jin and Ji Hyo- First place.
Earns 50 points each.]
- Then am I going to get 50 points?
- Yes, you've been given 50 points.
- Then I have a total of 80 points?
- Yes, that's correct.
You just need to earn 20 more points.
- Wow.
- Then he's all set.
[Will Woo Bin continue to lend a
helping hand even to the very end?]
At last, it's time for the
final mission.
I will now explain to you
what your final mission is going to be.
[A place that is filled with
impressive looking fossils.]
[A special setting
for today's final mission!]
Here's your final mission.
Your final mission is...
'Frightening name tag elimination.'
Frightening name tag elimination?
We will now start a name tag
elimination game.
Inside this museum...
there are a total of eight hunters
who are after your name tags.
Their goal will be to oust you
from the game.
- So we're not eliminating each other?
- I'm going to lose my mind.
- We're going to have to protect Suk Jin.
- You guys have to protect me.
- But there are five of them?
- Can we eliminate them, too?
You can earn a total of ten points for
each hunter's name tag that you eliminate.
[Hunter's name tags are worth
ten points each!]
- We have to help Suk Jin eliminate two.
- How are we going to do that!
- You guys can't leave me alone.
- What if it's that monster again?
What if it's the monster again?
[Five name tag hunters that are
far more fearsome than the monster!]
[Our names are...]
[Moo Sup Goon-
'Army of Fearsome'.]
Even the title of this mission is
'Frightening name tag elimination'.
I think we're really going to
spring into action today.
Is the mission over
once Suk Jin is eliminated?
- Yes, that would be the end of it.
- Then our whole race would be over.
My elimination would mean
the end of this race.
- You can't run away.
- No, I won't run away.
[A warning to the newbies
not to run away out of fear.]
If the situation becomes that dangerous,
then I'm going to run away first.
So you have to eliminate him
while I make my escape.
Then that's when you'll eliminate him.
You're just like how you appear
on the show!
Turn Big-nose into a winner... The name
tag elimination game will now start.
[Are you ready for the
frightening name tag elimination?]
Five, four, three, two, one... Start!
[Big-nose is the precious commodity that
Kkuk and Woo Bin have sworn to protect.]
- Don't worry, Suk Jin.
- You'll really have to help me.
I really haven't been very good
with the name tag elimination lately.
I keep grabbing the wrong thing.
[Ha Neul keeps following around
on Kwang Soo's tail.]
What the heck is that!
What is it!
- What is it!
- Go up the stairs!
[Everyone goes into a state of panic
after hearing the scream.]
[The person shouting out the screams is...]
What the heck is that!
[Junho's scream sends everyone
into a state of terror.]
[The scream sends these four members
into a cluster of terror.]
There was a guy who looked like
the grim reaper.
- What? He had his pants off?
- No, he had a black mask on his face.
[There he is!]
[Finally making his appearance is...]
[A member of the 'Army of Fearsome'.]
[Just then, Haroro discovers
the back of the army member.]
[A seven to one face-off.]
He's running away!
[The plan must be to eliminate
their prey one by one?]
Don't we need to eliminate them, too?
[An emergency meeting.]
- His build is no joke.
- Who is it?
- Is it a fighter?
- His build is no joke.
[The group continues to
quake with fear.]
- Let's all go as a group.
- There are seven of us right now.
Where did Suk Jin go? If he's
eliminated, then the race is over!
[Big-nose is busy practicing
his evasive moves.]
You have to do it right!
Woo Bin is doing a good job.
- This is how we're going to do it?
- Yes.
- You'll block him, and I'll evade?
- Keep your distance, to avoid being ousted.
We have to help Suk Jin
eliminate them, right?
- We have to eliminate some first.
- We have to bring down their numbers.
[They must eliminate at least
one member of the army first.]
- There!
- Where?
He's right over there.
Wow, he's really scary looking.
We can't run away!
[Everyone runs away at the speed of light
while shouting out that they can't run away.]
- We can't run away from them.
- We have to stick together.
- Some of us needs to attack.
- We have to stick together, and not run.
[Who should I eliminate first?]
- There are seven of us here.
- Come and get us.
- You can't take us all down.
[The group of seven is too much
even for the fearsome army member?]
[Time to retreat!]
[Two more army members join in!]
[An immediate U-Turn... and attacks!]
[Running Man members
are once again on the run.]
[The dead-end ends at an elevator.]
[There you all are.]
Fine, come on in.
Come in, if you'd like.
[I'll let you go this time.]
[What a relief!]
Who elbowed me while we
were running?
- Which one of you elbowed me?
- Maybe you were in the way.
[All the weaklings start the blame game.]
- We seriously have to stop running away.
- We're greater in numbers!
- I bet they'll be waiting for us.
[The group calms down,
and arrives back on the main floor.]
- Here he comes.
- Someone's behind us, too!
[The army members start to
make their appearance on the scene.]
- We have to stop being so afraid!
- Kwang Soo!
[Ha Neul sneaks behind the
column to hide.]
[Barely manages to escape danger
with the help of his members.]
[It's time to make our attack!]
[Another army member
runs over to the group!]
[Giraffe rushes over to block the attack.]
[While holding off
five members all on his own...]
[Huh?]
[Got it... no, lost it!]
[Haroro... successfully eliminates one!]
[One army member- Out!]
Here comes another one!
[Another army member rushes over
from the other side.]
[Gets a huge confidence boost
after ousting their first army member.]
[Both of his arms are pinned down
in the blink of an eye...]
[And Haroro attacks!]
Rip it off!
[Haroro already has the name tag in
hand, and Gary also reaches in?]
[Second army member is ousted
with Gary's assisted elimination!]
[What is going on here?
This isn't looking good for the army.]
[The brick house army member
launches his attack.]
[Faces off with all seven members!]
[It's time to put their
practice moves into action!]
[The army member is trying to
lure them into a corner.]
[What luck!]
[A chance for Big-nose to
score some points!]
That hurts!
Suk Jin has to rip it off!
[The army member continues to fend off
all ten members by himself!]
[Now... all they need is for Big-nose
to rip the name tag off of his back...]
[The name tag must be eliminated before
another army member shows up on the scene!]
[With every ounce of energy
he has in his body...]
[Big-nose successfully
eliminates the name tag!]
[Big-nose, with a total of 90 points!
Only one more name tag left to go!]
- Wow, you're unbelievably strong.
- Thank you for all your hard work.
[Only two more army members remain!]
I only need to eliminate
one more person.
- Okay, let's go.
- Hold on just a little bit longer.
- Everyone's doing a great job.
- Fighting!
[Greatest outcome they could hope for-
A total of three army members ousted already!]
[So, that's how you want to play the game?]
- Okay, let's go.
[Then we'll have to change our strategy.]
[The army members are nowhere
to be seen.]
[The group agrees to break off
to search in smaller groups.]
Should we go upstairs
to get a birds' eye view?
Think about meeting that
while you're in the water.
That thing is huge!
[Thinking about fending off the army
keeps them busy enough...]
That thing is absolutely terrifying.
It's not easy finding them
since there are only two of them left.
- Want to go towards the emergency exit?
- Okay, let's go.
[Do they hear a noise coming
from the emergency exits?]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are also busy
searching the emergency exit area.]
[The two remaining hunters were lying
in wait to ambush their prey.]
[Let's just escape for now!]
[Kwang Soo and Ha Neul follow
in the hunters' trail...]
[and suddenly finds themselves
in a two-on-two face-off.]
[Their hearts are still pounding
from the unexpected ambush attack.]
- No!
[Giraffe is easily eliminated...
and turns their attack on Ha Neul.]
Ha Neul, run!
Ha Neul!
Run away, Ha Neul!
[Everyone run towards the
sound of the Giraffe's screams...]
[But Ha Neul is already on the cusp
of being brought down by the hunters.]
[Lee Kwang Soo and Kang Ha Neul- Out!]
[The terrifying hunting scene
that they've just witnessed...]
[Has the other members
running away in fright.]
What we have to keep in mind is that
their goal is to eliminate Suk Jin.
- They win if they eliminate Suk Jin.
- Who just got ousted?
- Ha Neul.
- Ha Neul?
Did Kwang Soo get ousted?
I think Kwang Soo just got ousted.
Suk Jin, make sure to keep
this in mind.
It's okay if we get ousted, but if you do,
then this whole race is over.
That's why I have to eliminate one more
before anything happens to me.
[But where are the hunters hiding now?]
[Tightened security around Big-nose.]
So this is what it feels like to have
your own personal bodyguards.
You guys are doing a great job,
and you will be rewarded handsomely.
- Okay?
- Okay, thank you.
There will be gold.
Thank you.
I played the role of a bodyguard once
in one of my earlier sitcoms.
[What an ominous coincidence...]
This is the most anxious I've ever been
in all the times I've guested on this show.
[Jae Suk and Junho slip back
into their search mode.]
[Huh?]
[This is how you launch an
ambush attack.]
[Junho is brought down in
the blink of an eye!]
[We're going to get you back for
bringing down our fellow army members!]
[Junho and Jae Suk- Out!]
[What in the world is happening?]
- Ha Ha, what is it?
- There are two of them.
- We can't run away!
- Ha Ha, we can't run away!
- Let's just lead them out of here.
[It's imperative that the group faces the
hunters together before more are ousted!]
Wow, they're really scary.
[They must eliminate at least one hunter!]
- Since Gary's a good boxer...
What do my boxing skills
have anything to do with this?
You know that I'm not worth anything, right?
Can we just leave Gary here, and go?
[Can we just leave Gary here, and go?]
- What are you saying!
[By all means...]
[Goodbye, Gary.]
[Just get back to what you were doing.]
- Sorry, Gary!
- We'll just take our leave.
- We'll just be going now.
[What the...]
Goodbye.
Please take care of them for me.
[Haroro, and Blank Ji...
what will become of their fate?]
I think this is the worst betrayal I've ever
experienced in all five years on the show.
I seriously don't even know
what to say.
I feel about 200 times worse than any
betrayal I've experienced from Kwang Soo.
[And the pathetic fate
that his traitor is about to face...]
[Betraying his own member for
an extra five minutes in the game.]
Let's just go, Ji Hyo.
Let's just go home.
[Haroro, and Blank Ji are thus
brought to their demise.]
[The only ones left remaining in the game
are Big-nose, and his two bodyguards.]
[Time to prepare for the
final showdown!]
[Where could they be hiding?]
[Lie in wait in their hiding spot...
and launch an ambush attack!]
[It's three against two!
Time for the real face-off!]
[No matter what happens,
Big-nose must be protected!]
[The only place that
they haven't checked yet...]
[Huh?]
They're here.
[Before they can get into position,
the hunters' makes their approach.]
[Kkuk and Woo Bin, face-off
with the two hunters.]
[Kkuk is first to launch an attack!]
[The hunters lure them into a corner
where attacking will be more difficult.]
- Let's move back.
- Why am I even here?
Seriously, why am I even here?
I don't think this is going to work
as long as they stick together.
- Should I just go in the middle?
- What are you even saying?
- Why don't we do it like this?
- You can't use your moves on us like this.
We're going to unleash our own moves
if you guys keep doing this.
We're going to break out our own moves,
and start spitting on you.
[Kkuk launches another attack!]
No, get out of the way!
Am I getting in your way?
[Very tense atmosphere in the room.]
[Here's his chance!]
[The Tiger moves in!]
[One tiny moment is all it takes
to turn the battle around!]
[A hunter is successfully
brought down!]
You're amazing.
You're seriously amazing.
[Even his own teammates are amazed.]
- Good work, buddy.
[Only one hunter is left remaining.]
- We're going to lay ourselves down for you.
- Okay!
[The rest is up to Big-nose!]
[Three against one!
Team RM has the advantage!]
- No, get out of the way.
- Just tell me when.
It's time!
Get in here!
- You have to come this way.
- Move, Woo Bin.
[Even with the odds in their favor,
it's still not an easy situation.]
My fingers are pinched!
[You have to get in there, Big-nose!]
[The name tag is finally within his view!]
Move your foot out of the way!
You have to grab it!
[The name tag is within his grasp!]
[He did it!]
[But it isn't over yet!
A total shocker from Ji Suk Jin!]
Thank you so much for all
your efforts.
[Big-nose successfully earns
his 100 points!]
[With Big-nose's 100 points,
everyone celebrates their victory!]
[Big-nose, Woo Bin, and Kkuk enter
to celebrate their victory.]
They pinned him down, and I ripped it off.
- But there were two of them.
- Yes, but we got them both.
[A great victory with the
help of his two bodyguards.]
- Thank you!
- Thank you so much!
[The army of fearsome hunters
also makes their appearance.]
[Army's martial arts athletes.]
Wow, they're all so good looking.
[Lee Sang Soo, Cha In Ho, Jun Young Joon,
Yang Seung Ho, and Kim Chang Hyun.]
A big thank you to all five of you for coming
on the show, and making this so exciting.
- Thank you!
- You all did such a great job.
- Today's victory...
belongs to our Big-nose!
[Big-nose wins with a perfect score!]
- You won with the perfect score.
- Yes, that's correct.
Ten pieces of gold.
- But we have one question for you.
- Yes?
[There's something else?]
If you want to keep all ten pieces
of the gold to yourself
then you just have to shut the lid,
and walk out of here right now.
[What kind of an unexpected
event is this?]
- There are ten of you here right now.
- I wouldn't put it past him to do it.
But if you want this to be a group victory,
then just pass out the gold to other members.
[If he chooses friendship instead,
then he can share the gold with others.]
- What are you even hesitating about?
- Why are you even hesitating?
You worked hard, too,
but we brought you the victory.
Wait, stop straining your hands.
I even bled for you.
But I feel like there are other ways
I can make up for that.
- There are other shows in the future.
- Don't you remember us being a team?
- It's my decision to make, right?
- Yes.
[The decision is Big-nose's to make!]
Five...
[Will it be the friendship...]
[Or the gold?]
[What will Big-nose choose?]
[My friends, who have worked so hard
all day to help me obtain my victory...]
[Even in the face of all the drenching,
and the punishments...]
[And even through the sacrifice
of their own bodies...]
[With the singular goal of
helping me obtain my victory...]
[We've worked together as a team
to work towards one singular goal...]
[I'll see you guys next week.]
You've all just been used!
- I told you that I wouldn't put it past him.
- We totally got used.
He's not going to give it to us
after the cameras stop rolling?
No, that's not going to happen.
- He's getting in his car right now!
- His manager was waiting out front.
Isn't he going to come back in here?
[Did Suk Jin seriously just leave?]
- I think he really left.
Anyway, thank you to our three guests
for coming on our show today!
[Even though Big-nose may have left, a
huge thanks to Woo Bin, Junho, and Ha Neul!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
- I hope our friendship lasts forever!
- I wish you joy, and happiness.
We'll open the time capsule
in ten years.
- Who did this!
- Who took it!
[Their beauty outshines
the beauty of flowers.]
[But something about them
just seems a bit off?]
- Who did this!
- What's wrong with them!
[Suspicion, and ambition....]
- We have to find the treasure!
- Seriously?
[An unbelievable truth is revealed!]
[Next week's Running Man-
Don't trust these girls!]