[It's not uncommon to hear
them raise their voices]
[and they constantly
blame each other.]
[How can they be so different?]
[They couldn't trust
each other for five years...]
[And today!]
[A telepathic challenge
in an extreme situation!]
[They blame each other
for their continuous failures.]
[Will they be able to connect
with each other today?]
We're very tired now.
[The 24-Hour Observation Experiment:]
[Consensus.]
["A" studio in
Paju, Gyeonggido.]
- Hello!
- Hi!
- Hello, everyone!
- Hello!
- It's a personal room.
- It's a changing room!
Good morning!
[There are seven changing rooms]
Do you know what time it is?
[in the middle of the set.]
- It's noon.
- It's lunch time.
- What's this?
- What is it?
It looks cool.
Please change into
your team outfits, first.
Go into the room
with your name tag on it.
- And get changed.
- Right now?
It took us a while to get ready.
Why didn't you just say it before?
Please get changed.
Can't we stay a little longer?
- Is it a sponsor?
- Team outfits.
There are two outfits.
Pick one.
Which one do we wear?
- What?
- Do we just pick one?
Maybe the same colored
outfits are the same teams.
I should have worn a black hat,
I was matching for no reason.
- Just wear it!
- Don't try to match!
[They even complain
about picking an outfit.]
[Why are they asking us to choose?]
Are these the teams?
[Beige shirts: Ha Ha, Gary, Jong Kook.]
I should have wore a black hat.
[Khaki shirt: Ji Hyo.]
[Beige shirt: Kwang Soo.]
It's so hot!
[Beige shirt: Jae Suk and Suk Jin.]
[Ji Hyo's the only with
the khaki shirt on.]
[Am I the only one on my team?]
So what happens now?
- Are these the teams?
- Now, change back.
Pardon?
Change again.
We just got changed!
Do we have to match?
Please, change again.
[What's going on?]
I'm not changing!
I already said it.
- What are you saying?
- Who are you saying that to?
Is he a bully or what?
What are you doing?
I was saying it to you.
[They're fighting again!]
[We need to know
what the mission is]
[in order to change...]
What's going on?
- I'm done.
- Do we go out?
[Jong Kook keeps
his beige shirt on.]
It's hard changing back and forth.
Just come out, then!
I don't like the khaki color.
But I like Jong Kook even less.
Khaki's better than Jong Kook.
Are we on the same team, then?
- It doesn't work out, anyway.
- It's uneven.
Please change back.
I think we have to change
until we're matching!
Oh, really?
[Is that it?]
I'll be right here, so go change.
Wear the color you like.
We're going out.
We're coming out!
[Ha Ha, Jong Kook,
and Gary chose beige.]
- Jae Suk!
- Ji Hyo wore the same thing!
Ji Hyo wore it, too!
Gary and I never matched.
[How are we so different?]
Go back, and change!
Please change, again!
Just wear this!
You change!
You never changed!
Yeah, you change!
Listen to me!
You guys are fighting over that?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
and decide.
Okay, let's all play.
But since Ji Hyo's wearing this...
Just get a rep from
beige and one from khaki.
Why is nothing working out?
- Don't talk.
- Jong Kook doesn't have to be our rep!
- I'll do it.
- Kwang Soo, you go.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[They decided to match with beige.]
[I have to change again?]
Just go in!
Be cool about it!
- Jae Suk!
- I hate Jong Kook more than khaki!
What if this isn't the mission?
This is better than Jong Kook!
What if they tell us
to change again?
Then we'll do that.
Let's stop changing,
it's too troublesome!
- This color suits you better.
- Yeah, you look prettier.
[They're changing
into beige shirts.]
Is there a color decided already?
Don't talk if you
haven't changed much!
At least I'm wearing this.
We're all wearing this anyway.
I didn't say anything.
[Angry]
Don't be stubborn!
You have it all the way up your bum!
[He's so aggressive.]
Now, please go inside.
- Why?
- Maybe we did it right!
We were supposed to match.
[Now, into the unknown place...]
Do we go in?
[24 hour]
[observation]
[imprisonment]
[We've prepared
a special experiment lab.]
[We are inviting you to
this unfamiliar place.]
[Current time, 11:30 a.m.]
[The seven Running Man members enter.]
What's this?
It's refreshing!
- It's nice!
- What is it?
It looks like a show home.
Wow, it's so nice!
[It's an open and refreshing area.]
- There's "Ponpoko."
- It's my favorite!
I love it!
Wow, it's like an arcade!
[Confused]
I love this!
[A modern and simple interior
that captures their attention.]
[A special place that is made]
[just for the seven
Running Man members.]
There's a hammock!
It's an open space!
There are so many toys!
All the props that we've ever
used are all here.
- There's ping pong.
- Eraser!
There's a ping pong paddle.
This kind of place is my dream!
[Giraffe found his dream house.]
[They have so much to play with.]
There's an eraser.
I will hit your bum!
[Are we allowed to keep playing?]
What are we doing?
This is so nice!
It's so refreshing.
I want to live somewhere,
like this.
But it would be really cool
to live somewhere similar.
It would be nice.
I would want like
a gym installed here.
[They're slowing letting]
[their guard down.]
It would be so nice to have a gym!
Half-gym, half-house.
And bring friends, too.
- It would be cool to have a gym.
- Like the gyms in the U.S.A.
Don't talk about the U.S.A!
[They don't know
what is yet to come...]
Is it "The Battle for The Strongest"?
That scared me!
[The alarm went off all of a sudden.]
[What's going on?]
[24 hour, unanimous race.]
- "Unanimous"?
- What's a 24 hour unanimous race?
[24 hour unanimous race?]
So that's why they made us
wear matching shirts.
We need to be unanimous?
- 24 hours?
- Oh, my god.
[We're staying for 24 hours?]
[If all members are unanimous
within 24 hours, you'll succeed!]
You'll succeed if
you are unanimous.
So that's why!
We need to be unanimous.
If we are, then we leave?
Oh, we need to complete
three unanimous missions.
Don't they know
we're never unanimous?
We're never unanimous!
We're so different!
[If you fail, you must
leave after 24 hours!]
- After 24 hours...
- Oh my god.
[We have to leave after 24 hours?]
[Dumbfounded]
- Really?
- So, tomorrow morning?
[The 24-hour imprisonment starts now...]
Let's get it right!
We know each other.
- We know each other.
- I think we could do it.
We can be unanimous.
Almost all of us matched at the
beginning, with our clothes.
More than that,
we know each other's preferences.
But we could be wrong by guessing
each other's preferences.
We just need to choose either
Jong Kook's or Jae Suk's preference.
[They have to pick between
the polar opposites.]
We might be wrong,
trying to guess preferences.
What's happening?
[The countdown starts now!]
We're supposed to feed ourselves?
Really?
You see the
white acrylic box, right?
Please put all your
cellular devices inside.
Why our phones?
[They're not allowing any kind of
communication from the outside.]
It's not easy.
[They're stuck in
an unfamiliar place.]
Let's be unanimous!
[They need to know
each other's preferences.]
[They always blame each other!]
[For five years, there were
conflicts and betrayals.]
[An impossible mission
aimed at a consensus.]
[Everything depends on them.]
[Will they be able to succeed
in being unanimous?]
We can tell our managers to go out.
They probably already are.
I wish you would get along, today.
Let's show them we're family.
Let's show them!
Let's do it!
[What's their first mission?]
[First unanimity challenge.]
[Random box]
What is a random box?
Random box?
[All members need to
pick the same colored ball]
[in order to succeed.]
[Only three chances are given.]
[Discordance]
[Unanimous]
- We only have three chances.
- How is this going to work?
How do we do this?
This won't work!
But it sounds fun.
It's so intense.
My heart is fluttering.
There aren't any penalties?
It's going to be fun!
There are only
two balls in this box.
[There is a red and a blue ball.]
What if we're lucky
and we get it right all three times
and just go home?
You can turn air, like
"Animal Kingdom" or something.
Or we can play
"eliminate the staff's name tags."
You figure it out, on your own.
I'm nervous.
[First try at Random Box.]
You have three tries.
What if we get it right?
Round one!
- There are two!
- There are two balls!
[Nervous]
[Red ball or blue ball,
that is the question.]
[Five years worth of
teamwork and friendship.]
[Will all seven members
connect telepathically?]
[Did they connect...]
Round one!
[And the results?]
I'm going crazy!
[Blue ball: Jae Suk, Ha Ha,
Ji Hyo, Gary.]
[Red ball: Suk Jin,
Kwang Soo, Jong Kook.]
[They failed their first try!]
This is hard to match.
It's red, blue, red,
blue, red, blue.
Isn't this pretty good?
This was just a warm up.
This is how good we are.
So, there's two rounds left?
Please put it back in.
But Jong Kook and
Jae Suk are different.
[He's not letting go of the ball.]
Exchange boxes.
Take your hands out.
You're so smart.
I approve!
You're so smart!
We lost.
They've prepared a lot.
He knows what we're like.
Round two!
[You can see, right?]
[Which ball I'm holding?]
Ready, set!
What if we're right?
[They failed the second try.]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
are holding blue balls.]
[Kwang Soo, I only have you...]
The five of you
got it right, though!
That's so interesting.
We only have one try left.
We got three right
the first time, and then five.
Please, please!
Round three!
What color should we pick?
- What about blue?
- Blue?
Are we going with blue?
[Then I'll need to get blue as well...]
Ready, set!
I got it!
Let's go!
[Last try at Random Box.]
[If they fail this, they have to
wait until the next mission.]
[Will they get it on their last try?]
[They failed their first mission,
Random Box.]
[Blue ball: Gary, Ji Hyo,
Ha Ha, Jong Kook.]
[Red ball: Kwang Soo,
Jae Suk, Suk Jin.]
[The unlucky three.]
What's going on?
[Oh my god.]
[The punishers are here!]
[The incredible red devils]
[is charging!]
[Their first gift
is a water gun shower.]
[We will punish you for
not succeeding the mission!]
[They're so happy with
the shower service.]
[When did he hide here?]
We're sorry!
[They're restlessly shooting
their water guns.]
We're all wet!
Hey, Hwan Jin!
It's Hwan Jin!
Hwan Jin!
[We'll see you at the next mission.]
Who kept shooting
at my underwear?
Honestly!
Someone shot in my ear!
This is insane!
- Oh my god.
- Hwan Jin!
- Gary, why are you so clean?
- I was hiding here.
This is also luck.
Why aren't you wet?
They shoot really aggressively.
It's so cold!
Turn the AC off!
Why didn't you mention this earlier?
[They're complaining about
the punishers.]
The next mission is in an hour!
An hour later?
[The next mission
will be in an hour.]
We have to do something for an hour,
so we're not bored.
- We need to do something.
- You're so cruel.
[Mental breakdown]
Next time Jong Kook,
you take it and shoot them.
I should.
I didn't think they
would shoot for so long.
I remember all of your faces!
Hwan Jin is the leader.
I thought he was a ninja turtle!
[Ji Hyo... sorry for
running away by myself.]
Wow, honestly.
Please turn the AC off.
- This is nonsense.
- This is absurd.
What do we do?
This is a bolt out of the blue!
Do they keep coming
if we get it wrong?
What if we actually
leave tomorrow morning?
Right?
We're going to be a disaster.
This isn't easy.
How do we...
There's still...
There's an hour left.
Twenty minutes passed?
It's only been 20 minutes
since all of this happened?
If we don't do anything,
time won't pass.
- It'll pass by slowly.
- Do we just stay here?
We just have free time.
Should we make something to eat?
There's an arcade and stuff.
We can just rest and stuff.
For an hour?
What do we do for an hour?
[Twenty minutes after the seven]
[Running Man members
have been imprisoned.]
I used to be so good at this,
back in the day.
We need to wait a while.
[Category number one]
[passing time with art.]
- Do you know this?
- Ji Hyo, what did you bring?
A coloring book.
[Her masterpiece]
[with coloring pencils.]
There's nothing to do...
What are you doing?
Join in.
- What's up?
- That surprised me.
What are you guys doing?
I like it here.
I don't see why we have to get out.
[Category number two:
Self-regulation and free time.]
[Category number three: Daydream.]
There's nothing to do
without my phone.
There's really nothing to do.
[Category number four:]
[Puzzles.]
[A puzzle is the best way to pass time.]
[Focused, focused]
[Puzzles passes by time slowly]
[very, very slowly.]
[Category number five:
Indoor sport.]
[The two guys got rackets
because they can't stay still.]
Jae Suk, be careful!
[Huh, why?]
- Be careful!
- Okay.
[Jae Suk goes back to
focusing on badminton.]
Ji Hyo, do you like puzzles?
Jae Suk!
- Please, don't do that.
- It's not on purpose.
Jae Suk!
Don't do that!
For real, don't do it!
Gary, the birdie
keeps coming here!
- No, do it later!
- The birdie keeps coming!
[Everyone's doing fine.]
Jae Suk, please!
Time's actually passing by.
[It's just before the mission time!]
There are 20 seconds left!
- Oh really?
- Should we sit?
- We're good to go!
[Will we complete our
first unanimous mission?]
Good luck!
For real this time!
Let's empty our minds.
Wow, you guys got a lot done.
Two, one!
[What is the second
unanimous mission?]
[Second challenge of
the unanimity race.]
It's going off!
[Act it out.]
What is it?
Act it out?
[When a word is said, all members
have to act out the same pose.]
I think we can do this one.
It's telepathy!
- Wow, this is...
- Good luck!
[We will succeed this time!]
Ready...
[Super focused]
[Their first word is?]
A heart!
One, two, three!
[Ta-da]
[Oh my]
One, two, three!
[Oh my god!]
He's so annoying!
[He made a tiny finger heart.]
- He's so annoying!
- Why?
[Who got it wrong?]
[What did I just do?]
No, this is...
- But this heart...
- Everyone knows this!
Jae Suk, the heart!
- It's this!
- Who does this, nowadays?
No, but it's a habit now...
[He's become the sinner
thanks to his habits.]
You have to do it this way!
Okay, this is the next round!
Everyone's legs even
did the same thing!
It looks like I did it on purpose!
It's just a habit...
What is this!
It was so sudden.
I really didn't do it on purpose!
[What is their second word?]
Selfie!
[Selfie?]
One, two, three!
[The only left-handed.]
[Wrong!]
Why?
Why did you use your left hand?
It should be right, technically.
Are you left-handed?
Why are you so mad?
Your heart is weirder!
Everyone, look outside!
[A frightening silhouette.]
I forgot about them!
This your last chance!
Let's focus!
[What is their third word?]
We'll give you the last one!
Running Man!
[That's easy, if it's Running Man...]
One, two, three!
[All in different directions.]
[They failed the second mission.]
[They're coming!]
[The evacuation alarm is on.]
[Red devils, charge!]
[They try getting away
through the staff.]
[Rush in]
[Their second gift is a
toy mallet attack.]
[They don't exclude
beautiful women, either.]
[They chase them down
to the corners.]
[Smack!]
[No matter how much they complain,
they just hammer away.]
Go away!
[He's protecting his puzzle.]
Wow, they hit really hard!
[Smack!]
[That's bonus!]
[Take me with you!]
That's Gap Jin!
[Angry, angry]
Kwang Soo, come here!
Come here!
You blocked me from getting out!
Just because you want to live?
I did it on accident.
Did it get ruined?
[I worked on it, so hard.]
Who hit me as they were leaving?
[He gave a head massage
as he was leaving.]
Gap Jin was there!
I was surprised, too!
How are you taking care
of your manager?
He's very cooperative.
How can you run away
by yourself, like that?
You're so annoying!
This is annoying!
- What is this?
- How's that annoying?
I'm going to send you a
picture of this every morning.
Just your fingers!
It's so horrendous!
That's so terrible!
[Just the thought
of it is horrifying.]
[Start your morning with
Grasshopper's heart!]
Good morning!
My god, really.
But the heart was
really close, wasn't it?
- Yes.
- The heart was so easy!
It's become a habit!
A heart should be posed like this!
I'll do that from now on!
Don't use the other way, ever again.
Oh my god!
You're just picking on me!
- You got selfie wrong!
- Go reflect on your actions.
We are.
[Please forgive us.]
Do we rest, now?
You have 51 minutes
until your next mission.
What do we do now?
We go back to what we were doing.
Order food for us.
No, but seriously.
[While Gary gets
ready for his puzzle]
Gary's totally into it!
I'm going to play ping pong.
Let's play doubles!
[They get ready for a badminton match.]
[They're using the divider as a net.]
[They're hosting
a badminton rally.]
Let's have a punishment!
How about slapping the forehead?
- Slapping the forehead.
- Okay!
- How many points?
- 15 points.
It'll be quick.
[Game, start!]
[Jae Suk and Ha Ha vs.
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.]
Suk Jin!
[With Jae Suk's mistake,
they lost a point.]
It's okay.
[Jae Suk's error, once again.]
[Don't worry,
it's only the beginning!]
Okay, ready?
Go!
I couldn't see it.
Eight versus five!
12 versus 10!
I'm going crazy!
[Time's passing by quickly.]
[Jae Suk and Ha Ha 13
vs. Suk Jin and Kwang Soo 12.]
That's good!
Yeah!
Smash!
[Grasshopper's smash.]
- Out!
- In!
[It is now 14 vs. 13.]
This one is match point.
[We will slap your foreheads.]
Stubborn badminton.
Everyone just wants
to hit it hard.
Suk Jin!
[Just then, the shuttlecock
flies behind Suk Jin!]
[Nice receive!]
[Jae Suk's smash.]
It's over!
[Jae Suk and Ha Ha won the match.]
- It's over!
- It hit the floor, then the wall.
- Please offer us your foreheads.
- Kneel down.
[Their punishment
continues right away.]
[They're glued to the puzzle.]
Just crouch.
Since this is a punishment...
Obviously, I know but...
- Just be reasonable.
- Don't worry.
It'll finish in less than a second.
It'll start here and finish there.
Ready!
This is my first time.
[Forehead smash
like a bolt of lightning.]
From the right to the left.
From right to left.
[Please go easy on me!]
I told you, from right to left.
Wow, that woke me up.
Please get up.
[They're focused on their puzzle despite
what's happening around them.]
This is simple.
That's good.
- Water?
- You never mentioned this!
This sticks well.
It'll hit well.
It'll finish quickly.
Would you like a smash?
It's because of the water.
[Please go easy...]
The sound is louder with water.
[Dizzy, dizzy]
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
[I can't let it go.]
Let's do it again!
[Giraffe is still in shock.]
This is only the beginning.
Rock-paper-scissors isn't fun.
Let's play a game.
My ears were ringing
when I got hit.
[Big Nose is getting something.]
The sound is just loud.
Kwang Soo!
Are you confident with jegichagi?
(similar to hacky sack)
Should we play foot
volleyball with that?
Don't change the subject!
You're so funny.
- You two come here.
- Let's do something!
Let's do something!
Let's slap foreheads again,
with this.
It's not fun if it's too frequent.
I don't like things
getting personal.
I hate personal things.
I hate it the most.
People who get emotional
when they play games...
Let's just play it once!
[He's trying to make a deal
by touching him.]
Just this once!
[They're unbelievable.]
Let's just play this for once!
Listen to Suk Jin!
He's asking for it this badly!
I'm talking to you!
Let's just play this!
Let's play catch!
- Maybe you can use the pot.
- Why don't you listen to me?
[Overheating]
Wouldn't it be fun?
It'll fall between legs.
Sounds fun, right?
Imagine it will fall in between legs!
Look at them.
They don't care what we do.
Just use the pot.
- Don't we need to order something?
- Yes, we're hungry.
[We're confined,
but let us eat at least...]
[Thanks to Easy Brothers,
they've failed the game of Yut mission.]
Isn't this tasty?
[They ordered spicy seafood noodle soup
and sweet and sour pork unanimously.]
Even if I don't have my cell phone,
it's not too bad when we're together.
Since we don't look at the our phones,
we get to see each other's faces.
Maybe, this race is for that purpose.
You can tell each
other's personalities.
I can't stand still
doing nothing.
Me, too.
Do you think we can escape today?
We haven't succeeded at all, right?
If only I was able to make a heart...
The selfie was very close, too.
Yes, but heart was worse.
The two "Infinite Challenge" members
ruined it for the rest of us.
What are you talking about?
The two members of "Infinite Challenge"
made a mistake on Running Man.
It's not like you did very well today.
While you played the game of Yut.
That was your fault!
[All of a sudden,
it's Kwang Soo's fault.]
You flipped it.
I did?
When you play the game of Yut,
you only have two choices.
- That was my fault?
- Whatever that is, it's your fault.
Unlucky people like us
can't play games of luck.
You should go to a house of prayer
or get an exorcism.
I can't believe how unlucky they are.
Maybe you need to hire a shaman.
By the way, it's very delicious.
[The finishes eating while bickering.]
This is very nice meal.
[He finishes the spicy
seafood noodle.]
[The time left until the escape]
[The time flies while they
failed a few missions and ate.]
Maybe we're too relaxed.
- We only have seven minutes left.
- Seven minutes?
- We did a good job at killing time.
- Since we ate.
I started to like this place.
- That's true.
- This place is nice.
You should try to escape!
We're going to give you missions that
you can reduce an hour from now on.
We have many kinds of missions.
One of them is Pop-up Pirate
as we've always played it.
It's over there.
Since there are seven people
we'll reduce one hour, if it
doesn't pop up for two rounds.
There are many people
that make it pop at once!
[Mission impossible]
That's really difficult!
How is it possible to make it last?
It's ready!
[Pop-up Pirate starts!]
For two rounds...
- It's scary.
- Please, start the game.
Do you want to go first, Kwang Soo?
I'll do it first.
[Trying to stay on the safe side.]
[Even though we fail at it,
I don't want to be the one...]
[How is it even possible?]
Seriously!
Kwang Soo!
[The god of misfortune]
What just happened?
Is it possible?
What's wrong with you?
Wow...
You're worthy of respect.
[They fail to get a chance.]
He's truly cack-handed.
[The worst cack-handed man]
How am I going to live
the rest of my life?
[They're all standing up now.]
[They're standing up for the mission.]
[What will the next mission be?]
[Unanimous strike]
When the timer hits zero,
everyone throws a ball.
You'll succeed if you bowl a strike.
That's bowling!
You'll carry out this mission outside.
It's been a while!
It's like "Old Boy"!
They made a bowling alley.
It's bowling!
[A giant bowling alley]
It's incredible!
Running Man is the best!
[Will they be able to reach unanimity
at this huge bowling alley?]
They're here again.
- Gap Jin!
- It's water gun again.
Just push it straight.
I'll be in the middle.
I'm good at bowling.
Stand in the middle, Suk Jin.
Should I stand in the middle?
When Suk Jin says he's good at
something, he's usually not good.
- His pose isn't that good.
- I have experience.
Look, Gap Jin is aiming for you.
[Aren't you hot, Jong Kook?]
Earlier, you shot a lot of water.
Let's steal their water gun
if we succeed at it.
Get ready!
We need to make it straight
toward the pins.
- Let's start walking from three.
- Three, two, one.
That's too fast.
Walk slowly.
Jong Kook and Suk Jin
should hit it fast.
This is a good chance!
[Now is the chance!]
Gary!
[The members have proven
their bowling skills in the past.]
[They have a chance of success
if they time it right.]
Get ready!
[Challenge to win Unanimous Strike]
- Fight!
We need to roll it at zero.
Someone should read the timer.
- Fight!
[The countdown starts!]
Three, two, one!
[Everyone should think
the same and bowl.]
[This is the chance!]
One, throw!
[They throw at the same time.]
[Kkuk and Suk Jin throws it hard,
and the the rest throws it weak.]
[The bowling balls should not
crash into each other.]
[Please, please, please...
get a strike!]
It looks good!
[Will they knock down all the pins?]
[Hit, hit, hit]
Good, good!
[There's only one pin left!]
[Please!]
We did it!
[Strike!]
[They've reached their
first unanimity.]
[The Consensus Race]
[They've completed one out of three.]
[Laughing at the punishers.]
We almost failed.
Who threw the last ball?
Me, me, me!
[Gary's ball hit the last pin.]
Out of three chances
you've completed one.
[They have two more to go.]
[They re-enter proudly
after their first success.]
[What are we going to do
until the next mission?]
If we put another divider.
We can play foot volleyball.
I thought it was possible,
and we actually did it.
We can do it unless
we need to win by luck.
We're good at many things.
We could've done two
if it wasn't for this.
[Are they already giving
out another mission?]
What is it?
[Is it something different
than other missions?]
A coin falls into the fish tank!
All seven members should put
a coin in the dish inside a fish tank.
We can practice for an hour.
- For an hour?
- We can start practicing now.
Oh, in that fish tank?
- It looks easy.
- That's a big tank.
They told us to practice
for an hour, it must be hard.
- Don't you think so?
- We just need to throw it, don't we?
Is that difficult?
[Jae Suk tries throwing a coin.]
You need to control your power.
[A coin moves around because
of the resistance of the water.]
[The stronger they throw,
the more resistant the water gets.]
[It's simple but difficult.]
[Everyone has a different
method of tossing it.]
- It's too difficult.
- This is the game that's by luck.
[The goddess of fortune,
Blank Ji attempts.]
She's good at everything.
[She's lucky Blank Ji, indeed!]
What did I just do?
Why is she good at this?
[Will all seven of them be successful?]
[The conclusion is that
they need to practice.]
We shouldn't push the coin.
I can't do it at all.
Your coin is not even close, Suk Jin.
This upsets me.
Wouldn't it be possible
to see the flow of the water?
I did it!
[He made it.]
[Okay!
I've got the hang of it.]
It's in the right direction now.
- Look!
- You figured it out.
Who did it?
It's not always the same, but...
from here...
[Yoo Jae Suk's coin technique school]
[I admire you, Jae Suk!]
Please teach me.
Don't try putting it there.
[Let me try, give me the coin.]
You know how to do it.
Let me try it once.
Suk Jin, can I try it once?
[He can't hear it.]
Let Gary practice, too.
[Talking isn't going to work.]
[I need to practice, too...]
[Gary succeeded, too.]
Jae Suk's method is the best.
Isn't that the best?
- Can we put five at once?
- No!
[He refuses so fast.]
You could've consider it.
Because that doesn't even make sense.
[I'm sorry, my answer is no.]
Do you just say no to
whatever Kwang Soo say?
I didn't even finish my sentence.
[Big Nose keeps
bouncing a table tennis ball.]
- Suk Jin's good at it.
- Aren't I?
I can say I'm good at it confidently.
- How many times did you do it?
- I think I did about 30 times.
If Hyun Woo does it at home,
he stops him.
- [Suk Jin, stop!]
- Hyun Woo, stop it!
[Monday Couple fell into the puzzle.]
I think I've found my talent!
I still have the good energy
from the bowling.
I did it!
[At that time!]
[The alarm bell rings.]
You don't need to practice.
Everyone, come over here.
You don't have to do it in a hurry.
You can have five coins each.
Start with the those
who are good at it.
Jae Suk should start first.
If one person fails,
that's the end of it.
Should I go first, then?
Someone who can do it should start.
- Gary will start.
- I need to put one out of five, right?
- Wait a moment.
- I've succeeded twice in a row.
[Remember how I did it
when I was practicing...]
- Say that you'll challenge.
- Challenge!
[Resolutely determined]
We'll do it right away.
I'm happy as if I won
a gold medal at the Olympics.
[The second runner, Kwang Soo]
When we have a good luck,
we need to quickly do it.
Oh, I see.
[He realizes his mistake
quickly after he fails.]
[They're already having a crisis.]
Can I take a break?
Take a break.
Don't bend your wrist,
just release it from straight up.
Relax your hand as much as possible.
[He fails three times out of five.]
Take a break!
Just take a break for
two weeks from the show.
[You need an exorcism...]
How can you be so unlucky?
You've already failed three times.
[Kwang Soo takes a break]
[and the Coin Master
Jae Suk challenges.]
He's the best among us.
[His second attempt]
[It was close.]
It's okay.
What good is it doing it well
only when you practice?
Do it well.
You should get it this time.
He made it!
Next!
[Gary and Jae Suk]
You need to do it close.
- It doesn't matter
- if you practiced it or not.
He practiced the least.
He enjoyed his free time.
[Fail]
Do it slowly.
Don't miss your chances like that.
- Jae Suk seized the chance.
- I'm doing my best.
He's such a trouble maker.
The water is shaking.
Why did you cover the camera?
Don't put your hand in the water.
What do I do?
- Just do it.
- He doesn't know the basics.
- Ah!
- Just move aside.
Wasn't that pretty close?
[Jong Kook's first attempt]
It's so difficult.
[It was close...]
I think it'll be difficult
to give out the coins.
[Jong Kook attempts right away.]
[Gary, Jae Suk and Jong Kook
succeeded.]
Pushing is okay, too.
[Ha Ha fails at his first attempt.]
I think he will do it this time.
[He almost succeeded
at the second attempt.]
I can feel it now.
I'll do it this time.
Just do it boldly!
Don't be nervous.
[Goal in!]
Okay, okay!
We can do it.
One coin left?
I think it's better when
it falls straight.
Don't make it bend.
It's too close.
Did it get in?
Wow!
Do it properly!
[Now, only Kwang Soo
and Ji Hyo are left.]
I'll do it first.
She did it earlier.
[Her first attempt out of five.]
[She got lucky during the practice.]
[Will she be lucky for the real game?]
[Succeeded at once!]
[Gary, Jae Suk, Jong Kook,
Ha Ha, Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo]
[So much pressure!]
Why did you!
Good job, Ji Hyo!
[She's lucky Blank Ji!]
We didn't expect that.
[The only left is
the Variable Kwang Soo.]
[It's all in Kwang Soo's hand.]
[How did I get here again?]
[His misfortune continued
for the past five years.]
[His misfortune wasn't only his.]
[He always ends up at the point
where they decide for victory.]
[Many times, he lost the chance
of winning for his team.]
[Even today, he blew up
their chance with his misfortune.]
[He doesn't want to affect
the fate of the team any more.]
[But, he's doing it again.]
[He has only two coins.]
Wait for him.
[Will he be able to]
[break the chain of misfortune
and save the team this time?]
[A perfect success!]
[The miracle of the Variable!]
[Their second consensus!]
[What a nail-biter!]
[The Consensus Race]
[They've completed two out of three.]
Let's play foot volleyball.
- Let's bet a forehead slap.
- I like it!
We need chairs.
[They want to kill the time.]
I brought chairs.
Let's tie the net around the chairs.
- Let me see.
- We can tape it.
[They're making their
own foot volleyball net.]
[If they applied themselves
to studying this much]
[they could've gone to Harvard.]
Gary put a lot of pieces.
Don't you want to finish the puzzle?
[For seven hours, he's found out
the true meaning of jigsaw puzzles.]
[A foot volleyball court is completed.]
This is for the forehead slap.
Of course.
[Wait and see...]
[You insulted my forehead.]
[I think my forehead will hurt
when it rains.]
[Vengeance is mine.]
[They treasure the puzzle
and move it to a shelter.]
[Carefully]
Ji Hyo, sit over here.
[Monday Couple's first joint asset,
the jigsaw puzzle]
They treat it like their child.
[Three on three]
[The forehead cup foot volleyball]
You need a good player.
[Gary joins Big Nose and Giraffe.]
[Kkuk joins Grasshopper and Ha Ha.]
Win a forehead slap!
Let's play service game.
Let's decide who's going to serve.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I lost.
We'll just play service game.
Play fair!
[Grasshopper's team
vs. Big Nose's team]
We're doing all sorts of things today.
Take it, Kwang Soo!
- Nice!
- Out!
You said it's going
to be a service game.
[We won the serve by
playing rock-paper-scissors...]
You said we'll play a service game!
[They must hate to be slapped
on their forehead badly.]
No one scored, then.
[They restart the game.]
Out!
- In!
- It was on the line.
- Good!
- Head, head!
I told you head the ball!
One to zero!
- How much should we score?
- 15.
[Don't forget,
your skull is on the line!]
It's one to zero.
[Big Nose's team's serve.]
Again!
We have two chances to serve.
You're supposed to have two chances.
[Big Nose's second serve.]
Look carefully, Ha Ha.
- The ball come toward you.
- What are you going to do?
- My, my, my!
- Your, you!
[Don't touch the ball!]
My, my, my!
[Finally, it's a golden chance!]
[With the pain on his forehead...]
[take that!]
- Oh, damn it.
- Fail!
[What's wrong with me?]
That's what happens
when you're greedy.
One to one!
Are you trying to be funny?
Oh, my puzzle!
[My puzzle!]
Puzzle, puzzle!
Don't touch my puzzle!
My puzzle!
[Do you know how hard that was?]
[I've been assembling
it for seven hours]
[with Ji Hyo...]
[We put so much effort.]
They've doing it for the whole day.
He's having a mental breakdown.
[Hard work is actually wasted.]
Gary and Ji Hyo built it
for the whole day.
I'm going to win this.
Let's stop joking and
play it seriously.
- Two to one.
- I'm going to receive it.
You need to receive the serve.
I'm good at it.
I passed it like that.
Out!
[Powerful shot]
[Giraffe's "Unstoppable High kick"]
(Sitcom)
- Three to one?
- I'll make the ball float, so spike it.
Spike...
[A belly button trapping?]
Why?
[And he's talking about spike?]
Four to one!
- It's four to one!
- They're so bad.
[Again!]
Get the ball!
He received it.
[Wobble]
[Splayed apart]
- I'm sorry, Garry.
- This is frustrating.
Gary, I'll do better.
Why am I playing on this team?
- He's wrecked.
- Five to one!
[Grasshopper: Big Nose]
[5:1]
In!
The best play should've been
positioned over there!
It's out!
[Grasshopper: Big Nose]
[8:4]
My!
Kwang Soo!
Good!
It's a little too high, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
[Slip]
[Fall]
[Bowling Pin Brothers]
[They fell in sync.]
It's worth the photogenic award.
They fell as if they were bowling pins.
Match point!
[9: 4]
Let's just get slapped.
[He hit the ball with his face.]
It's over.
- Suk Jin!
- It's supposed to be over.
Because he hit the ball twice.
The umpire doesn't say anything.
But why keep passing
the ball to Kwang Soo?
[Gary flies]
[10: 4]
We won!
I'm sorry, Garry.
It's my fault!
[Total wreck]
Why do I belong this team?
Gary has no reason to join that team.
[It's time for the slap?]
Time to get beat up.
Take a seat.
We have a very inflexible player.
- I want to get slapped by him.
- No, Jae Suk will slap me.
We'll pick.
We'll play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Nice shot!
I want Jae Suk!
[Giraffe picked Jae Suk first.]
Yeah!
Ha Ha!
[Gary picked Ha Ha.]
He's going to slap you quietly.
It won't even be funny.
We'll start slapping.
We have two minutes left.
It's not a flick but a slap?
Ready?
- You know I helped you to win...
- I'll count.
One!
[Slap!]
[High five!]
Good night!
[Hair-raising]
It's Gary's turn.
I should have picked Jong Kook.
Wait a minute.
Ready?
- Dong Hun, think about our friendship.
- I won't hit you hard.
Our friendship...
think about it.
[Slap]
[Take the friendship!]
[It sounded like a wooden mallet.]
I didn't hit you hard.
That wasn't so bad.
You're lucky.
[Big Nose is extremely nervous.]
Did you pee, Gary?
Gary's crying.
I'm not crying because it hurts.
I'm crying because I'm upset.
It's Suk Jin's turn.
- My eyes hurt.
- I might die!
Gary's crying!
I'm going to hit you like this.
Time's up!
[Is Big Nose saved by the bell?]
- No, no.
- Time is up.
I'll hit like this.
I'll just touch it like this.
It won't be hard.
Let's do it now.
Please count for me.
One, two!
That was too weak!
He's too kind.
- He didn't want to hurt him.
- It hurts so much!
Ha Ha's slap was...
- What's the mission?
- "Her hair's rear-ly beautiful."
Wear a wig in the changing room,
and come out.
I think there will be two wigs.
VJs can go out first.
A long wig and a short wig...
Pick the shortest wig.
The shortest.
[We'll pick the shortest wig
and go home for sure!]
- Please stand in front of your name.
- Yes.
I'll count to three.
Wear a wig inside, and come out.
We can get out
if we succeed at it.
You need to come out
at the same time.
This is a variety show.
We can go home
if we wear the same wig.
- You only have one chance.
- Just once?
You can go in now.
- We have only chance.
- I can't open it.
This drives me crazy.
This is confusing.
[There are five wigs inside.]
[Will they be able to reach a consensus?]
[Which one is the shortest
or funniest?]
- This is...
- confusing!
- It's confusing.
- I told you.
[It should be the shortest.]
This is the only one.
[It's for the variety show, right?]
[What will be the result?]
- Wait a moment!
- Three
two
one!
Please come out!
[Time's up.]
[Partially bald head]
[Kwang Soo, Jae Suk]
[Gary]
[Partially bald head]
[Jong Kook]
[Ha Ha]
Please come out!
[Big Nose with funky
afro hairstyle appears.]
[Blank Ji with helmet-like
hair appears.]
[They fail to reach unanimity.]
[Their trick fails.]
This is a variety show!
I told you to get the shortest one.
[What will be the
punishment this time?]
- What are they doing?
- Only one!
Only one!
I don't know what it is but, Jong Kook!
Jong Kook!
I think they're saying only
one will be punished.
Go fight against them.
One person?
Why did you push me?
You can win.
You're the best game player among us.
Wait, I think there's an
oriental medical doctor.
Do I have to get an acupressure
or acupuncture treatment?
[Bingo!]
Only one!
[Kim Hyung Jun]
[Sport Massage Therapist]
Suk Jin, you won't feel hurt.
Did you decide?
It's going to be Suk Jin.
[All of a sudden, they pick Suk Jin.]
[Thank you for choosing me.]
You're not very healthy.
I can't feel any
strength from his slap.
Please lie down on your side.
- Without a massage chair?
- Yes.
[Can he really give
him a punishment?]
He looks familiar.
I have lower back pain.
You should be careful.
Tell me if it hurts.
- Ahhh!
- Is that hurt?
Dang...
[Back, legs... and dang?]
Doctor, are you kidding me?
[He strongly refuses the massage.]
[Embarrassed]
What are you doing?
It's acupressure!
Why did you push him?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to...
What's this?
Is it acupressure?
Can I switch with someone?
[Curious Giraffe comes
forward for the punishment.]
- Pelvis...
- I've never gotten a massage for pelvis.
You're getting it today.
[Big Nose is a crybaby,
it can't be that painful...]
[A touch from the hell.]
He's very persistent, too.
[Go away!]
Is it really that hurt?
He can't move.
Get up.
[Stiff out of shock]
We're filming right now.
Don't act like this.
Why are his hands stiff?
Doctor...
- Is it that hurt?
- Do you want to try?
Try it, it's a good pain.
I also want to try pelvis massage.
It's really good.
- I know it really hurts.
- I'm not joking!
[Grasshopper takes on
the punishment.]
[Wobble]
Wait!
This is...
Don't make a sad face like that.
I won't give you up.
Wow, Jae Suk almost cursed!
[Scream]
[Satisfied]
I wonder how hurt it is.
Try Jong Kook.
I've receive the treatment many times.
- Long time ago.
- Still, you should try.
I think you have a problem
with your hip joint.
You're right.
I do.
[He's good.]
Which side should I lie on?
This leg is a bit shorter.
- Don't let him move.
- Wait!
[I can't do this.]
You need to hold him down.
[They captures Tiger.]
[Tiger keeps crying while
they're trying to cure him.]
[Cry]
[Bite]
[Tiger shares his pain with Giraffe.]
[Long live, Tiger Kkuk!]
[It's Ha Ha's turn.]
You little!
Oh, no, mister!
This is insane!
[Ha Ha's pelvis is blessed.]
Gary's turn.
[Gary also screams out of joy.]
Stop, stop it!
That's too deep!
[What a bold touch!]
Wait!
Let's give him a round of applause.
[Thank you so much for
the healthy punishment.]
[We will never forget your touch...]
[Currently, they've reached
two consensuses.]
[If they keep failing,
they can go home in 15 hours.]
We're getting tired now.
Do you want to bet for some snacks?
Snacks and beverages.
- What do you want to bet?
- Give us some water.
Let's bet for an hour.
- For an hour?
- No, Haroro.
Let's not do that.
- Only 10 minutes left for the next.
- Let's eat some snacks.
Just buy some on the way home.
You guys are so stiff!
If you didn't put your left hand up,
we could've gone home.
Mister, you made a tiny finger heart!
Get out, both of you!
- Who came out with a wrong wig?
- Ji Hyo and...
- It was Suk Jin.
- Five of you were wrong!
[Shifting a viewpoint!]
[Cheeky]
Then what about me?
Then, all six of you
made a wrong heart.
I want to eat something like...
- Choco Pie.
- Gummy bears.
I want some ice cream.
- Some water.
- Shaved ice with red bean!
I was going to say it.
- Don't lie.
- I'm serious.
[They talk like someone
who just started their army service.]
- I'll eat that when I'm done.
- Don't leap into a fire pit.
[We really want to get out...]
Four, three, two, one!
[It's the mission time.]
What is it?
[It's back again!]
[What will the mission be?]
From now on, you can
go out for an hour.
Go out for an hour?
[What's this all about?]
We can go out for an hour?
[We'll announce an
enormous benefit after an hour.]
[Pick your cell phone and allowance.]
Seriously?
We can go out?
What is it?
- I don't want to leave.
- You're giving us allowance?
I feel lazy to go out.
We can really go out?
- For sure?
- Go out?
Can we eat with this money?
We can go out and eat.
Why did you suggest to bet?
I told you to be patient!
That's right!
We even have allowance!
[They almost bet for an hour.]
We can get out and buy
something with this money!
You don't have a hunch!
They gave us a lot of money.
Why?
Why do they tell us to go out?
I don't know.
Is there a spy here?
We can go anywhere?
The situation is somewhat similar
to that nap for an hour.
They're not going to make
someone as spy, are they?
Well, it's good to be outside.
I feel relieved.
- The air is fresh.
- It's good to breath in fresh air.
How long has it been?
Let's get going!
Where should we go?
- Should we all go together?
- Where are we going?
Where do they want us to go?
- Let's go.
- Suk Jin, where are you heading now?
I don't know.
Do you want to go with me?
Is it really okay to
leave only with VJs?
Can we go together?
[Monday Couple is already together.]
Let's go replenish our sugar, Gary.
Gary, I think...
we might get a mission
when we're get back together.
There's got to be a mission,
but why do they want us to go out?
Maybe there's a spy...
[I have no idea.]
It's suspicious.
[200 percent uneasy]
Maybe the mission is
to get there by 8 p.m.
Why did they give us the cell phone?
[Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Big Nose
and Giraffe are going together.]
Why did they let us
out for an hour?
But this is a mission.
Yes, it's a mission.
What time is it?
We need to go back by 8 p.m.
Maybe we need to
get back by 8 o'clock sharp.
I don't know...
I feel uncomfortable.
[Haroro joins Monday Couple.]
They told us to pick these up.
They even gave us our phones.
There's something about it.
Maybe we can go home right away.
Maybe only some of us have to stay
and the rest can go home.
Could it be possible?
I don't know what it's about.
Let's just get off.
They have seafood soup
and fish roe soup.
Abalone sashimi
and octopus ramen?
- Wow, octopus ramen sounds good!
- I need to lose weight.
Let's order one octopus ramen
Octopus and pork served with kimchi!
That's awesome!
I haven't had tofu and kimchi.
What's this mission about?
[They feel anxious while
they wait for their dinner.]
We're not going to
have a spy today, are we?
Let's eat quickly and
get back by eight.
Maybe they just want us to have dinner.
- Thank you.
- Hello!
Let's have small octopus bibimbap.
[They ordered small octopus dish
when the other group ordered octopus]
What is this about?
All of a sudden, they
told us to go out.
What is this?
I was happy to be out,
but now it's uncomfortable.
Should I buy some snacks
at a convenience store?
- Weren't you going to call Ji Hyo?
- Why do you keep trying to get snacks?
[He's avoiding eye contact.]
Does he need to do something?
Maybe he has an individual mission.
Maybe he does.
Don't be so sensitive.
We were making high fives a minute ago.
I'm very sure it's you!
[Absurd]
Jae Suk, say something.
You always keep quiet.
- I'm so tired.
- Are you together?
Oh, you two are the spies?
I see, these two are a team.
[Their distrust is growing.]
- In the morning...
- These two are...
It's coming!
[Time to enjoy octopus
and pork served with kimchi.]
Thank you.
[Look delicious]
Wow, we can have all these.
It's amazing.
[You can forget about the mission
at a time like this.]
Mmm.
We picked a good dish!
I hope it turns out
just as you expected.
Only if we can go home straight...
Isn't that right?
[Slurp]
[They're enjoying the octopus ramen.]
What time is it?
- Should we leave?
- Let's get there and wait outside.
- I'd like to pay.
- It was delicious!
Thank you for the food.
[They decided to go back.]
[Jae Suk's
group is still eating.]
Maybe they gave us time to eat.
No, they're giving some
time for Kwang Soo.
[Oh, no...]
- Isn't that strange?
- It's getting really uncomfortable.
Let's just separate.
I'll eat with Kwang Soo.
Why?
Do you need to discuss something?
He's driving me crazy.
"They're giving us time to eat?"
Isn't that strange?
He's suspicious.
They give us time to just eat?
It's strange, isn't it?
It is, but...
Anyway, we need to leave.
Let's go back.
Let's go!
[15 minutes before 8 p.m.]
What is it?
Well, I guess they let us go out.
Wait a minute!
- What?
- Do you know how to go back?
- Suk Jin!
- Did you figure out something?
- What?
- Isn't this unanimity?
[Isn't this unanimity?]
Huh?
Are we supposed to eat together?
No, I mean...
what did the mission say?
[From now on, you can
go out for an hour.]
[We'll announce an
enormous benefit after an hour.]
We can do anything we want?
[They said they will announce a
benefit, but not to come back.]
Do we need to go back all at once?
- That's it.
- That's not it!
We don't have to go back.
All of us!
All together, we can choose
not to go back.
- That makes sense.
- Doesn't it?
- Because it's unanimity?
- Yes.
If we just go home, then that's it!
We can go home?
It doesn't matter whether
we go back to the place or go home.
Don't you think so?
Should I tell them not to go back?
They told us to come back.
But we're the one
who can decide.
[Monday Couple and Haroro are back.]
We're back before eight.
We're here by eight.
You have 11 minutes left.
Give us some chocolate.
Snacks and chocolate?
For an hour?
Let's do that!
[What are you talking about?]
It's fine, no one else is here.
[We didn't have time to buy snacks.]
You want to eat, too!
Gary, Ha Ha's being stupid!
Let's do that!
You'll lose, if you don't throw
rock-paper-scissors!
[Betting can make you and
people around you unhappy.]
I'm going to go out and buy it.
- We have 11 minutes, right?
- 10 minutes.
[10 minutes before 8 o'clock.]
We just need to reach to unanimity.
Then we'll success.
Call them.
No one should be inside.
- Then we'll fail.
- Call them.
Wow, all of a sudden...
that idea hits my head.
- Then, why don't we just go back?
- I think we should all go back.
No, we don't have to go back.
- What next?
- We'll go home and that's it.
Or stay outside.
We're on our way.
Only 3 minutes
and 46 seconds left.
3 minutes and 46 seconds?
No, we don't have to go back!
Tell them to stay out of the building.
Just tell them to get out.
3 minutes and 40 seconds left.
Hurry up!
It's not that.
We've talked about the mission.
It's no use if you
talked about it alone!
The staffs are all sitting here!
- We need to go.
- Since it's unanimity, either...
- going back or not...
- You have a time limit!
Only 3 minutes and 12 seconds left!
I went the wrong way...
You got lost?
You...
I almost cursed.
What we're saying is, this is
the unanimity race...
- together, we can choose not to go back.
- We can!
And we'll still complete
the mission successfully.
No, the clock is running
and everyone is looking
at the clock here.
Because the staff are all acting.
Do whatever you want!
We'll do what we want!
Don't come!
If we can't get there on time,
you should leave the building!
- Just go!
- Tell them to come out.
Because I don't think
I can make it on time.
Let's just stand by the door.
1 minute and 43 seconds...
- 42 seconds.
- Anyway, let's join them.
- Wait, wait!
- You need to make another U-turn?
This drives me nuts!
Where are we?
[What's keeping them?]
[Should we go out of the building?]
We're late.
Are they waiting outside?
If they're outside, we've succeeded.
Park the car right here.
[Did Grasshopper guess right?]
[Hurry up, we don't have much time!]
[Either they're all outside waiting]
[or arrive on time.]
[The mysterious mission,
what will be the result?]
[They ended up getting in.]
You all came back and didn't go home?
[What did you say?]
We could have gone home.
[They were three minutes late.]
[For those who are late,
get the punishment!]
[You came back again?]
[What is it this time?]
[We'll make you stylish
by tying up your hair.]
[Scream]
What's this?
[You act like children,
we'll give you a topknot.]
(Hairstyle for married man
since Three Kingdoms period.)
[It's time for the
punishers to go back.]
I guess we could have gone home.
See?
I said we could go home.
But Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
kept saying we need to come back.
It feels weird to go home
just like that.
What are you talking about?
Why do you care about the slate?
I kept saying that we could go home.
But they kept saying
we need to come back.
Ha Ha mentioned that earlier.
What if we all arrived before eight?
Then, that could have
been a unanimous success, too.
That's more like a complete success.
If you didn't come
back and all went home
I was going to announce
your success by phone.
Anyway, you've failed the mission.
[Look at her!]
[Scruffy haired woman]
You look like a sinner
from a historic drama.
You should have told us
if you didn't know the way.
Try not to drive in case of emergency.
He was lost when he tried
to find my house.
We were late, too.
I don't do that on purpose.
That's suspicious.
- Now that I think about it...
- No!
- All the long, he was...
- Really?
Didn't I tell you to go home or not?
You told us but you brought us here.
You said it...
But it was a little weird
to just go home.
Wait a minute.
Do we still have 14 hours left?
- When is it going to end?
- Let's get some rest.
Take some rest.
We still can't go home.
What is it?
We have another mission.
[One versus six]
One versus six?
Does it mean one person can leave?
One, choose a rep.
Two, the chosen rep. will wear
headphones and turn around.
Jae Suk!
I'll do it.
Jae Suk is suspicious.
He's a spy.
Why would you choose the spy?
I'm not a spy!
- Are you sure?
- I'm not!
I hope he's not a spy.
Let's see how he does.
They doubt me so much.
[Falsely accused]
[He follows the command
and wears the headphones.]
[Next command appears.]
Pick a number for the rep and
he will jump to match the number.
[The rest of the members should pick a
number that Jae Suk is able to jump.]
He gets excited whenever
he listens to the music.
[Jae Suk's having fun.]
[They're having a meeting.]
Jae Suk wouldn't
just try to do a lot.
We can't really guess
how many he can jump.
When he hears the word "number",
he'll think about it.
If he doesn't...
I can only think he's a spy.
If he jumps as much as
he can, then he's a spy.
I think seven is a good number,
let's choose that.
We've decided.
[They chose number seven.]
[If Jae Suk can jump rope seven times,
they'll reach to unanimity.]
Please take off his headphones.
[Confused]
What is it about?
Take this.
[The fate of the members
depends on the jump rope.]
[They explain the mission to Jae Suk.]
A number that the
members could've picked?
We won't say anything.
We're going to get ready
to give you a hug.
Because we're a family.
We can go home, if you get it right.
Well, we're one.
[We're "one."]
I don't think it's a very small number.
[Why did you say "one"?]
[Oops, my mistake...]
How can I guess this?
We've been together for five years.
[What's wrong with him?]
Don't say stuff like that!
- I mean he can guess right.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't say any numbers.
- I don't know if it's right.
Please, please!
I'm going crazy!
You can do it!
I should do it so I can
clear myself of a false charge.
I think you know what it is!
[So many things depends on one string.]
A heart!
[He made a tiny finger heart once]
[then everyone doubted him
for everything he said.]
I'm going to send
a message via telepathy.
Let's just send him the message!
[If he succeed at it, we can go home!]
[Did you pick the number?]
[With all the pressure, Yoo Jae Suk
takes an action!]
[One!
Please don't stop it here!]
One
two, three
[He didn't stop, that's a relief!]
One, two, three, four
[Please...]
[Don't stop at five!]
We've been together
for five years.
Three, four
five, six
[Before the slogan of "one"]
[before "five years"]
[we were still too different
to come to a consensus.]
[But we were able to be
united around Jae Suk.]
[The members have chosen "seven."]
[Will he really stop at seven?]
five, six
seven!
[At the moment of choice]
[he stopped!]
five, six, seven!
[Right after jumping for seven times]
Wow!
[They've reached to
the final consensus!]
[They became one without
saying a word!]
We're a family!
"We're a family!"
[Summer, 2010. The seven members
met for the first time.]
[They bicker at times,
but they feel like they're a family.]
[The laugh and the sweat
they have shared together]
[The memory of the past five years
have passed just like that.]
[The seven members were
connected like a miracle.]
[We're proud of you, Yoo Jae Suk!]
All of a sudden, I was
chocked up with emotions.
I was touched!
[Teary]
This is way better than
going home earlier.
You're right.
[An unexpected fulfillment!]
- I had no idea what number it could be.
- Ji Hyo's crying.
I feel so weird.
Wow, this is amazing.
I could tell you were going to stop
when you jumped the seventh time.
I wasn't so sure.
Do you see?
The finger heart came out naturally.
I love you, Jae Suk!
You're supposed to do this for a heart.
Make a finger heart, Jong Kook.
I don't want to.
Jong Kook!
Why should I do that?
Just make it once!
He's cute.
That's a cute heart.
Wow, 13 hours left!
[With their teamwork,
they've done it in 10 hours.]
We completed the
race after 10 hours.
With three consensuses
you can go home!
Let's go home!
[We can go home!]
Yeah!
We can leave.
The staffs look so happy, too.
[You can tell?]
We're going to get going, then!
Thank you for your hard work!
Bye!
[The time taken until they escaped]
[10 hours 16 minutes and 40 seconds.]
[One thing they've realized during the
10 hours 16 minutes and 40 seconds is]
[the members are family.]
Hello, my name is Park Han Byul.
[Park Han Byul appears
on Running Man!]
[The goddess of dance, Stephanie]
[The queen of sport climbing,
Kim Ja In]
[Joy of Red Velvet]
[Attractive actress Gong Seung Yeon]
[and Comedian Park Na Rae]
[The hottest women
in Korea are all here!]
[Picnic with partners who
brought their own lunch.]
I made some and bought some.
[A special kimbap for female students!]
[Marvelous!]
["The Ring of the One Partner"
with special homeroom teachers.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next week, Running Man]
[The Partner Race]