[The legend that passes
through our school.]
[If the legendary
couple ring is worn]
[you will have true love, forever!]
[The students who are
searching for the ring.]
[A plot twist!]
[There are others who are
searching for the ring!]
[In whose hands will the
legendary couple ring go to?]
- Hello!
[A sunny morning.]
["Yongin Agricultural Theme Park,"
Gyeonggi-do]
It's a school.
We're in a classroom.
- Hello.
- It's the top student's seat.
Sit separately.
[Welcome to Running High]
- Should I sit at the back?
- You're supposed to, Jong Kook.
- Good students sit at the back, too.
- We have partners today?
- What is it today?
- Ji Hyo's not here.
[Will we have special guests?]
- So, we're students, like freshmen...
- Who's that?
I think so, too...
[Enter]
[Nice to meet you, everyone!]
Who's that?
- Isn't he...
- Wait a minute!
[What brings you here?]
[I'll introduce myself.]
Please show us your face properly.
Oh, now I remember.
[Chinese letters?]
Can you read it, Yoo Jae Suk?
- Mr. Jung Kyung Ho.
- That's right.
[Welcome!]
[He has some basic knowledge.]
You're wrong!
Pardon?
- That means old.
- I'm old Jung Kyung Ho.
Oh, old Jung Kyung Ho!
Because there's a younger one.
Da jia hao.
(How are you, everyone?)
Nimen hao ma.
[I will pour everything
into this lesson.]
[He's adjusting his vocal chords.]
[Running High Chinese teacher,
Jung Kyung Ho.]
- Class president!
- Attention!
[Disciplined]
Salute!
- Hello!
Before we continue on
with the lesson
there's a transfer student here.
Oh my god!
[Full of hope]
This is a co-ed school, right?
Please!
Please give them a warm welcome!
He's the Emcee today.
[Who is the new transfer student?]
- Bak!
- Hello!
Bak!
[The mysterious and
handsome guy is?]
[Running High school
transfer student]
[Yoon Bak.]
[An actor with full potential that
ranges from dramas to variety shows.]
[He will do everything he
can to find his soul mate!]
I'm the new transfer student,
Yoon Bak.
I hope that my partner
is a female guest.
Everyone wants the same thing!
Yoon Bak, sit here.
The back seat.
Sit in the back.
[Nice to meet you guys!]
He's handsome!
Ji Suk Jin speaks a little rudely.
Why?
- You asked why he has two surnames?
- It's true!
Why do you have two
noses on your face?
[That's pretty intense!]
[His straightforward joke.]
[Just kidding!]
I will now introduce you
to a female teacher.
There's a teacher?
Teacher Song Ji Hyo!
Is it the family studies teacher?
She's not that pretty.
Who is it?
[Who is the female teacher?]
[Calm]
She's beautiful.
[The most intelligent
and beautiful teacher.]
- She's been filming a drama.
- She's like a doll!
[Attention]
Buon giorno!
[Italian greeting]
[A high-pitched greeting
in the morning.]
It's a pleasure to meet you,
everyone.
[The beautiful and passionate teacher,
Hwang Suk Jung.]
[She captivates the
public's attention with]
[her skillful talking and
outstanding acting.]
[She came to Running High
to find true love.]
Ha, ha, ha.
Nice to meet you.
[Intrigued]
You probably heard from
Mr. Jung Kyung Ho
about why I came here today.
Today is the day,
that all students
will be having class together.
[Be happy, everyone!]
[We have waited for this day!]
Don't get too close
in such a short time.
Always keep your personal
feelings in control.
[She's like a real teacher.]
Be rational, and be careful
and keep a distance.
She must be a romance specialist.
Your ages are a little bit wonky.
[Ha, ha, ha]
You guys have so much going on.
So, always keep that in mind.
Be respectful to each other
as you would act around me.
[That move is addicting.]
Grazie!
- Shall we have some time alone?
- Yes.
I will follow your orders.
- Are you dating?
- You are too much!
They're leaving?
Please have a wonderful time.
Are you leaving?
[I have a date, so goodbye!]
Zaijian!
Are they really leaving?
- They left!
- What are we supposed to do?
Shouldn't some of the other
students come in, then?
Gary, you lead it.
I've never been
the class president...
How do I lead it?
Go to the front and
bring them in, one by one.
Would you please come in,
one by one?
Who's coming today?
[They're coming!]
[Who will be the]
[first female student?]
- It's Ji Hyo!
- Boo!
It's the class
president's girlfriend!
[Running High's first
female student, Song Ji Hyo.]
What did you bring?
She brought lunch boxes!
They said we were going
on a picnic today.
Really?
I brought lunches today.
What did you bring?
I brought some lunches.
And I brought fruit as well.
[Fruit for dessert is a bonus!]
She brought a lot.
I brought some side dishes.
[And even some side dishes!]
It looks good!
Do I just sit next to
whoever I want?
[Now, shall I go find my soul mate?]
Pick Suk Jin!
She's just passing by.
[Hmph]
[Blank Ji's choice is?]
- Hi, Yoon Bak!
- Hello.
I'll sit here for a bit.
[Shy]
They look nice together.
[Song Ji Hyo and Yoon Bak.]
Am I out?
Next student, please come in!
Who's the next student?
I have high hopes.
[I'm on my way to meet you!]
[Huh? That is]
[Park Han Byul!]
[Running High's second
female student, Park Han Byul.]
[She captivates everyone's eye
with her enthusiastic attitude!]
[She will find her soul mate
at Running High!]
[Everyone gets up.]
[Full of joy]
[Surprised]
[They go up to meet her.]
That's too heavy!
- Han Byul is a good friend of mine!
- Stop lying!
[Burdensome]
- Do you have her phone number?
- Hello, my name is Park Han Byul.
Welcome One Star!
(Han: one, Byul: star)
I'm re-watching the
drama she was in.
- One star came here.
- My mom hates her so much.
Then you must not like me.
[Don't worry, we'll protect you!]
Many older women don't like her.
I brought these to wear
with my partner...
I'm the only one without a hat!
[They're ready to wear the hat!]
I made lunch, as well as dessert.
[Introducing Han Byul's lunch.]
[The afternoon
before shooting day.]
I have prepared lunch to
eat with my partner.
Ta-da!
Fried tofu rice balls
and a shrimp salad.
And then on the bottom,
some fruit.
And then in the middle...
I have bought some Kimbap.
Do I just put it in?
Or should I re-arrange it?
The other way?
The rice was well made
so it was extremely delicious.
It seems as if I made it at home.
That's perfect!
[It's perfect!]
And it's complete!
[Is there anyone to
share this lunch with?]
One star!
[It's finally time to
choose her partner.]
Come here.
[I won't lose...]
[this chance.]
[Han Byul's choice is?]
[Park Han Byul and Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Excellent choice!]
[Depressed]
It's easier for me to get along
with someone I already know.
She's very shy!
Haven't you seen us on TV?
Okay, next up is...
- We'll bring in the next guest!
- I'm her fan, though!
Please come out!
[Calmly stares]
It's Stephanie!
Phanie!
How have you been?
It's been a while!
Phanie, how have you been?
[She's getting an intense
welcome from them!]
Phanie!
[Automatic dance]
[Who is this woman that gets
along well so well with them?]
[Running High's third
female student, Stephanie.]
[X-men's heroine that
took over variety shows!]
[She was famous for her dancing!]
[She returned with a new
and improved look]
[on a variety show!]
I made a comeback as
a solo singer, Stephanie.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome, Stephanie!
Please show us your lunch.
- Please send me.
- It's different!
Did you pack all this?
Yes, I packed it.
Are you foraging through, now?
Don't forage!
Don't do it!
[Introducing Stephanie's lunch!]
[The night before the shoot.]
Hello everyone, I'm Stephanie.
I received an order
to pack a lunch.
You can freeze your beef
before frying it.
[She's chopping some burdock.]
[Make the filling with rice,
burdock, and meat.]
Beef!
[Make the right size
of tofu rice balls.]
And make it to the right size.
[Ta-da!
The complete lunch!]
It has to look good.
There's high quality beef, inside.
And some burdock, as well.
[Come to me, Stephanie!]
[But her choice is?]
What are you saying?
You changed your mind
after 10 years?
I'm sorry.
Okay, then
Phanie, you sit here for a while.
[What?]
Can I give up now?
Can I change now?
Yes, would you do that?
You shouldn't do this to me!
I'll just give you the hat back!
I'm a little...
Look at her!
[Look at his guts!]
I'm a little hurt.
Jae Suk's so popular right now.
Hurry up and decide!
If it's too hard,
I'll just sit here for a bit.
- What are you doing?
- Don't do that!
[You're too absorbed...]
[The heroine's brother
is using physical contact.]
- What are you doing?
- That's too much.
[They suddenly became rivals.]
[What will their destiny be?]
Please come out!
[What kind of female student
will come this time?]
- Wow!
- She's cute!
Oh, hello!
It's Ja In!
[Running High's fourth
female student, Kim Ja In.]
["Spider girl" Kim Ja In,
wins world cup sports climbing.]
[She is called the "Empress."]
[A magical strength that
comes out of a small figure.]
[The world's number one
rock climbing Empress, Kim Ja In.]
- Ja In, Ja In!
- Oh, I know her!
Climbing, climbing!
World's number one!
[Nice to meet you, Running Man.]
She's beautiful, in real person!
I thought you would
be a lot taller.
Pocket girl!
- Hello, I am...
- She's cute.
I am the only athlete student
in this class, Kim Ja In.
Wow!
- Is it herbal medicine?
- I made it myself.
It's good for your health.
It's avocado and banana.
[His heart starts fluttering.]
[My lunch is pretty awesome, right?]
[I'm shy, for no reason.]
This is Jong Kook's diet!
[Will they be able to
get along like their diets?]
- Just walk straight.
- Keep walking to the back.
Our proportions are similar.
[He he]
[She starts walking]
[with an unknown expression.]
[Will it be Jong Kook?]
Would you like a sip?
Wow!
[Thank you...]
[Oh, just a sip?]
[She's playing hard to get.]
[Kkuk got rejected!]
That's so funny!
My stomach hurts from laughing!
[She picked her partner, just then!]
[She picked a partner
with matching proportions?]
[He swimming in a pool of laughter.]
[She made her decision!]
Thank you!
[Kim Ja In and Ha Ha.]
Party time!
[The fifth female student is?]
[Hello]
[Oops]
[It's Joy!]
Joy!
[Running High's fifth
female student, Joy.]
It's Joy from Red Velvet!
[Hello, you're new here, right?]
Hello, I am 20 years old
and my name is Joy.
We have a huge age gap.
Excuse me!
It's not a blind date!
[I was only thinking.]
You're just going to be
partners for one day.
I've prepared a lunch just
for one special person.
[Really?]
I'm going to empty my mind.
Shall we see?
Did you make it yourself?
Yes.
Did you all plan this?
It's fried tofu rice balls again.
[Did you all buy it together?]
Oh!
She wrote their name.
[The name she wrote on the rice.]
His name?
I made it overnight.
My heart's fluttering!
[Joy's lunch,
made only for one person.]
- Joy!
- Oh, hi!
I started making this
as soon as I was done today.
I'm going to make egg fried rice.
I'm frying ham first.
Are you doing it right?
I'm just going by feel.
To be honest,
I don't know what I'm doing.
I am making some
fried tofu rice balls.
It looks good!
This is my lunch box!
You've filled it up.
Does it look like his name?
[You will accept my lunch, right?]
I put some side dishes in, too!
Wow, what time is it?
- Is it Kwang Soo's?
- Who's is it?
She made it without any sleep
so I don't think it's Ji Suk Jin's.
I agree.
Now, go!
[Joy, who prepared her
lunch for one person...]
I think it's Kwang Soo...
[Who will that person be?]
She's giving glances at everyone!
[Just then!]
[Joy and Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Happy vs. Sad]
[He's congratulating
without regret.]
[Huh? What's this?]
She wrote Giraffe on the rice.
[Oh my!]
This is the first time!
She wrote it?
[Fascinated]
It doesn't look like Giraffe.
You didn't mistake it
for Gary, right?
[Everyone's jealous
of Joy's pure love.]
Isn't it Gary?
Thanks, Joy.
[Touched]
This is so moving.
I'm going to take this home.
You're not going to eat it?
Please come out!
[Who is the sixth guest?]
[Running High's sixth
female guest, Gong Seung Yeon.]
It's Gong Seung Yeon!
Oh, wow!
[With her elegant appearance,
and outstanding acting]
[she dominates over
ads and dramas!]
[I will find true love
at Running High!]
[Nice to meet you!]
It's so festive today!
There's hope!
[She's cute.]
[Oh my!]
[That's it?]
Doesn't it lack sincerity?
Isn't it frozen meat?
They're sausages.
Is that pickled radish?
What is that?
I think she added pickled radish,
but since it looked empty
she added pickles.
The leftover from
ordering pizza...
They're leftovers?
They're new from my fridge.
Hello, I am actress Gong Seung Yeon.
I am making a lunch right now.
I've been living alone
for a year, but
I never really cooked by myself.
I don't even have a rice cooker.
And no rice, either.
I'm making delicious
sausages, though.
So I hope you will
at least enjoy that.
Should I show you?
It's cooking well.
[That lunch turned out to be this!]
Did you force yourself to make it?
[I wish I could hide in a hole.]
There's one last box.
Oh, there's another one?
Did you two share?
Isn't that Joy's?
I think they'll stick
if they're put together.
[Dessert twins]
[Embarrassed]
Oh my!
Okay, it's time to pick!
Yes, I will pick...
Kwang Soo.
[Gong Seung Yeon and Lee Kwang Soo.]
[This is Giraffe's lucky day.]
Jong Kook, Ji Suk Jin, and Gary.
They've been very quiet.
I've never been this unpopular!
Kwang Soo, please sit over there.
[Gong Seung Yeon
and Joy sit side by side.]
There are mixed feelings
going around in this room.
[Worrying]
[The last final student.]
[Whose silhouette is that?]
[Running High's seventh
female student, Park Na Rae.]
[Skilled at talking
and extraordinary costumes.]
[She is Korea's hottest comedian.]
[Hello]
What's with the atmosphere?
[Evacuation]
It's Na Rae!
Is something wrong?
What's wrong?
[The atmosphere just dropped.]
[After calming down,
she goes up to the podium.]
Na Rae!
[She looks like the whack-a-mole.]
I can only see her face!
The viewers might think
that I'm being rude
and sitting down.
[Visual shock]
Na Rae!
You brought a lunch, I'm sure.
Could we take a look?
Do you reveal it now?
I think there will be three rice balls.
[Wrapped in foil]
I saw that in an old movie!
No, no.
I haven't see that in a long time.
Wow.
She packed it herself.
[The rice is pushed down.]
[Park Na Rae's specialty lunch.]
It's pushed down.
It's rice!
A man needs strength, from rice!
She packed it herself.
Wow!
It's thanksgiving food.
[Different kinds of
vegetable pancakes.]
She made mini pancakes?
Wow!
[Wow]
[Small octopus kebab.]
[Amazing Park Na Rae.]
What now?
[What is it?]
[Small octopus and beef.]
[Wow]
[Mouth wide open]
I came to find my husband.
[She got high points from
her future husbands.]
Na Rae, please pick your partner!
Na Rae's lunch is number one.
[Where will she head
with her quality lunch?]
[I want to eat it...]
Na Rae!
[Will you eat my small octopus]
[and beef, forever?]
- Kim Jong Kook!
- It's Kwang Soo!
[Park Na Rae and Lee Kwang Soo.]
- Me?
- Are you really happy?
[Giraffe got chosen by Na Rae]
[Seung Yeon and Joy.]
- Don't we look perfect?
- It's great!
[An aesthetic point
of view of halves.]
If you want to film them,
you have to pick one.
I'll be generous.
[The revolution of a two shot.]
You have to pick one of the three.
[Na Rae vs. Joy vs. Seung Yeon.]
[Giraffe's choice is?]
[Excuse me!]
You!
He called you out.
[Flustered]
[She's denying the truth.]
[How should I react?]
You guys clean this up.
I don't know what to do.
Get out!
[Do you mean, me?]
I hate tall guys anyway!
Na Rae, stay here for a second.
[Temporary isolation]
[Kwang Soo's final choice]
[is Joy.]
Sorry, this is my spot.
[You're too much!]
[Stephanie and Jong Kook.]
[Gong Seung Yeon and Gary.]
[Park Na Rae and Ji Suk Jin.]
[Round one selection, complete.]
[Current partners]
- Should I lay it out?
- No, it's okay.
There's cream cheese.
It's good.
Wow, the sausage
you made is incredible!
You cooked it on
the frying pan, right?
[Embarrassed]
[They're opening the lunch boxes.]
[This is like a buffet.]
Kwang Soo seemed weak,
so I wanted to feed him.
Who could be weaker than me?
[Joy's tofu rice balls for Giraffe.]
[After the partners'
lunch time is progressing]
[the two teachers are
having a secret date.]
Teacher Jung, say ah.
This is so good!
- I want to ask you something.
- Yes?
Do you know about the legend
that passes down in our school?
What legend?
Apparently there's a
legendary couple ring.
If you find the ring and put it on
then you will be
true lovers, forever.
I know that legend.
So if we find it and wear it
- we'll become partners for life?
- Yes.
We need to find the ring.
We will find it.
- We're only two.
- But we're a team.
We're on the same boat.
I'll give you victory.
I only have this day once a year
but today, I will give you victory.
Na Rae, Na Rae!
[The race starts now!]
[The first gateway of the
legendary couple ring race.]
Now that it's fall
it reminds me of my first love
that promised to
pick stars from the sky.
Please forget
about your past love.
Red sun!
(A famous hypnotizing line.)
From now on,
I will pick the stars from the sky
and even the stars on the ground.
Oh my goodness!
Why are there starfish here?
It's like a miracle!
That scared me!
It's such a mysterious thing!
Please give me stars!
You see the stars
on the ground, right?
We said we wanted to
see Stephanie's dance.
Should we get it going?
[Fall dance party]
[Let's party!]
[The beat is flowing under
the clear fall sky.]
First up, is Stephanie!
[Go, Stephanie!]
[Round and round]
[It's become a festival,
all of a sudden.]
[She has power, and is skillful.]
[Heart is fluttering]
Stephanie hasn't changed!
They met a while ago!
[She's bringing back a retro dance.]
[From X-men to Running Man, she breaks
through the history of variety shows.]
[Bravo, Stephanie!]
[What do I do?]
- Next up is Joy!
- Joy!
[She warms up first.]
[Show us, show us!]
Wait for it!
It's coming, it's coming!
It's almost there!
[She miscalculated]
[Off beat]
[Not yet!]
[This time, it was off beat again.]
[Where is the chorus in this?]
Joy, you have to walk like an idol.
Like Beyonce?
[You wanted a girl group dance?]
[I will show you!]
[A proper girl group walking.]
Two, three, four!
[Wobble, wobble]
[Release the zombie.]
[Her joints are
bending by themselves.]
Her ears touched her shoulder!
[Dangerous poppin']
I heard a noise from her ear!
[Unique Joy, who showed us
a zombie girl group walk.]
[Next up is Seung Yeon.]
[She walks in cheery,
and does the crab dance.]
[It's so rare to see!]
[The crab dance of an actress!]
Why would you do that?
[It's a perfect finish!]
[Han Byul's turn!]
You need to forget your image.
Park Han Byul!
[I'm already on it!]
[Han Byul's crab dance!]
[Her random dance is
almost funny as Ji Hyo.]
We're friends!
[The random dance duo]
They dance the same!
I said we're friends!
She dances like Ji Hyo.
They look like two drunk men!
Let's see Yoon Bak.
Yoon Bak!
Yoo Bak!
[A fan dance!]
[Splits!]
Ja In!
It's your turn.
[The last dancer, Ja In!]
[How will the sport climbing
world champion's dance?]
You should come forward.
[Where are you going?]
You don't have to do that!
[You don't have to
climb the street light!]
She must have felt so much pressure!
Why did you have to
put so much pressure?
Even a jimmy jib was recording.
Ja In's amazing!
We haven't had anyone like you
since Kim Byung Man.
I was wondering what you were doing.
We should play the
name tag elimination.
No one can eliminate her name ta.
She'll be stick to the ceiling.
Let's play the game.
Come here, Group one.
Group two.
[The first mission:
I'll catch a star on the ground.]
Are you okay, Seung Yeon?
- Let me know if you're uncomfortable.
- I don't think I can walk.
[Rule: Pick up as many stars as possible
and put it in your basket.]
I'm nervous!
Let's move forward, Joy.
Get ready, set,
go!
One, two, one, two!
[As soon as they started they fell.]
- Oh, no!
- No!
[While Ji Hyo and Yoon Bak
move slowly]
[the other teams start
picking up the stars.]
[We won't be able to win
at this rate!]
[It won't be easy to get up...]
[then, I'll crawl!]
[He carries Ji Hyo on his back
and crawls as he picks stars.]
Look at Yoon Bak!
[Yoon Bak is amazing!]
Yoon Bak!
[Dauntless warrior, Yoon Bak]
[He has full of stars in his hands.]
That's something new!
That's new!
[The crawling team is in the lead.]
[We're falling!]
How can we get up?
Let's get up!
One, two, three!
I can't get up.
What are we supposed to do
for getting up?
Joy, here are the stars.
[Meanwhile, thanks to Joy's flexibility
they're getting stars.]
You need to get to your basket!
Joy, let's put them in the basket!
[Yoon Bak and Ji Hyo
finally stand up.]
Get to your basket!
Gary, get to your basket!
Where's the basket?
Let's not touch other people's basket!
Play the game!
Why not?
[Yoon Bak and Ji Hyo put the stars
get ready for a physical fight.]
[Ji Hyo's still collecting.]
Flip Kwang Soo's basket
and win!
[Cut it out!]
[Do you know how to stand up?]
We're not a good team!
No, not my basket!
Bak, flip Kwang Soo's
basket and win!
[That's a foul!]
[A fatal accident!]
Oh, no!
[Joy kicks her own basket
when the buzzer goes off.]
I didn't kick it!
[It wasn't a foul.]
[The counting for the first round.]
One, two, three!
[For Kwang Soo and Joy]
Gary's team has nothing.
Yoon Bak and Ji Hyo has
two, four, six, seven.
Yoon Bak's team won!
[They won the first round.]
[The Columbus of games, Yoon Bak]
[Their crawling strategy worked!]
Yoon Bak used his wits.
It's the final round!
Let's go!
It doesn't fit.
- We're starting the final round now?
- Yes, we are.
[Suk Jin and Na Rae
won the second round.]
- Did you take off your shoes?
- Yes, it's easier.
Good job.
[Can we beat the monsters?]
Get ready!
Set, go!
[The final round starts!]
[Swoosh]
You're not supposed to do that!
There he goes again!
[We knew Kkuk is like a monster]
[but Stephanie is so flexible!]
She can bend like that?
That's not funny at all.
[It's not possible to defeat them...]
Wow, she can do that!
[He picks, and picks.]
[Their basket is full of stars.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[Yoon Bak starts picking up
the stars, super fast.]
[I can't lose!]
[He's so fast!]
It looks like Na Rae
came here with her work manager.
[It's a company fall outing!]
[Ji Hyo and Yoon Bak's
basket is full of stars, too.]
You need to give them
20 minutes!
Yoon Bak collected a lot, too.
I wonder who will win.
Get up.
[At that moment]
[Ill-tempered Big Nose
attacks Jong Kook and Stephanie.]
What is this?
What happened?
[What a windfall!]
Good job, you flipped it!
[What happened?]
I didn't do it!
Are we going to continue this game?
We just need to protect
our basket, Ji Hyo.
Yoon Bak is smart.
- It's not us, Jong Kook.
- Let's give up, Na Rae.
[And the time's up.]
The fact that we won
last time is more weird.
We don't even need to count them.
Therefore, Yoon Bak and Ji Hyo win!
The two of you can come
forward and receive it.
You might not be partners later.
- What's inside?
- They're different hints?
Maybe they're different.
Huh?
This is a hint?
[Ji Hyo's hint - "Green K"]
[Yoon Bak's hint - "Soe with a heart"]
Like I said before,
the winners are
Ji Hyo said she will break us apart.
Except us and Suk Jin's couple,
everyone will rotate.
- Why?
- To the left.
[Why not us?]
Ja In...
[They have to
be separated.]
- You look so happy.
- It's not true.
- Ji Hyo...
- What about us?
Just stay as a couple.
It drives me crazy.
- Get moving!
- Come here!
We're bored with each other
from the start.
Don't even think
about winning the race.
We meet again.
[It's new and awkward again.]
[Let's go to the next mission site!]
[Current partners]
- Miss Hwang.
- Yes?
- To make a return for your lunch...
- Yes.
I brought this.
Thank you.
[Bite]
It's so sweet.
You should try, too.
It's okay, you like ice cream.
I'm okay.
[She pushes it.]
Thank you.
[Cough, cough]
You're enjoying it.
[Miss Hwang...
Mr. Jung...]
[I think we can connect
without any words.]
It's like I'm back to
when I was a young girl.
To be a young girl, you're too...
[After the first couple game]
What's this?
- What is it?
- It's interesting.
- Kimbap!
- Maybe it's like pinball.
- Are all the men here?
- Yes.
Did you enjoy the lunch
your partner brought?
- Yes.
- This time, male students will
make kimbap for your partners.
- What's this?
- I'm good at making kimbap.
The thing is, this
is "kimbap of fortune."
We'll give you rice and laver,
but the rest
are in the vending machine
in front of you.
- You'll put tennis balls.
- That looks fun!
You'll get the ingredients by luck.
[They're given three chances.]
There's wasabi, too!
There's garlic, too!
- It's raw!
- Raw garlic!
Chocolate?
Saury and chocolate together...
It must be the worst!
[Horrifying ingredients are
side by side the normal ones.]
There're gummy worms, too.
If you use fresh garlic
and wasabi together...
But, wasabi as an ingredient
is too much.
[Is that a reward of a punishment?]
I'm not sorry.
[In the meantime, the female
students are upstairs.]
What are they doing now?
They're making a gift for you.
The new partners are?
My partner is quiet old
for that kind of stuff.
I feel uncomfortable.
[Na Rae, I might feel
even more uncomfortable.]
Do we just throw balls in there?
I think the unlucky
people should go first.
Then, I'll do it first!
- Which means Ji Suk Jin, Lee Kwang Soo...
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Who will go first out of three?
The unluckiest, Kwang Soo will!
- I'll do it first!
- There're more of good ingredients.
Get ready, set
[For his new partner,
Stephanie...]
Ready, set, go!
[The icon of misfortune]
- I wonder how unlucky he is.
- Dud!
[The ball keeps changing
its direction.]
[No way...
I won't be unlucky with this game.]
[Kwang Soo's ball is moving
toward pork cutlet.]
[Is he going to break
his serious of misfortune?]
[Kwang Soo's first ingredient!]
Dud!
- Dud, dud!
- Dud!
[That was close.]
- Indeed!
- You're unbelievable!
He's the unluckiest of all.
[He's always unlucky.]
Try doing it at the end this time.
Ready, set
go!
If he picks wasabi
or fresh garlic.
He might get another dud.
[Another dud?]
Dud!
[It really happened!]
[This can't be real...]
[It's rather frightening.]
How could it be even possible?
If he picks wasabi this time...
I can't eat cilantro!
Maybe pork cutlet and cream cheese...
Fresh garlic!
It's fast!
[The last chance for Giraffe]
[I don't want to lose it!]
[Kwang Soo's third attempt]
[He got salted shrimps.]
[A perfect landing!]
[Kwang Soo picks salted shrimps.]
We had salted shrimps?
That's the worst!
So, rice, laver and salted shrimps.
That's the worst.
How can anyone eat it?
[Absurd]
Come over here.
[Stephanie, I'm sorry...]
I've visited a
fortune teller.
And I'm supposed to have
good luck this year.
Throw it!
[He throws it confidently.]
He threw it boldly.
Imitation crab meat!
Yeah!
I told you I have good luck.
I hope he'll get a saury.
[What'll be his second ingredient?]
[It goes toward ham.]
[Please, get the ham!]
[Big Nose's second ingredient is..]
Chocolate!
[He picked chocolate.]
Imitation crab meat
and chocolate kimbap!
That might be okay.
Maybe it's good.
I wonder how it will taste.
[She reserves an imitations crab meat
and chocolate kimbap.
[What will be his last ingredient?]
[Cilantro!]
[Big Nosed Brother's last
ingredient selection!]
I can't eat cilantro.
I'm not going to eat it, am I?
He doesn't care.
- Is it my turn?
- No, it's my turn.
Up next is, one of the
three unlucky men.
I'm the next runner.
I have high expectations on you.
Yoo Jaesoo. (fortune)
I hope all of his balls go to wasabi.
[What will Yoo Jaesoo's
first ingredient bed?]
Gummy worms!
[Shock and horror]
- It'll be gross looking!
- Your kimbap will be gummy.
- How will she chew it?
- At least it's not a real worm.
- It's just gummy worms.
- Yes, it's still human food.
Wasabi, wasabi!
- Please, please.
- He might get a dud.
[His second ingredient is chocolate.]
It'll be very sweet!
It's junk food!
What a sweet kimbap it will be!
I feel so sorry for Seung Yeon.
Get a saury!
[Please give me a normal ingredient.]
[Yoo Jae Suk's last
ingredient is wasabi.]
- Wasabi!
- He's unlucky as usual.
What should we do?
Gummy worms, chocolate, and wasabi.
We've got the worst...
I'll get delicious ones.
- Yours will be salty.
- Salty taste is fine.
At the same time?
[He threw three balls at once.]
He's tough!
[He's a manly man.]
[How will this gambit turn out?]
[One of them fell.]
[The rest went on...]
A dud and a saury.
- Is saury really strange?
- His kimbap will smell like fish.
But, people make saury kimbap.
[In Jeju Island]
- They do?
- The canned fish is okay.
The other is pork cutlet!
That's not bad.
His is not bad?
Pork cutlet and a saury for kimbap?
- Should I start?
- Yes.
They make saury kimbap.
Where are you heading?
No, not there!
- Garlic!
- It's good for you!
What is Han Byul going to do?
Han Byul will smell like garlic.
Wow, nothing can cover
the flavor of garlic.
I just hoped for everything but garlic.
Well, it can't get worse.
How about cilantro?
- I gave up.
- Is that garlic again?
Cream cheese!
Garlic and cream cheese, yuck!
That's awful.
The combination of
fresh garlic and cream cheese...
[He needs to get something good.]
Wasabi!
Cilantro!
- Oh, no, poor Han Byul!
- This is the worst!
Even after brushing her teeth ten times,
she might still smell like garlic.
I think she needs a week.
I'll throw it now.
Currently, Jong Kook's
ingredients are the worst.
Fresh garlic and cilantro
are too much!
Ha Ha's first ingredient
is pork cutlet.
Pork cutlet kimbap is good.
You never know.
Younger people like cilantro.
Sweet pickled radish!
Wow, that's proper!
[Ha Ha acquires a
mandatory ingredient.]
It will be perfect if he
gets crab meat or ham.
Get fresh garlic!
[What will the last ingredient be?]
Imitation crab meat!
What a plain ingredient!
That's not funny!
It'll be so good!
How much salted shrimps should I put?
I think it's food.
I was imagining
something like hey holder.
That's so cute!
[While they're waiting for their gift.]
[They're making shocking
kimbap downstairs.]
I've never rolled any kimbap before.
You haven't?
- Me, neither.
- I have.
[The boastful cooking]
(Mimicking Chef Choi Hyun Suk)
Not too much!
[He also performs slapstick.]
Good riddance!
Bak is different
since he on a cooking show.
That's right!
(Mr. Baek The Homemade Food Master)
Oh, Bak learns from Mr. Baek.
We filmed about kimbap
a few weeks ago.
- You're his apprentice?
- He's gutting the saury.
I can't say I'm his apprentice...
Oh, no. I put everything
but laver on the roller.
- Look at Gary.
- Make it like California roll.
What were you doing?
He didn't put the laver.
[Big nose's kimbap]
[Kwang Soo's kimbap]
I see 300 shrimps on
Kwang Soo's kimbap.
Is that a fishing village?
If I put sesame oil...
I just put jelly and chocolate...
- That looks good.
- Mine's perfect!
Ha Ha, yours is a normal kimbap.
Ha Ha's kimbap will be delicious.
It'll be so good!
That's a real kimbap.
[He rolled it nicely, too.]
- Shrimp is leaking.
- I rolled it nicely.
You'll be surprised.
I'm good at it.
This is how you do it.
It would be good if he
put only a little salted shrimps.
It'll be like salty rice ball.
- What are you doing?
- He's plating.
[I'm a man who cooks.]
I need some sesame seeds.
- Bak, are you done with this?
- Yes.
[He takes the fish bone.]
It looks different
when you decorate the dish.
Sea!
It expresses the feeling of the sea.
[The have finished making
"the kimbap of fortune."]
But his kimbap doesn't
even have saury.
She will be able to fee the sea.
[Now, they'll bring this kimbap
upstairs for their partners.]
They're coming.
- They're here!
- I knew it!
Everyone!
We enjoyed your lunch so much.
So, we made it for you.
We'll repay you.
It smells so good!
Nutty smell like sesame oil!
Doesn't it smell good?
Starting from Yoon Bak...
the ingredients are...
Don't reveal it now.
Taste it.
[Saury and pork cutlet]
Feed her!
Because they can see what it is.
This looks good.
- Pork cutlet?
- They should close their eyes.
It's okay.
That should taste good.
His ingredients weren't bad.
[How will it taste?]
- Is it okay?
- It's so good!
- Really?
- Yes.
Really?
Let me taste it.
- It's good.
- Is it?
[It's not bad.]
Gary.
He removed the fish skin, too.
The flavor of sesame oil, though.
[Gary's kimbap]
[Saury, chocolate, spinach]
Don't smell too much.
Eat the middle piece.
Try it, Ja In.
It's okay.
It's not bad.
Chew it properly.
How is it?
It's not bad,
but it's not good.
How would you describe the taste?
Salted lollipop.
Wow, that's precise!
She's like a poet.
Because it has saury and chocolate.
What did you say?
[Saury and chocolate?]
I'm telling you, this isn't the worst.
I'll tell you.
That one is blessed.
Kim Jong Kook is the next.
[Han Byul's tasting time.]
[Cream cheese,
uncooked garlic, cilantro]
That looks good!
Wow, that looks different!
[Frown face]
How is it?
Can you taste the cilantro?
Tell him honestly.
[How should I describe this?]
How does it taste?
But...
- you can still eat it...
- Wow, she's nice.
You can still eat it,
but you wouldn't, right?
You won't be able to talk today.
Oh, garlic!
[It's Ha Ha's turn]
Joy is blessed.
[Pork cutlet, sweet pickled radish,
and crab meat]
Joy is lucky.
It's good that your
partner got changed.
[Wow, delicious!]
Maybe you saved your country
in your former life.
Can I have one of your pickled radish?
[I want to get rid of the odor.]
It's not going to help!
- Seriously, isn't that good?
- Yes.
[Getting a normal ingredient wasn't
easy at all, but he has all three.]
Sweet pickled radish,
pork cutlet, and crab meat!
- Seung Yeon's turn.
- That looks cute.
Something looks red.
For your information, these are
Running Man's three unluckiest members.
But mine is a little better
than these two.
- Really?
- Really.
- What's that?
- Isn't that a gummy bear?
What did you eat?
Seung Yeon, how is it?
- I think it's spicy.
- Yes, it's wasabi!
[Bingo!
It's wasabi!]
And hers is better than ours?
- How's the taste?
- I don't think I can eat it again.
[Chocolate, gummy worms,
wasabi]
The next taster is Stephanie.
You're so unlucky.
No, it's not that bad.
[Salted shrimps]
What's this?
[Decoration to express the giving sea]
- That's a comb.
- I thought it's a relic.
You can use it as a comb.
[She eats it in one bite.]
It's not that bad, is it?
I feel so bad for Stephanie.
Are you okay?
It's not that bad, right?
[Outburst]
[Why are you giving me
such a hard time?]
[She's dizzy.]
I've never rolled a kimbap in my life.
[No more excuses, just eat it.]
[Kwang Soo is
apologizing with his face.]
Na Rae, you know
why you're the last person.
[Oh my god!]
Is this the worst kimbap?
It looks nice.
The visual isn't that bad, right?
Try it, Na Rae.
Eat it at once.
It'll be good.
I think it's fine.
It should be okay.
[God!]
Oh, no!
[Chocolate, crab meat,
and cilantro]
[Joy is the lucky girl.]
She has the most delicious kimbap.
[After the fun snack time]
[A fairy tale passed
down at Running High]
[About the legendary couple rings,
that let you win your love forever.]
[We're on the way to find the legend.]
[They're on the way to
the final mission site.]
You don't have any hints, Han Byul.
[After the snack time,
they played a baseball game.]
[Jae Suk and Seung Yeon win
and they changed partners again.]
This hat belongs to you.
That's right!
[He's happy.]
The hint I have is...
[Right before they arrive at the site]
[It's at the hallway
on the fifth floor.]
I think this is the best hint.
Hallway on the fifth floor.
[Seung Yeon has the same hint.]
Jae Suk and I received the same hint.
Ji Hyo and Yoon Bak
have a different hint.
Different from us, too.
- A heart?
- A heart with "Soe"
(from "Yeolsoe" (key),
"Soe" itself means "metal")
It might be a key,
or metal key holders?
[They're guessing the imperfect hint.]
[They go to the final site
with their last partner.]
[At that time, the teachers...]
Is everyone studying hard?
[Stops abruptly]
They're supposed to be studying.
Where are they?
Mr. Jung!
They didn't, did they?
Miss Hwang, I think they went to
find the legendary couple rings
when they should be studying!
- Let's go get them.
- Wait a moment.
Mr. Jung...
I'll bring the student council members.
They're like my children.
Wait, calm down!
Student council!
Wait a moment, please.
[She's ready to bring 300 students.]
She's so lovely.
Miss Hwang!
[They're ready to chase.]
Let's go!
[Look at them...]
[They look strong!]
Let's go.
- Which way?
- That way!
[The students who left
school early are...]
We're going to search
for it without any hints?
What can we do?
We didn't get any hints.
[Each team is searching
for the ring alone.]
Maybe it's on the floor.
[Are they dating or
carrying out the mission?]
[Huh?]
[They're tied to each other!]
[One minute ago]
While you were eating lunch
- female students told you something.
- The legend.
The legendary rings!
Somewhere in this building,
there's a treasure chest.
You need a key to open the chest.
Find the key to open the treasure chest
and get the couple rings inside.
They're diamond rings.
[What a restorative announcement!]
[She's full of energy.]
It's embarrassing!
This makes me look bad.
She told me that
she's going to sell it on eBay
if she wins the prize.
You need to wear the rings.
And that's not it.
You need to wear them
and go to the platform.
The couple who gets there safely
and stands on the platform
will win the race.
The problem is...
in five minutes
the two teachers and
the student council members
will chase you
while wearing a bell.
That sounds scary!
Why make it so scary?
If they break your bracelet,
you'll be ousted.
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo's hint]
["Green K"]
Should we go to the rooftop?
What is green?
What is "Green K"?
The hint that I gave you
after the first game is
about the key.
It was divided into two parts.
[Yoon Bak and Joy
have "Seo with heart."]
I'm scared.
Wait, what's the meaning of the hint?
I think it's the shape of the key.
I think the first hint was the shape.
And the second one is the location.
So, where the treasure chest is.
Ha Ha received the second hint...
Where's Ha Ha?
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon's hint is
"Hallway on the fifth."]
[They're searching on the fifth floor.]
[Maybe the treasure chest is here.]
[They've found a key with a red heart.]
[They were looking for the chest,
but they found a key.]
[Too excited...]
[It's nothing, unless it's the
key with a green heart.]
Let's go downstairs.
Where's the key...
[They want to find the key first.]
Is it in this building?
[They need to find the key
before the teachers arrive.]
[Jingle-jangle]
They're downstairs!
They're already here?
[She changed to sneakers
to chase the students.]
["Class is forever..."]
Student!
[If they oust all the students,
the teachers will win the ring.]
[Run]
Student!
[Mr. Jung's also wearing sneakers.]
[Finding Students]
[Jingle-jangle]
[You better hide well,
because I can see your hair.]
Let's just wait here
until we can't hear the bell.
This is a large building,
how did they get down so fast?
I'll change the plan.
We'll start from the top,
and go down to the bottom.
We'll use the dragnet method.
[Dragnet: A net drawn
through a river or across.]
[A systematic search for someone,
especially criminals.]
[I can feel someone is here...]
I was startled!
I was scared to see myself!
I didn't know I could be this scary.
[Ashamed]
I was scared to death.
I've never been so surprised
to see myself before!
Student!
[Embarrassed]
They're not here.
[Gary and Ja In search
without a hint.]
- Where could it be?
- I'm scared.
Let's go downstairs.
[Maybe they will meet
a team with a hint.]
[Huh?]
[Maybe they'll have a
counseling session first!]
[Please, let us go!]
[Where are you going?
You need to have a make-up class!]
No!
[Dating is prohibited!]
[Gary, go out and get some air!]
I really love you, Gary.
Mr. Jung!
[Their dream of winning
the ring broke.]
[Gary and Ja In are ousted!]
Do you want to check the basement?
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
came down to the fourth floor.]
[Jingle-jangle]
The sound of the bell!
[It's getting closer!]
[Horrifying]
Where's the sound coming from?
[They decide to go down.]
Can you stand over here?
[What are you talking about?]
- You can block them.
- Shh...
This is floor P1.
The door will open.
[Jingle-jangle]
[Come back inside!]
[It's full of bells here, too.]
This drives me crazy!
They were right next to us!
I think they're on the P1
and the first floor.
Let's find a hiding spot.
I don't know why,
but it's so scary.
We can't both fit in there.
- You can hide.
- I can.
[They came to the auditorium.]
We'll be ousted if we get caught.
How about behind the curtain?
It's the wall.
I can tell there's someone hiding.
It's too obvious!
120 percent!
- Can you tell?
- I can't see you.
You can't see us, right?
If we get caught, give me the camera.
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo get off the
elevator on the fifth floor.]
- Is there only one key?
- I think there're many.
[Then enter the corner room
at the end of the hallway.]
Only one key will...
It there another one?
[They found a key with a green star]
[and a key with a red heart.]
We need to find as many as possible.
Kwang Soo, I feel uneasy
when we get off on the right foot.
I'll do my best today!
I can't let this opportunity pass!
[It's not a hallway?
There's another door!]
What's that?
[They found the treasure chest.]
[At last, they found
the treasure chest!]
Let's open it with the keys we have.
It doesn't fit.
It doesn't fit at all.
It has to be smaller than this.
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon
also enters the room.]
[That's Giraffe!]
Let's keep the key
so we can compare the size.
It didn't fit at all.
Ha Ha, wait...
[We already saw everything.]
Did you open it?
No, we didn't.
[Why would they still be there,
if they did?]
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon
have a key with a red heart.]
You found a key?
That's not it.
Let's not attack each other!
It doesn't fit.
[They thought they could open it
as soon as they found the chest.]
It wouldn't be this easy.
We need to find the right key.
[Jae Suk and Han Byul also
have the hint for the fifth floor.]
[Jingle-jangle]
[Run]
[Lock]
[Jae Suk and Han Byul hide
in the corner room.]
I think my hear will burst.
[Rustle]
What do we do?
[Lock]
[They go back to the corner room
from the secret room.]
They're so scary.
[Let's get out of here.]
It's locked!
[What's going on?]
[Rustle]
I think they're here.
Right out side of the door.
- Who's there?
- Open the door, Jae Suk.
Who's there?
Open the door!
[Oh, I know who it is.]
It's Jung Kyung Ho.
- Please, open the door!
- Suk Jung!
What are you talking about?
Open the door!
They're about to come!
Please, open the door.
It doesn't sound like Suk Jung.
But maybe they captured someone...
Tell me who you are.
I'm Dong Hun!
Ha Ha!
We're trapped!
Why are you upset?
Is this a door?
[They finally opened the door.]
Here's the treasure chest.
You know the lock...
It's connected.
You need to open the chest
with a key.
[Is that it?]
- There's the treasure chest.
- Let's go together.
If you have a key,
you can try opening it.
Then, we'll try and come back.
If you win the ring,
give us a half.
[Deeply moved]
Maybe we'll win the ring now!
[A key with a yellow heart
and a red heart]
This doesn't even fit.
[If it's not the key with the green heart,
it's not going to open it.]
[Who will find the right key?]
Where's the CCTV room?
There are CCTVs in there?
Excuse me.
They're nowhere...
[She found Giraffe.]
He's here.
Where is he?
He's in the elevator.
That's the elevator.
What floor are they?
[They're like a rat in a trap.]
I'm going insane, Kwang Soo!
My heart is beating so fast!
The door is opening.
[Peek-a-boo!]
Wait, Miss Hwang!
Listen to me!
[This is 100 times scarier
then getting caught as a student.]
[Horrifying]
It's okay.
Miss Hwang, please!
[Powerful discipline]
I can't help it!
[She broke the couple.]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are ousted.]
[Suk Jin and Na Rae have
eloped for an hour.]
Let's go to the jail
and ask what the hint is.
We have no clues at all.
Can you tell us the hint?
[Yoon Bak and Joy
are about the enter the jail.]
A key?
You don't know the location?
You don't.
You need to find a secret room.
Just check all the rooms.
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon think the same.]
Kwang Soo is over there.
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are ousted.
[They're entering the jail.]
They're ousted?
[Will they give them the hint?]
We found a key.
It's the red key.
Kwang Soo, why are you lying?
He's lying.
Ha Ha, my hint was...
"Green K."
Green key?
We guessed it's a green key.
Then it means a green key.
- There should be...
- It's red.
- You've already ousted!
- Why would you tell him?
I hope everyone fails.
We can't win the race.
Thank you, Ji Hyo!
Be careful, Ha Ha!
- Why would you lie until the end?
- We've searched for it all day.
We're already ousted.
Let the students win.
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon
are searching for a green key.]
[They searching from the corner again.]
[It's an empty box.]
Someone took it.
[We will never give up!]
They might have put it on the ceiling.
[They're searching every
nook and cranny.]
Careful, careful!
- There it is!
- Jackpot!
They hid here?
It's almost impossible to find it.
[It's a key with a green heart!]
It's green!
Let's go!
[Don't hesitate!]
Let's just go to the room.
The key is smaller then others.
Ji Hyo wouldn't have lied to us.
It's not a red key, right?
It'll never be a red key.
Do you believe what Kwang Soo said?
[It's open!]
Thank you, Ji Hyo!
- It's open!
- Ji Hyo!
[Thanks to Ji Hyo, they get
to see the legendary rings.]
Be careful, don't let
the bracelet rip.
[But, I'm too excited!]
Ji Hyo, we found it!
Now, we need to get downstairs.
- We need to hide it.
- Cover it.
Was that a mirror?
[What did you say?]
We don't have time for that!
I wasn't sure if it was a teacher.
[She's so different from
the character in the drama.]
[They get on the elevator quickly.]
Let's go to the P1.
[We've heard that the
platform is on P1.]
[It stopped on the third floor!]
The door is opening.
[Who could it be?]
[Could it be Ha Ha?]
[Or one of the teachers?]
[Ta-da!]
[Mr. Jung is here!]
[He's proud of himself.]
I've been waiting for you.
Why is it so easy to catch you?
[Use stairs, it's healthier.]
I'm a big fan of you.
I'm your fan, but I'm
your teacher today.
If you keep avoiding...
that's an infringement
of teachers right.
Please... let us go.
I'll tell you where others are.
No need.
I found the celebrity like a treasure.
Please give us
five more seconds.
You're standing too
close to each other!
I don't want to do this physically.
I know, I know.
Let's just go out.
It's too cramped here.
Okay.
- Do you want to run for a bit?
- Yes, just for a moment.
I see.
It's a children's game.
Red light, green light.
I'll count to three.
Red light, green light!
[run]
[Run]
[Stop right there!]
[Run for your life!]
[Body check!]
[She captures Grasshopper!]
[While Miss Hwang hold him...]
[Mr. Jung broke the couple up.]
Are they ousted?
Good job!
[They were wrecked in three seconds.]
[Jae Suk and Han Byul are ousted!]
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon
are running at full speed.]
[That's the wrong way!]
We can't get out of this floor.
We're almost there.
They've met.
They're running!
Don't we need to go now?
- Let's go!
- They got captured.
[Mr. Jung is seeing
them to the elevator.]
I almost captured Yoon Bak.
But they locked the door.
- It's impossible to catch them.
- I've caught them.
[The elevator opens.]
[Kkuk and Stephanie
are inside the elevator.]
[What a windfall!]
Mr. Jung!
I told you earlier.
[Kkuk appeared at a perfect moment.]
- Wait, wait.
- What about them?
We've already caught them.
[They're keeping an
eye on the situation.]
Are they walking around on P1?
[Let's go when they're busy!]
[They're still bickering.]
Kim Jong Kook!
They were on the fourth floor.
[What's going on?]
[They're the students
who are running away.]
[Victory is ours!]
[I can't let it happen.]
[Where is the platform?]
It's not here.
[If the platform is not on the P1,
they'll be like a rat in a trap.]
- Ahhhhh, it's here!
- It's right here!
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon
stand on the platform.]
We did it!
[Ha Ha and Seung Yeon
win the Legendary Couple Ring Race]
[Deeply moved!]
[We actually did it!]
[Too bad, I almost caught them.]
Today's winners are Ha Ha
and Gong Seung Yeon!
[The final winning couple are
Ha Ha and Gong Seung Yeon.]
Thank you.
[It's good that you won!]
By the way, Hwang Suk Jung and
Jung Kyung Ho were really scary.
- Yes, they were scary!
- Suk Jung, please show us how you ran.
Look at her!
[She runs like a ninja.]
She's so scary.
[Lucky, I didn't have to face her.]
Seung Yeon, how was the race?
I was worried about Running Man.
And it was scary.
But, I even won the race.
I'm so thankful.
It worked well.
[Congratulations!]
Your heart kept pounding, right?
Her Running Man experience.
She kept shaking.
Give us your thoughts.
I had so much fun.
I want to come back and win next time.
I'm regretting.
She's only warmed up now
that it's time to go.
She was absent-minded before.
Congratulations, again!
[Thank you, the two teachers
Jung Kyung Ho and Hwang Suk Jung]
[Yoon Bak, Park Han Byul,
Stephanie, Kim Ja In, Park Na Rae]
[Gong Seung Yeon, Joy.]
[A trip down memory lane]
Today's theme is
the Memory Throwback Race.
[The Running Man members'
throwback items]
[that made their dream come
true will be revealed!]
[Special command]
[Find the oldest shop in Seoul!]
[From a tail ship that's 100 years old
to barber shop that's 89 years old.]
[One on one mission at historic sites]
[Who will be the final winner
and adorn the history?]
I will win, no matter what!
[The Memory Throwback Race]
Subtitles by DramaFever