Subtitles by DramaFever
In recent news, the zombie rumpr
is spreading quickly on social media.
Apparently, zombies appeared in
a research laboratory in Seoul.
The government believes it will
destabalize the Nation
and requested an investigation by the
country's experts in cyber crime.
[Starring]
[Yoo Jae Suk, Kim Jong Kook]
[Ji Suk Jin, Ha Ha]
[Gary, Song Ji Hyo]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
That age-old zombie myth
has somehow come true.
The mysterious Zombie Virus
was not fiction.
They were not able to
figure out in advance...
The government has stated the
virus started in Europe ten years ago...
There are more and more victims...
A party who identified
the site has stated:
The government is in
control of this situation
all citizens may be at ease and
continue with their daily lives...
According to sources, buildings have
already been infected are uncontrollable.
All contact with field agents
has been interrupted.
False information about the virus
will be heavily punished.
The government has decided to
deploy the Running Men.
Many citizens are curious to see
If the Running Men can
break through this chaos
and find the cure for the Zombie Virus.
[Running Man Special Forces,
Operation: Area Deploy.]
[Gary]
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Ha Ha]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Ji Suk Jin]
[Yoo Jae Suk]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Special Forces' top agents,
all together at last.]
[Seoul]
[The Zombie Virus appearance location,
Operational Headquarters.]
[Running Man Special Forces' 7 members,
Danger Zone, secret mission.]
Semper Fi!
Commander!
Thank you all for coming here.
- Take your seats.
- Yes, sir!
Yes!
I saw him in a drama...
Don't talk about dramas,
he's our Commander.
I'm the director of the security program,
Commander Yeom Dong Heon.
What is the situation?
Where are the enemies?
As you all know, the Zombie Virus spread
from this secret research laboratory.
- Zombie Virus!
- Zombies!
We have figured out that there were
approximately 150 employees in the lab.
However, we don't know
how many survived
and how many have been infected.
We're in serious trouble.
[They must infiltrate the
mysterious operation area.]
[Find the survivors that are
hiding in the darkness.]
Our goal is to find all survivors
as well as finding Doctor Yeom,
the head of the lab
to find the solution.
Doctor Yeom?
Is he related to you?
Are you going to
come back with a mole?
We'll be disappointed
if you wear a wig.
I'm going to take off my wig!
Are you ready?
Once you've been bitten, you need to
take the cure within 30 minutes.
Or else, you'll turn into a zombie.
Unfortunately, the only
cure given to you
is this one.
Then we have to...
You will discuss who will
keep this among you.
The oldest one should take it.
So, me.
No, I'm in the middle.
[Their teamwork
collapsed in front]
[of the cure.]
- I can't protect myself!
- You've lived long enough!
Take your dirty hands off of that!
- Take your hands off!
- You guys are strong!
I'm weak.
- Be quiet!
- You be quiet!
Can I just take it now?
[He's trying to steal it?]
Is this for motion sickness?
It's not motion sickness medicine.
We will give a badge
to whoever rescues
the most survivors.
How much is it worth?
It's a badge, you fool!
[Oh, my Commander!]
[Ahem...]
Anyway!
The person who receives
the badge will be greatly honored!
I believe in you, soldiers.
I hope you make it back
without being infected.
- Don't worry!
- Dismissed!
Attention!
Bow!
- Suk Jin!
- Why are you taking that?
I'll just take it.
You guys are strong.
Someone must be sacrificed here.
In a horror movie,
you'd be sacrificed first.
Suk Jin would die first.
Jong Kook would be too confident and die
and they would die while in love.
So let's decide
between the three of us.
[I won't betray you with the cure.]
Can't you just say
"here have it"?
What's the point of you
having two lives?
[What did you say?]
[The truth came out.]
- Be rational!
- Let Jong Kook have it then!
He would be the scariest
if he turned into a zombie.
He would be on the zombies' side.
He would.
You usually save women
and the young ones first.
He might be clumsy
and spill it or something.
You're out, too.
[Giraffe was disqualified thanks to
his carelessness and being unreliable.]
[Who will keep the cure?]
I think it would be better
for Ha Ha to drink it.
[Quick witted Ha Ha is perfect for it?]
I think he would be best for it.
You can steal it
from each other, right?
He's already focused on thievery.
He's asking if you can steal.
[All the preparations are complete!]
[The Zombie Virus
that spread in the lab.]
[And the survivors that are
trapped in the lab facility.]
[They don't know how many survivors
there are or where they are!]
[Will Running Man be able
to save all the survivors?]
[Operation No. 9348234]
[Operation Lab Infiltration]
Please tell us
if something happens.
Stay focused even if
you turn into a zombie!
I got it!
Think about our memories and stuff.
We'll let you know
if anything happens.
- Let's go.
- Don't betray.
[Running Man Special Investigations,
Operation: Area Scout.]
Let's do our best until the end.
We'll rescue the survivors.
- Let's bring back as many as we can.
- Okay.
If you rescue them,
I'll bring them over.
What?
Let's not do that.
[Foggy view...]
[A dreary atmosphere.]
This building must be abandoned.
What's going on?
[How is it inside?]
It's scary.
[And there is...]
[And there is no one...]
[And there is no one to be seen.]
- It's spooky.
- It is.
We can't split up.
We need to stick together.
There are newspapers.
It's cold in here.
I know.
Did they make it colder on purpose?
We need to search all
the rooms one by one.
[The firmly shut doors...]
[There might be survivors.]
If we get bitten by the zombies...
Wouldn't there be
survivors in there?
The door's open.
[Agent Kim Jong Kook.]
Let's go see.
[The door is half open.]
I feel like a survivor
would be in there.
[Who left this behind?]
If you open if like that we might
bump into it while we run away.
Why are you so picky?
I don't think there are any zombies.
I heard something!
[Nervous]
We need to stick together.
[Looks around]
Let's go.
[Equipped with a weapon.]
I don't think there are any zombies.
No one's here.
Right?
- Let's go down.
- There are people there.
[They scouted out ground level.]
[Yoo Jae Suk, Ji Suk Jin,
Song Ji Hyo are deployed.]
I don't know what it is, but it's scary.
What happens if we get bit?
We need to save survivors, right?
Survivors!
Are there any survivors out there?
Doctor Yeom!
[The hallway's silent.]
Are there any survivors?
There aren't any here.
This is before something
big happened.
[Right before a storm.]
[Where are the survivors...]
[They]
[might be coming for us.]
[Agent Kim Jong Kook
and Lee Kwang Soo]
[are entering basement level one.]
[Thud!]
Why are you so loud!
It's so dark!
I think there will be survivors...
I don't think there
are zombies here.
There are zombies!
- What do we do?
- There are a bunch.
There are too many.
[What is the true nature
of the zombies?]
There are way too many!
[In the dark...]
[In the dark,
the zombies finally started to move.]
Do we just need to run quickly?
- I don't think they're fast.
- Right?
[They're entering the zombie
concentration zone.]
There are so many!
They aren't attacking us?
It's no joke!
It's so intense!
Let's go that way.
How?
Let's go to the machinery room.
Let's go this way.
Shouldn't we look at all of this?
Survivors...
Are you there?
Survivors?
They're not here.
Kwang Soo!
[Oh my god!]
[The zombies appeared!]
I'll actually hit you!
[Rational thinking went out the window
when the zombie showed up.]
[Oh my god]
[They recompose themselves
after their zombie encounter.
How do we go in?
There's so many of them!
Do we just have to run?
[How do you expect us to go in there!]
Maybe we just don't
need to get caught.
[Agents Yoo Jae Suk,
Ji Suk Jin, and Song Ji Hyo]
You're really scared, aren't you?
I'm so...
I can't even look at zombies.
The basement...
This building has up to
five basement levels.
I see zombies.
There's are zombies over there.
There are actual zombies!
There really are zombies!
Zombies...
Oh my god!
[What was that sound?]
You stepped on it!
Are you going to do this again!
- It was him?
- He stepped on it!
Don't be scared and run away!
Gwon Yeol...
[Zombie Cave: take two.]
[Pale]
[He takes a step back.]
There are more in there!
There are too many!
Wait a minute.
Wait, we're not supposed to run away.
Wait.
What's wrong?
[They ran into Gary and Ha Ha.]
- There are way too many.
- Really?
We can't even go in.
Do you know the
zombies' characteristics?
What do they look like?
You know the zombies in movies?
[The memory they can't get rid of
after looking at the zombies.]
- Can we get the zombies out?
- We don't know.
- Do they have name tags?
- Yeah they do.
- Maybe we eliminate them.
- We should try it.
- Let's try it.
- Should we?
[The zombies' labels on their backs.]
[This is the zombies' weakness?]
[Agent Jae Suk starts his
investigation on level two.]
There's more over there!
It's so realistic.
It's too scary.
[Are there really survivors here?]
[Blank Ji also enters level two.]
We need to find survivors.
They're over there.
[Why is there a door knob?]
[There's a secret room!]
[Who is here?]
Our goal is to find all survivors
as well as finding Doctor Yeom,
the head of the lab
to find the solution.
Doctor Yeom?
Is he related to you?
[Doctor Yeom, whom we have to rescue]
[is right here...]
[Doctor Yeom,
biotechnology expert.]
[He cut off all contact while
revealing truth about zombies.]
Doctor!
[Agents Grasshopper and
Blank Ji found the Doctor.]
Doctor!
What happened?
[What on earth happened?]
You've come a long way.
However, it's too late.
I've already been infected.
Wow, I'm so into this.
What do we do, Doctor?
How can we save the people?
How did you come all the way here?
I've done countless
experiments for
the extension of life.
And in one, there was a
modification in the DNA.
It developed into the Zombie Virus.
I was able to discover a few clues
thanks to my research.
[What are the clues
to get rid of the zombies?]
[Shake, shake]
I've found a few facts.
They have atrophied eyes.
They don't react to light.
They react to big sounds.
Lure them with sound.
With sound.
[Crash]
It's one hundred percent.
They're moving to the sound.
They can't see.
[But as soon as they are detected
by sound, they're in danger.]
And the second clue.
If you eliminate the
name tag on their back...
[Rip]
They die!
[Did they find the way
to kill the zombies?]
- Oh, so we do this.
- Let's eliminate!
If you eliminate the
name tag on their back
they'll faint for a
short amount of time!
It's only for a while!
And like me, if you get bitten
you'll be infected right away.
If you don't drink the
cure within 30 minutes
then you'll become a zombie.
We only have one cure.
There are cures hidden
throughout the building.
You must find them
and save the people.
[And!]
This is all of my research.
Please use this and
save the people.
[Take Dr. Yeom's research notes
and give it to the Commander.]
Argh!
[The transformation has begun.]
The Doctor is changing!
Let's go!
[Please save the people for me!]
[What kind of clues are
in the research notes?]
Jae Suk!
They're calm again.
There are so many!
Don't talk!
They're turning around.
I don't think we should make noise.
They turned around when you talked.
[Mr. Capable found out one
of their characteristics.]
There's a laptop with an R sticker.
Ahh!
[Scream!]
[This is big trouble if you scream!]
[The zombies are heading
to where Mr. Capable is.]
[He got away with his strength.]
[You betrayed me in front
of the zombies?]
[An eye for an eye,
a zombie for a zombie.]
[He's about to unleash
the zombie in the storage.]
Please listen to me.
Ahh!
[It's already our second encounter.]
She went back in!
Really?
Do they really react to sound?
They all turn around
when you scream!
Seriously... don't do that again!
Okay, I'm convinced now, thanks.
[They go back into the zombie
cave to retrieve the laptop.]
[Giraffe is leading the way
to atone for his actions.]
Ahh!
[Ahh!]
[Mr. Capable's counterattack.]
[Have a great time with
the zombies, Kwang Soo!]
[Thud, thud]
[The zombies moved
toward the door.]
[I can't let them hear me breathe!]
[He retrieved the laptop.]
[He escaped the zombie cave.]
They react to sound!
I'm done with Jong Kook.
I got everything
I need from Jong Kook.
[What's the clue left in the laptop?]
Observation summary!
"Observation summary.
Experiment number 45."
"They don't feel pain."
"What is the difference
between dead bodies..."
I was scared,
but not anymore.
I found out that they react to sound.
Everyone, you can escape a crisis
if you are calm like me,
in any situation.
[Zombies' characteristics]
[They react to sound.]
[The can't feel pain.]
[You must drink the cure within
30 minutes if you've been bitten.]
There are so many...
They're so scary!
Be quiet!
They're there!
There must be a clue.
What?
[Did he see a survivor or a clue?]
Is that a zombie?
[A questionable
zombie is collapsed.]
Go in!
- Why is it lying down?
- Go in.
[I said go in!]
- Did you find anything?
- Yeah.
[He found a clue.]
[A clue beside the zombie.]
"Observation date, summary.
Experiment Day 30."
"It still can't talk."
"It can't learn any of the words,
but only makes weird noises."
"It's more like an animal
than a human."
"It only moans without
any specific symptoms."
"All other subjects are the same.
No matter what medication is used..."
They did experiments on them...
"To obtain emergency food supply"
"go near the basketball court."
[They need a food cache
to fight the zombies all day!]
- That scared me!
- It's so creepy!
Why are they so good at acting?
That's incredible!
[Armory storage]
There must be weapons...
What is it?
What is this?
[Why are there neck warmers?]
It must be like a talisman.
Should we try
putting it on their neck?
Wasn't she wearing
something on her neck...
This is it!
Zombies die if we put this one them!
If we put this on their necks...
[They found the weapon that]
[could get rid of the zombies!]
Now, we have to be quiet.
[Neck warmers are the only weapon
that can get rid of them completely.]
[Agents Big Nose and Ha Ha, looking for
survivors in basement level five.]
You go in!
Survivors!
Is there anyone alive?
Are there any survivors?
[They search the hallway.]
Survivor?
[Surprised]
I think they would be in here.
That's really scary!
[Is that a zombie or a person?]
Are you a survivor?
Are you sure?
- Turn around.
- We found a survivor.
We're coming up.
[We need to take
the survivor out to safety!]
[Be quiet!]
Suk Jin!
Throw something over there.
[Zombie distraction plan.]
[They're heading towards
the emergency exit.]
There's another person in there!
Back there?
In basement level five?
[There are more people to rescue!]
[One point is given to the agent who
brings the survivor out to safety.]
What are you doing?
[I need to bring him out!]
- Survivor!
- He's a survivor!
It's Ji Suk Jin.
It's Ha Dong Hoon.
No, I saved him!
No, I brought him in first!
Ji Suk Jin came in first!
- What?
- Yeah, I came in first.
He said so!
[What is this nonsense?]
[Agent Big Nose saved one survivor.]
[Agent Yoo Jae Suk and Song Ji Hyo]
[returned to headquarters
with the research notes.]
I think we have to bring the survivors
and put stickers on them to win.
We need to hurry and find survivors!
[Agents Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo
are circulating basement level four.]
Is anyone there?
Are you a survivor?
Come out!
[They found a survivor.]
- Please come out.
- I'm hungry.
[Agent Giraffe hands her
a candy bar without hesitation.]
I want hard candies.
You're picky.
[Her blood sugar is low.]
I'm rescuing you, you know.
We don't have hard candies,
I'll give you the candy bar for now.
Have some candy.
Let's get out!
Come quickly.
[She need to escape first.]
You're such a picky eater.
We're surrounded by zombies.
Be quiet!
Don't refuse even if the food is bitter.
[They might be in a great danger,
if they get caught.]
My friend is hiding over there.
[Another survivor is hiding
on the same floor?]
Over here.
- There's writing, help.
- Where's writing?
[They move carefully in
case zombies attack.]
[It's over there.]
[Cough]
[I want to live!]
[He's holding his cough desperately.]
[Mr. Capable will take
her to the aide station]
[while Agent Giraffe
focuses on searching.]
It's okay, you'll be fine.
[Agent Lee Kwang Soo
finds a survivor.]
Are you immersed in the role?
My friend is hiding somewhere.
[Again]
Why does everyone have so many friends?
Can we just get out for now?
[There are zombies in front of them!]
[They need to move quietly.]
There' the exit!
[Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook, and
Lee Kwang Soo rescued one person.]
Here's the survivor!
I rescued her!
Everyone!
Here's the survivor!
[Running Man special investigative
team's emergency preparedness meeting]
This is just the start.
There's got to be something else.
Zombies let us walk around.
As time goes by, they might be faster.
Or get scarier in certain conditions.
Before it happens,
we need to solve the problem.
I think there are
scarier zombies inside.
Strong zombies will appear.
If something worse happens,
we have no ways to survive.
We found a computer file earlier.
It says they become smarter and smarter.
They're going to be smarter
as time goes by.
[30 minutes ago, Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
found the zombie observation journal.]
They can use their brain.
They can't feel the pain.
They couldn't talk before,
but...
I found out the same thing.
After a certain time,
they can talk.
That was number 88.
They'll have the ability to talk.
What's that?
[Jong Kook, Gary, Ha Ha and
Kwang Soo found Dr. Yeom's office.]
- Doctor Yeom!
- What are you doing here?
How's the situation?
I've met your twin brother.
Thank you for finding me,
but it's too late.
I'm already infected.
What about the cure?
Are you a zombie?
Trap the doctor!
Give him the cure!
We need to save the doctor.
I drank it already.
We need to save him.
It's too late for me.
You'd better leave here!
Doctor Yeom, promise me
you won't bite us.
In the movie, the doctor
usually asks to be killed.
I want to live.
He's very honest.
[This is reality.]
- Maybe it's better than turning...
- Just go!
[Do you know how hard
to act like a zombie?]
Stock up on some sugar.
[Scream]
You scared me to death!
[A zombie appears in the lab.]
[They can break into the lab now!]
[They didn't act like this before!]
[Their attacking skill and
the speed are upgraded.]
What happened?
[You need to escape!]
Look at him!
- Kwang Soo!
- Why is he so fast?
[Even the doctor?]
Kwang Soo, please!
Kwang Soo!
[Agent Ha Ha is infected
with the Zombie Virus.]
Did he bite you?
[If Ha Ha doesn't drink the cure,
he will become a zombie!]
How can they all leave without me?
They're really fast!
The zombies are a lot faster now.
Antidote!
Take the cure from Ha Ha!
Kwang Soo, take the cure!
Suddenly, they move so fast!
[Of course, he's trying
to drink the cure.]
[No, that's the only cure we have!]
Take it from him!
Antidote!
[We need to stop
him in case of emergency!]
[Will he drink, or will they stop him?]
Don't let him drink!
Quickly!
It's so delicious.
[He drank it in one gulp.]
Did he finish it?
I drank it all.
[Ha Ha was the wrong choice.]
How can you all run away without me?
We should've taken it from him earlier.
- We're done for if they bite us.
- Did he drink it?
[They lost their safety device.]
- They bit me, so I drank it.
- Why did we give it to him?
What are you doing in
front of a dying person?
They're so fast now, I couldn't
draw their attention with sound.
Doctor Yeom.
[How come you didn't give it to me?]
Look at his eyes, let's get out!
[Starting now, the zombies'
counterattack begins!]
[Currently, the zombies are evolving.]
[Speed up]
[The counterattack of
the running zombies]
They're so fast.
They're too fast.
- What do we do?
- It's over.
We're done!
[Will they be able to save the
survivors from the evolved zombies?]
[The zombies have finished
the second transition.]
[Something's different?]
[The zombies are noticeably faster.]
[They're working in
a worse situation now.]
- Huh?
- What now?
[He found a laptop
with an experiment log.]
Zombie Observation Journal no. 76!
First, they were only walking.
Now, they can run like humans.
We're in trouble!
They even talk?
[The zombies can run?]
[The zombies are becoming
stronger and stronger.]
[They're searching for the survivors
and cure in a hurry.]
They really run!
[And they're fast!]
Run, run!
[Terrified]
They can't climb up the stairs.
[The only safe zone is the stairs.]
They run.
Suk Jin, the zombies can run now.
- Did you see them running?
- Yes, we just saw.
[Like the journal says,
the zombies started to evolve.]
It's getting worse.
[It's going to be harder
to save the survivors.]
[At the same time, they're more active.]
There are so many of them.
Why so many?
[Agent Jong Kook is searching for
survivors on the second floor.]
[There's no way out.]
[Could there be anyone in here?]
[A survivor!]
[A zombie senses his presence,
and approaches.]
[Rip]
[Mr. Capable rips the zombie's
name tag mercilessly.]
[After attacking one, another
zombie attacks him.]
[Struggle, struggle]
[How come it doesn't open?]
Come over here!
[I don't want to.]
Bring it on, Zombie!
[Please save me!]
[He eliminates his name
tag with his strength.]
[This might be better.]
[While the zombies are out,
he escapes with the survivor.]
Let's hurry.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I didn't know you were in there.
[Two zombies couldn't stop Agent Kkuk,
and he saves two survivors.]
[Agent Giraffe searches harder.]
[Sneaky walk]
[Agent Giraffe goes in deep.]
What?
[He found the cure!]
[Knock, knock]
Someone just knocked!
Where is it from?
[Someone's near here!]
Where is it?
[A survivor successfully
signaled for rescue.]
[But, he could also be
a target of zombies.]
[It's full of zombies on the way out.]
[Both of them passed
the zombies safely.]
Why am I such a good finder today?
Are you okay?
Just trust me!
There's a survivor.
Are you a survivor?
[The found a survivor
hiding behind a pole.]
[They carefully checks to
see if he's infected.]
- A survivor?
- Another one?
There are a lot of survivors.
Search for more.
I'll escort him.
Suk Jin, why don't you search?
I need to escort him.
[Bickering]
[Of course, a zombie heard them.]
[Run to the stairs!]
[Here's another one.]
Run!
[There's another one.]
Quickly!
[Running at full speed]
There's a zombie!
It's not even funny!
[It's hard to find the exit because
the building is like a maze.]
Wait a moment!
[There's the exit!]
- Aren't they really scary?
- Yes.
[A group of zombies are
chasing after them.]
[The ultimate weapon, neck warmer!]
[He couldn't put it on him!]
[In a hurry, they run
toward the stairs.]
- Suk Jin...
- I tried to put it, but failed.
I can't go to the lower floor.
They can't climb up the stairs.
[It's too much.]
- The zombies are faster now.
- They're really fast!
Did you find any?
[What did I find?]
Kwang Soo?
You delete all the files
and rip all the journals
everywhere you go.
Are you really going to play like this?
Should we infect him?
- We might...
- I won't do it any more.
Don't we need to see what
happens, if we're bitten?
- How can you say that to me?
- Think about what you did.
Make one mistake, and you
won't ever be forgiven!
We're a team, you know!
Are you kidding?
I don't trust you.
I guess the survivors
must be scared, too.
They run so fast, when zombies approach!
The survivors act like zombies.
It's hard to tell who's zombie
and who's survivor.
The zombies are evolving.
Where did Suk Jin go?
Since he's not here...
Not yet.
[Agent Big Nose and Ji Hyo are trapped.]
We need to eliminate their name tag.
And make them faint for a moment.
He's coming.
[Tap, tap, tap]
Rip it now!
[While Ji Hyo lures him with sound,
Big Nose ripped his name tag.]
Run!
[And they escape while he passes out.]
- Is there a way out?
- Yes.
[Stomp, stomp]
[Imminent situation]
Suk Jin, hurry up!
[She lets Agent Big Nose escape.]
[And saves the survivor!]
[Thank you, Ji Hyo!]
[Agent Big Nose safely
enters to the stairs.]
I barely escaped.
[It feels like they survived
in the battlefield.]
With all the running,
it's pretty tiring.
[Agent Song Ji Hyo finally
saves a survivor!]
[Gary found a survivor on
basement level two.]
When I count to three, we'll
run behind the zombie.
Catch it!
[He drew the zombie's
attention with a stick]
[and rushes to the stairs.]
It's okay!
[Plop]
[Her legs gave way
with all the tension.]
[Noisy]
- Gary?
- Did you save her?
Gary, let me escort her.
I'll escort her.
[Everyone wants to get a point.]
I'll carry her on my back.
Wait, Kyung Hee!
- Kyung Hee...
- She's Suk Hee.
- Jae Suk, Kyung Hee's over there!
- Where?
- Kyung Hee's coming.
- She's infected!
In the lower level...
there are a lot of survivors.
[There are many survivors to rescue!]
[We'll be on our way...]
Where?
[The zombie's rush!]
[Gary's caught!]
[They leave Gary alone and run away.]
[Even though it's an emergency,
I must protect the survivor!]
[Scream]
He's bitten!
[Help me...]
[Big-nosed Brother stole the survivor.]
Gary's bitten.
I brought her.
- Gary saved her!
- Where's Gary?
[Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Suk Jin saved two,
Jae Suk and Ji Hyo saved one.]
[Scared to death]
It was really scary.
I need to eat something.
[The zombies are evolving quickly!]
I didn't think they'd be that fast.
[Faster than we thought!]
Was Gary bitten?
I think so.
I'm 100 percent sure he's bitten.
If he can't find the cure,
he's done for.
That's right.
We need to find the cure, too.
We should.
Where is the survivor?
Where did she go?
[Agent Giraffe arrives to
the crime scene a tad late.]
- Were you bitten?
- I wasn't.
- You dirty zombie!
- Come back!
[I'm not a zombie yet!]
I'm going bite you before
I turn into a zombie!
Where is the survivor you rescued?
I got bit and you're not
worried about me at all?
[Should I have expected otherwise?]
[I'll just go search for the cure.]
- I need to find the cure.
- Where is the survivor?
My life is over, so don't talk to me.
[There's no time to lose.]
[If he can't find it within 30 minutes,
he's going to the zombie world.]
Look at me, I got bit.
We're friends now.
[Gary is walking around
the zombies casually.]
[Searching]
I'll bring them here when I
become a zombie later.
I'm in trouble!
[He's in a hurry, but
this building is huge.]
[There's no clue or someone
who can help him.]
[Will Agent Gary be able to find the
cure and cure the Zombie Virus?]
[The agents are scared after
Gary's been infected.]
You've been bitten.
What are you talking about?
[Kwang Soo looks suspicious as usual.]
Why did you walk away
when you saw us before?
Gary!
I'm in a hurry!
I'm so sorry!
Call me if you find the cure!
I'm sorry, but I'll be in a meeting.
[I'm sorry, Gary.
I found the cure.]
[Air of innocence.]
- You didn't get bitten?
- No, I didn't.
He must have drank the cure
even if he was bitten.
But we don't have the cure.
He probably found one
already and drank it.
- Where did you hide it?
- I didn't find one.
Let me see.
[Will they find the
cure he's hiding?]
Do I have to get treated
like this every time?
[Rummaging]
[Phew... they didn't find it.]
Let's go.
Let's make them faint!
Make who faint?
The zombies, one by one.
We can rip their name tags.
[Basement level one]
[Agent Big nose is leading the troop.]
[To draw their attention,
he grabs a stick.]
[At the moment he was about to get in]
Big Nose!
[Huh?]
[Did the zombie just talk?]
[Slam]
[The door shut.]
[You were greedy for points,
have a taste of this!]
[Thud, thud!]
[Scream]
[What comes around goes around.]
Isn't that too harsh?
[He was betrayed by his colleagues.]
[And attacked by the zombies.]
They talk now!
[Hooray!]
[Agent Ji Suk Jin is infected
by the Zombie Virus.]
[The cruel end of their betrayal.]
It's Suk Jin!
It's all because of them.
- Did Suk Jin...
- He's bitten.
Kim Jong Kook shut the door.
- Seriously.
- Hurry up and find the cure.
Are you my colleagues?
Why did you keep stealing
the survivors, then?
He's bitten!
I brought a really important
piece of information.
What information?
A zombie talked to me.
What did he say?
He saw me and said,
"Big Nose!"
[Did the zombie really speak?]
[On many observation journals]
[they found the fact about the
zombies' ability to evolve.]
I'm serious!
[The zombies have evolved again!]
[Big Nose has to find the
cure in 30 minutes.]
Friends, it's me!
See?
- I've bitten.
- Big Nose!
Yes, I'm Big Nose.
Nice to meet you!
[It's just one word, but they do speak!]
Friends!
- Big Nose!
[He doesn't have much time, but he
gathers zombies and plays captain.]
Friends, do you know
where the cure is?
Big Nose!
[They can't make a sentence yet.]
Do you know where the cure is?
[Agent Gary has less than 10 minutes.]
[I hope it's here...]
[What?]
[He found it!]
[Agent Gary barely avoided
turning into a zombie.]
How do we know when he
turns into a zombie?
He's coming here.
Gary!
Do you feel any changes?
I found the cure.
Hurry up and drink,
and don't tell people.
[He's cured.]
Gary!
I'm your friend, Gary.
[I'm sorry, Suk Jin... I survived.]
[Basement level three]
[Agent Giraffe is searching
for survivors alone.]
[Since he has the cure,
he's walking between zombies.]
Are you a survivor?
[He walks faster than anyone else,
so he finds more survivors, too.]
[He shares his emergency food.]
[He's rescued three people so far.]
[In a moment...]
[He finds another survivor.]
[He rescues her safely while
surrounded by the zombies.]
[Basement level two]
- Are you a survivor?
- Yes.
There's no zombie here, right?
It's okay to bet bitten by a zombie,
but don't go to other agents.
- Are you bitten?
- What are you talking about?
- Aren't you bitten by a zombie?
- No, I'm not.
[He was too busy rescuing survivors,
so he doesn't know what happened.]
[Where could the cure be?]
[Another survivor?]
Let me take him to the aid station.
[Is he still trying to
steal the survivor?]
[Avoiding Big-nosed Brother,
he's leaving the building in a hurry]
- Did you find the cure?
- Kwang Soo.
Where do you find all the survivors?
Gary!
[While everyone wants
to steal the survivors]
[Kwang Soo saved six people.]
Justice prevails!
Lee Kwang Soo!
Don't worry, I'll save the planet!
[Yes, you can save the planet.]
[and Big Nose has to find the cure.]
Antidote, where is it?
[His body starts acting up.]
No, I need the cure!
I can't die like this!
Please!
Please, I don't want to be a zombie!
It's weird...
My body feels weird.
No, no!
[Chills...
His acting is brilliant!]
[Stay tuned!]
[Big Nose is zombie-fied!]
[What's the sound?]
What is it?
[Big Nose zombie]
[Scared to death]
[From the looks to the way he talks,
he's completely turned to a zombie!]
We're in trouble!
[Like old friend like zombies.]
[Big Nose has changed..]
Big Nose!
- Big Nose!
[Everybody say "Big Nose!"]
Bite... all!
[Big Nose's method acting]
[And Giraffe watches
him from a distance.]
[Laugh]
[This is too embarrassing!]
[He laughs without a sound.]
[He approaches without a sound]
[and records him in the face of danger.]
[It's an exclusive!]
[Look at this!]
Big Nose!
[Laugh]
[What a surprise!
That's how I look?]
[Shh... look at Suk Jin.]
[Peek-a-boo!]
[It's awkward for both of them.]
It's awkward for me, too...
[He's too awkward, he had to
express it to his old colleagues.]
- Hurry up and look.
- Is there anything fun to watch?
- Yes.
- Grasshopper!
[Everyone's laughing.]
[That's too funny!]
Why are you laughing?
[It's funny for me, too.]
That could've been me
if I didn't find the cure.
[Wait until you're infected,
I'll laugh at you so hard.]
[This is tiring...
but I must act!]
Grasshopper...
What's that?
[Agent Ha Ha found a survivor
while everyone's laughing at him.]
Let me escort her.
I found a critical hint.
I found only two so far.
- I saved... six.
- You saved six people?
Kwang Soo rescued a lot.
[Hideous]
Suk Jin couldn't get the cure.
Look at what happened to him.
I had it,
I should've given it to him.
You had it?
Why didn't you give it to him?
Antidote!
He had it.
- I have it...
- That's why you could walk around.
[His anger rises suddenly.]
I couldn't find him.
It's not that you couldn't...
that's why he could walk around
the building so freely.
[You had the cure,
but you kept watching?]
[Charge!]
[Angry zombie Big Nose's
target is Giraffe.]
He bit him!
[An eye for an eye,
a zombie for a zombie?]
[Was Big Nose's revenge successful?]
[He's relaxed about it.]
[Here, bite me as much as you want.]
[Big Nosed zombie is in front of him]
[but he doesn't bat an eye.]
[You watched me turn into a zombie]
[and laughed at me!]
[You had the cure,
but you didn't help me.]
[I want revenge by making
you a zombie, but I can't.]
[No matter how much you bite me,
it doesn't matter to me.]
[I have the antido...]
[He dropped it!]
[I have to find it no matter what!]
Friend!
[Welcome to the zombie world.]
This is bad, it's over if Kwang Soo
turns into a zombie.
[He's the icon of betrayal,
a war will break out.]
No!
Not the cure!
It's not going to work!
[He drinks what's left in the bottle.]
It's not enough.
[Throws and tramples]
I drank it, now what?
It's this much short.
What's wrong?
Why can he speak so well?
Am I going to be a zombie?
Feel, touch, cross!
I don't want to be.
I saved six people!
I saved six!
Let me find the cure!
- I must find the cure!
- Friend...
[He needs to find the
cure within 30 minutes!]
Antidote!
Have you seen any?
Move away!
Antidote!
My badge!
Antidote, cure!
It's fine.
We're fine.
[Ji Hyo puts him
at his ease like a real agent.]
Where did you find all the...
Are you okay?
Do you want to go with me?
[What is he talking about?]
[I need to rescue people...]
We're fine.
[Oh, my!
That's...]
Antidote!
[As soon as she sees Giraffe,
they're immediately on stealth.]
Antidote!
Have you seen the cure?
[Forget the answer!]
[Run for your life!]
Antidote!
- I'm in trouble!
- You have the cure, right?
[With Kwang Soo's call,
a crowd of zombies follows him.]
Jae Suk, I rescued six people!
- You don't have the cure?
- No, I don't.
[Completely surrounded]
[While Agent Jae Suk holds the zombies,
Agent Ji Hyo hides the survivor away.]
[Agent Jae Suk is left alone
with the zombies.]
[Bite]
Kwang Soo, you...
[He got bitten by the zombie!]
I had no choice!
This is how you play?
I have no choice but to do this.
You called all the zombies...
This is upsetting!
Go find the cure,
you're bitten by five zombies.
Seriously, you are...
No, just practice before
you become a zombie.
- I have no time.
- Let's work together.
We're friends now.
Wait a moment.
[Agent Jae Suk is infected.]
We survived!
[Agent Ji Hyo and the survivor
escaped the building.]
What a trouble for you!
I see many people here.
[Agent Song Ji Hyo successfully
rescued the survivor.]
I got scared!
[While searching for the cure,
he's back at the lab.]
Someone drank it already.
[An empty bottle]
[Disappointed]
Where is the cure?
Antidote, cure!
I don't have time!
Antidote!
Oh no!
[His face changed]
[and his eyes changed.]
[But why does he look natural?]
[I'm not Kwang Soo any longer,
I'm just a zombie!]
Ha Ha...
Ha Ha!
[Don't let me catch you!]
[Agent Haroro is searching
the basement level four.]
[He found something?]
[He found a laptop which has
a clue about the zombies.]
Save me!
[Someone's asking for help!]
Where's it from?
Did someone ask for help?
[Content of observation]
[We found a new fact.]
[It's a surprising turn!]
[A surprising turn?]
Help me!
I'm a survivor, please save me!
- Save me!
- Gary.
There's must be someone out there.
[It sounds desperate.]
Save me!
[Save me...]
[I can't control them any longer.]
[I've created a monster.]
Is that a woman or a man?
[Agent Ji Hyo follows the
voice without doubt.]
Save me!
What about Ji Hyo?
[Scream]
[A group of zombies tricked the agents.]
[And their leader Big Nose!]
[She's bitten.]
Friend... friend!
Friend...
[Agent Song Ji Hyo is infected.]
[Now the zombies are
as smart as humans.]
[Save me...]
[Here's a "person."]
The zombies talk now.
They sounds just like humans.
They're coming.
They're coming as a group!
Why are they coming all together?
They can move along the stairs!
[The stairs are not
a safe zone any more!]
Why do they chase us?
Why do they do it?
[The zombies have no limits!]
[Kwang Zombie is acting
like a leader already.]
Feel... touch... cross!
Ha Ha... Ha Ha...
Jong Kook...
bite him...
[Zombie Big Nose and Kwang Soo
are full of vengeance.]
[The grim air is spreading
from behind the door.]
[Agent Jae Suk became a zombie!]
[Three agents have been turned
into zombies already!]
I'm bitten!
[Ji Hyo's bitten but she keeps rescuing
the survivor before the virus spreads.]
[She uses the fact zombies don't
attack the ones who are bitten.]
[Big Nose zombie follows them around.]
[He bit him!]
What are you doing?
Are you bitten?
Let's find the cure together!
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha are at the lobby.]
[Currently, the number of
the agents who are uninfected]
[are three out of seven.]
You and I, you saw I drank
the cure, right?
Except who was bit or became zombies?
- So, it's us and Gary.
- Only three of us.
Then what do we do?
There are three survivors
inside the building.
How do we rescue them when the
zombies are running around?
[They don't have much time left.]
Somewhere here...
[It's the cure!]
We found it!
There's only one.
I'm bitten already!
I'm bitten.
I'm not lying.
Look at it.
I'm bitten, and he's bitten.
Don't attack us,
we're both bitten.
We're all friends!
[She calmly walks to the stairs.]
Don't attack us.
[They successfully escaped.]
[The two of them are infected,
but there's only one cure.]
Drink it quickly.
You need to survive first.
I'll go find the cure.
[She gives the cure to the survivor,
and goes back to the building.]
Stay here, I'll be back!
Lee Kwang Soo, the cure you had...
Lee Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
[We finally meet here!]
Do you remember me?
[Of course I do!]
[I'll get you!]
Why are you looking at me?
[Kwang Zombie's only target is Ha Ha.]
[He's running away at full speed.]
Why are you only following me?
It wasn't my idea,
I heard what they had to say.
I could live.
[If not you.]
I didn't have to wear this makeup.
[He can't forget his grudge.]
I rescued six people.
You tried to kill me
when I was drinking mine.
[It's best to avoid the
zombie with a grudge.]
[He won't be able to come inside.]
No, no!
[He tires to avoid Kwang Zombie,
but meets with Grasshopper Zombie.]
Wait, wait!
Come, my friends!
[Open the door,
Ha Ha's mine.]
Come over here, my friends!
[Scream]
[Bite, bite, bite]
[No, you can't...]
Let's go back.
At least, I wasn't
bitten by Lee Kwang Soo.
I'm already bitten.
[Why you little!]
It's all because of you!
[You made me a zombie!]
- I should bite him!
- I'm already bit.
[Blank Ji doesn't have much time left.]
Where's Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo is...
[What's that?]
[The super-arm she found
at the weapon storage.]
[If we use the neck warmer, she can
put the zombie to sleep forever.]
[She kept hidden the weapon
to eliminate the zombies.]
[It's time for revenge!]
[Burst]
[It was close but she failed.]
You made me into a zombie!
What are you doing, friends?
I can put this on anyone, you know!
- What are you doing?
- Come over here!
- Why?
- Song Ji Hyo, Song Ji Hyo!
[No one's on my side...]
[then, I'll run away.]
[Catch the big-nosed zombie!]
[We meet again.]
I hate to see them.
[It's Kim Jong Kook!]
He's... wearing... a jacket...
What a...
selfish... bastard!
Kwang Soo...
[The zombie couple]
[Laugh]
[Perfect sync]
We'll get you!
Just come over here!
He's the only one wearing a jacket!
He doesn't want to get cold!
[They're afraid to attack him.]
I'm sorry.
If we wear the red thing, we might...
- Are you bitten?
- Yes...
Really?
Show me your arm.
[He's pretending to be infected.]
[Is he really bitten?]
[Run]
[He escapes by acting to be infected.]
[As the zombies evolve,
the humans evolve, too?]
Antidote, I'll die if I can't find it.
[Ha Ha is busy searching
for the cure.]
[He found the cure.]
[Thrilled]
How could this be here?
Aren't I amazing?
[It's the second time he
drinks the cure.]
I'll drink it first,
and pretend I didn't.
I drank two cures now.
[Thanks to his eagle eyes...]
Don't tell anyone.
[he's not going to become a zombie.]
[At that time, the agents
get the radio from the base.]
All the agents who survived,
to the base!
- Gary.
- What's the current situation?
Thank you for your work.
From the sacrifice of our military,
we could save a lot of people.
Let's check what
Doctor Yeom passed onto us.
[Doctor Yeom's secret research
brought by Jae Suk]
She was contacted by zombies
but wasn't infected.
She must have an antibody!
We can make a vaccine in quantities.
Basement level three, restricted area.
The password is 2710.
That's the key to this problem.
Wait a minute, what do we do?
[A secret capsule
is hidden in the building]
[and the girl is sleeping in it.]
We checked all the survivors you rescued,
but the girl is not on the list.
Then, she must be inside the building.
She's resistant to the Zombie Virus,
only if we can rescue this girl
will the nation be saved.
Infiltrate to the building
and rescue this girl, dismissed!
[The girl rules the fate
of the zombie war.]
[Will they be able to rescue her?]
[It smells like human again...]
[Ha Ha and Gary infiltrate
to the basement level three.]
[Find the hidden restricted area!]
[Kkuk is heading to the
basement level three.]
We need to hurry and get there!
Maybe there's a hidden doorway.
[Where's the restricted area?]
It's not here.
Where's the restricted area?
Wasn't it here?
[Restricted area]
[He found it!]
[Inside the metal door,
there's a secret door.]
[We found it, finally!]
[The password: 2710]
[In here...]
[the ultimate weapon will be.]
[She can finish the zombie war!]
[Will they be able to cut their way
through and safely rescue her?]
The capsule is right there!
Is she sleeping in the pod?
How do we wake her up?
[Is there any way to wake her up?]
[Something's going on...]
[We need to find humans...]
Se Hwi, we need to get out!
We don't have time!
It moves!
[The pod is moving.]
She's so pretty.
She's awake.
[The capsule opens]
[and the girl wakes up.]
[Shin Se Hwi]
[Her DNA is resistant to zombies.]
Who are you?
- We came to rescue you.
- Are you Shin Se Hwi?
We'll rescue you to save the mankind,
so we can make the vaccine.
Just follow us, we'll protect you.
[Only if we can lead her to the base...]
[Do not let the humans escape!]
[Humans, it won't be easy to get out!]
- Let's go!
- Hurry!
[Let's escape!]
We need to run,
we don't have time!
We need to run!
We need to escape!
I've got bitten already.
[Are zombies make their way?]
Escape quickly!
What's wrong?
[Scream]
[Jong Kook, get out
while I hold onto them...]
We don't have time for Gary and Ha Ha.
They might turn into zombies.
Se Hwi!
I hope the vaccine will be developed!
[I hope you escape....]
[They're not attacked by
the zombie to a wonder.]
Just one more floor, Se Hwi.
[Welcome, humans...]
[Something's wrong...]
[The zombies aren't attacking us?]
[Then, I can escape, too...]
[If he can get out of the building,
Jong Kook will win the race.]
[Where do you think you're going?]
[We won't let you go that easily.]
[If the girl escapes,
the zombies will fall.]
[Hurry up and escape!]
[We can't let the girl go!]
[Bite]
[Before he turns to a zombie, Ha Ha
throws his body to block the zombies.]
[It's too late for us, anyway!]
[Leave the zombies with us.]
- I'm already bitten!
- I just want to bite you!
[Please go ahead and end this war!]
[The commander and the girl successfully
escape by the armored car.]
[Although all the Running Men
lost their lives]
[they finished the mission to save
humanity from the zombie threat.]
[That's how they saved
humanity's last hope]
[and zombies meet with a tragic end...]
[The case of the zombie appearance
at R research is completed.]
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
Thank you for the hard work!
Thank you for your trouble!
Bite this VJ.
[Special Appearance]
[Yeom Dong Heon, Shin Se Hwi]
[Announcers: Shin Dong Wook,
Jung Mi Seon]
[Ji Jeong Sik, Kim Yoon Sang,
Kim Seon Jae]
[The Zombies]
People might think it's real news.
Many citizens are curious to see.
[Thank you again
for all your assistance.]
Real!
Situation!
Sunday, I like Sunday!
X-men!
[Running Man presents
X-man for X-mas!]
[2005's legendary characters are back!]
[Chae Yeon, Lee Jong Soo,
Lee Ji Hyun, Andy, Stephanie]
[The challenge of 2015's!]
[Seolhyun, B.I and Bobby of iKON,
Kim Ji Min]
[The real battle between the legend
and the most popular rookies.]
You're the x-man.
[It doesn't end with X-man!]
[Find the hidden mission
of Running Man!]
Are you really seeing Song Ji Hyo?
[Running Man, X 2015]
Subtitles by DramaFever