Subtitles by DramaFever
[No one knows why.]
[No one knows where...]
[He's stuck inside the mystery cube.]
[Gary is nowhere to be found!]
[Find Gary, who's trapped
somewhere in Seoul.]
[The only clues are
Gary's testimonies.]
[As they close in on Gary,
the shocking secret comes to light!]
["Lost in Seoul"]
[Rescue Gary!]
[South of Banpo Bridge,
Seocho-gu, Seoul.]
- Hello!
It's so cold!
- You dressed warmly!
- It's so cold, Suk Jin.
- You're all here?
- Gary's not here.
- Where's Gary?
- Where is he?
Today, it's...
[No way!]
[Don't tell me...]
We're starting without Gary?
"Finding Gary Race."
- We have to find Gary again?
- Did he go to Europe again?
Isn't he at his place?
He's probably sleeping.
[What happened to Gary?]
[An hour ago.]
Hello, everyone!
It's cold.
It's so awkward being alone
with this many cameras.
You haven't seen the
members yet, right?
What are we doing today?
I can't lie to people, you know that!
What is that?
[A mysterious box?]
[A room?]
What's with...
That's prison.
You want me to go inside now?
Gary was here an hour ago.
We put him in a cube,
and sent him away somewhere in Seoul.
[You put him in a cube?]
- Why did you do that?
- Seriously?
[Yes, he's confined.]
Can you hear me?
[Gary is locked in
the high-security cube.]
Then give me some food!
I need to live!
[He went inside on his own two feet,
and now he's trapped.]
Can you hear me?
[What on earth is going on?]
Yoo Jae Suk, Ha Ha,
Song Ji Hyo are a team.
Kim Jong Kook, Ji Suk Jin, and
Lee Kwang Soo are a team.
You need to find Gary.
We just need to find him?
It's simple enough!
What happens if we find him?
Gary doesn't know this, but...
There's a bed inside the cube.
A bed and a wardrobe.
He'll sleep no matter what,
if there's a bed.
There are bunch of diamonds
underneath his bed.
[There are diamonds
underneath his bed!]
[Eyes wide open]
He doesn't know about the treasure.
If he finds the diamonds
while searching the cube
then he'll have a chance
of winning on his own.
[He has no idea he has
diamonds under his bed.]
[It's right here.]
They're not good at searching!
[Shake]
[The cube started moving!]
Please move it slowly, slowly!
[Gary is being moved
without knowing why.]
What is this...
It's still early!
Hold on, wait!
You should let me see the outside!
Excuse me!
[Blocked view!]
[Impossible to know the location!]
[Where is the cube headed?]
Whoever finds the diamonds first wins,
and the race will finish.
Either the two teams or Gary.
So it's a battle
between the teams, too.
It's not rescuing Gary,
it's just finding the diamonds.
Gary is just near the diamonds.
[Find Gary!
No, find the diamonds!]
[To Gary, it's just escaping the cube!]
[To the members,
it's finding the diamonds!]
[The destination is unknown.]
[He finally arrived]
[after a long drive.]
[Nervous]
[Open]
[Where is this place?]
[Water...]
[Bridge?]
[He can see parts
of his surroundings.]
[Where is this place?]
You have 60 seconds to make a call.
60 seconds?
That's too short!
[Find out as much as you can
about the location.]
[And let the members know.]
Huh?
It's the sound of a train!
What is this...
[There's a train running nearby?]
It's ringing!
[It's a three way call.]
How do you pick it up?
Did it work?
It is connected?
He's calling us.
- Gary!
- I think it hung up.
I can't work with old men.
What you mean old men?
Have you not tried a three way call?
Jae Suk hung up, too.
[This is so frustrating...]
- Pick up!
- It's ringing!
Hello?
- Gary!
- Hello?
- Hello, who is it?
- Gary, where are you?
Listen carefully!
I can hear a train.
You can hear a train?
The sound of a train,
and I see water.
- Water?
- I can see Han River.
- You can see Han River?
- Yeah, and I'm under a bridge!
- Under a bridge?
- Yes.
- There are at least 10 bridges.
- Dongjak Bridge?
It must be subway!
- I can hear a train!
- I think it's the subway.
- By the riverside...
- A subway?
Do you see any signs?
There aren't any!
- I'm trapped, come quick!
- Give better details!
What's on the other side of the river?
It hung up...
[60 seconds is over.]
He's bad at explaining things.
[His first call ended quickly.]
Jae Suk!
[Did they find out where he is?]
[The cube will move again
in 60 minutes.]
If you touch a single
strand of Gary's hair
I won't stay still!
[Jae Suk's team is on their way.]
[There are 31 bridges on Han River.]
[The subway passes
near seven of the bridges.]
[They have to get there in 60 minutes.]
I think I know.
In Dongbuichon-dong, the subway
passes where you can see the river.
[Ha Ha's guess: He can see the Han River
and a train can pass in Dongbuichon.]
I think I know where it is.
You know, trains can
pass the Cheongdam...
- Cheongdam Bridge?
- Yes, Cheongdam Bridge.
He said he can hear it,
he didn't say he can see it.
He would've said otherwise.
Under Dongjak Bridge...
It's Han River Park.
Oh, you're right!
- That's probably right.
- The parking lot.
Gary!
Where is Gary?
- Gary!
- Be quiet!
- Do it alone!
- Go over there and film it!
[Immersed in the act]
Gary!
Could it be that building?
Like that rooftop?
He could be on top of the building!
[He said it's under a bridge...]
[He's playing by himself.]
Not a train, it's subway.
Subway?
Not a train?
Dongjak Bridge has the
railroad for subway.
The subway passes
on Dongho Bridge, too.
It's either Oksu station...
- or Dongjak Bridge, which is closer?
- Oksu station.
- That's closer.
- They're in opposite directions.
We need to go that way to Dongjak...
The enemies have
used their brains well.
Just go do it over there.
[We'll solve the mystery.]
Our enemy is no ordinary man...
You're right.
They will move him again,
if we can't find him.
Yeah, if we don't find him in an hour.
There are train tracks here.
I was talking about here.
Look.
Maybe he thinks a
water reservoir is Han River.
Maybe he's in Lake Park!
A park here in Yongsan?
You can hear the subway from here.
[With these circumstances,
they think it's Dongjak Bridge...]
Gary sucks at explaining!
He must've have not seen
the movie, "Taken."
He should have said how
many pigeons he can see, too!
We only have two clues,
we can't find him.
For example, "there's someone jogging."
"There's someone on a bike."
He sucks.
[Jong Kook's team is
heading to Dongho Bridge.]
To put it out there, it doesn't matter
what happens to Gary.
[He's already in betrayal mode.]
It'll be good if we could rescue him,
but we just need to find the diamonds.
While you wait for the members
we will take down part of the wall
stickers, if you succeed the mission.
Then you will be able to see
more of your surroundings.
If you succeed, we will give you
another chance to make a call.
- Are you going to do it?
- Of course!
[It looks like private food in prison.]
[Water bottles and match boxes?]
Put the water bottles upside in order,
on top of match boxes.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Challenge!
Are you saying that the
bottles shouldn't collapse?
Does this even work?
Challenge!
[He can try unlimited times.]
[He failed so quickly.]
Even the first bottle fails...
[A bad omen from the beginning...]
I'd better do it quickly.
Challenge!
[He failed again.]
Is this possible?
[It worked.]
Challenge!
[Mr. Random Capable got two in a row.]
[The third bottle didn't make it.]
[While he doesn't know where he is,
he's still doing his mission.]
I look like a crazy man...
[Jae Suk's team is
going to Dongjak Bridge.]
[Jong Kook's team is
going to Dongho Bridge.]
[Jong Kook's team arrived
near Dongho Bridge.]
Oksu station is right
in front of this building.
There are trains there.
[Oksu station on Seoul Subway Line 3]
Wait, you can see the train here.
You can see Han River, and trains.
You can see the River...
You can see the River
and hear the train.
- Isn't it here, Suk Jin?
- The train passes the bridge.
Isn't it somewhere under the bridge?
I think so, too.
[Gary is somewhere here?]
- Is there a way to go under the bridge?
- Yeah, there is.
Okay.
Which way?
I can't believe I'm so important.
This is really hard.
What about Yanghwa Bridge?
Okay, okay.
- Are you annoyed?
- Yes.
I don't why you want to go there
so badly, but I'll go anyway.
Or should we really just go
to Dongjak Bridge?
Dongjak Bridge...
I don't think so, it's too close!
- I'm not feeling it.
- Let's go there first.
Alright, I'll go to Dongjak Bridge.
- I swear it's Yonghwa Bridge...
- Ji Hyo asked to go to Dongjak Bridge.
Let's hear Ji Hyo out first.
Jae Suk, we started on Banpo Bridge.
Do you think they put him so close?
You're not two passengers sharing a cab!
Think about it.
It's too close!
Well, we can drop by
since it's on the way.
This is the last chance to
enter Gangbyeon Expressway!
[The time is passing,
but they don't know where Gary is...]
Gary should have given
the tiny details, too!
[What is Gary doing at this time?]
I'm going mad.
[He's still struggling.]
[Why doesn't this work...]
[It's not something really difficult.]
I'm so angry!
It's been a long time since
I was so stressed out.
[He needs to get the hint.]
I need to do it in one try!
[Focused]
[Please, work...]
Okay!
[He did three bottles!]
[There is hope.]
Okay!
[There's only one bottle left!]
[He got it in one try!]
[He succeeded with all five bottles.]
I should have used my left hand!
Maybe I was a lefty.
[He got black bean noodles too
thanks to his left hand.]
Thank you very much.
[What?]
[He lifted the blankets!]
Gary doesn't know this but...
There are diamonds
underneath his bed.
Gary doesn't know about it.
If Gary finds it first
then he gets to keep it.
[Gary didn't know
about the diamonds.]
[Did he find out while he was
trying to eat black bean noodles?]
[But just then!]
[They removed a wall
sticker from the wall!]
[There's a number?]
[Stare]
This is under my building!
This is Ttukseom Resort Station!
[He got a huge hint
through the tiny hole.]
[It's a view that he's familiar with.]
I know where I am.
It is Ttukseom Resort Station.
I don't have to get out now,
can I eat the noodle first?
I haven't eaten a bite yet.
They can't unlock it
even if they get here.
Most likely, I'll solve
the problem on my own.
[North of Cheondam Bridge]
We got a call from Gary!
Where are you?
[Gary called after the mission.]
Dong Hun!
Calm down.
[He's more hyper than Gary.]
Jae Suk, I know for sure.
I'm under Ttukseom Resort Station.
- Ttukseom?
- Ttukseom Resort Station!
Not Ttukseom Station,
Ttukseom Resort Station.
Ttukseom Resort Station?
Gary, Gary!
[He calls Jong Kook's team, too.]
I'm at Ttukseom Resort Station!
I know where it is.
We'll come quickly!
I won't let them hurt you!
Take Gangbyeon Expressway.
And go through Han River Park.
We just need to stay on
Gangbyeon Expressway.
[Jong Kook's team is closer!]
Go straight.
We need to take Yeongdong Bridge road.
It's really close from here.
Ttukseom is where we rode bikes.
Take Seongsu Bridge,
and take the Olympic road.
[They just need to take
Gangbyeon Expressway.]
[Why are they going on the wrong way?]
I'm like a navigator, right?
I'm such a great assistant!
[Tactless Big-nose and Kkuk
who has no sense of direction]
[Together, they've
made a big mistake...]
Recalculating route.
We're going the wrong way!
[He figured it out too late.]
Oh my god...
He's not helping at all.
There's not so much difference.
You have to travel
twice the distance.
- We'll get there soon.
- We have to come back.
Yes, but it'll be quick.
[He's trying to be calm.]
Right, this way.
[Jae Suk's team is heading
to Ttukseom without a problem.]
There's an entrance to the
Ttukseom Resort Station.
It's under here, right?
[She's giving detailed information.]
[Navigator Blank is providing
even the tiniest details.]
- This way?
- Yes.
Oh, there's an entrance.
- It's here?
- Yes.
That's expected of Song Ji Hyo.
You came here for a date?
[Found guilty!]
- A jimmy jib over there!
- What is it?
- There's a camera crane!
- Where?
[It's right there!]
[They arrived to
Ttukseom Resort Station.]
[They got a call from Jong Kook's team!]
Suseo?
Why are you going there?
You went the wrong way?
12 kilometers?
The navigation is wrong!
Wow, this happens.
I can't believe this happened.
[How is it possible?]
I'm laughing
because we could have
entered Yeongdong Bridge.
We could have gotten there already.
It was four kilometers before,
now we have to travel 12.
[Will they be able to see Gary today?]
They're heading to Suseo?
- He's right there!
- Where?
- Gary!
- Dong Hun!
[Jae Suk's first encounter
with the cube.]
There are so many things around here.
Why did you explain it like that?
[There are diamonds inside?]
I didn't have enough time.
- Does it have to be you?
- I know, it's always Gary.
They ordered black bean noodles
for me though.
I ate the noodle at least.
It was so good.
[He's so simple.]
Looking at the river while eating...
[That's that...]
[But have you found the
diamonds underneath your bed?]
Please let me out.
[What's the mission
that can get Gary out?]
There's 14 minutes left.
In the meantime, do you see that?
Stand beside it and shout
"watch out for colds!"
[And you have to catch the
snot in ten seconds.]
You can have as many key cards
as the number of catches.
- Really?
- Yes, hurry since there's not much time.
We have to catch it, right?
Okay, ready.
Watch out for colds!
This doesn't work!
You're not doing it on purpose, right?
We're trying to rescue you!
Ji Hyo, I only have you.
Watch out for colds!
[Really?
You're sniveling this fast?]
You can't catch it?
This is frustrating!
It doesn't work...
Watch out for colds!
[He has to catch it when it moves.]
[It's not easy.]
How do we catch that!
- You really can't catch it?
- It's too fast.
Watch out for colds!
[Now, they can use both hands.]
[The screen is not paused.]
[Playing hard to get]
This is driving me crazy.
I really want to try it!
Watch out for colds!
I caught it!
You caught it?
[Their first success.]
Am I going out?
There are more than one key?
I caught it!
Song Ji Hyo!
That's amazing!
- She's good.
- I caught it.
Watch out for colds.
He's so determined.
He is determined.
[He has malice.]
[They only have one try left!]
There are two at the back.
Watch out for colds!
[Success]
We did it!
Awesome!
[They got three keys in total.]
We can at least do this
because we got here early.
Suk Jin's team won't
be able to see Gary.
[Jong Kook's team
is lost on the highway.]
We came all the way to Suseo.
[We just took Seongsu Bridge,
how did this happen?]
When we come to our minds,
we're in Suseo.
[Laugh]
Let's laugh it off.
[Do they laugh when
they're too stressed?]
[Finally, they' having the
opportunity to open the cube!]
How many keys do you see?
There are too many!
[They can pick 3 out of 30.]
This is insane!
- Pick one, Ji Hyo.
- You should pick, Ji Hyo!
[Each of them will pick one.]
[Did they pick the right key?]
Please open it for me.
[The race will be over if the door opens,
and they find the treasure box.]
[Please, please, please...]
[Failed]
- It didn't open?
- No.
It doesn't work?
[The second trial]
Both of them are wrong.
[It's Ha Ha's turn.]
Gary, good luck!
- You're the last hope!
- Open it!
- Here we go!
- Let's go!
I want to go out and play!
I want to save you, too!
[We want the diamonds!]
[Will it open?]
[Failed]
[60 minutes have passed,
the cube will be moved!]
Order another bowl of noodles!
Gary, tell us everything you see.
You should tell us
every single thing you see.
The location of the bridge,
something like that.
- You can see Han River very close.
- You can see the trade center from here.
Look at this, Jae Suk.
They block my view like this.
We'll rescue you, don't worry!
[We'll rescue the diamonds!]
- Ji Hyo, I'm counting on you!
- Wait a little, we'll be there soon!
Please!
[The cube is moving.]
[Help me!]
What are they doing?
Gary is almost 40 years old.
[A 40-year-old man is riding something
that other people push for him.]
What are we doing?
[Bizarre scene]
Seeing them makes me want to get out.
[His lonely battle continues.]
He's over there.
Right over there!
- There's a large box.
- Where?
[Jong Kook's team arrives on time.]
We found him!
[Right before they put
the cube on the truck.]
- Yes?
- Gary!
[They found the cube,
before the cube was gone.]
- Gary!
- Yes!
- Where are you?
- Please, rescue me!
[He was trapped in this kind of box?]
Get up!
- Gary!
- He's over here.
Who are you?
What have you done?
Kwang Soo, film that alone.
Come to the car when you're done.
Gary!
No!
[Actor Lee Kwang Soo is
burning his heart for acting.]
Suk Jin!
Why did you go all the way to Suseo?
It was the navigator.
Don't make us
look like a foolish team.
Think about it.
It's two to one.
What's two to one?
[Two fools vs. one ordinary man]
What are the two?
I become a fool when I'm with them.
I went to Suseo.
When it's so absurd,
you don't get mad.
I just laughed.
We kept laughing all the way.
[Could we possibly win the diamonds?]
[The cube was placed
in an unknown place.]
[Where could it be?]
[What's that for?]
[Mr. Gary is sleeping in the cube.]
[He doesn't he's stopped moving
and keeps napping.]
[The cube is revealed.]
[In the middle of a square,
an attraction is opened.]
What are you doing?
I have privacy, too!
[It's awkward for the
people passing by, too.]
Seriously!
Why are you doing this to me?
Please respect my privacy!
You should've told me.
[They don't care about his privacy,
the cube is on display.]
I'm staying here, as
if this was my house.
You can call the two teams, one by one.
[It's time to call SOS again!]
[I need to gather
as many clues as possible.]
[Where is this place?]
[He seems many female students.]
Wait a minute.
[There are many cafes and stores.]
Where am I?
Wait!
[Ehwa...]
[He found a crucial clue!]
I saw it clearly!
I think you've made a mistake.
[The six members are meeting
after the first mission.]
It's Gary!
- Let's just use one phone.
- Gary!
Kwang Soo!
I have no time!
- Hello!
- Gary!
Jae Suk!
[He has 60 seconds.]
- Where are you?
- I can see the outside.
It's close to Ehwa University!
Ehwa University?
You know that one way
that connects to Ehwa University?
Yes.
- I'm right there.
- We'll be there.
Who kidnapped you?
I'll be right there!
I won't ???
??
I told you to do it alone!
Jae Suk!
We've played a game here.
You know the place we
played Rolling the Ball?
I know!
On the tray?
- Yes, hurry up!
- I see!
- What tray?
- Let's go!
[Jae Suk and Ji Hyo
played Rolling the Ball.]
We'll go rescue him!
I don't know who they are.
But, I wont ??
You're in my hands!
Let's go!
[Jae Suk's team and Jong Kook's team
are moving toward Ehwa University.]
[Gary rescue team is on the move!]
[Diamond rescue team is on the move!]
[Gary's mission for
escaping cube starts!]
We'll get rid of another sticker
when you succeed at this.
I see.
Start now!
[Using the spatula, he has to
make the five sticks stay under.]
Do not hurry, there's got to
be an easy way.
Are you playing with me?
That's it!
[Satisfied]
[He attacks the second bottle.]
[Even with a slight move,
it goes back up.]
[He hit too hard.]
Even the people watching
look embarrassed.
This is embarrassing.
[Mr. Gary is struggling!]
There's no easy way for this.
I need to keep hitting.
Until it works.
I know where Gary is.
He doesn't need to give
us a clue, we know where he is.
I don't know what the mission will be.
If Gary doesn't find the diamonds...
How can we take out the diamonds?
We need to open the door first.
Yes, we do.
[If Gary doesn't know
about the diamonds]
[they should be underneath the bed.]
Do you think Gary found out?
Or he's just pretending?
They said the diamonds
are underneath the bed?
There's should be a way
that Gary can escape by himself.
If I were trapped somewhere
I'm sure I'd search up the room.
I have to make a left!
What are you doing, Suk Jin!
We were in the middle lane.
[20 minutes passed
since Gary started his mission.]
[Remain calm]
[He successfully gets
the first stick in the water.]
But it'll come up, when I hit this one.
[Be careful what you wish for.]
This drives me crazy.
[He accidentally did it by hand.]
You said I can do this!
[He can do it by either spatula or hand.]
[He has to do it in 30 sec. by hand.]
Please!
[Only one stick is left.]
Failed!
[Laugh]
[Such a push and pull!]
I don't know why I'm doing this here.
[One tap and all the sticks float.]
[Mr. Gary's plays it by hand.]
[He's working on
two bottles at the same time.]
[The maximum concentration]
[In 15 seconds, he got 3 bottles.]
[He's working on the last two bottles.]
[Will he succeed this time?]
One
two, success!
[He succeeded at it!]
Okay!
One more number will be removed.
[He succeeded at the mission,
one more number will be opened.]
[By the way...]
[Two hours ago, Cheondam Bridge]
[After Gary succeeded at his mission]
[He was enjoying the black bean noodles.]
[The lock...]
[A number!]
Huh?
Is that a pin number?
Zero is part of the pin number?
You're giving me the pin number!
How many numbers do I need?
[Another number is revealed now.]
[The two numbers are zero and one...]
Can I try to open the door?
If it opens, I'll escape right away!
[Out of four numbers,
Gary knows two.]
[If he's lucky,
he might be able to open!]
When they set a number,
they use a meaningful one.
[Gary's guess: 2016]
[Gary's guess: 1004]
2015.
[Gary's guess: 2015]
[Beep, beep]
What's wrong with this?
[It's so hard to open the door!]
We're almost there.
We're here.
This is one way.
[Jong Kook's team arrives
at Ehwa University.]
- Where is he?
- It must be over there.
[We need to get there first,
so we can get the diamonds.]
They're right there!
We're here first, right?
[That's the cube!]
[Gets up]
[Oh my brother!]
- Gary!
- Were you sleeping?
I just started to get comfortable.
What is all that?
For my mission!
[Gary has a mission?]
They gave you a mission, too?
What is the mission for?
I don't know.
They give me numbers.
A number?
They're giving me numbers one by one.
[The pin number?]
[That means Gary can take the
diamonds and escape by himself?]
[The diamonds are
hidden underneath the bed]
They said the diamonds
are under the bed, right?
[Mr. Gary was walking around the bed.]
[Did he find the diamonds?]
[Strong circumstantial evidence!]
[The bed skirt is lifted.]
[Is Gary acting innocent?
Or does he not know a thing?]
If Gary finds the diamonds
in the cube
then he will have a chance to
escape and have them for himself.
["Finding Gary Race"
Get all the treasure and get in the car]
[that the members brought,
and you will be the winner.]
I'm captured here, hurry up and come!
[He kept asking for help]
[but was he actually aiming
for their car?]
We need to get there first.
[What's the meaning of Gary's smile?]
[A fierce battle of wits
for the diamonds begins!]
[Two and a half hours passed.]
You need to play the game,
and acquire the card key for this door.
I can escape, If you get
the right key quickly.
Then your team will win.
Do you know what the prize is?
[Surprised]
They said we'll get a prize later.
We'll get something at the end.
I could escape from here,
but it'll hurt my pride.
[How can I say what the prize is?
Maybe it's on your body.]
[We're one step late!]
Gary was sleeping here,
when we got here.
[Jae Suk's team and
Mr. Gary meet again.]
Let me out!
What's that?
Zero and one?
Is that for the mission?
[Every single move he makes
becomes the cause of alarm.]
[Don't take your eyes off Gary!]
[We're watching your every single move!]
The mission is a
six-player pinball game.
- The pinball?
- That sounds fun!
You need to bring three citizens.
With them, try and move
the ball to score.
- 50, 100...
- It's 10 points.
You can pick a key for every 30 points.
Okay!
- Do you understand?
- It sounds easy.
Hello!
Try to pick meticulous looking person.
Get a man!
Who wants to play the game with us?
[Me, me, me!]
Hello!
- We need another person.
- My husband!
[A married couple joins Jae Suk's team.]
We have two.
Ji Hyo, you pick a person.
Can you play the game?
Do you have time?
Do you want to play the game with us?
- Do you have time?
- We have one man.
- Do you want to play?
- Yes, I do!
[Both teams recruited their teammates.]
[The result of the game
depends on the citizens!]
Let's start playing.
Good luck!
I hope I get lucky,
and get out now.
I'm counting on you!
[So polite]
He can escape from there.
It all depends on you!
I'll get more chances to get out!
Just escape from the window!
Can you hear me?
- Let's play and see.
- Let's see how it is.
Get ready!
They must be dating.
They're newly married couple.
The wife strongly
recommended her husband.
We started having a crush on each other
around the time that Running Man started.
Oh, when, around the
first episode of Running Man?
They've been together
for all of Running Man.
Really?
[Jong Kook's team has ten tries,
Jae Suk's team has five tries.]
Ready, set...
[They have less chances, but
they stand a chance of success.]
[If we can open the door,
the diamonds will be ours!]
[The first round starts.]
Slowly, slowly!
That's nice!
Good, good!
[The ball moved to the second zone.]
We need to stay calm.
Stay calm!
[They failed at it.]
[Look at that!]
[To stir up their mind,
he's acting annoying.]
[Calm down.]
We don't need to hurry.
[Like this?
He's Yoo Black Hole!
He can't make the ball go through!
Let's do it!
[The second round starts.]
We need to yield for each other.
Ji Hyo's partner is working so hard!
Good!
[Confrontation]
Don't fight between married couple.
One of you needs to yield.
That's how the married life is.
[Jae Suk's team failed twice.]
You should step back
for each other.
Please don't fight over this game
when you get home.
This is just a game.
Don't put too much meaning to it.
[The third pin ball starts.]
[Blank Ji controls the
direction in front.]
- This looks good!
- I have a good feeling!
We're so serious.
- They must have figured it out.
- I can't hear anything.
[Shake, shake]
Husband, to the side!
Just like that!
It's good!
Slowly, slowly.
[What's the score?]
[Dud!]
[Oh, no!]
[They're blaming each other.]
Dud, dud, dud, dud, duh!
Why are you doing that?
He has two names,
Yoo Dud, Yoo Black Hole.
- Yoo Dud, Yoo Black Hole.
- We'll put the rest in 50!
[The fourth round starts.]
Good, good!
What good is it if the ball passes
it will end up for a dud.
[Let's go, to 50!]
[It went to the hole.]
[What's that?]
[Making fun of him]
[Let's celebrate for the hole-in-one!]
What are you doing?
I see, I see.
[Their last chance!]
Here we go!
- Good luck!
- There's no time limit.
[Jae Suk switched with Ji Hyo.]
Slowly, slow!
It's okay, do it slowly.
Good!
They're in harmony.
[Push is to that side.]
What are you two doing?
- Your life...
- Slowly!
[It's going toward the goal!]
[Jae Suk's team gets 50 points.]
[That's nice!]
[From 0 to 50.
What a reversal!]
Wow!
[We did it!]
It's 50 points!
Good job!
One key card is enough!
Thank you for your work!
[Jong Kook's team got here first,
they have 10 chances.]
There's no time limit,
so let's not rush it.
Play is slowly!
[The first round starts.]
- Wait, wait.
- Just a little longer, Gary!
Focus!
You need to focus!
To that side!
Toward the hole!
It's good!
[It's on the right track!]
Good!
[Emergency, it's going toward the hole.]
[They've avoided the crisis with power.]
[They've acquired 50 points
from the first round.]
[You can win at
everything with power!]
We're a team with a monster.
They threw the ball.
[The second round starts.]
Go for 30 points!
30 points!
[They've avoided the hole.]
[Surprised]
[The ball bounced,
but it passed through.]
[The Full Power Brothers
will solve the problem!]
30, 30!
It worked!
[Jong Kook's team acquired 50 points.]
[Nice, Brother!]
Jong Kook's good.
It's terrific!
[The third pin ball starts.]
Slowly, slowly.
It looks good!
[Power up!]
[Jong Kook's team gains 10 points.]
10 points!
Are you allowed to hit the ball
with the game board?
We're too good!
Don't you think so?
[Power of the two men shines.]
It might go down the hole.
Stop, stop!
Okay!
[Jong Kook's team's current
score is 120 points.]
[The eighth round]
Let's go!
[Another 10 pointer.]
[Fantastic, Brother!]
- He's hugging him forcefully.
- Why so stiff?
You should go with the flow!
[They have 130 points now.]
[It's their last round.]
- Do it slowly.
- Make it flat first.
Look at that.
[A smooth pass]
Let's aim for 50 points!
[This is the last round,
we'll finish it with 50 points!]
[The ball is headed to a hole.]
[What will be the result?]
[50 points!]
[Unbelievable!]
[Jong Kook's team is the best!]
Awesome!
[Jong Kook's team scores 180 points.]
[They get to choose six key cards.]
Thank you!
[Thank you for the cooperation!]
Pick the key carefully!
We can use 150 points!
[It's time to choose key cards!]
Pick it well!
Suk Jin, pick the right one!
[Jong Kook's team can get 6 keys,
Jae Suk's team can get 1 key.]
Pick the right key!
I don't think it's not among them,
I think it's in the middle.
I think it's this key.
[Following Ha Ha's intuition]
Please!
If the door opens,
the light will turn green.
If the door opens now,
the recording will be too short.
We'll have to figure something out.
When the key fails,
it'll beep red.
You can try now,
are you ready?
- Please!
- What if it opens now?
Please...
[Gary, I'm sorry...]
You can do it!
[but our target is the diamonds!]
[Will the cube open?]
[Jae Suk's team's key card fails.]
It's red!
What a relief!
It's our turn.
- How many cards, can we have?
- Six.
I pick this one.
I'll pick number one.
I wanted to pick two, but...
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I pick number eight!
[Big-nosed Brother picks no. 8.]
I'll pick another one.
Pick another one, Jong Kook.
Should I pick in the same row?
- Maybe they can open it!
- We have six keys!
You can do it!
The looks on the
filming crews are strange.
Maybe we got the key.
They're bustling!
We must have picked.
[Trying Kwang Soo's key]
We six keys, it's possible.
[I'm counting on you!]
[Let's go, Kwang Soo!
To get the diamonds!]
[Kwang Soo's key card fails.]
Good riddance!
[I can hear you, Jae Suk.]
[His checking with the second key.]
Kwang Soo!
[The second key fails.]
I don't feel bad about it.
[Big-nosed brother
checks with his key.]
For some reason, I think he'll open it.
[Could it be true?]
No, it doesn't.
[He fails to open.]
[Anxious]
We have such a high probability!
- It's more than 20 percent.
- Nope!
[Big-nose's key card fails again.]
Is it Jong Kook again?
It's going to be a good show,
if I can open it.
The lead character appears
at the end of the show.
[I'm sorry, we'll take the diamonds!]
[Mr. Capable's first key fails.]
It wasn't.
Good, good!
What a good actor!
I have one key left.
[Nervous]
Please, please!
[This is the last chance!]
[The one who wants to open the
door and earn the diamonds...]
[The one who might be
hiding his real intention.]
[How will it end?]
[To be continued
at the next location...]
I knew it.
[Disappointed]
[Sigh]
It doesn't open.
Galory, see you soon!
Among these keys...
try number 29.
- I was going to pick it.
- Don't lie to me!
We really thought about that.
We almost picked it.
- It opens.
- It's that one?
Come out through the window.
Do you think it'll work?
It's the rule.
I'd go out if I'm allowed.
Should I go out like this now?
I can't get out
because of my pride.
[I won't crawl just to get out.]
Please, move him quickly.
I'll tell you all the details,
come quickly!
Gary, see you!
See you!
[See you again!]
[Does Gary know about the
existence of the diamonds?]
[He was circling around
the diamonds.]
then he'll have a chance
of winning by himself.
[To get the members' car,
he keeps calling them for rescue.]
[He looks more and
more suspicious.]
[What's the real
intention of Mr. Gary?]
[Gary cube, the third location]
[A river, and a field of reeds]
[Mr. Gary's cube is in
the middle of the reeds.]
[What will I see this time?]
[What... is this unfamiliar scenery?]
Where am I?
I have no idea where I am.
[What he can see are the river]
[a field of reeds]
[and an unidentified chimney.]
[He's trapped in a mysterious place.]
I have no idea what so ever!
[From a distance, he can see a bridge.]
Wait a minute.
Is that a bridge?
[Where in the world could Gary be?]
[At that time,
Running Man members are...]
Gary couldn't possibly
have found the treasure, could he?
I think Gary's doing
something on his own.
It's not about escaping.
I think he knows about the treasure.
What are the numbers on the wall?
I think they're giving him numbers
when he finishes his mission.
So, he can open the door by himself,
and escape?
[Gary can escape without
the members' help?]
He knows about
the diamonds, right?
Did he figure it out?
I don't think he knows.
He's calling!
[Gary called them right on time.]
Hello!
- Listen carefully, all I see is reeds.
- Reeds?
I'm sure it's one of the
parks near Han River.
- A park near Han River?
- He can see reeds?
- Anything else?
- A lot of reeds...
Anything else, such as a building?
I'm not sure, if I'm the
north side of the river.
From very far off, I see newly
built buildings in Yongsan.
[Putting her brain to work]
I'm in the middle of a field of reeds.
You're across the river from Yongsan?
I think so.
You know the part
in the middle of the river.
It's somewhat similar to that park.
On the left, there's a
thermal power plant.
By any chance, are you on an island?
I have no idea.
The chimney of Dangin-ri power plant.
I can see the chimney from here.
You see the Dangin-ri power plant?
The chimney, I can see the chimney.
Ha Ha...
[Ace Song Ji Hyo, has a hunch!]
I don't think it's near Olympic park.
- I think I know where it is.
- Let's go!
Wait, wait!
Wait!
[He can see something though the hole?]
A windmill?
You know the thing that
looks like a Ferris wheel?
There are three of them on the hill.
You need to give us more details!
And they're building a bridge.
- A bridge?
- They're building a new bridge.
I know it!
[Big-nose is getting ready.]
There are only reeds!
- Find me quickly!
- Let's go!
Where's the new bridge?
Let's go!
We know where it is.
Where in the world am I?
[Jae Suk's team is moving toward Mapo.]
- I think he's in Najido.
- You're right.
You know the wind farm,
the wind turbines.
He said there are three of them.
- And the bridge...
- Yes, they're building a new bridge.
On the way to the airport,
they're building a bridge.
It's Nanjido, then.
If we can't solve it this time,
or next time
Then, Gary will win this race.
It's confusing.
The new bridge is on
the way to Gimpo airport.
Where should I go?
Should I go that way?
But where should we go?
Should we go toward Hapjeong?
- Go straight here.
- Straight?
- Are you sure?
- Ah.. just go straight.
- We should go this way.
- No.
Should I go straight
and make a right?
You said you know where it is.
We should've taken the other way.
Then, it could've been short.
[Kkuk is scolding Big-nose navigation.]
You're right.
Are you a spy?
- I'm not a spy.
- Then, why?
- We had no reason to come this way.
- How about making a u-turn?
Can we even do the mission?
[They're moving toward the new bridge.]
[In the middle of the reeds]
[a man is left alone.]
How can I untangle this?
[He's doing the mission.]
Honestly, it's harder to
make it tangle like this.
Doing this mission is one thing
but I don't think the
members can find me here.
[Jae Suk's team is on
the way to Nanjido.]
Where is it?
- The wind turbines...
- Only Nanji Park has the wind turbines.
[A field of reeds]
And he saw the chimney.
It's in the middle of the river.
Maybe Seonyu Island?
It could be!
I was thinking about Seonyu Island.
Think about what he said.
"You know the park in
the middle of the river?"
"It's somewhat similar to that park."
"In the middle of the river..."
He said that.
That's why I thought
about Seonyu Island.
I think so, too.
From Seonyu Island,
you can see everything.
You can see Han River,
and Dangin-ri power plant.
And it's the island
in the middle of the river.
The bridge is over there.
Is it far?
Can we see Yongsan from here?
We can't.
Yongsan is far from here.
I can't see Yongsan from here.
[Yongsan is too far...]
- Isn't that a field of reeds?
- Isn't that Bamseom?
[Could Gary be inside Bamseom?]
[Jae Suk's team is
headed to Seonyu Island.]
There are reeds everywhere!
That's why I thought it's here.
From there, you can...
see the wind turbines!
The chimney is over there!
- Over there!
- Can we enter the park from here?
Ji Hyo, can we enter the park?
You could also cross Seongsan Bridge
and soon you can
go onto Yanghwa Bridge.
Ji Hyo knows all the parks.
[Ask anything.]
I'll listen to you.
Ji Hyo is amazing!
There's usually traffic over there.
Ji Hyo is the queen of parks.
Can I take this road, Ji Hyo?
Yes, toward the blue tunnel,
and to Seongsan Bridge.
She's like a tour guide for parks.
You'll see parking soon.
[Thanks to Blank navigation]
[they arrive at the park quickly.]
Did he say pinwheels?
We've recorded here before.
See?
I'll get out and ask.
[Run]
Excuse me,
did you see a container
Kang Gary is in a white box.
Have you seen it?
[Kang Gary?]
He's calling!
Hello!
Ha Ha, can you tell us where it is?
We have no idea.
Where are you?
We have absolutely no idea now.
You do?
Should I tell them or not?
Just tell them.
Just come to Seonyu Island Park.
[Ha Ha is sharing the information
that they're not sure of.]
- Are you sure?
- Okay, thank you!
We should keep this lane.
You don't see it?
[Shake, shake]
There's no container in the park?
[The cube is not in
Seonyu Island Park?]
[All the conditions are met,
but it's not Seonyu Island Park?]
He said they're not here.
Ji Hyo, he said it's not?
Then, the only option is Nanji Park.
Should we check Sky Park?
By the way, where's
Jong Kook's team now?
I told them to come here.
I think Jong Kook's team
will be here first.
For some reason.
[Gary's still tries untangling it.]
This is frustrating.
My pride has been hurt.
But, I'm doing it.
Did you think I couldn't do it?
I can do anything
once I've set my mind to it.
It's all good now!
Success!
- Huh?
- What?
- I received a text message.
- It's a picture!
Is it one of the parks
near Han River?
- Is it?
- Yes, it is.
Where is it?
There's a swimming pool.
It was Nanji Park.
Should I exit this road here?
- Not here, at the next intersection...
- Near the bridge, no?
- You can make a u-turn.
- We're allowed?
- Under the tunnel.
- Haengju Fortress?
- No, over here.
- How do you know the road so well?
She knows all the parks
that's good to date.
[Blank Navigation is the best!]
- Okay, okay.
- Three pin wheels.
[All they need to do is,
to get there before Jong Kook's!]
[Jong Kook's team was
headed to Seonyu Island.]
[Kwang Soo is checking Gary's message.]
He sent GPS coordinates on a map.
He's telling us to go there?
Youth Plaza, Nanji Hangang Park?
They tricked us.
They told us to come to Seonyu Island.
But it was Nanji Park.
- It's Nanji Park?
- Yes.
Are you sure? [Wait until I
get my hands on you, Ha Ha.]
[Jae Suk's team is
arriving at the park.]
They're building the bridge here.
Who are they?
There are people.
- It's right here.
- Can you pass me my jacket?
[They don't have much time.]
Reed field!
We need to look for the reeds!
I can see the bridge
construction from here.
If we can't see him,
it means Gary escaped.
It should be somewhere here.
It's over here!
- Ji Hyo!
- Where are you?
Where are you, Jae Suk?
[I found Kang Gary!]
[Why did he come so far in?]
They're here!
Gary!
- Gary!
- There's only ten minutes!
[They need to succeed in ten minutes!]
Gary, what are those numbers?
Every time I succeed a mission,
I get a number.
- Oh really?
- Yes.
I can get out, but I don't know how.
Where's the pinwheel?
It's right there!
[It's all the way over there...]
Oh my god, Gary!
And it was me
who understood "windmill"!
- Yeah, pinwheel!
- How's that a pinwheel?
You said ??
[That's Nanji Park...]
How am I supposed to know?
My god!
- What's the mission?
- There's ten minutes left!
Hurry, hurry!
Zone one is black, zone two is gray,
and zone three is blue.
All three of you have to
shoot and get it in.
I'll be in the blue zone,
you go in the black zone.
- Dong Hoon!
- Good luck, Ji Hyo!
Ready!
Start!
[Ace Ji Hyo passed.]
I like this team.
[Yoo Hyuk passed as well.]
[They'll get one key card
if Ha Ha passes...]
[Ha Ha failed.]
Ha Dong Hoon!
Just wait.
[There's no time to lose!]
[They're already on their second try.]
Ji Hyo's the best.
[Jae Suk got it in!]
[It's Ha Ha's turn again.]
[Shoot!]
[There can't be another mistake!]
This is driving me crazy...
[Haroro failed again.]
[Ha Ha's known to like basketball...]
Don't you go to basketball meet ups?
This is so frustrating!
What are you doing!
[Ji Hyo goals in once again.]
[Yoo Hyuk goals in,
three times in a row!]
Go a little closer.
[I will get it in.]
[Please, Dong Hoon!]
[He clears his mind and shoots!]
No!
[He threw it, but failed again!]
Are you crazy?
[Get your head together!]
He sucks at basketball.
This is driving me crazy!
Why isn't it going in?
He can't get it in!
Come closer!
This is for real!
[While Ha Ha is making mistakes]
[Jong Kook's team arrived
near Nanji Park.]
There's construction over there.
Oh, we found it?
There's not much time.
There's no time.
It's somewhere around here.
[Rushing]
[They got the location of
the cube with eagle eyes.]
The other team's here.
[Jae Suk's team is still
having a hard time.]
Wow, and you said
it was Seonyudo Park!
[They can't hear anything.]
[Goal in!]
How many minutes are left?
[They're continuing
without any breaks.]
Hurry and throw it!
- What am I doing?
- Listen to the explanation!
You have two tries left!
How much time do we have?
[Unbelievable Blank Ji,
nine goals in a row!]
[Jae Suk is also getting
a steady score.]
[And today's Black Hole, Ha Ha]
[succeeded, too.]
It's your last chance!
[So far, they've
acquired two key cards.]
[It's Jae Suk's team's last chance.]
[Ace Song Ji Hyo succeeded
with 100 percent rate.]
Great!
If Dong Hun fails, they're done, right?
Dong Hun?
[Haroro's got the hang of it now,
will he succeed at his last shot?]
[Two out of ten,
they've acquired two card keys.]
You're really good at it,
what's wrong with you?
- I can go first.
- No, let me do it.
First attempt!
[Big-nosed Brother silently
failed the first attempt.]
- Second attempt!
- No!
[Bounce]
[He failed twice already.]
This is frustrating!
You have three more attempts.
[Enthusiastic]
You have two more attempts.
What's wrong with you?
[No matter what, this time...]
[I'll fail...]
Suk Jin failed four times.
[He's trying to be funny, right?]
[Their last chance,
Kkuk starts and succeeds.]
Jong Kook did it,
so you can do it.
Can I throw from here?
[Cack-handed Big-nose,
finally succeeded at it.]
[Jong Kook's teams last shooter,
Giraffe]
[Without any practice,
he succeeds at it!]
[Goal in!]
[One out of five,
they've acquired one key card.]
[Will they be able to get me out?]
You only have two minutes left
to put the card.
Ji Hyo, you pick!
[Why did Big-nose Brother pick?]
[They chose the key cards.]
Let's go.
Please!
[Did they pick the real key?]
- There's another number?
- 0, 1, and 2?
They give me a number after
every succeeded mission.
- What number?
- The pin number!
The pin number!
[They're giving him the pin number?]
How many numbers are there?
I think four.
So if you get one more number,
you can get out?
I don't know the order, though.
Do you have a limited number
of tries for the pin?
No, it'll break in five tries.
- It'll break?
- No, I meant...
You're weird... what do you mean break?
Are you suspicious of me?
I'm not!
Look at me!
I'm not lying!
[Is this real or acting...]
Look!
[Look at my innocent eyes!]
I'm telling you the truth!
[They try Ha Ha's key card first!]
[Did he pick the right one?]
It's not it!
[Failed]
[They have one card each.]
[Is Ji Hyo's key the real one?]
[Failed]
- Is there even a key?
- It's in the middle, right?
Could it be?
[What about the icon of misfortune,
Big Nose?]
None of them work?
[Just like the expected.]
[They ran out of time.]
[They failed to open
the cube at Nanji Park!]
[Gary is getting hints
for the pin...]
Try to explain it well.
I'll only explain what's close then.
No, if it's far then
tell us that it's far!
- Okay, okay!
- How is that a ??
[Sad...]
Gary!
[Gary and the diamonds
are heading to]
[another location,
putting the members behind.]
[Jae Suk's team, Jong Kook's team,
or Gary?]
[Who will be owner of the diamonds?]
[The cube has arrived.]
[Where could it be?]
[The window is opened.]
[Half-asleep, half-awake]
[Where am I now?]
[Let me see.]
What's that?
How can I read that?
[A building with an English sign.]
[I need to find the clue
and call the members...]
[A parking lot?]
[A flag?]
[He can't figure it out
from the front window.]
[He's looking through
the revealed glass.]
Isn't it?
I think so.
[In front of a supermarket in Mok-dong]
[a big building?]
Could it be SBS?
Wait... yes, it is!
It's pretty cold today.
- Gary's calling!
- He is!
Yes, Gary!
- Kwang Soo.
- Where are you?
SBS in Mok-dong.
Hurry up!
Where are you now?
[They're on the move.]
That's a simple answer!
Hello?
They're so cold.
Are they just playing game only?
They're not really thinking
about rescuing me?
[I'll see you later...]
Let's go!
[The destination is set,
go straight to SBS!]
[Jae Suk's team is heading
to SBS without stopping!]
[Jong Kook's team leaves, too.]
[It's good to be there first.]
[He has to shoot five empty yogurt
bottles in a row with an blowgun.]
Who can do this??
[He'll be able to get the last number
if he succeeds at it.]
[Shoot]
[He has to get the tiny yogurt bottles.]
There must be a way to aim at it.
Okay, I think I got it.
[It hit the door and did a bank shot.]
It worked, right?
It doesn't matter how!
Why am I doing this?
The members will...
[The rule was only delivered to
the members this morning.]
[The diamonds that are]
[hidden underneath the bed.]
[Another rule for when Gary finds out
about the diamonds.]
He will have a chance
of winning by himself.
[Does Gary know about this and
is just waiting for the members?]
Gary doesn't know, right?
I think he knows.
- About the diamonds?
- Yes.
He keeps saying that he doesn't know.
But I'm sure that he knows.
I think Gary knows
about the diamonds.
He knows for sure.
[They're also sure that he knows.]
[Who will be the winner?]
[At this time,
Gary is using the blow gun.]
[Focused]
Okay!
[He's surprised, too.]
[One shot, two kills!]
You thought I couldn't do it?
Do you see anything I'm not good at?
[Bank shot, again!]
I hope this will end now.
Two at once!
[Shoot]
[Again, he hit two at once!]
Yes!
[He completes his mission perfectly.]
You thought I couldn't do this?
[The last pass code will be revealed.]
The first number was this,
and the second was that?
[He can call the members again.]
Gary?
Suk Jin, I've finished my mission
I got another number.
The four numbers are 1, 0, 2, 7.
What do you think the pin number is?
- It's four digits, right?
- If you press the number and get out...
I can get out.
What good is there for me
if I get out now?
- Don't come out now.
- Guess the pin number, Kwang Soo!
Yes?
Do you think he really doesn't know?
I think he means it.
But the way he hung up the phone...
Why did he have to shout my name?
I think he's doing it on purpose.
Maybe he found the diamonds now.
Maybe he came out?
[Gary acquired 0, 7, 1, 2.]
They wouldn't make it easy as 2017.
[He has to figure out the
combination of the pin number.]
[Could it be...]
Did Running Man start
broadcasting in July?
- I'm not sure.
- I think it is.
The first episode of
Running Man was in July.
0, 7!
1, 2!
July, 12th!
[Quiet]
It's not?
[Too bad, it was July 11.]
[Then, what could it be?]
I'm just going to press it randomly.
2...
7,1,0!
[It's not?]
7,0,1,2!
[What?]
[Seriously?]
I opened it!
[It happens?]
What is it?
I opened it!
Excuse me, I drooled
because I was so happy.
[Hooray!]
I opened it too early, didn't I?
Was is just a random number?
I'm too embarrassed to say it.
Number 7012 is too embarrassing?
I can't say it.
Seven Running Man...
I'm right!
Seven Running Man, forever!
[012 (yeong-one-ee: forever)]
[Laugh]
We're almost there!
Jae Suk, Dong Hun!
- What is it?
- I'm out!
[What?]
[He's out?]
- I'm out!
- Are you serious?
What was the pin number?
- Pardon?
- Pin number.
- It's too embarrassing.
- Tell us!
It's really embarrassing.
What is it?
You'll be able to tell, if I say it.
7012.
012, forever... something?
- Seven Running Man...
- Oh, no...
Stop, don't say it!
- I can't tell you more.
- Don't!
Seven Running Man...
I can't stand it already.
- Where are you?
- We're in front of SBS.
Hurry up, I've escaped.
It's over.
- Which floor are you on?
- I'm on the ground.
- Okay, I see.
- On the ground.
- Did he take the diamonds?
- That's what I'm wondering.
I don't think he knows.
It seems that he doesn't know.
[But why does he want us to hurry?]
This is too easy.
[Did Gary find the diamonds?]
[If Gary found the diamonds,
the only thing he needs is their car.]
[Gary has been trapped
in the cube all day long.]
[Did he find the hidden diamonds
underneath the bed?]
He's different now.
The door breaks, if I put the
wrong number five times.
He's suspicious.
Are you doubting?
[He pleaded his innocence
with the over action.]
[Could it be real?]
[Or was he acting?]
We need to get there fast,
I'll go inside the cube.
Keep Gary busy with you.
I'll do that.
We need to show the diamonds
in front of the camera to win.
- Gary...
- He's outside.
[Jae Suk's team arrives.]
[And Gary is watching them.]
[They're here!]
He's not acting while
he's carrying the diamonds, is he?
[They all got off the car...]
Gary thinks it's about
you rescuing him.
[Gary is walking toward the car?]
[Is he aiming for the car?]
You escaped!
- What about the seven Running Man?
- What seven Running Man?
It's too embarrassing!
[Jae Suk's team is
carrying out their plan.]
[While Ji Hyo is holding onto Gary]
[Ha Ha is searching the cube.]
[Big-nose is rushing, too.]
What's going on?
[Ha Ha checks the bed first.]
Search for it!
[Are the diamonds still here?]
Where is it?
It's here!
[It's still there?]
What's that?
[What is it?]
[No way...
he really didn't know?]
[Without knowing why,
Gary was trapped since morning.]
[The bed that the diamonds are hidden.]
[To Gary who doesn't know about it]
[It was just a temporary chair
for his meal.]
[Even when the bed skirt was lifted]
This is warm.
[It was just a warm nest for him.]
[During the mission...]
[he picked up the darts.]
[If only he turned his head...]
[But he doesn't doubt at all...]
[He was next to the bed all the long.]
[But he couldn't even
see a sight of a diamond.]
[Just by doing his missions]
[acquired the pin numbers
one by one.]
[He went through hell
and high water to escape.]
[It seems that the day
ends like that.]
[Why is this chaos
happening before me?]
Ji Hyo!
What's that?
[He gives it to Ji Hyo
through the doggy door.]
[but surrounded right away.]
What's that?
What is that?
Let me see!
It belongs to Gary.
Let's give it to Gary.
Seven Running Man, forever!
- Get lost!
- Seven Running Man, forever!
What's that?
[Scattered]
[The diamonds fell on the ground.]
No!
[Pick up the diamonds!]
[What's the ruckus?]
What's that?
- Just get going!
- Get off!
[Remain silent, if you don't know.]
The moment the diamonds scattered
was like a movie!
Greedy humans!
The black team won?
[The diamonds were thrown.]
[No winners today.]
Ji Hyo is the queen of Han River.
Queen of parks.
She knows all the entrances to parks.
I see what kind of date you enjoy.
You're amazing.
[She like to date secretly in the park?]
After all, I opened the door.
Will you give me some?
I opened the door for
them to take the diamonds?
- It turned out like that.
- You open the door for thieves.
The seven of us
are a team forever.
Don't make me laugh!
We're one.
We were so bad at telling direction.
This is upsetting.
- You should've taken Seongsan Bridge.
- You were sleeping!
We need to go drink together now!
Why did you drive?
You were snoring just now.
[Thank you for chasing,
and being trapped.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[There are survivors.]
[And...]
[there are them, too.]
[The Zombie War]