Subtitles by DramaFever
[Don't walk, run!]
[Running Man]
[100 vs. 100]
[The Running Man members walk into
a gym, without knowing anything.]
[The gym is covered in white.]
[And a mysterious number, 100.]
[And the mission is
finally revealed.]
In six hours, you'll play the name tag
elimination with these people.
[Judo]
[Action school]
[Pro-wrestling]
[Ssireum]
(Korean folk wrestling)
[Taekwondo]
[Athletes that represent Korea.]
[And they are 100 heroes!]
You must invite 93 guests within
six hours for the big match.
You can only invite those who can
be searched up on the internet.
[Only six hours are given]
[and the game has begun!]
In Sung!
- Hello.
- I'm filming right now.
You called the wrong number!
Have a nice day, I'm not buying!
[Absurd]
- Where are you, In Sung?
- I'm not subscribing!
Have a nice day, bye!
[Why is he acting like this?
We're really close...]
Hold on, hold on.
It must be an error.
[They must cast 93 guests.]
- I have a production announcement.
- Can't you go later?
Bring all the rappers that
can be searched up.
We need you for the
name tag elimination.
[An abrupt invitation
to fill up 100 people.]
Where are you, Kwang Gyoo?
[The first guest is here!]
[Who was the first to come?]
[Jae Suk's guest]
[Lim Hyung Jun, Actor]
It's the first guest!
[Starting from Im Hyung Jun
that Jae Suk invited to]
[Ha Ha's guests Lee Jeong
and Sam Hammington.]
[Kwang Soo's guest UEE.]
[From the hottest celebs to the
legendary champions, they're all here!]
[Slightly awkward...]
What did you hear from Kwang Soo?
To buy coffee...
That there's a fight...
He lied to me.
[Their reasons are all different,
but they're all here!]
We brought them,
but is it really 20 guests?
[As soon 20 guests arrived,
the atmosphere changed.]
[20 vs. 20, mission time!]
[Team Heroes is only made
with the elite members!]
[We can't step away now!]
[Team Running Man
is bound by loyalty!]
[Awaken the athlete DNA
that was asleep in you!]
[The first game is head squash.]
[With amazing athleticism]
[Team Heroes was ahead.]
[The Team Running Man kept losing.]
[Champion Chang Jung Koo
is on the move!]
[Champion Chang Jung Koo is up!
He succeeded.]
[Team Running Man vs. Team Heroes.]
[What will be the results
of the game?]
[Team Heroes won.]
[That was so close...]
[Team Heroes won head squash!]
[They failed at obtaining the chance to
reduce members on Team Heroes.]
You're here through invites and
don't know each other very well
but we became one with sports.
[The awkward Team Running Man]
[got so much better at teamwork.]
[Someone else is here?]
[There are actors, singers,
and comedians!]
[Team Running Man is growing.]
You're here because
of Jong Kook, right?
He speaks gently...
He told me not to become like him...
[Constantly exposing
one another.]
[A never-ending talent show
from the guests.]
If you're going to leave me after all,
don't give me deep affection.
- What's the title?
- "Deep Affection."
[Until they reach 100 people]
[their effort doesn't stop!]
[And this week]
[everything is more intense.]
[The new guests show off
their acrobatic skills.]
[Original b-boy vs.
ambitious idols.]
[Where there is beat,
it's my performance!]
[And an unstoppable dance battle!]
[And the real game started!]
[A crazy mission between
Team Running Man and Team Heroes.]
[And a special performance
by "G-Friend."]
[And the last match]
Running Man, 100 vs. 100.
Name tag elimination mission!
[The 100 heroes are strongly
built with strength.]
[Team Running Man have mastered
the name tag elimination.]
[A match they can't run away from!]
[Will they eliminate
or be eliminated!]
[The biggest and fierce match!]
[100 vs. 100]
[The game starts now.]
[They gathered 49 people in total.]
There's a lot of people so there
are some who are absent.
There's Kim Soo Yong...
Oh, he's here.
[Im Joo Hwan, Im Seulong,
Kim Kwang Gyoo.]
[Yang Sang Gook, Linda, Kim Won Hyo.]
[Ma Asung, Mino, Kingkong.]
[DJR2, Kim Jun Hyun.]
[Jung Tae Ho, Lee Jeong.]
[All these people gathered
for Running Man.]
There's an empty spot here.
They went to the washroom.
Please remember the person
sitting next to you!
Please keep an eye on each other.
It's a collective responsibility.
[Yoon Bak, Shim Hyeong Tak.]
[Park Geun Sik, Chi In Jin.]
[Others have arrived who may or
may not know of the situation.]
[Welcome!]
[This is your first time, right?]
[Screech]
Who is it?
They're idols!
- Got7.
- Got7?
[Wow, it's Got7!]
[Got7, Kim Min Kyo, Zizo.]
[Park Na Rae, Kim Sook, Lee Sung Mi.]
[Kim Chang Geun, Byun Seung Yoon.]
Jackson!
[Welcome]
[and thank you.]
[We meet here.]
It's Sung Mi!
[They're nervous]
[at one of the most
famous comedian's visit.]
[Everyone we've wanted to see is here!]
[Never heard of or seen
everyone here, altogether.]
[It seems like a good group.]
We have some more guests
who have arrived.
[They came with a phone call.]
For some people, I think
we've done some harm...
You've invited Sung Mi...
Everyone's too scared
to cast her even for comedy!
Why did you call her?
I love Ha Ha because my son
looks a lot like him.
My son is this tall.
- Why did you come here?
- Who knew it was this bad?
I don't see very many elders here,
except for Chang Jung Koo.
He's four years younger than me.
[Born in 1959 vs. 1963.]
[Unbelievable.]
Choong Jae, are you
younger than Jung Koo?
I'm older by four years.
[So is he the same age as Sung Mi?]
Were you born in 1959?
I was born in 1959,
but I entered school early.
Don't do stuff like that.
[The year of the pig.]
[She cleared it up, in a flash.]
Even though they're elders,
there's still genealogy.
Genealogy is indefinite.
[Sorry]
I've invited Kim Sook.
[Loyal Kim Sook.]
[Comedian, Jae Suk's guest.]
I always call her in times of need.
You weren't doing anything, right?
I was doing the laundry.
I haven't done my laundry in a month.
It should be done...
But there's no one to dry them.
Right when you need to switch them,
we'll let you go.
Don't worry.
Sook was talking about
the guests here.
I wore this today...
[I want to find my best friend.]
You're on the wrong show.
[Sympathy]
- Can't you hook me up?
- No.
[She came to the wrong place.]
[There's another one
who feels the same.]
Wang Bae!
You keep talking to UEE...
[Embarrassed]
You haven't even spoken to us!
He's even slanted towards her!
They exchanged phone numbers.
She said she would visit my house.
I asked and she said
she would visit.
I like meat, too!
You talk about meat,
while everyone else talks about shrimp.
[You like meat?
I like shrimp.]
[I just opened
a shrimp restaurant.]
[DJ Pumkin, Choi Kyung Ho, Young Jun.]
- Please do your best today.
- Yes, of course.
And I also called Na Rae.
[Park Na Rae, comedian.]
Your outfit is very fancy, today.
I came right after
my other schedule.
And I didn't know it was
this kind of atmosphere.
I bought some pants on the way.
I can't run with a skirt.
Look at her, she's so prepared.
You could have bought
long ones, why shorts?
They're too long for me.
[You need to check.]
Now that you're here,
could you show us your dance?
- It's a little hard with a skirt on.
- Just a snippet.
- Really?
- Yes.
Please show us "krumping."
I'll just put these on...
Why are you changing here?
[She's changing here?]
[She overpowers 60 people.]
What's going on?
[What's going on?]
There are people standing in the back...
[There's lots to see.]
You can just look,
but why are you doing this?
[They're stretching their necks out.]
We can't see.
[I'm so curious.]
[She's dancing to the
beat of the Hong Dae.]
[Dance, dance]
[Bounce, bounce]
[There's energy from
such a small body.]
[The old man is enjoying it.]
[Speed up]
[The God of Dance appeared.]
[Regardless of preference,
it's absorbing.]
[They can't take their eyes off
even for a moment.]
[I am the hottest, Park Na Rae.]
[Two thumbs up!]
That's precious!
[The old men are happy, too.]
She just bought her shorts
from the market.
She did her best.
That was great.
And next is Seung Yoon.
Whose invite did you receive?
I called him.
- How do you know each other?
- We take Chinese classes together.
[Byun Seung Yoon, comedian.]
- He can speak a little...
- Can anyone speak Chinese?
How about they
try talking together?
We have Jackson!
(He's faking it.)
If you can't do it,
don't force yourself.
[He's pretending to be Chinese
in front of a Chinese person?]
[A Chinese gag in front
of a native speaker.]
[It sounded legit to us...]
Jackson might be
a little flustered.
Jackson, you go first.
[Real chinese]
[Fake Chinese]
[Why does it sound real?]
[He's better.]
They're saying that he sounds
more real than Jackson!
He's better than him!
[Which is really Chinese?]
- Do it once more!
- Just one more time!
[What is this.]
He's just copying me!
[His Chinese sounds so real.]
Good job!
[Seung Yoon gave a big laugh
with his gibberish.]
- You're so good!
- That was funny.
[Sorry for joking around.]
[It was funny!]
Who were you invited by?
I'm Zizo, a rapper invited by Ha Ha.
[I've never seen a rapper.]
His freestyle is awesome.
Yo, let's go.
One, two, yo yo.
When I was told to rap,
my worries began.
But I'm always ready to
run on Running Man.
Seoul is represented by SBS.
I can find my way, like a GPS.
This is just like a
rap heaven, you see.
I will show you
everything, all of me.
Just fried it, fried chicken.
That's how I'll
walk straight, driven.
[His top-tier rap
was made up on the spot.]
[Bravo!]
[Swag!]
Show me the money!
Can you do Hong Kong rap?
[Of course!]
[Rap?]
You can do Chinese rap?
[I lost...]
[He's receiving the energy
through his fingertips.]
[He's energizing his emotion.]
[A language, never before heard.]
[A brand new world of rap.]
Huh?
[His performance was perfect!]
Jackson said it made sense!
But it was swearing.
[What?]
[He rapped without thinking
and what a coincidence...]
- Seung Yoon!
- I'm sorry!
I was so surprised!
Next is... this is my very
first time meeting you.
[Who are you?]
I'm Ha Ha's senior from school.
My name is Kim Chang Geun.
Are they from the
same high school?
Hold on, hold on...
As long as you can search them up, right?
It's right!
He's from KAIST.
[Kim Chang Geun, Ha Ha's guest.]
You're the representative
director of Webzen?
But why are you here?
[I don't know, either.]
But why...
Hey, you!
What are you doing?
- I needed to fill up the spots...
- You need to control yourself!
Are you crazy?
You called Sung Mi...
How did you meet Ha Ha?
We met through cycling.
He's great at cycling.
He's very nosy.
It's so extreme.
He even called up Kim Chang Geun...
[Embarrassed]
Don't worry,
he called Oh Joong Seok as well.
And he's over there.
Are you close with Ju Yup?
I met him today.
[They're already best friends.]
People with mustaches get along
with other guys with mustaches...
[Mustache zone]
It's so funny.
And if we go back here.
[A new mustache face!]
[Kim Min Kyo, actor.]
Suk Jin called me.
He asked me to eliminate
some name tags.
So I thought I was a special guest.
I thought it was
two or three guests.
Everyone here's the same.
Kwang Gyoo, too...
[Vacant]
[You said I would be a fixed member...]
Young Jun!
You're talking too much with Gary.
Sorry.
[Sorry]
[It's not class-time.]
You didn't do anything wrong!
He's asked me if we
validate parking tickets!
I told him not to worry!
I was worried.
I came too early.
[I've been here for four hours...]
And Got7 came to visit as well.
[All the members are here!]
[Got7, Jong Kook's guest.]
I invited them.
They're my junior singers.
They are competitive, too.
[In order of appearance: Jackson]
[Junior, Mark, Yugyeom]
[Young Jae, JB, Bam Bam.]
[There are seven young
and competitive members!]
It was so cool when
you did the tumbling.
Can you do it here?
[Yes, we can.]
- Please stand here.
- Okay.
[What is it?]
I was so shocked.
[The people in the back are
busy again, trying to see.]
I saw it on TV and was surprised.
[Everyone's standing
in the back row.]
[He's ready to film it again.]
[Takes it off]
[I will show you.]
Are you sure it's safe?
[Thrilled]
[A fancy back flip
that went over Jae Suk.]
[Amazing]
[Jumps, flips, push, and land.]
He pushed him mid-air!
[If there's Got7
in the world of idols]
[there's the Twins
in the world of comedy.]
[The acrobatic Twins
are on the move!]
[Intrigued]
Good luck!
[An eye for eye!
It's a back flip!]
[Wow!]
[Did they awaken Jackson?]
[Then let's just go home.]
[Bye bye!]
[Good job, Twins!]
[Stop!]
[There's a b-boy battle,
all of a sudden.]
[The Twins' specialty mid-air flip.]
[The audience is thrilled!]
[Mark's supportive fire!]
[The Twins are joint.]
[A high level
rotation technique!]
[Slap, slap]
[The atmosphere heats up
as the techniques get harder.]
[Spin]
[There's no giving up
in this battle.]
[Next is the Twins' turn!]
[The atmosphere is heating up...]
[They look like they have
no more techniques...]
If you don't have any left,
just stop!
[The battle ends here!]
[Fin]
[The perfect ending
for the final match.]
[The crowd goes wild!]
[It was a great break for the
tuckered out Running Men.]
Please give a big
round of applause!
[It's a festival!]
All of you said you were busy.
But now that there's so much to see
everyone seems to be enjoying it.
You're enjoying it, right?
Hyung Jun, are you okay?
[I love it here.]
He's been here for four hours.
- Sung Mi loved it.
- Did you like it?
It's like my 60th birthday.
[She likes their performance.]
[Meanwhile]
[What about the heroes?]
[They're training
before their big match.]
It's hard to
eliminate the name tags.
I'm so curious about our game.
[They can't just win with power!]
[Just you wait, Running Man.]
[40 vs. 40 mission time.]
[Running Man vs. The Heroes.]
40 vs. 40!
[What is this?]
Mission time!
[Wow]
[The Heroes are walking in]
[with No Ji Sim as their pillar!]
- There are so many.
- Right?
[Taekwondo, judo, ssireum, and
action actors are joined forces!]
[Gulp]
[Our opponent is... them?]
[Yes, that's right.]
[It's shocking to see them,
even for a second time.]
[The Team Heroes is more
intimidating with 40 members.]
They're so built.
[Shaking with fear.]
Some of their glares are...
40 vs. 40,
we will announce the mission.
The mission is
paper curling!
Everyone will line up.
Every other member of the same team.
You will throw a
roll of toilet paper.
The team that gets the most toilet paper
in the safe zone will win.
[Best two out of three.]
Ji Hyo and
Jong Kook, and you...
and you...
[There are 80 members in total.]
[That looks fun!]
[The gym is filled up with
all the big athletes.]
Isn't this such a large scale?
Throw it like this.
[There are people who are
receiving help from others.]
[There are people who don't
even have toilet paper.]
[People who have
met for the first time]
[have become friends.]
He looks so pretty.
We've invited some
of the greatest people...
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
We're very thankful.
[Mino, you're here too...]
[Thanks, Hyeong Tak.]
Yoon Bak, come here.
[Jae Suk is thankful
for his friends]
[who came without
knowing anything.]
- Can we practice, once?
- No.
If we practice,
we have to roll it up again.
[Please take good care of it.]
I'm strong so it'll
fly all the way there.
Prepare for round one!
Good luck!
[The key is to control the fingers.]
UEE, you can do it!
[Will it roll like
I'm expecting it to?]
UEE, you can do it!
[Weaklings like UEE]
[and strong athletes, all play fair.]
[They lost at the
head squash battle!]
[The lost the chance to reduce ten
members on Team Heroes.]
[What about this round?]
[No matter what happens]
[we need to win.]
[Lime vs. brown toilet paper rolls.]
[The 80 rolls of toilet paper rolls
are heading to the safe zone.]
[Some can't throw properly]
[and others bump into each other.]
[Chaos]
[Just then!]
It's here!
[The lime colored toilet paper roll
is moving forward!]
[It went in!]
[Team Running Man, succeeded.]
[Roll, roll]
[The brown toilet paper roll
is moving forward.]
[Team Heroes also succeeds!]
- That's mine!
- Good job!
Just a little bit more!
[He isn't cheering for his,
but the other team...]
[Whose side are you on.]
[The first round is over.]
Mr. Chang is cheating.
Mr. Chang!
You can't cheat!
[You can't do that, here.]
[The legendary champion
is fighting with toilet paper...]
[Our team needs to win.]
There are four
lime colored rolls.
And two brown rolls.
[Their first victory!]
[Yes!]
[Team Running Man: one
vs. Team Heroes: nothing.]
[They're all happy together.]
If we win this, we can banish
ten of their members.
We can be at an advantage.
[They're preparing
for the next round.]
[They're loading their bullets.]
[Best two out of three.]
[Was it this fun to throw
a toilet paper roll...]
[The 80 members are all ready.]
You must win this round!
If Team Running Man wins, they can
banish ten members of the other team.
Just go one more time!
Ready!
One!
Two!
[Go!]
[The toilet paper rolls are
moving forward, once again.]
This one, this one!
[The lime toilet roll is
moving toward the safe zone.]
This one, this one!
[No way]
[And the results?]
[It went over...]
[Kwang Gyoo's roll that he kicked.]
[It's moving slowly,
just like his strength.]
[It reached the safe zone.]
[Mine made it!]
[Wow, that's amazing!]
[Super power Hyun Ju Yup.]
[Will he show off his skills here?]
[His made it!]
[Did you see that?]
We got two so far!
[The other team's score is
the only way to find out.]
[And the results?]
The results are in!
[Team Running Man two
vs. Team Heroes nothing.]
[Team Running Man won!]
[Wow!]
[We won!]
[They're celebrating like they're
in the World Cup quarter-finals.]
[This is better than that.]
[That was an amazing match.]
[They successfully banished
ten members from Team Heroes.]
[Disappointed]
We lost!
- That's hard.
- It is.
We've been training
with heavy dumbbells.
And I can't control my strength
with toilet paper.
[Just as Team Running Man
is seeing the light of day.]
[Someone is wearing full
cycling outerwear.]
[Is it one of Ha Ha's
cycling friends?]
How do I park this?
- Park?
- Yes.
I can't leave it here.
It's my other half.
[One hour and 52 minutes
before the final match.]
There are a lot of empty spots.
There are a lot here.
Did they really leave?
I saw some black outfits in the
garbage cans outside.
[They left to go home after
dumping their team outfits.]
[I've been here for four hours...]
But you guys have done so well
in the previous game.
We got our first victory!
[They banished ten members!]
[This isn't impossible!]
[Someone is here!]
[Who is the new savior?]
[Park Joon Hyung, Tim, Ducky, Wax]
[Hyun Woo, Ryu Hyun Kyung,
Lee Haneul.]
[It's Joon Hyung!]
I just came back from the jungle!
[Yo, brother!]
[Gary's guest, Ducky.]
[And Wax.]
[Hyun Kyung came, too.]
[I've seen him before?]
[Cyclist, Lee Haneul.]
[He's such a free soul.]
- You got so tan!
- It's because of SBS!
[Calm down.]
You don't even feed me!
[He's in agreement.]
[He's dying at his motor mouth.]
Thank you for coming today.
We'll introduce
the guests, briefly.
So Lee Haneul,
who were you invited by?
Ha Ha.
Why did you come in
your cycling outerwear?
I got a call while I was riding.
- Really?
- The ride back was originally my course.
So it wasn't that far.
Did you know we were
eliminating name tags, today?
- Me, too?
- Yes.
Uh huh.
[If you knew who your opponent was,
you wouldn't be so relaxed...]
Please be healthy.
[A healthy and a long life.]
[Yes, yes]
And next is...
He's Ducky!
Hello, I'm Gary's guest,
B-boy Ducky.
- Ducky!
- B-boy!
He was a B-boy world champion.
[2009 Freestyle Session Japan Winner]
[2006 Korea, Battle Of the Year Winner]
[2002 UK B-Boy championship Winner]
[2002 Germany, Battle Of the Year Winner]
You don't look like b-boy at all.
Like Kim Chang Geun
you look like an IT guy.
May I request to show your dance?
Sure, I'll do that.
He's a world champion,
I'm exited to see his dance.
We have a member
who does b-boying.
Is it okay to show us
like a dance battle?
Please, come forward.
[B-boy world champion Ducky's
opponent is JB of GOT7.]
[GOT7 Dance Machine JB vs.
The Korean B-boy Legend Ducky]
He's a good dancer.
He's been dancing for a long time.
I'd say he's the first generation b-boy.
[He starts warming up.]
[The little brother starts first!]
[Flashy steps and powerful moves!]
[Good job, my friend!]
[The World Champion enters.]
[Slightly nervous]
[This is the original b-boying!]
[Powerful break dance!]
[Tremendous!]
[An extraordinary spin!]
[Wow!]
[His legs move nineteen
to the dozen at the speed of LTE.]
[Let me take a break!]
[I ain't that bad, aren't I?]
[He's a world champion, indeed!]
[Here's goes JB again!]
[If the big brother does it,
the younger brother does it, too.]
[Good job!]
[It's spectacular.]
His attitude changed!
[This is the world class b-boying!]
Please give them a round of applause!
I feel like I'm having
an early 60th birthday party.
- Are you enjoying it?
- Of course!
Everyone looks they're
having a good time.
They're really really good!
And the next up is "BBBAAAAMMM"!
Yo!
[Jong Kook's guest]
[Park Joon Hyung, Singer]
It feels like we're in
California all of a sudden.
I think it's enough for him.
This "BBBAAAAMMM" says
everything about him, "BBBAAAAMMM"!
BBBAAAAMMM!
[I'm a good dancer, too.]
Didn't you just come back
from filming "Law of the Jungle"?
- Yes.
- When did you come back?
I came back yesterday morning.
After sleeping for four hours
I got a phone call from Jong Kook,
so I came.
[No time for the jet leg!]
But, I have lack of sleep.
I will say strange things.
He's such a kid.
What?
Is this a battle?
[All of a sudden, a dance battle
between the elders!]
[Haneul starts dancing
in his cycling gear.]
[Come at me first!]
[I'm coming!]
[He's going in between his legs.]
[Taken off]
[An emerald head shyly appears.]
[The audience is burnt to the ground.]
[I'm not done yet!]
[He sparks up again.]
"BBBAAAAMMM" is the best!
[Here we go!]
['Class is permanent.' - Bill Shankly]
[And Brother Jun takes the baton.]
Show us the old dance!
[B-boying in his 40s!]
[Oh my knees!]
[Wriggle, wriggle]
[I'll show you, look closely!]
[Flutter, flutter]
[Thank you, Ancestors!]
All together, BBBAAAAMMM!
[That's it!]
Amazing!
Tim is here!
[The sweet and nice voice!]
[Jong Kook's guest]
[Tim, Singer]
- Who invited you?
- Jon Kook did.
We're gym buddies.
It's been a long time!
I'm sorry, my outfit is too...
I was on the way to gym...
He's wearing his sandals, too!
- You were on the way to gym?
- Yes.
We're going to play name tag elimination,
I called someone who exercises.
Yes, we need people like Tim.
That's right.
It's autumn.
The season of ballad.
I miss Tim's voice.
Tim's song, "I Love You"
is a really good song!
Can you sing it for me?
I hope you'll look back at me someday.
In his sandals...
[Culture shock]
if i wait endlessly like this
The one word in my heart that
I couldn't tell you still
Sing together!
I love you!
- Thank you!
- BBBAAAAMMM!
Bam!
Tim is a great singer!
- He's a neat person.
- Very good!
Wax is here!
When all is said and done,
there's nothing better than money.
[Gary's guest]
[Wax, Singer]
- What are you doing?
- Don't ruin the song!
- Who invited you?
- Gary invited me.
It's been a long time.
[Thank you for coming.]
I wanted to be on Running Man.
Since you're already here.
Could you sing for us?
- "Money" or...
- "Fixing My Makeup"
Could you sing
"Fixing My Makeup" for us?
"Fixing My Makeup"
I'll stand up and sing.
[After ten years,
how will she sing the song?]
There is nothing I’ve done for you.
I only received from you.
That's why I'm sorry.
Why did you love someone like me?
Why did you have to leave?
Whatever it takes,
we must love again.
[This the voice of
the original singer!]
It's so nice to hear it again!
The queen of parties!
[Gary's guest]
[Ryu Hyung Kyung]
- I watched your movie "Office."
- Thank you.
Where were you before you came?
I was packing my luggage.
Luggage?
Are you going somewhere?
- I'm going abroad tomorrow.
- She's going to Peru.
She's an assistant director for a movie.
You're going to Peru
to film a movie?
Please give her a round of applause!
Everyone comes when Gary calls.
Clap for Hyun Woo!
[Jong Kook's guest]
[Hyun Woo, Actor]
Who invited you, Hyun Woo?
I was going to meet
with Brother BBBAAAAMMM.
Jong Kook invited him,
so I came here, too.
Were you going to see him today?
He exercises, too.
Jong Kook said we'll do some exercises.
What were you planning to do
with Brother BBBAAAAMMM?
We were going to have dinner together.
I couldn't eat for days.
I've been starving in the jungle.
[All his story ends at the jungle.]
"Law of Jungle"...
I see.
[Currently, 63 Running Man
members are gathered.]
[Countdown 'til the final mission]
[100 vs. 100 Name Tag Elimination]
[What are the Heroes
doing at that time?]
[They're recharging their energy.]
[We'll use this energy
at the next battle!]
Let's go, let's go!
[It's time to go to the battlefield!]
Let's go!
- We'll win for sure!
- Fight!
[We will pay you back
for the last battle!]
[Wait for us, hated Team Running Man!]
[The music for the
missions starts playing!]
[Are you ready, Running Man?]
60 vs. 60, it's mission time!
[The 60 elite Heroes' warriors
head to the battlefield!]
[60 of them are coming!]
[Will the Heroes recover their honor,
or will another miracle happen?]
Exactly how many members do we have?
[They look scary.]
[Under lots of pressure]
You were standing in the middle,
why did you make a way for them?
I'm shaking.
Just stay in the middle.
I'll announce the mission.
Again, if Running Man wins,
10 of the Heroes will be reduced.
[This mission can cause a change
in the dynamics of the race.]
[What's the game for the 60 vs. 60?]
The game of 60 vs. 60
is dodgeball.
[Oh, my god.]
- All 60 will play?
- It's 60 vs. 60.
[What?]
What are we going to do?
When will we be able to
eliminate 60 people?
[In the past five years, Running Man
played dodgeball numerous times.
[One by one, they've acquired
skills and strategies.]
[A mega dodgeball game that will knock
down everything is about to start!]
[Are you ready?]
[The largest and greatest
blockbuster dodgeball]
[A mega dodgeball that
120 people will clash!]
[Which team will win?
[60 vs. 60]
[dodgeball war, first act]
[Team Running Man is doing a headcount.]
[Who knew we'd be counted by
crouching down on a variety show?]
[Currently, they have 63 members!]
[Jae Suk, Gary, Ha Ha]
We'll be outside.
We need GOT7 since they're fast.
[Running Man's strategy:
place fast members in the center.]
Maybe ten people will be out each time.
We just need to stay behind Soo Yong.
[Running Man's strategy 2: Hide behind
a person bigger than you.]
You can stand behind me.
[A human wall]
Come here, UEE.
[Giraffe feels bad for UEE,
and he takes care of her.]
We can stand in 5 rows.
I'm sorry and thank you.
[I'm sorry, and I love you...]
I don't want to go.
[Am I already attached
to the people?]
Judo is all about pulling,
we're not good at throwing.
Our muscles are developed to pull,
so we're not good at stretching out.
Who's good at throwing, Taekwondo group?
Taekwondo group should be mostly inside.
You should stay inside,
because you are fast.
Then, we'll attack.
[It's going to be a real game.]
[60 Running Man vs. 60 Heroes
are all gathered.]
Good luck, Running Man!
[The people who arrived after
60th will be cheering.]
[We won't be standing here.]
Good luck, Heroes!
[The team who gets the ball in the
center first will attack first.]
It's a single round match.
Get ready!
[Get rid of 60 opponents!]
[Make the miracle happen again]
Too many people over here.
[We can't lose again,
the powerful Team Heroes!]
[Who will be able to laugh at the end?]
[60 vs. 60 dodgeball starts!]
[He's out at the speed of light.]
He's out!
[Eliminated person goes
to the outside line.]
[Jung Tae Ho passes to Mr. Capable.]
Throw it immediately!
[He catches it!]
Good, good!
[He attacks right away!]
[Luckily it went out,
but it was powerful.]
Seriously!
[How can we possibly catch it?]
[The Heroes keeps attacking hard!]
[One shot, two kills!]
- Two, two!
- Who is out?
[The powerful shot
puts two players out.]
[Ma Asung and King Kong are out.]
Are you okay, Asung?
[Feeling helpless]
They're no joke.
Throw it!
[Kwang Soo's best friend,
Kim Ki Bang is out.]
He was just hit.
When you're out,
you can go attack.
Move aside!
[The tireless Heroes]
[Out, one after another]
[The Heroes attack hard
from the beginning.]
You should oust them, too.
[Currently remained players]
[Running Man: The Heroes]
[45:49]
[The Heroes' attack!]
[Grab]
Okay!
[Yang Sang Gook successfully catches
the ball for the first time.]
- Did you catch it instinctively?
- Yes.
[This won't be easy!]
[The Catching God, Yang Sang Gook]
[Awesome!]
[Go Woo Ri catches it reflectively.]
What happened?
Woo Ri!
[What did you just do, Woo Ri?]
How did you catch it?
[I don't know what I did...]
[Okay! We're gaining momentum!]
[A perfect mid-air steal.]
[Yoo Bak! Daebak! (awesome)]
It was Yoon Bak.
[This is the tight defense!]
[I'm going to show you something!]
[Min Gyo is helplessly out.]
[Oh, no!
Min Gyo...]
[In his mind, he played
just like Yoon Bak.]
[Ah... bitter reality....]
[Where did the ball go?]
[Ashamed]
Jeong is good!
[Lee Jung succeeds at
defense and attacks!]
[Ki Bang catches it and
successfully attacks!]
Okay, okay, nice!
I think we can win.
[We can't lose like this...]
[Currently remained players]
[Running Man vs. The Heroes]
[43:40]
[Team Running Man gets confident
and start passing it around.]
This will take some time.
[At that moment]
[A man rushes into the prey!]
I was going to handle it verbally
but this will not do at all.
[Wait for me... my prey...]
[Sniper Jung is coming!]
[The defense genius
Yang Sang Gook is out.]
We might lose...
[The atmosphere changed suddenly.]
[A chink in Running Man's defenses!]
[Jung Doo Hong is the center of attack.]
Quickly, quickly!
[The ball hit UEE's face
and she is out.]
[But Joo Hwan saves her.]
[I can jump as high as Jung Doo Hong!]
You need to throw it right away!
[Take my flame shot!]
[Don't go to the opponent's court!]
[The biggest hustle of the game.]
UEE, endure it!
You mush hold it out!
I don't want to endure like this!
You must!
[Running Man: Heroes]
[39:36]
When will it end?
[34:32]
[Hyung Jun Passes]
[and Comedian Lee Sang Min attacks!]
[We caught Lee Won Hee!]
[Running Man caught the
opponent's strongest leader!]
[Beep!]
We're going to shrink the court now.
[For a more effective game,
the court will be reduced.]
You've survived for a long time.
[34:31]
Let's pass the ball around.
We need to keep passing.
[Both team's strategy is to pass.]
- We have more people left.
- We're winning.
It's all black.
Who got UEE out?
I'm sorry.
What sport do you do?
I do taekwondo.
I'm sorry.
[What's happening?]
[He's Mino.]
I keep greeting people
because I've never met them before.
[Bow]
[New faces are everywhere.]
I think I won't be able to greet
everyone until the filming is over.
[Let's get close while we play
dodgeball together.]
[The court is reduced,
60 vs. 60 dodgeball continues.]
[Currently, Running Man vs. Heroes]
[34:31]
Kwang Soo, good luck!
[Heroes' attack!]
[Uee's short scream]
[UEE and Kwang Soo are out.]
[Come over here, UEE!]
You need to do it quickly!
[Embarrassed]
[Why my bottom?]
[Jung Tae Ho is ousted by
getting a shot on the bottom.]
[I've got you!]
[Jung Doo Hong's counterattack!
Who's his target?]
[Kim Jun Hyun is out.]
[Running Man starts feel nervous,
as Jung Doo Hong moves.]
[19:22]
Not now, keep passing!
Pass it around!
We need to pass the ball.
[At that time, DJ Pumkin attacks!]
[One shot, two kills]
Jung Doo hong is out!
Keep passing!
Everyone is so focused.
This is not a joke.
[He's scary!]
[You should've left the sleeping
Super Power alone!]
Hyun Ju Yup!
[That pose though!]
[Praise Hyun Ju Yup!]
[He becomes the ace at once!]
[Oh, no!]
[He slightly moves,
but the opponent gets scared.]
[This is the Hyun Ju Yup effect!]
[They keep passing the ball around.]
[Okay, it's good!]
[Slowly, only the strong
members are left.]
Jeong is doing good!
[The axle of Running Man
Hyun Ju Yup is out.]
[Currently remaining players]
[Running Man: Heroes]
[9:3]
[Anxious]
[Running Man corners the Heroes
with their passing strategy.]
[Steal]
[Is Lee Jeong out?]
[DJ Pumkin catches it
and saves Lee Jeong.]
[Wow!]
[Thank you, my brother!]
We need to do it quickly.
[Take that!]
Just throw it!
Throw it hard!
[Super Power is on!]
[One of the Heroes is out,
and only two left.]
[6:2]
[Keep passing!]
[With Hyun Ju Yup as the central,
they keep passing the ball.]
Out!
[What just happened?]
Just one more!
[Only one of the Heroes is left.]
Sook survived.
[Lee Jeong, Kim Sook,
Choi Young Jae (GOT7), Byun Seung Yoon.]
good luck, Heroes!
[There's only one opponent left!]
[But he's an expert Judo master
with power and speed.]
[Who will be the last survivor?]
Jeong, throw it hard!
Throw it hard!
[Here we go!]
Until we get him.
[Bring it on!]
[Exciting]
Throw it hard!
[At that moment, the ball
went into the Heroes' court.]
[Now, it's time for
the Heroes to attack.]
[Super nervous]
[Wait for a chance!]
[Choi Young Jae got greedy,
but he's out.]
[We still survived!]
Kim Sook survived.
Seung Yoon, too.
[Seung Yoon steals the ball.]
Good job!
[He's acting on defense.]
It's okay if it doesn't hit him.
Just throw it hard!
[He avoids it well with his reflexes.]
[Here we go again!]
That's it!
[The Heroes are all out.]
[Team Running Man wins
the 60 vs. 60 dodgeball.]
[That's too bad.]
[We won!
Be happy!]
[At this moment, 60 members of
Running Man become one.]
[See you at the final mission!]
For the participants of
the 100 vs. 100 race
we prepared a special performance.
[A special performance?]
Please welcome GFriend with applause!
[Special performance for 100 vs. 100]
[GFriend]
[Standing up.]
[Cheerful!]
[Both Running Man and
the Heroes are gathered.]
[Dazed]
[The way to the center of the gym
is already blocked!]
[The camera team is running.]
[Suddenly, the stage has changed.]
[Lee Haneul is running to watch them.]
[Surrounded in all directions,
GFriend starts performing!]
[Guys are smiling!]
["From Today" - GFriend]
[Jump]
[GFriend is fully
armed with cuteness.]
[His heart flutters...]
[Sing loud]
[Refreshing]
[Brilliant]
[GFriend makes Tiger dance, too.]
[Me gustas tu!]
(I like you!)
[It's just a beginning]
[but they've stolen
all the guys' hearts.]
[Warning: too beautiful]
[Capturing with cameras and eyes]
[Even Kim Ki Tae is taking a selfie.]
[Watching them makes me clap
while I don't know.]
Nice to see you!
[With one wave, the guys feel so happy.]
[At this moment, forget about
which side they are.]
[They're on GFriend's side.]
[Singing all together]
[Please shake my hand!]
[Touch]
[Ji Suk Jin is so happy!]
[GFriend takes care of their fans.]
- I'll comfort you!
- Always!
[The mood gets more exciting,
and he took off his sunglasses.]
[Look at Mister Hwang Choong Jae!]
[Super focused]
["Glass Bead" - GFriend]
[At this moment,
everyone is united.]
[Ma Asung gets dizzy.]
Look at Ju Yup's face.
[He starts filming Ji Yup immediately.]
[He doesn't even know that
Ha Ha is recording him.]
[He doesn't move at all.]
[GFriend is doing their best]
[and the other singers are proud.]
[He wants to be in the picture
with GFriend.]
[GFriend's trademark,
the perfect dance in sync!]
Hey!
[Everybody, scream]
[The special performance is successful!]
[One of the fans is too excited.]
[He's blocked by his colleagues.]
[Running Man is trying to
build a healthy fan culture.]
[GFriend is still puzzled.]
Please gave GFriend a
big round of applause!
[GFriend is the best!]
Hello, we're GFriend!
This is a diverse... festival!
More importantly, Mr. Hwang Choong Jae
took off his sunglasses.
And everyone saw Yang Sang Gook, right?
He was dragged by six people.
They pulled my hair.
[Lee Haneul threw his cell phone.]
What are you doing?
Oh, it's Lee Haneul's?
[I wanted to know their numbers.]
Don't act silly!
That's what people
used to do in the '90's.
[That's too bad...]
GFriend must be busy,
but they came for us.
Let's give them a big round
of applause for GFriend!
Thank you, Yerin!
Thank you, Yuju!
[Everyone is sad to let them go...]
GFriend showed us
the best performance
but one of our guests
has to leave now.
[Who's leaving?]
UEE.
[It's time for UEE to leave
because of her schedule.]
[Sad]
We can't just let her go.
Please play music for UEE!
[All of a sudden,
a farewell dance ceremony?]
[I feel sorry for UEE.]
UEE, UEE!
She's fixing her sweater.
[The sexy icon of After School
is ready to dance!]
[She was shy a minute ago,
but what a twist!]
[She gives off her charm
across the stage.]
[Her intense gaze!]
[She looked at me.]
[The guests get to see
GFriend and UEE, too!]
[She appears beautifully and
turns the stage upside down]
[then she walks out.]
[Bye, vye!]
[Bye, UEE.
Thank you for coming!]
[She's amazing!]
[See you again!]
Didn't you sweat a lot?
- Today's winner is GFriend.
- Hey!
Another one came?
[Someone else arrived!]
- Stop coming!
- It's Muzie!
Time is almost up!
[When the casting time is almost over]
[familiar faces show up.]
Jinu!
[The Big Brother of Hip-hop]
- Roy Kim!
- Muzie!
[And idols enter they gym.]
[Welcome, have you been
at a place like this before?]
- Nice to see you!
- Digiri!
[A lot of people came!]
[We're here, but why are there
so many celebrities here?]
More of the guests are coming!
Kwang Hee, you came?
UEE left just now.
- Pardon?
- UEE left.
You said UEE is here!
[She's gone, man!]
Don't lie to me!
Come over here!
[The casting time is over!]
We might have invited 100 people!
Hello, Muzie!
Hello, nice to meet you!
I'm Muzie.
[Suk Jin's guest, Muzie, Singer]
Suk Jin invited me.
He asked me to cancel my other schedule.
I don't understand that
he casts like pyramid selling.
He told me bring other people.
- I even called Roy.
- Where were you, Roy Kim?
I had a photo shoot. So, I came
when the photo shoot was done.
Do you know Suk Jin?
- He asked me.
- This is the first time seeing Roy.
- Me, too.
- It's multilevel marketing.
We can get to know
each other from now on.
This is how relationships start.
- Are you okay?
- Sure.
We're going to play
name tag elimination.
I'm ready for it.
Are you sure?
[Roy didn't see the Heroes yet.]
I feel like we have thousand troops now.
Muzie and Roy Kim.
It's been a while.
How do you know Moon Ji Ae?
[Suk Jin's guest]
[Moon Ji Ae, Mc, Announcer]
Have you met Ji Suk Jin before?
Yes, we've worked at a program together.
I didn't have him in my contact.
I never called her before.
And I made a first phone call
because of this.
You still came!
[It must be a reunion for many people.]
You usually know
each other's phone number.
He said he's filming Running Man,
and I came not knowing the situation.
Where's Hyung Jun?
I'm right here!
- He was the first one.
- It's been more than seven hours.
He's been here
for seven hours and a half.
If we're going to get paid
do we get paid by hour?
I'm so sorry.
Discuss about payment later.
We didn't know it would
turn out like this.
Please give her a round of
applause for Moon Ji Ae.
Chi Yeol!
- Where were you?
- I was in the middle of a meeting.
Park Joon Hyung called me.
Therefore, he's my guest!
- Brother BBBAAAAMMM!
- BBBAAAAMMM!
- You invited Chi Yeol?
- Yes, I said BBBAAAAMMM, and he came.
He went to the jungle
with Joon Hyung.
- Yes, I went to film.
- That's why you're so tanned.
He got too thin.
Chi Yeol's a good singer.
Please sing for us.
I'll sing "Confession" by Lim Jae Bum.
[Amazing!]
[He sounds exactly like Lim Jae Bum!]
(Mimicking the way of
Lim Jae Bum sings.)
Thank you.
[He appeals short and strong.]
That was nice!
If you just look at him,
he looks like Heo Kyung Hwan. (comedian)
Thank you for coming.
Hwang Kwang Hee.
You came to see UEE,
but she left.
Is that so?
I didn't come to see her only,
you invited me.
You're wearing makeup.
I was filming for a cooking show,
but why did you call me?
I wanted to appear as a star.
There are too many stars already!
He's out of his mind!
[Wake up, Kwang Hee!]
You should invited me as a celebrity!
It's the first time on Running Man,
after I got famous.
Look around!
It's an honor to be in the
same space as Chang Jung Koo!
There are so many famous people here.
Yoo Bak is at the very back, too!
Yoon Bak is at the back.
I'm serious!
[He passes the microphone
out of embarrassment.]
No one supported you on that.
Just stay calm and don't make trouble.
I can't take care of you on Sunday,
don't be sad.
Jinu is here!
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
[Ha Ha's guest]
[Jinu, Singer]
- Who invited you?
- Ha Ha did.
Why did you invite so many people?
He's in my cycle team.
[Lee Haneul, Kim Chang Geun, Jinu,
are Ha Ha enjoys cycling.]
He's luxurious.
You were on Running Man with Sean.
He was really nice.
It was really tiring.
I told you before,
Jinu is not a funny person.
He does his best.
- He's a handsome guy.
- Yes, he is.
Thank you, I'll do my best.
We have new faces here.
[Kwang Soo's guests]
[Seventeen, Singers]
UEE called us.
[The8, Jun, S.Coups, Joshua, Wonwoo]
[Hoshi, Seungkwan, DK,
Jeonghan, Vernon, Minkyu, Dino]
- UEE called you?
- Then, they're my guests!
And I'm also from Namyangjoo!
[The big son of Namyangjoo
and the little son of Manyangjoo]
Thank you for coming, Seventeen!
- Thank you!
- We'll do our best!
He's my friend and classmate.
- You can't invite your friend!
- He's a voice actor.
Sa Sung Woong, can you show us
a famous character?
Should I do Power Ranger?
Do you know Power Ranger?
[The idol of children, Power Ranger]
I did Engine Black and Magic Force
from Power Ranger.
I'll run for justice!
Power Ranger, Engine Black!
See?
[Proud]
He's my friend!
He's Power Rager.
After Sa Sung Woong
He's Digiri!
[Gary's guest]
[Digiri, Rapper]
- What were you doing?
- I was shaving.
I'll be on TV, so I wanted to look nice.
- So, I shaved.
- So, you were taking a break?
No, I mean...
yes, I took a long break.
Thank you!
[Good luck, Digiri!]
Hello, I'm a new actor, Kim Ji An.
[She's cute!]
Hello, I'm Cho Yoon Woo, a new actor.
[He's handsome.]
Hello, I'm a new actor, Jung Dong Hyun.
[They're actors from
Kwang Soo's company.]
And the group at the back is N.Flying.
You invited them?
[Kim Jae Hyun, Lee Seung Hyub]
[Cha Hun, Kwon Kwang Jin]
You know Jae Kyung (Rainbow)
Jae Hyun is younger
brother of Jae Kyung.
You look like Jae Kyung.
Woo Ri is over here.
- Did you say hello to her?
- Yes.
Along with Seventeen, N.Flying
members are fast, too.
You didn't see our opponent.
I feel relieved.
- I don't know if we're 100.
- Just think as 100 Kim Jong Kook.
[Are you serious?]
We'll count how many we are.
80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86!
87, 88, 89
90, 91, 92!
We're 92!
[Including seven Running Man members,
they've made 92 members!]
Thank you for coming!
[Thank you so much!]
I don't know how we can repay this.
[Can 92 Running Man members
will win against the Heroes?]
[They didn't know what
was coming at first!]
[The biggest mission in
Running Man history!]
[Play name tag elimination
with 100 Heroes?]
[Cast 93 guests only by calling!]
[Their fantastic casting
started that moment!]
[Like a miracle,
92 Running Man joined forces!]
We're 92!
[If you're ready,
we're on the way to eliminate you!]
[100 vs. 100]
[The final match!]
[Finally, it's today's last match!]
[The guests who've already fought,
the guests who've never fought]
[are all super nervous.]
[The Heroes enters.]
[Let's finish the match now!]
[As the Heroes enters the gym,
everyone becomes serious.]
[Their opponent is 100 heroic athletes
who represent Korea.]
[Against them is the 92 comrades
who are linked with friendship.]
We have to fight again them.
[You mean these monsters
are our opponents?]
It's mission time!
[The final mission of 100 vs. 100]
[100 vs. 100, final mission]
[The name tag elimination]
Running Man has 92 members.
The Heroes have 80.
[The final mission]
[80 vs. 92]
It has three rounds.
You can decide how many players
you will put in each round.
We'll need to put a lot in one round.
First one to win two
rounds will be the winner.
[First round, strategy planning]
- We need to win one round first.
- Are you fast?
- Maybe put strong people.
- Sang Gook and Won Hyo.
Kwang Soo, play the first round.
Sung Mi!
Ji Ae!
Ji Ae and Wax for the first round.
Ji Hyo, you too.
Four women together.
- We have 18 so far!
- 18?
Hyung Jun, play now.
Two from GOT7, Jackson!
[Kwang Gyoo and Kwang Hee]
[Jackson, JB, Yoon Bak, young blood!]
[The Heroes are planning
their strategy, too.]
Let's put some strong members first
and get a head start.
And make the second team weak
then the third round
will be filled with strongest.
[They're checking their name tags.
[Running Man members are
teaching their skills.]
As soon as they grab you,
rip the name tag right away!
[Even though the Heroes are strong,
they might be able to win!]
I can see you.
[No way!
How can you see this?]
[Trust your comrades in arms!]
[The first round will
decide the final mission!]
[The 92 friends with strong friendship]
[become one in front
of the final match.]
So nervous!
[100 vs. 100]
[The final mission, first round]
Running Man, 100 vs. 100!
The name tag elimination mission!
The first round!
Get ready!
[Finally, it's the last match!
[Will we be able to beat the Heroes?]
[Name tag elimination]
[It's starting!]
[While many of the
Running Man members hesitates]
[Young members are
rushing at the opponent.]
[The group of young members
start attacking one by one.]
[What a good plan!]
[Look at their spirit!]
[They come at once!]
[Rip]
Amazing!
[The young squad's next target is Former
Mixed Martial Artist, Yook Jin Soo.]
He's out!
[He's ousted in a flash!]
[Kwang Soo, the expert in name tag
elimination leads the attack!]
[Ji Hyo coaches them to defense.]
[Five years of experience,
quick back step]
[Running Man pressed the Heroes.]
[Front rolling break fall]
That's awesome!
[It's the last battle!
Running Man members are enthusiastic!]
[Are they really our members?]
It's scary!
[Kwang Soo is fighting
alone against the Heroes.]
[Grab]
[Rip]
[Kwang Soo is ousted by group attack!]
[Kwang Soo was leading their attack,
but he's ousted.]
[The atmosphere changes suddenly,
the Heroes started to counterattack.]
[Muzie is ousted in a flash.]
[The leader of the young squad
Yoon Bak is ousted.]
You shouldn't stay alone.
They're all attacking in groups.
[This is the scary power of the Heroes!]
[Hyung Jun is cornered by the Heroes.]
[In the crisis, he
eliminated one name tag.]
[Rip]
[To eliminate this name tag,
he must have waited so long.]
Are you okay?
[The battle gets hotter and hotter.]
[Grab]
[Fall]
[Chang Jung Koo takes
the giant No Jim Sim at once.]
[The fiery battle between
Korean legends!]
[Looks around]
[Anxious]
[Nervous]
[While the two groups
confront each other...]
[Slip]
[She tries again.]
[Rip]
[Sister Sung Mi's desire for hunting.]
[She gets close secretly.]
[Rip]
[She's ousted by an ambush, too.]
[One by one, the warriors get ousted.]
[Running Man couldn't
overcome numerical inferiority.]
[As the game continues,
Running Man keeps losing people...]
It's 14 vs. 8.
They're almost double.
[As proud as a peacock]
We have women.
[They're Ji Hyo and Wax.]
[The loyal Running Man
members become a shield.]
[No mercy for you!]
[Lee Jeong is ousted by four of them.]
[Their weight of numbers
secured the Heroes the victory.]
[Rip]
[Even Tim is ousted, only Ji Hyo,
Sung Woong, and Won Hyo survived.]
I'm fine.
[They're doing their best until the end]
[but Won Hyo is ousted.]
[And Sung Woong and Ji Hyo
are ousted, too.]
[The Heroes win the first round.]
[They play without mercy.]
Hey!
[The Big Sister is upset!]
[Brava! Sister Sung Mi!]
Mommy!
That's enough, come back!
[Wait and see!]
[Getting worked up]
[Burning with anger]
[Anyway, Team Heroes
wins the first round!]
[Will this force continue
for the second round?]
Players for the second round,
please come forward.
[Second round, strategy planning]
[Jong Kook, Ju Yup, Geun Sik,
and Gary are placed.]
We can make 31 members for this round.
If you lose this time, it's over.
They'll be moving in a group.
We need to chase them fast,
and attack someone who's slow.
That's the only way.
Do we have enough people?
Don't worry about this round.
[They will pick a few elite
members for the second round.]
[They place strong
pro-wrestlers in the front.]
- I want to try this.
- Grab the arms, and try.
[We'll try and run away!]
[If we lose this round,
this game is all over.!]
[The final mission, second round]
Don't think about the third round!
Just finish it now!
Finish it!
[They're standing face to face]
[and get nervous.]
Running Man, 100 vs. 100
Name tag elimination mission!
The second round!
Get ready!
[Team Running Man was defeated
completely during the first round.]
[Please avenge for us!]
[100 vs. 100, name tag elimination]
[The second round starts!]
[Running Man's strategy,
stick together!]
Stick together!
[Team Heroes has fewer members.]
- They have women.
- They have two women!
Run and chase!
[No one can easily come forward.]
Don't make a careless move!
[The calm before the storm]
Staking their all on the second round.
It's a human-wave strategy!
They're keeping the good ones for later.
How about a one on one match?
[Jong Kook's sudden suggestion]
One on one!
[Running Man's runner is Mr. Capable.]
[Hesitate]
[If they win, they can get a head start.]
Come forward!
[Who will be the Hero
to face off against Mr. Capable?]
[Pro-wrestler Kim Min Ho]
[Height 185cm, weight 110kg]
[He has a big figure.]
[A big match!]
[He's giant, it won't be
that easy for Mr. Capable...]
[Jong Kook is in trouble...]
[Name Tag Eliminator Mr. Capable
vs. Pro-wrestling Star Kim Min Ho]
[The fate of the two teams are
on the two men's shoulders.]
Kim Jong Kook!
Good luck!
[Kim Min Ho's drastic movement!]
[But Mr. Capable shakes him off.]
[I've got you!]
[Grab]
[Rip]
[Kim Min Ho is ousted at once!]
[Bravo, Kkuk!]
[He's our Mr. Capable, indeed!]
We did it!
[What a defeat!]
We might be able to win this time!
- Let's do two on two!
- Two on two?
[Running Man's runners are Mr. Capable
and Park Geun Sik.]
Park Geun Sik, Park Geun Sik!
[Aside from the individual skills,
they need to keep in step]
Good luck, Geun Sik!
[Mr. Capable doesn't
attack right away this time.]
What are you doing, Geun Sik?
You can't!
[It's one on one!]
Grab the name tag!
[As Mr. Capable taught him]
[he needs to grab
the name tag and rip it.]
[Rip]
[Geun Sik is ousted
by a hair's breadth]
[The Hero who eliminated Geun Sik
moves fast to Jong Kook.]
[It's one on two!]
[Grab]
[Rip]
[He runs in an instant and rips it!]
[I can't believe it!]
[They lost Mr. Capable
at the Heroes' pincer movement.]
[We did it!]
- No, Jong Kook can't leave!
- It's okay.
We still have more people.
Gather together, we have more people!
We need to stick together!
We have more people!
[That was so close...]
Think it as two on one!
[Attack!]
Go around them!
[Run]
[Good job!]
[Rip]
[In a flash, the Heroes are
ousted one after another.]
[This is the complete opposite
from the first round]
[They work in perfect harmony,
they help each other.]
Help them!
[Team Running Man is fighting so well.]
[They're our opponents,
but they're good.]
[The Heroes are surrounded.]
Corner them!
[Moving in perfect order]
[All starts attacking!]
[Rip]
[We'll end this soon for you.]
You did it very well!
[The second round went as they planned.]
[Team Running Man wins the second round.]
[The Heroes won the first round,
but lost the second round.]
[Now, they're 1:1, but they're
worried about the third round.]
[Only the members who haven't played
can be in the third round.]
[Will we be able to win?]
Gather here!
For the third round!
Let's cheer!
[The strongest members,
Lee Won Hee and Kim Ki Tae are entering.]
They have so many members!
[Majestic]
We have so few.
Because 34 members were
playing for the second round.
[Our strategy worked!]
They're too strong!
Running Man, 100 vs. 100
The name tag elimination mission!
Final round!
[The last battle of the race]
[With this one round,
the winner will be decided.]
[No matter who our opponent is,
we won't run scared!]
Stick together!
[As other times, Running Man
members are gathered together.]
[This is the time!]
Hold hands, and surround
them as if we are a fish net.
[A human net!]
[As soon as the third round starts,
they carry out their plan!]
[Running Man is surrounded
by the human net!]
[What in the world is that?]
[They lock them up in
one spot and attack!]
[Big-nosed Brother is ousted!]
[Rip]
[So many of the Running Man
members are gone to the wall.]
[Yoo Hyuk who's fast tries leaving.]
[The Grasshopper's in the net.]
[Rip]
[Chaos]
My shoe!
It's over there!
[She wears her shoes
and goes back to the battlefield.]
[Where did my name tag go?]
[It's inside his hair.]
Am I ousted or not?
You're not ousted.
Because it's just stuck to your hair.
[The name tag was stuck to
his own hair, so he's not ousted.]
[The Heroes are holding hands again!
[They shouldn't be surrounded again...]
Corner them again!
[Stomp, stomp]
[They're coming.]
Fight!
[Hand in hand, the human net
goes one more time.]
[Again, they're completely surrounded.]
[What do we do?]
[They're ousted thick and fast again!]
Grab them!
[The rest are helpless.]
[Rip]
[Running Man is about to exterminated.]
[In the meantime, a man ran far away.]
[Seung Kwan of Seventeen]
[DK from Seventeen becomes
the target and runs away!]
[I'm so sorry.]
Do Kyeom
[At last, Do Kyeom is ousted.]
[Therefore, there's
only one member left]
[It's Seung Kwan of Seventeen.]
Only one left?
[The Heroes vs. Running Man]
[18:1]
Let's do one on one!
One on one!
[I might possibly win,
if it's one on one match.]
[But his opponent is Lee Won Hee.]
[Lee Won Hee vs. Seung Kwan]
Boo Seung Kwan!
Isn't he Lee Won Hee?
That gold medalist Lee Won Hee?
[The two men become serious
before the battle.]
[In an instant]
[Grab]
[What just happened?]
[Seung Kwan is cute!]
[He grabs Seung Kwan
by the collar quickly]
[and attacks his name tag!]
[Rip]
[The last runner, Seung Kwan is ousted.]
[Team Heroes wins the third round!]
[With two wins and one loss,
the Heroes win the game.]
[Is this all over?]
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much for
staying with us for a long time.
Director Jong Doo Hong, Coach No Ji Sim
Director Lee Won Hee, Taemi
Director Yook
and all the athletes who came today,
thank you again!
[Thank you, 100 Heroes!]
Some of our guests had to go
but thank you for staying
with us until this late.
Thank you again!
The final winner is the Heroes!
[Regardless of winning or losing,
it's good to be together!]
[A few hours ago, 100 vs. 100 mission
sounded like a helpless one.]
[But we had friends
who were a phone call away.]
[A hundred of them!]
[We became one like that]
[and we were able to spend
wonderful time together.]
They're so strong!
My daughter is a
big fan of Running Man.
One, two, three!
My handwriting looks bad.
You look good!
You're in such a good shape!
Thank you for your work!
[Thank you for 100 stars and 100 athletes
who made today an exciting festival.]
Subtitles by DramaFever