[It's officially summer!]
[A healthy summer with health foods!]
[A heated fight to win the health foods!]
[Refreshing the body!
Refreshing the mind!]
[Extreme pool missions!]
[Go away, heat wave!]
We always come to
Gyeongju in the summer.
There are six pairs of chairs.
- Is it a blind date?
- Thank you!
- Getting me all excited!
- It says 'Peek-a-boo, Jae Suk!'
- 'Brother Jong Kook?'
- What is this?
- Wait.
- 'Bro Suk Jin.'
- Look at the writing!
- 'Bro Suk Jin?'
- 'Come visit me.'
- 'Bro Suk Jin!'
Who is this?
'You were in my dream, Gary'?
- Gary, today...
- What's this?
Don't come near me today,
don't come near my partner!
The writing tells so much!
- It's really vivid.
- I like this.
- Wait!
- Gary's partner might be Ji Hyo!
I really wish Gary
gets paired with Ji Hyo today.
Are you there?
- Who wrote 'Peek-a-boo'?
- Everyone sat down already.
- You have blinds in front of you.
- Yes!
Please lift the blinds slowly,
starting with Jae Suk.
I'm nervous!
[She covered her face with flowers.]
They're not boy group idols, are they?
[Her fingers...]
Wait a minute!
Her hands are delicate!
Her hands look young!
[One finger movement
captures their attention.]
[He carefully lifts up the blinds.]
Why are you going up?
[Her body is going up with the blinds.]
[Who's Yoo Hyuk's partner?]
Who is it?
Her hair's red!
[Soyu from SISTAR]
[SISTAR's fresh character, Soyu.]
Soyu!
[Cute]
[Everyone wants Soyu's attention.]
[Soyu's cool charm is coming soon!]
I like Soyu!
[Next up, single man Kkuk.]
[He dreams of love again today...]
So it's this kind of excitement.
Today's is like a girl idol concept...
Jong Kook should look for a bride now.
- Don't say that.
- You better prepare yourself.
[Brother Jong Kook]
You have to find a bride!
[Her nasally voice!]
Jong Kook!
[He suddenly gets up.]
- Her voice is so pretty!
- Who is it?
- Jong Kook, it's me!
Wait a minute.
Is it Bomi? Is that you?
[Bomi from A-Pink.]
[She has a fairy-like appearance
but an easy-going personality!]
She has such a husky voice
for an idol.
- Hello!
- Bomi is here!
Bomi came here last time!
Wow!
- Gary's partner is...
- What?
[Everyone's distracted
by Gary's partner.]
Jae Suk!
Why are you so excited?
- Is my partner pretty?
- Yes, she is!
- Lift it!
- She's incredible!
I hope Gary doesn't collapse!
[I was the one who
dreamed about Gary!]
You wanted to meet her so much!
[The woman Gary wanted to meet...]
- I'm getting my hopes up!
- You should!
[He lifts the blinds up calmly.]
I dreamed about you!
[She said she dreamed about him!]
[This is the power of
'I dreamed about you!']
Who dreamed about me?
[Rising star, Seol Hyun from AOA]
[From music charts and ads to dramas!
She's the hottest icon!]
[Heart attack!]
[Shy]
I have a crush on her!
He kept talking about
her in Hong Kong.
He said Seol Hyun was
the most beautiful girl.
- Gary said that to me, too.
- Thank you.
I've got a heart attack.
Gary is wearing really
expensive pants today!
Original Penguin pants!
Kwang Soo dressed up the most today!
[He looks likes a man
from the drama 'The Rustic Era.']
Have high expectations!
Your partner is awesome!
I can see Kwang Soo's partner.
[Wait, Giraffe!]
You see her?
- Next is Suk Jin!
- Why isn't anyone excited over there?
She's covering her face,
but her clothes look youthful.
[A heated response.]
This is it!
- Lift it up fast.
- She's young.
- She's younger than you think!
- Thank you!
- She's cute.
- Oh, black!
- Is it Ji Hyo?
- Suk Jin!
- Oh, wow!
[Why is he so surprised today?]
[Big Nose's partner is Blank Ji.]
Lift it up already!
- Oh, wow.
- What's wrong with you?
[Suk Jin's partner is Ji Hyo.]
Ji Hyo is pretty!
Me?
Who is it?
[Ha Ha's partner is blonde?]
- She's blonde!
- Her fingers scared me!
That scared me!
You're very provocative!
She's tanned!
She's blonde!
Who is it?
[Bora from Sistar!]
[She came with me.]
Bora!
You came, Bora!
[Ha Ha's satisfied with his partner.]
Kwang Soo!
[It's finally Giraffe's turn!]
[Who could it be?]
[Rustle, rustle]
They might go out in real life!
[Full of expectation.]
Let me roll it up!
[The woman who captured
my full attention...]
[The Ultimate Weapon, Lee Gook Joo.]
Gook Joo?
[Gook Joo and Giraffe
are the same age.]
Shake it, shake it!
Wow, Lee Gook Joo!
Like me!
More, more!
Whoo! Yes!
[That's it!]
He dressed up well today.
[He couldn't hold in his happiness.]
[An uppercut ceremony for the PD!]
[I want to share the happiness!]
[Nice to meet you, partner!]
[Extreme visual couple is born.]
I think Kwang Soo sincerely likes me.
That's a relief!
I think today's filming
will be a blast!
There's so much energy!
The staff is giving us a prize.
[After their happy blind date...]
'Running Man' is a great job!
- They give us a prize sometimes.
- It's the best workplace!
Gook Joo is wearing
her best clothes today.
[Shake, shake]
Gook Joo couldn't contact her stylist!
I left my house at 4 a.m.
to come to Gyeongju.
My stylist doesn't answer the phone.
I heard we were gong to play in the pool.
I'm just going in with my underwear!
- I don't have anything!
- What are you saying?
Should I cry and go back home?
I'm a pro!
Of course, I have to try hard!
She's a professional.
I thought you must be tired
because it's the start of early summer.
We've prepared some health foods
that will improve your stamina
for all of you that have
worked hard until now.
[Getting ready to eat.]
The couples will change
and meet up at a restaurant.
There are cars waiting to take you
to Korea's top three healthy foods.
You can choose whichever menu
you want and get in the car.
One car can take up to four people.
So only two teams can
go to the same place.
Your fate depends on
which couple you go with.
It might change
the whole game of the day.
You have to pick carefully.
[A worried face]
There aren't any mid-way
couple switches, right?
- Why?
- Are there?
- I'm just asking.
We're not going to
switch couples, right?
Well, we don't have
high expectations with these men!
[Gook Joo speaks like a professional.]
To be honest, the best one out of
the bunch already got married.
[Drop the detailed explanation!]
Is the six-pack all you've got?
- His toes are rotting!
- What do you mean?
[Extremely embarrassed]
He only cares about his abs!
Take care of your feet!
[I didn't know you could crack a joke
out of someone's toes...]
Take care of them!
[Let's take a look...]
Kwang Soo, don't wear sandals!
- His toes are curled up.
- I haven't wore them in five years!
[Will this couple be okay?]
[Escape the heat with summer delicacies
that boost your energy!]
[Enjoy the dance party!]
[And win the water games!]
Kwang Soo changed into sneakers
because of your joke.
Let's hurry!
What do you want to eat?
Hurry!
I want the chicken soup with ginseng!
[A race to eat the greatest dish.]
What should we eat?
- Premium beef!
[Team Yellow and Team Green
head to the premium beef.]
[Teams Yellow and Green
acquire the premium beef.]
[They don't even look
at the other offerings.]
[Hooray for premium beef!]
Premium beef!
[Team Red and Team Blue
ran to get the eel.]
[Who they go with is
an important matter.]
- I love eel, but it's Jong Kook...
- It has to be eel!
Eel is the best.
I want to eat
chicken soup with ginseng!
Is the car for the chicken soup full?
[He tries to negotiate]
You don't want to switch with eel?
- You don't want the eel?
- Who's over there?
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Oh, is that right?
We'll just have
chicken soup with ginseng.
[I have no choice
but to have eel with Kkuk...]
[Chicken soup with ginseng,
premium beef, and grilled eel.]
It's going to be delicious!
It's good for your health.
Yeah, I wanted chicken soup with ginseng.
I hope it isn't like where
only one team gets to eat.
[Sudden anxiety]
It makes me nervous.
If our team doesn't get to eat,
please feed Seol Hyun.
[Will only one team get to eat?]
Don't worry!
[Team Red and Team Blue
are headed to eat eel.]
- I've been to Gyeongju a few times.
- It's really nice here.
We came here for our school trips.
I came here for the Dream Concerts,
but it's my first time driving around.
- It's beautiful.
- It's really nice.
How long were you a trainee, Soyu?
- Since my first year in high school.
- Oh, you were pretty young.
I went on a retreat
and I've got picked up.
I used to be an idol...
- Didn't you debut in high school?
- I debuted after I graduated.
No, I meant for fighting.
Don't you have rock fists?
[They're heading to
the perfect mission for him.]
[Team Green and Yellow are...]
You guys might be the winners.
- Let's go, Gook Joo!
- You'll be focused only on winning.
When we were in the waiting room
she told me she wanted
to be Kwang Soo's partner.
Gook Joo's like my family.
I was really happy.
I never had a family member like you!
What are you saying?
- What are you saying?
- We're not family.
- Our genes are completely different.
- Well, yeah...
He revealed his six-pack to the public.
So I was really curious.
- Don't touch mine.
- He exercises.
He put pressure on
his stomach when I asked.
I didn't!
[Don't make me shy.]
Spend 10% of the time you worry about
your six-pack and focus on your toes.
- My toes aren't rotting!
- Because you need to wear sandals.
I brought many pairs of
sandals to wear today!
[Water park]
[Premium beef restaurant]
Premium beef, premium beef!
[Team Yellow and Team Green
enter the beef restaurant.]
You don't give food without
giving something in return.
If you give us premium beef,
I will do whatever you ask!
It's here, it's here!
They even have charcoal ready!
[Chant his name...]
[The beef god always protects
our dinner table...]
- Look at the marveling!
- It's victory onions!
You make wraps with it.
You can only get victory onions
at luxurious restaurants.
You can't eat it!
Put it down!
- Wow!
- Oh my god!
[The healthiest
chicken soup with ginseng.]
It's Korean native chicken!
[Full of stamina!]
We can't get this in Seoul.
The unit price is 55,000 won.
[His deep emotion with an appraisal!]
[Team Red and Team Blue
came to the eel restaurant.]
[Truly moved]
It looks really good!
[The guardian of health, eel.]
It's sizzling!
It's 'The Queen of Early Summer Race.'
Only one queen who
wins the final mission
can become the Queen of Early Summer.
- I need to make her the queen?
- That's right.
The females will put on
an armband on their left arm.
Don't wrap it too tight,
I'll have poor blood circulation.
[Aren't there any XL armbands?]
[The six Queens have
put on their armbands.]
- Starting now...
- Do I rip it off?
No.
[Goose bumps]
Each team member must obey
everything the queen says.
- You cannot disobey your queen.
- Really?
Can I tell him what to do?
The important thing is,
the queen that wins each mission
can merge with the other team's Queen.
What's merge?
- What?
- Merge?
- This is only two servings.
- It's only for two people?
The queen that wins the mission
can divide the food according to
the order of people they like.
The last person might not even
get a drop of soup.
First, the queen will eat
and then choose the order.
We can eat the leftovers...
You can eat this after
you complete the mission.
What's the mission?
Flip the cushion.
Each representative comes to the board
and they have to flip the cushions
that matches their side
The team that flips the most cushions
by the time limit will get a point.
It's the mission that Jong Kook won
by pinning me down last time!
[The memory of a white butt.]
Jae Suk!
[The history of humiliation.]
Soyu, if you don't win,
we're done...
Jong Kook carried me
and flipped all of them before.
There's a high chance that it will
happen again, so you have to win.
First, we will have the queens' battle.
If you meet her halfway,
just do whatever you want.
Take your hat off!
Soyu, do a dance first!
- Dance first.
- What were our choreography...
[This, this]
[A-Pink remembers SISTAR's dance moves?]
Just show us!
[Shake it, shake it]
I like this.
- This is your dance move?
- Yeah, it's an actual move.
- Bomi, do one...
- I'll do one from our new album.
Let's go on a trip!
- This is one of our dances.
- Really?
Let's go on a trip!
The dance is kind of modest...
[It should be more like this.]
One, two, three, four!
[Shake, shake]
[Wiggle, wiggle]
[Fierce SISTAR vs. Cute A-Pink.]
Let's go!
Soyu's pretty good at games.
[Team Bomi's cushion faces up
and team Soyu's cushion faces down.]
[Flip the cushion, starts!]
[Flip and flip!]
Oh, she's quick!
[Stacking up]
[That's a smart way...]
That's right!
Bomi, just take them!
[They changed their tactics
from collecting to dispersing.]
Soyu!
Possess the cushions!
[Bump]
[The unfortunate encounter]
Possess the cushions!
Bomi, where are you going?
What are you doing?
Bomi, just throw them!
- That's it, that's good!
- Go, Soyu!
Soyu!
[Girl group war.]
Bomi, are you tired?
[She's seeking an opportunity...]
[How dare you!]
She knows Taekwondo!
[Power sliding!]
[Out of breath]
[Which queen will win the battle...]
[and be the winner?]
[Time over]
We won!
[The last of flips!]
[She aims for the buzzer beater.]
[Both flips were a fail.]
- One, two, three...
- We won!
[Ten?]
- It's ten.
You guys tied.
You have to go again.
[Tied game]
This is really hard!
Bomi's slide at the end!
Bomi, would you like a beer?
[No thank you.]
[Team Bomi vs. team Soyu.]
We meet again!
I'll show you how to play this game.
This game has a solution.
[The flip game...]
[It's easy if you know the theory.]
- Jae Suk!
- That's why I told you to win.
What do we do...
[I won't lose twice...
beware, Kim Jong Kook!]
He's scary.
Jae Suk!
Get low!
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Lift]
Jae Suk!
[Flip the cushion is so easy.]
Soyu!
Get out of there!
[Swing, swing]
I didn't know it would be this bad!
[I didn't know either...]
[A strike to the face]
I'm so upset!
[Flip]
[He's doing his best
in his limited condition.]
Jae Suk, come down!
I can't!
[It's impossible to get down.]
What do we do?
[Poke, poke]
You're crazy!
[Game over!]
How do you win this?
This doesn't make any sense!
[Second round: 13 to 7.]
Is this fair?
- We're good to go!
- We lost one game.
[How will round three turn out?]
[What's the mission for premium beef?]
The first battle is
the backward step long jump.
Backward?
Each team takes turns five times.
[Add the scores and the team
with the highest collective score wins.]
I'm actually really light.
Look.
[For their motivation]
Not yet!
They put a slice of beef!
They're stimulating us!
[Bling, bling, marbling,
I will eat you today.]
[First round of backward
long jump, Kwang Soo.]
[Sloppy, sloppy]
This is really weird...
- How should I do it?
- You know what?
That's useless
when you jump backward.
- What do I do?
- That only helps when you jump forward.
You have to do it the opposite way!
- You know less than a girl?
- She's my queen.
You are qualified as a queen!
Kwang Soo!
Challenge!
[He jumped!]
[That was a jump?]
Are you serious?
That's it?
Stop kidding around!
Try it yourself!
[He's not useful of his long legs.]
- I can jump more than you!
- Try it!
I thought he was a ballerino.
He lifted his feet up like this!
[The biggest humiliation]
If you just jump, I think you'll
go further than Kwang Soo.
- It's weird.
- Achoo!
[It's almost the same as Kwang Soo.]
It's so weird.
This is harder than I thought.
How did you pass one meter?
- Gook Joo, you have to win.
- I think I can do this.
I think she's going to jump
further than both of you.
[I'm ready.]
Gook Joo, the meat's done already!
[If you don't hurry,
it might get tougher...]
[I'll hurry and eat it up.]
One, two, three!
[Powerful jump!]
[Fly, Gook Joo!]
She jumped more than you did!
[50 centimeters is beyond their capacity.]
We failed.
Challenge!
She did it!
[One meter?]
[Oh my god!]
[That's like Bora... what?]
[One step forward]
It's right here! Here!
We're safe!
We can eat!
[You crossed the line...]
That's too bad!
It's here!
[Bora's mistake,
her measurement is 0 cm.]
[Who will win the premium beef?]
[What about the mission for
chicken soup with ginseng?]
[Tie the drumstick
and eliminate the name tags.]
Tie the drumstick?
You have to roll a dice with
various types of gloves written on it.
You need to wear the gloves you roll.
You then have to take off
the opponent's name tag to win.
Please get mittens!
Mittens!
[Team Purple gets mittens.]
[Devastated]
We're doomed!
How did I get this?
- Seol Hyun will roll it for me.
- Get mittens!
[What will Seol Hyun roll for Gary?]
Scrubbing gloves!
[We screwed up!]
Mittens are better
than scrubbing gloves!
We selected the two worst ones.
How do you use this?
This is actually not that bad.
I think I can win.
Coming from Suk Jin,
it wounds my pride.
Okay!
[The first round of Tie the Drumstick.]
- Don't play 'Push the Palm'!
- I'm not!
[Sudden attack]
I'm not striking the palm!
[Risky]
I'm going to win!
I'm also going to win!
Go, Gary!
[Grab]
[Will the game end like this?]
[Name tag elimination
with scrubbing gloves?]
[He ripped it!]
[Big Nose...]
[Queen Seol Hyun's team
wins the first round.]
There was no surprise.
[Seol Hyun got scrubbing gloves.]
[and Ji Hyo got ski gloves.]
Fighting, Ji Hyo!
This is such a burden.
[Queen Seol Hyun vs. Queen Ji Hyo.]
- Fighting!
- Ji Hyo!
[Round two, start!]
[Will it be the ambitious Seol Hyun
or the expert Ji Hyo?]
[Which Queen will win this round?]
Very good!
[Close match]
That's it!
First, grab her...
[Head down]
[Pull, then rip!]
[Ji Hyo won the second round!]
Don't ask her if she's okay
after pulling her head!
I thought it was watching the UFC!
[I'm sorry I'm competitive...]
I'm okay!
Why do you act like this
when Seol Hyun's here?
I'm so sorry, Seol Hyun!
Let's have a dance battle!
I'm really sorry...
But go entertain yourself somewhere else!
Why are you trying to
amuse yourself here?
This is insane!
We're doing okay!
- I don't want to!
- Or go eat something else then!
[The last round for two points.]
This is the final round.
Ready, set!
[Start!]
[Collect all the cushions!]
[Attack!]
[The Lifting Ghost is back.]
[Lifts]
[Transformed into hot pants!]
What are you doing?
[If you don't put me down]
[I'll pull your pants up to
your shoulders.]
Are you crazy?
[The victory is in the Queens' hands!]
You're crazy!
[This time, it's a crop top!]
Soyu, come here!
This is the only solution!
[Free hugs everywhere.]
Soyu!
My back hurts!
It pricks!
[Time's up!]
[Flip the cushion is now over.]
How did it turn out?
[Seven facing up,
thirteen facing down.]
We won!
[Queen Soyu won!]
[Meaningless]
Unexpectedly...
Bomi's jaw is out.
She's angry.
The Queen that won the mission
can merge terms.
Bomi, please give your armband
to Queen Soyu.
[Queen Bomi is now a member
of Queen Soyu's team.]
You have to change into blue clothes.
Go change!
You'll look like a magnet!
[At the same time, at the
premium beef restaurant...]
[They jump...]
[and jump.]
Good job!
If you're going to fall, fall backward!
[Team Bora is at a disadvantage
because of her 0 cm.]
She's a good jumper.
[She reached one meter!]
That scared me!
[He almost broke his nose.]
- My forehead!
- You're crazy!
[Bora's team is at advantage.]
How is it possible?
[But Team Gook Joo has another chance!]
[We need to end this with our jump.]
- I'm going for real.
- Kwang Soo, shake it!
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it!
[The pronunciation
sounds a bit like a curse...]
I was just advertising my new song!
Kwang Soo, it's kind of addicting.
Kwang Soo, shake it!
Shake it, shake it!
[She's having fun.]
- I'm cheering for you!
- It's not cheerful at all!
What are you doing!
[What about this?]
Kwang Soo, I only have this left...
[Why are you so far...]
Just wait.
Just close your eyes.
What are you going to do?
- This works, right?
- Yeah, you saw earlier!
[Anxious, anxious]
Shake it, shake it, shake it!
- I'm ready!
- One...
Two, blast off!
[This is probably...]
[the end of my life...]
[Go, jumping booster!]
[High forehead!]
[He risked his life for that jump?]
His heart hurts...
His body is also hurt...
Why did you strike down?
You have to aim up, not down!
Did you hit me with your bone?
If you hit my ear,
my eardrum would've ripped apart!
You should have jumped further!
[Five scores vs. four scores.]
[Which team has the highest score?]
- We can't predict.
- It's done!
We will announce the results.
Team Green has a total of
291 cm.
Team Yellow only has four scores.
[The total score is...]
320 cm.
[Team Bora wins the backward long jump!]
[The premium beef is ours!]
Now your Queen is Bora.
You must obey the Queen
and change your clothes.
That's a harder mission for Gook Joo!
It takes me three hours to change.
Change into these.
[Rubber gloves vs. scrubber gloves.]
[Team Seol Hyun wins at LTE speed]
[Team Beef, Team Eel,
and Team chicken soup with ginseng.]
- Can I have some lemon-lime soda?
- I'll get you some!
[The Queen can choose the order
and the amount of food to divide.]
That's no fun!
You have to make the Queen entertained.
[She's full of rhythm already.]
Congratulations on becoming the Queen!
Where did it go?
I want to drink this.
It's the first time
I've seen a woman do this!
[She's making the noise with her mouth.]
Is it refreshing?
Of course!
Showing off your charm!
Is there any rice?
[Immediately at your service.]
You can't just give it to her!
Did you just call me 'Sir'?
There are pieces stuck at the bottom.
You have to shake it.
So it's clean.
What are you doing?
When you eat, you have
to eat with Gook Joo.
You must eat the victory onions as well.
[My mouth is full of premium beef.]
[Another bite]
[and it kept diminishing...]
[Binge eating broadcast]
But I wish the Queen would stop now.
You might have to eat
in the next game, too.
- I'll eat again.
- We can all eat together.
[I want to eat it just once...]
Let's have a toast for our new Queen.
Let's just catch Gook Joo.
Gook Joo, cheers.
And you're the youngest, so be quick.
No, I'm the Queen so don't
tell him what to do!
[Backs down]
He needs strength.
Eat a lot because you need
to use your strength.
I'm feeling a little upset.
Strong people are the best!
- We need to win!
- She's dividing it up.
[She distributes Yoo Hyuk's first.]
- You gave me the tail?
- Yes, you can only have that.
We can just eat now.
Thank you for the meal!
[Jae Suk is now useless.]
Thank you for the meal.
She's something else
after gaining authority!
Jong Kook and Bomi,
you guys aren't even looking at me!
- You really like the pumpkin.
- He's a pumpkin maniac.
You're harsh, ma'am!
- What do you mean 'ma'am'?
- You're too much!
She's the middle-aged Queen lady!
- I'll take my share first.
- The Queen's first.
You must like the legs.
- It must be soft.
- She must like it.
It's a really big chicken!
This is supposed to be good, sorry.
[Imprudent]
Take this away!
[He has to return the porridge.]
You have to do what the Queen says!
[They're showing flattery
to obtain some meat.]
I want to become a DJ like Ha Ha.
Always full of energy and spirit!
[Words like candy to my ears!]
I'm going to grow a beard soon,
just like you.
I just want to be just like him.
[What are you saying...]
- I'm going to draw it.
- If you're going to do it, do it now!
- Do it now!
- If you bring it, I'll do it now!
You just stay quiet!
[Discrimination between
human relationship.]
Whoever draws a funnier mustache
first gets the meat.
Okay?
Go do it.
[A lady's transformation is innocent.]
[But this is guilty...]
I think I have to draw one, too.
[What's taking them so long?]
The beggar has returned!
See who came back?
It's Bang Shi Hyuk
who came last year!
[Coming soon!]
[Uncle Gook Joo?]
Ha Ha, look at her forehead.
[Uncle Gook Joo's bottle cap show.]
Let me open it for you.
Bang Shi Hyuk opens
the bottle cap like 'Pop!'
- Eat!
- I will be eating, thank you.
Where did Kwang Soo go?
[He's preparing alone
for that big shot.]
[Gook Joo's on binge eating standby.]
You're not going to wrap it?
By the time she wraps one,
the meat's going to be gone.
Professionals just eat.
She eats really fast.
[She's downing meat like water...]
Who is that?
[The appearance of Mr. Charcoal!]
I'm a little late.
I was fetching some charcoal.
- That face...
- This is the overall style.
- Is she eating already?
- It's already done.
This is the last plate...
[Gray look]
[Finishing touches]
You didn't leave me one piece?
I was in a hurry.
I was really hungry, sorry.
Do you think I wanted to do this?
I'm still a woman.
You're more handsome like that.
Let's go Ha Ha, let's go Queen.
Let's go!
I didn't even get to eat one piece!
[Water park]
['B' water park in Gyeongju.]
- Jae Suk, you guys merged!
- Yeah!
- I grabbed Jong Kook with one arm.
- You?
I suppressed him, and then
pressed his knee down!
Is it true?
He's all shy now that you've said that.
- I pressed his knee down.
- Soyu did all the work.
Bora!
You guys merged!
[They're relaxed after
emerging with Team Gook Joo.]
She's good.
There have been rumors that
you tried really hard today!
It's no joke today.
[Victory for Queen Seol Hyun!]
I will merge everyone to Team Orange!
Are sure it's not pink
instead of orange?
Oh my god!
[A midsummer day dream.]
[Lovey dovey]
Have you been on that before?
[I can't believe it...
we're at a water park...]
Don't get a two-shot!
It's embarrassing!
[All three teams enter
the water park together.]
[What is that?]
[This is a huge rice bowl?]
There's fish!
- Is it sushi?
- It's rice with sliced raw fish!
Is it rice with sliced raw fish?
[What do you use this for?]
This is the second mission of the race.
It's the rice bowl fight.
Everyone will be dancing
in the bowl together.
When the whistle blows
you have to push your
opponents out of the bowl.
After the time limit passes
the team that has the most members
left standing will win.
[Woohoo!]
Who's going to push me?
[Mission impossible]
Who's going to lift Gook Joo?
I'm not lying but when
I fell into the water
four people couldn't even lift me.
Sorry, but everyone should help
in lifting Gook Joo first.
First Gook Joo, then Jong Kook.
[Try if you can.]
I'll just play a big part in this.
He's the youngest on our team!
Jong Kook's the youngest?
Your youngest member is cute.
I am cute, right?
[I'll show you how cute I am!]
One out of the three teams
will win by default.
That's advantageous!
That's intense!
The third team's queen
has to return the armband.
Along with the rest of her members,
they will be merged to one of the teams.
They will be split?
Gary and Seol Hyun
could be separated, too.
Is that so?
You can't separate our hearts
just by physically splitting us up.
The person that Gary liked before
and now are in one team.
I feel weird to be in this team.
Three queens will play
rock-paper-scissors.
We'll pick one team that
will advance to the finals now.
Queens, you'll play
rock-paper-scissors.
If we win, Ha Ha and Suk Jin...
[Throw scissors.]
Good luck, Bora!
[Suk Jin's team will throw scissors.]
Rock-paper-scissors, shoot!
[Queen Bora wins!]
[Her team goes to the finals.]
Pick the second winner.
[Did I make it too obvious?]
[Queen Soyu vs. Queen Seol Hyun]
It's unfavorable.
It's hard to fight against Jong Kook.
[Rice Bowl Fight, Round 1]
[Get ready!]
Good luck!
I heard Bomi is really strong.
- Soyu and Bomi are both strong.
- Soyu is strong, too.
[Power sisters]
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
Start the music!
I like this.
[They need to play the game
as soon as they hear the whistle.]
[Side dishes are added.]
[It becomes the giant bibimbap.]
[Let's go!]
[Dance party to celebrate early summer.]
Seol Hyun!
[After Seol Hyun, it's Bomi's turn.]
[She keeps dancing for
'Let's Go On A Trip.']
[The perfect ending!]
[The rice bowl turns
into a dance stage.]
[Their dance is hotter than
the hot weather.]
[They forget about the game.]
[Seol Hyun starts break dancing.]
I have no choice but to show it off.
What are you doing?
[Knee spin]
[The delinquent Yoo loses his mind
when the music starts.]
[At that moment!]
[Yoo Hyuk is surrounded
by the enemies.]
[The two teams play tug of war
using Jae Suk's arms.]
[Come back, Jae Suk!]
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Save the Grasshopper!]
[Gary is very enthusiastic today.]
I can do it!
Gary, Seol Hyun is watching!
The losing team will be separated!
[Hey, you don't need to do this...]
[At that critical moment,
the music resumes.]
[As soon as the music starts,
they start their dance party.]
[They forget about the game immediately
and dance passionately.]
[It's a good chance to escape
for those who reached a crisis.]
Don't use up your energy!
[He's supposed to rest
and charge now...]
[I'll follow him.]
[At that moment, the whistle blows!]
[Big Nose is surrounded
by the enemies now.]
[Big Nose is in danger!]
Oh, no!
[A forceful stretching]
[A desperate struggle]
[Narrow escape]
[At the moment,
Gary becomes the target.]
- No way!
- No!
[It's so exciting!]
[This won't do.]
[Roar]
[Lift]
[I'm the youngest member.]
[Am I cute?]
Be careful!
[Gary couldn't even use
his energy and get ousted.]
[Their next target is Big-nose]
[Another lift]
I'll stay here!
[Float]
[Drops]
[Big Nose is ousted.]
[Queen Soyu's team wins.]
[Thanks to the cute member,
they win the game.]
[Queen Soyu's team
advances to the finals.]
[The finals of Rice Bowl Fight]
[Queen Soyu vs. Queen Bora]
[But this team has
the Ultimate Weapon!]
This is awful!
[We forgot about her!]
[Jong Kook, did you forget me already?]
[Last year, during the hot summer...]
[Tight]
[He was cuddled by Gook Joo.]
It's so hot because of Gook Joo!
[We meet again.]
[I believe in you, Gook Joo!]
[Mr. Capable vs. The Ultimate Weapon,
will he be able to evade her this time?]
What are you doing?
Start the music!
You need to go out some other time!
Why do you have to do this here?
[It's party time!]
[Let's get sweaty!]
[This is the Rice Bowl Club!]
[Mom, don't wait up for me tonight.
I'll go home late.]
It's slippery here!
[Duet with Gook Joo]
[Soyu joins.]
[Bomi and Kkuk joins, too.]
[The human train dance]
[The players enter to the beat.]
[Slip]
Gook Joo!
What are you doing?
What were you doing?
[In the meantime,
the other players have entered.]
[The Ultimate Weapon
has fixed upon her target.]
Why are you doing this to me?
[You know why.]
[She grabs him and does the body wave.]
[The dance is getting intense.]
[Her fascinating dance!]
Lee Gook Joo!
[Wait, I'm not done yet!]
[What's my name?]
[Lee Gook Joo!]
[I can't lose like this!]
[The big match]
[Yoo Hyuk vs. Gook Joo]
[I heard you're quite the dancer.]
[I heard you know something
about dancing.]
[Slide]
[Roll]
[You didn't expect that, did you?]
[Hops]
[And a relaxed finish.]
[I acknowledge defeat.]
[The finals, first round starts!]
[Attacking Yoo Hyuk
as soon as it begins.]
[Don't go anywhere!]
[The Grasshopper's crisis]
This is tiring!
[Yoo Hyuk is almost ousted.]
[At that moment, the music starts.]
The music is playing!
[Peck]
I'm so sorry.
[The melody of peace]
Please, help me!
[Everybody charges up their energy.]
Hurry up!
[Whistle]
[Kkuk attacks Ha Ha before
he gets caught by Gook Joo.]
Help me, Gook Joo!
[Jong Kook, I'm right here!]
[Why are you here again?]
Ha Ha!
[The power sisters'
concentrated attack against Bora.]
[Bora rebounds to escape.]
[Ha Ha is one step away
from being ousted.]
[Did Bora push him?]
[Bora's outs her own teammate.]
[Ha Ha is ousted.]
- It was you?
- It was me.
- Why did you push me?
- I didn't know it was you.
[Kkuk is still tied...]
[The battle is getting intense.]
- No way!
- Gook Joo!
[I'm sorry guys...
I don't think I can help you...]
[I thought you're Mr. Capable...]
Jong Kook!
[I guess I'm not, in front of her...]
[Even though he's my enemy,
I feel sorry for him...]
Look at Bora!
[Powerful Soyu grabs Bora
and throws her.]
[Shiver]
[The queens are very competitive.]
[By the way, what is that?]
[She grabs the blonde hair...]
- Is this mine?
- Whose is that?
This is yours!
[Did you lose your hair?]
[Time's up!]
[The first round of the finals,
Team Blue wins.]
Does everyone wear this?
I think Soyu threw me too hard.
If I sit here for five minutes,
this rice bowl will flip over.
Does anyone have any sleeping pills?
Even if you inject a tranquilizer dart,
I'll pull it out!
- Stop giving me water.
- Drink it.
[The finals, second round starts!]
What is this?
You said you won't do it again.
[The dancing machine is broken.]
Very good!
That's not cool.
At least, move to the beat!
[Let's do this!]
[Yes!]
[I mean with my Kkuk.]
Why are you doing this to me?
[Release me.]
She's too funny!
[SISTAR's new song is playing.]
[Dance party with SISTAR]
[They immediately dance in sync.]
Bora, let's go!
[But who is she?]
[She dances for two people.]
[In perfect sync.]
[The dance cools down
the hot weather.]
[It's not over yet!]
[Shake it again!]
[A-pink's 'Luv.']
L. O. V. E. Love!
[They're united by 'Luv.']
[Bomi's passionate dance]
[A-pink is love.]
[And the next stage is...]
[AOA's 'Heart Attack.']
[Her face looks shy
but her dance is sexy.]
[Heart attack]
[Thanks to Seol Hyun,
the guys' heart rate goes up.]
[Pit-a-pat]
[I'm having a heart attack.]
What's wrong?
[She dances for the love of one man.]
Put it back!
[Her push-pull technique!]
She's playing hard-to-get!
[At that moment,
Bomi starts dancing.]
[Bravo, Bomi!]
That's great!
You've shown enough, Bomi!
Good job, Bomi!
[Gook Joo's counterattack!]
[Split]
[Scream]
[She fails at a counterattack.]
That's it!
[The finals, second round]
[While Gook Joo falls,
Kkuk attacks Ha Ha.]
Wake up, Gook Joo!
Don't attack me!
[As soon as Gook Joo gets up,
Kkuk runs away.]
- Gook Joo...
- That's very good!
[Let Kkuk be free!]
[Operation blocking Gook Joo!]
What are you doing?
Go away!
[Bora throws Gook Joo.]
[Queen Bora, what's wrong with you?]
[Kkuk is free.]
[Did you miss me?]
It's three vs. three!
Fight, Bomi!
[Lift]
[No! I can't lose like this!]
[Hanging on]
[Kwang Soo is about to fall as well.]
They're over!
[Ha Ha is ousted!]
It's over!
It's over now!
[Kwang Soo is ousted at the moment
the whistle blows.]
[Queen Soyu's team wins
the second mission.]
[Gook Joo, punish Jong Kook later.]
[Queen Soyu's team have
two consecutive victories.]
[The Rice Bowl Fight]
[1st: Queen Soyu, 2nd: Queen Bora]
The queen who placed third,
please return armband.
I'm sorry.
Therefore, the first winner, Queen Soyu
can pick one male and one female
regardless of the couples.
- Think outside the box.
- Thank you, Soyu.
Pick anything for the male member.
- Pick anything?
- Why are we a 'thing'?
[I'm sorry.]
Pick anyone you want.
Since Ji Hyo came...
Should I let 'Monday Couple'
reunite or...
Just do what you want.
I don't mind at all.
[Really?]
[Then come.]
Me?
I don't mind at all.
Come to our team, then.
[Big Nose and Seol Hyun
join Queen Bora's team.]
[Goodbye, Gary.]
[Our happy memory...]
[and dreamlike time together.]
[It was just a dream...]
[Queen Soyu's team]
[Queen Bora's team]
[The final mission]
[The collection of
the toughest missions!]
[I'll put my life on the line
for my queen!]
I didn't think it would be this tough!
[It begins now!]
The last mission of
'The Queen of Early Summer Race'
is 'Capture the flag.'
- What is it?
- Capture?
There are five missions
in this water park.
Whenever you succeed at a mission
you'll get different numbers of flags
according to difficulty levels.
After the 30-minute time limit
the team with the most flags
will be the winning team.
The winning team will ascend the throne
to the Queen of Early Summer.
The thing is, even if one team
puts their flags on a post
the other team can try the same mission
and switches it with their own flag.
- Both of them are SISTAR members.
- Open it.
That's the queen card.
If you use the queen card,
it will double the number of flags.
We can use it only once.
If you fail the mission,
the card will be discarded.
We need to keep it for something
that we're confident in.
I have a good feeling.
You can run around the flags and check.
Get ready.
Let's go check out
what the missions are first.
It starts from this moment,
ready, set...
[Capture the flag, starts!]
Go!
[They need to find
where the missions are.]
There are missions for three flags
and for one flag.
- Do you understand?
- We need to just find flags?
No, we'll get flags
when we succeed missions.
Will there be any missions
that I'm good at?
What are you talking about?
We'll do it whatever that is!
We can try something else
if we can't do it.
What is that?
What did you find?
Here it is!
[Gook Joo and Kwang Soo find it first.]
Three persons, mixed gender!
[A mission for two flags.]
Go down the water slide
and spot three numbers.
[From a 20-meter height...]
Don't we have to walk up?
[find three hidden numbers!]
There are three numbers on the slide.
Do you think you can do it?
- Hurry up and go!
- Let's go!
Ji Hyo, Bomi, and Gary!
- Go try this mission.
- Succeed it quickly!
Let's go somewhere else.
Isn't going up the slide
harder than the mission?
- Don't give up.
- I don't think I can.
- Gook Joo, hurry up!
- Getting there is the mission.
This is the real mission.
It's too far!
My legs are tired.
I want to try something else.
But I can do it!
[Jae Suk finds another mission.]
A person on the ride shots a ball
and the other person catches it.
Catch three times.
Mixed gender and no limit on
the number of persons.
It'll shoot us 10 meters high.
I'll catch the ball.
[Will it be okay to sit here?]
Catch it well, Soyu!
Throw it as far as possible!
Jong Kook!
It won't be scary, right?
['My Ball', Queen Soyu
needs to catch three balls.]
Get ready, it'll shoot you forward.
[Flying Grasshopper]
[He threw the ball!]
[It's too hard to catch it.]
[Splash!]
What are you doing?
Soyu, what is this?
What's going on?
[While Grasshopper
was flying in the sky...]
[he laid an egg.]
[The second runner is Kkuk.]
[Shots from a free throw position!]
[The ball traces better than Yoo Hyuk's.]
[Again, it was too short!]
What happened?
Hurry up, Jae Suk!
[While Queen Soyu is busy
catching balls...]
[What is Queen Bora doing?]
[She finds a new mission zone
with Haroro.]
Get the jump rope from
the bottom of the pool.
Stand on the floating disc and
jump five times with your partner.
[Within five tries,
jump five times in a row!]
[Getting the jump rope
at the bottom of the pool.]
[It's hard to stand on
the floating disc.]
[The first attempt]
[Splash!]
[There's a reason why
it's worth three flags.]
Let's do it!
[The second attempt]
[Steps on]
- You stepped on my foot!
- I'm sorry!
[The third attempt]
[Goodbye, Ha Ha!]
[He saves the queen.]
Let's do something else!
[They can try two more times,
but they give up.]
- It's lucky to fail the first mission.
- Why do you keep falling?
- It's cold, my butt is wet!
- Put your legs straight.
[Go down the water slide
and catch three numbers.]
[The boat moves.]
Oh, my, my. Mother!
[Why is this boat so heavy?]
Mother!
[Scream]
[It speeds up and goes down
through the tunnel.]
[Where is the number?]
[Water hits them from everywhere.]
[Before finding any numbers,
they can barely keep their mind clear.]
Where's the number?
[Wait, is that the number?]
[It's right there!]
Four!
[They said there are three numbers?]
[The slide was fear-inducing.]
- I never knew it was this scary!
- Where are the numbers?
[Where are the other two numbers?]
If you saw the numbers,
please tell me the three numbers.
First of all, four!
[Thinking]
Eighteen!
- Gook Joo!
- Why?
You need to pick a possible number!
[This time, Team Blue attempts.]
Look carefully!
[360-degree monitoring mode]
[There's a number
on top of the tunnel!]
[Did Blank Ji see it?]
- Five!
[It was a split second!]
[Wait, that's...]
[They found a number
on the side of the slide!]
[Did she actually see it?]
[The merciless torrent
doesn't give them time.]
[Right before the finish line...]
[There it is!]
[They need to see the number
in order to succeed.]
- Five, six, and seven!
- Did you see it?
[They're very sure
they have the answer.]
[Team Blue is back on the ground.]
Five, seven, and six!
[Team Blue succeeds at
'search the numbers on the slide.']
[This is the blue team's territory now.]
[The current state of flags]
[Blue vs Yellow]
Here it is!
What is this?
[Drink the juice out of the straw.]
This is for one flag.
[This spacesuit-looking thing
was a straw?]
[Challenge]
[He simply needs to drink it.]
[What a quiet mission it is!]
What kind of a game is this?
[It's passing the fifth row.]
[Cheer up, Big Nose!]
[The two queens play against
each other at the 'My ball zone.']
[Bora, I'll show you this time!]
Hurry up, Ha Ha!
[I believe in you!]
[Okay, my ball!]
[It bounces back!]
[Where did the ball go?]
[It went into the Queen Soyu's basket.]
[Ha Ha's ball flew in a beautiful arc.]
[Bora tosses it to Queen Soyu.]
Ha Ha, we gave it to Soyu!
[Nice play]
Good job!
[Team Blue's second attempt]
[Queen Soyu's consecutive catch]
[One more ball, please!]
[The third ball shots!]
[Focus!]
[If she catches it,
they'll succeed at this mission!]
[She made it!]
[Yoo Hyuk's precise shot]
[and Queen Soyu's safe catch.]
[Team Blue succeeds at
'My Ball Zone.']
[Did you see my ball control skills?]
[Team Blue marks
their second territory.]
She's my queen!
[The current state of flags]
We need to find something
you're really good at.
But we don't know
what games we have.
What is this?
Is it difficult?
- Let's just pass by!
- Drink a lot, Suk Jin!
[Team Blue wants to keep the advantage.]
Who do we need to give this card to?
We want to use this card.
[The queen card is being used for
the couple jump rope mission.]
[If they succeed at it,
it will double the number of flags.]
Gary, Bomi, we used up our queen card.
Do it well!
Be careful!
- Do you want to do without stopping?
- Yes.
Just keep the same spot.
[The first attempt]
[They fail at the fourth jump.]
It was close!
We can do it, Bomi!
[Their second attempt]
[They're faster this time.]
[They jumped four...]
[Just one more jump...]
[Wobble]
[and fall]
[Why does this always happen
after their fourth jump?]
Let's focus until the last one.
[Their third attempt]
[Stable footwork]
[Six flags depend on this jump!]
[Success!]
[Team Blue succeeds at
the couple jump rope.]
[We've seized the chance to victory!]
[They've acquired six flags at once.]
[The current state of flags]
[The gap between the two teams
has increased.]
We don't have much time left.
What are you doing?
Come over here.
Let's try this!
We'll challenge that!
One, two, three!
[Seol Hyun flies!]
[She threw the ball.]
I've got it!
Are you okay?
Can you throw two more?
You received it?
I'll do it!
What's going on?
[Elegance]
[She ties up her hair...]
[and gets ready to shot the ball.]
[The second shot]
[Nice catch!]
One more!
Seol Hyun, you're cool!
You look like a mermaid!
[While Seol Hyun is
showing off her graceful beauty...]
[Giraffe is having a hard time.]
[Stack up a can tower
of five cans on the tray.]
[Man carries Woman on his shoulder]
[while Woman stacks up
five cans on the tray.]
Where did the tray go?
[It has to stay for 3 seconds.]
[The tray is far away from them.]
Let me do it!
[Queen Bora is urgently deployed.]
[Gook Joo exits the mission zone.]
What is this?
Was this mission this easy?
[With Queen Bora,
the horse gets fast.]
[It has to stay standing
for three seconds.]
[Success!]
[Team Yellow begins
their counterattack.]
[Team Yellow wins one flag.]
I'll throw it!
[They'll succeed at it
if Ha Ha catches one more ball.]
[He received it!]
[Team Yellow succeeds at
'My Ball Mission.']
[The current state of flags]
[Finally, Team Yellow's
counterattack is working!]
Let's hurry up and go!
Aren't you good at it?
[They run to the slide mission zone
at full speed.]
This is 'Running Man'!
Just get on the boat!
It's almost there, Bomi!
[Bomi is wearing the straw
and drinks out of it.]
[The flag is switched to Team Blue's.]
[Let me absorb the juice!]
Little more, it's almost there!
That's right!
You did it!
[The yellow flag is back to its place.]
I think we can do this in the end.
When we feel thirsty.
That's very smart!
[Team Yellow tries
the water slide mission again.]
[We must see the numbers!]
[Right now!]
[The first number!]
[Work with your eyes
and catch the number!]
[That's the second number?]
Three, three, three, three!
It's eight!
[They spotted all three numbers!]
[The saw the three numbers correctly.]
[Team Yellow acquires two more flags.]
We don't have much time.
You need to do this.
[We're winning and
we have five minutes.]
Currently, the teams are tied!
What?
[The current state of flags]
Hurry up!
[Either of the teams that wins
another mission will win.]
[Team Blue is simultaneously playing
the water slide and stack the tower.]
[Team Yellow is playing jump rope.]
Hurry up!
[Team Yellow uses
the queen card.]
[If they succeed at it,
it will double the number of flags.]
[It's their last chance!]
[If they win the six flags,
they can win the mission.]
[They're under great pressure.]
[Their first attempt.]
[Splash]
[Even Team Yellow
can't avoid the curse of four.]
[They have four more tries.]
30 seconds left!
Hold the four cans.
[Maybe they can secure
their victory with this game.]
[Team Blue going down
on the water slide.]
The person sitting on this side
needs to see it.
[The second attempt]
[Let's calm down...]
[They fail right before
their fifth jump.]
Hurry up and go up again.
[They only have about 80 seconds.]
This is your last chance!
[The team who wins the current mission
will win the race!]
[Did Team Blue see the first number?]
[And the second number is...]
[I'm sure it's on the right side.]
Three!
[Team Blue spots the numbers one by one.]
[Team Yellow's third attempt]
[The fateful jump!]
[Win this mission and win the race!]
[They've seen two numbers already.]
[The last number is...]
[right here!]
[Blank Ji saw it!]
Seven, three, and one!
[The only thing left
is to say the answer.]
[Gary and Bomi constructed the tower.]
[Keep it standing for three seconds...]
[We will do it, no matter what!]
Seven, three, and one!
Seven, three, and one?
[Gary and Bomi's tower]
One, two...
[It collapsed.]
[The jump rope for six flags...]
Seven, three, and one!
[Is that the correct answer?]
[Team Blue fails at
the water slide mission.]
[What's wrong?]
Seven, three, and one!
[If only Team Yellow succeeds...]
[Just one more jump...]
[No way!]
[Team Yellow succeeds!]
[They won the last mission
even with the queen card.]
[They win the battle of pressure!]
[Team Yellow acquires six flags.]
[The current state of flags]
[No one expected these results!]
Bora, Bora!
[Team Blue was winning
until the midpoint.]
[Team Yellow members
can't believe it themselves.]
Seol Hyun, now you're smiling.
[She smiles after she wins.]
[Bora ascends the throne
as the Queen of Early Summer.]
Aren't they too much?
These are golden eggs.
Let's share the joy!
Please give one to my queen and Bomi.
Please, give me one.
Yes, give it to Bomi.
- Are you giving it to me?
- Sure, take one.
[Former Queen Soyu
takes the golden egg.]
[The special ceremony for
the Queen of Early Summer]
Is it fun, Bora?
Today's race is to find my house.
Are we supposed to find his house?
Maybe it's Tony.
Please find it.
- Let's go!
- We need to win to get a hint.
[The ill-fated battle
between 2PM and Kkuk!]
[The cool fight of
ripping each other!]
[Baek Jin Hee throws herself
to find a hint!]
Who is it?
[No one knows who it is
or where it is.]
[After many troubles,
the great plot twist reveals!]
Next week, 'Come Over to My Place.'