[The 'Running Man' fifth
anniversary special, part two.]
['Please, Find Me!']
[One summer night]
[they were left alone in
an abandoned school.]
[It should have been empty,
but someone's in there...]
[Who could they be?]
What are you saying?
You talked to me upstairs, just now...
[Horror...]
[always...]
[happens without warning!]
[A hot horrifying party
on a summer night.]
[Their struggle for survival]
[Mission: Escape the abolished
school with your VJ!]
[Survival or loyalty?
That is the question!]
Film me!
Hey, hey, you... you!
[From the VJs to the main producer,
they're all called out!]
[The hottest night in
'Running Man' history!]
[Never be caught off-guard!]
['Please, Find Me', coming soon!]
[Last week, The Million Seller Race]
[Running Man's
fifth anniversary party.]
[The Running Man members
were invited by surprise.]
This early?
[Who is the first million
seller they will meet?]
Hello, everyone!
Nice to meet you, I'm your DJ for today.
I'm Koo Jun Yup from CLON!
[First million seller,
Koo Jun Yup from CLON.]
[Bump]
[He has good endurance]
[and full of energy as a bonus!]
[He wins everything with power!]
[If you follow me,
you will see victory!]
[Koo Jun Yup from CLON]
[The second guest is here!]
It's g.o.d!
[Park Jun Hyung from g.o.d]
- Who did you like the most?
- I like Kye Sang.
[It's okay, I'm cool about it.]
It's okay, I'm already married!
Okay, we'll start.
[Class is forever!]
[Bro Jun played an active role!]
[Oh my, 'God Jun Hyung!']
[Park Jun Hyung from g.o.d]
[Wow, it's summer!]
[Here comes the icon of summer!]
[Third million seller,
Lee Jae Hun from Cool.]
[What's the other side of
Jae Hoon he's been hiding?]
[Incredibly competitive!]
[This is fun!]
She did it!
[He's willing to protest
against the opponent's tricks!]
[I will take over this race!]
[Lee Jae Hun from Cool]
It never stops!
[The bad boy that made the
entire nation dance is back!]
[Fourth million seller,
Lee Ha Neul from DJ DOC.]
[DJ DOC and CLON's hidden diss war.]
I go to church nowadays.
[I'm a new man, now.]
If you don't come,
I'll write you a letter.
[You're at it again?]
[No one can stop his bad boy DNA.]
[Lee Ha Neul from DJ DOC]
[The last guest that will conclude
the fifth anniversary party!]
[Fifth million seller, Kim Gun Mo.]
[But even he has flaws...]
[We need to save up!]
We can earn more!
Give me 500,000 discs.
What for?
So we can buy the
shaved ice for the staffs.
[He came to spend again.]
Don't use it just to be funny!
[He provokes the other team.]
I'm getting angry!
[And cheats.]
[Ddakji blowing technique]
[I will take over this
race with my tricks!]
[Kim Gun Mo]
[Million Seller Race]
[Million Seller race: Get a total of
10 million albums to win.]
The mission you will do first is
'Relay the song with the citizen.'
[He daringly tries the
relay with a foreigner.]
Hello, I'm alive and well!
[He's funny!]
[The battle between
the most popular songs!]
[What's the result
of the first mission?]
[6.8 million vs. 4.69 million]
Both teams had 13 people.
You have two chances.
[If a citizen sings a
million seller's song]
[that team can win
500,000 discs upfront.]
The second chance is
'I miss you, my friend.'
[The top album sales of
the invited singer will be added.]
Hey, don't come!
Don't come!
[I will not cast you!]
This is worth 500,000 discs!
[During the classic zero game]
[the red team wins 500,000 discs
because of Kwang Soo's misfortune.]
[Ddakji Othello round one:
Suk Jin vs. Jun Yup.]
[He hit his own team's ddakji!]
Hit the red ones!
[the red team wins 500,000 discs thanks
to Big-nose's spy-like activity.]
[I don't know what's
wrong with me, either...]
[Round two: Ha Ha vs. Gary]
[Their pride depends on this!]
[Ha Ha wins and
earns 500,000 CDs.]
It's the most frustrating
losing to him!
[6.4 million vs. 4.29 million]
[The blue team is leading.]
[Who will be the final winner?]
[An intense match for 10 million CDs!]
[A continuous twist!]
[The winner isn't determined yet!]
I have a cramp!
[Which team will get 10 million first?]
[And...]
He came!
[Finally, the red team's
reliever has arrived!]
[What's this man's identity?]
[Million Seller race, episode two.]
[At that moment, in Shinchon...]
[The capsule noraebang is thriving.]
[If a citizen sings a star's song,
that team can win 500,000 discs.]
[They're still having a heated battle
over at Sevit Island.]
Now, the score is 1:1.
This will be the runoff!
[Kkuk, the ddakji monster vs.
Jae Suk, the ddakji king.]
[Let's put an end to this today.]
This is the finals.
Start!
- Why are you so fast?
- Take it slow.
[Slap, slap!]
[Since they're experienced,
their aim is precise!]
- Wow!
- That's good!
[Jae Suk's flipping at
the speed of light.]
[Kkuk, what are you doing?]
Hit it harder!
[Are they glued on the floor?
Why won't it flip?]
Why can't you flip?
Go away!
Where did my flipper go?
[While Jae Suk gets his ddakji]
[Kkuk is still struggling.]
What are you doing?
[On the contrary,
Jae Suk's skill is very efficient.]
[Time's up.]
[Yoo Jae Suk wins a complete
victory at Ddakji Othello.]
[Is he a pro ddakji player?]
- You can't do this?
- It worked at first...
Here's 500,000 for the red team!
500,000!
[The red team got 500,000 CDs.]
We should have a round
betting on 2 million CDs!
[This isn't just a flip.]
[It's a flip out.]
Okay, now we'll pick a number.
[Just then, the alarm went off.]
Someone's singing!
- They picked a song!
- Please, please!
[Someone picked a million seller's song!]
[That singer's team will
automatically get 500,000 CDs!]
[Will the red team
continue their upturn?]
[Or will they be in disappointment?]
[Who is the owner of the melody
that spread in Shinchon?]
['One Candle' by g.o.d.]
[Oh, yeah!]
Don't lower your head,
don't lose strength
[The blue team is devastated.]
Lean on me when
you're tired and exhausted.
I will always be by your side.
[The red team's sweeping upturn!]
So that you never feel like
you're alone in this world.
[Even the blue team
is singing together.]
[6.4 million vs. 4.79 million]
[The red team is catching up!]
It's 'Pop-up Pirate'!
The one you push swords in?
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
are bad at this!
[Both teams take turns inserting the
swords until the pirate pops out.]
[The team that makes
the pirate pop out loses.]
[I'm not really good at this.]
[Just then...]
[Oh, my!]
[That person is?]
The second chance is
'I miss you, my friend.'
From now on, you can call
one singer friend.
If the singer completes
the mission with you
the top album sales of
the singer will be added.
Hello.
I'm filming 'Running Man.'
You need to come here.
Just for 30 minutes.
Come quickly!
[They succeeded right away,
and waited...]
He's here!
[The red team's guest singer!]
[Who will be the legend
that will flip the game results?]
[Kim Chang Ryul from DJ DOC.]
Kim Chang Ryul!
[He's a little confused,
but he greets everyone first.]
Doesn't he match with our clothing?
[He looks like a part
of the blue team.]
He wore his own clothes,
but they're that color?
I came because Jae Hoon called.
[Confused]
Chang Ryul is super busy, but he came.
[Thank you for coming
even though it was abrupt.]
- We're neighbors.
- Oh, really?
So, Chang Ryul us and play this game?
There is a separate
game he will challenge.
What if they fail that game?
- If they fail, it's over?
- They won't get any?
[They're explaining the rules now.]
You can flip the result?
[That's how it is.]
The mission you will be doing
is group jump roping.
Now that you have seven members,
two people turn the rope
and everyone will jump in one by one,
and when all five have jumped in
you will need to jump
ten times together.
You have three tries.
- If we lose... Ji Hyo jump in last.
- Let her turn the rope.
[1.95 million album count
depends on this game.]
[Pressure!]
- Chang Ryul, we believe in you!
- Yes, of course!
I've never played jump rope before.
How about we sing the
song in an irregular rhythm?
[You're a genius...]
[They're already making a plan.]
[The tricky brothers are on the move.]
[What the heck?]
[Are you guys ready to jump?]
[Group jump rope, round one start!]
[Perfectly off-beat]
[But Jae Hoon manages to jump in.]
[Next up is Chang Ryul.]
No, no!
[They failed their first try.]
[They succeeded with their plan.]
The beat was...
[What are you doing?]
[You did it!]
[Feeling wronged.]
[He makes a normal person into a
person who has no sense of rhythm.]
There were no physical collision,
so it does not count as cheating.
[Group jump rope, round two start!]
[The magical melody starts again...]
One, two, three!
[He even changed the song.]
[The song keeps changing
and they're off-beat.]
[This is driving us crazy.]
Don't get tricked by the sound.
[They can't even begin to jump in.]
Boom, boom, boom!
[He's counting the rhythm.]
[Oh, you're counting?]
[He changes the song again,
with a faster one.]
[The first runner up,
Jae Hoon jumps in.]
[They turn the rope
faster with the melody.]
[Caught]
[Chang Ryul fails.]
[What do I do?]
[Their plan succeeds, once again.]
[Bravo, Tricky Brother!]
It's more difficult to be wrong.
[He's a sinner for getting
caught in the rope once.]
Can Joo Hwan go instead?
[Chang Ryul came with
his son, Joo Hwan.]
This is the last try!
We have to focus.
We just need to jump ten times.
But on the last one,
we need to jump high.
[And another man is also
preparing the last battle.]
This time, it's a guitar.
[Group jump rope, round three start!]
[Now, he brings a guitar
in case they're used to the pattern.]
[The red team's last attempt.]
[Jae Hoon's stable entry.]
[Chang Ryul succeeds
at jumping in, too.]
Don't listen to them!
[Blank Ji's in!]
[Followed by Jun Yup!]
[Everyone, including bro Jun is in!]
[They just need to get 10 and
they will get 1.95 million!]
[Oh no... oh no... oh no!]
[They start counting!]
Four, five, six!
[Perfect synchronization!]
Five, six, seven, eight
nine!
[They got nine in a flash!]
[Just one more!]
[If we jump one more,
we'll get 1.95 million!]
Ten!
Eight, nine, ten!
[The red team succeeded
and earned 1.95 million!]
[We did it!]
[Their sense of rhythm overpowered
the tricky brothers!]
[The red team's superhero, Chang Ryul!]
[Chang Ryul... are you happy?]
Finally, we've reversed the score!
[6.4 million vs. 7.24 million]
[Thanks to Chang Ryul!]
Chang Ryul, we reversed the
score thanks to you!
I... I'm glad we won but...
If you're done, leave!
[Son, let's go...]
[He guiltily leaves in a hurry.]
- Bye!
- See you!
[The alarm is going off again!]
[Another million seller's
song is played!]
[Who's song is it, this time?]
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce!
['Run To You' by DJ DOC.]
[He's happy in a flash.]
[That's our song!]
What's going on?
They're singing right now in Shinchon.
[He's glad to see
his fans unexpectedly.]
[Thank you!]
If they sing your song,
does that team get CDs?
[Yes, 500,000 CDs.]
[Joo Hwan is shopping
at the snack bar.]
- Here, have this.
- You can hang it around your neck.
It's the best!
[They spend 300,000 CDs
for Chang Ryul's son.]
[Because of this gift, both teams
have a similar amount of CDs.]
- Thanks, Joo Hwan.
- Bye!
[Chang Ryul leaves after
reversing the scores.]
So now, this game
depends on 800,000 CDs!
The entire team has to take turns.
You have to insert the swords.
If the pirate pops up, that team loses.
- Single round?
It's a single-round match!
We're at a disadvantage!
No, people with bad
luck go to the end.
[The Goddess of fortune,
Blank Ji will go first!]
Before, I was the first runner,
and it popped up on my first try.
If the pirate pops up,
that team loses.
I hope it pops up now
and the game ends.
[Big Nose gets everyone
to have high expectations.]
I want to see it pops, too.
You lose this, and you'll fail the
jump rope game with Sung Soo.
[In other words,
I wish you guys would lose.]
[They start the game,
hoping for a dramatic scene.]
- Suk Jin, you go first.
- I have a bad feeling.
I'll do it in one shot!
He's so confident!
[He survived!]
- Yeah!
- Now, Ji Hyo.
[The icon of luck, Blank Ji.]
[Passed safely]
[Lucky Blank Ji!]
- Now, Kwang Soo.
- Unlucky!
- Don't call me that!
[Fixed stare]
Prove that you're not unlucky.
Okay!
[Kwang Soo passed safely, too.]
Next is Jun Yup.
[Let's see...]
- You can't tell by looking.
- You two look alike!
They do!
[Please don't pop out this round!]
[Push]
[Jun Yup passed.]
[The third player is Ha Neul!]
He is Mapo-go's unluckiest man.
He used to be Incheon's unluckiest man!
[He's from the national constituency.]
You conquered Inchon.
He's the country's unluckiest man.
He's the leader of
the unlucky association.
No way, no way.
[No way...]
[Pop!]
[I am a legend.]
[The country's unluckiest man
Ha Neul failed.]
[Today is a lucky for the red team.]
- Unlucky, unlucky!
- I can't believe it!
[Oh, lord, why did you
give me these hands?]
[6.9 million vs. 7.74 million]
This is Suk Jin's, and
this is Kwang Soo's.
[Theirs are all close to the pop.]
You guys are amazing.
[The X-Men trio!]
That's incredible!
[The alarm is going off!]
[Someone's singing
in Shinchon, again!]
[This time, who's song is it?]
['The Moon of Seoul' by Kim Gun Mo.]
[Hoorah!]
[The blue team gets 500,000!]
She sings really well!
[Her singing skills are amazing!]
[Currently, dual live broadcasting.]
She sings really well!
[Everyone is surprised
at her talent.]
[Gaze]
[He stared for a long while]
[at the lady who was
singing his song...]
[A sweet melody flowing
under the moon of Seoul.]
[Meanwhile, the same
time at Sevit Island.]
[Someone is approaching
with energetic footsteps.]
[One, two, one, two]
[He warms up, and even
fixes his shoes laces.]
[Who is this determined person?]
[Kim Sung Soo from Cool.]
[Even with the abrupt call,
he came in a heartbeat.]
[It's a party time during break!]
['Before Sadness Comes' by Cool.]
[It's our song!]
[No hesitation, he walks in right away.]
[He's already in the mood.]
[Huh? This person is?]
[Casually]
[Wow, it's Kim Sung Soo!]
[The blue team's guest is here!]
[If the blue team succeeds,
they get 1.07 million!]
[Confused]
You're on our team!
[What kind of situation is this?]
Save your energy.
You need to jump.
You need to jump rope!
[What? Jump rope?]
If you win with Sung Soo,
and someone sings in Shinchon, it's over.
Sung Soo needs to do well.
It's group jump rope.
- Practice game?
- Sung Soo needs a practice game.
Jong Kook, I need to do it.
- Now.
- Go slowly.
[Oh my god!]
[Big accident!]
[Why did it get caught there...]
[Emergency treatment]
[Dizzy, dizzy]
[Group jump rope, round one starts!]
Challenge!
[First up is Sung Soo.]
- Slowly.
- Go in!
[Huh?]
[Hop, hop]
[What kind of a hopping was that?]
[Sung Soo is really bad!]
[The blue team fails their first try.]
[It doesn't work
like the way I do.]
[It's not over yet!
Group jump rope round two, starts!]
[First runner up is quick-paced Ha Ha.]
[He jumps in, in a flash.]
[Mr. Capable follows in, safely.]
Slowly.
- Slowly.
- Ha Neul wanted to make it harder.
[Gun Mo is counting out loud.]
[Ha Neul passed safely
with Gun Mo's shout.]
[Everyone, follow me.]
[Why are they so good
all of a sudden?]
[Kwang Soo jumps in safely, as well.]
[Now, only Sung Soo is left!]
[I'll take no more humiliation!]
[Now's the time!]
[Oh!]
[He fails as soon as he gets in.]
[Is he a relief pitcher, or an X-Man?]
We're good, we're good!
For a second, I thought you
just brought a citizen.
[I've never felt this much pressure.]
This is the last chance!
Challenge!
[This is the last chance
to get 1.07 million!]
[Mr. Capable is up first.]
[Lightly, lightly]
[Ha Neul jumps in next.]
[Ha Neul also succeeds.]
[The problem is Sung Soo!]
[Will Sung Soo be able to
save the last chance?]
[He succeeded!]
[Ha Ha also succeeded.]
[Flinch, flinch]
[Kwang Soo also passed safely!]
[They just need to jump ten times.]
[Sung Soo, where are you going?]
[He broke away from the line.]
[Caught]
[Sung Soo is the only one out.]
[They failed their last try.]
[What on earth happened?]
Why did you go out?
[Goodbye, 1.07 million CDs!]
- I went in!
- You can go now.
[Sung Soo, you're the best!]
Did you come to
sightseeing at the Han River?
'Running Man' doesn't suit me.
Please give him a round of applause!
[Let's do well next time!]
Thank you!
[Coming soon...]
['Running Man' five year anniversary,
part two.]
[A loyalty game, never before seen.]
[Running Man vs VJ,
a brutal test of loyalty.]
[This is hell!]
[Coming soon!]
[Currently, in Shinchon.]
['Excuse' by Kim Gun Mo.]
[8.3 million]
['Sorrow Thoughts' by Cool.]
[8.8 million vs. 9.24 million]
['Wrongful Encounter' by Kim Gun Mo.]
[9.3 million vs. 9.24 million]
- Let's go with seven!
- Let's pick seven.
Seven!
Move the CDs with your feet.
What?
Do you move it with your feet?
Each team lies down
on the mat in a line.
And then the first
person has to grab CDs
with their feet
and pass it over their head.
The last person needs to put the
CD in the basket above the head.
You'll get the number of CDs in
the basket times 100,000.
Both teams could surpass
10 million with this game.
If that's the case, the team with
the highest number will win.
- Who's going first?
- We'll go first!
[The time limit is one minute.]
Ready, go!
Stay calm, stay calm.
Don't be too calm!
[Flexible Blank Ji gave it
to Jun Yup in one try.]
Wait until the next person says okay!
[There isn't one easy game!]
[Jun Yup hands it over to Jun Hyung.]
Not yet!
Okay!
Gary, keep going!
[Perfect rhythm]
[Please, hurry up!]
Wow, they're fast!
Wait, wait, wait, okay!
I'm too far from the basket!
[Now he just has to
put it in the basket.]
[Basket, where are you?]
[Gun Mo's helping hand.]
Jae Hoon, did you get them in?
It's a lot!
[They got a lot in.]
Did they go in?
[The CD relay continues.]
I'm getting a cramp in my toe!
- Give it to me!
- Here!
Gary, wait!
Give me more!
[Their passing speed
is getting faster!]
[They just got the hang of it,
but time's up!]
[Only if they got that in...]
[It was right in front of
the basket, too.]
How many are there?
I will count them!
One
two
three, four
five, six, seven, eight.
- We surpassed!
- Nine, ten.
[The counting doesn't end.]
18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23.
[The red team got 23 CDs!]
[One CD is equivalent to
100,000 times 23 CDs.]
[The red team got
a total of 2.3 million!]
[They have to get 23 or
more to surpass them.]
[But, just then!]
[The alarm is going off once again!]
[The noraebang chance
continues until the end!]
[The blue team has their
final mission left.]
[Who will receive
the 500,000 CDs?]
[Isn't the song...]
[Kim Gun Mo's 'Beautiful Goodbye.']
That's Gun Mo's song!
[Absolute winner of the
noraebang chance, Kim Gun Mo.]
[The red team is suddenly nervous.]
We're going to win the race!
- Don't push it too hard.
- Just be safe and do it slowly.
- If someone sings another song...
- We just need to move 18 CDs!
This is the end.
[9.8 million vs. 11.54 million]
Keep doing the mission even If
someone else sings one of your songs.
[The blue team's practice.]
Try reach my feet.
It's easier to grab them like this.
[Embarrassing]
He had poop feet!
[He has cack-handed and cack-footed?]
We're going to get in trouble
because of Kwang Soo.
I think I'm not good at it.
[Yes, Kwang Soo gives us hope...]
- Grab it like this.
- With the soles of my feet?
Try clapping!
Yes, with the soles of your feet.
[Like this?]
He moved his feet like this.
It'll be hard if you do that.
Do you have a cramp, Kwang Soo?
I really have a cramp!
Look how weird my toes are!
[He has all kind of reasons...]
He really has a cramp.
We need to massage them.
- This is serious!
- Massage them.
- My toes look so weird!
- You need to massage them!
- We need to pull the leg.
- Stretch your leg.
You need to exercise more!
Let's hurry up!
People might sing their song.
We need to finish it
before that happens.
Just take a little at a time!
[Move the CDs, starts!]
No, take a lot!
- We can move ten CDs twice.
- No.
I'll just take this much.
That looks good!
Just pass it along.
Just pass it right away!
[Kwang Soo passes them
to Ha Ha right away.]
[Ha Ha passes them
to Suck Jin quickly.]
[Risky]
Wow!
[The blue team's speedy technique.]
[Shake, shake]
- Let them go!
- It's so tight!
[They only dropped one CD.]
[That's not good for us...]
This time, it's a lot!
If they succeed at it this time,
they'll win the race!
[Oh, no!]
[Slips]
[We can't turn the table,
if I drop them!]
[He dropped on CD
and survived the crisis.]
[It's a speedy relay again.]
That's great!
He's biting my feet!
Close your heel!
[That was a lot!]
[They're moving the CDs the third time.]
Slowly!
Time's up!
- Time's up.
- That looks like a near thing.
We'll count them now.
One, two, three, four, five.
- It has to be 18 CDs, right?
- Six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
[I know we have more than that.]
- One, two...
- It'll be the same if we have eight.
- Don't hide any of it.
- I won't.
- Four!
- Film it from behind.
They're leaving, too!
[The nostalgic noraebang is empty now.]
[Now, it depends on the CD count!]
[The blue team will win,
if they have more than 19 CDs.]
- Eight.
- Now, we're tied.
[If he has at least one CD,
the blue team will win.]
[Does he have more CDs?]
Nine!
[He has more!]
Ten, eleven!
[The blue team wins
the Million Seller Race!]
[12 million vs. 11.54 million]
[The red team loses
by a narrow margin.]
If we had one more song,
we would have...
Yes, the song from the noraebang
made us win!
We'll reward the blue team
with golden discs.
Thank you!
Don't cry!
Take this!
[Only the winners
get the golden trophies.]
Therefore, today's
winner is the blue team!
Is that real gold?
- I didn't think I would work this hard.
- You did your best.
- You really did your best!
- You're normally not like this.
I'm very competitive,
but we did our best, too.
Even though we lost,
I'm still glad and happy.
That's right.
We also want to thank Kim Sung Soo
and Kim Chang Ryul
and the citizens who sang
at the nostalgic noraebang
and the citizens we
met in Apgujung-dong.
Thank you so much!
[Thank you very much!]
Thank you, everyone!
- Let's take a picture!
- Take two pictures!
Let's take a picture together!
[Through the night, the party continued.]
[A few days later...]
- It's the fifth anniversary party!
- It's the fifth anniversary.
This is only the beginning!
- What's this?
- It's the fifth anniversary party.
- There's a viking ship, too!
- The anniversary party?
A viking ship!
There's candy draw, too!
What's that?
Congratulations on
the anniversary party!
Thank you!
[Running Man Night Festival]
- Look at this!
- Thank you!
To celebrate Running Man's
fifth anniversary
we rented a school park and
set up a night market.
Think of it as a festival
and enjoy it.
[Really?]
Are you sure?
You've never been nice.
What's the matter?
Are you going to pay for us?
I don't have money.
[Don't worry about it.
It's on house!]
[This is so rare.]
Oh, I picked a dud!
- Oh, no, I picked 18!
- 31! I picked a butterfly!
- I won the butterfly!
- 18 was nothing.
[Mr. Random Capable won
a giant butterfly candy.]
Oh, no.
Number 18...
Oh, you put some ice cream there?
Thank you so much!
It looks good.
[Crunch]
[Sweet flavor!]
- I want to get one of this.
- Is that a squid?
- Is it free?
- It's deep fried squid!
I've never seen it before.
Wow!
[Laugh]
- Try it.
- Thank you!
[Blank Ji takes a bite.]
Isn't it amazing?
Gary!
[This is from my heart.]
Wow, I didn't expect it here.
[The fifth year anniversary is love.]
It's a heart!
Try this.
[Kkuk Thor is playing
with the hammer.]
[The highest score is 943.]
[What will be Jong Kook's score?]
[That was close!]
[Yoo-ames Bond is busy shooting.]
This is scary!
[Gary is riding
the viking ship by himself.]
When is it going to end?
[Kkuk and Blank Ji are horse racing.]
At this time of the day...
They're rewarding us
for the fifth year anniversary.
[The pirate ship is going to leave!]
[Scared]
My tummy is ticklish.
[That must be scary.]
Please, make it higher!
[The taste of hell]
They must be regretting taht.
[Noisy]
[The Running Men had no idea]
[about what would happen next.]
- Thank you!
- I won this!
- Wow, that sword?
- Yes, it's the dragon sword.
- How did you get this one?
- That's what I'm saying.
[Someone is approaching.]
- Oh, for Jae Suk's birthday?
- Ji Hyo, too.
Jae Suk's birthday is August 14,
Blank Ji is the 15th.
Ha Ha's birthday is 20th.
We have lots to celebrate!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Jae Suk,
Ji Hyo, and Ha Ha.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you!
[Blow out]
Even birthday party?
Something's wrong.
[A dark change]
[A sudden change...]
[What's happening?]
[What's the building
behind the market?]
The night market is over.
For the next event,
we'll go behind the market.
- All of a sudden?
- What's this?
Why did you stop it like this?
- Look, I see the red light!
- Why red?
What kind of a party
ends like this?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Wouldn't a scary story
be perfect for this place?
- What's wrong with the lighting?
- Are there people inside?
What are you talking about?
- Don't talk nonsense!
- I'm scared, Kwang Soo!
That school looks like
it's closed down.
The place you were
having fun a minute ago
was a girls' high school
that was established in 1934.
A girls' high school?
Yes, it's so-called
'Closed girls' high school.
It was a girls' high school.
The real mission you
need to carry out today is.
'The horrifying loyalty
test with the staff.'
Two 'Running Man' members
and the VJs in charge of the members
will enter inside the abolished school.
You don't have your name tags
on your back..
You need to get inside
and find your name tag.
Then, you can go home.
Isn't that simple?
- Go straight home.
- It's driving me crazy.
Inside, not just the member's name tags
but also the name tags
for the VJs who's been
working with you for
the past five years.
You can find all the name tags together
and escape together and stay loyal.
Find them?
Or you can escape as soon as
finding your own name tag.
What if the VJ finds it first?
The VJ can pass the camera
and go home.
[This is a good time to test
their friendship.]
We're going to attach
heart rate monitors on VJs.
The VJ with the highest number
will be the first one to enter.
And the first team and decide
who they'll go together.
That means, just one pair
will enter in the end.
[Scream]
No way!
I can't do that!
[Shocked]
- Stop it!
- Don't do things like this!
- He's really...
- Stop it!
I almost hit you!
If anyone goes with Ji Hyo,
we'll faint when we see her.
She debuted in
'Whispering Corridors.'
Toshio!
(A character from 'The Grudge.')
[A mass exodus]
You scared me!
[What's wrong with her?]
- This drives me crazy!
- What's with your voice?
- Was that your voice?
- What's wrong with you?
- That's how you say it!
- You scared me!
I'm scared, too.
The way I see...
[Scared]
It's just grass!
I think I'm going to be
more scared because of you!
[The ankle grab]
[Scream]
[A good example of
'being frightened.']
[He's nose is big, but his
nerves are the size of a micrometer.]
[He would have fainted
if he did it inside the school.]
One of the VJs heart rate was 80
when we arrived here.
Now, it went up to 126.
- It's Gwon Yeol.
- Yes, It's Ryu Gwon Yeol.
I told you.
He looks terrified.
- His heart rate is still going up.
- It's 130.
Don't you need to
go to the hospital?
Do you have heart problems?
The first 'Running Man' member
will be Yoo Jae Suk.
And Ryu Gwon Yeol will be going.
So, you can name the person
that will go with you.
I'll take someone weak.
Ji Suk Jin, Lee Kwang Soo,
or Ha Ha...
I'd like to go at first.
- They're all cowards.
- I don't want to be the last.
- I can't get in by myself.
- You're begging to get in first?
I'll stay until you find your
name tag even if I find mine first.
I'm not going to find my name tag.
I'll hide my name tag,
if I find it first.
What are you talking about?
- Why are you lying?
- You're talking nonsense!
[Kwang Soo is excluded.]
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Winner or loser?
- The one throws the same thing as me.
Just give me a chance!
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Big-nose: Scissors,
Jae Suk and Ha Ha: Paper]
Didn't you throw the same thing as me?
I thought he threw scissors.
[Jae Suk and Ha Ha are the first.]
[The members and VJs have
worked together for five years.]
[Their test of loyalty
is about to begin!]
[How strong their
friendship will be...]
[when they're placed in an
extreme situation?]
[We're going to find out.]
Four of you, go!
Promise me!
[Jae Suk and Gwon Yeol]
[Ha Ha and Sung Yong]
Gwon Yeol, let's go.
- Fight!
- I'll be back, Suk Jin!
- Oh, I won't be back.
- Right, goodbye!
[As soon as they find their own
name tags, anyone can go home.]
This is insane.
[The horrifying test of loyalty begins!]
The atmosphere is too scary!
I'm scared of grass
more than anything.
[Thump, thump]
Gwon Yeol!
Why are you keeping a distance?
I really don't want to go inside.
I'm going crazy.
I'm such a coward
and I hate it.
- What if we actually see a ghost?
- We'll go mad.
You scared me!
Don't kick things like this!
[Even before they get to the entrance,
they start making a fuss.]
I don't think I can go, either.
He's going to run
away before I will.
What a shame, both of you!
You stepped on a bone, Gwon Yeol.
[Gasp]
[He runs a mile away from it.]
What are you doing, Gwon Yeol?
He gets scared the most!
- Oh!
- What is it?
What's this?
What's on my shoulder?
Something dropped on my shoulder.
I felt something on my shoulder.
- There's nothing, Jae Suk!
- Something hit my shoulder.
It felt like a stone.
Isn't that more scary though?
In the middle of night,
who would throw something?
Can you tell them by radio?
I don't think we can do it.
If you're going to keep acting
like this, switch with Suk Jin.
This won't do.
- We can't move forward.
- Okay, I'll do it.
Hurry up.
Ha Ha, come here.
We can't escape it
if we just stand here.
[It looks mysterious
from the entrance.]
Should I really enter this school?
This drives me crazy.
[I miss my mommy...]
[Squeak]
[Why does the gate sound so scary?]
Is there any other way, Jae Suk?
[They open the gate.]
I saw it!
- You scared me!
- You're supposed to film me!
Gwon Yeol, you need to
go first and film me!
Aren't VJs supposed to do that?
Both of you need to
go first and film us.
- He drives me crazy.
- Where is this water flowing from?
Look, there's a mirror!
- How do they expect us to do this?
- Didn't you hear the music?
This is crazy!
How are we going to do this?
How can we search two floors?
Jae Suk, try covering
one of your eyes.
It feels a lot better!
Go this way, I'll go that way.
Let me know if you find my name tag!
I feel like I want to fart.
- Did you hear that?
- I heard it.
[Piano sound?]
It's girl's voice.
[It's hair-raising!]
- What's that?
- What was that?
Stop getting frightened!
[Grasshopper moves little by little.]
Honestly, isn't this too scary?
Why did they have to play the piano?
[There's a bathroom!]
[A lot of ghost stories in school
happen in the bathroom.]
[Maybe there's a name tag
in the bathroom.]
Gwon Yeol, you need to come in.
You need to film it here.
[Spooky]
[Surprised]
- This drives me nuts.
- What's going on?
[He found something!]
[Thump, thump]
This is place is bad.
There's poop.
[He found a suspicious room.]
[Glance]
I guess we're supposed to open it.
Look, there's an 'R sticker!'
- Should we open it?
- Scream and open it.
[Will there be someone's
name tag inside?]
[Scream]
What?
[In her arms...]
[she's holding a
suspicious clutch bag.]
Seriously!
[Let me see your bag.]
It's not going to move, right?
Something should be inside.
[Punch]
[He collects the
suspicious looking thing.]
What's this?
[Haroro collects the angel stone.]
[And he finds a flash light
inside the stone.]
We need to search places like this.
[There might be a name tag
inside one of the lockers.]
[Scream]
[Dud!
See you next time...]
[Aaaaaah!]
[I want to go home...]
We were scared of mannequins!
What's that?
What is it?
[Give me your legs!]
[Runs away]
Seriously!
[This is tiring...]
Where is the name tag?
Look at the hallway.
[How can a human
walk around this hallway?]
I'm going to go crazy...
That scared me!
You're not going to leave me
when you find your name tag, right?
[Are you talking about friendship now?]
Gwon Yeol, you haven't entered
any of these rooms first.
You always tell me to wait
until you get a good spot.
Why aren't you doing that here?
[What is this room?]
- Something's in there.
- Someone's in there.
[There's a mannequin here, too.]
[Surprised]
[They've opened the dance studio
that they shouldn't have.]
It's horrifying!
[The student shows up and dances
even after the school was abandoned...]
Why are you doing this?
Aren't you scared in here?
[Turns]
[Wimpy]
Gwon Yeol!
Where are you going?
Let me search here,
I need to find the name tags.
[Startled]
[She's coming!]
[Run for your life!]
[A ghost appears!]
[Oh my god!]
[What's that?]
[Trips]
Gwon Yeol!
[Is this slapstick comedy?]
Are you okay, Jae Suk?
What are you...
Seriously, what are you doing?
Are you okay?
Your ankle...
Do you know how many times
you stepped on me?
[The second floor is even scarier.]
This is unbelievable!
[Laugh]
Wasn't that Gwon Yeol's voice?
- Yes, it was.
- That was too...
There was a little boy
in Seorae village.
A ghost?
That little boy walked to Dong Hoon...
and told him to move
as soon as possible.
[Shudder]
I almost swore at you
with unspeakable words!
I saw his mouth!
The words I've never
spoke in my life...
Doesn't Ji Hyo look lively
ever since we came here?
Why did they scream?
What could it be?
[He's swearing out of fear.]
[Making spiteful remarks]
[If Ha Ha gets scared,
he becomes a master of the censor.]
Ha Ha.
[There's something inside
the mourning clothes.]
[Ryu Gwon Yeol]
[I found it!]
[Ha Ha finds Jae Suk's VJ's name tag.]
[He hides it in his back pocket.]
We'll escape together.
[Jae Suk's team is searching
in the candle room.]
By any chance, have you
seen any name tags...
[He has something.]
I'm sorry, but I need to escape.
[He finds Ha Ha's VJ's name tag.]
- Isn't Sung Yong Ha Ha's manager?
- Ha Ha's VJ.
[They both found VJs' name tags.]
We need to find our name tags.
[Jae Suk Joins in the
classroom full of ghosts.]
What's that?
You know what?
I found Sung Yong's.
What did you find?
- I found Gwon Yeol's.
- Let's trade.
What are you doing?
Don't I get to keep that?
That's mine.
Then, you're going to escape.
Let's just keep it for each other.
Let's trade when we find our name tags.
I'm sure he's going to leave me.
Wait a little, Sung Yong.
Come inside, Gwon Yeol!
[It's spooky here, too.]
Aren't they scared?
[Hesitates]
[Chaos!]
[Scream]
[It's a visiting service.]
Save me!
- This is hell!
- Get in!
There's no name tags here.
- Is this yours?
- I found it!
[Jae Suk found his own name tag.]
Let's get out of here.
We just need to get yours.
- Ha Ha has it.
- What should we do?
When you're feeling no fear...
I couldn't come here before.
[What's this place for?]
[Oh my god!]
Nothing can scare me any longer!
Where's Gwon Yeol's?
I want to give it to him.
[Jae Suk and Ha Ha trade their VJs'.]
Don't leave Ha Ha.
Let me keep it myself.
I won't escape without you.
I don't want to give you.
Where did you put it?
[Gwon Yeol already put it on his back.]
I'll give it to you later.
I'm sorry.
You've worked so hard.
Let me put it on you.
Let's get out of here.
[The two men who
were loyal to each other.]
[Jae Suk and Gwon Yeol
cleared the mission.]
[It's time to go home.]
That was really scary.
[When will they come back?]
Aren't they mime artists?
- He scared me!
- It's Jae Suk.
Jae Suk escaped.
Did you find your name tag?
- Gwon Yeol found his, too.
- They got out together.
How was it, Jae Suk?
Why do you look absent-minded?
He's thinner.
- How was it?
- It's the hell.
- It's that scary?
- What about Ha Ha?
Ha Ha's still there?
- Your name tag is...
- Gwon Yeol has it on the front.
He's the worst!
I'm not going to say it, but...
he fell over me.
Gwon Yeol.
Yoon Sang's child was born just now.
You need to go one more time.
- He cried just now.
- Really?
- His baby is just born.
- Congratulations, Yoon Sang!
- Seriously?
- He was almost crying.
Wouldn't Gwon Yeol go there again?
The baby cried bravely
so Daddy need to
go in and cry as well.
[How will the baby's daddy,
Yoon Sang's loyalty be?]
[Kwang Soo and Yoon Sang]
[Jong Kook and Ki Jin]
[How will Giraffe and Mr. Capable's
friendship with their VJs be?]
- When VJs run, together we can...
- I really don't want to do this.
There's something in front of the gate,
like Jae Suk said.
[Ha Ha is still looking
for his name tag.]
[He opens a locker.]
[Scream]
Get out of the way!
[Ha Ha acquires his name tag.]
[Ha Ha successfully
acquires his name tag.]
Let's go, Sung Yong!
[Shocked]
[Spring at him all of a sudden]
[Ha Ha and Sung Yong finally escape.]
- You've worked so hard!
- Ha Ha, how was it?
- You can't tell them all.
I'm sorry.
They can't show what I've done.
They can't broadcast it.
I swore so much.
Sung Yong swore a lot, too.
- You're getting old.
- Touch me, it's cold like ice.
Sung Yong's heart rate reached 130.
Maybe you're possessed.
[My heart isn't working properly.]
[While Kkuk was
looking for his name tag...]
There's an 'R sticker.'
Come in, what are you doing?
You need to come in.
- I can see it from here.
- You need to come!
The VJ should come closer.
Argh!
[Kkuk acquires the angel stone.]
[He gets a flash light.]
There's nothing here.
There's really nothing.
What's that?
Why would boxes be here?
[Peek-a-boo!]
[Frightened!]
[Even the VJ was frightened.]
Aaaah!
Aaw!
[Shocked]
[shocked]
[and shocked!]
[He has a heart as weak as glass
but he has a strong voice.]
[The school park is filled with
Kwang Soo's voice.]
VJ came out first!
- Who's that?
- That's Ki Jin!
Ki Jin escaped?
Did you give your
camera to Jong Kook?
Yes.
Wow, he's shameless.
[Ki Jin found his name tag
before Jong Kook's.]
Let it go, Ki Jin!
[Kkuk and his VJ was bickering.]
I wanted to come inside this room!
Then, I'll keep it for now.
I need to go to bathroom.
[But he ran away.]
[A VJ gave up on his camera
and escaped.]
I'll go home then.
- He's cruel.
- He doesn't have a friendship.
- Jong Kook didn't find his yet?
- No.
Kim Ki Jin, you can go home.
[Will he really leave?]
Are you leaving?
Wow, he's leaving!
People are merciless!
[VJ Kkuk is recording
the scary ballerina.]
[He carries around
the camera that his VJ left.]
I'm sorry, I need to find something...
[He's scared to death.]
[He said he was scared,
but he was shaking with his camera.]
I'm sorry.
My life depends on this.
[He found Kwang Soo's name tag.]
Kwang Soo is coming soon.
Please be harsh on him.
[Brother Kkuk is very thoughtful.]
- They come out at a place like this.
- Please!
I'm in a dangerous state.
I'm not afraid,
I'm just worried about you.
[Flinch]
What?
Please don't do stuff like that.
[Kwang Soo plucks up the courage
and starts searching.]
[He found Yoon Sang's name tag.]
I won't give it to you!
Just show it to me.
[He puts it inside his pocket.]
I see.
If you found it before me...
Let's get out of here first.
This room looks too scary.
We can't go in here,
they wouldn't have hid it here.
- Don't go in.
- We need to find it.
[The room full of unmarried ghosts.]
- They might all stand up at once.
- They're mannequins.
Wait, they might get up.
Let's get out!
[Kwang Soo couldn't
find his name tag yet.]
Do you even need
to check the desks?
[VJ Yoon Sang starts babbling
since he just became a dad.]
Let's do it together.
[Is he going to check all the desks?]
[Gets up!]
[This is my desk, Kwang Soo...]
[VJ Yoon Sang is just looking at it.]
How can a person stay still like this?
[Good students study
without moving their bodies...]
Let me just checked this one.
Thank you for your work.
[He found something!]
[He found Kkuk's name tag!]
Let's make a deal.
Take that and give mine to me.
This is a gift for you.
[Kwang Soo gives
Yoon Sang his name tag.]
[They can go home together.]
Gary, please decide who
you want to go with.
It might be funny
if Ji Hyo goes in by herself.
I'm going to put this
plastic finger from behind.
- It's the person that will go?
- Yes.
Please, hold this finger.
If Monday Couple go together,
it'll be boring.
Gary!
Please, save me once!
Gary, help me once!
I'm going crazy!
[Monday Couple, Ji Hyo?]
[Friendship between guys, Suk Jin?]
Oh, yeah!
[Seriously...]
[Gary chose Monday Couple, Ji Hyo.]
Ji Hyo!
[Big-nosed brother will
have to enter by himself.]
It's not even funny, Ji Hyo.
[As soon as they enter,
it's full of spooky air.]
Where do we need to go first?
[Will Monday Couple be
able to do it together?]
Let me wait downstairs.
Okay, get in.
I'll be watching you.
[Kwang Soo pushes him forcefully.]
I don't know what's in the room.
[When they opened the door,
she was there.]
You can't enter this room.
Seriously, I can't!
[Being too scared, he's laughing.]
She's dancing.
[Why is he filming his feet?]
[He runs away.]
[She's scary, isn't she?]
[Huh?]
Yoon Sang!
[Yoon Sang's gone, and
the camera is abandoned.]
Yoon Sang!
[VJ Yoon Sang escaped.]
[He shouldn't have
given him the name tag.]
Did he really leave??
[The reality he doesn't want to believe.]
['I'm all alone.']
[No choice but to pick up the camera]
[He opens the door again,
and she's still dancing.]
[I'll check this locker
and leave.]
[At that moment, the door closes.]
[Giraffe might master a vocalization
skill in the dance studio.]
[I have your name tag.]
Are you going to give
me the name tag or not?
I'll give it to you.
[Just tell me what you want.]
[Avoiding eye contact]
- My name tag isn't here.
- Did you check?
Yes, and there's nothing.
[Because I have it.]
[It's ridiculous.]
[They've hid each other's name tags.]
Let's get out together.
We'll put it for each other.
We should have given it earlier.
[Who are you blaming?]
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are escaping?]
- Put it on me.
- When we step outside.
Where did you put my name tag?
[I still have you name tag!]
[Jong Kook collects his name tag
and goes to throw out Kwang Soo's.]
Jong Kook, it's my fault!
I won't do it again!
[He gets to
the second floor in no time.]
[And he throws Kwang Soo's
name tag in the dance studio.]
My shoe is stuck!
My shoe!
[He needs to get back his name tag
in order to escape from the school.]
Where did it go?
[He saw it landed on the floor.]
Miss!
[Ta-da!]
Oh, please!
Please!
What's wrong with her?
[Don't eat it,
just give it to me!]
Let me go...
I really need to...
Ji Hyo and Gary are coming in now.
Please, let me go.
[Giraffe begged the ballerina
and received his name tag.]
[Ji Hyo is searching
the school by herself.]
[She's doing it because she's scared.]
[She's coming!
The horrifying stroller ghost!]
I'm on top of the world
and there are many people
who love me.
[They want to overcome
the fear by singing.]
[The dark spirit is getting stronger.]
[There's something!]
[Song Ji Hyo acquires
Gary's name tag!]
[Scream]
[Frightened]
Are you insane?
- Are you okay?
- It's so scary.
- Did you find anything?
- No, Gary...
[She's going to keep it as a secret.]
And that ghost lady is really scary.
[Monday Couple enter
the art room together.]
[That's Ji Hyo's name tag!]
[Oh, I found it!]
[Peek-a-boo!]
I almost hit him!
[Kang Gary acquires Ji Hyo's name tag!]
Please give me the name tag.
Don't worry, I'll give it to you.
- Please, give my name tag, Gary.
- Turn around, I'll put it.
- Give it to me, Gary!
- I'll put it on your back.
[Were you scared, Ji Hyo?]
[Don't worry,
I'm right next to you.]
[It's a sweet moment
in a long while.]
Gary, promise me one thing.
[He gives his pinky
even before say talks.]
Don't betray me for the next ten games!
- Why would I do that?
- Let's be loyal!
- Of course!
- Come over here.
- Did you fine mine?
- Yes.
[Ji Hyo answers with Gary's name tag
to Gary's loyalty.]
Let's get out together, Gary!
[Monday Couple escape sharing hands.]
Be careful!
Why did you jump three stairs over?
How was it?
- Offensive.
- The ghosts are?
How was it?
You...
do this before you know it.
[Scream!]
That's right.
The next thing I knew,
I was screaming.
- Let's clap for him.
- I'll be back.
It's bearable.
If you scream ten times, it's over.
I see.
This drives me crazy.
I'm going there by myself.
Seriously, we'll be together, Yoo Suk.
We will, right?
Don't grin like that.
I don't even know how to
operate this camera.
Thank you for your hard work.
You can go home with your VJs.
We're leaving. Will you be
able to sleep alone, Ji Hyo?
[You need to get beat up.]
I see.
[Even this doesn't work.]
What's that?
[For Big-nose, the PD came with them.]
That music.
Yoo Suk, come over here.
You need to film in front of me.
You need to film my face.
I'm going insane.
Mommy...
[He's calling his mom at age 50.]
[The nurse's office
is filled with red light.]
It's a doll.
[He's shocked to see the mannequin.]
[And he's shocked to see
inside the locker and the toy.]
There's nothing over here, right?
[He's shocked to see the PD as well...]
[The PD is big but weak]
[and Big-nosed brother is old
but acts like a child.]
I'm going crazy...
[He enters the dance studio.]
[He only saw her from the back
and he's taken aback.]
Aaaaaah!
[He move to the end of
the hallway instantly.]
[Unfortunately, he ran
to the classroom of ghosts.]
They're just mannequins, right?
[He checks the locker first.]
[He found the name tag!]
[After that, he runs
out of the classroom.]
[The stroller ghost visits
when they're careless.]
Don't come near me!
Don't come!
[Runs]
[He doesn't think about
anything else but runs away.]
No!
Don't come!
[The PD and VJ Yoo Suk follow him.]
[Suk Jin, let's find my name tag
and escape together!]
Yoo Suk, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Yoo Suk!
I can't do it any longer!
I'm going to get mad!
I think I'm going crazy!
I'm sorry!
Yoo Suk!
I think I'm going crazy!
No, I think I'm going crazy!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Yoo Suk!
Suk Jin, let's go together!
I'm sorry!
I'll get out first!
Let's go together!
[Suk Jin left.]
- Suk Jin!
- I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
[He keeps repeating
that he's sorry.]
[He's puzzled, and
his footsteps are heavy.]
Suk Jin!
I never want to do it again! Never!
[After five years of working together...]
[Loyalty yields to fear.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Suspicious taxi drivers are coming!]
[Kang Sung Jin, Park Gun Hyung,
Kim Su Ro, Nam Bo Ra, Kim Min Kyo]
[Go! Cab drivers' favorite
restaurant expedition!]
[They will go and eat,
as they were told!]
[Guess the cab driver's
favorite meal right!]
Drive safe!
[Let the cab drive my body!]
[Eat, eat and eat!]
[Until you get the correct answer!]
[They receive a
secret mission from the PD.]
[Who will clear the mission
and take the absolute menu?]
Next week, 'Cab Drivers'
Favorite Restaurant Expedition!'