[The Girls Generation package
has arrived!]
[The girls have changed!]
[They let everything go.]
[They release their inner variety.]
[Welcome to Game World,
Girls Generation.]
['Running Man']
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Ha Ha's office in Seoul.]
[Focusing intensely]
[He's completely absorbed
in a video game.]
[Celebrity Ha Ha vs.
Manager Hyung Chul.]
Why doesn't it work for me?
I think this is broken!
It doesn't work!
[Repeated mistakes on Ha Ha's team.]
Why doesn't mine work?
This broke.
How come yours works
but mine doesn't!
Wear this and play!
I'm wearing sunglasses,
so you have to wear this!
Only mine doesn't work!
[A message arrives.]
[Angry Ha Ha]
What is this?
[What could this be?]
[A mysterious invitation...]
[He presses yes.]
[Ha Ha disappeared?]
[Was he invited to the
virtual game world?]
[Was I mistaken?]
Ha Ha disappeared!
[Our boss disappeared.]
[Anger-management fail Ha boss,
where did he go?]
[At the same time, Kwang Soo...]
An enormous fellow has appeared.
[A smile of satisfaction
towards something...]
It's been a while since
I've seen such a fellow.
[A facial spasm]
[A game of pushing out!]
[He's letting out his craziness.]
You can't win against me!
[A message arrives.]
[What is interrupting my
moment of happiness?]
What is this?
[The mysterious invitation
that Ha Ha received.]
[Suspicious, suspicious]
Will you respond to the invitation?
Yes.
[Kwang Soo disappeared as well!]
You are invited to the
virtual game world.
[An invitation to
the virtual game world]
[was sent out to all the members.]
Oh, what is this?
Yes!
That's awesome!
Yeah!
[Then, they disappear!]
[That's the end of a relaxing break.]
[If the response is a
yes, they disappear]
Yes, no?
Yes!
[Instantaneously!]
[All the 'Running Man' members vanished!]
[At the same time,
at a hair salon in Seoul.]
[Eloquent steps]
[Her back is quite provocative.]
[Who is it?]
[The youngest of
Girls Generation, Seo Hyun.]
[Everyone else is here, too!]
[Sunny]
[Tiffany]
[Tae Yeon]
[Yoona]
[Soo Young, Yuri]
[Hyo Yeon]
[Girls Generation are planning a
comeback in a year and five months.]
[They've never come on 'Running Man'
with the whole group before!]
[A leisurely time at the salon.]
[I'm becoming prettier.]
[Aren't you too girly?]
[Seo Hyun also got an invitation?]
What is this?
[She clicked yes.]
[Seo Hyun vanished, too!]
[Who's phone is it?]
[Tae Yeon found the
invitation as well!]
[She also vanished.]
What is happening!
[Sunny disappears in a flash.]
[Now everyone is disappearing
like dominoes...]
[Sunny, Yoona, Tiffany,
Yuri one after another!]
[Soo Young is dozing off.]
[Nobody's here?]
Where did they go?
[She checks the
invitation half-asleep.]
[Did everyone go here?]
[Girls Generation
accepted the invitation!]
[Where did the 'Running Man' members
and Girls Generation vanish off to?]
[Welcome to Game World!]
How long has it been since
we last saw Girls Generation?
[The first time]
Welcome back!
[They came as a whole!]
Thank you!
Girls Generation!
But more than anything
- I heard it's Tiffany's first time.
- Soo Young, too!
- It's Soo Young's first time.
- She didn't come last time.
It's almost like the
year-end awards ceremony!
They don't know anything
about the mud flat!
[A standard mud flat photo shoot.]
It can be seriously physical...
[Tremble, tremble]
In my opinion, Sunny knows
the least about mud flats.
- Why?
- Her clothes...
She's in Miami!
It'll take forever to dig out
the dirt in your belly button.
Are these the teams?
In the same color?
Yes.
Yuri and Tiffany saw my shirt
and they cursed.
[I can relate.]
Why can't Yoona and
Soo Young look at Gary?
Are you shy?
[He's so charming...]
He's a lump of charm!
- That was smooth, Gary.
- I can't help but look...
Everyone has entered
into the game world.
In order to go back to the real world
you must clear all the
missions in the game world.
[Every time a team wins the
interim mission, you will receive]
[a hint exchange ticket that is
beneficial at the final mission.]
Only one team can return
to the real world.
Basically, you don't get to go home.
I don't want to go back today.
This is the location
for the first game.
The first game is...
[What game will it be...]
- You know the game 'Pac-Man,' right?
- Yes!
- 'Pac-Man'!
- I used to play it when I was young!
[A classic game, 'Pac-Man.']
If you see from above, the set
is prepared like a 'Pac-Man' game.
Of the five teams,
one team will go against the rest.
And the rest of the teams
must guard the gateway.
Oh, like the children's game?
If you go over there, you will see
the suspension bridge.
The defense team stays at the bottom.
The challenge team must get
through and cross the bridge.
You can help the member
who is crossing.
In the next one
[Palm strike zone.]
one representative has
to knock everyone down.
After that, at the third gate
[One-legged fight zone.]
All three members must do
a one-legged fight.
The challenge team can get up
even if they fall and retry.
This is the last one.
[Steal the sock zone.]
One person on defense
will be wearing a sock.
You have to take that sock off.
We will time you from the
moment you start and finish.
We will give hints to the top two
teams who have the shortest record.
[First challenge Team Yellow,
Gary, Yoona, Soo Young.]
Take it easy.
- Do I look weird?
- Just don't throw us, please.
Soo Young, why are you
trying to look nice?
This is a mud flat!
This is my first time,
of course I have to look nice!
Okay!
[You don't know anything about women.]
[Gate Two defense, Team Blue.]
Can Gary be their rep?
- Why?
- He looks easy to deal with.
Gary?
Who's on Gary's team?
Yoona and Soo Young.
- Who's stronger, Yoona or Soo Young?
- Yoona's the strongest out of all.
I'm going to do my best today!
Good luck!
- Soo Young, do well!
- Okay, good luck!
[First mission, 'Pac-Man' game.]
Ready, start!
Our enemy is coming!
[Team Yellow is running towards
the first gate, the suspension bridge.]
[Soo Young is very energetic on her
first appearance on 'Running Man.'
[Fall]
Why did you fall?
[Gary crosses the bridge.]
[Let's just get through Jong Kook...]
[If I get through Jong Kook,
all that's left are two delicate girls...]
[Give us your pants, you'll pass!]
Gary, good luck!
[Everyone wants
a piece of... his clothes.]
[They look like girls,
but they act like old ladies.]
- Gary, your pants!
- Hurry and come!
[The member that succeeds can
help other members pass through.]
Step on me!
[I am a man.]
[Yoona succeeds thanks to Gary's help.]
Soo young, what are you doing?
Hurry!
[Tickle, tickle]
That tickles, stop.
[If Soo Young passes,
they can clear the first gate.]
- It hurts!
- Go, Soo Young!
[Soo Young passes the bridge!]
- We tried really hard.
- What is this?
[Dizzy, dizzy]
I tried really hard.
My face got stepped on.
[Team Yellow goes to
the palm strike zone.]
Yoona, you go!
[Yoona's elected to be their rep.]
- Who's stronger?
- Yoona's the strongest.
[Let's go, Yoona!]
['Running Man' ace Ji Hyo vs.
Girl of strength Yoona.]
[Let's play...]
[Her avoiding technique!]
[Blank Ji is out by
Yoona's strategy.]
[A complete ace Yoona vs.
The small but strong Sunny.]
[She uses her trick again.]
[Sunny's ousted with the same skill.]
[Slap]
Gary!
[The trickster Yoona vs.]
[the man of gender equality, Big Nose.]
I won't go easy!
- What was that?
- What are you doing!
What are you doing!
[Flustered, flustered]
[Pantomime]
[Thud]
[They're going to the third gate,
the one-legged fight.]
- This team is fast!
- They're fast!
[You've made huge progress...]
[We'll give you a break...]
[Thrown]
[They're accelerating the process
instead of giving them a break.
[Tiffany's ousted
at the speed of light.]
[Yuri's also ousted.]
[The third gate is just
an automatic gate.]
[They're entering the fourth gate,
steal the sock zone.]
- You have to block her.
- Gary, what are you doing?
[Give me your sock!]
[Grasshopper is fleeing.]
[I can't let Gary pass until
mud gets in my eyes!]
[Here you go!]
[Rub, rub]
[You, too.]
[It's good for your skin.]
Help me, help me!
[Grasshopper is surrounded.]
[The sock is in front of their eyes!]
[Bite]
[The girl of strength is on the move!]
[They got the sock.]
Na Na Na boo boo!
[They pass the steal the sock zone
with the help of Yoona and Soo Young.]
[Team Yellow's record is 4:46.]
[Team Pink, Jong Kook,
Tae Yeon, Seo Hyun.]
Jong Kook, you better watch out!
[She almost went tumbling
with that hair flip.]
We don't really need to go fast here.
[Will she be able to complete it?]
Why does Kwang Soo look like that?
He's weird!
Yuri!
What are you saying!
Don't you remember way back when?
[She was darker than
an espresso in her old days.]
I thought he was handsome.
[Falter]
Are you ready?
- We don't need to go fast.
- Ready!
Let's go!
['Pac-Man' Round 2, starts!]
You can't pass through!
[Sink]
- Tae Yeon!
- Are you praying?
[Is she human or paper...]
[Mr. Capable is her
direct transportation.]
Gary, grab Jong Kook...
that's not fair!
- That's not fair!
- Turn him around!
[Mr. Capable is in a guerrilla pose.]
Hey!
Tae Yeon!
[Kkuk's in danger.]
[Kick, kick]
[Their laundry skills are amazing!]
Wow, he's stubborn!
[Mr. Capable is charging forward.]
[Mr. Capable passes
the suspension bridge!]
[He goes to support
his team right away.]
[Thanks to Mr. Capable's support]
[Seo Hyun also passes
the suspension bridge.]
[The problem is Tae Yeon...]
- Let's go!
- You can't protect me.
[She falls by herself.]
Tae Yeon, you're like paper!
[She's fighting with gravity.]
[Mr. Capable's fast paper
delivery service.]
[Thanks to Mr. Capable,
Tae Yeon passes as well.]
They're coming!
Do you really have to go this far?
Jong Kook made up his mind, watch out!
Jong Kook's face changed!
[Roar, roar]
[Angry tiger Kkuk vs.
Long arms and legs Giraffe.]
[Fall]
[One shot, one kill.]
[Mr. Capable is awesome!]
[Have a seat.]
[Mr. Capable vs.
Grasshopper.]
[A forceful bedtime.]
[He clears it with three high fives.]
This is unfair!
- This is so upsetting!
- It's upsetting!
Girls, we have to be strong!
[You need to stay strong...]
Jong Kook!
Why are you so close!
[Lands by himself]
[How scared were you...]
[Yoona falls with Jong Kook's knee.]
[Soo Young's ousted as well.]
[They're heading to the sock zone.]
- Who has the sock?
- I don't know.
It's Sunny!
Grab Sunny, she has the sock!
[Blank Ji guards Seo Hyun.]
Sunny has to sock!
[The sock hunter is...]
[The human piece of paper, Tae Yeon!]
[Better luck next time!]
[Mr. Capable joins in.]
[Give me the sock!]
[This time, I'll get it for sure!]
[Mr. Capable gets the sock!]
- We did it!
- What is this!
[Collecting waste paper]
[After clearing each gate, the entire
team has to be out of the finish line.]
- Does everyone have to be out?
- Yes.
[Wait! Paper human!]
Jong Kook's like the hulk!
[Drop kick]
[Why you!]
[Collapse]
[Bedtime]
[Team Pink's record is 5:33.]
Just wait and see!
I'm not letting anyone go!
I did just about enough
but this won't do!
[Get ready for Team Pink's revenge.]
I can't move my face anymore...
You only have one emotion.
- Only one emotion.
- I'm actually smiling right now.
[Team Blue is heading
towards the start line.]
We're in big trouble.
It's them.
[It's the cheating
brothers at Gate One...]
We're in big trouble!
[What's this?
We're even worse than you.]
[Next target]
[Giraffe's hair is grabbed.]
Ji Hyo, don't put your feet there!
[There...]
[The taste of hell!]
Ji Hyo, not there!
Ji Hyo, if you put your feet there...
[Ji Hyo passes the bridge.]
[As soon as she passes,
she actively supports Sunny.]
We just need to grab Suk Jin.
[After getting Blank Ji's help,
Sunny goes in.]
- Help me!
- Your pants are loose!
Oh my gosh!
[He'll have abs soon.]
Hurry up!
[Clumsy, clumsy]
Can you lift my pants up for me?
[He's very polite...]
- My pants...
- He's so annoying!
[The female team members
are carrying him all the way.]
[There will be an inspection.]
[Fall down]
Leave him there!
Sunny, let's go!
Just let Suk Jin go!
[Only Yuri thinks of me...]
I'm bored!
[I want to go home...]
[Big Nose exceeded his time limit
and got eliminated at Gate One.]
We're the last ones.
[Team Orange got a record]
I think Gary's team was the fastest.
[Ha Ha's team: 5:03.]
- Yeah.
- How should we do this?
- The first gate is the most dangerous.
- The first gate.
I think if you do something wrong,
you're gonna end up like Suk Jin.
If we don't watch out,
Kwang Soo and I will get caught
and we'll end up like Suk Jin.
- We just need to get through Gate One.
- Yeah, just this one.
- Last race, get ready!
- Let's go, one, two
three, good luck!
[Round Five of 'Pac-Man,' start!]
[Tempered tailbone]
- Charge!
- Bring it on!
Come on!
I'm not letting anyone through!
- Let Hyo Yeon pass.
- Hyo Yeon, you can go.
[Scared]
[Attack]
[It's about time to get punished!]
[Shall we start?]
Sunny!
Hey!
[It's clothe-collecting season.]
Come on, come on!
[Fourth gate, steal my sock zone.
What is Team Orange up to?]
We're going to bury the sock.
That's a good idea!
They're so funny!
I think we should all bury our feet
so that they don't know who has it.
There's time, right?
[But none of you can move.]
Where are you going?
[One, two!]
[Grasshopper and Hyo Yeon
pass the bridge.]
- You can't go!
- Kwang Soo, hurry up!
- What are you doing!
- Just come!
[Fall]
Just come!
[A big slide.]
[Hesitantly puts his
hand in his pants.]
Hurry!
Hurry and go up!
[Ah... I miss my mom...]
Catch Kwang Soo!
He looks like...
someone who came for a
whole-body mud pack.
- Hurry up!
- Kwang Soo!
- Hurry up.
- Just step on me, hurry up.
Go, oww!
[Stretch]
[Slap]
Kwang Soo, your legs!
Legs!
- Sunny!
- We did it!
[Kwang Soo passed the
suspension bridge.]
[Beard man, who are you?]
[Team Green is heading to Gate Two.]
- Who is it?
- Let's go!
[Grasshopper Jae Suk vs.
Paper human Tae Yeon.]
[Thud]
Tae Yeon!
Who's next?
[Second opponent, Seo Hyun.]
Go away Seo Hyun!
[Fall]
Seo Hyun!
[Playing hard to get genius, Seo Hyun.]
- Nothing's going my way!
- One, two, three!
[Strike]
- Jae Suk!
- She won't fall!
[Seo Hyun's ousted
thanks to Hyo Yeon's help.]
[Grasshopper vs.
Extreme tiger.]
[She's providing support again.]
[He became a marionette.]
It's three versus one!
Damn it!
[Punch]
You're so frustrating!
[There's no tomorrow!]
Kwang Soo, pull me out.
[Switch players]
[from Grasshopper to Giraffe.]
[Spin]
[An outburst of rage.]
[Punch, punch]
[Extreme tiger, out!]
[After Gate Two, they finished
the one-legged race in a flash.]
[The only thing left
is the fourth gate.]
Where is it?
[All the team members
have buried feet.]
You don't know where it is!
Where could it be?
It's here!
- No!
- Defend Yuri!
[They might beat Team Orange's score.]
Left foot!
No!
[Roll]
[Victory is decided
right here, right now!
[We found it!]
What is this?
Where is this?
This is a towel!
Yuri block them!
[The sock is on Tiffany's foot.]
Grab Jae Suk!
- Are you crazy?
- Is this funny to you?
[What are you doing?]
What is this!
[You should do at least
this much in a mud flat.]
[The mud flat is alive.]
[Is it Girls Generation or
the prehistoric generation...]
[Let's go to it Grasshopper, too.]
Jae Suk, what's with
the color of your underwear?
What is this!
[Orange boy...]
[Blow]
[Team Green is eliminated
after running out of time.]
Why does this happen every
time I wear orange underwear?
[The curse of the orange underwear.]
People must think
I have no other underwear!
We can't go all the way over there!
- Just stay where you are!
- Okay!
I'll announce them!
[Team Yellow: 1st, Team Orange: 2nd]
[Team Pink: 3rd]
[Team Green: disqualified]
[Team Blue disqualified.]
[Only the top two teams get...]
[the beneficial hint exchange ticket.]
[Angry, angry]
You...
I won't let this go!
It's no joke!
[Everyone's combat skills rose.]
I'm not letting this go!
I'm not joking!
Honestly...
I can't believe...
- They stripped us like that?
- It wasn't even underwater.
And also
why do I also get stripped when
I'm wearing orange underwear?
When I was picking it out today,
I thought... now way.
Your orange underwear has been on
the show more than most guests.
It had a lot of appearances.
People will misunderstand...
that I only have one underwear...
I'll buy you some on your birthday.
I have many!
I have the most in my neighborhood!
Why do you mean neighborhood?
But we've already used up so
much energy on the first mission...
What do we do?
Do you still try hard?
But when filming starts,
everyone tries right?
- The competitiveness comes out again.
- Yeah.
But I'm kind of slow at running.
That's okay, I don't think
we'll be running.
That's a relief.
Did you just act cute?
Were you showing your cute side?
Guys misunderstand.
- How?
- Guys think you're doing it to them.
Oh, really?
Guys act like they're inattentive
but they think about it at home.
- Really?
- Before they go to sleep, he thinks...
Why did she say
'that's a relief' to me?
You know what it is, right?
Do they really do that?
Wow.
- What is this?
- It's a video game!
- The bugs are a part of nature.
- Gary!
They taught me.
Yoona is teaching Gary how to
gain popularity by women.
I'm learning.
Tell us, too!
When we were eating,
Kwang Soo ordered a dish for Ji Hyo...
He didn't order it.
He took some of what we were eating
so we thought Kwang Soo
was going to eat it
- but he put it in front of Ji Hyo.
- Without saying anything.
Because of that,
they love Kwang Soo now.
[That's nothing...]
A gentleman!
- Kwang Soo does that on purpose.
- What are you saying!
He does that for you to see!
[Was that what it was?]
[Gary still shoos
the insects for them.]
Those guys say dogs
are cute in front of women.
[They become an animal lover
only in front of women.]
Mind your own business
and get a girlfriend!
There are a lot of guys like that.
[Scream]
Wait, stay still.
That's not manly, right?
- He's scared of bugs.
- It's cute.
Kwang Soo,
Soo Young says you're cute.
Kwang Soo, Soo Young said
you were cute just now.
Being scared of bugs?
[Like this?]
Soo Young wants to see you dance!
- I haven't danced in a long time.
- She said it on the way here.
[Please dance, Kwang Soo!]
[A passionate dance]
[I can dance anytime, for you.]
[Oh my eyes! Once is enough...]
You guys have already
fallen in love with him.
The second game is
'Gigantic Tetris.'
- 'Tetris!'
- I'm good at it!
The color of your board is
the same color as your shirt.
The first team to fully
stack the blocks will win.
- That's hard.
- With these Tetriminoes.
They fly out from here.
[Six different types of Tetriminoes.]
Then you have to fill your board.
You can fight for the blocks.
However, you can't steal the ones
that have been inserted.
The team that wins round one
gets 1st place.
The team that wins round two
gets 2nd place.
Do you understand?
We'll start right away.
[They're ready.]
Hyo Yeon, let's do this!
[It seems like they
still have a grudge.]
We'll play rough, but don't get mad.
[More than anything, the point is to
get as many pieces as possible.]
[They're already marking down
their opponents before the game.]
- Be careful!
- Ready, set!
[Gigantic 'Tetris', round one starts!]
It's too big!
[Giraffe catches
the flying Tetrimino.]
[Catch Giraffe!]
[He's busy running away...]
[The second piece shoots!]
[No mark zone]
[What a welcome windfall!]
[Team Blue inserts the first piece.]
[Shooting two pieces in a row.]
[Wherever the piece lands
becomes the battlefield.]
[Big-nose gets two pieces.]
[Fighting for a piece
or aim for a new piece?]
Just catch another one.
[Team Green only gets one.]
- Get it!
- Watch out!
[Big-nose picks up
a Tetrimino quickly.]
[Big Nose's rush!]
[Team Blue is in the lead.]
[Kick]
[That's my Tetrimino!]
[Run, Ha Ha!]
[Trust me, Tiffany!]
[It's the wrong board.]
[Oh, it's wrong board!]
That's mine!
[Is this the right Tetrimino?]
[Drops]
[Yoona and Soo Young
keeps getting Tetriminoes.]
- Gary, she's here.
- I'm too short for this.
[The current state of the board]
[Ha Ha catches the Tetrimino.]
[Well, let me see...]
Grab that one!
[It's time to think
about the arrangement.]
- Ha Ha.
- Let's hurry up.
Hurry, hurry!
- We don't have space to put it.
- Kwang Soo!
[Run about in confusion]
Not there!
[Yoona and Soo Young has
a success rate of 100% in hunting.]
[Team Yellow starts to arrange
the Tetriminoes again.]
- We should put it like this.
- Yes, that's better.
Put this one on the top.
Why are you stealing from me?
[Team Orange starts hunting again.]
We have three segments left.
- What do we need?
- Three segments left.
- We need a dot and an I.
- We don't need the O.
[Grabs]
[He gets one as soon as
he starts hunting.]
We need an L.
I need a purple colored shape.
[With an I, Team Orange can win.]
Let's swap it.
That's right!
That's better.
[Team Yellow is
rearranging everything.]
[At that moment...]
[Kwang Soo steals their I.]
You can't steal it!
[Team Green also need
an O and a dot.]
[Team Yellow is in confusion
because Giraffe took their Tetrimino.]
[Meantime, Jae Suk and Hyo Yeon
get another Tetrimino.]
Kwang Soo, take the I out.
Please give me the purple one!
We need the purple dot and an L.
We don't need it.
Kwang Soo, let's trade!
That doesn't fit.
[Ha Ha tries to steal.]
- We can end this.
- I need this one!
[Hyo Yeon gets the dot
and runs to the board.]
[And she picks up the O
Ha Ha dropped.]
Kwang Soo, here.
Take it out, Kwang Soo!
[They can complete the board
with the O and the dot.]
They will finish it
if they take this I!
- Kwang Soo!
- They can finish it now!
[Hang in there, Kwang Soo!]
Steal it!
Finish it!
[We'll lose if they steal it.]
[We only need to put this in...]
Hyo Yeon, step on my back.
Hurry up and finish it!
Finish it!
[Team Green finishes the 1st round
of 'Gigantic Tetris.']
Good job!
[Their fantastic teamwork let
them win a losing game.]
- Very nice!
- That's mine!
[Team Orange lost by a whisker.]
We did it!
Our strategy worked!
- Our team's victory!
- It was a close call.
- Are they done?
- Yes, they are.
Yah!
We got first place!
The winning team will
shoot the Tetriminoes now.
Yes, we'd like to do that!
We'll show you!
[The first place is Team Green.]
[The second round of
the Gigantic 'Tetris' starts.]
From now on, we're going to
start a dance battle.
[It's dance time!]
[I'm ready for it!]
We'll start when the music starts!
Start the music!
[Music starts.]
[Everyone starts dancing
as soon as the music starts.]
[It's nice to be the winner.]
How about a battle between teams?
Starting from Suk Jin's team!
One, two, three, four!
[The dance!]
[The legendary 'Tetris' dance!]
Turn right!
[People with joint problems
can't dance it!]
Get off the stage!
[Suk Jin dances with a stoop.]
Next!
[Team Orange's turn.]
One, two, three, four!
[Their dance moves are in-sync!]
[They don't have join
problems for sure!]
Wonderful!
[Ha Ha tries dance duet.]
[They enjoy the music.]
Go back!
Next!
[Team Yellow come forward.]
Five, six, seven, eight!
[Wave]
[Advanced break dancing!]
[Feel the groove!]
[I'm feeling it!]
[Their intense dance fever!]
[Don't stop the music!]
[Each of her bones moves on its own.]
[You look different today...]
[They agreed to give a Tetrimino
to Team Yellow.]
[It's a precious piece
that they earned with the dance.]
[Tiffany's attempt.]
[I'm the dancer of this club!]
[Sunny's attempt.]
She's coming again!
[Crayon Shin Chan's dance.]
Jae Suk!
That's great, Yuri!
[The 'Hoot' dance.]
[Give me a Tetrimino!]
[Dance gangster]
[That's it!]
[It's working!]
[Drops]
[The giving tree, Kwang Soo]
[They get a rare piece.]
[She doesn't stop dancing.]
[I sacrifice my joints
for Tetriminoes!]
[Move away!]
[Team Orange get two long pieces.]
[Kicks]
[Ha Ha gets the piece.]
That's mine!
[Team Orange has three pieces already.]
It's fun!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Already four Tetriminoes!]
[Nice catch!]
Grab it!
[Yuri passes it to Ha Ha.]
[Nice teamwork!]
[They're winning...]
[When did Team Yellow
collect them all?]
[Yoona's nice catch!]
- Give me!
- Steal it!
[Team Yellow filled more than
half of the board.]
It's O again.
[Ha Ha keeps catching pieces.]
[We're almost done.]
[The rich get richer
and the poor get poorer.]
[It's the battle
between the two teams.]
Watch out, Tiffany!
[Ha Ha keeps grabbing them.]
Here's another one.
[They add two more.]
[They can finish it
if they have an I.]
They're almost done.
They need an I.
[It ain't over till it's over.]
- Blue piece!
- Then it'll be over.
[Soo Young and Yoona's
delivery service.]
- We need an I!
- Get a small one!
Wait, please start the music!
We need a dot.
[A dot or an I?]
Wait!
Please start the music!
[It's the 'Tetris' music!]
[They start dancing automatically.]
[Give me Tetriminoes!]
Give us a dot!
[A piece looks like this?]
Jae Suk, yes that one!
The small one!
Please!
[This is fun!]
The dot!
[Until when are you going to
make us dance?]
To the right!
To the left!
[Just give us the piece!]
Why aren't you giving us?
[Not that one, the dot!]
[The rare piece appears.]
[Drops]
It's the I!
[Come on, I!]
[One step late...]
Get up, Tiffany!
[Kkuk gives her back.]
[But that's their last piece!]
[Team Orange wins the second round.]
Jae Suk!
[Wait, is it over?]
- Jae Suk!
- It's over.
I'm sorry.
Who told you to dance with us?
I'm very sorry.
I was busy dancing.
I was enjoying it too much.
- Didn't I, Hyo Yeon?
- We had fun, didn't we?
How many times did I tell you
that we wanted the small piece!
[Here it is!]
Should we get down now?
[They have finally arrived at
the final stage of the game world.]
[In this mysterious maze...]
[who will survive to the end?]
It's the final mission of
'Welcome to the Game World.'
There are four bar codes
to let you escape the game world.
They're hidden inside this building.
There are four kinds of bar codes
which are A, B, C, and D.
On the ground floor, we'll see
a platform with a bar code scanner.
If you scan the four bar codes
in the order of A, B, C, and D
the password will be revealed
and it will open the gate.
Only one team can escape
the game world.
If you fail to escape, you have to
live in the game world forever.
- Oh no!
- What are you doing?
You're supposed to immersed
in this situation.
You can't even release your album
if you can't get out of here.
You need to search and find
the bar codes to escape.
But there are gatekeepers
who are aiming for your name tags.
[There are gatekeepers!]
- You can't oust them no matter what.
- We can't oust them?
No, you can't oust them.
Will we be ousted when they
eliminate our name tags?
Isn't that obvious?
- Is running the only way to avoid it?
- Yes.
[The unidentified gatekeepers...]
[who appear during the final stage.]
[What they're aiming for is...]
[only the name tag of 'Running Man.']
[Will you be able to avoid them...]
[and survive the final stage?]
There's another problem.
There's another entity
that blocks you from escaping
and it's called the 'Angel Code.'
[Angel Code]
Before the Angel Code
blocks you from escaping
you need to open the gate and escape.
Angel Code?
Here are the hints for the winners.
The first and second winners
of the first mission.
of the second mission.
[Team Orange has two hints.]
Don't show it to others.
Keep it to yourselves
and start finding them.
This is a team battle.
[The final stage
of the game world starts!]
We should stick together.
- In the beginning.
- We shouldn't separate.
We need to find the bar code first.
[Ground floor, 'C' store]
[The third floor, 'V' hat store]
What's our hint?
[2nd floor, jewelry store]
[3rd floor, household items.]
Then we'll go to the second floor.
We'll split up here.
Go down where no one is around.
- Then we need to hurry up.
- Let's scatter and search!
Let's scatter.
Where do you think it is?
[Scream]
What is it?
[Shiver]
What's the sound?
I don't think it's here.
Someone just screamed.
What's the noise?
[Scream]
What's wrong?
- What is it?
- I'm scared.
[The cry gave everyone pause.]
What is it?
That's very scary.
[Surprised]
[Why does it happen
when I'm by myself.]
Why?
Who's screaming?
[Shocking]
[What are they?]
[The 3rd floor gatekeepers]
[20 masked men]
[The group masked men
attack Blank Ji!]
Suk Jin!
What's going on?
They're coming here!
[Go away as far as possible!]
Wait!
[A creepy chase on the third floor]
[She got caught!]
Suk Jin!
[No one's going to help you...]
You're too scary!
Why are you doing this to me?
Why me?
Oh no!
Song Ji Hyo is out,
Song Ji Hyo is out.
[What's going on?]
[Creepy]
Is Ji Hyo ousted?
[The 'V' hat store in third floor]
- Unbelievable!
- Ji Hyo is out.
It should be inside a hat.
- In a hat.
- Be careful.
- Should I go out and watch?
- Yes, watch for them.
Run, if I say so.
[Haroro joins Team Green.]
It's so strange.
- Why?
- Ji Hyo got out so fast.
- They might oust us, too.
- It's so scary all of a sudden.
Hyo Yeon, you're not hiding
anything from us, right?
What is it?
[They're back!]
Hyo Yeon!
[The men run away
leaving Hyo Yeon behind.]
Hyo Yeon, we're sorry!
[They couldn't care about her.]
[How could they...]
[They didn't see Hyo Yeon.]
Hurry up and hide!
[Throb]
[They're gone, right?]
[Hyo Yeon keeps
looking for the bar code.]
Huh?
[She finds the bar code A!]
[She acquires one of
the four bar codes.]
[On the second floor...]
I'm shaking.
What's the sound?
Here it is!
[She finds the bar code B.]
This is it.
Quickly, before anyone comes.
Barcode B...
Ha Ha!
[She is even more scared outside.]
What should I do?
I'm so scared!
[She runs to the corner.]
[Scream]
[Ti...Tiffany?]
Oh my god, I was scared to death!
I was hiding in here.
Where did you go?
Is Ji Hyo out?
I can't believe it.
This is tough!
It's very tough today.
[Wriggle]
Don't go out this way.
[It feels weird...]
[Someone is walking around.]
[Grab]
What are you?
Wait!
Are you trying to
eliminate my name tag?
Wait a minute!
[He eliminates Suk Jin's
name tag in a flash.]
[What is it?]
Am I out?
What just happened?
[He bows and disappears.]
Am I really out?
Ji Suk Jin is out!
I think gatekeepers are strong.
- How do they look like?
- They're wearing masks.
- Really?
- It's so scary.
They're really scary.
[The bookstore is in panic.]
- Do you want to go up?
- But if we go, the gate...
[Shocking!]
[What did she see?]
[He's back!]
[The killer in crimson suit!]
What do we do?
What is going to happen
to Soo Young?
[She attacks his vital spot!]
[Kick!]
Choi Min Ho!
[The gatekeeper on the second floor]
[Shinee's Min Ho]
[The fastest gatekeeper]
[The most athletic idol]
[He's here to hunt us!]
Choi Min Ho, go away!
It's me, Min Ho!
No!
[Haroro witnessed this.]
Who's that?
[It's like an African safari tour!]
Who is it?
Here's another gatekeeper!
- Jae Suk!
- Kwang Soo...
There's a guy here who's
wearing a crimson suit.
[No one is willing to help her.]
Min Ho, no!
[Soo Young's life hangs by a hair.]
Min Ho, I'm on 'Running Man'
for the first time.
Please give me one more chance!
Your surname is also Choi like me.
Min Ho, you know
how much I care about you!
We even took the same class.
- The drama class we took...
- Okay, calm down.
- I see.
- Don't tell anyone that I'm here.
I'm sorry and I love you, Min Ho!
I'll come back later.
Unbelievable!
It was Shinee!
I was scared to death!
[The king of persuasion,
Soo Young survives.]
[Is he gone?]
Who's the man wearing the mask?
[This is just a warm-up!]
[The instinct for hunting name tags!]
It's all because of Soo Young.
[The atmosphere is really weird.]
[Get ready, if you're
on the second floor!]
No, don't do that!
Eh?
How can you do this to me?
Come over here!
Min Ho, come here!
Choi Min Ho is here!
[Tiffany went out
at the wrong moment.]
[She is targeted by Min Ho
right away.]
[Min Ho ousted three people.]
I met you yesterday!
Why does it matter?
Tiffany is out!
[He's enjoying a glass of water
after the hunting.]
[He's giving it to the VJ.]
You've worked so hard.
Let's just do this a little longer.
[He's aiming for his next target.]
[It's Seo Hyun.]
Min Ho!
[I've caught another one...]
[He runs to attack another one.]
[No mercy!]
Min Ho!
Whose team are you on?
[Why, all of a sudden...]
Kim Jong Kook!
It's Kim Jong Kook, right?
Tae Yeon is out!
[Well... who else is there?]
What if Min Ho catches me again?
[I think Min Ho might come back
if I stay on the second floor.]
[She hurries to go down.]
[Oh my god!]
[There's someone on the ground floor?]
[And that's even scarier.]
[Terrified!]
[The huge presence
on the ground floor]
[Ground floor gatekeeper,
Choi Hong Man]
[The strongest guy in Korea]
[He becomes the final boss
of the game world]
[and appears in front of 'Running Man.']
[They tried to avoid Min Ho...]
[but they might get
caught by Hong Man.]
[They start running instinctively.]
[You'll die if you get caught!]
[Min Ho approaches from upstairs]
[and Hong Man attacks from downstairs!]
[Frantic struggle]
[They are sandwiched
in between the two!]
[Grabs!]
[Hong Man captures Giraffe!]
[Min Ho eliminates it.]
[Hong Man keeps smashing Giraffe.]
[He's about to rip his shirt.]
I ripped it.
[Giraffe's skin is exposed by force.]
It's my mistake!
[I'm still hungry...]
[This is the strongest back smashing
I've ever had.]
[Lee Kwang Soo is out.]
[Next...]
[who should I please?]
[They're analyzing the situation.]
I think Hong Man
stays on the ground floor.
That man stays on the second floor.
He looks like Choi Min Ho.
- Who's that?
- Min Ho from Shinee.
- Really?
- I think he's Min Ho.
- I was shocked.
- Scary!
What's that?
[They saw the masked men now.]
Can they oust us?
They can?
All of them?
Hurry and find it before anyone sees us.
Check that side
and I'll check the other side.
Where is it?
How can we find it here?
Look! I found it!
- I found it!
- Where? Amazing!
Let's check all the stores.
Let's get out of here.
I can't go downstairs.
- Maybe it's in the kitchen.
- Should we look here?
I'm not good at searching.
I'm not good at finding stuff.
Me, neither.
[They find a mysterious cube.]
Do you know how to solve it?
[Let me see...]
I think this is...
the angel code.
Yes, this is angel code.
- Is that really?
- Yes, it is.
- You didn't solve it.
- Look.
I solved one face.
- Sad.
- I think there's a letter.
It's so pretty.
It's cold.
[She accidentally finds a cube.]
What is this?
Should I solve it?
I'm bad at this!
[What is this for?]
I suck at it.
What am I supposed to do?
How do I solve it?
I found a weird thing.
Isn't that the angel code?
- What did you say?
- Angel Code.
[What is angel code...]
They mentioned angel code before.
I think that's it.
Let's meet.
I'll be there.
[Is the angel code
really related to this cube?]
Choi Hong Man is unlocked.
Min Ho is unlocked.
[The gatekeepers are unlocked
after they found the angel codes.]
[Which means...]
Min Ho is unlocked, too?
[the gatekeepers can
go anywhere they want.]
Now, it's time!
Let's drink some water and go.
[There's no safe zone!]
We need to solve it quickly.
[They're looking for bar codes again.]
[And he sees the gatekeepers!]
What is Jae Suk going to do?
[He's chased by the masked men.]
[He goes to the second floor.]
It was close.
[At that moment!]
[One shot, one kill!]
I got caught by Min Ho!
- Min Ho!
- I'm sorry.
- You've worked so hard today.
You've been running by yourself.
When did you get here?
I saw the color of Grasshopper...
- Min Ho...
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yoo Jae Suk is out.
[Hyo Yeon is the only survivor
of Team Green.]
We need to find it quickly.
There's no other way.
We need to search
every nook and cranny.
[Team Orange has
the bar code A and B.]
What do we do?
It's right there!
I found the bar code D!
I found A, B and D.
I only need the bar code C.
[They can escape
if they find one more!]
Yuri, we only need the bar code C.
[Meanwhile, Yuri is...]
[solving the cube
in a hidden spot.]
Ah? Ya?
[Team Yellow tries to solve it, too.]
It worked!
Look, I solved one face.
That's an 'A.'
But why?
- With an 'A'...
- Angel?
[She gets nervous all of a sudden.]
- Let me get inside the fitting room.
- Soo Young.
I solved another face.
Another A?
[What does this mean?]
[At that moment...
someone is breathing hard?]
[Ta-da!]
[Peek]
It's Hong Man.
What do we do?
[Why are they quiet all of a sudden?]
[He's too nervous, he starts laughing.]
[We need to get out of here.]
It seems like there's something here.
[Yoona escapes.]
[What a chance!]
[While Hong Man looks at Yoona,
Gary escapes, too.]
[Run for your life!]
I thought I was going to die.
I thought you already left.
I was trying to lure him.
Min Ho came here, too.
Come on.
Yoona!
[Min Ho passes Yoona.]
He's really fast!
[This is the speed
you can see on TV.]
[Gary is doing his best to run away.]
Yoona!
[He gets caught soon.]
Gary is over.
It's interesting to watch it live.
Did he eliminate his name tag?
Is he out?
Gary is out.
- Gary is out.
- What do we do?
[Was it a good idea to be in here?]
[Huh?]
I think there's something inside.
[Hong Man's attack.]
There should be something.
[Extreme fear]
There's got to be something.
[On top of that, Min Ho joins him.]
- It's me.
- Who is it?
Is it Soo Young?
It's Soo Young.
- Please, let me live.
- Should I break the door?
I'm going to break it!
- Hong Man, I...
- What?
This is the first time
I'm on 'Running Man.'
This is my first time, too.
It's my first time.
Can't you let me live once?
Then, I'll give you all
the SNSD members' phone number.
Really?
[He's hesitating.]
I shouldn't do that...
Then, I...
will buy you a meal anytime.
Really?
This is such a nice offering.
But I shouldn't listen.
Are you willing to give up
on the phone numbers
concert tickets and
a CD with autographs?
I see.
I'll leave for now.
I know you're just pretending to leave.
[Hong Man leaves with a huge benefit.]
[Is he really gone?]
[Soo Young is the
queen of negotiation.]
Not many people have gone
to the ground floor.
I'm sure there's
something there.
[I want to at least find a bar code.]
[Min Ho is walking
around the ground floor.]
[Did he see me?]
[At a time like this...]
[Run!]
[Speed vs. speed]
[Min Ho's full speed!]
[Kkuk lost?]
[He seizes Kkuk
and calls out Hong Man.]
Hong Man!
[I'm on my way!]
[He needs to hold Kkuk
until Hong Man gets here.]
It's slippery!
[If Jong Kook is a tiger...]
[Hong Man is... a dinosaur.]
[How will the battle between
a dinosaur and a tiger be?]
[One-way discipline mode.]
[Kkuk looks small and weak
for the first time.]
[Even after he eliminates his
name tag, he keeps disciplining.]
Thank you, Hong Man.
[Kim Jong Kook is out.]
I thought I can't oust you by myself.
[Total wreck]
This was the climax of the day.
We caught him.
Jong Kook is really fast.
He's weaker than I thought.
[He's the only man
who can actually mean it.]
[After gathering all the bar codes...]
[they need to get to the platform.]
Where are you?
[Ha Ha searches for bar codes]
[Yuri solves the cube.]
I found the bar code C!
Where is she?
[Finally, Team Orange
found all the bar codes.]
Min Ho is right there,
what can I do?
[He needs to run to the platform!]
You need to hide.
I saw Y and A.
Also an O...
[Min Ho starts his engine again.]
Yellow face has an 'O.'
and the red face also has an 'O'
The green has 'Y.'
[Someone is around here?]
[It's going to be one on one
with Min Ho!]
Yoo Ee?
Or Yoo...
[Yoona... hi?]
Could it be...
Yoona?
[The gatekeeper passes her?]
[We need to stop Yoona now!]
I need to find Yoona.
[He's definitely not catching her!]
Yoona, it's me!
[Earlier...]
[Min Ho did not catch Yoona either.]
[Gatekeepers don't attack
the angel code.]
[Because the angel code
is the game master.]
[Y O O]
[N A]
[YOONA]
Why was I even running then?
You are the angel
of the game world.
The moment you connect
to the computer on the platform
a virus will spread on the computer,
and no one can escape.
Please go to the platform immediately
and scan the bar code on your wrist.
[Yoona needs to go to the platform.]
Did you solve it?
[Yuri is in front of her!]
Yoo Ee, or Yoo...
Yoona?
[Yuri knows Yoona is the angel code.]
Did you solve the cube?
[Did she figure out
that I'm the angel code?]
Where are you, Ha Ha?
[Ha Ha is looking for a chance
to get to the platform.]
[Ha Ha needs to leave Min Ho out.]
[Yoona will succeed if she keeps
her name tag and gets to the platform.]
[Where is Ha Ha anyway?]
Ha Ha!
[Min Ho sees Ha Ha first!]
[I have to gamble now!]
[Ha Ha throws down the four bar codes.]
Run, Yuri!
[But Hong Man is waiting
on the ground floor.]
- Run!
- Why did you do that?
Hong Man, you need to catch her!
No, run!
Hong Man, catch her!
[Yuri runs to get the bar codes!]
[I need to get to the platform
before Yuri gets there!]
[Hesitate]
[How can I avoid Hong Man
and pick them up?]
Yoona, let's help each other.
Look at Hong Man!
[Is she aiming for Yoona's name tag?]
No!
[Yoona starts running.]
[Yuri, it's up to you!]
[Please stop Yoona, Hong Man!]
[But the angel code Yoona
is not afraid of Hong Man!]
[Yoona gets to the platform.]
Why doesn't he attack her?
Why not, Hong Man?
[Yuri knows that Yoona is the angel code
but does not know he doesn't attack her.]
Why do you let her go?
[The computer is recognizing
Yoona's fingerprint.]
[Yoona only needs to scan
the bar code on her wrist.]
[Yuri, what's going on?]
[Finally! Yoona scans the bar code.]
[Yoona successfully spreads the virus.]
Game over!
[Disappointed]
We lost.
[The angel code, Yoona's victory!]
[Min Ho was the strongest hunter.]
- Min Ho ousted everyone.
- Hong Man is upset.
No, I'm happy to have this.
It's only name tag elimination
but he was going to rip my shirt.
He hurt you?
You've work so hard!
Yoona wins in solo
and the rest of you'll stay here.
Don't you need to call their agency
since they can't go out?
I don't really mind staying here.
Please turn on the air conditioner,
then it'll be perfect.
Thank you for being on the show,
SNSD, Min Ho, and Hong Man.
Subtitles by DramaFever