[When we go on vacation, 2015.]
[Upload video.]
We're camping!
It's nice to be outside.
- It's nice out.
- The breeze is nice.
It'll be nice to cook some meat.
Let's pick up some girls!
This is my outfit today.
[Handsome and tall Do Sang Woo
sent you a friend request.]
It's Do Sang Woo!
[An SNS friend who joined
in on the vacation!]
Why are you so late, Sang Woo?
[Handsome and tall,
Do Sang Woo!]
A cool guy completes the men's group!
[Are you curious about him?]
[Click]
[An actor and a former model,
who suppressed the small screen.]
It's been a while!
We need someone like him, that way
people come from the other tents.
In this large area
there are only two tents.
We'll die of heat!
A long time ago, we would talk
to the people in the other tents.
Then I'll visit that tent over there.
- Why are you going?
- I'll go.
- Sang Woo should go!
- I'll go!
- Go Sang Woo.
- Check how many there are.
- Bring something.
- You have to offer them something, I've done this before!
You have to take expensive fruits.
Someone has to play the guitar.
[The romantic band.]
If there are any duds, let us know!
Knock just in case they're changing.
Okay.
- Get out.
- Yes.
[Flustered.]
Sang Woo's an amateur.
You have to be casual.
- Do it well.
- Oh no!
- How is that casual?
- What are you doing!
[Kick, kick.]
- What are you doing?
- Someone kicked me four times!
Is it just you girls?
Ow!
[Her intentional way of refusing.]
They didn't even see us yet!
I think only one of
them is a troublemaker!
There's always at least
one person like that!
One of them is a dud.
- Oh, it's this person.
- Why are you doing this?
- Hello, ma'am!
- Ma'am?
You must be out on a family outing!
- Dame, come this way.
- If you do this, I won't open the door.
- Okay Dame, come this way.
- I won't open the door.
[Finally!]
[They're coming out of the tent!]
Oh, it's Hae Ryung!
It's Hae Ryung!
It's Hae Ryung of Bestie!
Oh, hello Ye Eun!
- Hae Ryung!
- Hi, Ye Eun.
Wow, this is awesome!
[Nice smile, Park Hana.]
[The hottest model, Irene.]
[This is an unbelievable tent!]
[A charming woman, Hwang Seung Eon.]
[The pure and innocent, Seo Hyun Jin.]
- Wow!
- Hello.
[Bestie's Hae Ryung, CLC's Ye Eun,
and Park Hana.]
[Irene, Seo Hyun Jin,
and Hwang Seung Eon.]
This is great!
[The arrival of beautiful women
at the camping site!]
[They are so mysterious!]
[Innocent and pure!]
[Refreshing!]
[Elegant!]
Dramas, fashion, and stages!
[The hottest women!]
[These women will be with us today!]
[Their hidden talent or
variety shows unveil!]
[There were no other vacations
like this before!]
I want to stay with you tonight.
[The counterattack of
the 6 unique women!]
It's Seo Hyun Jin!
[Her innocent-like wave.]
She's pretending to be cute!
- Do you know her well?
- Are you close?
We were in a drama together.
She's the shallow type!
Be quiet!
[Nothing changed...]
- Were you active before you became an actress?
- Yes.
Ex-idol!
She used to be an idol!
- They were called MILK.
- From SM?
- That's right.
- Really?
- Yeah, Hyun Jin was a singer at SM.
- Oh, I've seen her before.
- And now she's an actress.
- She was so young.
- She always wore white clothes.
- Am I old now?
[Noisy.]
Everyone please take a step back.
Don't point fingers at a guest, please!
Wait, wait.
I think Gary has someone
in mind right now.
No!
You're not talking much!
Is there someone here that you like?
- No!
- Be honest!
There are two people.
[He's been in a loving mood
ever since he saw their tent.]
- I couldn't decide.
- Okay.
- She brought something.
- What is it?
She reminds me of 'A dog of Flanders.'
- Sandwiches.
- Really?
- You packed these?
- Yes, I woke up early.
She made them herself?
- There are no vegetables!
- You woke up at 6:30?
[Embarrassed.]
- Why aren't there any vegetables?
- What's wrong with you!
- The jam flavors are all different.
- Really?
- Is it good?
- The jam is jaggedly spread.
It's because there were too
many sandwiches to make.
- She probably made them carefully in the morning.
- Anyway it's delicious.
Thank you very much.
[These are the couples.]
- I will explain the rules for today.
- Yes.
In order for you to spent
a refreshing summer
there is something inside
so would you open that up?
Inside the cooler.
- Ice?
- It's a heart-shaped ice!
- Should we lift it?
- Yes.
Do we have to do something
before it melts?
This ice is given to
each of the couples.
And inside, there is a key that can
open a special box at the mission site.
There are surprising
prizes within those boxes
so melt the ice with the power of love
and obtain the key.
- Okay!
- Within each round
the top three teams that win
will be given the advantage
of melting the ice quickly.
Today, the sun is very hot
so you will be given the chance
to expose it in direct sunlight.
First place will be given 30 minutes.
Second place will be given 20 minutes.
And third place will
be given 10 minutes.
If you win, the more time
you have to melt the ice
so you have the chance to quickly
melt the ice and take the key.
- Can I just break the ice?
- No, you can't.
[Why would we play the game, then?]
[Kkuk always makes a fuss.]
[Let's go to the vacation location!]
- Can I speak informally...
- Yeah, absolutely.
We've met twice already.
I knew we would.
[They modeled together before.]
The-18 year-old, Ye Eun is really cute.
She's pretty but also cute.
- Yeah she was cute and pretty.
- Am I like an older brother or an uncle to you?
- To be honest, an older brother.
- Brother, right?
- Brother Ha Ha.
- Okay! You can call me brother!
My niece.
Out of all the Running man members,
who's the most handsome?
Kwang Soo.
What?
Kwang Soo drools!
He usually drools.
Don't show it in front of him.
Do not show it.
Kwang Soo will start
liking you right away.
He's delusional,
he'll think you like him.
He's the delusional type.
I was going to pick Jong Kook
because I was blinded by victory.
What are you talking about?
- What are you saying!
- I thought about it...
If you're with Jong Kook,
you'll be exhausted.
- His nagging?
- Yeah.
Jong Kook doesn't
want to get married...
No way, he can't?
You don't think there's a reason?
There's got to be a reason.
I won't say any more.
[Is someone talking about me?]
- I started off with an album.
- Really?
- You released an album?
- Yes.
What song?
People don't know because
it wasn't that great...
- I don't know.
- We were trying to aim for 'Cool.'
- What was the group name?
- Funny.
We failed funnily.
- You were in a singing band.
- Yes.
Now, I see the light.
Your parents must be very proud.
They're in the local area, in Chungnam.
You're a daughter of Chungnam!
Son of a Chungnam.
- I'm pretty tough.
- I see.
You're a daughter of Chungnam.
[Let's go with the son of a Chungnam!]
[The hottest vacation, episode 1.]
['O' Waterpark, Goyang city]
[What kind of memories will they make?]
[Everyone's getting ready
for the first mission.]
[Huh? A handbag?]
- She's setting aside her handbag.
- Hae Ryung
is not ready for outdoor variety.
- She brought a bag?
- Yeah.
[A lovely pink item.]
Hae Ryung!
It's outdoor variety!
Hae Ryung is a very honest person.
I asked her which Running man member she likes,
and usually you answer the person that asked.
She honorably answered Kwang Soo.
I asked her who was second place
and she answered Gary.
The two are here.
- What place was Suk Jin?
- I didn't ask.
I gave up after the third place.
Third place was you.
[I've never been so sorry
after placing third...]
I didn't ask the rest.
Who's last place?
[I can't say it...]
She's not going to say it.
Stop.
She won't answer.
You're with the last place?
- I learned something new about Seung Eon.
- What is it?
I was told not to tell...
Seung Eon's friends went to a bar...
and saw Lee Kwang Soo.
- Me?
- What happened?
They witnessed that
he was on a blind date.
- Was it me?
- That's too much!
But Kwang Soo kept
showing his profile.
[I shall earn victory with my profile.]
[Where's your house?
Am I handsome in person?]
- Only his profile!
- You're that type?
- No I'm not.
- So she left because he was annoying.
Where's your house?
Hyun Jin's leaving to Spain soon
[Startled.]
Don't say it!
[What about Spain?]
- She practiced one phrase very hard.
- What is it?
She said 'I will say this
to a man in Spain!
- What is it?
- Tell us!
- Say it.
- Do it.
I really like the
pronunciation in Spanish.
As soon as I was taught the word,
it memorized on its own.
- Say it in Spanish.
- What is it?
- What does it mean?
It's long.
I want to stay with you tonight.
[Suddenly romantic.]
[Shy, shy.]
[The atmosphere is warm.]
There are people who only
memorize that kind of stuff!
It's the same as do you wanna me?
It's not 'do you wanna me?'
It's 'do you want me?'
[I talk free-style...]
Are you a 'wannamin'?
(native-speaker)
[Yes, we are all
Korean native speakers.]
Do you like me?
[I will learn other phrases, too.]
Do you want me?
Do you see the floater behind you?
The first mission is 'Love Island.'
Everyone will dance facing this way.
When the music stops
and the whistle blows
the women will run towards the floater
and the men will run toward
the path with the elephant and lion
and if you see the middle,
it's a diving board.
They will jump into the pool
and onto the floater.
After that, the couple that stayed
on the longest on the floater
with the bridal-carry pose will win.
- It's dance time!
- Yeah!
It's a fun dance time!
[A dance parade in the hot summer.]
[Let's go!]
[The youngest Ye Eun's up first!]
[It seems like an eel is
ascending to heaven.]
[Unidentifiable dance.]
[A commercial-like pose.]
[Hae Ryung's dance time.]
[Am I cute?]
[Her stage manners are good.]
[Seung Eon's dance time
with her long hair.]
[Her extraordinary energy.]
[She's getting into the rhythm.]
[Can you handle it?]
[She's catching everyone's eye.]
[She knows how to party.]
[I can't lose!]
[Wow!
Hwang Seung Eon.]
[Hana's in the house!]
[She's playing with the rhythm.]
[She's feeling it.]
[The Beyonce of Chungnam.
Her waves are amazing.]
[Irene's slim dance moves.]
[Her chic style.]
[The ex-idol Hyun Jin is out!]
[I'll help you friend...]
Oh my god!
[Direct punishment.]
[I'm not ready for
that kind of dance...]
[Now, it's time for
our only male guest.]
[Do Sang Woo's dance time!]
[While everyone is drunk
in the rhythm...]
[Whistle.]
[Love Island, start!]
[The girls head toward the floater.]
[Then men run towards
the diving board!]
[It's an advantage to take
over the floater first.]
[The men take the alley]
[and arrive at the diving board.]
[They jump without hesitation
towards their partner.]
[Wait ladies!]
[Splash.]
[They show their courage
in front of their partners.]
[Everyone dived.]
[Meanwhile, there's a
war on the floater.]
[The men also need to get
to the floater quickly.]
[They are swimming
towards their partners.]
[One person who can't swim.]
[The men have arrived on the floater.]
[They push them if it
isn't their partner.]
[Hurry up.]
[No way!]
[Blocking with all their might.]
[Hana, I'm here.]
[Jae Suk, gets on the floater
thanks to Hana.]
[Shove]
[Re-dive after two seconds.]
[Gets on the floater by force.]
[You must lift up your partner
for three seconds!]
[The men are getting on the floater
one by one.]
[Where is my partner?]
[Hae Ryung, I'm here!]
[But, I don't think I can come soon...]
Wait, my shorts!
[Lift]
[Still in the same spot
since five minutes ago.]
[Right then, Ha Ha lifts up Ye Eun.]
[Sang Woo also lifts Ji Hyo up.]
[You only have to wait
three seconds...]
[Splash]
[Giraffe and Kkuk's
joined interruption.]
[While everyone is focused
on Ji Hyo and Sang Woo.]
[Gary and Seung Eon's attempt.]
[Gary and Seung Eon win first place!]
[First place, Gary and Seung Eon.]
Oh my god!
[While the other teams are
having a bloody battle, they won.]
[It's already over?]
[First place, Gary and Seung Eon.]
I was surprised because
my feet don't reach.
I was also surprised as well.
I thought my feet
would reach but it didn't.
I swam with my eyes open.
[The returned dance time.]
[They're slowly moving towards
the diving board in rhythm.]
Why is everyone over there?
[Because it's better to be closer.]
[The women are all heading
towards the floater.]
[Modern ballet.
The title is 'Heading towards you.'
[At this rate, they're going
to dance on the diving board.]
[Come here.]
[You never know when the
whistle will blow.]
[Whistle.]
[Love Island round two, start!]
[The women towards the floater.]
[Let's meet at the floater!]
[They reached the diving
board in a flash.]
[Ji Hyo reached the floater first.]
[Let's go!]
[Perfect diving position.]
[The rest of them dive
without hesitation.]
[It's all or nothing!]
[May I shouldn't have done that...]
[Kkuk is in the lead.]
[But Irene hasn't even gone
up on the floater yet.]
Irene didn't go up yet.
Isn't it because she's tall?
[Lion's attack.]
[Sang Woo got on the floater.]
[By the way, where is my partner?]
[Does anyone know how to go forward?]
It's impossible!
Sang Woo tries lifting Ji Hyo
as soon as he gets on the floater.
[Hana's attack.]
Wow!
[Now's the time!]
[Lion's attempt at lifting Irene.]
[Jae Suk gets up on
the unoccupied area.]
[He lifted her up but...]
[He failed at enduring it.]
[Kwang Soo is distracting
Jong Kook and Irene]
[while Jae Suk distracts
Sang Woo and Ji Hyo.]
[Both teams fail.]
[Chaos.]
[There is one woman who is peaceful.]
[I want to try this, too.]
[He's approaching at the
speed of 10 cm per minute.]
[It's so hard to keep you
close when you're so far.]
[Sorry, Hae Ryung.]
[The only couples left on the floater.]
[First you lift up your partner]
[then you have to wait three seconds!]
[But...]
[Oh my god.]
[Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin
fall with Ye Eun's block.]
[Jae Suk and Hana are defenseless.]
It's Jae Suk.
[Jae Suk and Hana succeed!]
[Second place.]
[Am I that heavy, Kwang Soo?]
[Jae Suk's attack and Hana's defense.]
[An amazing collaboration.]
[Second place, Jae Suk and Hana.]
Jong Kook, why are you still here?
The viewer might think
that Irene is heavy.
She wasn't heavy at all.
Kwang Soo, I don't think you
should be the one saying that.
My partner can't even
come onto the floater!
I'm waiting!
Just wait!
I'm sorry.
You've never been on the floater?
The game ends before
I can even get to the floater...
[It's a funny story
but it's sad for them...]
People don't know, but Suk Jin is
actually having a deadly battle.
[A big match, the pool vs. Big Nose.]
A battle within himself.
Everyone, it's now time
for a couple dance.
Everyone's makeup is
slowly wearing off.
Hyun Jin as well.
But they are still pretty.
- There's no difference.
- Do you know what's scary though?
Hae Ryung still has the full makeup.
No, her makeup wore off.
We'll do a quick test to see
if the couples are a good match.
The mountains or the sea?
- The mountains!
- The sea!
Black bean noodles
or spicy noodles?
- Spicy noodles!
- Black bean noodles!
Summer or winter,
one, two, three!
- Summer!
The mountains or the meadow,
one, two, three!
- The mountains!
Summer or winter,
one, two, three!
- Summer!
They planned it ahead of time!
I'll give you another chance.
He never loses even
for this kind of stuff!
Look, her makeup wore off.
I want to try hard, but I can't.
No one thinks of me as a target.
Now, it's the couples' dance time!
We'll take a look at the couples
- and we'll pick the order.
- That's important!
Is it clear?
[Glare.]
I'll give you the order.
You have to do your best.
[Couple dance, round three.]
The music is great.
Jump, jump!
[This depends on getting a head start!]
[First up is Suk Jin and Hae Ryung.]
[Gross]
Go back in!
Why?
[Too cloy.]
[Best friend couple,
Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin.]
[Sorry, Kwang Soo.]
Go back in!
[Full of energy,
Ha Ha and Ye Eun.]
[Perfect match]
[A couples' shake dance.]
Come this way.
[A beneficial spot.]
[The handsome couple,
Ji Hyo and Sang Woo.]
Go over there!
[The children's dance for
track and field day in the 70's.]
[The healthy couple,
Jong Kook and Irene.]
[Reveal]
[He got a good spot
thanks to his six pack.]
[He called himself up to the stage.]
[Perfect match.]
[I can't handle it.]
[Ji Hyo and Sang Woo's re-attempt.]
[They earned third place
with the fitness style dance.]
[Suk Jin and Hae Ryung's
never-ending attempt.]
Go to the end!
[Is this not good enough yet?]
Third place!
[The last one standing,
Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin.]
- Do you know how to do the collapse?
- How am I supposed to do that?
[The whistle blew at the
same time he fell.]
[There's no time to be in pain!]
[Love Island, round three starts!]
[This is the last chance!]
[The last speed battle.]
[The ultra-speedy dive.]
[Except one person...]
Hae Ryung!
[Hurry and jump...]
[Sorry, I don't think I can handle it.]
[In a flash]
Push him, push!
[Jump.]
You need to push him!
[He takes advantage of the chaos]
[and lifts up Irene!]
[But he fell into the water.]
[Ji Hyo and Sang Woo also fell.]
That was close.
[Now Kwang Soo, Hyun Jin
and Ha Ha, Ye Eun are left.]
[Kwang Soo lifted up Hyun Jin first.]
[If they wait three seconds,
they will win.]
- Were Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin faster?
- Yes.
Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin win!
[They win by a split second.]
[Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin
get third place.]
That was really close.
Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin!
[I'll do well on the next mission!]
[I wish the next mission
is an individual match...]
[Third place, Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin.]
You are given 30 minutes
to melt your ice.
- You have 20.
- And Kwang Soo.
- We have 10 minutes!
- The rest of you
- will keep your ice in the cooler.
- Let's go!
[No one is awkward with
each other anymore.]
[First mission, complete.]
[♪We'reFreindsNow]
[♪BigNoseSank]
[♪SorryHaeRyung]
[That summer vacation, episode two.]
[What kind of mission will this be?]
We're here, Hae Ryung.
- Cooler...
- The cooler?
Oh, the ice is inside!
It's so cold!
The teams that have won
1st to 3rd place.
- Yes?
- The team that placed first
will take their ice out
and place it over there.
Yes!
- That's a relief.
- It's freezing!
Don't break it.
If it breaks, that's the end of it.
The sun's facing this way.
Shouldn't we move it slightly?
Sir
please take good care of it.
It's okay.
[Now it's Jae Suk and Hana's turn.]
Thank you very much.
- Don't touch it!
- I'm not touching it.
Don't touch it!
I'm just checking it!
I'm just checking if
it's placed correctly!
Now it's Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin's turn.
- You have 10 minutes.
- Please take care of it.
Please time it well.
Kwang Soo, go touch it!
[Sneak.]
Kwang Soo, please come here.
[Slurp.]
I kissed it.
[Poor ice.]
First place gets 30 minutes,
second place gets 20 minutes
and last place gets 10 minutes.
We'll put it back in the
cooler after the correct time.
- Yes.
- We'll now do the second mission.
The second mission is
'When we go on vacation.'
It's a memory game.
When you go on vacation
there's blank.
You need to decide a pose
related to the theme
and hold the pose
when it's your turn.
After the first couple, the second couple
needs to hold the first pose
then hold your own pose.
If you don't do the pose properly,
or if you forget
you will be eliminated.
I will give you the
theme for the first round.
The theme of the first round
is 'Lovebirds'
You can decide a pose
and come back.
Everyone, go!
We need to think of a difficult pose.
Let's go to that side, Ji Hyo.
[What poses will they show off?]
Maybe we need a few poses,
in case we have more than one turn.
What should we do?
We need to think of something
the other teams can't do.
Yes, we need difficult poses.
Can we just strike any poses?
No, it has to be something lovey-dovey.
Doesn't it have to be difficult?
Yes, difficult and lovey-dovey.
What will be...
What do we need to do?
What do lovey-dovey couples do?
I'm far from it.
But you are.
I only know this.
Just pretending to be cute.
- But that's too easy.
- We need something they can't remember.
- It should be either difficult...
- What should we do?
Or something that's too lovey-dovey.
What could it be?
Something touchy-feely...
I'm not saying we should...
It's okay, we decided
to act like siblings.
We can do it, but others can't.
We don't have many choices though.
[Hurt]
If you say so...
Should we hug?
[Should I hug you?]
[You and me...]
[we're just friends.]
[This hug...]
[can change our relationship...]
It's too much!
I can't handle it!
It's not like I like it...
[It feels uncomfortable!]
I mean something like this
can't be done with other teams.
You know I only tried it
for the game, right?
I said I've got it.
Hana, are you flexible?
- A little.
Can you...
- Put your leg around your neck.
- That, I can't.
Can you grab your leg like this?
Maybe I can put it on your shoulder.
Ugh, wait a minute!
[Back pain]
Did you fracture your pelvis?
- Did it hurt you?
- That was little hard.
Was that?
[The flexible idol is here.]
This is good.
I think Kim Jong Gook will
strike a really difficult pose.
Maybe he will hold her.
[That is true.]
[When we go on vacation,
you will see an iron man.]
[They are getting too physical.]
[It's getting annoying.]
[Suk Jin and Hae Ryung
want to counterattack.]
It seems Hae Ryung
doesn't want to do it.
What is that?
Why do you have to bend her back?
[Passionate!]
Great!
Let's do this!
It looks like Thai massage.
What should I do?
Hugging from behind won't work.
What do we do then?
What do we do so no one can't do?
[The time-out is over.]
Everyone, come back!
As you already know,
the order of your turn is important.
Who goes first matters.
Ladies will come out and play
rock-paper-scissors.
Isn't that too simple?
Just play scissors and you'll win.
- Win!
- Good luck!
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Hyun Jin, Hana, Seung Eon,
and Ye Eun played paper.]
[Blank Ji, Irene and
Hae Ryung played rock.]
Hae Ryung, I told you to play scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Blank Ji: paper]
[Irene, Hae Ryung: rock]
I told you to play scissors!
If you say that loud...
Rock-paper-scissors.
[She keeps playing rock.]
[Is it that you hate the Big-nose
or you hate scissors?]
You don't match at all.
They're going further from winning.
[Can our relationship...]
[be saved?]
Hae Ryung!
['When We Go On Vacation.']
Let's begin!
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Ha Ha's couple.
I knew they would do
something like this.
[Shocking]
How can we do that?
Wait a moment.
It's not even funny!
[The scorpion pose!]
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Ha Ha's couple
we'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
[Will she be able to do
the scorpion pose?]
[She successfully repeats the pose.]
It's okay.
Just hold on for a second.
We'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
Hey, hey, hey!
[Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin's pose...
is push-up.]
[Her legs fell.]
[Landed]
- They did three times.
- Five times!
It was three!
She fell!
It's three, then.
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Ha Ha's couple
we'll see Hyun Jin's couple
we'll see Seung Eon's couple.
We'll see Kwang Soo's couple!
[They held the first pose.]
[They held the second pose.]
We'll see Gary's couple!
[What will be their pose?]
[Surprised]
Wow, she can do that?
[The bridge!]
[I'm very sorry.]
It's the easiest one for us.
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Ha Ha's couple
Do Ha Ha's couple's pose.
[They held the first pose.]
We'll see Kwang Soo's couple!
You feel numb, right?
[She's screaming inside.]
Hana is holding her pelvis...
One...
Why are you...
Is she heavy?
The next.
We'll see Gary's couple!
The third pose.
The bridge.
That's right, Hana.
Great!
You did it!
[They held the third pose.]
We'll see Jae Suk's couple!
Hana, come over here.
Are you okay?
[Deep bow]
[His weak legs!]
They failed!
Does the fall include?
Yes, our pose include the fall.
- The fall is part of it.
- What?
It's part of it?
Look, you're supposed to fall
and casually get up.
- Again.
- What is that?
They're so shameless.
Clap your feet five times.
Don't make up stuff now!
What are you doing all of a sudden?
- This is it.
- Doesn't it count as two?
- Squat five times.
- Just do one thing!
We'll cancel the previous movement.
One, two, three, four!
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Ha Ha's couple.
- Can Ji Hyo do it?
- I don't think she can.
I did it!
This is right!
That looks totally different.
Show her.
[High-rise building vs.
One story house.]
Ye Eun is a little annoying.
She said in a cute voice.
'This is it.'
Even the tone of speaking is different.
[A baby-sounding tone vs.
Passionate tone]
Excuse me, old lady!
We'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
Sang Woo is shaking.
His legs are very thin.
We'll see Gary's couple.
I don't think she can.
Don't push yourself!
- Your hands are wrong.
- The other way.
Why did you do this pose?
- Why?
- I'm sorry.
She can do it.
- Like this?
- She did it.
I started clapping for some reason.
Ji Hyo did it.
I was cheering her from my heart.
We'll see Jae Suk's couple.
[Charge!]
He did what I did.
This is exactly what I did.
Very good!
One, two, three, four, and five!
One, two, three...
- four, five.
- He's doing it too lightly.
Anyway, they did it.
We'll see Sang Woo's couple.
- We'll see Sang Woo's couple.
- It's easy.
What is their pose?
(Children's play: Little husband)
[Embarrassing]
This is hard.
[I can't take it sober.]
It's too hard.
We'll see Sang Woo's couple.
This is too much!
[After the four physical challenge,
they have to face a mental challenge.]
[Mr. Capable couple's turn.]
[The most powerful, Mr. Capable
and former volleyball player, Irene.]
- Can Irene do the pose 1?
- She's doing it.
She's flexible.
Look, he's doing it properly.
[She's doing the bridge easily.]
[Look at this couple...]
One, two, three, four.
You need to look at each other's eyes!
[They cleared the fifth state easily.]
We'll see Jong Kook's couple.
Wait a minute.
[She sits on his shoulder.]
[Pale]
You need to use one hand.
[How could I possibly...]
Bye-bye!
See you next time, Hae Ryung!
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Ha Ha's couple.
[The first, scorpion pose.]
That's good!
[She does it easily.]
When we go on vacation
- We'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
- This vacation won't last long.
Bye!
[When everyone thinks it's over...]
[I can't end it like this!]
[I will make up
for the previous games.]
[Just trust Big-nosed brother!]
[Plop]
[Stop dreaming!]
[I feel so bad for Hae Ryung.]
Please give them one more chance.
- One more time.
- Sit on his upper back.
That's right.
It's better.
He's not really doing a push..
He did it.
[Fall]
Hae Ryung, come back next time.
Try come back for another time.
You should have won
rock-paper-scissors.
We prepared so many poses.
One team is dropped,
so it makes six teams.
We will have three winning teams,
so three more teams will be dropped.
We'll change the theme.
The second round's theme is
'The Model Couple.'
- It's a pose, right?
- Yes.
You can discuss it now.
Can you give us
cross stitches materials?
So we can kill our time.
- This one's okay.
- This one and...
Like that, and I can
hang on to your legs.
- Is that okay?
- Yes.
I don't think other guys can do this.
It's good enough.
- Are you flexible?
- No, I'm not.
Should I do splits?
You can do splits...
- I did it.
- Then I will...
you can grab here or
do something behind my back.
I'll do the nike kick and turn.
Then, I'll do this.
Wait, this is too hard.
- Let's do this one first.
- The time-out is over.
I feel so bad for Hae Ryung.
[The first and second winners'
ice hearts are still in the sun.]
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Kang Gary!
[Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Ha Ha: rock]
[Gary, Sang Woo, Jong Kook: scissors]
Jong Kook, your luck is not so great.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Gary and Hwang Seung Eon is the fourth.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Jong Kook and Irene: the fifth]
[Ji Hyo and Do Sang Woo: the sixth]
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Kwang Soo and Seo Hyun Jin: the first]
[Jae Suk and Park Hana: the second]
[Ha Ha and Ye Eun: the third]
I think it's not so bad be the third.
Please stand on the R mark.
This is 'the Model Couple.'
One, two, three, four!
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
- What is it?
- Hey, hey!
She's so flexible.
It might be finished early.
[Are you talking about me?]
He can't hold his pose.
[Fall]
[I looked very casual.]
Is that it?
Show us properly.
- Hurry up.
- What are you doing?
- Please twist my legs.
- You can't help him!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
You said you can do it.
He's disqualified!
[Surprised]
This isn't right!
I'll give you one more chance.
- You should hold a pose for 5 seconds.
- Just hold any pose.
Let's hold all the pose
for five seconds.
This is too hard.
Am I the last one?
[Ta-da!]
[Safety comes first.]
- What is that?
- Good job!
[Kwang Soo and Seo Hyun Jin's
turn is over.]
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
I think she can do it.
- Wow!
- Wait!
Hana!
Just do it quickly.
That's right!
- Hurry up, Jae Suk!
- Did you forget?
Don't tell him.
Put one knee on the ground.
One, two, three, four, and five!
Hana!
[My pelvis!]
Hana, you should stay home for a while.
Cancel tomorrow's schedule!
Her pelvis is...
Isn't it too much?
[Is this hard?]
[A taste of hell]
That's like splitting the pelvis!
You did well, Hana.
Should I bring you a screwdriver?
Do I need to tighten
some screws of yours?
- Are you okay?
- Show us your pose!
One, two, three!
[Ta-da!]
What is that?
[Does it supposed to be
an elegant pose?]
Her fingers are pointing down.
[They held the overhead kick pose.]
Very good, Hana.
[Ha Ha and Ye Eun's turn to
reveal their pose.]
We'll see Ha Ha's couple.
- What are they doing?
- One!
One, two...
Is this for getting rid of Jong Kook?
They did it!
[The female has to carry the man
on her back and squats 5 times.]
Amazing.
[Gary and Hwang Seung Eon's turn]
When we go on vacation,
we'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
She's flexible, too!
Why come everyone can do this?
I know one person that can't do this.
Everyone except Ji Hyo can.
You'll see Jae Suk's couple!
[The second pose, overhead kick]
[She looks comfortable.]
You made it.
We'll see Ha Ha's couple!
[We'll be in trouble
if they can do it.]
It's five squats!
Wait!
[Just doing it once
will make her fall.]
They should not be able to do this!
It's over!
Stop it!
[It's exciting!]
Stop it, Jae Suk!
[You've worked hard, Gary.
It's time to leave!]
- Wait a second.
- One...
two...
[Landing]
[Gary and Hwang Seung Eon drop.]
[Thanks to you, we're survived!]
We survived!
Do you want to see her pose?
Seung Eon, come here.
Show them.
Why did you make us drop?
- You must see her pose.
- Show us.
I was going to turn
something like this.
[Rotate]
[Her wrist turns 360 degrees?]
[What is going on here?]
[Shocking!]
We could have finished them.
- What was that?
- Can we show it on TV?
- Why not?
- If you can show this.
Don't you have any skill like this?
[The third round]
[Hana and Jae Suk are dropped.]
The next theme is 'creepy couple.'
I'll give you three minutes.
If anyone can make
their eyes exotropia, they will win.
You could have used your pose
for this topic.
It's too bad!
I was watching 'The true game.'
Someone said she's in
the Guinness Book of Records.
I just did it and thought
what's so special about it?
How is it possible?
I feel really sorry for Hae Ryung.
Please show her reactions on TV.
Even on the floating mat...
she waited for me
for the whole time.
Then I couldn't even do one push-up.
I feel really bad because...
I asked if she can do stretches.
She can do it all.
Can she?
[It rips my heart apart.]
She can do all of it.
I feel sorry, too.
[A bad memory of a big-nosed man.]
[The time-out is over.]
Please come back!
They just need to make one team fail.
[They will play rock-paper-scissors.]
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Hyun Jin and Blank Ji: paper]
Irene, Ye Eun: rock]
[Jong Kook and Irene: the third]
[Ha Ha and Ye Eun: the fourth]
[Maybe playing later
is better now.]
- Is Ha Ha's couple last?
- Yes, they are.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Kwang Soo and Seo Hyun Jin: the first]
[Ji Hyo and Do Sang Woo: the second]
We'll start now!
One, two, three, four!
When we go on vacation
Kwang Soo's couple.
I'm nervous.
What are they going to do?
They always sit down.
[They look like circus crews.]
- She has to hold him?
- Can you actually do it?
- Are they deciding now?
- They're fighting.
What are you doing?
- Is it your first time?
- I don't want to give up!
I'm scared!
Usually, female starts on the top.
Think carefully.
You're only here because of Hyun Jin!
- He told me to roll, but...
- Be quiet!
Can you actually do it?
He wants to roll?
[If they succeed...]
[no one will be able to do it.]
[A head shot on the ground]
This is it?
What is that?
Kwang Soo!
Just do the split.
All of a sudden, do the split again?
When we go on vacation,
you'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
- That is creepy.
- How about a center split?
Just worry about your couple.
- I feel so bad for them.
- Just take care of Hae Ryung.
I'm so sorry, Hae Ryung.
[Kwang Soo's support]
[Another try for the twisted legs]
He twisted twice.
What's that?
- It has to be twice.
- This is it.
- Wait.
- Do you have another one?
[one eye squint.]
It's just one eye!
- What do we do?
- That's great.
What did he do with his legs?
You twist your legs twice.
Jong Kook can't do it.
Jong Kook's thick muscle
prevents him from doing it.
When we go on vacation,
you'll see Kwang Soo's couple.
It's going to be hard.
Ji Hyo can't do a split.
Do you need my help?
Ji Hyo is upset.
Wow!
Why are you screaming?
Don't lie.
That's too much support!
If you look at her from behind.
She's just doing this.
- No! I'm not!
- It's not exactly like that.
Come see her from behind!
Or use the helicam.
You can't compare her
with someone who practices yoga.
That's right.
I haven't tried yoga.
Even if we let her pass,
if Sang Woo can't make the squint eye.
No one can do it.
It's easy to squint with both eyes!
But one eye squint is hard!
Let Ji Hyo pass.
[Center split+leg twist
+one eye squint]
Check his eyes.
Did he do that?
- I did it.
- He did it.
- Should I pull your legs?
- No.
- Just a little.
- Hey, Kwang Soo!
She did it!
[She needs to hold it for 5 seconds.]
Ji Hyo made it.
Hurry up!
[Ji Hyo and Do Sang Woo fail.]
We're relieved.
Ji Hyo did it very well today.
I don't practice yoga.
You should let it pass!
You try!
[Why me?]
You, try!
[Gangster Ji Hyo returns.]
- Ji Hyo.
- Mr. Kim Jong Kook!
I understand.
This is how you do it?
Kwang Soo's couple is winning.
We should have gotten rid of Kwang Soo!
To get rid of Kwang Soo,
we need to play this game.
But I was going to fail next.
We feel very uncomfortable.
[We've already lost,
do we have to listen to them?]
Look at us.
Look at me and Hae Ryung!
Why do they talk about it for so long?
Hae Ryung, they will show you
when you react to other people.
We're so sorry!
Why don't you try?
[Let's go to the next mission site!]
[Episode 2 during the vacation]
[Episode 3 during the vacation]
[The third mission of 'Love vacation.']
Are we going to get
some cream on our faces?
Isn't that the whipped cream game?
Ji Suk Jin almost won this game.
That's right, I remember.
That's whipped cream?
What is that?
[The full packaged summer vacation]
They put some balls in the water.
Kwon Ryul is enjoying the bubble bath.
You must be rich.
[It's really nice.]
What is this?
Are we going to take a bubble bath?
The third mission is the pool party.
This place is designed
for pool parties.
It's a party pool.
I host pool parties every other week.
You?
You don't even host
your birthday party.
[It's party time!]
One person sits on the cream machine.
The other person goes into the pool.
Search and pick up the ball
with the color I say.
You will win when you put the ball
in the donut pool float
in front of your partner.
Except that couple, everyone will
have the cream on their faces.
During the first round, guys will sit
on the cream machine.
Hana!
Hana is the one and not two.
Eon is Eon and it's not Non.
- Hana, you can do it!
- Good luck, Seo Hyun Jin!
- Hana!
- Hae Ryung!
We've done nothing so far!
We need to win this!
[Hae Ryung has to believe in herself.]
For those of you who
one the previous round
we'll give you the better reward
because the sun is not out.
We'll put some water
in your coolers.
[For 15 minutes!]
It so unfair!
That's too much!
It will melt the whole ice!
Stick to the original plan!
[The ice and the water's
blind date for 15 minutes.]
[How much will the ice
melt in the water?]
You need to find... green balls!
- Let's go!
- Hae Ryung!
Hae Ryung!
[Splash!]
[Let's party!]
[Find the green ball.]
- Hae Ryung!
- Hana!
[Are they in the middle of
photo shoot?]
[Throbbing]
[The photo shoot is over.]
[It's like a blind test.]
It's here!
It's over here, Seung Eon!
Get the green!
[The green ball under the bubble...]
[is right next to her feet!]
[Ji Hyo dives in!]
[Ji Hyo acquires the green ball!]
Ji Hyo caught it!
Ji Hyo!
[She drops Ye Eun and shot!]
[The ball is heading
to the donut pool float.]
[They couldn't win the previous games.]
[No goal!]
[I missed it!]
Try to look for it under the water.
Run as soon as you grab it!
[Irene found a green ball.]
[Irene's shot!]
[Former volleyball player Irene...]
It's too short!
Just crawl up!
What are you doing, Hae Ryung?
[Under the bubbles,
Hyun Jin catches a green ball.]
[But Hana is standing
right in front of her.]
Steal it, Hae Ryung!
Hyun Jin, no!
Don't let her throw the ball.
Wait a minute!
Kick them with your knee!
Let me get out for a second.
Hey, let me...
What are you doing, Seung Eon?
[She is searching for the ball
by herself.]
Where are you, Ji Hyo?
[Ji Hyo is surrounded by the bubbles.]
Look at her!
She caught one.
Irene has it.
[Go to the right!]
[Hyun Jin jumps.]
[Grabs]
- That's right!
- Hyun Jin!
[Irene attempts to
get out of the pool.]
[Give me the ball before you leave.]
[The ladies' powerful party.]
[Founders, keepers.]
Great, Ye Eun!
Dunk shot!
[I don't want to get
the cream on my face!]
[What a passionate vacation!]
[Who will the lucky guy
that will avoid the cream?]
[Ye Eun wins.]
[Ha Ha and Ye Eun's ball is in.]
[Head shots!]
[The summer facial massage!]
Very good, Ye Eun!
[The first winner of the pool party.]
[Totally exhausted]
[I don't think I can win this round...]
I'm sorry, Sang Woo!
It's okay, Ji Hyo.
It happens.
Kwang Soo!
[Is he happy to be touched?]
[The cream hit Yoo Hyuk's nose.]
Hae Ryung, you're doing it on purpose?
We're out of this now.
[I'm going to win this
no matter what!]
[The second round of the pool party.]
This is for the second place.
Kwang Soo!
[Everyone is cheering their partners.]
I feel sorry for Hae Ryung.
[She's ready for the cream.]
Hae Ryung already gave up.
This time...
there are only three balls in the pool.
And the color of the balls is pink.
I will stay dry.
Ready... go!
[Dive in!]
[He grabbed it but lost it.]
I can see it!
[I'm not afraid of the bubbles!]
[I'll get the second place!]
[The guys are very enthusiastic.]
- It's really hard to see.
- It is!
Where is the pink ball?
Don't talk, just come!
I can't see!
[Yoo Hyuk dives with his eyes open.]
[The bubbles swallowed the pink balls.]
I can't see it!
[Did he get the pink ball?]
[His cover-up strategy worked!]
[There is no one to stop him!]
[He goes straight
to the donut pool float.]
I did it!
- It's a red ball!
- It's red!
Is this a red ball?
[This is the pink ball
he's supposed to get.]
That is red!
You surprised me!
[He goes back to the pool.]
[It's embarrassing.]
[They can't find the pink balls.]
That's red!
We all have color-weakness!
[Mr. Capable gets the ball first.]
[No one figured it out.]
[I need to finish it in one breath!]
[I need to block him...]
[He concealed it perfectly.]
[Mr. Capable puts the pink ball in.]
[The cream goes on their face!]
[To be with Mr. Capable or not
makes the difference.]
That monstrous...
[Jong Kook and Irene
get the second place.]
[We could have won it.]
[It feels like we're in a cake shop.]
I couldn't see any of the pink.
Because you're not
wearing your glasses.
You should have seen
Jae Suk's face before.
It was over here.
- Is this red?
- It's red.
Are you okay?
Jae Suk is acting strange!
Just wear your glasses.
[Ten minutes passed.]
[The last round of the pool party.]
Please let me win once.
You will have to get two colors.
You need to put a yellow ball
and a blue ball.
That's too hard!
Why are you so mean to us?
Once the ball goes in,
you can't take it out.
The couple with two balls
will get the third place.
[Go away!]
Hana, I'll win this time!
It's yellow, not green!
[They found a yellow ball.]
It's yellow!
Don't lose the battle!
I love you, Kwang Soo!
Do you mean it?
Kwang Soo takes it as a yes.
We're just friends.
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Go, frog fingers, go!
Good luck, God Yoo!
Hana, just wait for me!
Go, Kang Gary!
Let us win once!
I'll make your dream come true!
Isn't this sad?
I'm sorry, Hae Ryung...
Let's begin!
[The pool party, third round]
Yellow and blue.
Get ready!
Set, go!
[Fall!]
[Except Big-nose, everyone dives in.]
Suk Jin is the goalkeeper.
[Grab this blue ball...]
[Kwang Soo finds a yellow ball.]
[Splash!]
Suk Jin is telling on Kwang Soo!
[Kwang Soo approaches
to the goal.]
[Jae Suk has two balls!]
Look at Jae Suk!
[Only if he can put them...]
[Giraffe leaps at once.]
[Catch him!]
[He gives up on his shorts
and gets the goal.]
[The yellow ball is in!]
Block Jae Suk!
[I won't make the same mistakes again.]
Jae Suk!
[This is my only chance!]
[I need to block him!]
[Jae Suk goes back to the pool.]
[The partners fluctuate
between hopes and fears.]
- He will win.
- Block him!
[Gary goes into water
and gets a blue ball.]
[Sang Woo disappears in the bubbles.]
[Gary holds the blue ball
and runs.]
[Big-nose is having a battle
with Jae Suk.]
[When everyone is concerned
about their own balls...]
[Sang Woo goes through
the thick bubble wall...]
[Do Sang Woo appears!]
[He casually walks to
the donut pool float...]
[and puts the yellow ball
and the blue ball.]
[Ji Hyo and Do Sang Woo
get the third place!]
[The last four recipients]
[It's a pleasant sound that
wraps up the pool party.]
Hana, you look funny at least.
Was that me?
[Just give up like me
and you'll be peaceful.]
[Ji Hyo and Sang Woo
finally wins a game.]
Suk Jin didn't even get one.
Hae Ryung, sorry for today.
Jae Suk wears glasses
then he says it's red.
He regained his health.
It has melted so much!
It's melted!
Good, good.
Hyun Jin!
We need to start
the final mission quickly.
- Our ice is this small!
- Really?
[Who will get the key
during the final mission?]
[♪BubbleParty]
[♪YeEunTheStrongest]
[♪HaeRyungWeSuck]
[The hottest couple
during the vacation.]
[The seven couples' coolers
are in a row.]
This is it.
They're space heaters!
[The reward of the third mission]
I wonder how big
Hae Ryung's ice is.
We have a brand new ice heart.
As Ha Ha and Ye Eun won the first place
you can melt your ice with
the fan heater for five minutes.
Jong Kook and Irene
can melt it for three minutes.
I'm sorry, but the second and
the third place are different...
Yes, I know.
The third couple...
Your temper is very hot.
Can use the fan heater for two minutes.
Five minutes, three minutes
and two minutes.
After they used the fan heater,
you can all take out your ice.
Ha Ha and Ye Eun,
please take out your ice.
[The first winner
of the last mission]
- It's pretty thin!
- We'll turn on the timer now.
After five minutes,
the ice will be gone.
- It's over.
- I'm sorry.
They're so close.
I think the key will be out
before we take out our ice.
Jong Kook could have
taken out the key already.
With his finger, he can lift it.
[They're all gathered
around the heater.]
- Move aside.
- I want to warm up.
- It's pretty cold.
- This is for the ice.
Now, take out your ice, Jong Kook.
What if they key is out?
- Jong Kook's key is deep inside.
- It's true.
Watch if Jong Kook press it
with his thumb.
- He is pressing it!
- Don't do that!
The key is standing vertically.
What are you doing with your mouth?
She's melting it with her breath.
It's the first time
for Ji Hyo's couple.
- Take it out.
- Look, it's the same.
That's the ice age.
[It is preserved well.]
It's still in the ice age.
Jong Kook, please don't touch it.
- I'm just holding it.
- Your body heat!
- I'm just holding it here.
- Think of your body heat!
I'm just going to hold it.
I think the time is up.
Our ice is brand new.
Ji Suk Jin's ice is like
a frozen cloud from interstellar.
The ice age and
the interstellar.
He never once took it out.
I think Ha Ha will make it.
Their key is near the surface.
I'm so sorry.
In 10 seconds,
the fan heaters will be off.
- Let's do it!
- Nine, eight, seven...
six, five, four, three...
two, one!
[Get the key in the ice!]
Turn off the fan heater.
Okay, let's do this!
[What a tiny ice!]
[We can win this!]
We're doomed.
[Heavy]
What's this?
Put the lid on.
[It's too heavy to hold it.]
Flip the lid.
Where is the key?
It's so cold!
[Show me the power of Mr. Capable.]
[What do we do?]
[Are they planing?]
[Will it be Ha Ha's ice...]
[or Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin's
smallest ice?]
[It's neck to neck.]
[Ha Ha and Ye Eun's key
is about to reveal.]
- This is it!
- Where is it?
[Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin
acquire the key.]
[They will win when
they find the matching lock.]
What's going on?
It's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo must have gotten the key.
- Kwang Soo has the key.
- Does he?
[But he can't find the lock.]
It's the wrong box.
[We can't give up!]
[Ha Ha and Ye Eun gets the key.]
[Did he open the box?]
[It ain't over 'til it's over.]
- You opened it.
- He opened it.
[Unlocked!]
We won!
[Kwang Soo and Seo Hyun Jin
are the final winners!]
We won!
Yes!
I just got the key...
- It's over.
- I just got it.
[Kwang Soo and Hyun Jin
were one step ahead.]
[The atmosphere turned ugly
as soon as they won.]
No one congratulates for us.
We're far from winning.
We were close!
[The benefits of the previous mission
were the driving force of the result.]
[Ten minutes under the sunlight.]
[Melting in the water for 15 minutes]
[Their ice got small
and it lead them to win.]
The final winners are
Kwang Soo and Seo Hyun Jin!
- Lee Kwang Soo...
- Kwang Soo won.
- The prize is...
- Just give them some ice.
Give them an expensive ice sculpture!
Eat some fruits!
Eat lots of fruits!
[Depressed Kwang]
[Everyone else is happy to see
the fruit baskets.]
Isn't that what we used
at the beginning of the show?
As expected, that producer is cheap.
I heard the prize is gold.
Am I wrong?
Not today?
Eating apples in the morning
is like eating gold.
Yes, eat it in the morning.
- Eat the gold.
- It's very nice.
Here's a golden kiwifruit, too!
[Everyone is congratulating them.]
Kwang Soo, you've worked so hard.
Anyway, today's winners are
Hyun Jin and Lee Kwang Soo!
[Now, they're officially
congratulating.]
[They are cool and attractive
like a vacation!]
[Hope you keep rolling!]
[An invitation for
a mysterious game...]
[And... Girls' Generation disappeared!]
Tetris!
[Have the girls been
trapped in the game?]
[Working as game pieces
in Tetris game.]
[Desperate effort for escape!]
[The girls are tougher and uglier!]
- Who did it?
- I don't know.
It's like a zombie game!
- I'm so scared.
- They're running toward us!
[Will they be able to
get out of the game?]
I want to escape!
'Welcome to the game world.'