[Yoo Jae Suk]
[Ji Suk Jin]
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Gary]
[Ha Ha]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Park Seo Joon]
[Son Hyun Joo]
[A Kidnapped Actress:
The Secret of a Fake Detective]
Did you receive the
invitations I sent you?
Are you joking?
What invitations?
Just call us from now on.
I see you're wearing baseball caps,
but I always wear...
Are you serious?
You don't know anything.
You look like Yoda.
The world renowned detectives
carry this around.
These days, detectives wear
snapbacks.
I can't work with these
novice detectives.
You're the best private
detectives in Korea.
That's right.
Before I request
any investigations
I've also invited
two famous detectives.
- We have enough detectives.
- Do you think we're not capable?
You underestimate us!
Are they detectives, too?
Please, reveal yourselves!
[Shocked!]
[Out of the table...]
Wow, you came out of the table?
[Legendary detective, Son Hyun Joo]
- I'm startled!
[Handsome and hot, Park Seo Joon]
- The space was too small!
[Blank Ji and Gary
bounced out of shock.]
How long were you inside there?
[Welcome, Detective Son
and Detective Park!]
Climb over it!
[They successfully surprised
the members...]
[but they can't get out.]
- This way!
We've been there for about
10 minutes.
My knees hurt.
What did you talk about?
Running Man always
gives me a hard time.
- You won last time.
- You've gone through a lot.
I remember that.
[Crawling under the table.]
[Detective Son also crawled inside.]
Don't touch this.
They're coming in!
[It seems like they're waiting
for a punishment.]
[By the way, when are we
going to go out?]
[After 10 minutes...]
Running Man gave me
a hard time before.
[It's tiring to wait like this.]
[In sync]
- One, two, three!
[Heading!]
It's so tiring!
[Detective Son is extremely serious.]
You've won the race last time.
I brought the ring of power.
[The ring of power, winning prize
from the previous game.]
You brought this.
I want to win again.
That's incredible.
You have thin fingers.
It's the first time.
You're the first one wearing the ring.
These two detectives will
help investigate this case.
I won't tell you the mission now.
You'll be listening to it through cellphones.
Because we're detectives.
- Maybe we'll get different cases.
- There's got to be something.
I'm an expert on this.
It's getting interesting today.
- It's been a while.
- Very interesting.
[What is the mission that
the nine detectives will receive?]
Reporting crime!
A famous actress is kidnapped.
Is anyone out there?
Please save me!
You, a private detective...
should find the hostage
and rescue her quickly.
By the way...
there are detectives that don't
know this rule amongst you.
From their headsets,
this rule is not playing.
If you look around
there will be someone
who looks puzzled.
[Grin]
[Gaze]
[Poke]
[What?]
The fake detectives won't know the rules
and have to guess during the race.
There will be hints of the
whereabouts of the actress.
To figure out
who the fake detectives are
and how many of them there are
you will need to win the missions
to obtain a hint about them.
Reveal who they are
and get the final hint from them.
The first one to solve the final hint
and rescue the hostage
will win this race.
[Find out who the fake detectives
who didn't hear the rules are!]
[The fake detectives have the final hint
about the actress's whereabouts!]
This is a psychological warfare!
There was a really obvious member.
Can I just reveal
the fake detective now?
I don't know what's going on...
Is everything a secret?
There is someone
who doesn't know the rules.
Those who know the rules
and the 'quick-witted' detectives
who don't know the rules
will carry out the missions together.
[The quick-witted detective
will be revealed now.]
From now on, don't make it obvious
and listen carefully.
Today, you will
not be given any rules, whatsoever.
[Quick-witted detective, Song Ji Hyo.]
Today, you mustn't
let the others know
that you don't know the rules.
You must complete
the missions until the end.
[Don't get caught!]
There is one other detective
who also doesn't know any
of the rules.
[Another fake detective?]
If someone seems puzzled,
he could also be a fake detective.
If you win a mission, you will be given
hints about the other fake detective.
Find the other fake detective
the rules of the race,
and win the race.
[No time to lose!]
The detective who doesn't
know the rules
please keep a poker face
so you don't get caught.
I still have to guess, even though
I know the rules.
[Everyone's keeping a poker face...]
Now, we will begin the race.
Let's go!
[Trust no one...]
We have to find the one
who doesn't know the rules.
- Where are we going?
- To the next location.
I don't think Hyun Joo knows the rules.
- It's Gary and Hyun Joo.
- You listened to music, right?
[Who is the other fake detective?]
Everyone's going separately?
Let's go!
To be honest, earlier...
when everyone had their
headphones on
I was looking at the members' faces.
When I was looking at their faces
Kwang Soo was suspicious.
He was scanning at a similar time.
Gary was also a little...
[Gary's random grin.]
I'm getting nervous.
[Could it really be Gary or Kwang Soo?]
We, detectives, have a few rules.
First, be careful of when
you are alone.
When you are in the car, your expression
your eyes, and your breathing.
With that, you can be
caught immediately.
[Ha Ha, driving next to him...]
Ha Ha has the face of...
a tired father.
For sure, every time
we do stuff like this
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook are dangerous.
Right now, Gary seems like
he doesn't know.
[Yawn.]
I also think it's Hyun Joo.
He has a lot of experience,
I think he could guess and play.
The Ring of Power!
There are only a few in Korea.
The Ring of Power.
[Is he the fake detective?]
[Gulp.]
It actually has taken place,
I am at a loss.
[You're at a loss of what?]
I'm so embarrassed.
Can't you get out?
I'll film by myself.
[He wants to be alone?]
[The lord of the ring,
Detective Son arrives first.]
[All nine detectives have arrived
at the first mission site.]
[They are listening to the rules.]
[What are the rules
for the first mission?]
[Will Ji Hyo be safe even if
she doesn't know the rules?]
[Who is the other fake detective?]
Oh, we don't take turns
but we'll do it altogether.
- Starting at the same time?
- We have to watch while we run.
It'll be too obvious
if they do it alone.
That's right.
This mission is
the Random Obstacle Race.
The first obstacle is a hurdle race.
You can jump over this hurdle
but you can also run through it.
But, the last hurdle
is made of real wood
so, make sure you jump over it.
The second obstacle is a hat on a pole.
You need to wear it and finish the race.
The person wearing the hat,
and finishes the race first will win.
Dear detectives
who don't know the rules
the first mission rule
will not be given to you.
You can figure it out on your own.
You can head over to
the mission location.
Ah, this is hard.
[It's too difficult to figure
it out from this arrangement.]
- Isn't this too obvious?
[I need to find out what game it is.]
One of them will get caught this round.
Like Hyun Joo, for example.
- Just an example.
- We all start at the same time, right?
[Is Hyun Joo the fake detective?]
Now, we will start the first mission.
It will be divided into three rounds.
There will be three rounds.
The first round winner gets first place.
The 2nd round winner
gets second.
The 3rd round winner
gets third place.
Suk Jin, don't look
at other people, but me.
I was observing everyone's face.
But the Running man
members can guess easily.
It's not going to be a
normal game though!
Why are there hurdles?
As soon as you're on the field
the game will start.
You can decided where each of you
will run on your own.
Gary is warming up.
He doesn't know the rules at all.
- Gary usually warms up.
- Are you going to run, Gary?
Kwang Soo, are you sure
you know the rules?
Of course!
You're suspicious of me?
Are you sure?
Hyun Joo, please say something!
Hyun Joo, you're really weird.
He kept snooping around
when he got here.
He keeps reading others faces.
- Are you okay?
- I know everything.
I know everything.
- Why is your voice so shaky?
- Let's go!
[The other detective...]
[could it be Son Hyun Joo...?]
- Guess it carefully.
- They have to.
That's lane one, right?
I'm lane four.
[What is this game?]
We need to run
and look at other people.
Fake detectives,
you better warm up!
Kwang Soo, you talk a lot.
I feel good today.
[Whatever this game is...]
[I need to guess the rules.]
[Random Obstacle Race, round one.]
This mission
is the Random Obstacle Race.
You can jump over these hurdles
but you can also run through them.
[But Ji Hyo doesn't know that.]
[How is she going to pass?]
[Jumping hurdles.]
[Then who else doesn't know this?]
[Hesitate.]
[Everyone runs differently.]
You can jump over these
you can also run through them.
However, the last one is a real hurdle.
You can't pass through.
[Last hurdle, break or jump?]
[Jump.]
[Glance.]
[Did you break it or jump?]
[Ji Hyo hops until the end.]
[That must have hurt.]
[Two detectives aggressively passed
through the last one.]
[In the midst of all this]
[Kkuk catches the hat first.]
[He finishes the race in first place.]
[Kkuk, first round winner.]
[Excuse me,
round one is over.]
[He picks the hat like
a coconut in a tree.]
[Hyun Joo retrieves the hat,
Big Nose steals the hat.]
[KKuk secures the best hint.]
- Am I fourth?
- Suk Jin.
- Why were you crawling?
- What?
Who broke their last hurdles?
[Lane four, Jae Suk.
Lane five, Suk Jin.]
[Did they really not know?]
- Which lane?
Lane four and lane five.
[Are one of them the
other fake detective?]
Two people did it.
Are you okay, though?
- Who is it?
- It's not me.
- It was Suk Jin.
- I couldn't stop because of the inertia.
How did you even break it?
Who was it?
Why isn't your first hurdle broken?
[Lane one, Ji Hyo
Lane two, Kwang Soo.]
[Lane five, Suk Jin.
Lane nine, Gary.]
I wanted to go fast.
[They all seem suspicious.]
[It's so confusing.]
[She's observing from afar.]
- How was Hyun Joo playing?
- Why are you trying to crawl?
- My knees are weak.
If your knees are weak,
why did you only crawl once?
- You didn't know the rules?
- Of course I do.
To be honest, I thought
Seo Joon was a little suspicious.
He's usually really fast.
But he was slow today.
I think he followed me after looking.
- He could have copied!
- That's true.
He didn't start right away,
he was running behind.
I think Seo Joon doesn't
know the rules.
Also, Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo.
I don't know about Kwang Soo
but Ji Hyo is slow, so
she must have seen us.
Jong Kook, I didn't see anything!
I'm serious!
- I didn't see anything!
- I only observed Suk Jin!
He was trying to crawl under.
[I should be careful...]
Ready, set...
[The rules have already
been discovered.]
- Start!
[Now it's just competition for speed.]
[Ji Hyo breaks through the hurdles
now that she knows the rules.]
[Everyone is only running
without suspicion.]
[All the hurdles are now broken]
[except for the final hurdle.]
[Jae Suk, breaks the last one again.]
[Seo Joon heads for the hat first.]
Seo Joon figured out the rules now.
[Seo Joon grabs the hat with full speed.]
[Seo Joon, winner of round two.]
Seo Joon's done already?
Park Seo Joon gets
second place!
It's Seo Joon!
Seo Joon figured out the rules.
- It's Seo Joon.
- He ran really fast this time!
- He observed first.
- I just observed.
I just wanted to see how you ran.
[What is Seo Joon's true identity?]
How many missions are there?
What are you thinking about?
I think you're one of them for sure.
- You're faster than me.
- I don't think you know.
- I got second place in the first round.
- I have a feeling...
What do you mean?
I think it's at least one of
the guests.
That's not right.
I've watched a lot, and
even when there are guests
they weren't always the culprit.
But I'm not sure if
it's you or Hyun Joo.
Gary.
I think it's Gary.
- I think it's Gary.
- He doesn't know either.
Gary doesn't know.
Gary jumped over one of
them, at the beginning.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I saw it.
- He started later and jumped?
- Yes.
[He jumps, observes,
then passes through the hurdles?]
Gary and you are suspicious to me.
I don't think you know the rules.
- Why?
- I'm only going to look at you, now.
I'm going to start
observing them one by one.
[It's getting more and
more confusing...]
Get ready for the third round.
[Can she find the other fake detective?]
This is the third round!
The winners will receive hints.
Don't forget that.
Ready, set, go!
[At full speed.]
[Everyone breaks through.]
[This is the last chance
to receive a hint.]
[Everyone reaches their
last hurdle already.]
[Jae Suk, catches the hat first.]
[Outstanding speed.]
[Jae Suk, wins the third round.]
[It's over...?!]
- Who won?
- You have to try hard to get a hint.
- You're suspicious.
[Jae Suk is suspicious?]
- He knows the rules.
[Why is everyone suspicious?]
- He did what he could.
[You said there was only one more!]
This hint is...
[This hint is about
the fake detectives.]
Read this in the car.
- He's getting a hint about himself!
- Right.
He needs to find his partner, too.
The fake detective has to win
to cover up these hints.
That one is a lot thicker!
- Please read it in the car.
- You can't give it to Jong Kook!
[What is that?]
- It looks like a phone book.
[Stare.]
Let me see it.
Let me hold it once.
It's pretty heavy.
You can go into your cars
and check.
[What do I do?]
[Everyone's waiting in their cars.]
[Jae Suk, checks his hint in the car.]
The person is..
[The fake detective is shorter
than 185cm!]
shorter than a pole measured 185 cm!
Then it's not Kwang Soo.
[Seo Joon also checks
his hint in the car.]
[A picture of trophies?]
- Seo Joon!
- Did you check?
- The hint?
- I checked it.
- You did?
Is it crucial information?
- Is it crucial?
- No, it's more confusing.
- Is that so?
- Really?
Let's do a trade!
With the Ring of Power.
Let's do a trade.
It's tempting because
I've never won a prize.
There are only a few in Korea.
You don't want to share your hint?
No, of course not.
You've been on Running man a lot,
you've changed!
Be like that!
Hyun Joo is right, be like that!
We still have many movie
promotions to go to, together.
Why is my hint so thick?
What is this?
[A drama script?]
I've done a bit of drama...
What is this?
Is it someone who is in a drama?
Seo Joon...
[What is the meaning of this hint...?]
- Ji Hyo, you know?
- Yeah, I know now.
- You know what we're doing today?
- To be honest, I just got it.
Seo Joon, you got a hint right?
How... how is it?
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I was talking.
I can't see your face
because you're too tall.
I'm not asking you to tell me the hint.
The more you do this,
the more you become suspicious.
This place is nice.
I can't hear you.
I should hide
Kwang Soo's car over there.
I should park it at the back.
[Jae Suk plans on hiding
Kwang Soo's car.]
[Kwang Soo is still talking to Seo Joon.]
[He succeeded at
stealing Kwang Soo's car.]
[Now, let's move it far away.]
No one knows.
We'll leave it here
so that no one knows.
And I'll go back to my car.
[Jae Suk is going back to his car.]
Hurry up!
[The operation is successful.]
Children who want to be detectives...
A detective must keep an eye
on the suspect when he's alone.
Everyone, don't forget that!
[Huh?]
[Everyone is leaving Kwang Soo alone.]
[No one told them to leave,
but they communicate by telepathy.]
[Where are you going?]
What's going on?
[Where is my car?]
He can't be a detective.
He can't even protect his own car.
- Suk Jin!
- Yes?
- Open the window for a second.
- Why?
[Giraffe is making an attempt
to steal Impala's car.]
What are you doing?
[A fight between two herbivores.]
You want to drag me out?
[A drive-in theater opened up.]
He's dragging Suk Jin out.
[Satisfactory]
[The finals for the weakest Running Man.]
- Where is your car key?
Hey!
[Giraffe wins.]
[He succeeds at stealing Impala's car.]
[He's getting ready to leave.]
- Give me your car key!
Seriously...
Your car is right there!
[It's fortunate to have Suk Jin.]
[On the other hand...]
I became a mute earlier.
I couldn't say anything,
or talk to anyone.
I have no idea what's going on.
I felt so incompetent
that I couldn't figure it out.
I wonder what the hints were.
Among those who received the hints,
there might be a quick-witted detective.
It'll do a lot of damage because
Jong Kook received the best hint.
[In any case...]
[rescue the actress
locked up somewhere!]
I'm over here!
Please help!
[And the biggest hint to the rescue]
[lies in the fake detectives.]
[Who is the other fake detective?]
- Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
- Yes?
Your car doesn't have a GPS.
I won't be able to trust you
for the rest of my life!
Why did you hide my car?
So you took my car away instead?
How did you get here?
- By Kwang Soo's car.
- Did you come together?
[At the auditorium...]
[nine individual desks
and boards are ready.]
Someone who doesn't know the rules...
[What is this for?]
The title of the second mission is
'I Won't Tell You.'
Read members' faces
and guess well.
During this game,
please watch carefully
and try guessing the
other fake detective.
Go to the mission site
and do well.
What are we supposed to do here?
[Keeping a poker face]
What do you think we'll be doing?
What is this for?
During this mission,
you'll play 'Gesture Bingo.'
There are cards hidden
all over this place.
Search and bring 25 cards
under the category of movies.
When you find 25 movie cards,
take off the stickers from the cards
and put them on your bingo board.
You'll take turns being a caller.
When you call out your card
you have to strike a pose
that's same with the sticker.
The first one who completes
a row, column, or diagonal wins.
[Who is the other
quick-witted detective?]
You've heard the rules, right?
You have ten minutes.
Go!
[Go even if you don't know the rules!]
Kwang Soo, don't run!
[They need to search
for the cards first.]
[They're on a visible spot!]
[Child's Play], [The Lord of the Rings],
[Rabbit]
[You Hyuk starts searching, too.]
[Yoo Hyuk finds one.]
[The Game of Death]
- Did you find one?
- Yes.
[The news spreads quickly.]
What did you find?
There are so many cards over here!
They're all over!
They're all over and I'll take them all!
[They just collect all the cards.]
There are cards hidden
all over this place.
[They only need to collect movie cards.]
Search and bring 25 cards
under the category of movies.
[Blank Ji doesn't know the rules.
She's not collecting movie cards?]
[And collects 'push-up' card.]
[This looks good for some reason.]
[She collects 'swimming' this time.]
[Lots of them are under the
exercise category.]
[Blank Ji thinks the more is better.]
[Detective Son saw Ji Hyo.]
- How many cards are we collecting?
- A lot!
How many?
You really don't know that?
[Is he pretending that he doesn't know?]
[Blank Ji runs away to an empty room.]
Hyun Joo!
You scared me!
[Detective Son's rush!]
You can't carry them all.
I'm here to help you carry them.
You drop them all.
See?
My hand!
[He grabbed the E.T card.]
- I've got to go.
[Is he collecting them by the rules?]
[Kkuk has lots of cards, too.]
Perhaps this one...
[He threw it out?]
[At that moment!]
[Seo Joon appears!]
[And picks it up.]
[Weightlifting]
[Why did he pick it up?]
Where am I supposed to go?
Hyun Joo, you're from
the opposite side of the building.
Did you pick up all the cards
that were left on that side?
They can't take mine away here, right?
You can't steal
other people's cards here.
You know a rule that I don't know?
There was a rule about stealing?
- There wasn't?
[I was the only one stealing then?]
[I need to sort out the cards.]
- Let me help you.
- No, I don't need it.
[Go away!]
[He collected many cards
unrelated to movies.]
Why did you take the snake card?
[Does he not know the rules?]
There are lots of cards everywhere.
Are you trying to sell those?
What are you doing?
- Give me some!
[Is it better to have more?]
Look at the desk.
Please open the boards
on your desk.
The one at the bottom.
[Only the real detectives
know what this board is for.]
[This is the bingo board.]
[What is this for?]
Search and bring 25 cards
under the category of movies.
When you find 25 movie cards
take off the stickers from the cards
and put them on your bingo
board.
You'll take turns being a caller.
When you call out your card
you have to strike a pose
that's same with the sticker.
[So, I need to put
the stickers on the board.]
[Huh? A golf card?]
- Song Ji Hyo?
- Yes?
- Are you playing by the rules?
- Of course.
[I don't think she knows.]
- Don't underestimate me.
[He's outright looking.]
Hyun Joo, why are you looking at mine?
- You shouldn't look.
- I didn't look.
- It's very important.
[He keeps looking at it.]
I'll be in trouble, if you look.
[Did Detective Son complete
his own bingo table?]
Starting from Suk Jin...
- Go luck, Suk Jin!
- Give us a good one!
- It looks good!
[The first runner, Detective Big nose]
- Is this one okay?
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- I will go back!
[Big nose recreates the scene
from 'Peppermint Candy.']
[I don't have it.]
Peppermint candy!
Some pretend that they have it.
Let it go, let it go!
Isn't that from Drunken Master?
Monster!
[It's Ha Ha's turn.]
- What are you doing?
[Was there a famous scene
like this from any movies?]
- A frilled lizard!
(From Quiz Exploration-Mysterious World)
[Absurd]
[No one expected to see this.]
[Except one person...]
Didn't you just mark it?
[It's the Quick-witted Detective,
Blank Ji's turn!]
[Many people suspect her.]
[Will Blank Ji be able to
clear their doubts away?]
- That's right!
- What is it?
- Sunflower?
- Christmas?
[She made it!]
- I have the card.
[Was I wrong?]
Okay!
[My Sassy Girl]
- Hyun Woo!
That's great!
It's your turn.
[It's Detective Son's turn.]
- I have high expectations.
I wonder what he picked.
- You don't have to do that.
[Is this from Terminator?]
[Rocky]
- Rocky!
[Unexpectedly, Rocky!]
[It becomes more of a mystery.]
Wait, Bingo!
[Already?]
- Bingo!
[Did Gary understand the rules?]
Seriously?
I did it, right?
Gary is in first place.
Yes!
- Seriously?
- Already?
[Did he understand the rules?]
He finished one row?
Check this in the car.
- I wanted to get a hint.
[Second place, Kwang Soo.]
Why is mine so thin?
Is there a hint inside?
[Detective Son checks
the hint discreetly.]
Listen to the two people's
footsteps carefully.
Is that a hint?
So, there are two fake detectives...
[Is he one of them?]
What's this?
[I checked the ID,
and there's a big gap in age.]
There are two fake detectives and
between the two there's a big gap in age?
Big age gap means
Seo Joon is one of them.
[Gary's hint is in shredded papers?]
Why is my hint so complicated?
Wait, isn't this a 'S'?
It's obviously 'S.'
The names with the initial 'S'...
Song Ji Hyo
Son Hyun Joo
Park Seo Joon
Ji Suk Jin, and Yoo Jae Suk.
What kind of hint is this?
There are too many!
Ji Hyo had no idea about the rules.
When she was sorting out the cards...
it was obvious that she didn't know
it was related to movie titles.
She collected random cards.
Of course, Ha Ha was strange.
Ha Ha said something random
on purpose.
Ji Hyo actually didn't know
the rules at all.
[It's time to catch
the fake detectives!]
I was acting foolishly.
I don't know what's going on!
Because I haven't received
any of the hints.
It drives me crazy!
Very important clues are hidden on
the quick-witted Detectives.
[After reading each
others' faces all day...]
[only the final mission is left!]
[Who will be able to
rescue the actress?]
Let me introduce the rules
for the final mission.
The hostage is locked up
somewhere in the final site.
The hostage is locked up.
Anyone?
Is there anyone out there?
- Please save me!
[A beautiful actress is locked up.]
You need to get hints about
where the place is and how to excess.
The clues are hidden within the
detectives that do not know the rules.
[Quick-witted Detective, Song Ji Hyo.]
[Who is her partner?]
There are interoffice phones
all over the final location.
There's an extension number
on the phone.
Pick up the receiver with one hand
and put it on the ear
on the other side.
[Saying 'Hello, Diririririree'
will connect to the informant.]
Please tell me your name.
The informant on the other end of
the phone will give you a hint.
Please tell me the password.
'A big pork cutlet
bigger than my face.'
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Please use another phone.
[Big pork cutlet fails.]
What do you mean disconnect?
[Gary makes an attempt.]
What are you doing?
Hello, Diririririree.
Hello?
They can't hear you
if you hold it like that.
That's right.
What's wrong with you?
- Diririririree.
[Is he one of the fake detectives?]
Hello?
- Hello?
- You need to press extension first.
Do I have to?
I was in a hurry because
you suddenly came to me.
Do you know what the rules are?
Of course I do.
I don't need to explain that to you.
You're either one of the detectives
who don't know the rules
or a real...
I don't want to hear 'fool'
out of your mouth.
[You just said it yourself.]
To you, who doesn't know the rules
we will never tell you
what the final mission is.
There's another detective
that doesn't know the rules.
As the password for
the secret rendezvous
the other person will say
'I have a cramp.'
Then wet your finger and
put it on his nose.
Shout 'Sesame oil!' when you do that,
then the contact will be established.
Meet with the other
fake detective.
Together, find out the final rules
and win this race.
Is there another mission?
[Where are you, my partner?]
Why would I walk around
like this if I knew the hint?
[He doesn't know the hint?
Could it be him?]
[They found the password
on the receiver.]
Arctic Fox, what are you doing here?
I have a cramp in my leg.
[She's trying to see if anyone
notices the word 'cramp.']
[Jae Suk looks a little suspicious.]
[Hyun Joo looks very suspicious.]
That Arctic Fox.
[Jae Suk is gone with the wind.]
[Hyun Joo is obsessed with the phone.]
[Who is my partner?]
- Is that you?
- Yes.
- Is that really you?
- Yes, it's me.
- Don't stand next to it.
- It's really me.
Don't go near the picture.
There's no difference
between me and the picture.
I got a cramp in my leg.
[Did you catch the signal?]
- Did you say you have a cramp?
[Kwang Soo responds?]
[He's giving her a massage.]
[You're not the one.]
I had a cramp in my leg,
and Kwang Soo gave me a massage.
- Did he give you a massage?
[He's tying her shoelaces.]
[It's not Big-nosed Brother, either.]
[Then could it be Park Seo Joon?]
I just want to call my mom.
That's all.
Why would you call your mom
in a department store?
Wait, I got a cramp in my leg.
What's wrong?
[He's not interested.]
He's not my partner, either?
How come nobody is my partner?
[Who is the other
quick-witted Detective?]
The building has a fifth floor?
[There are two Quick-witted Detectives.
Who are they?]
[Startled]
[Look at the way
he is holding the receiver...]
- Kwang Soo.
- Did you just...
Wait, did you answer the phone?
Did you answer the phone
by any chance?
- Where are you coming from.
- From downstairs, but...
- You can use the phone.
- You looked startled.
- Was it connected?
- No, of course not.
Am I supposed to get connected?
[Wait a minute.]
- Use the phone.
Hyun Joo!
Why are you so puzzled?
What are you trying to hide so badly?
- What's the reason?
- Is something wrong?
He acted really suspicious.
- Did anything happen?
- He looked very confused when I came.
Don't mind me. Since when
did you start caring about me?
You just looked very suspicious.
I'm sorry but you were
too suspicious to ignore.
[He doesn't match with
the hint I received.]
[Is Son Hyun Joo the other
Quick-witted Detective?]
[Mr. Capable is on the same floor.]
[He found one of the phones.]
Pick up the receiver with one hand
and put it on the ear
on the other side.
[He is a normal detective
who knows the rules.]
Diririririree.
[Glance]
Rolled dried persimmons!
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Please use another phone.
Diririririree.
[Gary is not a Quick-witted Detective
but a foolish detective.]
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Then, why did you pick up the phone?
No way!
[Detective Son,
will he properly make a call?]
Hello.
Hello!
Diririririree.
[He's peeking at this
embarrassing site.]
Please give me your name.
It's Son Hyun Joo.
Please give me the password.
The spicy rice cakes are red.
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Please use another phone.
Hello?
[He's smiling.
What does this mean?]
Here's a phone away from everything.
I have a feeling that this is the phone.
I like the password.
I'm very sure this is it.
Watch carefully.
Hello.
Diririririree.
This is Ha Ha.
Please give me the password.
This time, it's the real deal.
Funny and Spicy Seafood Noodle Soup!
You are successfully connected.
From now on,
I will give you the hint.
The hint is written on
the inner soles of the detectives
who don't know the rules.
They are on the inner soles!
By the way, if you flip the inner soles
of the normal detectives
you will be ousted.
Reporting crime!
A famous actress is kidnapped.
[There are two quick-witted detectives]
[who played the race
without knowing the rules.]
[The hints are hidden within
those two detectives.]
There are cards everywhere.
[What kind of secrets do they have?]
[It turns out that the hints
were on the inner soles!]
It's awesome!
I know who those detectives are.
I'm going to win this race.
When did you put anything on it?
[Detective Ha wants
to check his own inner sole.]
I wore these all day long.
It doesn't even make sense.
It's only 0.5 mm.
When and how did they put anything?
[Do you remember?]
[You'll be ousted if you flip
a normal detective's inner sole.]
[Ha Ha is ousted by looking
at his own inner sole.]
Are you kidding me?
This is not right.
I can't follow that.
I'll win the race today.
No way!
It doesn't make sense.
No, no!
Don't come near me!
Don't try to drag me!
Let me go!
Run, Sung Yong!
It doesn't even make sense!
Why?
This is not right!
I just checked my own thing.
[Unfortunately, Detective Ha is ousted!]
Ha Ha is ousted.
- Ha Ha is ousted.
- What?
Why did he get ousted?
Ha Ha is ousted.
- Ha Ha is ousted.
- Ha Ha is ousted?
[Everyone is surprised to
hear that Ha Ha is ousted.]
- Really?
[I wonder what today's mission is.]
Please save me!
I'm over here!
[They suddenly joined forces.]
- If we can get a hint from here...
Hello.
Diririririree.
[He sounds very much like the original.]
Please give me the password.
It's burning sweet potato.
Don't press anything.
You are successfully connected.
From now on,
I will give you the hint.
He will give us the hint now!
The hints are written on the inner soles
of the detectives
that don't know the rules.
Take out their inner sole to check
the hints and rescue the hostage.
By the way, if you flip the inner soles
of the normal detectives
you will be ousted.
[I couldn't hear it clearly.]
This mission is too...
You can't use it again?
Try it.
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Please use another phone.
I think I know what it is now.
- I'll be ousted if I see the others feet.
[Jong Kook clearly understood the hint.]
I know it's Ji Hyo.
What should I do?
She's not the type
to show her feet easily.
I can't find any phones.
[Jae Suk found a phone for the mission.]
[What's going on?]
[Something is wrong.]
[Grasshopper is holding the phone
on the wrong side.]
[He's going to change his hand.]
- What's wrong?
Hello.
- Hello.
[He's not changing.]
[Something interesting is going on.]
Hello.
A chain of Vienna sausages!
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
What?
[Jae Suk is really suspicious.]
I have goosebumps now.
Was it you?
I never thought it would be you.
I'm not.
- Why?
[You think I can believe that?]
Don't act like this again.
You're not supposed to do this.
- Then what am I supposed to do?
- I can't believe this.
- It was you!
- Wait, listen to me!
Listen before you go.
- You're one of them.
- I'll be honest with you.
Seriously.
Do whatever you want.
It was you.
I feel a shiver down my spine.
[Grasshopper is the
other quick-witted detective?]
Hello.
Diririririree.
Loach soup for low temperature.
You are successfully connected.
From now on,
I will give you the hint.
The hint is written on
the inner soles of the detectives
who don't know the rules.
Take out their inner sole to check
the hints and rescue the hostage.
By the way, if you flip the inner
soles of the normal detectives
you will be ousted.
This is it.
[If Seo Joon is the quick-witted detective,
he can check his own sole now.]
The inner sole...
I have to take it from them.
[Park Seo Joon is a normal detective.]
[During the hurdle mission...]
[Seo Joon broke all the fake hurdles.]
[And jumped high only for the last one.]
I can't have two of the same,
and the card has to be about movies.
[He only picked movie cards.]
[Seo Joon kept proving that
he's not a quick-witted detective.]
[Seo Joon knew all the rules
from the beginning.]
[What he doesn't know is
who the quick-witted detectives are.]
How can I take
the inner soles of others?
It's driving me nuts.
Should I start wrestling?
[Wait for me, Quick-witted Detectives!]
[Not that long ago, he witnessed
Jae Suk's strange behavior.]
- Hello.
[This drew Kwang Soo's suspicion.]
[Also Seo Joon was watching it.]
[Yoo Jae Suk, you're very suspicious.]
- I have something to tell you.
- What is it?
[He blocks Seo Joon
without knowing the reason.]
No, don't do it.
[Capture the Grasshopper!]
Kwang Soo!
- Suk Jin!
[People who know the hint]
[and the people who don't know...]
[chase Grasshopper together.]
We need to catch him.
He's the suspect.
[When Seo Joon chases a person,
he becomes the suspect.]
[What are you doing?]
[He took his shoe.]
[Runs with the shoe.]
[Give me back my shoe!]
The mission must be taking
off my shoe.
[Hyun Joo and Kwang Soo
caught Seo Joon.]
You want it that much?
[Impregnable defense.]
[Wait, now that I think about it...]
[Detective Son was suspicious, too.]
[Is he trying to protect his partner?]
[Is that why he's protecting the shoe?]
Can I take off your shoe?
Can I take it off?
Think carefully.
Show me.
[Embarrassed]
- I can take it off easily.
- Okay.
I said I can take it off easily.
[He took it off.]
[He changed his target
at the last minute.]
[Kwang Soo ran away
with Jae Suk's shoe.]
[What's in this shoe?]
[Is he really one of the
quick-witted detectives?]
[Or could it be Son Hyun Joo?]
[Are both of them normal detectives?]
['Out' sticker is on
Detective Son's inner sole.]
[Park Seo Joon is ousted.]
[The out sticker on the
inner sole means...]
[that Detective Son is
a normal detective.]
[Detective Son knew all the rules
from the beginning.]
[He acted out to lure the
quick-witted detectives.]
[Park Seo Joon who fell
for his acting is ousted.]
[What about Jae Suk?]
[Was he also acting?]
I have a cramp in my leg, Ji Hyo.
[What does this number mean?]
[Grasshopper is the other
quick-witted detective!]
[Quick-witted Detective Jae Suk,
he was...]
You shouldn't let other detectives
know that you don't know the rules.
Carry out the mission to the end.
[Is that so?]
[No.1 - Hurdle mission]
[Hesitate]
[He followed what other detectives did.]
[He broke the last hurdle.]
- Jae Suk was running here.
I didn't break this hurdle.
I'm serious.
[He got out with an excuse.]
[That's how he hid himself.]
[No.2 - Movie Bingo]
I have no idea.
[How many should I find?]
[What am looking for?]
What's this about?
Which card is it?
Come out and show the action,
then others can answer.
[He observed what the normal
detectives were doing.]
[I know what it's about now.]
- 'Mr. Vampire!'
[Jae Suk only called out movie titles.]
[He survived at the second mission.]
I won't tell you about
the final mission, either.
I'm walking around not
knowing what it is about.
I need to make a contact.
[He found how Seo Joon was
holding the phone.]
- There should be something.
- Why?
[Seo Joon didn't show
anything more to Jae Suk.]
He was looking for
something on the phone.
There are phones with stickers.
[He found out about the
phones for the mission.]
[He was making a phone call
and got caught by Giraffe.]
[Confidently]
- Hello.
Was that you?
[He overcome the crisis
and escaped.]
[On top of that]
- I have a cramp in my leg.
Do you want me to give you
a massage?
[He must not be my partner.]
It's okay.
Suk Jin is not my partner.
[Then he witnessed something weird.]
- What am I supposed to do?
[He was touched by the scene...]
[and he casually walks to her.]
Ji Hyo, I have a cramp in my leg.
[He says the password
to Ji Hyo confidently.]
[The Quick-witted Detectives couple
have met!]
[The only thing left is...]
'Sesame oil!'
[They have successfully contacted.]
You had no idea for the whole time.
It was horrible!
Where have you been?
Isn't it narrowed down by now?
They suspect you and me.
Are you going to give us a mission?
Since you've found each other,
I'll tell you the rules.
Somewhere in the final site
a hostage is locked up.
You need to get a hint to
open the door.
There are interoffice phones
all over the final place.
There's an extension
number on the phone.
If you say the word or act incorrectly,
it won't be connected.
[Jae Suk and Blank Ji
now know the final mission.]
Hello.
Diririririree.
Please give me the password.
A wet bun with tears!
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Please use another phone.
Please give me the password.
Please give me some ice cream.
I'm sorry.
This phone will disconnect now.
Please use another phone.
[When will the quick-witted detectives
be able to get a hint?]
[Someone takes the risk of
walking with one shoe.]
What's that?
Isn't that my shoe?
My shoe...
no one is picking it up for me.
[It's self-service.]
This is sad.
You've gone through hardships.
[Let's anticipate Detective Son's
remarkable actions.]
Isn't that Jae Suk?
I don't think so.
I've been working as a
detective for 15 years.
You've been acting as a detective.
I think it's Song Ji Hyo
or Jae Suk.
- Why do you think it's not Gary?
- He's not.
I'm bad at acting.
He won last week.
I think it's one of you.
My instincts say so.
[Didn't you get a hint?]
[While the normal detectives
are guessing wrong]
[the quick-witted detectives are
searching for the phone.]
Hello.
Diririririree.
Please give me the password.
Spinach in between teeth.
You are successfully connected.
From now on,
I will give you the hint.
The hint is written on
the inner soles you're wearing.
[The inner soles?]
[She checks her inner
soles immediately.]
This is the first time
wearing these shoes.
[On the right inner sole: 61]
[On the left inner sole: Lounge]
When did they put these on?
It's unbelievable!
[That means, Jae Suk has hints
on both of his inner soles?]
[I need to meet him
as soon as possible!]
Ji Hyo!
[Great! I found Grasshopper.]
[He's only wearing one shoe.]
- There's a mission, right?
Check the inner sole of your shoe.
My hints are 61 and lounge.
It's on the inner sole.
On the inner sole.
Fifth floor?
[On the left inner sole: Fifth floor.]
- When did they put it here?
- That's what I'm saying.
- They're on both sides?
- Yes.
- There should be one.
- There must be a lounge.
[They don't have the hint
that Kwang Soo took.]
Let's go to the fifth floor.
They took the shoe.
Without a shoe...
what am I doing?
[Giraffe is still wandering
around on the third floor.]
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
Come over here.
I won't be nice if I have to
catch you.
- Pardon?
- I won't be nice if I catch you.
I'm serious, I warned you!
If I have to catch you...
If you catch him...
I will spank him 100 times.
I'll follow you forever.
Okay!
[Welcome!]
- Did you see it?
- It's not Jae Suk.
What do you mean?
Then you should have been ousted.
Please give me back my shoe.
Give me back my shoe!
There's nothing in that shoe.
Give it back to me!
- Give it back.
- Let me check the shoe.
There's nothing!
I'd rather be ousted.
I'll check and be ousted.
[Grasshopper is better
than Mr. Capable.]
You saw it, right?
I think he saw it, Hyun Joo.
He saw it.
That's why he's acting this way.
I need to catch Jae Suk again.
Let me see it.
What do you want to see?
[Grasshopper couldn't even
check the last hint.]
I don't care if I will be ousted.
Just show me your shoes.
Okay, do whatever you want.
There's nothing.
Look.
[Mr. Capable takes both
of his shoes off.]
Hurry and check.
Fifth floor?
94.
Seriously...
[Giving out two hints will be okay.]
See?
I said it'll be on the fifth floor.
[Mr. Capable is going
to the fifth floor.]
It was the fifth floor.
[Oh my, Mr. Capable is coming!]
[Alert! Mr. Capable is entering
the fifth floor!]
[Hello, the fifth floor!]
[For her, it's hell not hello.]
What a coincidence to meet him!
[Looking at his shoes.]
I'm not the one.
[Fortunately, he's not
a real detective.]
[Jae Suk finally has
a chance to be by himself.]
I saw it.
It's 94.
What's 94?
[The critical hints are the
fifth floor, lounge, 61, and 94.]
94, 94...
What's 94 mean?
How come I can't see
Song Ji Hyo around?
[Finally, his intuition is right.]
I haven't seen Song Ji Hyo.
[Meaning she's hiding something.]
[Song Ji Hyo finds something.]
[It's the lounge!]
[The lounge on the fifth floor is
detected under Blank Ji's radar.]
[R mark is there!]
[Fail]
[Ji Hyo doesn't know the
last hint, 94.]
Ji Hyo!
[I need to let her know the last hint.]
- Miss Blank!
Where did she go?
If she gets caught by Jong Kook,
that's the end.
[360 degrees rotation,
Kkuk's radar detection starts.]
94, Where could that number
be used?
[I should start moving then...]
- 94... 94...
[Someone's coming!]
[That's Detective Son
who kept guessing wrong!]
[Song Ji Hyo, you...]
What's wrong, Hyun Joo?
- What's wrong?
[Blank Ji is in danger!]
- Why are you attacking me?
- What's going on?
[Looking at the situation...]
[It's you two!]
[He rounded up the quick-witted
detectives at the end.]
Don't do this to us.
Song Ji Hyo, I haven't seen you
for the past two hours.
[Scuffle]
- Why did she take off my name tag?
- You're ousted.
[Really?]
You're ousted.
Take your name tag and go.
You'll find nothing with my shoes.
There's nothing.
- I have nothing, either.
[You really have nothing?]
And you're ousted.
- Why did you eliminate my name tag?
- I'm sorry.
[They're indeed
quick-witted detectives.]
I have 15 years of
experience as a detective.
[Pitiable]
- I'm sorry, Hyun Joo!
- The last hint was 94.
- 94?
Song Ji Hyo, where are you hiding?
What does 94 mean?
[Detective Son keeps laughing.]
[It's a speed battle now!]
[Who will rescue the actress first?]
[The hostage actress has been
locked up for more than two hours.]
[Someone unlocked the door.]
[Who are you?]
[Quick-witted Detectives,
Jae Suk and Blank Ji.]
[They have entered the lounge
on a wild dash.]
- 94!
[They entered the pin number safely.]
[It's open!]
- Who are you?
- We finally found you!
That was it!
Who are you?
[Mysticism]
- Excuse me, who are you?
- We've gone through a lot.
- Can I see your face?
We ran everywhere to find you.
Hello!
[That sounds familiar...]
[Seo Woo]
- Did you find her?
- Where did you come here?
Jong Kook!
[Detective Son comes to
see her in a hurry.]
Hello, Hyun Joo!
Release her.
[The two detectives succeed
at rescuing the actress!]
Thank you, Seo Woo.
[Thank you for being locked up.]
Hyun Joo acted like a real
veteran detective today.
No, he kept guessing wrong.
He seemed like a culprit.
Ji Hyo and I rescued the actress.
I prepared a personal gift.
She prepared a gift?
010...
[Her phone number again?]
[The firecracker cracked hysterically.]
- It scared me.
Why did you say 010?
- Why were you saying that?
- This is my day!
[010- thanks-everyone!]
Thank you for being here, Seo Woo!
Veteran detective,
Son Hyun Joo and Park Seo Joon.
Let's give them a round of applause!
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Kwang Soo!
- Congratulations on your house warming!
[Event 1. A surprise
house warming party.]
Why are you doing this?
[Event 2. A special guest
visits Kwang Soo.]
[Kwang Soo is holding our lifelines.]
[Event 3. As Kwang Soo Says.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
- I'm Lee Kwang Soo!
- Would you like to be ousted, Suk Jin?
[Of Kwang Soo, by Kwang Soo,
and for Kwang Soo!]
[Today is the day!]
See you later!
[Next week]
[Happy Kwang Soo Day!]