Running Man
Episode 236
[The Real Man]
[In this variety jungle,
power is the only way to talk.]
[The strongest men in history
are gathered here!]
[Do you want to survive?]
[Be wild like an animal.]
[This is the world that real men live in.]
The strongest men on Sunday nights
that run 365 days a year.
Hold the cool pose a bit!
[They're full of energy today.]
[The First Real Man Team,
Running Man members.]
It's hard to believe
that they debuted 17 years ago.
They're still powerful and popular.
The original beast-like idol group.
[The original beast-like idols have returned.]
[Shinhwa]
[The representative idols of Korea.]
[Their manly performance!]
[They show the result of
17 years of dancing.]
[Awesome!]
[They have no clue what
awaits them today.]
It's been a while!
[Everyone is dancing]
[But he shows his back?]
[Jun Jin's solo dance time.]
[Too much testosterone]
[He doesn't stop.]
[He finishes in a manly manner.]
I danced alone?
It was a cool and funny
performance.
[The Second Real Man Team- Shinhwa.]
All six members are here today.
Do you think you can win over
the Running Man Team?
Who's the black hole (troublemaker)
of this team?
Dong Wan was the winner last time.
My nickname is Dong-hole.
['Dong Wan the black hole' becomes
Dong-hole.]
[What a clear explanation..]
I won't disappoint you.
Dong-hole!
The third team is
one of the top idol groups
of the Korean Wave.
They are expanding their careers
in dramas and variety shows
and are still growing.
[Who are they?]
[ZE:A]
- They're ZE:A!
[We are the future icons of real men!]
Kwang Hee!
You need to come out!
[They break into the stage.]
[Kwang Hee, you don't look
like you're one of them.]
[The rest of them are dancing.]
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to sing.
[Finally, Kwang Hee gets to
dance in sync.]
[They finish the performance professionally.]
[The Third Real Man Team- ZE:A.]
Hello, Mister Kim Jong Kook.
Hello, Mister Jun Jin.
Ji Hyo ran there.
What are your thoughts
before today's battle?
- What kind of MC are you?
- I was scared.
She sounds very serious.
Don't you want to start playing?
Hyung Sik's drama is done.
It was a good drama.
You're done with a girl, too!
[Look at this man!]
[They don't know the details
but they're curious.]
[Giraffe gives us weekly news.]
Taehun participated
in a mixed martial arts match.
[An idol singer and a mixed
martial arts fighter, Taehun.]
I lost the match.
He got choked.
Taehun fractured his nose.
But he did very well.
I was so sad because he started
kickboxing to loose weight.
Other people encouraged him and
he ended up debuting as a fighter.
He was exercising to the beat at first.
They encouraged him
so he got beat up.
When the entertainers learn them,
trainers always encourage us.
Jong Kook almost debuted as a boxer.
Jong Kook is really good at boxing.
Too bad! I should have seen
him getting beat up.
[It's fun to imagine Kkuk as a boxer.]
Hello. I'm Moon Jun Young,
the leader of ZE:A.
[ZE:A's leader who was in the veil.]
He was really famous for a while.
SNS!
[He was the center of
controversy on Twitter.]
Oh, he's the one?
I really wanted to see you!
I remember now!
He's the one?
He's very famous.
Everything is okay now.
It's good for you!
There are nine members in ZE:A.
Why did only six members come today?
Because there are six members
in Shinhwa.
Everyone should have come.
Even Eric is here.
[Why me?]
Eric didn't appear
on variety shows back then.
I have the character of Eric.
Don't be ridiculous!
[He overpowers
Kwang Hee in one word.]
What's wrong with you?
[The fringe on his sleeve
got caught on the button.]
- What did you do?
- I clapped.
Look at you.
What's wrong with your outfit?
Now, I'll explain the rules
for today's game.
Today's theme is 'The Real Man Race'
with MC Blank.
- You get it?
- Yes.
You will be scored
based on the rank of each round.
The team with the highest score
will win the race.
Do you understand?
You will get the scores by
rolling the dice.
You will get a different die
according to the rank.
The golden die has 80, 90, and 100.
The first rank will roll it out.
- The silver die has 60, 70 and 80.
- It's gold, silver and bronze.
The third die has 40,50, and 60 on it.
The first rank can get the
same score as the second rank.
Please keep that in mind.
I hope you get the good dice.
- I understood the rules.
- It was such a clear explanation.
MC Blank! MC Blank!
Sing a song!
- Dong Wan has gotten weird.
- He's been like that.
[Can this be 'Dong-hole'?]
[Each team needs to get to
the mission site.]
- Which car do we take?
- The first one.
See you there!
Team Shinhwa can take this car.
Team ZE:A's car is over there.
Which car do I take?
- What do I take?
- Come with us. We're similar in age.
[Dong Jun reaches out his
hand to Ji Hyo.]
I'll go with team RM.
Thank you, Dong Jun.
[MC Blank gets to team RM's car.]
- Can I go with you?
- Do you have to?
- I need to go.
- We don't have a space for you.
- We do have a space.
- We don't. Go away!
Bye!
[They are laughing inside.]
[Disappointed]
Wait for me!
She's coming!
[Team ZE:A welcomes MC Blank.]
She can take the front seat.
The Running Man members
abandoned me!
I can't believe this!
Listen, everyone.
She'll fall asleep soon.
So, keep quiet.
I don't do that anymore.
This is absurd!
We should try really hard today.
- Suk Jin! Try your best.
- Suk Jin!
Show them!
- We're pretty strong as a team.
- We do have experience.
- To the heart!
[Scream]
[17 years of teamwork and
their cheers.]
- Isn't this a mudflat?
- Where are we?
[The real man is a strong man!]
[ZE:A and MC Blank arrive.]
- Go that way.
- We're the last team.
Are we walking on the mud?
[Team RM and
Team Shinhwa arrived first.]
We got lost.
Sorry to come late.
That happens.
Hurry up!
Hurry up.
They're all ready.
- How long since you debuted?
- I'm sorry!
We... need to take off the shoes.
[What does Kwang Hee put in his boots?]
Kwang Hee, why are you putting
the shoe lifts in the boots?
[The first boots with shoe lifts
on Running Man.]
[By the way...]
Why did they make the big puddle?
It's almost like the rice field!
Stay with your team!
MC Blank!
Each team has six members.
For this game...
you'll divide into three pairs
that are upper, middle, and lower.
Let's make the lower class pair.
- I'm the middle class.
- No.
After you make the pairs,
I will draw lots.
Then, the picked pairs will
play the push.
[Real Man Survival in the mud!]
Move like this!
This is the puddle for it.
The final winner gets one point.
If a team gets two points,
that team is the winner.
- Is there any other way to win?
- No, there isn't.
You'll lose if you fail.
Dong Jun and Taehun are the upper class.
You and I are the middle class.
They should be the lower class.
They're the weakest.
Are you okay with that?
We already know the pairs.
- Do you want to be the upper class?
- No way.
You can be the upper class.
- I'm the lower class.
- You are?
How come Min Woo
is the lower class?
- Even Andy is the lower class?
- I'm very weak!
Eric! Eric should have
gone to the lower class!
Andy is not in good condition!
We decided our classes
based on the facts.
These four are the lower class
for sure.
We'll begin now.
Come out if your class is picked.
Pick a good one!
Your fortune is in my hand.
It's not going to be us.
I'll say it now.
It's the middle class!
- It's the middle class!
- Draw it again!
Just come out,
middle class pair!
[The middle class pairs reluctantly get in.]
[Jun Young and Hyung Sik]
[Hye Sung and Dong Wan]
[Jae Suk and Gary]
Gary, show them what you've got!
Boys, they're your seniors.
Don't be too harsh.
Seniors don't get advantages.
Don't be...
fair!
Game start!
[Battle of the middle class begins.]
[This is the battle of pride.]
[We must win!]
[They start with investigation.]
As soon as you show your
weakness, two teams will attack!
Don't go in the middle!
[Jun Young attacks Hye Sung.]
[It catches on fire!]
[After Jun Young makes a dash]
[Hyung Sik is by himself!]
[Jae Suk and Gary surround him.]
[Dong Wan attacks Jun Young's legs.]
[ZE:A's crisis]
[Hye Sung holds him]
[and Dong Wan pushes him out.]
[Jun Young is out.]
[Hyung Sik tries resisting...]
[Hyung Sik is out.]
[Team ZE:A is out,
Team RM vs. Team Shinhwa.]
Gary!
[Dong Wan attacks the legs again.]
Gary is out!
[Since Gary is out...]
[This is a 2:1 match.]
[Dong Wan and Hye Sung vs. Jae Suk]
[What should I do?]
Splash the water!
Put Jae Suk on the ground!
[They are closing in on Jae Suk.]
- What a coincidence!
Slowly! slowly!
[This is the facial wash of
a middle class man!]
I'm afraid.
[Bring it on!]
[Team Shinhwa runs away from him.]
Come at me!
Run!
[A mud wash with anger!]
[Charge!]
[He's scary.]
[Dong Wan is out.]
[Jae Suk and Hye Sung
are the last fighters.]
Run!
[I got you!]
Guys! He's weird!
[Will he resist?
Will he push him out?]
I have nothing to lose!
[Team RM wins
and gets one point.]
[A valuable reward
for giving up on his looks.]
[Mud wash ceremony.]
[The final survivor in the middle class,
Jae Suk.]
Why did you run away?
We could have won.
No, you can't win this over!
[This is not a joke.]
[This is the real deal.]
[A middle class man's mud wash.]
This time, it'll be
the upper class match!
[Real Man Kwang Soo with
too much desire.]
Taehun is a mixed martial arts fighter.
Can I withdraw?
What are you talking about?
Just get in.
This match gets the most attention!
- Fire, fire!
- Fighting!
- Fight, real men!
Upper class match... Start!
Watch out!
He's a professional fighter!
[He walks in a distance.]
[Cheer leader, Eric.]
[Jun Jin makes a dash!]
[Jong Kook vs. Taehun]
[Dong Jun pulls Jong Kook!]
[Taehun blocks Jong Kook's legs.]
[They pull him up!]
[Mr. Capable's crisis!]
[Mr. Capable gets through the crisis.]
[This is the power game.]
[Jun Jin lifts Kwang Soo, too.]
[Jun Jin and Eric together.]
[Kwang Soo is out.]
Lee Kwang Soo is out.
[We're in trouble.]
Each person lift
one of his arms of legs!
[Public enemy Jong Kook must
be eliminated!]
[Four people lift Jong Kook's limbs.]
[The humiliating moment of Mr. Capable.]
We're sorry we can't protect you...
[Is this the end?]
[They tripped.]
[He turns it into a chance to resist.]
How heavy is he?
I'm at the site of SBS's Running Man.
In spite of the cold weather,
five bulls were fighting
and one of them is almost dying.
A bull named Kim Jong Kook
is the healthiest of all.
What will happen to the bull?
Please keep watching.
Out of four fighters
Eric stops and watches.
He tries lifting Dong Jun's legs
but nothing happens.
[1 vs 4]
[What would be his limit?]
Jong Kook is dealing with four people!
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Oust the other team.
Make an alliance with Jong Kook!
[He starts negotiating.]
When I'm out.
Team Shinhwa will win.
Let's attack them first.
Then you'll have more change to win.
[Target changes to Shinhwa.]
[ZE:A's rush.]
Mr. Capable attacks Eric.
[Shinhwa's crisis]
Why don't you attack them with Eric?
[Everyone's calling Jong Kook.]
Are you using me?
Let's attack ZE:A together!
This is the first time that ZE:A
members are on a variety show!
[Jong Kook, look at my heart.]
I'm not going to meddle with it.
I want to rest.
[Suddenly, it becomes a
one on two match.]
Jun Jin is out!
I thought it was cold today
but it's not.
I'm not cold at all!
This is the perfect beach weather.
[Real men' beach party starts again.]
When Eric wipes his sweat...
[Dong Jun catches it and attacks!]
Enthusiastic Kim!
[Eric is out.]
[Enthusiastic Kim attacks
Jong Kook right away.]
[Jong Kook vs. Dong Jun and Taehun.]
He's used up all his energy.
[A desperate mud fight.]
Why do you have to go this far?
This match doesn't have a winner!
[They began to reach their
physical limits.]
[His eyes are smeared with mud.]
It looks like a martial arts match.
Where are we?
Please give me a glass of water!
We're all winners!
[That's an excuse!]
If you were alive,
this wouldn't happen.
You're not cold?
Give me some water.
[They never felt this tired before.]
[Way to be a real man]
[I want to win, but I'm too tired...]
If this match doesn't end
in two minutes
ZE:A will get one point
because two players remained.
If the situation continues
for two more minutes.
[Should we start the real men'
beach party again?]
[We'll hold it for two minutes!]
ZE:A's Kim Jong Kook!
[They don't even have any
energy to laugh.]
Turbo! Turbo!
[He really needs the energy
of a turbo engine.]
Don't.
Get up and do it again!
He chained his fingers.
[They're blocking Mr. Capable.]
Only one minute left!
[Just one more minute to hold.]
The time is almost over.
[He can't even talk straight...]
[Taehun doesn't let him go.]
Lie down!
One minute and thirty seconds passed.
Only 30 seconds remaining!
No! Don't!
[I'm Mr. Capable.
I don't know what giving up means.]
[I'll push you out!]
[Dong Jun resisted til the end.]
[The battle of the real men.]
[Team ZE:A wins.]
[The teams gets one point.]
You've worked so hard.
[He can't get up by himself.]
[The real men showed their passion.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[The real man who couldn't stand up.]
Sadly, each team has one point.
What was the benefit to
winning this round?
- The dice.
- Are the dice that great?
What if everyone gets in?
Why don't you get in?
I think we can draw lots by luck.
Two members from each team.
- I have it right here.
- It looks fun!
I will draw it myself.
[From team Shinhwa...]
Min Woo!
[Min Woo from the lower class.]
This isn't fair!
He is the Celebrity Shim Kwon Ho!
(legendary wrestler)
From Team ZE:A...
- Pick Kwang Hee!
- No, don't pick me!
Hyung Sik!
[Hyung Sik from the middle class.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Is it going to be Kwang Soo?]
Ha Ha!
[Ha Ha from the lower class.]
[Celebrity Shim Kwon Ho
checks his boots.]
Dong Wan!
Jun Young!
I'm sorry.
Ji Suk Jin!
[Suk Jin from the lower class.]
It's all over.
Two lower class men will fight for the team.
[The last round]
- Two members from each team.
Are you ready?
Don't betray from the beginning.
We'll begin now!
[RM team and ZE:A making
an alliance?]
Begin!
[The last round starts!]
Stay together!
[Confidence from the alliance.]
Right now!
[Hyung Sik attacks Min Woo.]
Lower your stance!
[Ha Ha attacks Min Woo's legs.]
[Big-nosed brother lifts!]
Ha Ha, use little more strength!
[Jun Young lifts Dong Wan.]
[Dong Wan is out!]
[Dong-hole is indeed a black hole.]
[Min Woo is risky.]
Lift Suk Jin's legs up!
[The alliance broke.]
[Big-nose is out!]
Push Ha Ha out!
[While they push Ha Ha,
Min Woo escapes.]
Plan change!
Min Woo, let's attack them!
Ha Ha, be careful!
[The alliance keeps changing.]
[Min Woo starts moving.]
[His target is Hyung Sik.]
I don't belong to any teams.
What are you, then?
[Min Woo tackles.]
You're on your own!
[Jun Young attacks Ha Ha.]
It's one on one!
[We need to win...]
Ha Ha, why are you there?
You shouldn't be there!
[They go to help Hyung Sik.]
Help me!
[Ha Ha attacks Jun Young.]
[Min Woo joins.]
[Jun Young is out.]
[Three players left.]
[Min Woo vs. Ha Ha vs. Hyung Sik.]
Time!
There's no time out during the battle!
[Hyunk Sik is already groggy.]
Help him!
Ha Ha, help him!
Please save me, Ha Ha!
[They lifts Hyung Sik together.]
[Hyung Sik rotates.]
[They try oust Min Woo again.]
[They push Min Woo's leg out.]
[Min Woo revives again!]
[It's so tiring!]
Do you want me to go, Ha Ha?
[Let's attack Ha Ha together!]
Wake up!
[Did you forget what we promised?]
He's sitting.
We need to attack now!
[Ha Ha betrays and Hyung Sik is out.]
[We were close...]
[The last match,
Ha Ha vs. Min Woo.]
[Min Woo was going to help him]
[but attacks!]
[But Ha Ha...]
[He steps on the ground, jumps...]
[and rotates in the sky.]
[Air Ha Ha!]
[Like a martial artist...]
[The best moment
of the 'Real Man Race'.]
[Attacks right away.]
[Min Woo resists but...]
[Min Woo is out.]
[The last survivor of
the mud puddle is Ha Ha.]
[He defeats the strongest
opponent, Min Woo!]
[Who said Ha Ha is
the lower class man?]
He's awesome!
Encore!
[Team RM's hero.]
[That's cool!]
[The real man Ha Ha
becomes a legend.]
[And the hug between
the real men.]
Team RM wins!
[Team RM wins.]
[Float like a butterfly
and sting like a bee!]
Team Shinhwa gets the silver dice
and Team ZE:A gets the bronze dice.
We'll roll the dice!
The third ranking team
will roll the dice.
- Roll the dice!
- Okay!
[What will it be?]
- 50!
[ZE:A's score is 50.]
- Roll the dice!
- 80! 80!
- 70!
[Team Shinhwa's score is 70.]
Roll the dice!
[What will Team RM get?]
[Team RM's score is 100.]
Team RM's score is 100!
[Big-nosed brother's dice magic.]
[Which team will get the
highest score with next mission?]
[The real man is a gentleman.]
['O' Women's University,
it seems like spring has come.]
Everyone's worked hard.
[Countless university students
greet them.]
[Welcome to a woman's university.]
[They're welcomed with an
enthusiastic greeting.]
[The women's university is filled
with fever in early spring.]
[What kind of match awaits them?]
[This looks like they're having a festival.]
Thank you for coming.
We're at Ewha Women's University.
As you can see from the arrangement,
do you know what you'll play?
- Dodge ball!
- Yes, it is dodge ball.
Please do not dodge when you talk.
Only two teams can play
at a time.
So we'll pick a team
that will win by default.
We'll play another game for it.
Everyone knows this game.
The team representatives are
these three?
They are the trouble makers of the teams.
Dong-hole, Kwang-hole, and Hee-hole.
Hello, everyone!
We're the holes!
- You'll play 'rock-paper-scissors'.
- 'Rock-paper-scissors'?
It'll be a single round match
at MC's discretion!
- Can't you control her?
- You're out!
[Charismatic MC Blank]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Rock, paper, scissors]
Kwang-hole and Hee-hole win.
[It's fine, Dong-hole.]
[Kwang-hole and Hee-hole's match.]
You'll win by default
if you win this one.
I'm nervous.
You'll lose if you don't play.
[How did the teams' luck
end up with these two?]
Rock, scissors, paper!
[Kwang-hole wins.]
[Team RM wins by default.]
[The semi-final is
Team Shinhwa vs. Team ZE:A.]
- Men choose rock!
- Thank you, Kwang Hee.
This is the main match.
[We'll play dodge ball
with students of this school.]
This is a game of 'Queen dodge ball'.
You need to protect your queen.
The last person who survives
with the queen never dies.
The last person needs only
to protect the queen.
Even though he gets hit,
he's like a Super Saiyan.
Super Saiyan?
('Dragon Ball Z' reference.)
[She might attack you
with energy waves.]
We cast 100 students from
Ewha Women's University.
We'll pick three numbers.
Students with the chosen numbers
will play dodge ball.
[We'll pick a number for each team
and select their queens.]
[100 candidates to be queen.]
Who will be the Queen of Team RM?
The Queen of Team RM is...
Number thirty...
- Number 34!
- Did you see it?
[When did he see it?]
- He saw it.
- It's number 34!
- Where are you?
- Number 34!
[The Queen of Team RM.]
[She's lucky!]
Oh, my Queen!
Oh my Queen!
Next, we'll pick for Team Shinhwa.
The Queen of Team Shinhwa is...
- Number 14!
[The Queen of Team Shinhwa]
[Queen's bodyguards walk with her.]
It's ZE:A's turn!
- The Queen of Team ZE:A is...
- Number 31!
[The active Queen of ZE:A]
[They must be happy.]
- Please stand next to Jae Suk.
- Come here.
Jo Yun Sun! Jo Yun Sun!
Did you want to be
the Queen of Team RM?
- Yes.
- You did?
Who do you hope will stay
until the end?
- Don't worry, I'll protect you.
- You'll be ousted soon.
I'll be your bodyguard.
Don't worry!
- What's your name?
- We'll introduce her.
Our queen is Julie, Julie, Julie.
We're Shinhwa, Shinhwa, Shinhwa.
Oh, Julie!
[The Queen of Team Shinhwa, Julie.]
- Do you know the group, Shinhwa?
- Yes.
My Norwegian friends like
Shinhwa's songs.
Do you know what
'Queen dodge ball' is?
- Queen dodge ball.
[I don't know what queen dodge ball is.]
You know dodge ball, right?
We'll protect you during the game.
Because you're the Queen.
Okay, then you can explain to her.
[MC Blank lets them explain to her.]
What's your name?
Seo Min Ji.
- Do you like ZE:A?
- Yes.
- Who do you like the most?
- Park Hyung Sik.
Why?
[Hyung Sik stands
next to the Queen.]
Look at Hyung Sik's eyes.
He's romantic.
I will put my life on the line!
The bluish team who won
by default can go to the side.
She called us 'the bluish team.'
[Team Shinhwa vs Team ZE:A-
Getting ready for the competition.]
- You can do this, right?
- Forget the queen, and just protect me.
We have to be careful,
and protect my nose and my face.
I'll stick close to the queen.
[Once again, Eric takes on the role
of explaining the rules of the game to her.]
The opposing team will try to kill you
by hitting you with the ball.
Team ZE:A, fighting.
One, two, three, fighting!
[Even their cheers are all over the place.]
[No matter, fighting!]
One, two, three, fighting!
[Continuing to cheer on even after 17 years.]
[Passionate round of cheers
from the crowd for the teams.]
The first team to grab the ball at the sound
of the whistle will possess the ball.
[Hit the opposing queen with the ball,
and it's an immediate win for the team.]
[It all comes down to how well
they can protect their own queen.]
- Ready...
[Will Team Shinhwa maintain their dignity...]
[Or will the enthusiasm of the
younger idols bring home the victory?]
Ready... set, go!
[ZE:A's Dong Jun races forward...
then freezes.]
What is he doing?
[Thanks to Dong Jun's speed,
Team ZE:A's on the offense.]
Do it.
[In the blink of an eye,
Min Woo is ousted.]
[Rule- Even though one may be ousted,
one can still attack from the sidelines.]
It's our ball now, isn't it?
[Team Shinhwa takes over the offense.]
[Hye Sung shoots!]
[And spikes the ball into the ground.]
[Hye Sung's newly invented
shooting star spike.]
[It's not as easy as it looks?]
Who should I go for?
[Absolute fear]
[Min Woo shoots the ball.]
[They're very good at avoiding the ball.]
- We have to protect the queen.
- Kwang Hee, don't stand off on your own.
- Don't go off on your own.
[The queen avoids the ball on her own.]
[Min Woo slams in another shot.]
[Hyung Sik is eliminated.]
- Are there two queens on their team?
[A newly invented version of dodgeball.]
You just need to eliminate the queen
in order to win the game.
Yoon Sun, don't worry about a thing,
and just use us as your bodyguards.
Okay?
[Team Shinhwa continues their offense.]
- Please save us.
[Throw it up high.]
[Even as Eric only grabs the ball,
the fans from the crowd goes crazy.]
[Even though he may be our opponent,
he's still so cool.]
[While everyone's attention
is focused on Eric...]
[Hye Sung shoots the ball.]
[The queen's eyes are still
fixated on Eric.]
[Who cares about the ball
when Eric is here!]
[It's a direct hit on the queen!]
[A quick victory for Team Shinhwa!]
[The queen gets ousted while
her focus is shifted over to Eric.]
[Even the onlookers are confused
by what just happened.]
[What just happened...
Did we just lose?]
[Team Shinhwa moves onto the playoffs.]
Shin Hye Sung!
Those ground spikes I did
were done on purpose.
- Wow, I can't believe it.
- That was unreal.
[A huge round of applause for the queen.]
- We're sorry for having lost so quickly.
- Who was supposed to shield you?
- Heechul.
- But Heechul avoided the ball.
[Heechul avoids the ball at the last minute,
and gets their own queen ousted.]
[As the ball flies towards him,
he instinctively moves out of the way.]
- Heechul, you were supposed to block her.
[Did I really do that?]
- I was going to do it, but the ball...
- You waited for six years to do this?
[The fear of being hit by the ball must've
been worse than the six-year wait.]
[At last, it's time for the playoffs.]
[The masters of the game, Team RM,
are well rested for the round.]
[Team Shinhwa defeats Team ZE:A,
and showcases their amazing teamwork.]
[Which of the two teams will
manage to keep their queen safe?]
- Is everybody warmed up?
- Yes.
- Okay, we'll get started.
- Wow, I'm feeling nervous.
[Team RM is ready and revving to go.]
[Team Shinhwa has gotten a good feel for
the game after playing the previous round.]
- Who's going to shield the queen?
- I'll shield her, and keep her protected.
[Mr. Capable volunteers himself
as the shield.]
[If Jong Kook is the shield...
then how are we going to do this?]
[Practicing the moves with the queen.]
The winner of this round will
get to roll the gold dice, okay?
- Who's going to go for the ball?
- Let's have Kwang Soo get the ball.
[The two teams are ready
to protect their queens.]
- Okay, we're going to get started!
[Even Team ZE:A looks nervous.]
Ready...
[This is the round where the pride
of their manhood balances on the line.]
[Keep the queen protected to the end,
and win the golden dice.]
Ready, set, go!
[Dong Wan of Team Shinhwa
rushes out to grab the ball.]
[Team Shinhwa is on the offense.]
[But why are they hesitating
instead of attacking?]
[A steel-like line of defense.]
[Team Shinhwa's resolve is shaken
in front of Team RM's line of defense.]
[Andy's unbelievable mistake.]
[The offensive move is handed over
to Team RM in the blink of an eye.]
[Ha Ha shoots the ball
with everything he has.]
[Team Shinhwa is in extreme danger.]
[He manages to grab the ball!]
[Even the onlookers can't help but
be impressed by Jun Jin's move.]
[With Jun Jin's miraculous defense,
the offense changes hands once again.]
[Gary's lightning fast reflexes.]
[Impressive ball play in the playoff round.]
Jun Jin, I can't believe
you grabbed the ball.
- Ugh, I was so shocked.
- Gary, you can do this.
[Team RM takes over the attack.]
[Team Shinhwa's turn to showcase
a nice defensive move.]
[As soon as their offense is over, Team RM
is back to being a fortress of defense.]
[If you think you can get through,
then why don't you give it a try?]
[If that's the way you want to play it...]
[Team Shinhwa switches up their plans.]
[Team Shinhwa uses the same color of
their jacket to confuse their opponents.]
[The orange army's plan of confusion.]
- I can't see the ball!
- Where did the ball go?
[Where did the ball go?]
- I can't see the ball!
[Then shoots the ball!]
[Team Shinhwa eliminates Jae Suk.]
[Team Shinhwa's attack breaks through
Team RM's steel-like line of defense.]
- What just happened?
- They have the ball.
- We have to try flustering them.
[Team RM also switches up their plan.]
[It's impossible to decipher
Kwang Soo's shuffle moves.]
[Even his own teammates are
quite confused.]
- What are you doing?
[Knock it off.]
[The safety of the queen is
entrusted to Mr. Capable.]
[Easy Brothers resort to
their secretive offense moves.]
[What are they working on?]
[What luck is this?]
[Ah...]
[Oh my goodness.]
[I can't believe this!]
[His own teammates, opponents,
and the onlookers are all feeling shocked.]
- Don't you think that's going overboard?
- Jun Jin, that was a great shot!
- Suk Jin.
- Ugh, that was hurtful to my pride.
[Big-nose is ousted with a big laughter.]
- That was like a cartoon scene.
- Sorry, Suk Jin.
[Team RM: 4 vs Team Shinhwa: 6]
Stand over there.
[Team RM's turn to attack.]
[The ball keeps on rolling...]
[Jae Suk grabs the perfect chance!]
[Jun Jin grabs the ball again...
but ends up being ousted.]
[Jun Jin is ousted,
and is sent to the sidelines.]
[Team RM: 4 vs Team Shinhwa: 5]
- Can I stand over here?
- Yes.
[Min Woo passes the ball
perfectly over to Jun Jin.]
[So, you've eliminated me
from the game?]
[Ha Ha's provocation.]
[Eye for an eye,
provocation for provocation.]
[In the midst of provocation...
Jun Jin shoots the ball!]
[Ha Ha barely manages to
escape the danger.]
[Eric puts up a tight line of defense
over his queen.]
[Gary continues the tight offense.]
[Hye Sung is already ousted
from having touched the ball.]
[Instantly throws the ball,
and instinctively ducks from the ball.]
[A bloody battle between real men.]
You're already ousted.
[Just then, Andy grabs the
chance to attack.]
[Mr. Capable is ousted.]
[Gary grabs the ball that Jong Kook was
ousted by, and leans into an attack.]
[Shoots the ball directly
in the queen's direction.]
[Eric grabs the ball!]
[The force of a superhero!]
[I made a promise to my queen
that I would protect her.]
[Team RM is thrown into danger
with Eric's surprising defensive move.]
[Ha Ha is immediately ousted with
Team Shinhwa's combo play.]
Come on, Kwang Soo and Gary!
[Team Shinhwa has the upper hand!]
Make sure that they don't get the ball!
[Jun Jin shoots the ball!]
[But Team RM barely manages
to avoid the ball.]
[Team RM continues to be in danger.]
Throw the ball towards Gary!
- Be careful not to get hit on your legs!
[Team RM continues to escape the ball.]
[Team Shinhwa continues to
sharpen their offensive moves.]
That's okay, it's still our ball.
- I'm really exhausted.
- Grab the ball!
[Jun Jin throws a power shot.]
[A direct hit on the camera.]
[Sorry...]
[Team RM finally gets a chance to attack.]
[Kwang Soo's giant power shoot.]
[Eric drops the ball,
but Min Woo manages to grab it.]
[This is a showcase of 17 years
worth of teamwork.]
[Team RM is back to being in danger.]
Sorry, Hye Sung.
[A momentary mistake could mean
a huge moment of danger.]
[Kkuk shoots the ball.]
[Bodyguard, Eric, is out.]
[No, Eric!]
[Eric entrusts the care of
his queen over to Min Woo.]
[But Team Shinhwa doesn't leave the queen
unprotected even for a moment.]
[With a direct hit, Andy is also ousted.]
[Team RM: 2 vs Team Shinhwa: 2]
[Team RM evens out the score.]
- Pass the ball.
- Did Andy just get ousted?
[Team RM's stable long pass.]
[Oh no!
Misses the pass!]
[Team RM is back to being in danger.]
[Jun Jin's powerful attack, and
Kwang Soo's fast-footed defense.]
[Jun Jin's powerful attack
directly hits the camera again.]
[Jun Jin's attacks are about to
destroy the fleet of cameras.]
- That's good!
- He hit the camera again!
[Even with their exhaustion,
neither team leaves their queen.]
[Jun Jin continues to target
Team RM's queen.]
[Just then, Jae Suk ousts
Team Shinhwa's Dong Wan.]
[Team RM finally takes over the lead.]
[Team RM: 2 vs Team Shinhwa: 1]
[Min Woo is the only defender
left on Team Shinhwa.]
[Rule- Once only one member is left standing,
then they're safe from getting eliminated.]
- Grab the ball!
- Pass the ball around!
[Gary is given the perfect opportunity.]
[No...]
[Team Shinhwa's queen is ousted!]
[A direct hit on the queen
around her defender, Min Woo.]
[Team RM wins the
Queen Dodgeball game!]
Thank you for your efforts, Queen.
[A heartfelt gratitude to their queens.]
[Team RM wins the golden dice chance.]
[Thank you to all the students for
cheering on the teams to the end.]
The winning team gets the gold dice.
[Team ZE:A's queen is first
to throw the dice.]
[Team ZE:A wins 50 points.]
[Kwang Hee denies the results.]
[Team ZE:A may have won the bronze,
but Kwang Hee's humor is gold level.]
[Team Shinhwa's turn.]
[Team Shinhwa earns 70 points.]
[The first place winner, Team RM's turn.]
[Could it be 100 points?]
[Close, but ends up earning 90 points.]
[Powerful and mannerly,
Team RM wins twice in a row.]
- 90 points.
- Okay, everyone...
We'd like to give another round of thanks to
the three queens and to our cheerful crowd.
[A shocking and totally unexpected
final mission is soon headed your way.]
[Han River Yang-Hwa Jigu.]
What's this all about now?
[Why do they all look so shocked?]
I've never seen such a huge
setup before.
[A specially prepared setup
for the toughest of all men.]
[When it comes to real men,
it's all about loyalty.]
[Dream big, and keep it loyal-
A set prepared for our group of real men.]
This is our final game of the day.
[2015's masterpiece that combines
science and entertainment.]
- Do you see the set behind you?
- Yes, we see it.
We have prepared something special for you.
You can imagine what's to come, right?
Yes, I see that there's
a bell up there.
The first team to climb up and ring
the bell, wins the round.
[Rule- It's very simple,
be the first to ring the bell to win.]
But it's not just a simple
climb up the ramp.
The first person will climb up,
then the next person will climb up his back.
It will continue in this fashion
until all members are finished climbing.
All five members have to climb up, and
the last person will have to ring the bell.
- That's how the game will be won.
- Climb on top of each other?
- We have to step all over each other?
- This is just absurd!
Is this even possible?
[You want us to become a human ladder
to climb up this giant ramp ourselves?]
[It's a game of endurance and loyalty!
Which team will get to ring the bell?]
- The lightest person will have to be last.
- Let's have Andy go last.
[The teams are given some time
to formulate their game plan.]
- Just step on the back and the shoulders.
- One, two, three, four, five.
[Figuring out the correct order of players
will be a key to winning this game.]
You have to lean your weight
onto the angle of the ramp.
- We have to utilize the angle.
- Position your weight onto the angle.
- I'll go first.
- You can be the first player.
[Taehun of Team ZE:A volunteers to be
on the bottom for being the strongest.]
The last person to go needs to be the one
who'd be best at climbing over people.
- It needs to be whoever is lightest.
[They're not going to pick me, are they?]
Either the strongest or the tallest
needs to be on the bottom.
- Either Kwang Soo or myself...
- I'll go first.
- I think you need to go second.
- I'm not sure if I can climb up.
I don't think too much weight will be placed
on the bottom because of the ramp's angle.
- But there's still going to be some weight.
- Then I'll go third.
[A real man speaks with his actions.
Team Shinhwa launches into practice mode.]
Don't slam into the person,
but carefully climb over their bodies.
[Hee-hole already starts to scream out in
protest on only their third member.]
- Kwang Hee, you have to support him.
- Ouch, that hurts!
[I don't think this game
suits me very well.]
- What are we going to do with him!
[He can't be trusted to handle anything.]
Kwang Hee, you're really worrying us.
I'm okay, you can step on me.
[1. Kwang Soo. 2. Suk Jin. 3. Jae Suk.]
[Kwang Soo and Suk Jin are bearing
the most of the weight by themselves.]
- Hang on.
- Are you sure that you're okay?
[Once Jong Kook is in place,
their fourth level will be completed.]
You're starting to crumble.
[Suk Jin is throwing up his hip in defeat?]
- Just let go, and have Kwang Soo get up.
- Wait, not yet.
[It seems Big-nose may have to
move onto a different position.]
We can't have Suk Jin be
the second player.
I feel really nervous.
This is much harder than it looks.
[The giant ramp is much harder than it
looks now that it's become a reality.]
[But it's now time to join hands
and climb over the wall together.]
- Okay, have you all formulated your plans?
- Yes.
[Final mission-
Human Ladder Game]
The first person to
ring the bell wins first place.
Second to ring will win second place,
and the third will come in at third place.
- Okay, we understand.
- It's one single game.
- Okay, let's do this!
- Fighting!
[Only one chance will be given! And
there will be only one team of real men!]
[Gather together, endure together,
and trust in each other!]
[A battle of endurance and trust,
Human Ladder Mission.]
Ready, set, go!
[First players rushes over to the ramp.]
[In first position-
Kwang Soo, Eric, and Taehun.]
[In second position-
Suk Jin, Hye Sung, and Jun Young.]
[The third position of the ladder
has to be of someone trustworthy!]
[In third position-
Jae Suk, Dong Wan, and Hyung Sik.]
[The third position is completed
for all three teams.]
[Fourth position-
Jong Kook, Min Woo, and Kwang Hee.]
[While fourth position gets into place,
first position is already feeling like death.]
[Fifth position-
Ha Ha, Andy, and Heechul.]
[Once the fifth position is in place,
victory is just around the corner.]
[First to get into fifth position could
determine who'll become the victor.]
[Overenthusiastic Dong Jun runs in
before fifth position is even in place]
[Team ZE:A attempts to kill
two birds with one stone.]
[Wait... will this be their victory?]
[At this rate,
Team ZE:A could win the mission!]
[Wait, a member of Team ZE:A
slips out of place!]
[Member in third position
crumbles under all the weight.]
[Failure is a learning opportunity! The team
groups together for another attempt.]
They crumbled.
[In that case...
This could be our chance at a win!]
[Goes in for the victory
with a powerful run.]
No!
[The ladder crumbles!]
[The team crumbles under the weakened
bottom and the powerful run of the final player.]
[Team RM is the only ladder left intact!]
[Perhaps the steady footsteps are
the better way to go rather than speed?]
Jae Suk, no!
- Jae Suk is starting to slide.
- Fighting!
[I think I'm starting
to get a little tired...]
- Get down.
- Why!
[Even being too slow is a problem.
The bottom rungs are feeling exhausted.]
[The teams seems to have gotten a
feel for it after their initial failure.]
[There's no more room for failure!
Launches back in without any hesitation.]
[Team Shinhwa assumes
their original position.]
[Team RM and Team ZE:A swap out
their first two positions.]
[Team RM- Jong Kook for Suk Jin.
Team ZE:A- Dong Jun for Jun Young.]
[Third position-
Jae Suk, Dong Wan, and Jun Young.]
[The teams have found new determination
after their initial failure.]
[Fourth position-
Suk Jin, Min Woo, Heechul.]
- Andy's coming!
- Step on the shoulders.
[Fifth position-
Andy, Hyung Sik, and Gary.]
[A very close competition.]
[The victory comes down to
the final player.]
Here I come!
[Final position-
Jun Jin, Kwang Hee, and Ha Ha.]
[Gather together as a team!
Endure and trust in each other!]
[The battle between real men where
endurance and trust is the key!]
[Will Jun Jin win with his determination?]
[Or will it be Kwang Hee, the black hole?]
[Or the unexpected, Ha Ha?]
[Team Shinhwa and Team ZE:A's final spurt
with their pride hanging on the line.]
[Just who... will take home the victory?]
[I will keep going forward
with my gritted teeth.]
[Hold on just a little bit longer.]
[Team Shinhwa wins first place
in the human ladder mission.]
[This is the strength of having been
a team for the past 17 years.]
[Kwang Hee's struggling to move
forward with his slippery socks.]
[Even takes off his gloves in his desperation
to come in at second place.]
[Please hurry...]
[I've finally made it to the top!]
[Team ZE:A wins second place!]
[Team RM crumbles in their disbelief
at having come in at last place.]
[We are... Team Shinhwa.]
[I won first place!]
[Who cares about having won?
Bottom rungs are completely exhausted.]
- I'm sorry, it was my slippery socks.
- He's definitely the black hole of the team.
- Come down, Hee-hole.
[Just what is he ever good at?]
[At a loss for words.]
[After today's events, he'll be
forever known as, 'socks of holes.']
- I was so close.
- We know, but Kwang Soo slipped.
- I was so close to being first.
- But Kwang Soo started to slip.
This is the first time we won today.
- Get us the 60 points.
- Will he get a miracle?
[The dice is thrown into the air.]
[Could this be their lucky day?
Throws the highest score of 60 points.]
[Why do they feel like they've
just lost?]
Doesn't that mean you've
won first place?
[Team ZE:A throws second for
having come in at second place.]
[Not a bad throw of 70 points.]
[What will the first place winners,
Team Shinhwa, throw?]
[A high score of 90 points.]
- All the games are now over.
- Okay.
The fate of the final score
with these numbers...
[What?
It's not over yet?]
[It's not over until it's over.
Running Man's final hurdle.]
[A surprising final medal judging platform.]
- What is this?
[What could this setup be for?]
[Look at how the set shines
so brightly against the night sky.]
I see something over there.
[Suspicious looking rolls of
brightly colored paper.]
There's something.
[Real man and the lady of luck.]
Song Ji Hyo will now turn in her MC mic,
and go stand on the gold platform over there.
[What will MC Blank be doing
with the rolls of colored paper?]
- It must be up to Blank Ji.
- What is this?
[Lady of luck.]
I'm the Lady of Luck.
[MC Blank is immediately transformed
into the Lady of Luck.]
[All the men are trying to win
the favor of the Lady of Luck.]
[What is the reason for needing
the Lady of Luck during this event?]
You'll see that your team banners
have been set above your heads.
Your current standing scores will be
lit up above each of the teams.
The first number is the combined score
after the first two rounds.
And the second number represents
the score that you've just received.
In the rolls of paper in front of Ji Hyo,
there are either plus or minus signs.
[Plus and minus signs sit in
front of Ji Hyo in the rolls of paper.]
[A 50/50 chance-
30 minus, and 30 plus signs.]
Ji Hyo will pull out a sign and
determine the teams' final score.
[Depending on the sign that she chooses,
the victory is still up for grabs.]
The two teams with the lower scores
will have to face a penalty.
- Seriously?
- Two teams will have to face a penalty!
- It's either a plus or a minus signs.
- The fate rests in Song Ji Hyo's hands.
[Time to start cheering for Ji Hyo!]
Wait, can I go and take off
my underwear real quick?
[Afraid of getting soaked by the water.]
We're not going to get
rained on by rocks, are we?
[All the men are starting to
shake with fear.]
Let's all go home nice and dry.
- Please take care of us, Ji Hyo.
- Seriously, this is so chancy!
- Please, Ji Hyo!
- The beautiful Ji Hyo!
[Depending on what she pulls,
it could either be a plus or a minus!]
- Team ZE:A!
[A red roll is pulled for Team ZE:A.]
Song Ji Hyo!
[ Team Shinhwa-
Either 230 points, or 50 points.]
- Team Shinhwa!
[A blue roll is selected for Team Shinhwa.]
Take care of us, Blank Ji.
[Either 250 points,
or 130 points for Team RM.]
You look really sweet today. Think
of the five years we've spent together.
Take care of us.
Don't choose the white roll!
I have a bad feeling about
the white one.
[Since you say that you have
a bad feeling about the white...]
[I'll choose the white for you!]
[Depending on what she's chosen,
Team ZE:A could even take over the lead.]
[Which team has the Lady of Luck
smiled down upon?]
We can win if we got the plus sign.
- Are we going to look at the score now?
- I'm going to stand here with confidence.
- Let's start off with a minus sign!
- Team ZE:A first!
[Team ZE:A's sign is...]
- Let it be a minus!
- Minus!
- No, it has to be a plus!
[Team ZE:A.... a plus!]
[The best case scenario-
A total of 170 points.]
[Team ZE:A's final score- 170 points.]
Song Ji Hyo!
If the two other teams get a minus,
then Team ZE:A will win.
- I doubt that'll happen.
- Let it be a minus!
- Minus!
[Let it be a minus for Team Shinhwa.]
[A minus would mean a penalty for Shinhwa,
and a plus would mean a penalty for ZE:A.]
Shinhwa's sign is...
[Shinhwa's sign is...]
[A plus sign for Shinhwa!]
[Currently in the lead with 230 points.]
[Team ZE:A earns one penalty spot.]
Song Ji Hyo!
[Team Shinhwa ends with
a total score of 230 points.]
- Team ZE:A will have to face a penalty.
- We've been prepared to face it.
Team ZE:A final score is 170,
and Team Shinhwa's final score is 230.
Team RM currently has 190 and 60.
If they get a plus sign, they win with 250.
If they get a minus, then they lose with 130.
Please just end this suspense!
In which case, Team Shinhwa will win,
and Team RM and Team ZE:A are penalized.
But with the two plus signs already,
there's a high chance for a minus sign.
- Plus sign!
- Minus sign!
I really don't want to get
soaked right now!
- Just accept your fate.
- Why are you doing this to us now?
[What will be the final result?]
[Team RM's sign is...]
[Please Ji Hyo...]
[Team RM's sign is... a plus!]
[A celebration of joy,
and tear showers of sadness.]
[Chilled down to the bones.]
[What a great feeling!]
[Shocked out of their minds.]
[We are... Shinhwa!]
[With the mentality of idols,
bright and cheery to the very end!]
[Real Man Competition-
Team RM wins!]
We're ZE:A!
[Lady of Luck saves Team RM
with her selection!]
You have no idea how nervous I felt!
[The seniors and the juniors of idol world
says their farewell in the icy shower.]
Can we start over from the beginning?
[Can't stop the enthusiasm from
this group of real men!]
The winners will take home the gold!
[The winners are awarded with gold badges.]
[And another surprise event.]
[A surprise birthday party for
February birthdays- Suk Jin, Gary, and Eric.]
[Cheers to Shinhwa and ZE:A for
bringing their masculinity to the show!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[To the fresh new lineup that
blew in with the warm spring breeze.]
[Hani, Jung So Min, Yoon So Hee,
Yeh Rin, and Nam Ji Hyeon.]
[The start of a sweet budding
campus romance.]
- Stop acting like you're all that.
[Not what we quite expected?]
Can I swap out my partner?
[The love quarrel is about to begin.]
[What is the reason for
having to send them away?]
Can't you please let us be in love?
[Next week's Running Man-
The Greatest Love.]