Subtitles by DramaFever
[Christmas special]
[Running Man]
[Running X-man]
Real situation!
Good Sunday!
X-man!
Hello!
You must have been surprised!
- You must be surprised.
- Why X-man all of a sudden?
They probably thought
it was an old rerun.
You might have been thinking
this was an old show, but since
it's almost Christmas, we have a special
collaboration with X-man and Running Man.
[Ten years later!]
[X-man and Running Man
together at last!]
[And!]
[There's something special
in Running Man!]
[What's the hidden special mission?]
- Team Leader Kim!
- Yes?
This is usually Ho Dong's spot.
And after so many years,
Team Leader Kim is standing here.
I've been promoted.
He's been promoted.
This spot is for the big guys.
This spot was usually Kang Ho Dong's.
In this spot, there was
Kim Jae Dong, Park Kyung Lim
and Gong Hyung Jin.
There have been many changes.
It's not a very good spot.
- It keeps changing.
- It does.
Our team leaders may have changed
but it will be just like
X-man from 10 years ago.
Please welcome the
members of both teams!
Please give them a round of applause!
I'm so excited to see
who our guests are!
Gary!
Lee Kwang Soo!
Bobby, B.I, Song Ji Hyo
Kim Ji Min, Seol Hyun!
Andy!
[Who will their opponents be?]
Gary!
[Chae Yeon, Lee Ji Hyeon,
Kim Jung Nam, Stephanie]
[Andy, Lee Jong Soo, Ha Ha.]
Jin Sook!
Ji Hyeon!
Kim Jung Nam, Andy!
Eagle Eye!
(Pun: it also means glaring.)
[The special members have entered!]
It's Eagle Eye!
[Nice to meet you.]
[Everyone's focused on
the veteran, Eagle Eye.]
I was so surprised as soon
when they came out!
So we have two teams,
Team Kim and Team Ji.
Team Kim is with people who played
a major role in X-man back in the day.
And they're the members of X-man 2005.
And on this team,
although they weren't on X-man before
if there X-man was still around today
they would be on 2015's X-man.
Today, we will...
- I want to go there.
- Where?
Jin Sook, you need to stay there.
[Her real name was released!]
[Jung Nam who's never been
on X-man is on their team?]
Team Leader Kim suggested him.
[He was allowed in.]
(Ex-Turbo member)
- Another Turbo album is coming out.
- Yes it is!
Let's introduce everyone, one by one.
I haven't seen this guest in a while.
It's been a long time.
- Her stage name is Chae Yeon...
- Jin Sook!
Jin Sook!
[X-man's legendary Sexy Queen!
Chae Yeon]
We have to talk about your
romance with Kim Jong Kook.
He was playing hard to get
but he leaned more
towards Yoon Eun Hye, right?
Yes, I wasn't enough...
Do you actually like
Kim Jong Kook back in the day?
Maybe I did since I was young.
[Shy]
- Is he no good now?
- We're very awkward now!
Don't ask about the past.
Why is your back to your teammates?
[He becomes smaller in front of
his girl teammates.]
If he looks at you, you look away.
And when you look at him,
he looks away.
He's really weird.
[It's suspicious.]
What are you doing?
You can still find love now, right?
X-man doesn't work like that.
How does it work, then?
[Glance]
Gary!
Stop looking at Seol Hyun.
Did I get caught?
You look at her too much!
I was staring the entire time.
[He was scanning her
underneath his sunglasses.]
He stares at her too much!
[Can't you pay attention?]
[Who's the second member of Team Kim?]
She was a legend at
the game "Of course."
[Queen of "Of course!",
Lee Ji Hyeon]
I really like you!
Clap, clap, clap!
It's been a while, Ji Hyeon.
She has since gotten married
and has become
a mother of two.
She was talking about
her kids behind the stage.
I was talking about
how much time has passed.
Do you miss any of the X-man
members that aren't here right now?
Kim Je Dong!
Is there a reason?
When we played "Of course"
I remember saying "you don't have
lenses in your glasses, right?"
I still feel so bad about that
You asked if I took steroids!
[That's harsh.]
You're less than 160 centimeters, right?
[2005 X-man, "Of course" game.]
Did you get those muscles
by taking drugs?
[Mr. Capable was KO'ed
at her spiteful remark.]
- Do you still remember that?
- He holds grudges.
She had the title of a Queen just to
win the game and stuff but
your personality isn't
like that at all, right?
It's done so much damage
as I lived throughout my life.
I literally had to prepare so much
just for the game, at home.
I prepared, but...
- People thought I was a mean person...
- I thought that, too.
So I've prepared again today!
[Her spiteful remarks
start once again!]
I'm going to do it again!
You used to date Yoon Eun Hye for real
back when we filmed X-man, right?
[The Queen's instincts have
awoken after ten years!]
[It will be revealed soon!]
Wow, Ji Hyeon.
Next up is
Stephanie!
[X-man's Dancing Queen, Stephanie.]
She was the icon of the dance segment.
She just goes by "Stephanie" now.
But she was "Cheonmu Stephanie."
(Heavenly Dancer)
She was Cheonmu Stephanie
of "The Grace."
All the members had nicknames.
"Heavenly Dancer Stephanie"
"Divine Beauty Lina,"
"Soft Voice Sunday," "Delightful Dana."
Delightful Dana?
Her tone changed!
She sounds like a middle aged woman.
- I was the youngest.
- You were!
I'm still the youngest on this team.
[Big gestures and greasy comments.]
Even her walk is different.
What's with that gesture?
Her movements, too.
She speaks like an old lady.
I don't know if it's possible, but I'll
try my best to "shake it" later on.
Yes, Stephanie!
Next up after Stephanie
is Kim Jung Nam!
[The return of Turbo's engine,
Kim Jung Nam.]
I'm a Turbo fan.
- How many years has it been?
- 20 years.
You're coming back as Turbo!
Our album is being released
tonight at midnight.
["Again", Turbo's new song.]
[Turbo's coming back
with a stronger engine!]
[Jong Kook, Jung Nam, and Mikey.
After 20 years]
[they're coming back as a whole,
and the countdown starts!]
How does it feel
to be reunited as Turbo?
We were a dyad before,
and now we're a trio.
They don't really say dyad nowadays.
- Dyad?
- A dyad?
Every comment is
taking me down memory lane.
We were a dyad, but became a trio.
So my part shrunk.
- Your rap part?
- When we record and I make a mistake
I should say "okay" to Jong Kook
but instead I politely say "yes."
Time has passed.
It's as if you're treating
him like a rookie.
[Turbo is coming soon!]
And next up is Andy!
[King of Hearts, Andy.]
Back in the day,
he used to do heart dances.
Do you remember Andy's heart dance?
Yes, that's right.
Everyone was dancing
the heart dance in clubs.
He was there, at the clubs.
[He goes to clubs to spread the dance?]
Do you remember the heart dance?
[Seol Hyun mastered
the heart dance?]
She's the best!
Why are you smiling?
Because I like her!
Why do you keep asking?
Gary, be cool!
[He can't keep a poker face
in front of Seol Hyun.]
- Andy!
- Yes?
It's been such a long time.
Can we see the original dance?
Is it the front pocket
or the back pocket?
- From the top?
- From his heart.
[I am the Prince of Hearts.]
He's still good!
B.I. and Bobby, too!
[It's awesome!]
But it's so interesting!
It's so smooth when he does it!
He's the original!
- You need to do it like this, nowadays.
- Stop it!
Don't do it!
- Don't make that tiny heart!
- He's so weird!
Here, here!
[Here's a gift!]
- It's weird!
- It's not!
It's weird!
Jin Sook, look at this.
[This is how I feel for you.]
Why are you taking your
heart out of your bum!
Jin Sook, it's from my back pocket!
You know me, right?
It's my back pocket!
[Be thoughtful when
taking your hearts out!]
We'll be looking forward to
Andy's active participation!
And everyone probably
knows him already, but
it's Eagle Eye with his glaring eyes!
[Eagle Eye, Lee Jong Soo.]
You probably all remember
his glaring eyes.
Eagle Eye!
More than anything, you...
He doesn't say his name!
Do I not have a name?
She's Jin Sook, too.
Can you make
eye contact with Ji Hyo?
I think she'll fall for him
in less than a second.
[He's exercising his
extra ocular muscles.]
Please stare into his eyes.
You'll see why his name is Eagle Eye.
Ladies, come and experience this.
[He's pouring his love
and passion for Blank Ji.]
[Oh my god!]
Eagle Eye!
[I haven't given up on you yet!]
[You can't look directly
at the intensity.]
He's so cool!
[Eagle Eye is still passionate
as ever ten years later.]
Eagle Eye has come back!
Please look forward
to his part here today!
This time, we'll introduce
the new X-man members!
[It's finally time to
introduce Team Ji's members.]
It's Seol Hyun!
[2015's hottest, Seol Hyun.]
She's been on Running Man
many times before.
She's like family, now.
Why are you stepping forward?
[Let's spectate together.]
When else would we
get to see her in person?
They've all turned their heads.
You're too much!
You too, stop moving forward!
I can't see because of you!
Get lost!
If you move forward to see Seol Hyun,
I move forward then he moves forward!
Then he moves forward!
We can't film like this!
[Seol Hyun is top priority
over filming.]
I'm really sorry, but I
would really like it if Jong Kook
stopped turning his back to me.
You seem awkward.
I'm sad because our team is like
a duck egg from Nakdong River.
- A duck egg from Nakdonggang River?
- I haven't heard that in so long!
A duck egg from Nakdonggang River.
(Being in misery)
That's like a proverb.
That's what my dad used to say!
I almost cried!
My face is red!
Seol Hyun, could you
show us a few moves?
- From "Like a cat."
- Like a cat!
[They're all pretending to be a cat.]
I won't do it, so don't do it either.
Please show us.
The movement is like a cat.
[They're happy just watching!]
[Meow]
[Gentlemen, be joyous!]
She did it to me! All the guys
will think she did it to them!
[We saw it.]
You've done everything.
- We got good footage.
- She's cute.
- Gary isn't doing much today.
- He's not interested.
Why did your face turn so red?
[He can't keep a straight face.]
[What will be the end to Gary's
pure love for Seol Hyun?]
[Gary charges to win
Seol Hyun's heart!]
[Gary is starting his plan on
getting Seol Hyun's heart!]
[And!]
[Gary and Seol Hyun are writing
new history in "Of course"?]
Seol Hyun, let's play a game!
[How will their fate turn out?]
Next up, we have the Queen of comedy
Kim Ji Min!
[Queen of comedy, Kim Ji Min.]
We haven't filmed X-man in a while...
have you ever thought you could
do well if you were on the show?
I think I would have done well
in the game, "Of course."
I think I would've done
better than Lee Ji Hyeon.
[She's challenging the
Queen of "Of course"?]
I think Ji Min would do well, too.
But since she's married,
I can't really talk about her past.
[That's harsh.]
- That's not how you play the game.
- Really?
You're not supposed to
dig up the past!
Aren't you supposed to
send people off?
We'll see them later in "Of course"!
[The true Queen of "Of Course"
will be determined!]
My type, my type.
It's iKON!
[The hottest iKON, Bobby and B.I.]
It's their first time
on a variety show.
- Really?
- Is it really your first time?
I took a Cheongsimhwan.
(A pill that calms him down)
He probably thinks that
he's speaking very loud.
Isn't your voice a lot
quieter than expected?
Yes, it's quiet.
Let's start with a shout.
Yeah!
You need to be twice as loud.
He's so good at rapping, though!
- Is it your first time too, Bobby?
- Yes.
Why wasn't iKON
on any variety shows?
We were working hard on our music.
Then what about me?
Don't I work on music, too?
[Musician Gary is upset.]
[We didn't mean it like that...]
We will be looking forward
to your participation today.
Please give iKON
a big round of applause!
We will officially be starting now.
2015 Running Man and
X-man collaboration!
Dance session!
The music is old-schooled!
[The subtitles will
also be old-schooled.]
[2015's hottest icon,
Seol Hyun's up first!]
[Shy, shy]
[Shift in attitude, head banging.]
Seol Hyun, dance with confidence!
[Heart dance 2015,
Seol Hyun's version.]
[I like the heart dance.]
This is awesome!
I like this!
[All the men's hearts are melted.]
[Did you get a heart attack?
I'm the hottest, Seol Hyun.]
Next up is Andy!
[The original heart dancer, Andy!]
[Do you remember this heart?]
[Of course!]
[His heart hasn't
changed in ten years.]
[My body remembers it!]
[Do you remember these graphics?]
[The best heart.]
[I love it!]
[Chae Yeon's dance
is in full force!]
[Should we go back to ten years ago?]
[Are you ready?]
[Sexy]
[This is it!]
[Her seductive instincts.
Her name is Chae Yeon.]
[I like it!]
[This is how you do it!]
[Jin Sook of Jinri]
(Pun: Jin Sook is always right)
[Asia's Prince, Kwang Soo!]
[Roll]
[Innovative moves!]
Dance!
I said dance!
[His writhing series continues.]
I'm really sorry...
[The music is off.]
I'm sorry, but this isn't how you do it.
You have to keep
the feeling going.
It's the first time that the
music's been cut off on X-man.
- This can't happen.
- I'm sorry.
We'll try it again.
We'll liven up the atmosphere again!
[Good luck!]
Please give us the music!
[He lost his confidence
but he still tries hard!]
[He's cute.]
[Do I do it like this?]
[He tries hard!]
[Giraffe is here!]
Yeah, that's it!
That's the one!
[Kwang Soo safely passed
the dance session!]
[The big kid of hip-hop, Bobby!]
Bobby!
[All the ladies' type!]
[Krumping]
[She went blank at
his shocking dance.]
Next up is B.I!
[He's a prepared rookie, B.I!]
[His moves come naturally.]
B.I, give us a little more!
B.I, a little more!
[Poppin']
[Can I do that?]
Yeah, it's awesome!
[He reminded us of all the
dancing machines in the past.]
[Approved!]
[Dancing machine, Kim Jung Nam!]
[Of course!]
[The subtitles that waited for
this man ten years ago...]
[Dancing machine]
B.I, dance with him!
[You can't fool your age.]
[Kim Jung Nam and B.I:
a collaboration performance.]
[Give and take!
They're a great match!]
[Hooray!]
[Perfect teamwork between the two.]
Eagle Eye, Lee Jong Soo!
[What dance did Jong Soo do?]
[Shy, shy]
Eagle Eye!
[It's back, the dirty dance!]
[Shocked]
[He's quite aggressive.]
[His dance is in between seducing
and provoking a dispute.]
[He still has desire
left in his eyes.]
[He's back, Eagle Eye!]
[Forever a Queen, Lee Ji Hyeon!]
One, two, three, four!
[She's doing the wave!]
She's good!
[With the same moves
as ten years ago.]
Let's go Ji Min!
[Happy virus Kim Ji Min!]
[Burst of laughter]
[Cute dance]
[The hottest comedian.]
She's so cute!
[Kkuk also approved!]
Next is Kim Jong Kook!
[Kkuk's "cool" dance.]
Finally, next up is Stephanie!
[Full of anticipation]
[The girl who became a legend,
Stephanie.]
[Shall we enjoy this like it's 2005?]
[She deserves the name.]
Awesome!
[A heavenly dance that sends
shivers down your spine.]
[She's speeding up her dance.]
[Her dance is a classic
for dance session.]
[They're going wild.]
We will be starting officially!
[Running Man and X-man's
collaboration starts now!]
[The table's full of presents like
a typical Running Man Christmas.]
[It's as if Santa left them
a gift for their hard work, dancing.]
[It's filled with
sweet Christmas cakes.]
[They're re-energizing.]
While you eat casually
you will be given a secret command.
Ha Ha, would you like to go up first?
[They will be given the command:
"you are/aren't X-man."]
Please pay close attention
to his expression.
[Running Man Producer]
The current Running Man PD used to
give the command on X-man back then.
Hello?
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
It's been a while.
[It's been a while
since this atmosphere.]
[You are/aren't]
[X-man.]
That's right!
Pay attention!
[Overreacting Ha Ha, is he X-man?]
[You are/aren't]
[X-man.]
[Unresponsive B.I is X-man?]
Please let me be X-man!
[Is this all a scheme?]
[Is the hottest girl given
an important role?]
[Is the glare of X-man?]
[Is it nervous Kwang Soo?]
Is it true?
[What's the meaning
behind Stephanie's smile?]
Me?
[Ji Min's casual acting is suspicious.]
[Is it silent Andy?]
[Did Bobby smile for the special role?]
[Queen]
[Ace]
[And Mr. Capable.
We can't tell with their reactions...]
[Could it be Big-nose?]
What?
It's me?
Really?
[Terrible actor Gary, is it him?]
[Running Man Christmas special,
X-man has been selected!]
[We filmed this part
in the same style.]
[X-man's counterattack
is about to start.]
Who is it?
- I'm so curious!
- You're dead!
[Who is X-man?]
[X-man is starting to act
as a spy from now on.]
[The Running Man have experienced
countless of betrayals for five years.]
[Will they be able to keep
their identities hidden?]
[They come one by one
in their changed uniforms.]
What's with him... his pants!
[Yoo Hyuk wore his pants backwards.]
B.I and Bobby wore
their pants properly...
[I copied them
because they looked cool...]
I'm actually so embarrassed!
- I doubted it.
- Ha Ha did it, too.
Why didn't you guys
wear it backwards?
[The trend changed already!
The concept is to wear it low.]
[It's a long and rough path
to being a fashionista.]
Now, it's time to
play a game altogether.
We will start "Go fight"!
(modification of Tug-of-war)
You probably already know
you have teams on both sides.
We've done this on Running Man
a couple times over water.
We're very used to it.
Both teams will play
best two out of three.
X-man has been selected.
It will be too easy if X-man
actively plays their part now.
- That's true.
- Yes.
That is why there is R-man today,
since it's a collaboration.
[R-Man?
What's that?]
R-man will be helping X-man.
[R-man will help X-man.]
So when they got the call,
did they say "you are R-man"?
[The R-man was already assigned!]
[Who is it?]
[While everyone was
getting changed.]
[The person coming out
of the building is?]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
Why me?
[What's going on?]
[He's laughing?]
Because we're holding an
X-man special on Running Man
we will be giving you
a special mission.
You are not X-man.
However, you are R-man.
[I am R-man?]
You will be helping so that
X-man's team loses.
You will protect X-man
with different tactics.
If X-man doesn't get
caught until the end
it will be X-man
and R-man's victory.
X-man will know that there's R-man
but they won't know who it is.
I was a little upset
that I wasn't X-man.
[Will Kwang Soo be able to
carry out his role well?]
[His top priority is finding
X-man in order to help them!]
If we can't find out, then the prize
is shared between X-man and R-man.
So we could be confused whether
they're X-man or R-man.
It could be R-man!
To make it seem like they're X-man?
You're top on the list!
You're pretty suspicious.
Anyway, if X-man succeeds
then R-man will also win
and share the prize.
Rux... X-man and Running Man...
- Rux Man?
- What's Rux Man?
It's a collaboration between
R-man and X-man.
[I need to find X-man!]
I'm sorry but,
is this even competition?
[The proficient and experienced Team Kim
vs. the less-prepared newbies Team Ji.]
If X-man is on that team
isn't the mission way too easy?
If Jong Kook is X-man,
we're in big trouble.
Exactly.
[Is Kkuk X-man?]
You need to pay attention!
People do stuff like this on camera!
[X-man will be giving hints on camera.]
[They need to observe carefully!]
[Kwang Soo makes an
R sign instead of an X.]
Okay, we're starting!
[Round one of "Go fight."]
[Big-nose pushes
Seol Hyun to the front.]
[Goddess' shield]
[Complaints]
Let's go without Seol Hyun!
Why?
We lost, we lost!
[The guys on Team Kim are
helpless in front of Seol Hyun.]
Are you kidding?
I will push you!
[In a foul mood.]
Chae Yeon returned as a heroine.
She's intense!
[If they have heroine
Chae Yeon on Team Kim]
[they have Ace Song
Ji Hyo on Team Ji.]
Jin Sook, you need to go ahead.
You sound so awkward!
You guys don't seem close!
[Go fight starts with a polite bow.]
[Heroine vs. Ace]
It's no joke.
[She's already using her
superhuman strength.]
[Surprised]
[But Ji Hyo isn't easy either!]
[Both teams are
already pretty intense.]
[She's not that weak.]
[It's no joke!]
[But, they're making the
two women work so hard...]
[Oh, my arm hurts.]
Men should come forward!
- Come forward!
- Am I crazy?
[Tiger is waiting for him,
why would he?]
It makes sense.
Look, Suk Jin folded his arms.
[One on one match]
Let's finish it quickly!
[Team Kim's runner will be Kkuk.]
[Who will be Team Ji's runner?]
[Seol Hyun is Team Ji's runner.]
- Not Seol Hyun.
- No, we can't.
[Jong Kook, are you going
to fight against me?]
[This drives me nuts.]
[What should I do now?]
[Give me your hand, Jong Kook.]
But, he does what she says.
Just push her if you're
not going to date her.
It's not that.
[Seol Hyun tamed Tiger in one second.]
[Conflict]
[No, I fell!]
What are you doing?
[We won!]
[All upset!]
I tripped!
It's been such a long time!
[Could Jong Kook be X-man?]
[How could Mr. Capable
fail so easily?]
Come out!
Bring it on!
[I don't care who she it.]
[Smile]
["Hello, Jung Nam!"]
[What do I do?]
[The smile of an Uncle.]
He won't attack her, will he?
[Heart attack...
I can't look her in the eyes.]
Look her in the eyes.
Jung Nam, don't fall for her!
[Seol Hyun slowly pulls him to her side.]
[At that moment,
Kwang Soo's sudden attack!]
[Holding his leg]
[Flop]
[She out him easily.]
[With Seol Hyun's beauty,
they eliminated two men!]
[Turbo Brothers lost too easily.]
We don't know how strong iKON is.
Andy, show the power of Shinhwa.
[Andy is really strong.]
[Andy of Shinhwa vs. iKON B.I]
[Tight]
[It's neck and neck.]
[B.I grabbed the
opportunity and attacks.]
[Andy uses the strength of B.I!]
[B.I was pulled inside Team Kim.]
[Chaos]
[Many Team Kim members
are out in the middle of chaos.]
[Only Andy survived.]
[Andy tried to hold it out,
but out.]
[Team Ji wins by chance.]
[Team Kim vs. Team Ji]
[0:1]
We lost too easily, didn't we?
Why do you think we lost too easily?
It's all because of you!
She didn't say much back then.
I'm surprised, Chae Yeon's changed!
[By the way...]
Everyone suspects you
for being the X-man.
No, I'm not.
I'm not X-man.
Aren't you that?
R-kong or something.
[It's not R-kong, it's R-man.]
[Embarrassed]
It's not, R-kong, but R-man.
Don't put up Seol Hyun first.
[The more I think about it,
the more suspicious he is.]
[She pulled him slightly,
and he's out...]
[And he even rolls down by himself.]
[Kkuk and Jung Nam are suspicious!]
We'll start the second round now.
[Go fight, second round!]
[This time, Young Blood
Bobby comes forward.]
[Roar]
[Relaxed]
[Nervous]
People at the back, watch out!
Bobby, we've tried that before...
[Dash!]
[He fell!]
[But, Kkuk fell, too!]
[By sacrificing himself,
they got Mr. Capable out.]
[Full scale war between
Eagle Eye and Giraffe.]
[His eye shake so fast!]
Are you okay?
How many fingers?
Three, I'm fine.
[No matter what Kwang Soo does,
he looks so clumsy.]
[Andy's sudden attack!]
[He pulls Kwang Soo's arm.]
[Kwang Soo and Ha Ha were
tangled and out together.]
Wait a moment!
[Other runners fall one by one.]
[Both teams have a man and two women.]
[Hyper]
Calm down!
Both teams have a male runner
and three female runners.
[It's the same, but
they look very different.]
Seol Hyun, you go first.
[He even pushes Seol Hyun.]
[Again, Seol Hyun's eye attack?]
[He staggered.]
[He comes to himself
and tosses her to the female players.]
[She's out like that.]
[Thrown]
[Oh, no!
I can't believe Seol Hyun is thrown!]
[Thrown to the floor]
[Big-nose can't turn back now.]
[Charge!]
[Huh?
He's out so naturally and easily!]
[Big-nosed Brother is suspicious, too.]
[Ace Song Ji Hyo
doesn't hesitate to attack.]
[She's out with
Stephanie and Chae Yeon.]
[Team Ji's only survivor is Kim Ji Min.]
[Sympathy...]
[lie down flat]
[She struggles, but out.]
That makes Team Kim the winner!
[Team Kim vs. Team Ji]
[1:1]
It's one to one now!
Do you want to have men's game?
Okay, we'll have a men's battle.
[Five on five]
I'll walk over you like a cat.
And take them down easy!
Good luck, Team Ji!
[Cute and lively]
[They're refreshed!]
Even the opponent looks refreshed.
[We gained strength.]
Thank you, Seol Hyun.
That was nice!
Ready!
[On the cheers]
[the third round of Go fight starts!]
Look!
Why don't Jong Kook and
Jong Soo use only one arm?
Let's play fair even if we have to lose.
Sure, I'll use one arm.
We'll use both arms.
- That's better, right?
- Yes.
[It feels like they tricked me.]
[No plans, no tactics!]
[We'll charge now!]
[The battle is on!]
[Kim Jung Nam and Ji Suk Jin are out.]
[Even Gary's out.]
[Currently, Team Kim has four players,
and Team Ji has three.]
[Mad house]
[Andy, Bobby, and B.I are out.]
[Andy and Jong Soo versus
Kwang Soo.]
[Giraffe falls like a paper.]
One, two, three!
[I should've been out earlier.]
[I'm suffering like this,
because I'm the last one...]
[Team Kim wins the
third round of Go fight.]
X-man is among that team.
No, I think it's Jong Kook.
It seems he's X-man.
So many look suspicious.
The first game, Go fight's
winner is Team Kim.
[Who do you think X-man is?]
Jong Kook?
He's really strong, you know.
But he keeps losing.
Jong Kook is an ace,
but he loses at every game.
I think Kim Jong Kook is suspicious.
He fell down, when I
pushed him really lightly.
So, I think he's suspicious.
I think it's Seol Hyun.
When she was pushed
she could have grabbed
at least one player.
She didn't even try.
She didn't resist at all.
[Who will be the X-man
on the special collaboration?]
[R-man Lee Kwang Soo appears.]
[R-man has to guess
who X-Man is and help.]
This is... more difficult
than I thought.
As far as I know, Andy's competitive
and strong, too.
He was out easily today.
[R-man Lee Kwang Soo decides
to help Andy.]
Everyone was waiting for this moment.
This game represents X-man,
"Say of course" game!
[Say, of course!]
You aged while I was away.
Of course!
[There have been harsh
and revealing words!]
Of course!
[No matter what your opponent says
you have to say "of course!"
[You'll lose If you can't answer
or get angry.]
First, we have the Queen of the game.
Why don't Ji Hyun and Jong Kook
show us how to play the game?
[It's a practice round.]
I'll sacrifice...
I can't believe I can actually see it.
It's been such a long time.
They used to divide the screen.
I'm facing Jong Kook?
It feels like a dream.
Me, too.
I see Ha Ha over there.
He was at the same spot.
Jong Soo was there, too.
Looking at this side.
Everyone was there.
I was in the army that time,
and we used to curse at you.
[Upset]
Women think he's romantic.
But, he was kind of gross.
[The scene that made the
soldier Kwang Soo feel gross.]
Do you like Eun Hye?
Do you hate her?
[Kkuk had to say "of course"
to win the game.]
[He walks to her and
carefully covers her ears.]
Of course!
[It was one of the
best scenes of X-man.]
Hand off!
With your dirty hands!
We were so upset!
[Embarrassed]
Let's start the game now!
It's been a long time!
Starting with Kim Jong Kook.
[Lee Ji Hyun vs. Kim Jong Kook]
Are you happy with your married life?
[Hesitate]
She can't answer to that?
[Everyone's surprise]
I was just greeting.
[It turned out to be a sticky question?]
Of course.
If she answered three seconds later,
she could've lost.
I thought this was easy to answer.
You should've said
"of course!" right away.
When were you filming X-man back then...
[She's not going to ask that, is she?]
When were you filming X-man back then,
you were dating Yoon Eun Hye, right?
[You were actually dating
Yoon Eun Hye, right?]
[Embarrassed]
Finally, she asked that!
I was curious!
[For the past ten years!]
[And... the man couldn't answer.]
[The romantic scene made
our hearts flutter.]
[Finally, the truth reveals today!]
What's your answer?
Finally, it's time!
Answer me, truthfully!
There was a news article about this.
I'm so curious!
Please, edit this out!
[Too bad...]
You shouldn't ask this question.
This question makes me fall.
- But, you weren't falling.
- I didn't, but you didn't hold me.
Actually, Ji Hyun almost fell.
With your question.
The Queen of Of Course,
almost collapsed.
You need to hold me.
Applause for these two.
[That was harsh.]
[Nervous]
It's deadly!
A long time has passed,
so I wasn't sure.
- But it's still shocking.
- I have a spasm.
Who's the first player?
- A girl should go.
- Jin Sook should go.
Chae Yeon!
[She's like a shy girl.]
[Team Ji's new face]
Ji Min!
This won't be easy.
- It's a big match.
- I'm expecting a lot.
First, Ji Min will start.
[Chae Yeon vs. Kim Ji Min]
I kept watching you
since I arrived here.
You know your foundation
creased in your wrinkles?
[Wrinkle attack]
[She's so harsh!]
Suck it up!
[Not yet!]
She almost lost.
[It was expected,
but the impact was very big.]
I knew she would say that.
Of course, I'm fine.
I can suck it up.
You... you...
you...
- She's embarrassed.
- Her face turned red!
I'm not going to laugh.
You...
You'll lose if you laugh.
Did you stop growing
when you were in elementary?
Of course.
[She doesn't care.]
Maybe she did.
You...
A young guy to you would
be in his thirties?
[Straightforward!]
[About to cry]
[I thought dissing
between rappers were harsh...]
Just give up!
Can you still play?
[She's changed!]
She's resilient!
Isn't this powerful enough?
She would've given up.
She's stronger now.
You... got your outfit
from the children's section right?
That wasn't bad!
Of course!
She's so cool about it!
You go to the children's store.
If you had married earlier,
your son would've been in university.
[She could've been a parent.]
This won't do.
Kim Ji Min wins!
How can you attack me for my age!
[I'm sorry, Chae Yeon.]
She could hold for the second time.
She was doing a good job.
Ji Min is so strong.
Ji Min is a new queen.
Jong Soo!
[Glaring Eagle Eye, Lee Jong Soo]
I don't really know him well.
If you have nothing,
just seduce her.
[Seducing while playing "of course"?]
You know you can't do
anything without me?
I have a crush on you, Ji Young.
- You know what I'm doing right now?
- I don't know.
I'm thinking about you.
[Lee Jong Soo fascinated countless
women with his glaring eyes.]
[Will his glaring still work?]
It's been 10 years.
My heart is pounding.
But, I'm not sure it's because
it's been a long time
or because I see Ji Min.
[Surprised]
It's on!
[Eagle Eye is alive!]
He's not dead yet.
It's so awkward!
He's greasy like mayonnaise.
[Lee Jong Soo vs. Kim Ji Min]
What you just said...
[She's already...]
It didn't get me going at all.
[I'm not excited at all, you know?]
[His glaring eyes are counted
as nasty eyes now.]
[She's... too strong.]
[He was hitting on her bravely]
[but she's indifferent.]
[Is he going to step down like this?]
- That's too bad!
- Give him another chance.
I've seen this before.
- Then, say "of course."
- Of course.
[Blanked out]
- My brain is empty.
- You know your face is so red!
I thought you turned
into a frilled lizard!
- It's so funny.
- I'll do an acrostic poem.
- With Ji Min's name?
- All of a sudden?
- Please say the initial for me.
- Kim.
Kim Ji Min!
- Ji.
- Jigeum(now), we'll start dating.
- Min.
- Minmang haji? (Aren't you embarrassed?)
I'm embarrassed!
Of course.
[Ji Min will answer.]
Lee Jong Soo!
Jong!
Jongmal... (actually)
I've been watching you this whole time.
"Jongmal" is close enough to "Jungmal."
It's allowed.
She's been watching him.
Soojak burijima.
(Don't even think about it!)
[She answers with angry eyes.]
[Eye to an eye!]
[Kim Ji Min wins two rounds in a flash.]
Old X-man members!
What happened to the original members?
She's the new queen!
I haven't hit on her yet...
Take a break for now.
Let Seol Hyun do it.
[The hottest idol, Seol Hyun]
[Hesitant]
No one's daring to play!
Who wants to play?
Ha Ha? Andy?
[Against Seol Hyun?]
Play, Andy.
[To play against, Seol Hyun,
Playboy Ha Ha should.]
I'm not sure if Seol Hyun
can take him.
He used to be a playboy back then.
Everyone here is witness.
[To his wife]
I do this for work.
Ha Ha will start first.
Go, Ha Ha!
You've gotten even prettier.
Of course.
[It's Seol Hyun's turn.]
You...
are shorter than me, right?
[You're shorter than me, right?]
It is true!
[Seol Hyun, did you have to do that?]
Let him take a break!
[With her angelic smile,
she's being straightforward!]
[Everyone turns like this here.]
[Let Ha Ha take a break.]
Andy should go.
[Everlasting pretty boy, Andy]
Seol Hyun's doing well!
Why do you have so many weaknesses?
Try, Andy.
You should feel it.
You hear that from
someone nice and pretty.
- It's okay.
- It's Andy vs. Seol Hyun.
- I'll finish it now.
- Are you sure?
Can he finish now?
She won't be able to say yes to this.
Will you marry me?
[Will you marry me?]
Just marry him.
[You mean, marriage?]
If you say yes,
you have to marry him.
It's just a game!
[His proposal turned
both teams upside down.]
Seol Hyun!
You should answer it properly!
[No one can answer
to that question easily...]
Of course!
[It's a good news!]
[Congratulations on Andy
and Seol Hyun's marriage!]
I'm finally getting married!
That's too bad...
Do you want to have a drink with me?
They even tossed him in the air,
even though it's a game.
She still said "of course."
[The two who agreed to get married.]
Let's get a divorce!
[Let's get a divorce!]
[A bolt out of the blue]
[Their short marriage life's ended.]
[She's brilliant!]
[Team Kim vs. Team Ji]
[0:3]
[Dizzy, dizzy]
Who didn't play this game yet?
- B.I didn't play.
- B.I!
[iKON's leader, B.I]
From Team Kim?
Stephanie!
It looks like B.I can play it well.
I don't really know him.
What do I do?
B.I will start.
You know, I don't really
know you, either.
[Shocked]
[She's losing her mind.]
[They never expected it from B.I,
but so happy to see it.]
[He's shown his talent
for variety shows.]
Actually...
Fannie's face turned red.
Of course.
[It's Stephanie's turn.]
Only your name is English, right?
- Of course.
- What's your real name?
- Kim Han Bin.
- It's a cool name.
What's B.I?
What does it stand for?
I've never been to the States.
[Oh... right.]
[Every single word is like an attack.]
Many drops make a flood.
B.I's turn.
I don't know if this is okay...
- he helped me with this me.
- Say it.
If you're Stephanie, are you ttang Fani?
(digging the ground)
[What was that?]
It wasn't my idea.
- I'm warning you.
- It's just an attack.
[It rhymes, though.]
Of course.
If you're B.I,
are your underpants B.I.C?
[With an old brand name
of underwear, Stephanie wins.]
It's fine, it's fine!
[That's how it is?]
[Team Kim vs. Team Ji]
[1:3]
[Now's the moment!]
The queen has to play now.
[Queen of "Of Course," Lee Ji Hyun]
Did you get buff by taking steroids?
You're actually E.T., right?
Are you still constipated?
[I'm the Queen of "Of Course Game!"]
[After 10 years away,
her new target is...]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[How good will the game be today?]
He can say harsh things.
Yes, he's incredible.
Among the Running Man members,
Kwang Soo is the best player for this.
But, Kwang Soo falls in love easily.
- You want to start first?
- Yes.
[Lee Ji Hyun vs. Lee Kang Soo]
I wonder... if you know
you're prettier... May I ask?
[That's not how you play.]
You should drop the honorifics.
It's the rule for the game.
- Did know, you're prettier on TV?
- Yes, I know that.
Of course!
You're doing good!
She's so reliable.
She looks like an old sister
who came to avenge.
[With her warm smile]
[will she start attacking now?]
Not too long ago, you made a movie
in a fish costume, right?
[You mean... this?]
I heard you're practicing for
the next movie as a turtle?
[Will his next movie be
"Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles"?]
[It's funny but sad...]
[She's very sharp.]
[It seems he's hurt.]
It's okay.
You can do it.
It's fine.
Wake up!
She teats my heart!
[Maybe I was too harsh
from the beginning?]
Three, two...
[If he can't admit it, he'll lose.]
Of c...
- Who do we have now?
- It's four to four.
Four to four?
This is the last match!
Gary didn't play.
[Running Man's rhapsodist, Gary!]
They have ha Ha.
Ha Ha was taking a break.
[Running Man's two rivals battle!]
[They're close, but
they don't get along.]
[Bickering, they've fought so much!]
[More than anything, they get upset
when they lose against each other.]
It's so upsetting
to lose against him!
[It's time to settle!]
What a big match!
Yes, it's a big match!
As you said...
They're the rivals of Running Man.
They're real rivals.
I don't even want to see his face.
It's getting funny already.
You start, Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha vs. Gary]
You were standing next to B.I...
[He's going to attack my appearance.]
- You were standing next to B.I...
- I'm laughing already.
- I see, I see.
- Let me ask you this.
Are you a squid?
(Squid became a byword for being ugly.)
[Gae... quid?]
[Laugh]
Gary, you're not a squid!
It's okay, Gary!
[He kind of looks like a squid.]
Can you play the music?
[I like it!]
[When you're upset and annoyed]
[let's dance to "I like it!"]
It's okay, it's fine.
I haven't requested this music
in such a long time!
I'm sorry, but it was too funny.
Wasn't it funny?
[Even the queen keeps laughing.]
They can't stop laughing.
Why are you laughing so hard?
[Because I imagined.]
I feel shameful for myself.
Because, I keep trying to
put my hand in the pocket.
[He forgot his pants are inside out.]
I keep doing this.
The squid was too harsh!
It's fine.
[Will Gary be able to attack him back?]
Squids are beautiful looking!
It's fine.
The woman you really like,
isn't Byul, is it?
She's Go Eun.
Of course!
This upsets me!
I get upset when he does that!
- Don't do that.
- Or everyone.
Don't add any explanations!
- He said, everyone.
- I warned you!
You... Squid!
[This won't do, play the music again!]
[Forget the hatred!]
[Everyone, dance!]
[I like it!]
I saved you.
Suck it up, we need to win.
- Are we tied?
- Hey, you!
[Upsetting]
[He can make Gary frustrated.]
What's he doing?
Anteater.
Your house... is in Noryangjin, right?
[Noryangjin Fish Market?]
Are you talking about the fish market?
Yes, of course!
Of course, he's a squid.
[Everyone's laughing except Gary.]
Would a squid live in Gangnam?
Because of the squid...
That's too powerful.
[Blank Ji helps him.]
Only Ji Hyo helps Gary.
They're Mung Gae.
(Sounds like sea squirt)
Gary?
- You think you're the god of reggae?
- Of course!
I hate it!
He doesn't hesitate at all.
He sounds like he really admits it.
[It's time to end now.]
Let's make a cool ending.
Just finish him now.
Are you actually dating Song Ji Hyo?
[Hot issue]
Many people want to know.
[If X-man had the "Of Course Couple,"
Running Man has the "Monday Couple."]
What are you hinting at?
[Five years ago,
they met for the first time.]
[One by one]
[they build memories together.]
[Little by little]
[they become close to each other.]
[On Mondays, Gary's been
dedicated to Ji Hyo.]
[But Seol Hyun came like spring breeze.]
[In short, his feeling for
their first meeting was]
heart attack!
[He'll tell the truth,
when the two women are present.]
[Finally...]
[he makes a move!]
[Will he admit that he's seeing Ji Hyo?]
[In front of Seol Hyun?]
Of course!
[Burst of laughter]
[This looks so familiar!]
[He parodies Kkuk.]
[Just tell me you've
always wanted to do it.]
There's someone
who shouldn't listen!
Someone shouldn't listen!
Why did you cover
Seol Hyun's ears?
Why cover Seol Hyun's ears?
Good job!
[I didn't see that coming,
but thank you Ha Ha.]
- We get to see that in ten years.
- It's a remake!
Do you... honestly like
- that program more than "Running Man"?
- You can say it, "Infinite Challenge."
Do you like "Infinity Challenge"
more than "Running Man"?
Is that real?
[The viewers are watching!]
[Running Man members
are right in front of him.]
Is that real?
[Is he walking away like this?]
Of course!
Did you plan for this?
That was incredible!
[What just happened?]
[It's shocking!]
We could even do it for men.
This actually happens while filming.
Funny things happened during this game.
Did you have to do that?
Squid!
If you go out and get some air...
you'll become a dried squid.
You know that?
[It's the best bar snack!
Dried Gae... quid?]
[Come over here!]
Ha Ha wins!
See you at my house!
We'll play this again!
[The rivals' match isn't over...]
Therefore, Team Kim wins the game!
["Say, of course," 5 to 4]
[Team Kim wins.]
It's so funny.
You've been waiting a lot.
Finally, it's the time!
The air gets romantic
during this session.
"Couples and Warriors Forever!"
I'm sorry, are you a bandit?
I need to show off my charms today.
So, I'm wearing fashionable clothes.
That's too much.
[Chae Yeon looks exactly
the same as 10 years ago.]
[I'm the queen of fashion!]
[You are... the same.]
She's pretty.
- I think Seol Hyun is X-man.
- Me, too.
- That's what I was worried about.
I'm really bad at playing games.
Really, I suck at games,
and I'm weak.
She played against me,
but she's not bad.
Then, she's either X-man or R-man.
I don't know who X-man is.
- I don't know.
- You forget while you play games.
We all forget about it.
Exactly.
At first, we pay attention
- but then we totally forget.
- We think about it at the end again.
[More than anyone, I
need to find X-man...]
It must be awkward for you,
since you never did this before.
Gary, Kwang Soo and I...
If there's hell,
I think it's here.
[In between handsome men,
there's a squid hell.]
I worry about this team.
I see three beautiful ladies
but everyone might
want one specific person.
It'll be really competitive.
I think it'll be a mud fight!
I can see that already.
[Scared]
Ji Min, Song Ji Hyo, and Seol Hyun
they are all nice ladies.
I'm confused.
Ji Suk Jin, show your charms!
Let me ask if there's a person
you want to be a couple and play games?
Of course!
Since long time ago, I saw her on TV.
I think she's my type.
You're type?
You need to show your heart here,
so they will think about it.
I have only one person in mind
and I'll show it.
She's not Ji Hyo, is she?
[Who's Suk Jin's ideal type?]
[Nasty, nasty]
[He approaches to Seol Hyun first.]
[Then, walks to Ji Min.]
[Then, he glanced at Ji Hyo.]
It's so hot, it's so hot!
My heart burns because of you!
[Big-nosed Brother sings
enthusiastically.]
I can't see that, Director!
[He doesn't know the lyrics,
so he has a cheat sheet.]
[The cheat sheet is moving.]
[Big-nose follows the cheat sheet.]
You're inside of me!
[Suk Jin's ideal type is Ji Hyo?]
[She hates it.]
Is that Ji Hyo's picture?
[Uncomfortable]
[Ji Hyo, you know how I feel?]
[Unlucky]
[Lucky]
[The song is reaching it's climax.]
[Although he doesn't know the lyrics,
he knows the heart of a woman.]
[He slowly walks to Ji Hyo]
[and appeals to Ji Hyo at the end.]
Applause for Suk Jin!
Ji Hyo is his ideal type?
The funny thing about Suk Jin is...
whenever we have new guests,
he shows interests.
But when it comes to pick a couple,
he always picks Ji Hyo.
I know, right?
B.I will keep up the heat!
What did you prepare, B.I?
I'll dance.
[Oh, no!
I'll dance, too.]
Let's see B.I's dance!
Start the music!
[2005 style subtitle]
[B.I makes a sortie.]
[Looking forward]
He's warming up.
[He stretches in style.]
[His charisma blows
up everyone's heart!]
What was that?
[Splendid!]
[The innate ability to dance!]
[Please take my heart!]
[B.I is desperately heading to...]
[Ji Hyo!]
[Right in front of her,
he aggressively appeals to Ji Hyo.]
[What is he doing?]
[Wave]
[I'll fail...]
[Grabs her shoulders]
[we'll leave for love...]
Continuously!
[Gary's move!]
[As soon as he starts,
people laugh hard.]
[Flop]
[He tries to break dance!]
[Fall]
[Oh, no...
The years rolled by...]
Stop it!
- That's too bad.
- That's it?
Jae Suk, let him dance as same as B.I!
I can't do that!
- Try it, Gary!
- You can do it.
[Gary didn't show
all of his charms yet!]
How did you do that?
[Gary's trial for B.I's dance!]
He was doing this before.
[He stretches like B.I first.]
Seol Hyun smiles!
[Will Gary be able to show
off his charms like B.I?]
[The Radio Exercise like dance.]
[He walks to Seol Hyun in samba steps.]
[And the pelvic dance!]
[Is he trying to break dance again?]
[Flop]
[That's weird, I used
to do that in 2005.]
[I feel relieved, thanks to you.]
Gary, stop!
I haven't danced for so long!
Please give a round of applause
for B.I and Gary!
I've learned something.
Thank you!
This is the kind of dance
I want to do.
Why don't you try, Jae Suk?
Please start the music!
Please show me how.
I'll copy him.
Stretch, first.
[I'm starting.]
[How can it be the same?]
[It's totally different.]
[His face looks serious.]
[The pelvic dance is similar.]
I want to hit him!
[B.I's dance will be a hit!]
What was with your face?
I was immersed into the dance.
Next up is Bobby!
Among three ladies...
there's a person I'm a big fan of.
I like her.
- I want to confess my heart.
- Oh, my god!
Confess?
[Who will be the one to
hear Bobby's confession?]
Excuse me, lady.
All I want from you is time.
Please rewind the time
to become a girl.
Don't expect for me to call you sister.
You look a lot younger than me.
Look at the mirror, Ji Min.
There are lots of comedians around you.
Making people laugh is your occupation.
At least today, I want to
make you laugh, Baby!
Just for a day
please let me act like a man,
and not a younger brother.
[He impressed her!]
Ji Min's all set.
Please show us your dance, Bobby!
Please start the music for Bobby!
[Smiling]
[To win her heart, he dances, too.]
[The powerful krumping!]
[From a romantic rapper,
to a manly dancer!]
[While he's at it,
he shoots out hearts!]
[She's mine!]
[Standing ovation]
[Bobby successfully
showed off his charms!]
[They lost their will to fight.]
[Hooray, Bobby!]
He's incredible!
Are you ready, Kwang Soo?
[Right after that is Kwang Soo...]
I want to show the serious side of me.
Kwang Soo's been clumsy
and silly on the show.
Please show us how gorgeous
you are on the stage.
You will see how he is.
He sings very well, too.
Please play the music!
What's wrong with him?
Is he doing pantomime?
I think he's just making it up now.
[No matter what they say,
I'm very serious now.]
Such a nice song!
He's good at it!
[I want to express my heart!]
Is that Ji Hyo?
[Ji Hyo, you know how I feel?]
[Punch]
[He starts singing as
if nothing happened.]
[He fails to be serious in one minute.]
Your nose is bleeding.
[This time, he takes off his sweater]
[and gives it to Ji Min.]
[Why are you hitting on me?]
[The melody sounds even more sad.]
[At that time, Kwang Soo's
secret weapon arrives.]
[The only woman left is Seol Hyun.]
[Please, take my heart.]
[The climax of the song]
The "remories" of
loving you like crazy.
[He mixed up with "memory"
and "reminiscence."]
I asked them to make the key lower!
[He can't sing the high notes.]
[He might get a perfect voice today.]
[He wakes up at the end,
and confesses his love.]
[The coat he was going to give Ji Hyo]
[and the sweater he was
going to give Ji Min]
Applause for Kwang Soo!
[The giving tree, Kwang Soo]
Why did you take off your shoes?
[The men's session is over.]
Everyone, finally...
it's women's session!
First, Seol Hyun's stage!
[Looking forward to see]
Play the music!
[Seol Hyun starts off stretching, too.]
[She walks straight to Kwang Soo.]
[Seductive]
[Then, she seduces Gary.]
[The dance time!]
[Her secret weapon, the red scarf]
[Flashy]
[After throwing the scarf,
her dance heats up even more.]
[The powerful dance from
the slender figure!]
[She stirs up the stage]
[suddenly walks toward Gary.]
Gary!
[Come on, Gary!]
[The passionate couple dance!]
[Both of them are wearing all black,
what a charming dirty duo!]
[The only beneficiary of
Seol Hyun's stage is Gary.]
[I sang so hard for you...]
What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
Gary must be happy.
[What's Seol Hyun thinking?]
She's the best!
I'm happy even though I can't be paired.
[Ji Hyo's session!]
[She danced a lot for the members.]
[But she dances in front of him
for the first time.]
[Cute, cute]
Physiognomist, isn't that weird?
I'm already a king,
but you said I'd become a king.
Physiognomist!
Isn't that weird?
[It's somewhat similar.]
(Kim Jong Kook's thin and high
voice is referred as whiz.)
[Upset]
[Be careful of mosquitoes!]
It sounds exactly like Jong Kook!
[Approved]
That's it.
[Ji Min showed off her charm.]
Physiognomist and Kim Jong Kook.
It's time to choose now.
From Ji Suk Jin.
Do I say it now?
When I count to three,
say her name.
Everyone's heart is fixed.
And shout "Let's play games together!"
One, two, three!
Ji Hyo...
Let's play games together!
[Ji Hyo hated his performance,
did she change her mind?]
One, two...
[What'll be her answer?]
three!
Play games with Kwang Soo!
Why are you including me?
[I'm sorry.]
Next up is B.I!
They're older than me
but, I will drop honorifics.
Women like that kind of stuff.
- You'll be paired.
- Ji Hyo...
Let's play games together!
[Flutter, flutter]
She already set her mind
at the beginning!
[What's the meaning
behind Ji Hyo's expression?]
Please wait for the countdown.
Wait for the countdown.
One, two...
- Yes!
- Wait for three!
[Please answer after three.]
I'm slightly upset.
Aren't you too much?
I like it!
[Ji Hyo and B.I are a couple.]
Next up is Kang Gary.
- Gary, Kang?
- Seol Hyun!
Let's play games together!
[Seol Hyun is smiling?]
[Anticipation]
[No!]
[What's Seol Hyun's answer?]
Yes!
[How can this be?]
[Gary and Seol Hyun are a couple.]
[There's still a chance left
for Kwang Soo.]
And next is Bobby!
Ji Min!
Two, three...
Can you read that I'd be
a couple from my face?
[Bobby and Ji Min are a couple.]
Kwang Soo's left alone.
[The only one left is Lee Kwang Soo.]
Lee Kwang Soo,
you're the only one left.
I've been a fan since a long time.
And I will be sincerely sincere.
Don't fool around, be sincere.
One, two, three!
[Who is the woman that he'll pick?]
Seol Hyun.
[Seol Hyun, I'm here...]
[Will his sincerity
reach her heart?]
[A love triangle between Gary,
Seol Hyun and Kwang Soo.]
He's cool.
[It all depends on
Seol Hyun's choice!]
[A man who's trying to acquire love.]
[And a man who wants to protect it.]
[What will the final decision be?]
[A shocking plot twist!]
[Who will the final winner be?]
[The real party starts now!]
[This is the dance fever
of the original members!]
[The hot romance comes
back in ten years!]
[Where does Jong Soo, Chae Yeon,
and Jong Kook's love triangle end?]
[And finally,
the final mission is revealed!]
[Run, search and make a guess!]
[The identification of X-man
that no one expected]
[will be revealed next week!]
Subtitles by DramaFever