Subtitles by DramaFever
[Come out, come out wherever you are.]
[Watch out, we're coming to get you.]
[An assault on "that" man's house!]
[We'll see how lonely
and pitiful they are.]
[We're revealing the secret
lives of the men who live alone.]
[On a rainy autumn morning]
[the Running Man members
are visiting guests.]
Hello.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
[Nervous, excited]
I have thick clothing.
[Who are they visiting this early?]
The weather is pretty bad.
This is your partner for today's house.
Their house?
The actual house?
[A surprise attack at
their partner's house!]
- This place is...
- Kwang Gyoo's house.
[What just happened?]
Can I re-record it?
We were filming
"Same Bed Different Dreams" yesterday
and he said "see you tomorrow."
I asked him what he was talking about.
He has a big mouth.
- He's not allowed to tell, right?
- He knows he's going to be on the show.
But he doesn't know that
he's your partner.
This worked out well,
I felt bad.
I told him that he could
be a regular member.
That's why he came last time.
[For the 100 vs. 100 Race]
He'll know that it's me, by my voice.
[He covers the camera.]
He's not picking up.
- Who is it?
- See? It's Kwang Gyoo!
Who is it?
I'm your partner for today.
Darn, it's a guy!
Please open the door!
Do I get to be a regular?
What are you talking about!
Come in.
It's open.
I've never been to Kwang Gyoo's house.
[May spring bring
abundant joy and happiness.]
It's already winter!
[Waiting for spring year-round.]
He still has the spring message.
[The sparkly guy]
[Kim Kwang Gyoo.]
[Of all people...]
[I thought spring was
finally here today.]
Why did you put this on your door?
I'm a regular now, right?
Shiny, shiny.
I liked your shiny eyes.
[Introducing Running Man's
constant guest]
[Kwang Gyoo's lovely house.]
[No matter where we look]
It's winter already!
[it looks like the house of a man
who lives by himself.]
[Tsk, tsk]
Why did you put cellophane
tape on your window?
I'm a celebrity.
[It's more eye-catching.]
What were you trying to peek at?
Joong Hwan is moving in the
building across from me.
- The building next door.
- Really?
[The eye-catching items
are laying around.]
[He uses them... right?]
Don't leave these out because
there's a cameraman here!
[It's a bit much for the camera.]
[You need to be Kkuk-strong
to lift those.]
What is this?
[Fall]
I thought this was a
"Lava" pillow, but it isn't.
It was fuller before.
I feel so bad.
I had a fever a few days ago.
You were lying down here with it?
Why did you have a fever?
Let's go eat.
- Have you eaten?
- Yeah.
Why do you have so much medicine?
- Are you ill?
- No.
Why is there medicine everywhere?
"If you're living the
same today as yesterday"
"expecting a different
tomorrow is foolish."
"If you're desperate,
you will find a way."
"There might not be a tomorrow."
Why did you write these?
[Alone, a lonely tomorrow, desperate]
[and in 2070?]
"I won't be here in 2070?"
Why are you writing these?
I have bad luck this year.
I'm sensitive nowadays.
[The rice is healthy,
multi-grain rice.]
It's not just white rice.
It's multi-grain rice.
[How long has it been since he's had
someone over for breakfast.]
The eggs are warm.
Thanks for eating with me...
It feels special.
It totally different than eating alone.
I'm getting teary-eyed.
Why is Running Man so sad?
Don't think of me as a
senior who lives alone.
I wasn't thinking that at all.
[Sigh...]
What's wrong with you?
This is such a happy day!
It's the first time.
Running Man never
visited my house before.
Are you filming "I Live Alone" today?
What is this?
Are you sure this is Running Man?
Are you still on "I Live Alone"?
This is Gary's house.
Right?
Am I supposed to go in?
[Ha Ha, the uninvited guest.]
I love going to other people's houses.
Gary's expecting someone to visit.
- He knows?
- He knows, but
he doesn't when or who is coming.
If he's ready, that's a relief.
How come you and Gary aren't
getting along nowadays?
Whenever we did games together,
it was always like that.
It's because we're so close.
My new rival Gary is my new partner.
[Will Gary welcome
Ha Ha's sudden visit?]
Do I knock?
Can't I just go in?
[He rings the bell since it's early.]
[Puffy face]
[Gary just got up.]
- Who is it?
- It's me!
[Surprised]
Introducing, Kang Gary's house!
You have so many shoes!
My face is so puffy.
[He deeply sleeping
instead of getting ready.]
[Ta-da]
Are you invading my
house like Kwang Soo's?
This is his studio!
This is where he wrote
"Get Some Air."
I didn't make that song here!
I'm so curious!
This is his studio!
[Gary's never-before-seen studio.]
This is amazing.
This is where the party's at.
[He has a built-in
studio in the house.]
This is where the party's at.
[A place where lots of songs
were written and will be written.]
- It's so nice.
- Why are you here?
[Ha Ha doesn't know why he's here,
but he's having fun.]
This is so uncomfortable!
This is super uncomfortable!
The view is incredible!
What is this?
[Outside the window is an
excellent view of Han River.]
Did you do this on purpose?
Please sit down over there!
This is the party zone!
[Chaos]
I don't even jump on this sofa!
Oh, so you check stuff in this area?
- This is like a bar!
- There's nothing to eat!
- Let me have a glass of water.
- I'll pour it for you.
What is this?
My face is so puffed up...
[You should have woken up earlier...]
You have ice cream, too.
[Ha Ha briefly lived with him
before he got married.]
This brings back memories.
I should check the washing machine.
[He gave up.]
He already knew we were coming.
- He cleaned up everything.
- I was going to clean up...
- I was...
- Yes.
That's why you shouldn't
tell him beforehand!
[It was a trap he wasn't expecting.]
I look so ugly.
I should have gotten up earlier.
[They're supposed to
be on their way now.]
You knew that your partner was
going to come today, right?
[This won't do.]
Let me just wear my sunglasses.
[Gary, who will be handsome momentarily,
and Ha Ha are one team!]
I feel like old people live here.
[Who will be Jong Kook's partner?]
Maybe he gets yogurt drink deliveries.
He takes care of his health.
I guess he drinks one everyday.
- Who is it?
- Sir!
I'm here for a family visit.
How is it a family visit
when I have no kids?
Go away!
[His voice is familiar...]
Is it Soo Hong?
[Is this Soo Hong's house?]
Soo Hong!
You live in a nice place!
This is an amazing house.
[An elegant interior.]
[He's organized.]
It's a little big for one man.
Someone is probably hiding.
I thought Jae Suk was going to come
since he knows my house.
But I think we're going to win
because you're here.
Since your house is so nice,
let's take a tour.
Is this "Love House"?
They might be curious.
- I was in a rush...
- Did you put this fruit out for us?
This is my mother's set-up.
She put them there two days ago.
[He's even entering his bedroom?]
- This pillow is good for the health!
- That's right.
This is from my mom.
For good sleep.
But you have two pillows?
[Why are there two pillows in a
house where he lives alone?]
You never know.
[He's already prepared
for married life.]
[He visits his closet.]
[Organized]
- Do you work out...
- If we keep up with this tour
when are we going to
eliminate name tags?
I can't just not look around.
Who wears this?
Me.
[It's my house, they're my clothes.]
Shall we take a look at the bathroom?
- The bathroom.
- Why are you going there?
There are two toothbrushes!
There's a green and a red!
No, that is...
[You should answer that question...]
On weekends, I use this one.
I use this on weekends.
[His quick wit surprised himself.]
This one's for weekends.
And this one for the week days.
Why do you have two toothbrushes?
- One's red and one's green.
- I use both of them.
Okay, that's enough.
There's a cleaner bathroom over there.
[We need to go do the mission!]
[Another man
who's dreaming of love.]
- This is their house.
- House?
Where they live?
This is the house of a famous idol.
[This is the house
where an idol lives?]
You can find out who your partner is.
Is it okay for me to
visit without a gift?
[His lighthearted knock.]
Please put this on your partner.
[But what if it's a girl?]
[It's a guy.]
Oh... hi, Niel?
You seem very disappointed.
[The charismatic performer
from Teen Top, it's Niel!]
Nice to see you, Niel!
- Are you disappointed?
- No way!
[Is he the same person?]
Your face was...
No, it's because I was flustered.
Can I come in?
Yes, come in.
[Presenting... Teen Top's dorm.]
[We were curious what the dorm
of an idol would look like.]
[Who knew it was this empty...]
I haven't got anything
in my schedule today.
- So you're alone?
- Yes.
[Niel's dorm is empty.]
- Are you disappointed?
- I was just surprised.
- We were on the same team last time.
- That's right.
- You remember, right?
- Of course.
- In the rice paddy.
- Yeah, the rice paddy.
[Shall we take a look?]
- Can I look around?
- Yes, of course.
But there's not much.
- Is this a room?
- Yes, it's my room.
[An idol's room.]
Your fans will be curious, too!
Oh, it seems like you stuffed your
clothes in the corner in a hurry.
This is where I usually put my clothes.
[There are clothes here, too?]
I already washed those.
- It's already washed.
- What are you talking about?
[It obviously doesn't look like it.]
[A shocking space
shared between men.]
There are six guys living here.
Sorry for coming, empty-handed.
- Do you have anything to eat?
- Yes.
Niel, throw this away.
[There's trash on the floor.]
- I can't stand stuff like this.
- That's where the garbage used to be.
What's with this?
What's wrong with you guys?
- Why do you live like this?
- We don't eat here.
Don't be mistaken.
We usually don't eat in our dorm.
What is this?
What's wrong with this?
[The pickled radish exploded.]
What's wrong with the pickled radish?
Sorry, I didn't think it'd explode.
- Did it go bad?
- No, it didn't.
It didn't go bad.
It's gone sour!
It's pickled.
Of course it's sour.
Why are the wet wipes so dry?
Let's go grocery shopping.
This isn't the time to be doing this.
[Will he be able to do well with Niel]
[who urgently needs to go grocery
shopping more than anything?]
[Where's the next partner?]
[Ji Hyo came to an agency
instead of a house.]
No one's here...
Huh?
I know this!
This is Brown Eyed Soul.
Hello.
It's all Brown Eyed Soul!
Am I here to see Young Jun?
There's Jung Yup.
There's Buzz!
Buzz.
Who is it?
I'm so curious now.
Who could it be?
[It's for sure one of them,
but which one?]
Hello, Kyung Hoon!
[Huh?
It's Min Kyung Hoon!]
[Buzz's vocal, Min Kyung Hoon
is Ji Hyo's partner.]
You're the guest today, right?
It's nice to meet you!
It's been a long time.
[It's been 13 years since his debut.]
[A skillful vocalist who has
both the looks and the talent.]
[Min Kyung Hoon's first time
on Running Man.]
There's Buzz, and other singers too.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
He was good at singing and
my sibling was a huge fan.
- Is it a he?
- No, it was my younger sister.
Do you only like girl fans?
[How will the rest of
the day go for them?]
[Another person who
visited an agency.]
[Big Nose's partner is?]
Hello.
My partner is here?
Oh, in the building?
Hello!
Nice to meet you.
There's Eddy.
[Could it be Eddy Kim,
Ga In or Lim Kim?]
It might be one of these.
[Please let it be Ga In...]
[Or Lim Kim is okay, too.]
[It's Jo Jung Chi.]
[Oh no...]
[Why are you here...]
Jung Chi, is it you?
[He's also disappointed.]
I'm your partner, today.
Why.. why you...
[Of the many singers
in this agency...]
[And there were
female singers, too...]
I didn't know who would come,
so I made coffee.
You finished it, already.
- I was waiting.
- You waited a lot.
You look a lot weaker than me.
[Whatever the mission is,
will they be okay?]
[Kwang Gyoo & Jae Suk]
[Soo Hong & Jong Kook] [Niel & Kwang Soo]
[Kyung Hoon & Ji Hyo]
[Jung Chi & Suk Jin] [Gary & Ha Ha]
[They finished breakfast
at Kwang Gyoo's.]
- Go easy.
- No, I can't do that.
I need to make them clean.
With my personality,
I can't just leave them.
You should clean
the bottom of the sink.
I still cleaned because
you were visiting today.
What?
What have you done?
I cleaned the floor.
- You did?
- Yeah.
What are we doing today?
Today, you will be camping.
- Camping?
- Then why are we at my house?
You will be camping today.
With him?
Alone?
I like the luxurious resorts.
Glamping?
I like that.
[They finally agreed on something.]
Camping's hot right now.
I don't really like packing
and going places.
And the outdoors...
My mom told me not to do
anything where there's no roof.
I like cooking meat.
I love camping.
I love it, but I've never been.
Are we a team or not?
You are one team, today.
- We're a team?
- Yes.
I would rather be on the
same team as him.
[It's annoying if he's on
the opponent team...]
[What is this?]
[A belt?]
There's no way Running Man
would just have normal camping.
What's this?
[What's with this belt?]
What are you doing?
[The staff is putting
a belt on them.]
Maybe you and I are being linked.
Please put the belt on.
Maybe we have to go
everywhere together.
This isn't a parachute, right?
It reminds of the time
I used get training...
[We will fasten you together.]
[What is that?]
- Can't I wash up, first?
- Put it on, then wash up.
But I have to be with him
as he washes up!
[Lock]
[Link, complete.]
[Chain link camping.]
You need to be linked
until the trip's over.
And you cannot unlock it
no matter what situation.
You really want us
to go around like this?
[Shock]
I should have gone with Song Ji Hyo!
What is this?
[The distance is 180 centimeters.]
Don't do that, it's so
depressing between two men!
What are you doing?
Why would you do this?
[Annoyed]
You need to go to
the bathroom together.
There's an exception for your team.
We will only unlock it
for a bathroom break.
- So all the other teams...
- When they change
and the bathroom, too.
No, it's okay.
Don't unlock it.
[All six couples have
become linked by their chains!]
You tie our hands,
and now our hips too?
How are we supposed to go around?
I need to go to the bathroom
because I ate an apple.
[I'm in bigger trouble...]
I'm a little worried.
I just need to use the bathroom.
- My goodness!
- You stay there.
I can see everything
because the door's open.
[This is real variety...]
Come in!
Then what do we do?
You can see everything, just come in!
It already started?
- I need to go!
- It already started?
Just come in already!
- I need to do number two!
- Okay, just come in!
[A link that makes them
share all sorts of things.]
What are we doing!
Just sit down!
What do I do...
Go over there!
If you just unlock it,
I need to use the bathroom.
You can go, linked.
We cannot unlock it,
under any circumstances.
- From now on?
- Yes.
You need to go to
the bathroom together.
For real?
The bathroom as well?
Well, we're guys.
It's okay...
[Awkward]
But I feel a little awkward.
It's very awkward.
Go and take care of your business.
[What am I doing in front of
a bathroom at this age...]
Do I really have to listen to this?
It's going to be a long day...
A long...
[The sound that I heard just now...]
[Trauma]
He didn't even get ready yet!
[Please let me get ready.]
Please give me the key.
I'm serious, I need to take a shower.
Why do I need to see him take a shower?
Then you turn around.
I need to take a shower.
What is this...
[Help me...]
[Gary went in to take a shower.]
What is this?
This looks weird.
I'm actually going to shower!
What is this!
[All he can do is laugh...]
I'm actually going to take a shower!
You look like a pervert if
you only have sunglasses on.
He really needs to shower
because he likes to be clean.
He's very clean.
- Do you want to take a shower?
- What is this!
Take your sunglasses off!
[He looks like a gangster.]
He's actually taking a shower.
He also needs to use the bathroom,
do I have to stay?
It's a little far so you'll
have to come in anyway.
[Shock]
We'll have some alone time...
You need to pack items for camping.
You can only take the
items you can carry.
There's not much to bring...
What do you mean?
There's instant noodles!
Let's just go and have instant noodles.
- Yeah, let's do that.
- And maybe like two eggs...
- Eggs?
- We'll add some protein.
Wait, hold on...
[There's no "hold on"
when we're linked.]
- Four instant noodles.
- Four?
I always keep in mind to take extra
in case I get them stolen.
[They have to be together even when
they're putting their shoes on.]
[Jong Kook and Soo Hong
are packing as well.]
[They're in a tiny space together.]
Wow, what is this?
[A tent and a mat.]
[And even some food!]
I have meat and shiitake mushrooms.
Let's bring this, too.
I think we should bring food
we can eat without heat, too.
[Kkuk begins coaching.]
[He adds some nuts, right away.]
We should bring red pepper paste
no matter what we eat.
- Should we bring this?
- Do we need that?
Who brings a lidded pot
for the outdoors?
They usually bring tin pots.
Yeah, like that.
Yeah, we should bring that.
You should have bought
some plastic containers...
[My ears are going to bleed.]
I'm sorry, but...
[Slightly embarrassed]
You can put the portable pots in there.
I was just going to...
[Ha, ha, ha.]
He's like a mother-in-law.
[A muscular mother-in-law.]
[I need to be linked with him
for the whole day...]
[At Gary's house.
He's offering Ha Ha ice-cream.]
What is that!
He freezes his compost!
I need to throw it away,
but I didn't get the chance.
[What do we do with him...]
He freezes it so that it doesn't smell.
Kyung Hoon, this is your office...
Can I wrap it around my neck like that?
- What?
- My neck.
He's so picky, this guy!
What is this?
But we can't touch this.
They're not mine...
You can just tell them later!
- Come this way.
- Wait, there's something!
[Drag]
- There's an owner for everything.
- Just tell them afterward!
Our life depends on it!
- Then we'll just take one.
- He's so timid.
[He's timid and careful.]
He's really timid.
Let's bring towels just in case.
Just put everything in for now.
[A big load.]
[Struggle]
I was wondering why
you were so close...
It's all for a reason!
Just a little bit more.
Okay, we're good.
You should drive...
Okay, I'll drive.
[They need to get in the car.]
[But how do we get in?]
- Okay then, I'll go in from this side.
- Good idea.
[He's so lazy.]
You're so funny!
How do we get in?
You need to get in
from the passenger side.
No, you go in from this side!
I have to go in this way?
You can get in from the passenger side!
No, you can get in this way.
- The handle though.
- I'll drive, so get in from here.
This is so uncomfortable!
[Struggle]
You're stepping on the seats!
I can't get in without stepping on it.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo are
getting in from the passenger side.]
We need to get in and out...
[This is so uncomfortable.]
We need to get in the car like this?
[Will everything go well today?]
[The six couples are heading
to the grocery store to shop.]
[Kwang Soo and Niel's partners
are Ji Hyo and Kyung Hoon!]
[Is it a battle between the older
and newer flower boys?]
[Half delighted, half awkward.
We hope you get along soon!]
They're here?
They are, who is it?
- It's Suk Jin.
- And Jung Chi!
[What is the idea behind
the guests today?]
Are the guests all pitiful?
Is this an anaconda or what?
It's so frustrating!
[Kkuk and Soo Hong give
their shopping mate a present.]
[The fur hat fills his empty forehead.
It's love.]
The fur hat finally found its owner!
- What is the stuff that you keep saying?
- It's that one!
- Is it really that good?
- Yes, it's really good.
[From ramen to pork belly]
Meat, meat, meat!
[Nagging mother-in-law Kkuk
and the daughter-in-law Soo Hong]
[What's the mysterious meal?]
[Don't forget the link
between you and me...]
Buy me a bun with red bean!
Wait... bun with red bean...
[All six teams are ready
for the chain link camping.]
[To the camp site for peak fall color!]
Welcome to the Linked camp site.
[Welcome to the linked camping!]
The guests that are
linked to each of you
appeared to be weak from
the previous activities
on Running Man.
[Are you talking about me?]
You're at the lowest level among the
places you'll be using today now.
There are multiple levels
in this camp site.
We have prepared five trailers.
We put R flags at the trailers.
When you get the flag of a trailer.
You'll be using the trailer.
- You have your bags in the trunk?
- Yes.
You need to carry it by yourselves
and capture the R flag.
We didn't have enough money
to buy plastic bags.
I'm sorry to interrupt you, but you said
we're the weakest people...
Stop talking about it, Soo Hong.
He's clingy.
We're going to cook today.
Do you have the tools and fire?
Yes, there's fire.
We brought a grill.
[That's unbelievable...]
We didn't have to bring it.
- That gas grill...
- What did he do so wrong?
Will you stop if I cry?
Do you want me to cry
in front of everyone?
- And say sorry?
- It won't be enough.
It's first come, first serve.
- Start!
- Let's go!
[Let's go!]
Come, Kwang Gyoo!
Trunk, trunk!
Did we put our stuff in the trunk?
Start running!
[Gary and Ha Ha are the first to start.]
[Lightly packed and a plastic bag]
[They're ready to run.]
It was good that we
bought the plastic bag!
Don't drop anything!
[They'll lose it if they drop anything.]
- Let's go!
- Where are we heading to?
Hurry up, Kwang Gyoo!
My chopsticks!
Jae Suk!
Run, run!
[Jae Suk forces Kwang Gyoo to run.]
Which button should I press
to open the trunk?
Oh, no!
I opened the bonnet!
- Where is it?
- You opened it earlier!
[The other teams are
running at full speed!]
- Hurry up!
- Their luggage is light!
[He dropped a bag of bean sprouts!]
Give us what you dropped!
That's the most important ingredient!
- Jung Chi!
- We don't have a lot of food.
Don't just run.
We need to think about
which zone we want to go.
They have flags.
Kwang Gyoo, hurry up!
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo are the
first ones to enter the camping zone.]
[On top of the hill,
there's a luxurious trailer.]
The one on the hill is the best!
[We're finally here.]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo
get the best trailer.]
Is that occupied?
Do we have to get down?
[Too bad...]
That one was the biggest.
They got the best one.
[They're entering the trailer
breathing heavily.]
- Isn't this the best?
- It seems like it.
[How does the interior look?]
It's like a hotel room.
[Awesome!]
Wow, it's incredible!
[The living room is decorated
with high quality hardwood.]
[It's spacious and a convenient
kitchen is included.]
[With a fireplace, a romantic
and dreamy trailer.]
- So nice!
- Let's check the upstairs.
It's a bedroom.
[There's a sweet and cozy bedroom
at the top of the stairs.]
- Kwang Gyoo!
- There's a shower, too.
[A clean looking white shower space]
It's so nice.
[Let me try the bed, too.]
[They're enjoying the luxury
of an exotic vacation.]
So far, so good!
Just like this, we'll
be able to take a rest.
This happened because we
were moving diligently.
Our plan worked well.
We packed light so we
got the best trailer.
We're having the best day!
[This is heaven.]
[Will it be this happy until the end?]
[At the second best trailer]
[Kwang Soo and Niel enter.]
[This is as nice as
Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo's.]
I think this is nicer than your dorm.
[What are you talking about?]
It's so clean!
- What's that?
- It's a bunk bed.
We wasted so much time.
The other teams have luxurious trailers.
Running Man...
[Maybe we'll get a decent place, too.]
What's this?
No way!
[Empty]
What is this?
Why did we wait in the middle?
[Right next to the luxurious trailer,
a very simple tent is waiting for them.]
This is so unfair.
- What do we do?
- What about the grill?
Why did you stop there, Soo Hong?
Didn't you stop?
It's my fault, I admit it,
but I might be upset later.
I have no choice.
Actually, when we were climbing up,
Soo Hong looked so tired.
I thought where we're going
to stay doesn't matter
but he doesn't even realize
I thought about him.
He blamed me for stopping first.
He's nitpicking over that stuff,
I think that's wrong.
I hope he will realize it
as time goes by.
I think I was being lazy.
It's not how an old
brother should behave.
I should have said "let's run,"
but I was lazy because it was heavy.
It's all my fault.
[Satisfied]
I don't think this interview
comes from the bottom of my heart.
It's fine.
Should we build the simple tent?
Yes, it's so easy you can throw it.
Let's not do the hard work.
- What's that?
- It's a pop-up tent.
We're not going to stay over night.
It's already set!
Jae Suk!
Look at this!
We have a house!
Oh, it's not quite done, yet.
That looks so pitiful.
[As long as we're okay,
we don't care.]
They need to clean it later.
Tent is good, too.
But it's better to be in here
in this weather.
- It's done.
- Did you put the mat?
- Put the mat.
- Why aren't you doing it?
You're doing it already.
We can put some blankets on it.
Yes, we have blankets!
[Laugh]
We have sleeping bags!
What could've happened
if we didn't bring it?
We didn't bring it,
but it's all prepared inside.
I'm sorry, but it's between us.
Why do you meddle with us?
Do you want us to rent this space?
No need!
Is that a table?
[That looks good.]
Do you want to use our deck?
Wait a minute, mister!
Your deck...
Can you let us used to space
in front of the deck?
Cold air comes from the ground...
If you don't want your
colleagues to have bell's palsy...
Right here?
Yoo Jae Suk, you're such a nice guy!
[Let's move to our new home!]
Wait, wait!
Your choice is to yield...
[Let's calm down...]
Bell's palsy puts your
mouth on one side.
When it gets that bad,
just turn over to the other side.
Do you want us to look like flounders?
Are you being violent?
Do you want to see what violence is?
We can break things you have!
Let's talk.
If you give us some meat...
- Give you what?
- Some pork belly...
If you give us some meat.
Then, let's share the kitchen, too.
We can have a barbecue together!
Let's share!
If you give us all of your meat,
we'll cook and give some to you.
[The negotiations broke down.]
[This is too much!]
[What negotiations!]
What are you doing?
[While Jong Kook is bickering,
Soo Hong trespasses.]
[We need to survive, too!]
Oh, no!
It's my house!
Why is that so weak?
You know how hard it was to buy this?
- That's too weak.
- Pay for it!
My house...
We're going into a sit-in!
Do you want to put it
on top of this deck?
A house on the hill?
This is nice, too.
Then, we'll share the
barbecue grill with you, too.
Please give us some meat.
We'll share the kitchen.
I guess so.
Why can't you say it nicely?
[Getting upset]
[Laugh]
This is 2015, are you still
thinking about using power?
I see, then let's cook some meat here.
- Let's cook the meat.
- We don't need to feel small.
And we'll give some meat.
Start cooking the meat,
we'll be back in a moment.
Start a fire.
It's a bit cold.
We're going to start a fire
so we can cook the meat.
I know, I know.
This is so nice.
Look how comfortable they are.
- Only we're poor.
- This is more fun.
[How will the two families get along?]
[Ji Hyo and Kyung Hoon
took a while to open the trunk]
[and enter the camp site last.]
Isn't this nice?
But this is a space for a tent.
[All the linked couples
arrived at the camp site!]
You can unpack your stuff now
they it will be lunch time.
You can cook anything with
the ingredients you brought.
There's a trailer at the back
you'll see a tool zone, if you go there.
You can take anything from the zone.
Okay!
Hope you enjoy your lunch!
Let's go to the tool zone.
We need a pot.
The trailer has a stove.
Make me something delicious, Dong Hun.
Don't worry about it.
It's so frustrating!
We have to go everywhere together.
[His stress goes up.]
Kwang Soo.
- What did you buy?
- The ingredients for fried rice.
Fried rice?
I was going to make stir-fry pork
with bean sprouts but we dropped it.
[He's going to tell everyone...]
I can only laugh.
So, the main ingredients
are pork and bean sprouts
but he dropped bean sprouts.
[Jung Chi feels small
with his partner's diss.]
It was the main ingredient...
I feel so bad...
Bean sprouts!
[I'm still upset!]
[He keeps nagging about
the same thing over and over.]
You dropped bean sprouts!
[Their conflict starts
with bean sprouts.]
You know what the main ingredient was?
Our dish was stir-fry pork
and bean sprouts.
And what did you drop?
You dropped bean sprouts.
Please don't drop anything.
I beg of you!
Actually, it's because of Suk Jin.
I was running fast, but
he couldn't keep up.
[So, it's my fault?]
I felt it was too tiring for him.
While I was concerned,
I was tripped and dropped it.
And he kept blaming me on and on.
I hope he doesn't me a long lecture.
It's so frustrating.
We have to stay close for every move.
If you do this while I do that...
how convenient will it be?
[We can't even divide tasks...]
- Maybe they did this way back when.
- Sesame oil?
Because we only have sesame oil.
We don't have vegetable oil.
I think they have it.
I see it, but we're too far.
We both have to walk,
and that's kind of scary.
Let's just go.
We have no choice.
Should we?
If we were smarter,
we could have taken it earlier.
That's vegetable oil?
I think the one at the left corner is.
[They're almost there.]
Please, please, please!
[It's vinegar!]
- Jung Chi!
- No!
It's vinegar!
[You know how we came here.]
I told you it was vinegar!
I thought it was vegetable oil.
I saw it earlier!
It's tiring for me, too.
[The link makes them more
and more uncomfortable.]
Kyung Hoon, we need to spread it first.
Under the link.
It's good now.
Connect it!
[Ji Hyo's slapstick!]
[It's not easy to carry
out a simple task!]
[Starting a fire, so he can't move.]
[Getting something from inside.]
This will expand that much.
Try getting it.
[Struggle]
[Even a simple cooperation
is impossible.]
[Careful, careful]
[Everything gets in the way,
because of the link.]
[In the middle of Gary's interview]
[I'm thirsty.]
Can you cut the link for a moment?
This link?
So uncomfortable!
Why are we doing this?
Gary, let's just make some ramen.
I'm so hungry.
Let's do that.
You need to get inside no matter what.
[I can't even get some air...]
We can cook here.
[As soon as Gary gets inside,
he sits down.]
[Make some ramen...]
I put water and...
Come over here, let's play.
[Glance]
[He's sitting the whole time.]
They even have a ventilation fan.
I really want to cut this link!
If one person prepares
ingredients, it'll be a lot faster.
We can save some time.
How much is it to use this trailer?
It's so nice.
[Will he help me this time?]
[What are you doing, Gary?]
Are you lying down on the bed?
- Are you on the phone?
- No, it's just so nice.
[This is too much!]
Dong Hun...
There's nothing I can do.
- You were on the bed?
- Take some rest, I'll do it.
I was lying on the bed.
He was cheeky.
For example, he was lying
on the bed when I was cooking.
I was working so hard,
he should've cheered up for me.
But he was just lying down.
I hated him at that moment.
[He's making noise.]
[It's your fault!]
[Gary is heading somewhere.]
Dong Hun, why don't you move
to this side for a bit?
I'm cutting right now.
What are you doing?
I need to use the bathroom!
[I can't say no to that...]
Can you make this link a bit longer?
Just do what you need to do!
I can't do anything.
- Where's the flush?
- You need to step on it.
At lease, we need to go
to the bathroom alone.
Why do we need to be tied
when we go to the bathroom?
He's going to have
a constipation because of me.
I'm really sorry, but let
me fart in front of you.
Just do it!
[He farted.]
I was holding it for so long.
I'm okay, but why did you do it on TV?
[He farted in front of the viewers.]
[Let's share everything.
Where are you going?]
[The link between you and me.]
They're coughing!
[One hour passed since
they entered the camp site.]
[Ha Ha and Gary start eating.]
It would've been really good
if we had some rice.
[They finished the noodle in a flash.]
What's that?
Can I try?
- Try the soup.
- Where is the noodle?
It's really good.
Maybe a few noodles are in there.
Isn't this crazy good?
The noodle was really good, too.
- You put peppers, too?
- It's really good!
I can't believe this!
We'll grill some meat now.
Do we need to wash this?
[Will you stop it?]
[He doesn't give him back.]
You're going to finish it?
Don't drink it all!
[He finished the soup.]
You can't stop eating it.
- I ate a lot.
- What's the name of the ramen?
[He acted badly and tried to steal.]
I just need to catch one person,
and you can't run away.
[Thanks to the link]
You stole my ramen.
What are you talking about?
You can be imprisoned for this.
Suk Jin steals it before my eyes.
Are they thieves?
They are thieves.
When one person steals,
the other person should stop him.
But they were praising each other.
It's fine, Suk Jin.
I'll distract them next time.
Yes, let's pretend that
we want to see their room.
Ji Hyo!
What are you cooking?
[They're approaching
Ji Hyo and Kyung Hoon.]
- We won for the grocery shopping.
- What did you buy?
- Kimchi and meat.
- Meat?
What kind of meat did you buy?
- Pork.
- Pork?
- Where is it?
- It's right here.
It's right here.
[Hide]
[She figured it out.]
- She's hiding it.
- What's wrong with that?
You guys don't trust
each other on Running Man?
You should've marinated it more.
Did I make another mistake already?
We could've eaten the other meat first,
and cook this one.
Then, I'll put it back.
No, don't do that.
Let's just cook it.
It'll be good if you
put it in the middle.
[He fires his nagging bullet
indiscriminately.]
Jong Kook looks like a sergeant
with little time left in the army.
And Soo Hong looks
like a private first class.
[Do you mean this, sir?]
I hope he speaks informally.
He never treated me as
an older person any way.
I just hope he keeps
his attitude toward me.
I hope you guy will be happy together.
That's the end of the
"Bottom of the Heart Interview."
Are you done?
Was it good?
Of course, everything went well.
I warmed the chair for you.
Take a seat.
Soo Hong, you need to walk that way.
Think about it, the belt
it connected this way.
I care about him,
that's why I keep telling stuff.
As time goes by, I think we're
getting along very well.
He follows me around and listens to me.
[You know I'm just joking.]
This is humiliating.
He's younger than me...
[I'm not going to cry any longer.]
[Kwang Soo and Niel are making
[Fried rice.]
It's almost done.
- Should I drain the oil and add rice?
- Yes.
Don't most people fry
vegetables first and add rice?
Well, if you know so much,
why don't you cook?
Kwang Soo...
[Cutting with scissors]
Do you use scissors when
you cut ingredients?
Is it important?
Cutting with scissors or knife?
Not really, Kwang Soo.
Do you just hate to see everything I do?
[Being sensitive even
at minor disagreement]
When he's not happy with something
I do, he complains with wide eyes.
Other than that,
I'm happy to be his partner.
He cooks something good and gives me.
[What's good to be Kwang Soo's partner?]
So far, none...
[Who do you want to be partnered with?]
I think Jae Suk or...
[Are you out of your mind?]
Answer it properly.
Thank you for being my
partner, Kwang Soo.
Don't we need to cut these?
Let's just eat now.
I can't even flip them...
This isn't right.
Let's share the food.
How does it taste?
Hey, Jae Suk!
At least, ask before you eat.
I'm going to give one to Kwang Gyoo.
[Now, the trailers owners
are begging for the BBQ.]
Let us eat the good slices.
Kwang Gyoo, it's really good.
You cooked it very well.
Let's be on good terms.
- Let's make up.
- We never had any fights.
It's not like we're living there
because we're poor.
We never said that.
[They misunderstood each other
all because of the link..]
You cooked it so well.
[Let's eat together, and
forget the bad feelings.]
Don't cut the meat in advance.
Yes, cut it when you eat it.
[Seven hours later,
how do you feel about your partner?]
We've gone through
the good times and the bad.
I think we bonded in a way.
When we first started,
we hated each other.
Little by little...
as how snow melts....
I was worried so much at first
but she's so thoughtful,
she made me feel comfortable.
I think we'll keep our relationship
in good terms.
[What will happen to the groups sharing
a destiny who are linked to each other?]
[Seven hours and a half passed.]
At least, Soo Hong listens.
[The members are going
somewhere after lunch.]
This is extremely rare
for him to praise someone.
- He listens...
- I feel pity on Soo Hong.
[He looks more like
Jong Kook's secretary.]
The fact that he's tied to Jong Kook
makes me feel sympathetic.
No, I actually feel at home.
He brings me to take a walk.
[Where are they heading?]
It's a foot volleyball court!
[Welcome to foot volleyball world!]
[There's a ball waiting
for the members.]
What is this for?
This is a sport that I'll be blamed for!
- I don't want to be on Suk Jin's team.
- We'll lose, if we are.
[Will they play foot
volleyball with the link?]
Foot volleyball?
This is what people always
play when they go on a camping.
It's foot volleyball.
It's six versus six
linked foot volleyball.
The rules are simple but
if you lose the game
the length of the link will
shrink to 90 centimeters.
You can't!
[It's half of what we have!]
We need to win this no matter what!
[If it shrinks to 90 centimeters,
they will be really close.]
[Yoo Jae Suk, Kim Kwang Gyoo, Ha Ha,
Gary, Lee Kwang Soo, Niel]
[vs. Kim Jong Kook, Park Soo Hong,
Song Ji Hyo, Min Kyung Hoon]
[Ji Suk Jin, Jo Jung Chi]
Let's kick the ball toward
Jung Chi and Suk Jin.
They're in yellow.
We can't lose.
They're a black tunnel,
not a black hole.
- We can win this.
- It's impossible to lose.
- Are you good at foot volleyball?
- Of course!
I'm good at it.
He's athletic.
[Even Brother Kwang Gyoo
seems confident.]
[On the other hand,
Team Jong Kook is worried.]
I'll just stand behind Kyung Hoon.
- Then, I'll stand over here.
- It's so uncomfortable.
[On top of Big-nosed Brother,
they have Jung Chi and link!]
Do I look useful?
[Kyung Hoon's ball technique
doesn't look ordinary.]
[He's good at trapping the ball, too!]
I'll just follow around.
Get ready!
Good luck!
Let's win this!
We'll go crazy if the link
becomes 90 centimeters.
Good luck!
[The linked foot volleyball,
first round!]
Niel, heading!
[Nice heading, Niel!]
It hurts!
[Jae Suk gets the ball and attacks.]
[Tight]
[It's too short!]
[Wobble]
[They couldn't defend
because of the link.]
[Thanks to Soo Hong,
Team Jae Suk scores first!]
- I'll do better.
- Don't worry, we can win.
I'll start!
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[1:0]
Receive it!
That's nice!
[Kyung Hoon attacks quickly.]
[But Ha Ha blocks it.]
[Jong Kook and Kyung Hoon
barely saved the ball.]
[It's time to attack!]
[Tight]
[It's too short, again!]
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[2:0]
Soo Hong!
I'm so sorry, but stop talking about me.
People make mistakes, you know.
[Cheer up, Soo Hong!]
Here we go again!
Run!
Receive it!
[Kkuk's heading attack!]
[Yoo Hyuk's mistake,
Team Jong Kook scores.]
It was too low.
We only need two good players...
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[2:1]
Niel's good!
[Niel receives the strong
serve with heading again.]
[Jae Suk makes another mistake...]
[Maybe he's not good at it?]
My team has me, and
their team has Jae Suk.
[They quickly change positions.]
Niel is good.
[He seems weak, but he turns out
to be the king of defense.]
The ball is really hard.
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[3:2]
Okay, I'll lower my head here.
[Niel's high serve!]
It's good!
[Team Jong Kook returns it easily.]
Kwang Soo!
Get it!
Good, let me!
[This is a perfect chance!]
[I'll show you all!]
Jae Suk!
[He missed the ball big time.]
Move aside!
I didn't do anything!
[Tell me before you move.]
[Thanks to Jae Suk, we
might win this game!]
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[3:3]
- Here we go!
- We need to say "mine" clearly.
[He still looks weak,
but he doesn't let the ball go.]
[Ha Ha returned the ball.]
[The foot volleyball expert,
Kyung Hoon's attack!]
[Kyung Hoon is aiming for the back.]
[He's supposed to play foot volleyball,
not hacky sack!]
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[3:4]
We can do it.
Focus!
Here we go!
What's the score?
[Receives it with heading,
and the assistance!]
[Kwang Gyoo's bald heading shot!]
[They returned it!]
[Ha Ha's attack was a bit too high.]
Just leave it out!
[Fall]
[As Soo Hong falls,
Jong Kook loses his balance.]
[They tried hard...]
[but the ball was caught in the net.]
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[4:4]
[Because of the link,
he can't keep his balance.]
[This link is so troublesome!]
[They're all in the same situation.]
Why did you fall?
You fell, so I was dragged, too.
[Because of the link,
they're in the same boat.]
If this belt gets shorter,
it'll be awful.
[We must win!]
[Just one more score left!]
Mine, mine!
[The ball is up in the air!
[It's a good chance to smash!]
Move back!
[The foot volleyball expert
Min Kyung Hoon]
[tosses it slightly.]
[It fell right in front of the net?]
[Min Kyung Hoon tricked
Team Jae Suk.]
[Min Kyung Hoon becomes the
king of foot volleyball.]
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[Set score-1:0]
- I'll leave you the back.
- That's what I've been doing.
We'll do better this time!
This won't do.
Take it off!
[Team Jae Suk is heated.]
We can't lose it!
[Tight]
Move a little, Gary.
Just take it off and throw it.
This drives me nuts!
This links is really uncomfortable.
If you lose, the link
will be shrink to half.
It means, we have to
go to the bathroom...
together...
in the same room...
[The link foot volleyball,
second round!]
Spread out.
Call "my ball."
[The game starts with Gary's serve.]
Mine, mine, mine!
[He's proving that he's a black hole.]
We just need to return the ball.
[Coach Kkuk is trying to give the
black hole a lesson quickly.]
It was an unfortunate bounce!
Even if we lose, let's play hard!
Mine, mine!
[Suk Jin, move out of the way!]
[Move away, Suk Jin!]
When my turn, then?
[Big-nosed Brother
attacks his own team mate.]
[Is he on our side?]
[Nonsense]
[At this rate, we'll win this game!]
[They're so excited, they don't
realize the links are tangled.]
[Chaos]
Keep up the pace!
[Confident]
Let's go!
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[0:2]
The ball bounces pretty fast.
Mine, mine, mine!
[Kkuk pushes the black hole away]
[and Kyung Hoon returns the ball.]
We just need to return the ball.
[Niel's over head kick!]
[That's awesome!]
[Kyung Hoon aims for
an empty spot again!]
[It's successful!]
[The king of foot volleyball
overtake their defense!]
[Proud]
He's good!
Okay, let's begin the real game!
[We didn't begin yet?]
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[3:3]
That's good!
Move, move, move away!
[The king of foot
volleyball's power shot!]
[Everybody, put your hands up!]
- Gary!
- Slow down!
[With the tight game,
everyone seems excited.]
[After continuous tossing,
the king of foot volleyball's kick!]
[They scored!]
[Team Jong Kook is leading.]
I don't want to play it!
The longer we play,
the more embarrassing it will be.
It's like he's playing around!
[What are they doing now?]
[It's only a serve...]
Let Niel do it!
Why are you trying to serve, Kwang Soo?
Who told you to serve?
[Hmph!]
[My poor brother...]
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[4:3]
[Niel serves instead of Kwang Soo.]
He's good!
[From Jong Kook to Kyung Hoon,
then a smooth shooting.]
[Jae Suk slides to save the ball,
but it got caught in the net.]
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[Set score-2:0]
[One more loss, and it's over...]
[They're close to the punishment.]
[And Team Jae Suk
starts counterattack!]
[His cool face return!]
[Nice shot!]
[This is just the beginning!]
What happened?
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[1:0]
[2:0]
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[3:0]
[Hop]
[That looked like an air dancer!]
[That was a poor movement...]
[He's doing a slapstick
while giving them a score.]
We found a way to win!
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[4:0]
Kyung Hoon!
[Heading!]
[He fell but the ball was there...]
[Emergency]
[Gravity...]
Please love me...
Think about your mommy.
[For the team, Kyung Hoon
doesn't spare himself.]
You're funny today.
[With Team Jong Kook's mistakes]
[Team Jae Suk vs. Team Jong Kook]
[2:1]
[1. The black hole Soo Hong]
[2. The black hole Suk Jin]
[3. The king of foot
volleyball Kyung Hoon]
[successfully shoots!]
He's really good!
[He aimed for the middle of their link.]
[Confused]
[He's got stronger after his injury.]
Nice!
Kyung Hoon!
[Follows up]
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[1:0]
[2:0]
[Team Jong Kook vs. Team Jae Suk]
[3:0]
[4:0]
[Team Jong Kook is in a festive mood!]
[Depressed]
[Why do you always blame
everything on me?]
Min Kyung Hoon is such a weasel.
I really hate him.
Kyung Hoon has good techniques.
It's the last round!
[If Team Jong Kook gets one more point,
they will win foot volleyball.]
[Yoo Hyuk's shot!]
[Kkuk doesn't let them
score until the end.]
Save the ball, Kyung Hoon!
Okay, do it slowly!
Mine, mine!
[Kwang Soo has to return the ball.]
[He had to kick the ball,
but he tripped.]
[Odd... but he kicked it over the net.]
Mine, mine!
[He missed it!]
[I'm so sorry!]
[With the set score 3:1]
[Jong Kook's wins the foot volleyball.]
[Team Jong Kook will be
wearing the same belts.]
You're really good, Kyung Hoon.
It's going to be really uncomfortable.
The tail gets shorter.
[Their link is half as long now.]
[How will they stand it?]
- Foot volleyball is fun.
- I didn't show my ability.
You had more than enough chances.
It was your best play so far.
[When they return to the camp site.]
- It's a bonfire!
- That's wonderful!
It's a real bonfire!
They prepared sweet potatoes,
and white potatoes for us!
[Pork belly slices, and sausages...
everything is set for a barbecue!]
Let's have a party!
[Now we're talking about it!]
We lost the game, but I feel so good!
It's so hot!
It's hot!
[They forgot that they're
tied to each other.]
[Laughing and eating]
[they're truly enjoying the camping.]
[To recharge their energy,
they're taking a break.]
Why don't you go to the bathroom?
Do you want me to go?
So, I can go, too.
- Go to the bathroom.
- Kwang Gyoo...
[It's even more inconvenient
to have a shorter link.]
[Ji Hyo, Kyung Hoon, Kwang Soo,
and Niel are having a snack.]
We should've done this earlier.
I don't understand why we fought.
[Suk Jin and Jung Chi are sleeping.]
[When everyone enjoying
their free time...]
What's going on?
[With the howling sound,
someone punched the trailer.]
- What was that?
- Is that a ghost?
Isn't that the sound of a wolf?
I'm scared.
I heard howling.
What's that?
[Around their trailers]
- People with animal masks are walking.
- Will the catch us if we step outside?
[What are these animals doing here?]
They're walking around.
Be careful.
Come back inside!
There's a tiger.
Close the door!
[A tiger?]
[Why are you doing this to us?]
[At that moment, a mail box is
put in front of their trailers?]
There's a mail box.
What is it?
What's this?
Something is in there.
We have mail.
That scared me.
[In the mail box]
It's the final mission!
Acquire the key to cut the link
and escape the camp site.
But, there're only five cars.
- There' only five cars.
- Two teams can't escape.
This is so vague.
What are these animals doing here?
Maybe they're here to catch us.
How are we supposed to get the key?
No clues?
It seems they're coming toward us.
They're coming!
It's scary!
- Are they after us?
- They were coming toward here.
[They run away in a hurry.]
We need to stick together!
They're coming, coming!
What is it?
It's so scary!
Watch out!
[The animals are acting violent.]
No, no, watch out!
[They're holding the name tags.]
- Run, run!
- They're not after the name tags.
They're not trying to rip it off.
[They're not attacking the name tags,
but moving around them.]
What is this?
- Is this a summer special episode?
- My stomach hurts.
[Wait, now that I look around...]
- The ones that are walking further.
- Let's catch them.
[They all have name tags.]
Maybe we need to
eliminate their name tags.
[What secret are they carrying
under their name tags?]
We need to rip their name tags off.
There's got to be something
under their name tags.
- Are you sure?
- I think so.
[Then, let's rip it off and see!]
It's a tiger!
[Rip!]
[The tiger calmed down.]
There's nothing underneath?
- What's going on?
- I'm sorry.
[There's something
about the name tag.]
Attack the ones that walk alone.
[The name tag hunting begins.]
Keep the name tags.
[Everyone's after the
animals' name tags.]
Wait!
Wait, it's better to get
eliminated by us!
[Rip]
[They're ripping the animals' tags]
[but is it related to the escape?]
[I don't know what's going on, but I
won't let you rip their name tags.]
What is it?
What's with the name tag?
Rip it, Niel.
Niel, you must rip it!
[The name tag hunt keeps going on.]
Look, there're more animals over here.
- We need to rip their name tags.
- Name tags?
Aren't they the same
animals from before?
[The same animals?]
[Well, actually...]
[The same animal that was eliminated
is wearing a name tag again?]
[Ah...]
Maybe we need to rip two of the same.
Which animal did we rip so far?
Fox, lion...
husky, pig, and squirrel.
[At that moment, they
found another husky.]
[Husky is hiding.]
[We're not going to let you go.]
[Rip]
[Kwang Soo and Niel acquired
two husky's name tags.]
[Nothing happens...]
What is it?
Should we go to the car?
Let's go near the car.
Everyone's thinking the same thing.
Look, something's wrong.
[The three teams arrived at the
parking lot at the same time.]
[There must be a clue over here.]
Kwang Soo!
[What's that?]
[At the corner of the parking lot,
he found a mysterious platform.]
[Run over]
[What is this?]
What could it be, Kwang Soo?
I guess we need to put
the name tags here.
Let's put any name tags.
A lion and a pig...
[Nothing happens.]
Put the same ones.
[It might be the two same name tags?]
The same ones.
What are they doing?
[Stop whatever you're doing!]
[What's going on here?]
Maybe you need two
of the same name tags.
I don't know.
Let us try.
Husky and husky!
[They put the two same
name tags on the platform]
[and arrows appear!]
[What does this light mean?]
What's that?
[Something rises up.]
[They found a key!]
[We're free from the link!]
[Since the morning, the link was put.]
[Every time they move]
[it was the most inconvenient
experience ever!]
[My body feels like it
doesn't belong to me.]
[I'm sick and tired of the link!]
[It's time to say good-bye!]
- Are you done?
- I think so.
[As soon as they open the lock,
they can escape.]
Did you unlock it?
Husky and husky?
Oh, two of the same!
Let's go, Kwang Soo!
Do we have to pick the
best car or something?
No, we just need to leave here.
- Are you leaving?
- Bye, Suk Jin!
Tell us what it is!
[We need to hurry up.]
We're the first place!
- What did I tell you, Niel?
- How was it possible?
Awesome!
It's unbelievable!
[Niel and Kwang Soo win the
first place and escape.]
[Thanks to Niel and Kwang Soo,
the final mission is revealed.]
[They're targeting the two
same name tags in earnest.]
[Jong Kook and Soo Hong are hunting for a
chicken because they already have one.]
[Rip]
Hurry up!
It's chicken!
[Jong Kook and Soo Hong
put the two name tags.]
It worked!
[Jong Kook and Soo Hong
acquire the key as well.]
[Finally, I'm released
from this nagging link...]
[Bye, bye!]
Let's go!
[Jong Kook and Soo Hong escape second.]
[There are only three cars left.]
[The rest of them are impatient.]
[Ha Ha and Gary get two
squirrel's name tags.]
[Turtle, come over here!]
[Ji Hyo and Kyung Hoon
get two name tags of Turtle.]
Thank you, Turtle!
[Gary and Ha Ha put
two squirrel's name tags down.]
[Ji Hyo and Kyung Hoon put
two turtle's name tags down.]
Okay!
[Gary, Ha Ha, Ji Hyo, and Kyung Hoon
acquired the key.]
[The dreadful link is lifted.]
[We're free!]
Let's go!
[It feels so much better
to be released from the link.]
I was going crazy.
Let's go!
[Gary and Ha Ha win the
third place and escape.]
Bye, we're leaving!
[Ji Hyo and Kyung Hoon go home, too.]
I'm going home!
[I've never been to
such an exhausting camp.]
[There's only one car left!]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo needs
one more name tag of the lamb.]
Excuse me, wait!
Wait for us!
We just need to...
Wait, Mister!
At this rate, we can't escape.
I'm begging you.
Kwang Gyoo is really tired.
Please let us escape!
Save me!
If I was alone, I could've
ripped it right away.
Why do you blame on me?
I'm fast, too.
- Can you do it?
- I can run, count one, two, three.
[Move!]
We caught him!
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo
acquire two names tags.]
[They can escape if they put
them on the final platform.]
What?
I dropped it!
I lost the name tag.
- Where?
- I don't know.
[He lost the name tag?]
[This is driving me crazy.]
I shouldn't have taken off my jacket.
Catch him!
[Suk Jin and Jung Chi
are doing their best.]
Are you not running on purpose? No.
[I wonder what happened
to Team Jae Suk.]
Kwang Gyoo ruined it.
[They need to find the name tag
before Suk Jin and Jung Chi get theirs.]
What do you have?
[It doesn't matter,
Kwang Gyoo will lose it.]
Where are you going?
[Found it!]
- I should have picked it up!
- Did you find it?
That name tag!
They must have dropped it.
It was such a drama.
I thought each of us has to get one.
My idea was wrong.
Open sesame!
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo
acquire the key!]
Why do you make me so nervous?
There's only one car left.
We were supposed to put the
two of the same name tags down.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Gyoo
release the link, too.]
Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Kwang Gyoo
can escape now.
Bye, Suk Jin.
[Lastly, Jae Suk and
Kwang Gyoo escaped.]
- Bye, Suk Jin!
- Good luck!
[Suk Jin and Jung Chi have to clean
up the trailers in perfect order.]
- The rest of the stuff...
- We need to recycle them.
The first ones who escaped
will be in Seoul by now.
[Clean every nook and cranny.]
If they released the link,
we could've cleaned easier.
- Same as before.
- It's perfect!
[All the trailers are cleaned.]
What time is it?
Jung Chi, I don't think we have
a good relationship together.
What a terrible thing to
be linked to each other!
Jung Chi, I hope we don't
see each other often.
Should we erase our memory about today?
[I'm so sorry...]
I can't just say good-bye to you.
We bonded with each other.
Jung Chi, what a long day!
It was too long!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[It's all set!]
[The best stage,
the most powerful line-up]
[Rival: A person who you are competing
against in the same area.]
- Rival...
- Make the rank clear...
[Hong Jin Ho vs. Lim Yo Hwan]
[The recreation of Lim Jin War!]
[Will history be re-written?]
[Hee Chul vs. Lee Teak]
[The two men who have been
friends for 11 years]
[The Hottest Goddess Hani
vs. Running Man Ace Song Ji Hyo.]
[The hottest girl is
here to catch the Ace.]
[They will have a battle with something
that no one did before!]
Let's make the ranking clear.
[The final match with their rival!]
[The Rival Big Match]