[Get to Daegu as soon
as possible by public transit!]
[Special Command -
Protect the water of mystery!]
[Betrayal, struggle and plot twists!]
[It couldn't be harsher than this!!]
[The war of water begins!]
[SBS Building,
Mok-dong in Seoul]
[Look forward to meeting the
formidable fairies!]
There's one person that
would get along with you.
It means today's guests
are around my age.
So the fairies are older
than 30 at least.
I can't wait to see them!
Please come out!
[Who will be the formidable fairies?]
Fairy!
[Ta-da!]
Kim Seo Hyung!
[Kim Seo Hyung]
- She's wearing a dress!
[Fairies wear dresses.]
[A pure-white fairy, Seo Hyung]
I'm a fan of yours!
[Special note 1
- She's a former Miss Korea.]
You're really attractive.
[What a surprise!]
She hasn't said a word.
[Special note 2 - She expresses
her feelings with gestures.]
Show me the face again.
[The statue of a fairy]
[What a fairy-like expression she has!]
You haven't say a word yet.
It's amazing.
Do you want to say
hello to the viewers?
[She's very funny.]
- Say hello.
- Hello, I'm Kim Seo Hyung.
[Special note 3 - She
speaks less and acts more.]
[Will the next fairy be as
special as the first fairy?]
That girl...
[Jae Suk knows her by
looking at the back?]
[Ye Ji Won]
[Three distinctive fairies.]
We were classmates.
We went to same college.
[A twirl for her fans.]
I saw her at our school
reunion not too long ago.
- Ji Won!
- Older Brother!
We're friends.
Why are you calling me that?
I'm younger than you, Older Brother.
We both entered school in 1991.
But I entered
kindergarten earlier.
We had so much fun at the reunion.
- Who showed up?
- Tae Kyun, Ji Won and me...
- Who's the most famous person?
- Jae Suk.
I mean, Older Brother Jae Suk.
[Fiery spirited fairies are here.]
Today's race is 'The Water Fairy Race'.
In these bottles, there's special water
that can purify any kind of water.
Bring this bottle and find the black muddy
water at the world water forum in Daegu.
Then purify the black muddy water.
[Purify the black muddy water!]
The winner will be the first
team that purifies the water.
By the way, you can only use two
public transits to get to Daegu
among the train, airplane,
inter-city bus, city bus, and a taxi.
You will have to complete
the missions in the middle
and come to 'D' park in
Daegu as soon as possible.
- You mean a park in Daegu?
- He tells us so casually.
He said 'Come to Daegu quickly.'
You'll pick which public transit
you'll use.
- Pick now?
- Yes.
- I want to take the train.
[They all want to take the train.]
[Fairy Ji Hyo's team
picks the red envelope.]
[Jae Suk from Fairy Ji Won's team,
comes out to pick.]
Please give us the yellow one.
Can I take the yellow one?
I was going to pick the blue one,
but I changed my mind.
He's annoying.
- We picked the bus.
[The bus tickets and a taxi ticket.]
- And a taxi.
- The bus and a taxi?
The bus and... the train!
[Fairy Ji Won's team,
KTX tickets and bus tickets.]
The train is good!
We can eat there.
- We've got airplane tickets.
- Isn't that the fastest way?
We have to go all the way to Kimhae
and then back to Daegu?
Then we can't go straight to Daegu.
[We didn't prepare direct
air tickets to Daegu.]
They might as well just
go to Jeju Island.
Fairy Seo Hyung's team picked
the airplane and the bus.
When you arrive in Busan, take
the bus and get to Daegu.
Look at Seo Hyung's face.
I can tell she's thinking
'what are they doing?'
As if she doesn't care.
Aren't you a little cynical?
She doesn't speak much.
Fairy Ji Won's team picked
the train and the bus.
You can take the train
for two stations maximum.
Pardon?
If you don't get off at the first station,
you have to get off at the second station.
You need to get off and
take the bus.
Then we don't know where
we'll be getting off.
We picked the best.
We can directly go to Daegu.
I'll ride my bicycle.
What if the first station is Daegu?
Then we can just get off
at Daegu station.
It might be Busan station, too.
[Which team will be the first
team to arrive to Daegu?]
[Use only two types of
transportation to Daegu!]
[Complete the mission!]
[Overcome the adversity!]
[What will be the fortunes
of the three teams?]
[Fairy Seo Hyung's team starts.]
We don't know what will happen,
but we cannot lose to this team.
[The airplane leaves at 10:30.]
Can we call you sister?
Or fairy?
I want to be your friends,
but I'm older.
[Sister fairy and younger guys.]
Since the new year began
I don't mind younger guys.
But younger guys might
mind older woman.
What are you talking about?
What do you think about
a guy like Jong Kook?
He's strong so he can protect you.
[Turbo's fan for 20 years.]
- Very nice.
I wish I wasn't older.
I'm sorry to sit in the middle.
[They seem like they have good
feelings for each other.]
Hold hands behind my back.
You don't have to tell me that.
It's not that hard to
pick Jong Kook up.
If you confess that you like him,
he'll open his heart.
[Knock at his heart,
and it will be opened.]
Pocket your pride today,
and ask him out three times.
You'll be holding hands
by the time we're done.
She has her own type.
You shouldn't speak
about type at that age.
You just woke me up!
Ji Hyo always picks the best.
I hope the rest of the
games will be by luck, too.
I want to win by luck once.
- We'll probably get there first.
- I think we don't need to hurry.
- Do you know where KTX stops?
- First stop is probably Gwangmyung.
After Gwangmyung is...
They'll mostly likely get off in
Cheonan or Daejeon.
I think it'll be Cheonan.
You know we can take a taxi
now and still be the first.
Right, the cost might be high though.
We can taxi and say
'To Daegu, please.'
[Take a taxi and ask to go to Daegu?]
Pardon?
Just listen.
Don't question her.
- Was that a song?
- She hates to be stopped when she sings.
Again, encore.
Do you actually know
how to play guitar?
She's feeling it.
Yes, she's good.
Yoo Jung (Ji Won's real name)
dances, too.
She's very artistic.
She used to wear trench coats
when she was a student.
A lonely and solitary girl.
She was popular, too.
- A mysterious woman?
- Someone with a cold heart.
[Parole artist, Ye]
Hey, we should have
done this on the train.
- 'Hey' to your Older Brother?
- I'm sorry, Older Brother.
[KTX to Busan leaves at 10:20.]
[All the teams have
no problem so far...]
[The train leaves at 10:20]
[and Fairy Ji Won's team
arrives at the station now.]
[There's no time to lose!]
Watch out!
Ten minutes before the train leaves!
[Ten minutes before the train leaves!]
Which platform should we go?
- Where's my magic wand?
- I have it.
[Fairy Ji Won doesn't
forget about her wand.]
It's right here.
[Run for the train!]
Too bad we don't have
time to get lunch boxes.
They have them on the train.
We didn't miss the train.
[They barely got on the train.]
It's 10:14.
We got on six minutes before.
We could have missed it.
This train goes all the way to Busan.
- The final destination is Busan.
- We might go all the way to Busan?
- Where does it stop?
- It's nice.
Don't we get to see the ocean
if we get off in Busan?
[Then you won't be able
to play the game.]
[By the way, what is this water for?]
This trains leaves from Seoul and
stops in Suwon, Daejeon, East Daegu
and Ulsan...
Then we need to get off in Daejeon.
It stops in Suwon at 10:42
and it stops in Daejeon at...
11:55!
How long does it take to
go from Daejeon to Daegu?
It's not too far.
Let me find out.
[The train leaves.]
[The flight time is at 10:30.]
- This might be better than KTX.
Who knows which train
they will take?
We're here.
Look, the graduations are
marked on the bottle.
I think we might lose the
water during the missions.
It's better to have more water.
Then it'll be easier to
purify the muddy water.
- We'll use it at the end?
- Yes!
We should try not to lose this water.
We should try and
keep the full bottle.
We'll use our tickets.
See you!
[To Kimhae!]
[At 10:30 sharp, the plane takes off.]
[The bus leaves at 11:20.]
We're running late.
Let's hurry!
- We can't miss this bus!
- We need to buy the tickets first.
What will be the fastest
out of taxi, plane, and our bus?
I think we'll be the fastest.
If we don't miss the bus.
We're late!
Hurry!
We have to get on this bus!
- Here is it!
- Where?
- Number seven.
- It's right here, West Daegu!
- It's that bus.
- Are you sure?
- We got on.
- It's an express bus.
It goes to Daegu without
stopping in other cities.
It makes me worry.
What if we can't get on the
bus by failing the mission?
We can take a taxi.
We can't get a taxi
at the resting area.
There's always a call taxi.
[We don't mind if you
guys pay for it.]
We'll get there first.
And this is the most comfortable way.
[Thanks to Blank Ji,
the Goddess of fortune?]
- It doesn't stop any other places.
[The bus leaves at 11:20.]
[Gwangmyung to Daegu]
It's been a while.
Right, Yoo Jung?
The name Yoo Jung suits you well.
Yoo Jung is a pretty name.
I don't know why but
I feel shy hearing the name.
- Why?
- I don't know why.
The name wasn't used
that much?
I have an introverted
and pure personality.
Says who?
She was like that when
she was a student.
Yoo Jung, Jun Do Yeon...
and there were few girls
who were really pretty.
- Really?
- Yes, you were one of them.
Jae Suk was... I mean,
Older Brother Jae Suk...
[Stop calling me
Older Brother, Yoo Jung!]
He was already a star.
He got awarded at the gag concert.
You mean, the gag contest?
[Older Brother Jae Suk was
awarded at the Gag concert?]
Yoo Jung confuses things.
She makes a lot of
mistakes when she talks.
That's why she didn't talk much.
Jae Suk was MC'ing for
all the events.
Everyone cracked up when he
told jokes.
Wow, you've been a star since then.
- Let's eat, Ji won.
- Bon appetite!
- Do you have a girlfriend, Kwang Soo?
- No.
- What's your ideal type like?
- I...
- What's my idea type like?
- Huh?
You know me.
Kwang Soo likes
pretty and cute girls.
Jae Suk used to like
thin girls when he was in college.
Very thin, right?
I liked delicate and graceful girls.
You know non-glamorous types,
like a stick figure.
Didn't you say Ha Soo Bin
went to the same school?
She spread a rumor.
I thought he was dating her.
I really thought you dated her.
I only found out recently.
She was mistaken and spread the rumor.
She spread the rumor for
more than 20 years.
Ha Soo Bin was the
prettiest girl back then.
I was wondering how could
he possibly date her?
Jae Suk is a conglomerate.
Otherwise, it's not possible.
- She kept spreading rumors about it.
- Yes, I kept saying he's really rich.
Did you like her?
Soo Bin's family used to pick her up.
She was about to make a debut.
That car! I heard the rumor
that it was your car.
She only told me recently
that she kept thinking it was my car.
My family wasn't rich at all.
We didn't really have
many handsome guys.
[Here's the example.]
I was within top three.
What are you doing?
Picking my tooth.
You're going to use the stir stick?
Why not?
It's my coffee.
[One of the most
handsome guys in 1991!]
Imagine if this kind of
guy dated Ha Soo Bin...
He wasn't doing this kind of stuff.
You should go to the jungle.
She keeps telling me to go
to the jungle.
[The rumor about Jae Suk and Ha Soo Bin
was revealed after 24 years.]
[Kimhae airport]
[Fairy Seo Hyung team
arrives in Busan.]
We were in Seoul a moment ago.
Now we're in Busan.
It was quick.
I'm shooting Running Man,
but it's fascinating.
[Seoul to Busan,
the swiftness of Running Man.]
They came to the bus terminal.
- I've never been to Daegu before.
- Really?
- Yes.
- No way!
[Thousand faces, Seo Hyung]
Believe me!
It's very meaningful today.
- You sound so different when you sing.
- I know, right?
People say that to me.
My voice gets thin when it's high.
Wouldn't it be nice to have
a boyfriend who sings well?
[You mean, this guy?]
Aren't you too bold?
I told you he's not that cold.
Would you like a girlfriend who
makes you laugh like this?
I'd be happy, sister.
He keeps calling me sister.
I can't just call you by name.
[Bold fairy and younger guy]
I think you can take a roll in a
Chinese martial arts movie.
Let's do it together.
[Will this Turbo's fan's
dream come true?]
We didn't have any traffic.
But this bus hasn't stopped
at any resting areas.
What's happening?
We've talked to the bus company
and found there was
an accident on the highway.
We're actually taking a detour.
Really?
It's not what the
producers planned on.
It's going to be delayed
about 30 minutes to an hour.
- We're in trouble.
[She's ready to sleep.]
[She speaks halfheartedly.]
- What do we do?
We might be the last
team to get there.
30 minutes to an hour?
We're in trouble...
I'm the only one who's in trouble.
[What will happen to
Fairy Ji Hyo's team?]
- Daegu is not that far from Daejeon.
- That's right.
[Fairy Ji Won's team
arrives in Daejeon.]
[Daejeon station]
It's been a long time since
I've been to Daejeon.
[They can take the bus from now on.]
We'll take a taxi...
You can't take a taxi,
you can only take the bus.
Even to the bus terminal?
- I see.
- How can we get to the bus terminal?
You didn't have to put
your hand up like that.
[To the bus terminal!]
[Street performing while
waiting for the bus.]
I write a letter in the fall...
It's spring.
Is it spring?
Sing something that
matches the weather.
The bus is here!
[The express bus comes right away.]
- Hello!
[They get on the city bus in Daejeon.]
How many stops should we go?
- Where are we?
- We got on here.
The terminal is only two stops away.
[Two stops]
[They arrive at the bus terminal.]
I see something over there.
- I see the 'R' flag.
- Yes, it's the 'R' flag.
- Is there a mission for us?
- Let's get off first.
[What is waiting for them?]
- What is it?
- It's a mission.
It's Coke.
You can take the bus only if
you complete the mission.
- We can't just get on the bus.
- I knew it.
Your mission is to make
the soda cans stand on their own.
You'll succeed when you make ten soda
cans stand for more than 3 seconds...
Isn't that too easy?
on their side, at a 45 degrees angle.
Use the edges.
They're standing up, why should
we make them stand on their side?
- It's going to fall.
- Is it even possible?
Ten cans?
- What? How?
- They want this.
- Is that possible?
- There's a man who makes stones stand.
- What should we do?
- Does it make sense?
- It doesn't.
- On it's edge?
It's not possible!
[What is he doing?]
You're not supposed to do that.
[Don't you know Columbus' egg?]
[It can't be...]
[Wait and see my success...]
[You're not a performance artist...]
He always try useless methods.
- It's cool.
- Let me drink, I'm thirsty.
- Is it?
- Drink from here.
Not one can but ten cans...
How could it be?
You use your brain on Running Man?
This isn't brain work.
Isn't it?
This is not it.
They're not going to stand like this.
Look! We can do this!
[They can rely on each other!]
On it's own.
- On it's own, right?
- Yes.
Strop screaming for nothing.
I'm trying to focus here.
[How should I do it?]
[They're not standing up
any time soon, either...]
- It doesn't stand.
- It's not going to work.
They don't want us to go, right?
Do you have gum?
[They wouldn't have any...]
[They have?]
[He's got a piece of gum.]
We're not allowed to use dirty tricks.
Are we?
I'm allowed to, right?
You don't need to add anything.
They stand on their own.
Do you know how long I've been trying?
You need to drink some.
Drink some?
How do I do it?
I drank some already.
Drink some and leave some!
It makes sense!
That's right!
Drink some and alter
the center of gravity!
Pour some here.
We can't drink them all.
Let's ask if they're thirsty.
Would you like some coke?
Don't drink it all.
Leave some in the can.
[Yield for the center of gravity!]
[They hang together with the people.]
In return...
we'll succeed!
[He boasts openly.]
Would it really work?
How much do you have in the can?
It doesn't stand.
[Will this half empty can
stand on its side?]
[It stood up on its side!]
- Jae Suk!
- It worked!
It worked!
- Jae Suk!
- It stood up!
Thank you so much!
The one who told me this...
Where are you?
Thank you so much!
Thank you.
We did it together!
It's the answer!
[Group 'Cola' is
taking a final bow.]
How did you figure it out?
Did you already know this trick?
It's amazing!
How is it possible?
How it is possible?
Incredible!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine and ten!
[Success! They make
ten cans stand on their side.]
Thank you!
You did it!
Thank you.
[Fairy Ji Won's team,
gets on the bus to Daegu.]
[Fairy Seo Hyung's team arrives
at Busan Bus Terminal.]
The 'R' flag is over there!
What's that?
Two plates of snacks?
Your mission is to
move the onion ring.
Each of you will hold a
cracker with your mouth.
Using the cracker, move five
onion rings one by one.
- Isn't this too thick?
- It's piece of cake!
Go, team, go!
This is our first game.
- Don't make it wet!
- It melts in your mouth.
Ready, set, go!
[Mission start!]
[Mr. Capable starts off fast.]
[How well is Kim Seo Hyung playing?]
No! Not like that!
[The first ring fails.]
[Jong Kook's ring gets go.]
[These two rhinos are the problem.]
[I can't work with you!]
Make it lower!
[Taking off!]
[This looks familiar...]
[Doppelganger?]
[They couldn't stop laughing.
They fail the first try.]
You should lower it down like this.
We can do it!
And I love this food.
[Second attempt, Start!]
[They start off fast again.]
[She gets the feel of it.]
[Their second ring.]
[They quickly moved two rings.]
[At this rate, they'll
succeed for sure.]
[Three rings are left.]
[Three rings are moved.]
[Fourth ring is on delivery.]
[Four rings are moved.]
[The last ring gets go.]
[They'll succeed, if they
don't make any mistakes.]
You did it!
[They succeed at moving
the onion rings.]
It's very embarrassing.
You move too much!
[They show off their ability
and pass the mission.]
You moved a lot!
[Fairy Seo Hyung's
team gets on the bus.]
[Fairy Ji Hyo's team is on
the bus for three hours.]
The bus will stop now.
Everyone, get off the bus.
- There's the 'R' flag!
- Hurry!
[What kind of a mission this?]
They prepared something here.
Your mission is to make eggs stand.
Making eggs stand?
All the team members should
make an egg stand on its end.
You can't break the egg.
Even Columbus broke it
to make it stand on its end.
You know Columbus' egg.
Does it actually stand on its end?
The bus stops for 15 minutes.
Hurry up and give us the eggs.
You should finish it in 15 minutes.
- Don't shake the table.
- How is it possible?
[Make an egg stand on its end!]
[Start!]
Is it even possible?
Does it really stand?
It does?
It's not going to happen.
[He's loosing his mind.]
Please give me another egg.
This one's crooked.
[Time marches on.]
It's frustrating.
I think I'm getting upset.
[Is it possible?]
I did it!
[It stood up.]
[The egg and his dream
broke at the same time.]
[Attention!]
Get a new egg, Suk Jin.
- Switch with me.
- We need to do it together!
Get a new one!
- The one that's heavier at the bottom?
- Yes.
[Can I have your attention, please?]
[The announcement is about
the bus leaving in five minutes.]
Gary needs to go to the bathroom.
[He's focused on the mission.]
[Work of concentration!]
- Hold it.
- Be quiet.
I'm even more pressured now.
[If Gary makes it stand on
its own for 3 seconds...]
One, two, three!
[They succeed at it!]
[Columbus, are you watching us?]
We're done, right?
- Let's eat this.
- Go to the bathroom now.
[Fairy Ji Hyo's team
gets back on the bus.]
[The water fairies are
getting close to Daegu.]
[Which team will be able to
purify the black muddy water?]
- We're here!
- We're here, Gary.
[Fairy Ji Hyo's team
arrived in Daegu.]
[They take a taxi right away.]
[Will Fairy Ji Hyo's team
arrive to 'D' park first?]
[Another team arrives in
Daegu around the same time.]
[They can only take the bus.]
This is not the end.
Let's run.
This is the stop for
the bus number 512.
Ji Won, why don't you sing a song
while we wait for the bus?
A song?
[A chanson jukebox.]
Listening to her song makes
it look like we're in Paris.
The bus is coming!
It's bus number 512!
[The bus came as soon as
she started playing guitar.]
[Will Fairy Ji Won's team
arrive at 'D' park first?]
The bus came so fast.
- I think there are many buses.
- They come when you play guitar.
[After the long journey...]
[they have arrived in Daegu.]
[The air in Daegu is full of spring.]
[What missions awaits them?]
['D' Park in Daegu.]
I think we're here.
- It must be here.
- It's here.
Are we here?
We took the hard way.
- That's true.
- It took us a while.
It could have been easy
if we could get off the
train in Daegu.
Then we could take a taxi
to get here.
[Fairy Ji Hyo's team
arrives at the park.]
We came first?
[A large stage awaits them.]
- We came first.
- We came first?
The express bus is the fastest.
[The Water Fairy Race]
You came first, as expected.
You'll have to face the
final mission soon.
You'll have to complete a mission
to get the address and a car key
so you can get to the
final mission site by the car.
You see these pretty
apples in this basket.
Inside, there's a mission.
You'll find out where
the final mission site.
Can we do it now?
They're here.
Hurry and give us the apple.
If you fail
you'll have to give us
100 ml of the fairy water.
- I knew it.
- We guessed it right.
[In a moment...]
[The mystery of fairy water revealed!]
[Who will be the last fairy
that solve the mystery?]
[Fairy Ji Won's team
arrives at the park.]
- We came first... no, they're here.
- They're here first.
What took you so long?
- When did you arrive?
- We just arrived here, too.
Did you have time to play guitar?
We did. Whenever she plays
guitar, the bus comes.
- You guys are totally lying!
- No, we're serious.
- The bus seriously comes when we play this.
- Are you serious?
[The miraculous bus calling guitar.]
- I was really surprised.
- You pick it.
- You have the best luck.
- She's the queen of choosing lucky.
Choose one, and show others
only when I tell you to.
- Have you made your selections?
- Let's see what it is.
- Fairy's bell.
[Ji Hyo's selection- Fairy's bell.]
[Fairy's bell-
What kind of a mission will it be?]
[A huge mat materializes on scene.]
- Is it going to be a gym?
- No, it's not going to be a gym.
[Team Fairy Ji Hyo- Fairy's bell.]
The men will takes turns twirling their
fairy once around their waist.
Each male will have to twirl her around
a total of three times
and ring the bell with her head, and
make the ringing sound to win the mission.
- They're totally going to fail.
- This team won't be able to do it.
[Why did they have to
pick such a mission?]
- You'll have 30 seconds.
- 30 seconds?
- We have to twirl her in five seconds?
- Of course.
- You just have to do it like this.
- Twist her around, and hand her over.
[So easy to say, isn't it?]
- Just twist, and flip her around like this.
How did Hee Suk do it in the past?
I remember he was so quick with it.
Wow, what did you have to
eat this morning?
- One, two, three.
- There you go.
[Throws her down on the ground.]
[Even the first spin results
in a dead drop to the ground.]
- What are you doing?
- You have to flip yourself around!
[They have to twirl her around six times,
and ring the bell with her head?]
There's no way we'll be able
to do this.
[Makes their first attempt
with a lot of nervous energy.]
- Ready!
- Wait!
- You can tell from their first movement.
- Yes, there you go!
- No, they're done.
- Can she walk over to me?
- That was already ten seconds.
- Walk over to me!
[Attempting to pass over to Big-nose,
and fails to pass her over.]
- Twirl her around quickly.
- One, two!
[Big-nose makes another attempt.]
Ji Hyo's the only one suffering here.
The poor thing... I feel so bad for her.
- The poor thing.
- We can't do this.
- Why are you guys so weak?
- Ji Hyo's holding herself back right now.
If she wasn't on camera right now,
she would've cussed already.
[Who cares if we got here quickly?]
- Ugh, my knee really hurts.
- Stay down and get some rest.
- Do you have any tiger balm?
- Tiger balm?
[No tiger balm, but a
tiger will be coming by later.]
- Want to pass on this game?
- Let's just give up now.
We're not going to do this game.
This is too much for us.
- We'll pick next.
- Okay, come up and select one.
Team Fairy Ji Hyo will lose
100ml of their water.
- I hope you get something awful!
- 5m flipper relay.
You'll take turns running around the
parameter of the mat in your flippers.
You'll have to run with the baton in hand,
and make it back across the starting line
and you'll have a total of
15 seconds to complete the relay.
- We'll run around it like this.
- You might be able to do it.
[Not the easiest mission
with the flippers on their feet.]
- Then we only have five seconds?
- Five seconds per person.
- It's five seconds per person.
- Kwang Soo, you'll have two seconds.
How would I be able to run around
in only two seconds?
Ji Won will have eight seconds,
and you'll have two seconds.
- This is the only thing we can do.
- The one and only thing.
- I actually want to take off my pants.
- Why would you take off your pants?
- I have another pair on underneath.
- Then take them off.
I need to reduce the weight
on my body.
These are running pants that
professional athletes wear.
Professional athletes wear these.
This is okay, isn't it?
- Yes, we're fine with it.
- Many athletes wear these.
- Go for it.
[If it's for the win...]
- We won't stop you.
- Professional athletes wear these!
- But professional athletes..
- But those athletes you speak of...
they wear another layer on
over those.
- But athletes wear these all the time.
- Seriously?
- But they usually wear another layer.
- Athletes wear these all the time.
- Aren't those long johns?
- No, they're not.
We might not be able to air this segment.
Is this going to be okay?
What's wrong with these?
These are just a normal pair of pants.
But when you start running...
Just don't get the camera
too close to me.
What is he doing right now?
Why is he doing that?
I have a short pair of shorts on,
so can I just wear those?
- Will my shorts be okay?
- Can he just wear his shorts?
[Kwang Soo has shorts on underneath!]
- We need to check the brand first.
- I'm going to check the brand first.
- Gary, can you go and check his shorts?
- They're really shorts.
- Then let me see.
- What are we going to do?
[They're obviously underwear.]
- They're definitely underwear.
- Athletes wear those, too.
[Who cares if they're underwear
in the name of victory?]
- No, you can't take off your pants.
- This is a variety show.
- They should be considered uniform.
- Let's see what you've got.
- We're going to go for it.
- Do you have any diapers?
[A little too much even for
his own teammates?]
- Wow, they're no joke.
- What is this?
- Athletes don't look like that.
- I think he looks cool.
- He actually looks like an athlete.
- I think I'm jealous.
Winning is what matters here.
We have to win this mission.
Kim Jong Kook will be here soon.
We have to do this before he gets here.
Ready, set, go!
[The effect of his pants?
Off at an alarming speed.]
[All three must cross the starting line
within 15 seconds to succeed the mission.]
[Already rounding the corner,
and hands off the baton to Kwang Soo.]
[Gallops around on his long legs,
and hands off the baton to Ji Won.]
[Ji Won takes off like
a feral beast of the jungle.]
[A clean relay race.]
[Would they have completed the race
within 15 seconds?]
[Ji Won crosses the finish line.]
[What is their finishing time?]
- I think we did it!
- 16.31 seconds.
[Unfortunately misses the deadline,
and loses 100ml of the water.]
- We were so close.
- I thought we made it.
But he even took off his pants.
Maybe he should've kept them on.
- It was because of his pants.
- Maybe he should've kept them on.
[Then you should've stopped me...]
[Team Seo Hyung finally arrives.]
- What the heck?
- We're the last ones here?
- You guys are finally here.
- What took you guys so long?
[The three teams are finally altogether.]
[Now that all three teams are together,
the mission can finally start for real.]
[Team Seo Hyung is feeling the exhaustion
after having taken the bus.]
- Did you guys receive the mission?
- We're doing it right now.
- Let us do it, too.
- You need to choose.
[Team Seo Hyung chooses their
mission as soon as they arrive.]
- Doesn't this look so pretty?
- It's as if we were meant to choose it.
- What is that?
- Fairy pyramid run?
Okay, listen carefully.
You're aware of what
the human pyramid is, right?
You just need to cross the finish line within
ten seconds while in the pyramid formation.
I thought Seo Hyung said she was going to
seduce Jong Kook by the end of the day.
- Really?
- I think he's already halfway there.
It's no big deal.
Jong Kook has a nickname,
and it's 'Ahn-Man-Nam.'
It means that he'll never
meet you halfway.
- Where do you live?
- In Geumhodong.
Okay, it's Seducer Gemhodong,
against Ahn-Man-Nam of Ahnyang.
- It's a close call.
- We'll even sing you a serenade.
[A sweet serenade for the two lovebirds.]
Our fairy will sing you a love song
while you do your mission.
[The Parisian atmosphere
is already in the air.]
Okay, we're going to start the serenade.
With our Ahn-Man-Nam of Ahnyang...
Seducer Gemhodong.
- This is such a relaxing song.
- It's a really nice song.
[All the focus is on the singer even with
all the ruckus going on around them.]
[Ji Won's love song lights a fire under
a flame that's already gone out.]
[There's the part we've all
been waiting for!]
[The lyrics are powerful enough to have
Seo Hyung break out in a dance.]
[Falling under the spell of the song's magic.]
[Everyone else is focused
on singing the song.]
[They all seem very enthused
from the song.]
Why do I feel so exhausted
all of a sudden?
- Get in position.
- Okay, get ready.
- All bodies must cross the line.
- I'm going to go really fast.
Ready... no, wait.
- That was a knee-kick.
- That looked dangerous.
- What are you doing?
- Get on!
[Goes from a human pyramid to a single
ride on Jong Kook in the blink of an eye.]
- Why do you keep doing that?
- What were you doing?
[Seducer Gemhodong's eager attempt
gets her team to fail the mission.]
- What am I, chopped liver?
- Just get out of their way.
She doesn't lean on me at all.
[Seo Hyung, you can trust me...]
[But Jong Kook is all I need.]
- Why are you getting in the way?
- That was crossing the line.
You're coming on way too strong!
You're scaring him away.
[Too bad... maybe next time.]
[Team Seo Hyung makes
another selection.]
- The Fairy Bell?
- What is that?
[Team Ji Hyo's previously failed
mission is selected.]
- I think Seo Hyung and Jong Kook...
- I think this game is meant for them.
- This game was designed for them.
- Can Jong Kook twirl six times by himself?
[Each man must twirl their fairy three times
and ring the bell with her head to succeed.]
- Wrap your arms around my neck.
- Did you see how he lifted her up?
He sounds like he's getting
his workout.
[Mr. Capable successfully twirls her
around in his first attempt.]
Let your body go loose,
and drop your arms down.
[Screams out loud in a high-pitched scream.]
[Seducer Gemhodong loses all her
resolve in front of Ahn-Man-Nam.]
- The way she just sounded...
- It's like she fell off of Namsan tower.
I thought she was falling off
the 63 Building.
[Practice round is over,
and it's time to start the mission.]
- Okay, we're going to start.
- Seducer Gemhodong...
- Against Ahn-Man-Nam of Ahnyang.
- Hold on, okay?
[And the serenade starts off again.]
- Ugh, this is sapping me of my strength.
- Knock it off, you guys.
[The finishing lyrics to the song.]
- I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
[The serenade has the strange power
of sapping Ha Ha of his energy.]
Ready, set, go!
[Mr. Capable, having figured it out earlier,
easily twirls Seo Hyung around.]
Hey!
[Hands off the fairy over to Ha Ha.]
Hey, pull my leg out!
[But Kkuk rescues his fairy from
the moment of danger with ease.]
[A speedy twirl.]
- Wow, they really are pretty fast.
- I think they're picking up speed.
[But Ha Ha still remains an issue.]
[But successfully hands the fairy off
thanks to Kkuk's help.]
[Kkuk's third, and final twirl.]
[Continuing to pick up the speed.]
[Ha Ha's final twirl.]
[A fast enough twirl, and they
might actually have a chance!]
[There's the high-pitched scream again.]
[Team Seo Hyung fails,
and loses 100ml of their water.]
You, come here!
I'm so sorry, but I didn't
have any strength left.
[Weak Ha Ha's powerful drop.]
[A total of 200ml loss for the team.]
[Hope these missions won't make her ill.]
- Okay, let's finish this.
- Is it our turn?
- Cheek to cheek?
- Yes, cheek to cheek.
All three will have to run a circle around
the mat with a can held between their cheeks
and drop the cans into the basket within
ten seconds in order to succeed.
[Team Ji Hyo- Cheek to Cheek.]
I hope Seo Hyung and
Jong Kook get this mission.
Okay, let's go.
[Great teamwork is of the essence
for this mission.]
[What is this!]
What is he doing!
[Sorry, I was wrong...]
[Ji Hyo explodes!]
Ji Hyo...
[An attempt to interfere
results in a complete stampede.]
- That was crossing the line!
- Then we're going to start interfering, too!
You did good.
All three of you timed it perfectly.
All of you kicked out at the same time.
[All three kicked out at the same time.]
- All three kicked out at the same time!
- Three feet at the same time!
- The decision is up to the other teams.
- Are we letting them do it again?
- Okay, no more interfering from now on.
[Team Ji Hyo gets a do-over.]
- You can't step on the line.
- Ready...
[Must get the cans in the basket within
ten seconds in order to succeed.]
[Five years' worth of teamwork is in play!]
[Will they be able to succeed
within their time limit?]
[The cans are dropped into the basket.]
[But did they succeed in getting it
done within ten seconds?]
Team Fairy Ji Hyo's time is...
- 9.9 seconds.
- Yeah!
[Team Ji Hyo succeeds the mission.]
[Still succeeds the mission
even with the interference.]
Before you go...
[A total of two mission failures-
Thus, 200ml is deducted from their bottle.]
You have 800ml, and here's
the final mission location.
Win the race by turning the cloudy
water supply into clean water.
You may get started.
[First team to get on their way
with the car keys in hand.]
- How about we do it like a competition?
- In that case...
We will make you an offer.
Take this mission, and make your own deals.
Let's do the flipper run mission
with 200ml on the line.
The loser team will lose 200ml of their water
and can leave five minutes
after the winning team leaves.
[Rule- Loser team loses 200ml,
and stay behind an extra five minutes.]
Okay, we can do this!
[Only one challenge left to face.]
[With the short distance,
the first runners plays a crucial role.]
You have to run faster!
[Jae Suk's flipper falls off!]
[The prop failure brings the
game to a halt.]
Isn't this all a part of the game?
- I think I should tie them.
- That's not fair.
Sorry to say this,
but Seo Hyung's really mad.
- She's not even saying a word.
- Who cares if your shoe fell off?
Let's just get back to the game.
She's really angry right now.
[Fairy Seo Hyung's full of anger,
and Fairy Ji Won is full of cheer.]
She can't stay still
not even for a single second.
I think I get why you're so well-suited
for the jungle now.
- I think I get it now.
- I'll do my best.
[On the other hand,
Fairy Seo Hyung is full of nervous energy.]
- But you've been wanting to run all day.
- Yes, it's time for you to run.
- Let's give her the chance.
- I'll run later.
[The fairies will now be the first runners.]
- Ready... set, go!
- There you go!
[The two fairies are off
at a powerful start.]
[Arrives at the halfway mark
almost at the same time.]
[Makes a slide across the line.]
- Time!
[A quick time out.]
[Seo Hyung's slide brings
the game to yet another halt.]
[Each team takes their turn
bringing the game to a halt.]
I'm injured right now!
- But falling down is the fun of the game.
- Falling down shouldn't count!
- What are you guys even saying!
- This shouldn't count.
[This is going to take all night.]
- It's already getting dark!
- But she's saying that she's hurt!
You guys saw how hard she fell.
But she's not even hurt
because she didn't scream out loud.
[If she had been hurt, then she would've
let out a high-pitched scream.]
Let's just stop all this, and
have one final round to end it all.
Let's stop playing dirty,
and finish it with one final round.
- Then Jong Kook must show off his moves.
- What are you doing!
[Taekwondo Jong Kook immediately
launches into his moves.]
- How about a roundhouse kick?
- What are you doing!
- What was that all about?
- Why did you want to see that?
[Jong Kook earns his team another chance
with his show of taekwondo moves.]
- What did seeing any of that do?
- This is the final round.
No more giving breaks for falling down,
or having their shoes fall off.
I'm not going to do anything,
so whoever crosses the line first...
- Why aren't you doing anything!
- You have to play the mediator!
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm not going to do anything.
- We've already wasted so much time!
- Kwang Soo...
Let's win this round,
and leave them behind.
[Rule- Loser team will lose 200ml,
and must wait another five minutes.]
Ready, set, go!
[The fairies' powerful start.]
[Ji Won is first to pass off her baton.]
[Jae Suk takes off at a sprinting pace.]
[Ha Ha is right at Jae Suk's tail.]
[Passes off the baton
almost at the same time.]
[Mr. Capable is now on the move.]
- Kwang Soo!
[A high pitched cheer for Kkuk.]
[Mr. Capable unleashes his full power.]
[Will he successfully take over the win?]
[Kwang Soo crosses the finish line
first by the split of a hair.]
[Team fairy Ji Won finally
wins the mission.]
[The frightening final round
against Mr. Capable.]
[Team Fairy Ji Won wins the competition,
and the chance to leave immediately.]
Wow, seriously!
[Cheery Fairy's celebration of victory.]
- She wants to do this.
- Why are we doing this?
That's enough.
Just get going.
- Let's get going.
- Just leave, so I don't have to look at you.
You now have a total of 700ml,
but you can get going immediately.
Here's the final mission location,
and you will be deducted 400ml.
No, not 400ml!
That's too much!
[What is the secret behind this water?]
[This is the site of the final mission.]
[Final mission- Clarify the water.
But first, they must find the location.]
[Team Ji Hyo is first to arrive
at the final mission site.]
- It feels like a race of some sorts.
- I think you're right.
- I think we need to find the site first.
- Should we separate or what?
- I'll go up to the second floor.
- Okay, I'll go check over this way.
Where's the mission?
[Where's the mission site?]
- Oh, there's the top.
I have a feeling about this place.
[Gary is already at
the top floor of the building.]
[This is the contaminated water
that they must clarify.]
[Team Fairy Ji Hyo is first
to discover the mission site.]
You need at least 1L of the fairy water in
order to clarify the contaminated supply.
Stealing the other teams water
is also allowed to accomplish the task.
[Must clarify the contaminated water
by obtaining 1L of the fairy water.]
[Team Fairy Ji Hyo currently has
800ml of the fairy water.]
- It's on the third floor, and we were right.
- What is it?
- We have to steal, don't we?
- We need a total of 1L to win the race.
- Is that the mission?
- Then we have to dump it all in the supply.
[Team Fairy Ji Hyo has the advantage
for knowing the rules of the game.]
Getting here first gave us
a huge upper hand.
[Team Fairy Ji Won is the second team
to arrive on scene.]
If we do this right,
then we can win this right away.
[We'll end this game before
the other team even finds the final mission.]
Gary, I'll go up to the third floor
with our water bottle.
[The plan is for Gary and Big-nose to ambush
their opponents and steal their water.]
[Then pass it off to Blank Ji,
who'll be waiting on the third floor.]
- Do we have to find the mission card?
- I don't know.
[Team Fairy Ji Won is still unsure
of what the final mission is.]
[Here comes the prey!]
- Be careful of our water.
- I don't know what to expect.
[Not knowing what to expect
puts them on edge.]
- Ji Won, are you feeling nervous?
- There's Ji Hyo!
- Where? Song Ji Hyo!
- Have you found anything?
- No, I haven't found anything yet.
[Something smells fishy!]
[Gary's plan is to make a casual
approach, and eye for his chance.]
We have to find it first.
- I think they know something.
- I'm getting a weird feeling about this.
They keep following us.
- Why are you following us?
- We were headed there, too.
You guys are running away from us,
so it's just making me run faster.
[Big-nose makes a sloppy approach.]
[This is what you call an ambush?]
- You're after our water, aren't you?
- We just want to see how much you have.
- They're trying to steal our water.
- There must be some sort of a mission.
[Team Ji Hyo's plan comes to an end,
only after giving their opponents a hint.]
[Team Fairy Seo Hyung is the last to arrive.]
I'm already getting weird vibes.
What is it?
[Team Fairy Ji Won discovers the mission.]
[Enter the safe zone with at least
1L of water in order to win the race.]
We have to steal their water?
[All three teams needs the fairy water
from their opposing teams in order to win!]
[Which of the three teams will successfully
clarify the contaminated water supply?]
[Team Fairy Seo Hyung also
gets on the move.]
I think they're headed down here.
[Team Ji Won- Up above.
Team Seo Hyung- Down below.]
- I don't see Jong Kook down there.
- Where did he go?
[Jong Kook is nowhere to be seen...]
- That's a definite trap.
- Should I go down there by myself?
- Go down there.
[Ji Won takes the water bottle,
and Kwang Soo gets on the move.]
[The Giraffe is right
in front of their eyes!]
[Have they been cornered?]
Jong Kook, I don't have anything!
[Giraffe... an ambush attack
is the Tiger's specialty...]
- What are you after?
- Don't come here!
Don't come here!
- See? I told you that it was a trap.
- It was, wasn't it?
[Sacrificing the Giraffe was something
we've been prepared to do.]
[His foolish attempts at an attack
result in his own agony.]
Jong Kook, let's go and get
Suk Jin together.
[What was the herbivore thinking
by attacking the carnivore?]
- Come here, and chastise him.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'll just leave, okay?
- Doesn't this mean that Kwang Soo is dead?
[This is just a variety show, Seo Hyung.]
Let's go and steal the water from them.
- What if we stay in hiding?
- But we're dead if we're caught.
- Let's go and hide amongst the staff.
- Amongst the staff?
I know it's not a solid plan,
but it's also the safest.
If you hide behind all those people,
then they might not see you at all.
No one will see you back there, and
we'll go steal the water from someone.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, and we'll be back within ten minutes.
- We'll check in every five minutes.
- Okay.
- Come and check in.
- We'll come back and check in with you.
- No, don't go anywhere! Stay right there.
- Stay safe.
Just stay right there.
Let me just stay here
right between you guys.
[This is where Blank Ji is hiding.]
- That's the final mission site.
- We have to come up with a plan.
[Just then, the arrival of their
opponents!]
No matter what happens,
you just stay right here and wait.
[Oh no, it's Jong Kook!]
- It's cold out here.
- It is, isn't it?
- Just keep walking around.
- Okay, I'll walk around.
[Hmm... where should I hide?]
[No, don't come here!]
[Kkuk also takes his spot
amongst the staff members.]
[What a novel site.]
[Meanwhile, Haroro and Seo Kyung
are off on a search for more water.]
[Huh?]
Jae Suk, come here!
[Giraffe gets to him first!]
- Stay right there.
- Help me get his shoes off.
[What do I do?]
- Let me see your shoes.
[The opposite of the earlier scene.]
Here, Jong Kook!
Ji Won is alone, and now's the chance!
- Now's the chance!
- Don't make me thrown this down.
Ji Won is alone!
Right now is the chance!
[Just then... Gary makes his move!]
[She really threw it down!]
[The woman from another star...
She throws away the precious water bottle!]
Get down!
[The first person to get to the bottle
gets the chance to win!]
[Big-nose took the elevator?]
[The water bottle is mine!]
[Gary gets to it first!]
[Gary... Suk Jin is still in the elevator.]
Suk Jin!
[Gary tosses the bottle away.]
[Big-nose is nowhere to be found,
and the water is returned to its owner.]
[We must steal that bottle away!]
Where did Suk Jin go!
[I'm coming... huh?]
[Must steal the water away,
and get it to our Tiger.]
- Where did Seo Hyung go?
- Where are you?
Where are you!
[Seo Hyung makes her attack.]
[But the fairy water is passed off
to Yoo Hyuk's hands.]
[After all the tussle, and fighting,
the fairy water makes its way to the top.]
Jong Kook!
[It's not time yet...]
[They didn't know it at the time...
but all three bottles were in one place.]
Kwang Soo, you know what to do, right?
Just dump it if anyone tries to get it.
- We'll let the other two teams battle it out.
- Really?
- It's no loss for us.
- We'd rather just dump it out.
- Do you think you're brave enough to do it?
- Why don't you try it?
Dump out everything you've got.
Don't do that!
[My chance will come...]
It's only going to get colder for him.
- Kwang Soo...
- I'm not cold yet.
Ha Ha... where's Ji Hyo? I think
she's hiding around here somewhere.
- What do I do?
- We have to find Ji Hyo.
- I'll go around.
[The net is closing in.]
[Big-nose also takes off his socks.]
[Team Ji Won is in danger!]
[Barefooted Giraffe attempts
to make his escape!]
[Just what is going on here?]
[Will they steal...
or have it stolen away?]
[The battle where the victory
hangs on the line!]
[Should I go out there and help them?]
[Huh?]
[What is this weird feeling?]
- Where's Jong Kook?
[Makes eye contact with the Tiger.]
[Blank Ji flees for safety.]
[Ji Hyo must be captured!]
[It's time for me to start
making my move.]
[Ji Hyo becomes the main target.]
[A battle to clarify
the contaminated water supply.]
[Any one of the teams has the chance to win
by stealing their opponent's water.]
[Ha Ha successfully steals it away!]
[This is the moment that he's waited for...
Kkuk is on the move!]
[What the heck?]
[What is Jong Kook doing there?]
[Ha Ha plays defense...
and Jong Kook breaks past Jae Suk!]
[No!]
[Kkuk enters the safe zone.]
[The winners are determined
in the blink of an eye.]
- Jong Kook and I were both hiding there.
- But neither of you knew?
[The evidence of a fierce battle.]
Dump the contents of both the bottles,
and the men will have to stir it up.
[Seo Hyung's 600ml, and Ji Hyo's 800ml-
A total of 1400ml of fairy water.]
[The contaminated water supply
is starting to change!]
The water is starting to dilute.
[The once muddy looking water...
is all of a sudden clear as crystal!]
[As the water clears up, a written
word can be seen at the bottom!]
[Team Fairy Seo Hyung wins the race!]
[Winning prize- Gold rings.]
[Breaks out in a bright smile
after having seen her prize.]
You two should get married!
[The two should get married!]
- This was so much fun.
- Thank you for coming on our show.
[Thank you to everyone who participated,
and for making this filming possible.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A wild night!
Everyone gathers around in secrecy.]
[Unlock the mysteries!]
[The man with the brains-
Sung Shi Kyung.]
[The man with the looks-
Kim Dong Hyun.]
[There's only one goal-
The golden key.]
[Must unlock the mystery!]
[The real race starts now!]
[A fierce battle of the brains.]
[Ferocious physical battles.]
[And... the clash of the monsters.]
[This is the moment that
they've been waiting for.]
[Next Week on Running Man-
The Dark Knight- Hunter of the Key]