[A day in the month of May, filled
with the endless laughter of children...]
[Suddenly, all the toys disappeared.]
[Where have all the toys gone?]
Kids will like it.
[Running Man members
have come to a toy store.]
- I really like toys.
- Toys!
[The toy boxes are empty.]
They took all the toys away.
There are no toys.
- There aren't any toys!
- Empty boxes!
[At that moment!]
- What's that?
[Startled]
Get me out of here!
[The last toy box that has a toy in it.]
- He scared me.
- Oh, someone's in there?
- I like the wrapping paper.
- Open it?
Let's open the wrapper.
[Full of excitement.]
[What kind of gift will they receive?]
[The return of the Hip-hop
Godfathers, Jinusean.]
Hello!
It's so old-schooled!
[The feel of the 90's.]
[Hip-hop Papillons inside the CD.]
It's too old-school.
[We'll show you what old-school is.]
[Making a triangle with his hands.]
[The 90's hip-hop style.]
[It's nostalgic!]
It's too old!
It's this kind of stuff.
Please get us out.
It's stuffy.
Hurry and let us out!
[Opening the CD case.]
- Jinusean is here!
[The big brothers of the hip hop
world visit Running Man!]
I can smell the cologne!
[Welcome Jinusean!]
Thank you!
It's been a while since I've seen
a guest with so much hair gel.
- It's hair mousse!
- I think it's hair gel.
- Is that hair mousse?
- Everything is mixed together.
You know what YG says about Sean.
Sean is the least humorous
person in the world.
- He said Sean isn't funny.
- YG says that in the office.
YG is not funny, either.
- He is funny.
- Is he?
- Yes, he is.
[They're complimenting YG.]
He's funny when he's feeling
the rhythm.
[Yang Hyun Suk's signature
neck movement.]
Before I explain the rules
I will announce the teams first.
Jinu, Sean, and Kim Jong Kook
are a team.
[The 90's singers trio?]
So you put him in as part
of the old-school team?
What do you mean old-school?
You weren't popular at all back then!
Were you?
Old-school...
[He is heartbroken by the
unexpected comment.]
You know when I had meetings
with my fan club...
- he was emceeing for me.
- I admit it.
You know what upsets me the most?
I emceed at the inauguration
ceremony for his fan club
but he couldn't remember me.
[I don't remember.]
- Seriously.
Were you a recreation instructor?
Back then, his boss paid me
right after the event was done.
It wasn't even in an envelope.
- Not in an envelope?
- From his wallet?
- I said 'Excuse me...'
[Fumble, fumble]
Take it!
Thank you.
[The sorrowful days...]
Then, it's Jae Suk,
Suk Jin, and Kwang Soo.
I think I get the idea of the
roles we're assigned today.
And Gary, Ha Ha, and
Ji Hyo are one team.
It's a love triangle.
Here are the rules for the Children's
Day special, The Toy Race.
All the toys in the world have
vanished because of the toy collector.
Your goal is to find all the toys for
the hopes and dreams of all children.
We must give their
hopes and dreams back.
A donation Angel,
Sean is here today, too.
Today... we need to...
do something nice.
You look so excited today.
You're excited because
all the 90's stars came back.
To the winning team
we will give a ticket for which
you can use to donate all the toys.
- Something Sean would be greedy over!
- Sean loves donating.
[An intense mission contrary to the
month of May, the family month.]
[Get hints of where
the toys are hidden!]
[There is only one place
you can find the toys!]
[The place they go to get a hint is...]
Is it a school?
Maybe it's indoors.
[Running Man goes to
an elementary school.]
Are we first?
Are we the only ones?
Yes, you are first.
Our team matched with these hats.
I didn't want to wear it,
but they forced me.
But ever since I wore it,
I'm already out of energy.
I'm so tired after I put it on.
This hat makes you look weak.
It's not cool no matter
how you wear it.
You want to look cool alone?
Don't you know I'm cool
when I take the hat off?
I'm wearing it on purpose!
We're in Anyang!
- Hey.
- It's Anyang!
Why did you guys change
your hats?
- Wear it like us!
- You have to match.
What are you, a duck?
- You're like a duck!
- Wear it!
- Are you a duck?
- It's embarrassing!
Show them how weak it looks.
- What is this?
[He becomes a village foreman.]
[The next example, Gary.]
[The moment Gary wears the hat,
the game is over.]
- What do I look like?
[He becomes a naive country farmer.]
Do I look weird?
Tell me what I look like!
[When Sean wears it...]
[He looks weak.]
[When Jinu wears it...]
[He looks handsome.]
- He's handsome.
- Jinu looks nice in whatever he wears.
He looks like a typical
handsome student from abroad.
ugly student from abroad.
I became a singer by luck,
he became a singer by looks.
- Good comment!
- You're funny.
- Why did YG say he's not funny?
- That's what I'm saying.
We have arrived at
an elementary school
to bring back the toys
from the toy collector.
You will be doing a mission
with three junior students.
First, you will need to find a friend
to do the mission with.
We have recorded the cute
voices of the students.
- How do we find them by voice?
- It's one per team.
One student per team.
Go find them after listening
to their voice.
Twinkle twinkle little star,
how I wonder what you are.
It's a boy's voice.
Chicks go chirp chirp.
Cows go moo moo.
There's a tadpole
wiggle wiggle wiggles around.
- His voice is a little hoarse.
- Amongst first to third graders.
How do we find them?
[To find all the missing toys,
Running Man's adventure starts.]
It doesn't sound like a first grader.
- They're in second or third grade.
- You know these kinds of things.
- Hello!
- What grade are you in?
- You're in grade two?
- Do you know whose voice this is?
- I know!
- Who is it?
- Grasshopper!
- No not that.
No, not me.
Sing it for me.
In a little pond
You're on TV, right?
wiggle wiggle wiggles around.
You're not the one, but thanks.
Sing it for me once.
In a little pond, there's a tadpole.
Ha Ha, isn't it him?
One, two, three, four!
In a little pond, there's a tadpole.
No, it's not him.
He's missing the huskiness.
In a little pond, there's a tadpole.
Why do they all sound the
same to me?
[Meanwhile Jinusean...]
It's Jinusean!
Wow, they know us!
[Jinusean is still hot nowadays.]
Elementary school kids know us!
What grade does this sound like?
Grade one?
I know a kid in grade one
that has the same voice.
Really?
Who is it?
Let's go.
It's a huge testimony.
- Min Suk, where did you go?
- Min Suk, what floor is it?
- Min Suk, maybe it isn't your friend!
- First floor.
Hello!
- Here?
- Where is it?
- Is he here?
- Where is he?
- Hello, teacher!
- Hello, children!
You're very good at greeting people.
- Hi! They're so cute.
- Min Suk, where is he?
- Hi.
- Him?
- Hi guys!
- Jae Wook?
Sing for us!
The weird thing about Jae Wook
is that he seems slightly nervous.
Jae Wook, did you sing it
by any chance?
- Twinkle twinkle little star.
- Can you sing it?
Ready, start.
- Twinkle twinkle little star...
- It's not him.
- I don't think it's Jae Wook.
Jae Wook, you didn't sing it, right?
- Hunter goes bang, bang...
- Whose voice is this?
It's her!
It's you, right?
You recorded this, right?
Sing it.
[It gets more and more confusing.]
- They're all similar.
I think he's here somewhere.
You sang it, right?
You sang it?
In a little pond, there's a tadpole...
No, it's not him.
Sorry, you try.
In a little pond...
Try it again.
In a little pond, there's a tadpole
wiggle wiggle wiggles around.
- It's not him.
- You're so cute.
Sing for me once, please.
In a little pond...
[Comparing his voice to
the recorded voice.]
[Could it be... you?]
- What's your name?
- Oh Seung Hun.
- Seung Hun, is this you?
- Yes.
Making a face like an old man.
- Is this really you?
- Yes.
- Ready, go.
[Dream's father double checks.]
Gary, he's here!
At this part, he sings it like this.
Listen carefully.
It sounds the same.
- It's him!
- It sounds the same.
We found him!
It's you, right?
We'll win with Seung Hun!
Bye!
- Hello!
Brother Jong Kook!
I like you out of all the
boys in the whole world!
- Thank you, really?
- Yes.
- Is this one of your friends?
- Who do you think it is?
Who does this sound like?
Her?
It's me.
- It's you?
- Sing it for me.
Do you know what her name is?
Chicks go chirp chirp.
Cows go...
- moo moo.
- It sounds like her!
- Is this you?
- Yes!
- Really?
[Success at finding Shin Ye Ju.]
I think she told the truth
because she likes you.
Is it really you?
Let's go!
[Now it's time to do the real mission!]
Let's be quiet, everyone!
Sing 'twinkle twinkle' for me.
- Twinkle twinkle...
- Do it properly!
- One, two, three, four!
- Twinkle twinkle...
Why are you singing like that?
Did you record it?
He's not singing with his real voice.
Did Jun Ho sing it?
- He's not singing with his real voice.
- He's using a fake voice.
- Do it, do it.
- Sing it.
- Twinkle twinkle...
- Look at him.
- See?
- It's not his real voice?
- No!
- What his name?
- Kim Hyun Woong.
- Hyun Woong, is it you?
- No.
It's Hyun Woong!
It's him for sure!
- We found him!
- It's Hyun Woong!
- It's okay.
- We're on the same team!
- He did leave the class before.
- Then it's him!
- Hyun Woong, let's go!
- We'll be back with Hyun Woong!
[The mission with the
three students starts.]
Let's get in.
We arrived first.
[Shin Ye Ju, age 8.]
[Blue Team arrives.]
You don't have to change
your voice anymore.
You already found her?
[Kim Hyun Woong, age 8.]
How did you find him?
He kept changing his voice.
He's still using a fake voice.
Everyone was singing
normally, except for him.
Hyun Woong is very shy.
Introduce yourself.
- Hyun Woong, introduce yourself.
- Start!
Hello.
- Use your real voice.
- They've arrived.
Hi!
[Oh Seung Hun, age 8.]
- Please introduce yourself.
- He's emotionless.
The first mission is
'I see the children's mind.'
The kids will take turns
giving questions.
The kids will watch and
listen to a song and repeat it.
Your job is to guess the song.
You need to guess three songs
correctly.
The first one to get three
answers will get the best hint.
The songs that the kids will sing to...
are 90's hits.
It sounds difficult.
We have to guess them?
- The kids will look at the videos?
- That's right.
Ye Ju's good at singing.
Her dream is to become a singer.
Go, Seung Hun, go!
[Nod]
[Emotionless Seung Hun.]
Seung Hun is quiet
and expressionless.
He's young and shy.
That's why.
[Will they be able to
understand the children?]
Good luck!
Seung Hun, good luck!
[Nod, nod]
Ready, set...
['I see the children's minds,'
first round.]
[What is it?]
[Quiet]
- Seung Hun!
- Try it.
- It's okay, just do it.
- I can't do it.
- No, it's okay!
We can get it right.
Answer!
Just come, just come!
Turbo's twist king!
[Is this the dance moves
from Turbo's twist king?]
Such an old reaction!
Just do whatever you see!
[This hand movement is...]
- S.E.S!
- No, no, no!
I hope you believe me.
Hurry and say the answer!
S.E.S, 'I hope you believe me.'
S.E.S, 'I'm your girl'!
[Brother Jong Kook, get it right.]
Blah blah... over!
Answer!
Jinusean's... 'I hope you tell me!'
It's 'Tell me'!
[Listening it once more...]
It's right, it's right.
[Blue Team, correct.]
[We didn't get our own song right...]
Still aiming to be number one again.
[He copied Uhm Jung Hwa's
dance moves correctly.]
[And Sean's rap, rhyme part.]
We promised over and 'over'!
Blah blah... 'over'!
My love, it was 'over.'
My heart cries 'over.'
[His rhyme part is spot on.]
- Blah blah... 'over'!
[Blue Team gets one point.]
[We should have gotten it right...]
[It's the power of the hat!]
We did it!
[Seung Hun is good at
pointing out the highlight.]
- You're really good.
- Good job.
[Still emotionless.]
There should be a limit.
Like, you can't answer for 15 seconds
after giving the wrong answer.
Why is your style so old-school?
Nowadays, we just go out!
Oh, nowadays?
You invited the 90's stars and
tell them they're too old-school?
You guys only do what
Jong Kook tells you.
When he tells you to go, you go.
- It's their personality.
- We're trying to help.
- Ye Ju, good luck!
- Go, Ye Ju!
- Good luck!
- Just look at me!
[Okay, Brother Jong Kook.]
[Round Two.]
[Hands behind her back.]
[This time, we'll get it!]
[This song!]
[Everyone knows.]
Fin.K.L's 'Forever Love'!
[Everyone sings 'Forever Love.']
[It's this dance, when
it comes to Fin.K.L.]
[Ye Ju and Fin.K.L's comparison.]
[Young Hyori sings
the beginning of the song.]
[Her pitch was 100% in sync.]
Fin.K.L's 'Forever Love'!
[Green Team, gets one point.]
You did so well!
Ye Ju sang for us.
- Hyun Woong, we're a team!
- Hyun Woong, do well!
Brother Jong Kook, good luck!
- Thanks, Ye Ju!
[A fatherly smile.]
[Kkuk's admirer.]
You be quiet, Ye Ju.
Ye Ju, look at us too!
Ji Hyo's here.
We're here too, Ye Ju!
[No, Big Nose!]
[Sow the wind and reap the storm.]
[Good luck, everyone!]
Do well, Hyun Woong!
Blue Team can win if
they get this right.
Don't miss a single thing
Hyun Woong does.
Clon's 'Nan'!
Now, it's us!
Dance?
Answer!
Clon's...
'Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah'!
Clon's 'Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah'!
Kung ddari sha bah rah,
Pa pa pa pa!
[Blue Team, first place.]
It's the power of the hat!
[Devastated.]
[Hyun Woong played a big
role in helping them win.]
He's an expert at the 'papa' part.
It's for the second place now.
I think it's the hat.
[The magic of the blue hat.]
You did well.
Good job.
[We can't lose second place!]
Answer!
Turbo's 'Love is.'
[Incorrect.]
[Hip dance?]
[It's that!]
JYP's 'Don't leave me.'
The answer is
[Correct.]
[The expression expert,
emotionless Seung Hun.]
How did you do that?
[The song's highlight
is the hip dance.]
[He got it on at first sight!]
- You're so good!
[He can point out the highlights.]
[Pink Team, gets one point.]
He points out the highlight!
There are kids who know
the critical parts in things.
He's good.
[Ye Ju's turn to explain.]
[This rhythm!]
Answer!
DJ DOC's 'Dance with DOC.'
[Correct.]
[Great job!]
[Green Team, two points.]
[Pink Team, one point.]
[If Green Team gets the next one right
they are second place.]
We will win for Ye Ju!
['I see the children's minds,'
round two.]
He always gets the important part.
Here it comes.
[Green Team was fast.]
[This dance must be...]
HOT's 'Candy'!
[The hammer dance in 'Candy.']
[Green Team, second place.]
[The hero of this mission, Seung Hoon.]
[A big success with the children!]
- Good job, Ye Ju!
- You guys are awesome!
- Great job!
- You are very good!
Each team, please check your hints.
- Can we look at it now?
- Yes.
This is it?
Wow, our hint is awesome!
- You gave us the answer!
- South Korea!
[South Korea]
Thank goodness
it's not overseas!
The place is in Korea.
[First and second place
have a discussion.]
Are there a lot of things to discuss?
Isn't it in our country?
[Hwa Chang Elementary School.]
- Thank goodness we came second.
- It was risky.
Our hint was 'Children's Day.'
Usually, they have events
at Central Park.
When we were young, we
used to go to the cinema.
We used to watch a movie,
then go eat black bean noodles.
But now, I think it's...
the amusement park.
I wonder what the best hint was.
Ours was 'Children's Day.'
We're doing well today!
It's working out well.
Our hint was 'screaming and laughter.'
Do you really think it's
the amusement park?
Our first hint says so.
If it's screaming, then
it's an amusement park for sure.
Screaming and laughter?
[Gwangmyeong cave,
Gwangmyeong, Gyeonggi Province.]
How could there be a cave?
Is it a temporary cave
or ancient remains?
It was an abandoned mine
turned into a tourist attraction.
This mission is a cave adventure.
You'll get a hint about the missing toys.
You see Gwangmyeong cave here.
I never knew there was such a thing.
You must finish the missions fast.
The fastest team to exit
this cave is the first winner.
Let's finish it fast!
Now, everyone can go in together.
[Secret cave adventure, start!]
There's already a cool
breeze coming out.
Wow, it's really breezy.
- It's kind of cold!
- It's like the air conditioner.
[The secret cave, go to R1!]
There's something over there...
There is?
- There's something?
- It's a die!
[We saw it, too.]
- It's better to be there first.
Seo Jang Hun would be
too tall for this cave!
[What are these objects for...?]
What is this?
The secret cave, first game is...
'Face Off.'
- You turn off... your face?
- Change your face.
This is all by luck.
First, I will pick a
number between 1-30.
I like this!
I'll explain with an example.
Let's say I pick the number eight.
A team member will roll the die.
If Jae Suk rolls a three
Jong Kook rolls a four
and Gary rolls a two.
Then, one member will
come up at a time
spin the knob as many times
as the number they rolled.
Then when the total comes to eight
the member who's up there
will get a cream pie on the face.
- Let's do it!
- This is fun!
It's similar to Russian roulette.
Since there are 1st, 2nd, 3rd places
you will see that there are
three paths.
You can choose which way
to go based on the order.
It's all luck!
This is good.
Which one is the good path?
Choose your runner up.
We choose Suk Jin.
I will go.
- We will choose...
- I'll go first.
Ji Hyo?
[That's too much of a ladies first...]
Gary or Ha Ha should go!
Song Ji Hyo!
- You're too harsh!
- She's lucky, that's why.
You didn't even hesitate!
We're trying to overpower
them on our first try.
The first set, Blank-Jisean.
Only we can see this.
I think Gary's trying to peek!
You've seen the number, right?
- I will throw it.
- Oh, you're throwing it?
It's better for them to throw it.
- Three!
- Three's not bad.
- A small number can be good.
- Five!
- It's one!
- That's good.
Please get six.
Three's a good number.
I hope Sean gets hit on the first try.
For everyone's laughter?
[The cream pie is ready.]
We will start.
Ready set...
[Face Off, round one start.]
I doubt the penalty number is one.
[Sean survives his first turn.]
[Followed by Big Nose's turn.]
Ji Suk Jin!
- Are you going to keep the glasses?
- You should take them off.
- He has no lenses.
- I don't have any.
But I still want to see.
I'm too ugly to take them off.
He's the ugliest one on our team.
He's third place.
Don't lie!
You are...
It's Suk Jin.
We didn't say that out loud.
He's third place.
Third place in our team.
Let's go.
One...
It's okay, just spin it.
- You're still okay.
- You're fine!
It won't knock out his teeth, right?
Three.
My heart's racing.
Don't say stuff like that!
What if his teeth actually fall out?
Then, we would be doing
the next game on TV.
I think it's definitely under ten.
If I just get this
one, would it be four?
It could be.
Be ready, just in case.
[Big Nose is safe.]
Wow, this is really nerve racking.
- Ji Hyo.
- This is really scary.
I think Ji Hyo will survive.
- She'll pass.
- She's lucky.
Let's count from number five.
Five, six, and seven.
- Five.
- Blank Ji, spin it.
Five.
Why am I nervous?
Spin it.
I'll be surprised if she can avoid it.
- I don't think it's you, Ji Hyo.
- Six!
Spin it, Ji Hyo!
It won't be you!
[The penalty number is six]
[Shocked]
[The Goddess of fortune
couldn't avoid it.]
[Big Nose beat the Goddess of fortune!]
[Blank Ji is ousted early!]
Are you okay?
- You were lucky!
- Fortune smiles on me!
First romantic moment in
a long time?
Blow your nose.
Blow your nose, too!
He doesn't miss his chance.
When did you come near Ji Hyo?
I've prepared wet wipes for you.
[The first runner Blank Ji drops out.]
[The first penalty number is six.]
One person is dropped,
who will play this time?
Song Ji Hyo again.
[Seriously, these men...]
I'll enter it.
[Pink Team's second runner is Gary.]
It's Gae-Jisean, this time.
It was Blank-Jisean before.
[The first letter of my name
always sounds like a dog.]
With Gae-Jisean...
[The number is decided.]
It's good to pick a small number.
The number is picked.
One, one!
[Oh no, Big-nose rolls a five.]
Small numbers are better.
[Sean rolls a one again.]
He's cheering in old fashioned way.
[It's similar to Hiddink's
famous 'upper cut' ceremony.]
[It's feels like we'll
make it to semi-finals.]
[Gary quickly rolls a one.]
It's going to be me.
If I can survive here,
I have great luck.
Five, one, one means...
I hope it's one.
As soon as he turns...
Why are you so mean to me, friend?
You know how it is now.
I don't want to worry too much.
It won't be one.
1 is fine.
[Sean's first turn, safe.]
Please count from two.
- Relax.
- Don't worry.
Two!
[Gary passes his first turn safely.]
I'll spin it without stopping.
Three, four..
five, six, seven!
- You should have opened your eyes.
- It hurts if the cream gets in.
[Big-nose puts eye health
over his image.]
- Eight, eight.
- Eight, lucky!
It feels weird.
Your number is eight.
Shoot it!
Your face is white.
[Sean passes his second turn safely.]
What's with 'shoot it'?
They used to say it for
lottery tickets.
What's wrong with that?
Get ready... and shoot it!
Shoot it, Gary!
- Nine!
- It's nine.
- Close your eyes!
- Just do it!
It'll hurt your eyes.
[It won't be Gary, will it?]
[Yes, it is.]
[Nine is the penalty number.]
[It sounded like a flyswatter.]
Why me?
Fortune favors me!
[Big-nose spins it five
times but survives.]
We're unlucky today!
Nothing works for us!
By the way, it sounded really nice!
It was like a drum!
[Face Off, second round.]
[Even the last runner Ha Ha dropped
out early during the third round.]
We're already done.
Only we can see the hint.
- We should have less numbers.
[Blue Team vs. Green Team]
15?
There are up to 20.
[They pick the number.]
There's a lot of whipped cream.
So, it comes a bit slow.
Just wait and feel it yourself.
Jong Kook doesn't like whipped cream.
Use some dung instead.
[It's so funny!]
[You must be enjoying
your life too much.]
- Follow me.
- Record this!
Gwon Yeol, record this!
Watch out!
It's not a good place to get beat up.
We're in a cave!
We want to participate in the game.
It's so cold.
Roll the die!
[The Face Off, fourth round]
What's with the knee kick?
[Big-nose rolls a six.]
We'll win!
Roll a one!
[Sean rolls a five.]
It's good!
It's almost the same!
[It's nip and tuck.]
Go ahead.
- You know it's a competition.
- Yes, I know it's a competition.
[Will his good luck continue?]
- Is it six?
- Turn it slowly.
One!
Two!
Only if I can pass this turn...
For some reason, I think it's three.
Three!
Please, put your face forward.
I guess I'm going to get the cream?
[Why else would he wants to see
his face closely all of a sudden?]
Not even before I start,
he tells me now.
- Is it fourth time?
- Yes, it's fourth time.
[Will Big-nose drop out like this?]
Hold it out!
Just two more spins!
[Five!]
- It's the last spin.
One more spin, and his turn is over.
[We survived!]
[Lucky-nose!]
Today must be your lucky day!
[Sean will drop out if the
number is between 7 to 11.]
Seven!
Eight!
Three more spins!
From nine to eleven?
Nine!
Just two more spins!
Please!
Ten!
[It reaches the halfway point.]
You're still alive!
Wait!
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo, I might be the one!
The last spin...
[Head shot]
[The penalty number is 11.]
[Joy!]
[Disappointed!]
[It's stuck.]
[It's fun to watch it.]
[Jinusean or broken lotion?]
Aren't you a little too happy?
So funny!
I've never seen him like this before.
Oh no!
[The Face Off Game, fourth round]
[Sean drops out.]
[The penalty number of
the fourth round is 11.]
What's with my luck today?
It's incredible!
We couldn't win over him.
[This is the power of Lucky-nose!]
[His beginnings will seem humble...]
[the result was so prosperous.]
[He crushes the
Goddess of fortune, Ji Hyo.]
[He also defeats human percussion, Gary.]
[When Lucky-nose spins...]
[all goes well.]
[When Lucky-nose spins]
[they win every battle.]
[Lucky-nose defeats
Jinu during the fifth round.]
[Am I the only one left?]
The next runner is Kim Jong Kook!
I'll have to play this game any way!
We'll make your face greasy!
I'll give you some oil on your skin.
[Will Mr. Capable win?]
[or will Lucky-nose win?]
[Will Lucky-nose be able
to overpower Mr. Capable?]
[Jong Kook is safe.]
Let's see if I can
defeat Mr. Capable?
- Four, five!
[The victory is mine!]
[Lucky-nose is safe.]
This isn't normal.
I need to buy a lottery ticket.
[Kkuk's second turn.]
[Jong Kook is safe again.]
[Mr. Capable isn't an easy opponent.]
[Free from all thoughts and ideas.]
If he passes it again, it's a miracle.
[After one more spin,
it's Jong Kook's turn.]
Nine!
[Goodbye, Lucky-nose!]
- His luck ended!
[We won!]
[A sad ending.
Mr. Capable rains on Suk Jin's parade.]
[Celebrating in 90's style.]
You're rude even at playing games?
What did I do?
Seriously, didn't you want to
see me win all the way?
You rude bastard!
He wanted to win today.
He's upset.
Look how red his face turned.
Who will come out now?
There are two unlucky
people on that team.
The two unluckiest people
in the whole world.
Out of the two...
It doesn't matter.
- You go, Jae Suk.
- Should I?
- I will win.
- Suk Jin doesn't seem to care.
I missed the opportunity
to win all the rounds.
[The penalty number is decided.]
One!
[Jong Kook rolls a six.]
[We'll win.]
- What if Jae Suk gets six, too?
We won, right?
Jong Kook will win
at picking the order.
Put lots of cream!
[They think they'll win.]
- Four!
- It's not very safe.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Jong Kook can decide
who will go first.]
It's difficult to decide.
It's very confusing.
It'll take less than two rounds.
My face smells like a cake.
I'm smelling it for
more than 20 minutes.
It smells like cake.
You will collect flies
when you go outside.
It feels like my birthday.
Isn't it like a bakery here?
It's my birthday.
Did you decide?
I'll go first!
[He rolled a six, but
he wants to go first?]
He's going first?
Stop putting it more!
- Stop it!
- Okay!
What are you doing?
You're wasting it!
It's all for you.
It's not a waste.
How can it be a waste?
Give him plenty of it, Jae Suk.
[Will we be able to see Jong Kook's
face covered in whipped cream?]
I think it'll be you, If he doesn't
get the penalty this time.
One!
Wait, wait!
Two!
Three!
Oh my god!
Please!
[Three more spins and
Jong Kook's turn will be over.]
I'm almost crying.
No, I'm crying.
Jong Kook!
Just deal with the pain.
[Four]
- Was it five or four?
- Four.
Two more spins left!
- I'm about to cry.
- Calm down, lucky guy!
Five, six!
It's safe again!
Please, please.
[One more spin, and
Jong Kook's turn will be over.]
This is the last spin!
Relax.
- Please, be six.
[Jong Kook's destiny will be?]
[Jong Kook's first turn is safe.]
[Dazed]
Give us some cameras.
Let us film it.
We have nothing to do.
[We want to work, too.]
He went first.
How did he know?
- Does he see something?
- He's Mr. Capable.
I can't win against Jong Kook.
You have to spin four times.
If he can pass it over...
[The cream drips.]
Wait, it's been here for a while.
Then it'll be me.
Aren't you too kind?
It's all for you.
[What Jae Suk said earlier
comes back to haunt him.]
- Lots and lots.
- Jinu is funny.
Four spins, right?
Seven, eight, nine, ten!
Let's count it down.
Seven!
Three more spins!
Eight!
I think it's eight!
[Two more spins and
Jae Suk's turn will be over.]
Are you going to keep your
eyes open?
Nine!
One more spin!
[It's almost there...]
[The penalty number is between 1 to 20.]
[It's getting dangerous for Jong Kook.]
What should I do?
I'm ruined!
Please, please, please, please.
Ten!
- Ruined!
- Ten!
- Please save me once.
- Are you talking to the whipped cream?
To whipped cream.
I hope it saves me.
[Kkuk is nervous, too.]
- Please, please!
Please save me once!
[The penalty number is 11.]
[He fails communicating
with the whipped cream.]
[Mr. Capable makes it to the finals.]
[Again, the 90's ceremony]
[The 7th round's penalty number is 10.]
We can only beat him
with these kinds of games.
[What will be the penalty
number for the last round?]
- You should have thrown like me.
- Three is okay.
- Throw it with more power.
- But this will make them more nervous.
They will have to take
turns a few times.
[Kwang Soo wins the
rock, paper, scissors.]
Do want you don't want to.
You're pretty unlucky.
- I want to go later.
- Then do it first.
- I'll go first.
- Your hunch is worth crap.
What do you mean crap?
Are you cheering for me or what?
- Let's go!
- I'll do it now!
I'll count one, two, three.
- Three!
- The final match!
One!
- Two!
- Look at his eyes!
[What is he doing?]
[Kwang Soo safely
passes his first turn.]
Do we need to see that again?
Mr. Capable!
- Two spins, right?
- Two spins.
I hope it ends here.
Hit him this time.
- Four.
- It won't hit him.
[Will Mr. Capable be safe again?]
[Jong Kook safely
passes his first turn.]
[He survives.]
Kwang Soo, it's okay.
Your Eyes.
Six!
He looks like a sly fox.
[He starts moving his eyebrows again.]
Seven.
I think until eight is safe.
It's okay.
Until eight is safe.
[It's not okay.]
[High Five!]
[Hooray! We won!]
[The penalty number is eight.]
[A pure white, Lee Kwang Soo.]
It was a hard slap, this time.
You look like a statue of Agrippa.
Why does his face look like...
His face looks like the one...
- from the movie Saw.
- The one in Ju-on, the grudge.
He should have followed
Kwang Soo's hunch.
You didn't let me do
what I wanted to do.
I wanted to go later.
Didn't I say that I want to go later?
- Calm down.
- But he said my hunch is crap!
Calm down, calm down.
Why am I a crap?
I have money.
- Why is my hunch crap?
- I'm sorry.
I think you're very upset.
Why don't you go home?
We'll win this race and call you.
- I think you're too upset.
- No, I'm not.
Go take some rest.
You shouldn't film when you're upset.
No, I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Green Team is the first winner.
You're second, and you're third.
There are three paths to R2.
We'll follow Mr. Capable's decision.
Don't do that.
There's a straight path...
These two men are like
Jong Kook's servants.
- No, we're not servants.
- Slaves!
That path is too shiny.
I don't think it's the right one.
- That might be the worst path.
- Right? This one, too...
If you can't decide, let us go first.
[Let us play the game, too.]
Let's pick the dark path.
- Go straight?
- We'll go straight in the middle!
We'll pick the one in the middle.
- What's second team's decision?
- Where do you want to go, Kwang Soo?
- Let's pick the last one.
- Then let's pick the other one.
[Blue Team picks the shiny path.]
[Pink Team gets the dark path.]
[Go to the R2!]
I have no problem running!
Run!
Think of it as a marathon!
Are we going to the same spot?
What is this?
Is this a mission or what?
- Watch your head!
- We need to get to R2 first.
- We just need to get there first.
- That's right.
Where is it?
Are we going to run without cameras?
Run with your cameras!
- It's not the right way.
- It's a dead end.
I see.
It's like a maze.
That one's a dead end, too?
Then let's go this way.
Let's go that way.
It's like an underworld.
We can use underground passages?
- Where are you going?
- I can hear the Pink Team.
- They're coming!
- Ji Hyo has a hunch.
[Green Team keeps running straight.]
Maybe it's not here.
Should we go to the stairs?
- I don't think we should go down!
- Let's go down!
- Then we can't go on the elevator.
- This is amazing!
This is fascinating!
Be careful.
It's a bit slippery.
Do you think it's here, Ji Hyo?
- Are we going up again?
- I'll try this way, you try that way.
- It's here, come over here!
- Be quiet, Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo is a genius!
- It's here!
[Pink Team arrives at R2.]
- Is it here?
- You're amazing, Ji Hyo!
It was the right way.
Is this R2?
We just followed Ji Hyo.
The second game is
'The Cave Water park.'
You will play jump rope now.
Three of you will stand in a row.
The two people at the
end will turn the rope.
And three of you will jump together.
The person in the middle will have
a glass of water on their head.
You will have to jump 15 times.
Do you see the line?
You'll pass, if the water
is higher than this line.
- Is it down there?
- Come!
We'll turn the rope?
[Green Team finally arrives at R2.]
It's right here.
[We shouldn't have picked
the road in the middle.]
[Long time no see, Peaceful Gary.]
Ready, set, go!
[Water gets all over his face.]
- They will fail.
[That looks cold.]
Jump slowly.
[Peaceful Gary turns to scowling Gary.]
Nine, ten, eleven!
Please do it again.
[They can try three times,
if the water is left.]
- How many jumps?
- 15 jumps.
[They don't have enough water.]
Try next time.
[Kkuk coach's order]
- Ready!
- Set...
- Wait, we'll start when...
- Starve!
- Wait!
- Don't say 'start'!
- I said 'starve.'
Start!
It's a fail.
[Luckily, they still have water.]
- Wait.
[They have two chances.]
[Grasshopper is extremely focused.]
[The three of them are
in perfect harmony.]
[They jumped more than 10 times...]
[All of a sudden, a hat is in the way!]
[They fail at the 14th jump.]
[Out of all times, why now....]
[I want to blame him...]
- There's no water.
- Really?
[Even though they have jumped
15 times, it's a fail.]
Green Team, start!
[He bows with water.]
Good riddance!
Again.
[Their second try]
- Ready.
Start!
Jinu is really bad at jump rope!
Their teamwork is getting worse!
Aren't you getting frustrated?
Why aren't you yelling?
Until when are you going
to be nice to each other?
[Green Team's last attempt.]
One, two, three, four...
[Serious look]
- five, six, seven...
It's very close!
[They jump in perfect harmony.]
[The water stays the same.]
[Three more jumps...]
It's dangerous!
[Will Green Team succeed again?]
[Just one last jump!]
[They succeed at jumping 15 times!]
[If the water is higher than the line...]
- I think it's enough.
[Green Team succeeds easily.]
[The 90's stars win again.]
Okay, okay!
What do you need to practice
to be good at this?
[We're surprised, too.]
- See you later!
- Take your time!
[Green Team needs
to escape the cave.]
[The rest of them are fighting
for second place.]
- Good!
- Five.
[Good to be wet...]
Six, seven!
Is the water enough?
[It's like taking a shower.]
- It's over.
[Blue Team's attempt.]
- Start!
[The water park is having a festival.]
I can't see anything.
Start!
One!
Why is Jae Suk wearing sunglasses?
I can't see anything.
- Over there!
- Here?
- Oh, it's here!
- It's the end of the game!
- We won!
- We're the first winners!
[They have escaped.]
Now, we'll be sure of the place.
The hint we'll get
this time is important.
[Green Team gets the best hint.]
[Yongin City, Gyeonggi province.]
Oh, it's the place.
- It's where it is.
- Yes, it's the place.
[The second team to escape is...]
[Pink Team.]
[They walk out all wet.]
It's too bright!
It's been a while.
[Screaming and laughter]
[Dating]
[Children's day]
[Yongin, Gyeonggi]
[South Korea]
[Family Month]
[A museum in Gyeonggi Province]
- They're acupressure mats!
Oh no!
- I hate it!
- Why?
I want to burn all these mats!
Who stole all the toys?
Turn yourself in,
if one of you stole them!
I won't let you escape!
Are we going to play with
our bare feet?
This is the last mission
and it's simple.
Pick a court, starting
with the first winner.
Then play dodgeball.
The team in the middle will
be attacked by both teams.
Therefore, the team in the
middle has a disadvantage.
Pick a court for your team.
The closest one.
- The one with better lighting.
- We'll be here.
The first team to fail
will be in third place.
It'll be more fun to be in the middle.
We should pick the middle?
Do you think we're that stupid?
Don't you want revenge?
You can only attack them from here.
We couldn't take revenge
for the past five years.
You can directly attack
them from the middle court.
I see.
Then take the middle court.
- I mean, you can take...
[His attempt fails.]
We don't have time to waste.
Oh my god!
It's been a while.
What is this?
This is the acupressure mat!
- It hurts!
- Go to the back!
You're not going to attack us, right?
Think it over, you shouldn't
attack us!
You betrayed me.
Today is the day!
Just this once, if you...
- Be...
- tray...
- ers!
- Cross!
You're not going to betray us.
Are you?
Trust me this time!
- I promised you!
[I believe in you...]
It hit him!
[Ha Ha is ousted.]
Why did you throw it at him?
You know, it was a pass.
[That was a pass?]
[The allied teams are about to break.]
Gary, they did it on purpose!
We were going to attack them,
but you're not helping.
I didn't mean it.
[Ha Ha is going to attack them.]
We can't fight against each other!
We have nothing to lose!
Green Team will
be happy to see this!
Wake up, Ji Hyo!
You'll be ousted if we
just throw it at you!
- We're really sorry.
- I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'll show you.
[They change their target.]
[Their target is Green Team.]
We have nothing to lose!
Dong Hun, take this!
- Hey, hey!
[Startled]
Don't do that.
I'll run to that side and...
I can attack you right away!
I'm sorry.
- Just stay there!
- We should attack them!
Jinu!
I feel sorry for him.
I can't attack him.
- Are you okay?
- Try holding it out!
- Finish him!
[Oh no!]
Looking at him hurts me!
Don't be weak!
- Suk Jin is weaker than him.
- Gary!
Finish him, finish him!
[He catches the ball and
suddenly becomes arrogant.]
- I told you to finish him!
- Can you hit me if I walk like this?
The thing you see at a theme park.
It's tempting.
Can you actually hit me?
- Hit me.
- But you'll move backwards.
[He goes closer to him.]
- You pay more for closer targets.
[It hits the pit of his stomach.]
[Suk Jin is ousted.]
- You told me to hit you.
- It's precise.
[Big-nose's luck is blocked
by Mr. Capable today.]
[Wait and see, Mr. Capable.]
You were saying
that you'll hit Gary before.
I was going to trick them.
- I can't fully trust you.
- Pass it to me, I'll oust them.
Stay over there.
Corner them.
It'll be a triangle pass.
- It hurts.
- I think he's acting.
[Hollywood action]
It's so hard to attack him.
[At that moment...]
[I am here.]
[Let me handle this!]
[I... trust you.]
Quickly!
[Big-nose's only target.]
[It's for you, Mr. Capable!]
[It hits the ground.]
He can't hit him very near.
[It doesn't work the way I want.]
He sucks!
[Pink Team continues to attack.]
Run!
You can't stop!
Suk Jin!
[Jinu tries stealing
the ball but fails.]
Help us from outside.
I didn't get ousted on purpose.
- Kwang Soo!
[Suk Jin passes to Kwang Soo.]
What are you doing?
[It's a powerful shot.]
- Wait a minute!
- I was passing it to Suk Jin.
- Did you really pass it to Suk Jin?
- Gary cursed at me!
When did I?
Gary!
Gary, wait!
- It's upsetting!
- It's a war now!
[Kwang Soo's pass]
[Ha Ha intercepted.]
- What are you doing, Suk Jin?
[Ha Ha hits immediately.]
[Sean is ousted.]
- This is getting bad.
Jong Kook is the only one left.
[Kwang Soo stands behind Jae Suk.]
- You shouldn't be there.
I'll pass now!
[Jinu attacks instead of passing.]
[It touches the ground first.]
Did you get hit?
- I was hit.
- Didn't it hit the ground?
You didn't get hit!
[It's the only way to
escape from this mat.]
I got really hit.
Check the camera,
I got hit.
- You weren't hit.
- I was actually hit.
- It hit the ground first.
[Jae Suk fails at escaping.]
[Gary is ousted.]
- Hit him, oust him!
[Hit me!]
It's done.
What's wrong with him?
- It hurts for me, too!
- Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Don't try catching the ball, Ji Hyo!
[Kwang Soo passes it to Big-nose.]
[Again, his target is Mr. Capable.]
[Goodbye, Kim Jong Kook!]
[Will this time be...?]
[Jong Kook is ousted.]
Suk Jin ousted him!
Suk Jin performed a fiery shot!
Jong Kook grabbed it,
but he couldn't endure it.
So, he dropped it.
[In Giraffe's eyes...]
[Big-nose was Dodgeball King, Tonki.]
Please help us.
We might be able to win.
- Let's win.
- You can't do that!
[Kwang Soo hides behind Ji Hyo.]
What are you doing?
Let go!
Let go of me!
Ji Hyo, you need to hide!
- Kwang Soo!
- Move aside!
Step on Kwang Soo's feet.
[I'm sorry, Ji Hyo!]
- Wait, wait!
One more time, Ji Hyo!
Don't do that!
[Giraffe's crisis!]
Don't grab me!
[He stays closer to Ji Hyo
as it gets dangerous for him.]
Turn your back!
Kwang Soo, you can survive!
[What are you two doing?]
[At that moment!]
[Ji Hyo rolls away.]
Ji Hyo, move!
[Where are you going, Ji Hyo?]
[I'm sorry, Kwang Soo!]
[Kwang Soo is defenseless.]
[Oh, no!]
[Kwang Soo is ousted!]
- Didn't it hit the ground?
- No, it hit you.
- We're the winner!
- Good job!
[Ji Hyo's last roll was fantastic!]
My feet are really hurting.
What are you doing?
- What were you doing?
[Don't get hurt, Lucky-nose.]
- I'm sure.
- Yongin.
Ji Hyo said the greatest
gift for the children
is to going to an amusement park.
I thought that's possible.
- As soon as I saw 'season pass.'
- Should we go there?
Yes. It's the only place.
It's here.
What was the last hint?
- It was 'parade.'
- Then it is for sure.
- The second hint was dating.
- Yes.
The last one was parade.
It's clear.
The destination...
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Let's go!
[The three teams are going
to their destination.]
[Will they be able to get
to the final destination?]
['E' amusement park in Yongin.]
[This is the final site
of today's race.]
[A giant robot that swallowed
all the toys is here.]
[In front of the robot...]
[A time bomb?]
[At that time...]
Look at the lighting.
It's for the filming.
It's right there.
We're here.
- We're here.
- We just need to find the villain.
Ji Hyo, we just need to win this race.
[Where are they heading?]
[A car arrives.]
[Which team will it be?]
It's right here.
[Blue Team arrives
at the right spot.]
[As sure as they were,
they arrive at the right place.]
It's here.
We must enter here.
It's the place for the tulip festival.
[What will be the final mission?]
- What's that?
- It's a bomb!
The toys!
Give us the toys!
The bad toy collector
brainwashed the robot.
And the robot swallowed
all the toys.
As you can see, a bomb
is installed here.
You'll see five colors inside
the bomb.
You need to cut the wires in order
and there are the hints for that.
Find the scrolls with hints
and deduce the order.
If you cut the wires in order
the timer will be stopped
and you'll be the winner.
You have only one chance.
Start searching,
the timer will start now.
- Let's try the garden.
- The time is ticking!
- Let's go quickly.
- Let's check the garden first!
Suk Jin!
- Huh?
- Did you find one?
[Jae Suk finds a scroll.]
White one is close to red one
but far from green one.
It's either white first and red or...
- Jae Suk!
- Look at this!
White one is before red one.
- So, white wire first.
- Yes.
Here's another one.
- I found one.
- What is it?
Here's another one!
The first one is green.
- It's very important.
- It is important!
It starts with the green wire.
[Green Team is one step behind!]
[Right behind them is Pink Team.]
[Both teams guessed the right place.]
Are we in a hurry?
Are we supposed to find
something here?
Hurry up!
You're at the right place.
The first team arrived
and time is running.
There are wires inside the bomb.
You'll have to find scrolls
in the park to cut the wires by order.
Hurry up and find them!
- What do you want us to find?
- Scrolls!
[He doesn't know what's going on.]
Scrolls?
Gary, find them quickly!
- I found one!
- It's here!
[All the toys will be gone.]
[Find as many hints as possible
and cut the wires in order.]
- What should I find?
- I found one!
- Scrolls?
- Here's another one!
- Yes, that's right.
Found one...
Yellow one is not the last one.
White one is next to yellow one.
White one... I found one!
Next to red and green...
- Let's meet for a second!
- Okay, Ji Hyo!
It starts with green one.
Green wire is the first one.
Green...
something and red.
Yellow one is not the last one.
Yellow wire is not the last one.
Wait, what colors are there?
- It starts with green.
- What colors are there?
White, blue, green.
White one is the fourth.
White one and red one are
close to each other.
There's something in
between blue and white.
- I think I know.
- What is it?
I know the order.
Green one first.
We don't know what's
the second and third.
There's yellow.
In between white and blue...
there's something.
I think it's yellow.
- So the first one is white?
- No, it's green.
The second one is blue.
And the the third one is yellow,
then white and red.
There are two colors in
between white and green.
Two colors...
It's in this order.
Let's go!
Run!
Hurry up!
Let's go!
Suk Jin!
- Let's go!
- We need to go!
Let's find one more and go!
We need to go!
- Let's go!
- Sean is running!
- Hurry up, run!
- It's the answer!
[Blue Team and Pink Team
arrive at the same time.]
- In between the white and blue...
- What was the first one?
It's the green wire.
Cut it.
The first one is green.
There's something in between...
- Green wire, first.
- Green and yellow.
- Yellow.
In between the white and blue...
It's yellow!
- Yellow?
- Yellow.
No, it's blue... wait!
- Wait!
- We guessed it all!
- I found another one on the way.
- Okay.
- Red one and blue one are far?
- Green and yellow.
[Time is running.]
- Green and then yellow.
- Red!
White!
- White!
- The last one!
Red first!
Okay, we're done!
[Pink Team finishes cutting.]
[Was that the right order?]
[The timer didn't stop.]
- It was the wrong answer?
- Ha Ha!
[It's good news
for the other teams.]
[The bad spirit gets stronger.]
There's something between
the white one and blue one.
Yellow one is the third.
- Is that the one?
- This one.
- And the next one is?
- And?
- This one.
- Then this one.
- Okay!
[Green - blue - yellow - white - red]
[Blue Team cut the wires.]
[Will they be able to stop
the timer this time?]
Okay, it's the right order.
[It stopped.]
[Blue Team wins the final game!]
[Green Team is one
step behind Blue Team.]
- We did it!
- The weak team did it!
- It's unbelievable!
- We did it in ten minutes!
[The toys that the robot swallowed...]
[went back to their places.]
[They foiled the bad toy
collector's evil scheme]
[and return the world
of hopes and dreams.]
The fools won the race.
We fools won the race!
- We fools really won it!
- With this stupid hat.
You can donate 4 million Won
worth of toys.
- That's really nice!
- Poor Sean.
- It's fine.
- Can I be in that team?
- Come over here.
- You should wear this hat.
[He changes his team
at the last minute.]
Donate this under Sean's name.
- What are you talking about?
- You're a donation angel.
He's a donation angel,
I'm a delightful angel.
Put my name, too.
Then Sean and Suk Jin's
names will be used.
- Really these two?
- It's weird!
Instead of Sean and Jinu,
it'll be Sean and Suk Jin.
[Thank you for Jinusean,
forever hip hop warriors!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Is there anyone?
[A top actress is kidnapped!]
[The best detective's psychological
warfare in 2015 starts!]
You're not a client but a detective?
[Do not trust each other!]
[There's someone suspicious among us!]
[A battle of wits between
Running Man members.]
I think it's the hardest game
in Running Man history.
[You'll regret if you think of
this as just another game.]
[Kidnapping case of an actress]
[The Secret of a Fake Detective]