Running Man
Episode 235
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle]
[What are you making?]
It's a combination of an Italian
and a Korean dish.
Cheese wheat flake noodles
in curry kimchi stew.
The cheese is inside the dough.
I need to knead this dough.
If this dough fails,
everything will be ruined.
I need to let out all the
air inside the dough.
I tasted it earlier and it's fantastic!
The dough is great and
I think my team can win this battle.
If we lose with this dough
then it's all Shoo's fault.
[Best dish for 2015 New Year's Day.]
[The best dish made with Kimchi.]
[Are you ready to taste it?]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle]
[The Running Man members
are all scattered.]
[Thailand]
['Up and down' team,
Gary and Sung Ryung.]
[Eat the top three street
foods of Khaosan Road.]
They're bean sprouts.
[Which Thai dish
will be infused with Kimchi?]
Will it be good with white Kimchi?
[Bangkok, Thailand]
[Bulkyo, Korea]
[This mudflat is the largest
in Running Man history.]
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo's mission
is to dig out 1,000 cockles.]
[A battle to acquire
cockles in Bulkyo.]
[The combination of cockles and Kimchi.]
[What will be their hidden dish?]
[Bulkyo]
[Jungsun]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon.]
[Jungsun, Kangwon Province]
[Learning the secret recipe from
the great Jang Geum of Jungsun.]
I can tell you've never done this before.
Han Ga In does all the work.
[A Young Master from Seoul, Jung Hoon...]
[who can't even peel potatoes.]
Ga In, you're doing a lot of work.
I can tell.
[Will he be able to show his cooking skills?]
[The great Jang Geum of Jungsun's
buckwheat porridge soup recipe.]
You can use it if you want.
[Add in a little bit of MSG,
if it doesn't taste very good.]
[How will it change
when they add Kimchi?]
[Jungsun]
[Taean]
[Off the coast of Taean]
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun fish for
small octopus.]
[A fisherman's daughter?
Yoo Sun's amazing skill.]
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun's new menu...]
[small octopus Kimchi something?]
[Taean]
[Jeju Island]
I hope you believe in me.
[Troublesome date in Jeju Island,
Ha Ha and Shoo.]
[Winter carrots, Jeju black pig meat,
and Kimchi...]
[A recipe made with love.]
[Jeju Island]
[Hong Kong]
[The city of fashion, city of taste.]
[In Hong Kong,
the world's greatest food heaven.]
[Fei who's good at cooking and
Prince of Asia, Lee Kwang Soo have met.]
[Breakfast in Hong Kong.]
[Find a dish that
best fits with Kimchi!]
[A dish that no one has
eaten before.]
[What will be Kwang Soo and
Fei's Korean-Chinese fusion food?]
[Hong Kong]
[Jeju Island]
[On a blue night of Jeju Island]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon
went fishing for cuttlefish.]
[The struggle to get the cutlass fish.]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon succeed
in getting the cutlass fish?]
[Getting the best ingredients
by land, sea and air...]
[what will be the results?]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle]
[In a moment, the battle will begin.]
[A train of events!]
[Cooking is a battle!]
[Combine Kimchi and their special recipe.]
[What synergy effect will they create?]
[In a moment, the battle will begin.]
[Khaosan Road,
Bangkok, Thailand.]
[Eat the top three street
foods of Bangkok.]
[The have successfully eaten two.]
- Kwetiau Kai.
Let's ask her.
I have a question about Itim Kati.
Oh, it's a coconut?
Juice or food?
Is it juice or something else?
[She realizes she spoke in Korean.]
You were speaking in English, then...
Is it juice or something else?
- He said coconut, so I was wondering...
- Juice or tea?
Is it juice or something else?
They don't understand
when we try to speak in Thai.
Speaking in English is one thing,
but I had to speak in Thai...
My pronunciation wasn't good.
It was very difficult.
- I found it!
- Where is it?
Coconut ice cream?
They have portable carts.
Itim Kati!
Sawadikap! (Hello.)
Itim Kati?
Itim Kati! Okay!
One Itim Kati, please.
[Itim Kati- Coconut topped
with ice cream.]
[A harmony of a soft coconut
and cold ice cream.]
They scoop the coconut out.
I don't know if this will match
with the Kimchi flavor.
For dessert!
It will be perfect with a spicy dish.
Like steamed egg
for spicy chicken feet.
- Oh, that kind of combination?
- Yes.
It's really good!
Other ladies use napkins to
wipe their mouths
but she just uses her sleeve.
I like street food.
I think it's romantic.
It's the food that people
enjoy in the country.
I think I enjoyed it more
than eating at a famous restaurant.
Mission completed.
- I'm still hungry.
- Then should we try another mission?
[What will be their next mission?]
[Thailand]
[Hong Kong]
[Kwang Soo and Fei are greeted with special
dishes from the best chef in Hong Kong.]
[The best chef's secret recipe
will be handed down.]
[Paul Lui]
[Chef of 'R' Hotel in Hong Kong.]
[Michelin starred chef.]
[Guangdong culinary artist.]
- We'll start eating.
- Sure. go ahead.
[Tasting the food that the Chef made.]
[Celestial taste.]
- Thank you.
[Steamed Crab with Egg Whites
and Hua Diao Wine.]
- This is har gow (shrimp dim sum).
- Har gow?
I think we can put Kimchi
in the filling.
I think it'll be good.
I think we should focus on dim sum.
We can take advantage of the filling.
This is really delicious!
[Xian shui jiao]
(Sweet rice dumplings)
Hong Kong style cuisine is
not really spicy.
I wasn't sure if we could
combine a dish with Kimchi.
When I tasted the dim sum,
it seemed like a good idea.
- Is that wheat flour?
- That's sweet rice flour.
[Recipe- Mix sweet rice flour
and wheat flour for dough.]
Make dumplings with pork fillings.
Deep fry in hot oil.
- Isn't it hot?
- It's little hot but not too much.
[The Chef teaches Fei in Cantonese.]
Fei did all the talking in Cantonese.
I think she was jealous
about me and the Chef.
[It's done if the dim sum floats.]
Let's check how it tastes.
[It's time to taste it.]
- Please tell us if we passed.
It's really good!
[They successfully learn
the secret recipe.]
[How will the combination of Kimchi
and dim sum taste?]
[Hong Kong]
[Jungsun]
- Jung Hoon.
- Yes.
Look for mushrooms carefully.
Jae Suk, I don't know what
it looks like.
I've seen on TV but I've
never gotten any mushrooms.
I've never done this either.
You have to gather 1kg of
wild mushrooms from now on.
You will get the invitation for the cooking
battle when the mission is completed.
[They didn't know any better
at the moment...]
[Just how horrible the mushroom
expedition would be...]
[The mountain gets more and more stiff.]
[Climbs one after another.]
Finding mushroom is
extremely difficult.
[He sweats in the middle of winter.]
[30 minutes later]
- Are we almost there yet?
- It's a real expedition.
[The expedition never ends...]
I think there's a mushroom store
in the middle of this mountain.
- Did you say there's a mushroom store?
- No.
[All we hear is heavy breathing.]
- Wait for a moment.
- What's wrong?
The VJ can't keep up with you guys.
- Are you okay?
[Not at all.]
Why did you drink last night?
[Where in the world are the mushrooms?]
- Gwon Yeol.
- Yes.
- Are you giving up on recording?
- No way.
What do you mean 'no way'?
You were in front of me.
Why are you behind us?
[Covered in sweat.]
This is unexpected.
I would have worn proper gear had I known.
[We keep the mission in secret.]
[Yeon Jung Hoon,
Member of the Mushroom expedition.]
It was really tiring.
It felt like an army's winter camp.
I thought the mushrooms were
near at first.
The mountain wasn't too bad at first.
I think they couldn't record much.
Everyone was getting tired.
The producers were having the worst
time in Running Man history.
We can't even air it on the show.
Nobody recorded us.
We'll be in and out of the mountain
but we don't have the mid-process.
The producers were too tired.
Please let us know where we're going.
- The camera operators are wearing sneakers.
- They didn't even know?
- They never tell us.
- That's too much.
Ga In will cry watching this at home.
She wouldn't know that
you're experiencing such a hardship.
[But the mushrooms are
on top of the mountain.]
[They brace their energy.]
[In an hour and 30 minutes.]
Why do we have to...
[Finally, they arrive at the
Phellinus linteus habitat.]
- There's only one camera left.
- That's right. There were three before.
It was tiring getting here
but they didn't record it.
They couldn't.
The camera operators can't climb up.
- Are you sobering up?
[VJ Yong Jae.]
[Natural hangover chaser,
mushroom expedition.]
The last camera operator is coming.
[ENG Director who's fallen behind,
Jung Pyo.]
Someone else is carrying the camera.
I'm sure he had to go through
the same thing before.
['ENG' team suffers the most
due to the heavy camera.]
Can we go now?
All three cameras arrived.
It was really difficult.
But we couldn't film our journey.
The camera operators suffered the most.
We couldn't record it.
I'm sorry.
[Jungsun]
[Jeju Island.]
[The cutlass fish expedition
on a blue night in Jeju island.]
- Look at the sunset.
- And I see the stars... Hi, seagulls!
There are seagulls.
[Seagulls and the full moon greet
Ji Hyo and Taecyeon.]
We're going to catch
the cutlass fish soon.
[Will they be able to catch
five cutlass fish?]
[Ji Hyo puts the bait on.]
Cutlass fish, please take this bait.
- Like this?
- Yes.
You did pretty well!
Was it okay?
[Please come, cutlass fish!]
[They wait for cutlass fish anxiously.]
I miss my mom.
You have the fish.
- Pardon?
- It seems like you have it.
[The rod is curved.]
[Is that a cutlass fish?]
[That is!]
- It's a cutlass fish!
- Jackpot!
[It looks totally different than
what we see at the market.]
We did it!
[They catch one cutlass fish.]
[The cutlass fish is clear silver.]
What do I do?
Mine is moving!
- It's here!
[Ji Hyo catches a big one, too.]
We can go home soon.
[They catch two cutlass fish.]
[And the third one is caught
right after.]
[The cutlass fish's spectrum is amazing.]
We just throw the fishing rod.
Then it gets the fish.
They were shining like a U.F.O.
It felt like that.
Here it comes again!
[A huge cutlass fish!]
[They've caught four cutlass fish
in a flash.]
Hi, I'm a cutlass fish.
[The mackerel is a bonus.]
[The revolution of novice anglers!]
- The cutlass fish!
[The fifth cutlass fish!]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon succeed
at catching five cutlass fish.]
Captain! Taecyeon!
We've got them all!
I never thought it would be this easy.
We didn't know that, either.
The Dragon King of the sea
may think that we're nice.
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon continue to fish.]
Fishing is fun.
- We've completed our mission.
- Thank you for your hard work!
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo succeed in
digging out 1,000 cockles in the mudflat.]
Ma'am.
[Seo Woo gives snacks to the ladies.]
I'll do better when we cook, Jong Kook.
- I'll make up for it.
- You should.
[Ha Ha and Shoo get their
ingredients early.]
It's really good.
You know the ingredients are
50% of the dish.
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun succeed
in getting 6 Kg of small octopus.]
[What will be Suk Jin and
Yoo Sun's menu?]
[Gary and Sung Ryung learn
how to make 'Som Tam.']
You eat this like we eat Kimchi in Korea?
[Recipe- Julienne papayas.]
- Like a radish?
Sung Ryung, only half of your
papaya went into the plate.
[Pound mung beans, tomatoes,
dried shrimps, and papayas in a mortar.]
[Add some lime juice for tangy flavor.]
- It's lime juice?
- I think the peanuts will make it delicious.
[Add some peanuts in the mortar.]
['Som Tom' is ready.]
Why can't I make it the same?
- Tom Yum Goong.
- I like Tom Yum Goong.
- It's galangal.
- Ginger.
[Recipe - Put ginger in chicken broth.]
- 500 ml of chicken broth.
[Use whole prawns.]
- Root parts for fragrance.
[Add Thai pepper paste and coriander.]
- It's hot pepper paste.
Put the stem parts first.
[What will it taste like?]
It's good!
[This is it!]
This soup has to be in that tureen.
We don't have this kind of soup plate.
Can I borrow it from you?
Sure. No problem.
- Kokunkap! (Thank you!)
[Gary and Sung Ryung learn in Thai.]
[And the taste?]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon
start picking mushrooms.]
That tree looks amazing.
The tree over there.
You have good eyes.
There are many mushrooms
on a dead tree.
Wow, there are so many!
Just like I told you.
[Phellinus linteus,
Gift of the heavens.]
[They have come a long way,
and they're right in front of them!]
That one is a bit thin.
You'll need to put some more strength
for the thicker ones.
- They grow on this kind of tree?
- Yes, they do.
They're right here!
Right there, at the top!
- Is that a phellinus linteus?
- That's right.
[A huge one appears!]
I found it!
I found phellinus linteus!
[No pain, no gain.]
We might win this battle!
We've gone through the hardship.
- But this one doesn't even need a recipe!
- We can just boil it and drink!
[They use an ax for a huge one like this.]
I will pick them up.
[The huge one comes off.]
Wow, this is huge!
[It's enormous!]
This is the Phellinus linteus!
- That's very thick, too.
[This is a real Phellinus linteus.]
- It is worth coming here.
- It is.
[A broken piece weighs 940g.]
This one big piece weighs 475g.
[They succeed in picking up
1kg of mushroom.]
We're thankful to the Kangwon Province.
For the air, breeze and everything
that grows the Phellinus linteus.
We will win this battle.
[What will they make with
this gift from the heavens?]
[Kwang Soo and Fei acquire the invitation.]
[In Bulkyo.]
- Now we can participate.
[ In Jungsun.]
- Congratulations!
[All the teams get an invitation.]
- You are invited to...
the New Year's cooking battle.
[They have the recipe and the ingredients.]
[It's all ready.]
[All teams report to the battlefield!]
[Congratulations! You are invited to
the New Year's Cooking Battle.]
[As last year's winner,
who do you think is your rival?]
Rival?
It's myself.
I don't really think about rivals.
I think my team can easily win
if we can show the skills we have.
[Next day,
'M' mall in Incheon.]
[From all over the nation,
and other countries.]
[They have gathered here.]
[Everything looks better
than last year.]
[It's the 2015 New Year's Cooking Battle.]
[Each team's ingredients
are set on their table.]
[The fresh cockles
from Bulkyo are still alive.]
This looks like Iron Man.
They were in the ocean yesterday?
Did you wrap them in tin foil?
Yoo Sun, this is phellinus linteus.
This is real phellinus linteus.
- Isn't this a broken piece of tree?
- No, it's really expensive.
That looks like a dried dog poo.
What are you talking about?
I will make some tea and give it to you.
[You will change your mind
when you taste it.]
Before we begin the cooking battle
I'll tell you the rules again.
2015 New Year's Cooking Battle.
Use your own ingredients and Kimchi
which is the main theme of this battle.
Within 100 minutes...
[Within 100 minutes!]
the team that makes the most
delicious dish will win this battle.
When the timer hits zero,
you can't submit the dish any more.
It means some teams can
be disqualified.
You can only open the cockles
in 100 minutes.
We have invited special judges
for this competition.
The four handsome chefs are here.
[Handsome?]
[They are as handsome as
their cooking skills.]
[The young chefs.]
[The four flower chefs, F4.]
[Italian chef, Nam Sung Ryul.]
[Professor at Seoul HOSEO Technical College,
Head Chef at 'Table Star']
[Chef Mr. Right in Italian cuisine.
Currently in the "O'live Show".]
Pasta!
Spaghetti!
I'm Park Sung Hoon
specializing in European cuisine.
[An elite chef that won the gold medal
from WorldSkills International.]
[Cooking shows -A Chef's Late Night Snack,
O'live show.]
Fusion Korean dishes are my specialty.
I will analyze your dishes realistically.
[Fusion Korean Chef, Shim Hyo Sup.]
[Owner chef at the Korean restaurant, 'Umui'.
CEO of cooking studio, 'Inskitchen'.]
[He appeared on the '100 year guest'.]
Hello, I cook Thai cuisine...
Thailand!
[Thai Cuisine Chef, Heo Hyuk Koo.]
[A star chef who is
in the middle of Thai fever.]
He's nice.
The dish has to be delicious.
I will focus on the taste.
Don't focus on the decoration.
That's what my team seeks in food.
I want to focus on creativity
rather than techniques and preparations.
That's our motto.
We're going to focus on creativity.
I want to see the popular appeal.
That's right.
We're all for the popularity!
How can phellinus linteus be popular?
Just keep quiet!
[Jae Suk, it's embarrassing.]
- Do you like S.E.S.?
- I like S.E.S.
[They're sucking up.]
The chefs will now go back to
their seats and judge the dishes.
See you soon!
We will see you with a good dish!
- There are five kinds of Kimchi.
[Old fermented Kimchi]
[Radish Kimchi], [White Kimchi]
[Whole cabbage Kimchi],
[Young radish Kimchi].
[Five kinds of Kimchi.]
Two teams per Kimchi will be accepted.
Who gets to choose first will be
decided by rock-paper-scissors.
One person from each team
come forward.
[Each team's thinking of a
certain kind of Kimchi.]
It's too much pressure.
You're the main chef of our team.
What do we need?
First, Old fermented Kimchi
and second, whole cabbage Kimchi.
Old fermented Kimchi is the first?
Old fermented Kimchi,
I want Old fermented Kimchi.
Old fermented Kimchi is
the best for stews or soups.
Old fermented Kimchi.
I think we need Old fermented Kimchi.
- I've interviewed five people.
- Do they all want the same one?
I guess that's what we like the most.
- What if you can't pick that one?
- Pardon?
No way!
Then we can't make our dish!
Then we'll fail.
Just like that!
[He's scared thinking about it.]
Then we'll start rock-paper-scissors.
I'll ask what you're going to play.
[Can't you see what's going on?]
Are you from the women association?
Ladies are participating
at a Kimchi making event?
[Three of them are married.]
[I'm not even married.]
Are you ready?
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Fei is the last one to pick.]
[Second round.]
Rock-paper-scissors!
Wait a moment.
I understand you're in a hurry.
I should call for the game.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Sung Ryung and Seo Woo lose.]
[Yoo Sun and Shoo get to pick first.]
Old fermented Kimchi!
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun pick
Old fermented Kimchi.]
[Ha Ha and Shoo
also pick Old fermented Kimchi.]
- Old fermented Kimchi is sold out.
- The liquid is crucial for them.
[The rest can't pick Old fermented Kimchi
from now on.]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon
pick Whole Cabbage Kimchi.]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon pick
Radish Kimchi.]
[Gary and Sung Ryung pick white Kimchi.]
- Should we pick white Kimchi?
[Seo Woo picks whole cabbage Kimchi.]
[Kwang Soo and Fei are left
with the White Kimchi.]
[Kimchi selection is over.]
The cooking will begin now!
[100 minutes are given.]
Let's go for it!
- Let's have a fighting spirit!
- Fighting!
I'm nervous!
Let's go with it, Jung Hoon!
We might win this battle!
[Who will win the battle?]
I want to make something
that no one can think of.
I think Ha Ha can follow my lead.
One of the strong candidates is Fei.
Fei is really good at cooking.
I've tasted a dish she made
on a show I'm hosting.
She's really good.
She was on a competitive cooking show.
Indeed, it's Fei.
Fei's team.
It's not fair! We're amateurs
and she's a professional.
[Kwang Soo and Fei are
in the highest level of alert.]
[Her cutting technique is amazing.]
You're really good with knives.
Am I?
[She's good at handling cleavers.]
[See-saw motion, what a cutting technique!]
[You are now watching Running Man.]
(Not a cooking show.)
[What kind of dish will she make?]
I think Suk Jin and Yoo Sun
are my rivals.
I heard Yoo Sun is really
good at cooking.
Sung Ryung's face changed
when she heard Yoo Sun is
participating.
She suddenly said 'Let's not win.'
'Let's just enjoy the show',
when the cameras weren't around.
[A dark horse who psychs out Sung Ryung.]
- Did you catch them?
- Yes, we caught them.
[She cleans them with flour?]
- You're not scared?
- We caught them.
- You're really not scared?
- Why should I be scared?
[Rub with flour to
thoroughly clean the octopus.]
We'll make pasta with the small octopus.
We harvested some Jerusalem artichokes
for two and a half hours yesterday.
We'll make Jerusalem artichoke
salad dressing.
We've suddenly decided it yesterday.
We put it in a blender with
milk and honey.
Yoo Sun suggested that
we should make a salad dressing.
The dressing is so good.
I want to let the world know.
Did we actually make this?
- This is really good, isn't it?
- It is.
[Jerusalem artichoke is high in inulin,
which mimics insulin.]
- What is it?
- I'm going to make the dressing first.
- Let's trade Kimchi!
- You can't trade Kimchi!
- It's really good!
- It's good?
We grated the fresh Jerusalem artichoke
and it was nutty.
I thought I can add some perilla powder
to make it more nutty.
And make a salad dressing.
It's the best.
I never thought it'd be this good.
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun finish
making the dressing.]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon]
The buckwheat that
great Jang Geum gave us.
Should we make four servings?
Two dumplings per person...
then we need eight dumplings.
- Will this be enough?
- Yes, it looks good.
Did you discuss it with Han Ga In?
I told her everything.
My wife was asking my mother-in-law
on the phone.
Later, we decided to create
a pure and clean dish
to keep the original form
of porridge soup.
Besides the porridge soup
we will serve phellinus linteus tea.
I think we can get some
additional points for it.
[Making the phellinus linteus tea
with jujubes.]
Don't we need to add more jujubes?
No, it's enough.
- Have you made jujube tea before?
- I always make it at home.
Your family lives in harmony.
Your family makes tea
and dumplings together.
- I'm going to make Pad Thai.
[Pad Thai and Tom Yum Goong.]
I will soak the rice noodles
in water for about 25 minutes.
[Making the broth for Tom Yum Goong.
With palm sugar, mushrooms and coriander.]
[Add prawns and hot pepper paste.]
[Coconut milk]
[and lime juice.]
[She put everything in the recipe...]
Can I taste it?
Wait! Wait!
It's not like you're making
some bean paste stew!
Sung Ryung!
I didn't know that she was stubborn.
I want to make Tom Yum Goong again
but I think she wants to
fix it and submit it.
Win or lose this battle,
I will try making a delicious dish.
[Is this White Kimchi?]
[Today's theme, Kimchi
is being used for the first time.]
[She cuts White Kimchi
and puts in Tom Yum Goong.]
[Is the taste better than before?]
It's good!
We can cook it a little longer.
[Gary and Sung Ryung revived
thanks to the white Kimchi.]
- Wash the cockles in salted water.
- Okay.
[Washing cockles in salted water
to remove the mud.]
[Washing big fan-mussels.]
Fire!
Are you allowed to have
things like that?
- What is it?
Why did you bring table tennis paddles?
- Because I thought I'll be bored.
- Why did you bring them
Where did you bring them?
Are you going to use abalone, too?
Of course!
I'm going to make another healthy dish.
We'll make some shiitake cakes
and spicy cockles.
We'll also make cockle bibimbop
and cockle stuffed cucumber. So we
can make several dishes using cockles.
We have a hidden card,
but you'll see it later.
[You still have another dish to make?]
Cockles are cooked.
It's a lot of work.
Cockles are a lot like you.
[Cockles and Seo Woo.]
Am I now Cockle Seo Woo?
- Did you prepare Kimchi?
- Let's rinse the Kimchi.
[Kkuk opens the cockles
and wash them one by one.]
You're taking too much time.
- Open them all and then wash it!
- Okay, I will.
I need to... move away!
Go do it somewhere else.
- Where?
- On the floor.
[It looks somewhat familiar.]
[Until the moment...]
[Jong Kook scolded Seo Woo.]
- What are you doing, Seo Woo?
Girls from Seoul are a handful.
Your persona is 'burden' from now on.
- You're a burden.
[Kkuk didn't know...]
[that he would be the 'burden'.]
[He's getting scolded at the corner.]
- Just open them all and then wash them.
It'll take too long to wash it one by one.
Now I'm nagging.
[Kkuk is acting like a new bride.]
[Yawning?]
[Taecyeon tries to cut the fish.]
[He ruins his image
as a masculine idol.]
[He is sawing, not cutting.]
[Ji Hyo is busy making the sauce.]
- Hot pepper flakes.
[Adding cooking wine and yuzu citron.]
[She puts everything that she sees.]
[And she tastes it.]
It's the second time
I've made any kind of sauce.
I was only focused on the sauce.
Taecyeon is working in his own space,
and I'm working in my space.
I don't know how he's doing now.
[Taecyeon tastes Blank Ji's sauce, too.]
- Did you put some garlic?
- Yes.
Garlic...
Do I need to put some more?
- I don't know what I need to add.
[Please don't add anything more, Ji Hyo.]
We're going to be the winners
at this pace.
We would have failed if we
didn't get the Old Fermented Kimchi.
[Finally, the Old fermented Kimchi
is released.]
It's really good!
I'm not lying!
You will go mad if you eat this.
[Stir-fry the pork forelegs marinated
in curry sauce with Kimchi and vegetables.]
Please help us, Old Fermented Kimchi!
[They've only started cooking.]
[40 minutes passed.]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon replace
radish with radish Kimchi.]
Braised radish Kimchi is a lot better
than braised radish.
I think Ji Hyo and Taecyeon
will make a very good dish.
[Kwang Soo and Fei
start to prepare white Kimchi.]
[Fei's knife skills are still amazing.]
[Fillings for dim sum:
Stir-fry chopped pork and vegetables.]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon
use the Whole cabbage Kimchi.]
Their Kimchi is not fermented.
You can add some vinegar
when you cook unfermented Kimchi.
[Kimchi porridge soup:
Stir-fry Kimchi with beef and garlic.]
[Add water and bring to a boil.]
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo
prepare their kimchi, too.]
[Seo Woo's knife technique
is as good as Fei's.]
[She puts kimchi into the hidden dish.]
[Kkuk is still struggling with cockles.]
I can't believe you're
still doing that!
It isn't as easy as it looks.
I'm getting upset. I guess there's
a reason I play a bad woman.
[Kimchi shiitake mushroom cake:
Coat mushrooms with cornstarch.]
[Stuffing the mushroom with diced
kimchi, pancake mix, and vegetables...]
[Gary and Sung Ryung start
to make their pad thai.]
Yes, Chef.
- Let's add three.
[Cook all the ingredients together in a pan.]
- Add the noodles.
- We need some sugar.
[A perfect harmony of the ingredients.]
- We need the fish sauce.
- What else do you have? Add it!
[Perfect teamwork.]
- Do we have a dish to put this in?
[Flips the hot sautè pan around.]
[And within minutes, pad thai is ready!]
- Kim Sung Ryung, you're disqualified.
- Why?
[Who do you think you are?]
What do you mean, why?
Why am I disqualified?
I'm working so hard.
What are you guys doing
over here?
Didn't I tell you that you'd waste
all your time shucking those cockles?
There's a tool for shucking these cockles,
but we didn't bring it with us.
Shucking those cockles isn't easy.
[Jae Suk heads over to heckle
Suk Jin and Yoo Sun this time.]
You're lucky with your home at home,
and you're lucky with your partner here.
- Yoo Sun, you look like quite the cook.
- I told you that I'm good.
Why do you always add in the shoulder
shrug instead of just saying the words?
- Yoo Sun always does that.
- We always laugh about it.
[Half the competition is already over.]
[Kwang Soo has been mixing the same
bowl of dough for the past 50 minutes.]
[Looking more and more at a loss.]
[But thinking back...]
[Kwang Soo already has a deep past
with making the flour dough mixture.]
[I'm so sick and tired...
of these flour dough mixtures.]
- No, I don't think that's right.
- Just trust me, Fei.
- What am I going to do with that?
[A dangerous situation with the dough.]
- I think we have to start over.
- No, we don't.
[In the end, Fei steps in
to help save the situation.]
[I vow to save this dough mixture myself.]
[With a mixture of a soft and firm touch...]
[Dough mixture with the chef's
heart and soul mixed in it.]
Why are you able to do it, and I'm not?
I think that's enough to help us win.
I think that's more than enough.
[The dough is saved!]
- Okay, I can handle it from here.
- No, don't do it.
- What do you mean, don't do it?
What do you mean by that?
Fei, that's so disappointing to hear.
Don't do anything and just
cheer me on from the sidelines.
I have a very clear picture now.
Flour dough and I don't go together.
Flour dough isn't my style of cooking.
Kwang Soo keeps giving me his opinion,
but I keep telling him that he's wrong.
I think he's putting a lot
of his faith in me.
[Meanwhile, Ji Hyo and Taecyeon are busy
prepping their cuttlefish dish.]
[Gets rid of the fishiness by dipping
the fish in the curry mixture.]
[Their secret weapon is out!
Charcoal grill is fanned to a flame.]
[Even the panel of judges seems
impressed by their move.]
But I really would prefer that they don't
grill the curry coated fish on the grill.
I have a feeling that it's going to burn up
like the way my heart is burning up right now.
[The cuttlefish is burning up
just like the judge had predicted.]
- It's okay, everything is going to be fine.
[Sings a song to comfort himself.]
It's a total failure.
[The two of the lesser burnt pieces.]
I don't think this piece is going to do.
[How is he going to rectify this
emergency cuttlefish situation?]
[And that's none other than
by decorating the dish!]
[With an impromptu sauce piping bag.]
[Decorates the dish with
the prepared citron sauce.]
[But even his attempt at decorating
the dish is a failure.]
Maybe I should've used
a smaller spoon.
[Taecyeon makes another attempt by
transferring the fish to a smaller dish.]
Okay, I'm going to make another attempt
with a smaller spoon this time.
[With all his hopes in the small spoon...]
[Fails again! Guess the size
of the spoon wasn't the issue.]
[Puts his heart and soul into the dish, and
finishes with a sprinkle of the sesame seeds.]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon are busy
cooking up their pot of kimchi noodles.]
[Add in the soaked buckwheat rice to the pot
of already cooked kimchi, meat and veggies.]
[It's time to add in the dumplings.]
They're all stuck together.
[All the dumplings are stuck together
in one huge lump of a mess.]
- I can't believe this is happening.
- I think I've got this one.
[What are you going to do with that?]
[Dumps in the whole mess into the pot.]
[Gives up on maintaining
the shape of the dumplings.]
- Why is there so much of it?
[There's enough for the entire staff!]
[Meanwhile, Suk Jin and Yoo Sun are...]
[Their own dish creation of stuffing
the octopus head with the filling.]
- I really think this is going to be amazing.
- Let's cook it a little bit longer.
[Stir-fry the kimchi stuffed heads
in the heated pan.]
[Create a tomato based sauce with minced
fermented kimchi, onions, garlic, and bacon.]
Maybe we should've used smaller heads
to stuff these in.
- There are only 30 minutes left.
- I know, we don't have much time.
- Only 30 minutes left on the clock!
- 30 minutes?
Jung Hoon, there are 30 minutes
left on the clock.
- Do you think 30 minutes is enough?
- It just needs to come to a boil.
- Then it just needs to simmer for a bit.
- But what is the dish?
[With only 30 minutes left on the clock,
they're trying to figure out what it is?]
- It's porridge.
- Porridge? I see...
- But it's North Korean style.
- It is?
- My father really likes this dish.
- He does?
He'd always eat this as a
hangover cure
- and I remember eating it as a kid.
- This soup dish?
[Tries their secret weapon,
mushroom and jujube water.]
[Even offers a taste to the camera man.]
Come on, just try it.
- That's pretty good.
- Not bad, is it?
Drink this, and go for a second kid.
- At my age?
- What's wrong with your age?
I'm telling you that this mushroom tonic is
going to bring you the magic for another kid.
- Okay, then leave some for me.
- That's what I'm talking about!
[Will this magical elixir win
the panel of judges over, too?]
We'll just feel it all out.
Okay, let's do this!
He has a mortar in his hand.
They call those 'Mortar and pestle'.
People in Taiwan uses it to mince garlic,
spices or such when they're cooking.
- That's a real and authentic mortar.
- He's doing it up right.
[Crush the dried shrimp, peppers, garlic
in the mortar and add in the sugar...]
[and season it with fish sauce, then mix it
together with papaya and kimchi with lime.]
Yes, I think that's enough.
- Okay!
- Let's add in the papaya!
[Automatically starts clapping
in the midst of all their excitement.]
- Time to crush it together.
- Let's start singing.
[Gary and Sung Ryung are
totally in sync as a team.]
- Okay!
[Even their second dish is now complete.]
[Wow, that's good!]
- It's good with the lime, isn't it?
- I don't think it needs anything else.
- Right?
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo
on the other hand...]
[Seo Woo has five different dishes
going all at the same time.]
[Top slices of cucumbers with
steamed cockles and seasoned soy sauce.]
[And their secret main dish.]
[A mix of abalone, octopus, and other seafood
in a pot of broth with fragrant veggies.]
- What is this?
- It's our seafood stew.
By any chance... you're not here
to interfere with our cooking, are you?
I really was a huge fan of yours
in the drama, 'Heirs'.
- Thank you.
- She's so cool.
- She's cool, she still goes clubbing.
[Even Mr. Capable is impressed by Sung Ryung.]
- I don't go clubbing.
- Want to go with me some time?
- She's seriously so cool.
- Okay, it's a deal.
[Kwang Soo and Fei are getting serious
about cooking their dishes.]
[Stir-fries the cold rice with egg.]
Kwang Soo, we have to be quick
and not let it overcook.
[In the meantime, Kwang Soo
gets the dim sum ready.]
[Fei adds in her own special seasoning.]
- That's your own seasoning, isn't it?
This is how you actually cook at home?
[Adds minced chicken, vegetables,
kimchi and seasoning to the rice mix.]
[Will the Chinese seasoning mix well
with Korean kimchi?]
We're going to make shrimp chips
with the dough.
Ha Ha...
Okay, this is frying up nicely.
[Fries up the dumpling dough
and sprinkle it with the shrimp powder.]
- We're going to fry it until golden brown.
[Makes a topping with the minced kimchi.]
[Their hands starts to move faster
as the clock continues to tick.]
[Create your best dish for the chance
at becoming the top chef.]
[Everything is hanging on the line!]
Only ten minutes left on the clock!
[All the dishes must be completed
within the next ten minutes!]
[Kwang Soo and Fei are
feeling the pressure.]
[In the midst of all this chaos,
Fei starts to cook the egg drop soup!]
- I've never cooked like this before.
- Fei, you're really impressing me right now.
We're definitely going to win this.
It's hot, so be careful.
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo are putting
finishing touches to their final dish.]
- How does it taste?
- It's good.
[The perfect amount of seasoning.]
It's not even salty.
I like that it's not salty.
[Add the steamed cockles into the mixture
of sauce and fresh vegetables.]
- Where's the shucked cockles?
- Over here.
[Gary and Sung Ryung even have
a dessert dish to present.]
Are you grilling up the meat?
[Jae Suk and Sung Hoon are grilling the meat
as an accompaniment to the noodle soup.]
We don't need too much of it.
[Ha Ha and Shoo are juicing up the carrots
that they've harvested themselves.]
[While each team are busy preparing
their secret ingredient dish...]
[Yoo Sun is now adding in the pasta
to keep it from getting too soggy.]
[Even twists up the pasta like a pro.]
[And finishes up the dish
with the stuffed octopus heads.]
[Doesn't even forget to add
the potato dressing to the octopus salad.]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon even have a refreshing
shikhye to go along with their dish.]
- Okay, we're all set.
- I'll take it over to the table.
Fei, we've ruined this one, too.
[Fei calmly plates the fried rice
in the midst of all this chaos.]
- We're in trouble.
- No, we're fine.
- One minute!
- No, just plate it.
[One minute left!]
[The time is almost up!]
- Jong Kook, take this out there.
- Is it ready?
[With all their hearts and soul in the dish,
they're taken out to the judging table.]
Okay, the dishes are on the table.
[The judging will begin in the order
the dishes are placed on the table.]
Are we done?
- Ha Ha!
- It's already on the table.
- Where do we need to take this?
- Let's go!
[Disqualified from the judging
once they miss the time limit.]
Get it on the plate.
Ouch, that's hot!
That's so hot!
No, just get it on the table!
- Four!
- Here it is!
[2015 Cooking Battle is now over.]
[From every corner of Korea...
and even from Hong Kong and Thailand...]
[Dishes with the hearts and souls
of these seven teams.]
[Just who will take home the victory
from the 2015 Cooking Battle?]
- All the dishes are now complete.
- Yes.
Panel of judges, please come out.
[Which of these dishes will win the hearts
of this beautiful panel of judges?]
Each team will now step forward
and introduce their dishes
and the panel of judges
will judge their dishes.
First up, we have Taecyeon and Ji Hyo.
[First dish- Taecyeon and Ji Hyo.]
Can you please tell us about your dish?
We traveled to Jeju Island for our dish.
We were actually at a loss as to how we were
going to combine these two flavors together
but when we saw radish kimchi on the table,
with the harmony of radish in the dish
we cooked the fish with radish kimchi
to bring out the flavors together.
Then let's try the dish.
[Time to test it out.]
- Why do I feel so nervous?
I feel more nervous than
I did last year.
I really hope that you enjoy it.
[How is the joint flavor of
radish kimchi with the cuttlefish?]
I'm curious to see how the cuttlefish
would taste with the radish kimchi.
I'm sure that it'll just
taste like radish kimchi.
[Will it just taste like plain radish kimchi,
or will it be a match made in heaven?]
- They don't seem to look too happy.
- They should be commenting on it by now.
[How will the panel of judges
rate Ji Hyo and Taecyeon's dish?]
First, the dish is very...
- First, the dish is very...
[The dice has been rolled.]
[How will he rate the dish?]
The cuttlefish is so fresh, and
the flesh is so delicate and delicious.
But I can't help but think that the
radish kimchi may be too unfermented.
I think the cuttlefish itself may be
some of the best I've had
but I can't quite figure out what you were
trying to do with the radish kimchi in the dish.
I agree with your comment.
- But thank you for your hard efforts.
- Thank you.
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon's judging is complete.]
[- Cuttlefish itself is outstanding.
- But it's a wrong combination of the two.]
[Huh?]
[Second dish- Jae Suk and Jung Hoon.]
First, our dish is...
[Is this supposed to be a joke?]
- I see that our panel of judges...
I see that they can't contain
the laughter on their faces.
This isn't just a joke,
but this really is your dish, right?
[A bowl of mixed porridge?]
- I'm really sorry that you're disappointed.
- But Jung Hoon's father is from North...
- No, he's from Gangwon-do.
- I mean, he's from Gangwon-do.
- Did you say he's from the North?
His father originates from Gangwon-do,
but whenever he'd have too much to drink...
- Why don't you explain it to them?
- Let me explain it for you.
When Jae Suk and I went to Gangwon-do,
we learned how to make buckwheat noodles.
We took that concept and added kimchi to it.
And as for the tea
we went into the mountains ourselves
to find the Phellinus mushrooms.
- Yes, we harvested the mushrooms ourselves.
- Then we simmered it with jujubes.
- We've brewed the tea ourselves.
- What do you think of your situation?
This is the worst case scenario.
We're in critical danger right now.
But you may have a change of heart
once you taste the dish.
The dish was sitting out too long.
[Will the dish taste
as surprising as it looks?]
- Are there dumplings in this dish?
- Yes, I taste the dumplings.
- His father really loves dumplings.
- What's the correlation with kimchi in this?
It's kimchi dumplings.
[Okay, I see...]
- It's kimchi dumplings.
We didn't add any other seasonings,
but relied on the filling of the dumplings
to season the dish as a whole.
- I actually kind of like it.
- You like it?
- I think it's actually kind of good.
- That's so great to hear!
I like the flavors of kimchi in the dish.
What's going on here?
[Everyone's flustered at the sudden
twist of events.]
- You should try the tea, too.
- I really enjoy the tea that you've brewed.
We hiked through the mountains for two hours
to find and harvest those mushrooms.
- I really enjoy the tea.
- Thank you.
[The unexpected deep flavors from
the kimchi and the buckwheat noodles.]
[All the judges are impressed with
the flavors of the brewed tea.]
We sustained some injuries from
the cockle digging we did yesterday.
- My hand, especially.
- How did you hurt your hand?
- I had to cook five dishes.
- Yes, she took on a lot of work.
I was watching from the sidelines,
and it was from her own carelessness.
I like the cleanliness and
the simplicity of these dishes.
[A five course cockle and kimchi spread.]
Even from a quick glance,
I can see the harmony of the dishes.
- The first dish we have for you is...
- Healthy cockle stew.
[Main dish of the spread-
Healthy cockle stew.]
- As for the Bibimbap...
- Mix all the ingredients together.
Then the cucumber slices are topped with
cockle and seasoning as a small dish concept.
Then the portabellas were stuffed with
chewy cockles and grilled to perfection.
- Have you ever studied cooking before?
- I used to have a roommate...
- I had a girl roommate for a brief while.
- Are you sure that it was a girl?
[Is that supposed to be a joke right now?]
- We'll assume that it was a girl.
[The questions about the identity
of her 'roommate' are flying in.]
We'll start trying the dishes.
[Time to taste all the dishes.]
[Will the dishes taste as good
as they look?]
- They're saying that it's good.
- Really?
- Grilled mushrooms are delicious.
- The sauce is excellent.
- It's grilled to perfection.
- Thank you.
[A shower of compliments.]
In addition, I don't live
with my roommate anymore
and I'm now living by myself.
- Why are you telling them that?
- If you're ever in the area...
My phone number is, 010...
[Please look kindly upon us.]
- You don't need to do that!
- Don't be persuaded by her charms!
- You're going too far.
- I'm just trying to win us some points.
[The panel of judges are
very focused on tasting the dishes.]
Bibimbap is the highlight of our course.
The combination of the Bibimbap
with the accompanying soup...
- I cleaned all the octopus myself.
- Yes, she's very impressive.
Eating too much now
is going to ruin your appetite.
- Please take just one small bite.
- All the dishes go together.
- I would pay money to eat these dishes.
- I agree.
If you're ever in the area...
[Han-Nam-Dong's beauty Chef, Seo Woo.]
The level of these dishes...
I really am quite impressed.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you both for all your hard efforts.
[First strong candidates for the win?]
[- A match made in heaven combination.
- No negative comments to even think of.]
[Fourth dish- Suk Jin and Yoo Sun.]
I'm actually very eager to
try out your dish.
We actually used a lot of
Jerusalem artichokes in our dishes.
We harvested the artichokes ourselves to
ensure the freshness of our ingredients.
Even the salad dressing was made
out of the Jerusalem artichokes.
Jerusalem dress... I mean, the dressing...
No, the artichokes were ground up...
He has no idea what he's saying.
What do you mean,
Jerusalem artichokes dress?
- What are you trying to say?
- I'm sorry.
[Is he going to get himself
a balsamic dress next?]
Freshen up your palate
with the salad and the dressing.
The dressing was made of
freshly pureed Jerusalem artichokes.
We added some sesame seeds to bring out
the nuttiness in the flavor
for the completion of the salad.
Then our pasta dish is a
baby octopus-kimchi pasta.
The fermented radish's flavor is enhanced
when you stir-fry it in the pan
so we added the tomato sauce after
the radish has already been stir-fried.
- She sounds like a cooking instructor.
- She sounds very professional.
Since kimchi is added in the dish,
instead of using Italian arugula
we used kketnip instead to bring out
the Korean flavors of the dish.
Why didn't you tell me about that?
You should've told me about the arugula.
Anyway, we topped off the dish
with ribbons of kketnip.
I think using baby octopus
and Jerusalem artichokes together
while they're both in season
was a great choice.
[Time to taste the dishes.]
You should try the stuffed
head portion, too.
[Chef Big-nose offers up his service to
cut the stuffed head pieces for the judges.]
Okay, give it a try.
- The texture of these are great.
- We caught them from the ocean ourselves.
- The kketnip is a great combination.
- Thank you.
- We didn't use the ddong-kula.
- It's not ddong-kula!
What kind of a thing is that
to be saying during a meal?
- They're eating right now.
- Give the Jerusalem artichoke juice a try.
[Their secret weapon-
Jerusalem artichoke juice.]
- It tastes similar to the mushroom tea.
- Really?
Then I guess they're disqualified.
- The juice is better than the main dish.
- Our juice can be the main dish.
Yes, of course.
We can turn the juice into the main dish.
[- A perfect combination of the ingredients.
- The juice unfortunately outshone the main.]
Thai food, which isn't too common here,
is combined with the flavors of kimchi
to be the main point of our meal.
You can also mix in the sprouts, sugar,
and the pepper flakes into the noodles.
- The mixed flavors are delicious.
- We've also added some oyster sauce to it.
The noodles are not as soft anymore
since they've been sitting out for a while.
Why don't you also try the
tom yum soup?
[Time to taste the tom yum soup.]
You see the chunks of
kimchi in there, don't you?
Sir, are you okay?
- What's wrong?
[No, I'm not okay!]
- Are you okay?
- Here's some water.
[Everyone rushes over with water
in order to win some brownie points.]
- What did you put in there?
[Are you okay?]
The flavor of the broth
in the soup isn't bad.
But I'm not sure how adding the kimchi
to the soup is improving the flavors any.
- It just tastes like tom yum soup.
- Adding the kimchi makes it healthier.
- Then can we just eat it separately?
- That's such a nonsense argument.
- Sung Ryung really is...
- One thing I'd like to say is...
- Yes?
- I think it's a love-it-or-hate-it dish.
Isn't that the case
with thai food in general?
[Is this a judging panel,
or a discussion panel?]
This isn't a great dish, but I'd like to
learn how you used the kimchi in there.
It's a dish that I'd like to
experiment with myself.
- We've also prepared a dessert.
- You didn't make this yourself, did you?
- Yes, we did make it ourselves.
- But isn't this a store bought ice cream?
- Yes, the ice cream was...
- Then what about it is self-made?
We have the evidence of it right here.
[The chances of winning first place
is getting dimmer and dimmer...]
[- The flavor isn't bad, and kimchi is good!
- Too strong of a thai flavor?]
- Hello.
- I'm Papa Ha Ha...
- And Mama Shoo.
[Curry kimchi sujebi
and shrimp nacho chips.]
We traveled down to Jeju Island.
The trip we took to Jeju Island was the first
trip I've taken alone in over eight years.
[Why are you suddenly tearing up?]
- Why are you crying?
- Why are you suddenly tearing up?
- How is that related to cooking?
[It's not our fault that you haven't
been on a vacation in over eight years...]
She was so happy to be away on the trip,
but she immediately thought of her family.
She was thinking of how nice it would've
been, had her family been there with her.
So we've relayed those feelings
in the curry dish...
[What's the meaning of that comment?]
[Time to taste the shrimp nacho chips
and the kimchi salsa.]
- Is there shrimp in these chips?
- We ground up the shrimp into fine powder.
[Nacho chips with freshly ground up
shrimp powder.]
We took fresh shrimp and
ground it up into fine powder.
- It's the freshest you can imagine.
- I love the salsa.
- Isn't it good?
- It's made with kimchi.
- It's awesome.
- It's good, isn't it?
[Ha Ha and Shoo's dish is getting
rave reviews right from the start.]
[This time, it's tears of joy.]
I love the flavors of
the kimchi in the salsa.
- Really?
- Shall we try the main dish?
We've also added some cheese
to the sujebi dish.
Cheese was added to mellow out the spiciness
and all the strong flavors of the kimchi.
[Pointing out the flavors of the pork
and the kimchi in the dish.]
Even though the curry and the kimchi
may sound like an unlikely combination...
Yes, it is quite unlikely.
[A stew that isn't quite a stew,
but a curry flavored stew.]
It tastes like B-level dish
with the use of A-level ingredients.
[- Unlikely combo of the main dish.
- Amazing combo of the side dish.]
I made a broth out of the chicken breast,
and made egg drop soup with it.
Then the fried rice was made with white
pepper, white kimchi, and scallions.
It's a fusion of Korean
and Chinese cuisine.
- That's the key to our dishes.
- We learned of these dishes in Hong Kong.
The dim sum dish was taught to us
by a top chef in Hong Kong.
- Which of these is the main dish?
- We took the dishes up a notch.
The dim sum was a fusion of
using the western baguette.
- What about this is using the baguette?
- You'll know once you try it.
I really enjoyed watching you cook
during the screening process earlier.
I really think that the Chinese flavors
will come through on these dishes.
- You cooked like a real chef.
- Your skills were that of a top level chef.
[Nonstop compliments towards
Fei's cooking skills.]
We were quite impressed with how you were
using the heat of the fire while cooking.
- We have high anticipation for this dish.
- We can't wait to try it.
You seem to be too focused on Fei,
but I also...
[The panel of judges seem sure of the fact
that only Fei's handiwork is in the dishes.]
- Did you use white kimchi in your dish?
- Yes.
- Is there kimchi in this dish, too?
[Even Fei can't escape their scrutinizing.]
[Time for the taste test.]
Fei is used to cooking
Chinese cuisine at home.
It's really good.
The filling is made with pork and shrimp.
- Did you see the ingredients being used?
- Yes, I did.
I saw all the ingredients she put in there,
and there are lots of healthy ingredients added.
Is there a reason why you
added cumin to your fried rice?
Um... I thought that the use of cumin would
bring out the flavors of Chinese cuisine.
I like the texture of the kimchi in it,
but the cumin is overpowering the flavors.
The cumin did smell pretty strong.
[Sung Ryung's greed for the win
is shining through in her comments.]
- I saw you cooking the kimchi on its own.
- Yes?
I think that improved the kimchi's texture,
and I like the use of cumin in the rice dish.
I like the combination of the flavors.
It's not easy for us to make the egg soup
taste this good with just the salt either...
Bringing out the deep flavors of
such simple dish isn't easy.
- Yes, it's a wonderfully deep flavor.
- If Fei and I hadn't worked together...
- then we wouldn't have been able to do it.
- One disappointing factor is...
No, you can save that comment
for some other time.
It's very easy for one to think that
the texture of these dishes are too dry.
- That's why we've prepared the soup.
- We were going to mist it with water.
- Because their dishes are so dry.
- A sip of our juice will rectify that.
- Take a sip of our juice.
- Our tea would be perfect to remedy that.
- Keep it down!
- Eat the rice with our tom yum soup.
- Try our tom yum soup with it.
- How about our carrot juice?
- Thank you for your hard efforts.
- Thank you.
[The judging panel is now over.]
[The only thing left to do is to
reveal the top three placements.]
[Just who will become the new champion
of the 2015 Cooking Battle?]
[Skilled Fei impresses the judges
with her cooking, and as for Kwang Soo...]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle.]
[All the teams are busy tasting
each other's dishes after the judging.]
- That's really good.
- Isn't that good?
- I can't believe how good this is.
- Wow!
[The dishes prepared by the seven teams
tastes as good as the efforts put into them.]
- That is so good.
- I really like that dish.
[With how good all the dishes are,
how will they ever choose a winner?]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle]
The results will now be revealed.
The judges will flip over the name tags
of the four lowest scoring teams.
When only the three
highest scoring teams are left
the name tags of the only the top
winners will be lifted into the air.
On the count of three, Yoo Jae Suk can...
Or maybe you should do it?
- Why not?
- Should I do it for him instead?
[Why?
Am I going to lose?]
I think your team is going to be
the first one to get eliminated.
- I think you'll be the first one out.
- All the dishes are better than last year.
- Yes, they were all delicious.
- I really liked them all.
[Which of the dishes will be the first
to get eliminated?]
[Will it be Suk Jin and Yoo Sun's
octopus-kimchi pasta?]
[Kwang Soo and Fei's chicken and
kimchi fried rice?]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon's
kimchi buckwheat noodles?]
[Ha Ha and Shoo's curry pork
and kimchi stew?]
Three!
[Could it be?]
[Gary and Sung Ryung's
tom yum soup and pad thai?]
[Jae Suk and Jung Hoon's dish
is the first to get eliminated.]
[There's no arguing in this round!]
[A total visual shock.
Kimchi buckwheat noodles are eliminated.]
- Next... Ji Suk Jin?
- Yes?
- Get ready to join us here.
- No, I'm not.
[Is Chef Big-nose's pasta dish
next to get eliminated?]
Two... three!
No, don't look at our names!
[No...]
[Really?]
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun
are eliminated in sixth place.]
Didn't I already tell you?
What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
Come over here.
[Pasta dish with their
Jerusalem artichoke dressing is out.]
One, two...
Three.
[Wait, that one is...]
[One of these two teams
is next to get eliminated?]
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon are eliminated
in fifth place.]
[Jeju Island's braised cuttlefish is out.]
[Only four teams are left on the table.]
Only one team left to get eliminated
in the lower ranks.
One, two...
- I went all the way to Thailand.
- Three!
No problem, it's okay.
[Gary and Sung Ryung are eliminated
in fourth place.]
[Tom yum soup and pad thai are out!]
Coming in at third place is...
- Why are they all staring at us?
- Ha Ha and Shoo!
[Ha Ha and Shoo comes in at third place.]
[Only two teams are left on the table.]
They're bringing out the gold knife
and the cutting board as the winning prize.
[Here's the winning prize!]
Kwang Soo, if you were to win that knife,
what would you like to do with it?
[What will Kwang Soo do with the knife
if he were to win the prize?]
What are you going to do to me?
[Has Kwang Soo been sharpening
his own knife for this moment?]
- I'm saying that I'll give it to you.
- You'll give it to me?
[2015 Cooking Battle-
Who will be the ultimate winner?]
Three!
Thank you for all your hard work.
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo win!]
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo win
the 2015 New Year Cooking Battle!]
[Mom, I'm a champion!]
[The five course cockle meal
is the winner!]
Just like last year,
I got very lucky with my partner.
To be honest, I really didn't expect it,
but I'm so grateful for this honor.
- Seo Woo, any comments?
- Thank you for all the help and hard work.
[Seo Woo thanks the panel of judges
for the hard work and kind words.]
I can't believe Jong Kook won
for the second year in a row.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Thank you for having been a member
of our Running Man cast.
[They really are two peas from the same pod.
Both acting so childishly...]
We really would like to thank everyone
for all the help that they've given us.
We couldn't have done this
without them.
- Thank you to everyone.
- Thank you!
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo-
Champions of the 2015 Cooking Battle.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A real man.]
[The man of all men...
The real men battle one another.]
[Team RM- We will take you on with
our years of expertise.]
[Team Shinhwa- All six members
of the group will take them on.]
[Team Z:EA- Takes on the challenge
with the passion of their youth.]
[Their hidden wild fierceness will come out
to battle each other in the competition.]
[Keep pushing forward with
their eyes wide shut.]
[We will put our lives on the line
to save the one we've sworn to protect.]
The real man!
[And the fierce friendship of
these real men.]
[Next Week's Running Man-
The Real Man Competition.]