[An ordinary looking high school.]
[But this place is...]
[It's time to choose the
order of bluffers.]
[Come to the roof!]
How are you supposed to bluff?
I've never bluffed before.
It's easy.
[I will destroy everything...]
[that gets in the way.]
Is that bluffing, right now?
- Of course.
- It's been a while!
- Independent study, dinner, music...
- I didn't skip school today!
[Randomly, he does a gangster pose.]
Hey you!
[Haroro, exceeds in bluffing.]
[Gangster Blank Ji.]
Look at this!
Nothing can cool down the
passionate and fiery athletic club!
Don't lose to the hip-hop club who
only know how to run their mouths!
Oh, we're the athletic club?
[We're going crazy right now...]
[I left my body and soul in the beat.]
There's a different feel.
Jae Bum is just a rebellious teenager.
[The pungent scent of
the athletic club.]
I don't have a pose.
[It's time to purify your tired souls.]
What?
What's that?
Oh, Jessi's a member?
[The hip-hop club.]
[A powerful entrance.]
Jessi!
Are you guys the hip-hop club?
[Hip-hop Goddess, Jessi.]
[Lazy rapper, Eun Ji Won.]
[A load of swag, Jae Bum.]
[A rhyming tyrant, San E.]
[A hip-hop rhapsodist, Verbal Jint.]
- San E!
- Gary!
[Welcome to the bluff world.]
I'm your fan, San E.
[It's a friendly atmosphere, for now.]
Shouldn't Gary have been on that team?
- Why Gary?
- Gary's the hip-hop chief.
I'm not a chief.
Who's the chief?
I can't be on the same team as her!
He's the chief according to age.
Why did they give this
old boom box to San E?
[The symbol of hip-hop, a boombox.]
[I want to try.]
You have to face this on the outside.
Your eardrum will be destroyed!
I can't hear.
[It's a new type of
hearing aid boombox.]
- I'll introduce my teammates.
- I know them.
- I'll introduce my crew.
- Yeah, go ahead.
Hello, I'm Jessi.
What's up!
- Ho Jessi.
- What's wrong with you?
Everyone's so bling-bling today.
Why am I always on your team?
We always lose.
[A direct insult.]
Watch your mouth!
Stay calm.
[It won't be quiet today...]
He is my brother, San E!
[Rap Genius, San E.]
San E!
[A hip-hop gesture.]
Did you see that?
He's San E.
And here we have
the mischievous hip-hopper.
- Mischievous?
- The mischievous rapper, Eun Ji Won.
- Eun Ji Won!
- It's been a while Ji Won!
- You know him.
- Jay Park!
Jay Park!
[Jae Bum.]
[This quiet man...]
Isn't he from Seoul University?
[A forceful public address
about his university.]
[Intelligent Rapper, Verbal Jint.]
- Law School!
- Seoul National University!
Jessi looks like she's the toughest.
[The strong Jessi,
and the gentle lambs.]
- Verbal...
- And they're all nice, too.
Verbal Jint is nice.
Why is San E so gentle?
It's because he's beside Jessi.
We're thinking about trying our best.
- We're thinking...
- Don't just think it, show it!
'We're thinking of trying our best.'
What are we doing?
Are we versing them?
Jae Suk doesn't fit.
He just looks older.
At least wear your hat backwards!
You guys don't even know
the hip in hip-hop.
When you wear your hat,
you have to wear it forward.
- There we go.
- Oh, just like this?
[He looks silly.]
[An embarrassing look for his team.]
Hey you, come here.
I think those ears suit you
better than your actual ears.
- It's Yoda ears.
- These ears are more Yoda-like.
Yeah it looks like Yoda ears.
Take off your glasses.
- No.
- This is it!
[I am the hip-hop president!]
[It's not that great...]
You should be blinded.
[The wrong style.]
Forget seeing,
I have triple vision right now.
[Jae Suk's vision.]
It looks cool.
Everyone on this side
are hot and fiery
and are always running towards passion
the athletic club of
Running Art High School.
The athletic club of an Art school?
- Not a Phys Ed High School?
- What about us?
Rhythm flows through
their veins instead of blood
and they make every sound into rhymes.
- What is this?
- They shout at the world
the hip-hop club of
Running Art High School.
Did you understand?
After all your classes are done
Everyone is going to the roof...
- Roof!
- Everything goes down on the roof.
The rules are as follows to
determine the king of bluffs.
There are number cards.
And sign cards.
Both teams will each choose one
after classes are done.
The number cards have
the numbers one to six.
The sign cards have add, multiply,
and subtract.
The team who gets a better result
will pick two cards between
the numbers three to six.
And the other team will pick two cards
between the numbers one to four.
So higher is better.
The first class, if you see across
is the study hall, so please go there.
[The first class is in the study hall.]
[Do you want to become
the king of bluffs?]
[Earn that title on the roof!]
[Study hall.]
It's the study hall.
[The Best High School Bluffer Race.]
[1st period, independent Study.]
I'm going to humble Suk Jin's pride.
[Students who talked during class.]
- What is that?
- That's the rule.
We need to read the announcements.
I was the class president
during self-study!
A dark force in the teacher has arisen.
I can't proceed with class,
so do some self-studying.
If you keep track of students
who talk during class
I will factor that into their grades.
- Do we lose if our name is repeated?
- I didn't understand anything.
- What do we do?
- I don't know either.
We all don't understand.
- Dark force has arisen.
- Verbal, you understand?
Not really.
Doesn't it just mean blackening?
Oh my god!
'Doesn't it just mean blackening?'
Wow! It sounds the same!
- Was that Jae Suk?
- 'Doesn't it just mean blackening?'
[A vocal clone.]
[A new skill thanks to Verbal Jint.]
Out of the six, four people get chalk.
And two people get erasers.
When the whistle blows,
go to the other team's black board
and write the name that you
want ousted on the other team.
Then, it has to stay for three seconds.
Only then, you will be ousted.
But isn't 'Verbal Jint'
too many letters?
English!
You have to write it in English!
[The wrong time for
a real-name movement.]
- Jessi is Ho Yeon Joo.
- It's Ho Yeon Joo?
- You knew it!
- I didn't...
Gary!
Did you do something wrong to Jessi?
Last time, she told me,
'I can hit on you in two hours'.
Really?
- When did I say that?
- You did!
- When?
- You said that!
Jessi, is two hours enough?
Sorry, but on our team
Kwang Soo has both erasers.
He's holding both,
so you could get hurt.
Kwang Soo's going to hold the erasers,
and I'm going hold people.
- He's really scary!
- Oh my goodness!
- Warm up ahead of time.
- Let's go!
[Why are you warning us
on a variety show...]
- You have to be aggressive.
- Okay.
It's best two out of three.
This is the first round.
Ready, set!
[Hip-hop warriors, charge!]
Just write!
- Just write!
- Jessi!
[Kkuk has one person in each arm.]
[The athletic club is
focusing on Jae Suk.]
[Kim Jong Kook is really popular.]
Over there!
Go over there!
[Grabs by the collar
instead of erasers.]
[Giraffe is also on
defense with erasers.]
Just write!
San E, here!
[San E, out!]
[San E was blocked by
Jong Kook the whole time.]
[The people who are ousted
have to do their punishment.]
[Kick.]
[Jessi kicks Giraffe away.]
[In the meantime, writes Kim Jong Kook.]
[Kim Jong Kook, out.]
- Am I out?
- Kim Jong Kook's out!
San E was out, but I didn't know.
[They're focusing on Jae Suk.]
[Yoo Jae Suk, out!]
[Only one person is holding
the eraser on his team.]
[The only defense is Giraffe.]
[Gary, out!]
[This time she head locks Giraffe.]
[She throws Giraffe down.]
- Am I out?
- Verbal Jint out!
- Ha Ha out!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
[Yoo Jae Suk is already out.]
[What is Ha Ha doing?]
Verbal Jint, out!
Ji Hyo!
Eun Ji Won!
Eun Ji Won, out!
[Me?]
[Jae Bum writes Big Nose in the corner.]
[Ji Suk Jin, out!]
[Jessi, out!]
Ha Ha's out!
- Jessi!
- What are you doing!
Jae Bum, there's still some left!
Hurry!
Verbal Jint is out.
[Kwang Soo is stopping
Jae Bum at all costs.]
[While Kwang Soo and
Jae Bum are fighting.]
[Ji Hyo writes Jae Bum's name.]
[She wrote it.]
[Park Jae Bum, out!]
[Best 2 of 3, 1st round,
athletic club wins!]
You did well.
[Way to go Ace!
Ousted 3 people by herself!]
Where's Kim Jong Kook?
Where are the victims?
What did he do?
I thought my arm was
going to be ripped apart.
What about you, San E?
This is our first time meeting,
but I was grabbed by the collar.
You met him today!
San E's in hip-hop!
You don't know who he is?
Sorry but, I went easy because
this was our first time meeting.
What Jessi?
Wait, why am I out?
Jessi did this to me!
Wait but why am I out?
We wrote your name.
[She understands the rule now.]
Why didn't you tell me?
[We've been playing that way.]
- What are you doing?
- This is a competition!
Jessi blocked me when
I was trying to write a name.
I told her 'not me!'
I couldn't see.
I ousted a lot of people.
- He did the most.
- MVP, MVP.
We lost, what do you mean MVP?
We lost!
Ready...
Why, you little brat!
[I have Kim Jong Kook behind me!]
Bluff!
[Why you little...]
[What are you going to do?]
[I have Jong Kook on my side.]
Doesn't anyone fight on this team?
Look at him.
Do you really want to fight?
[I won't someone who I can
pick a fight with...]
He's not human.
[Best 2 of 3. Round 2 start!]
[Jae Suk, Verbal Jint,
Jessi, Jae Bum on offense.]
[Move!]
[Kwang Soo, Gary, Ji Hyo on offense.]
[Verbal Jint is writing Ha Ha
at the no mark zone.]
[No, come here!]
[Ha Ha, out!]
[Kwang Soo takes down San E.]
[Completely blocks San E.]
[It's Ji Hyo, Gary vs. Ji Won.]
[Big Nose is on defense.]
[Erase!]
[Erase again!]
[Big Nose's defense is awesome!]
[Suk Jin! I've tied them up here.]
[Jessi is the master of defense.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[Kim Jong Kook, out!]
[Kwang Soo is blocking San E
who has an eraser.]
[Ji Hyo is attacking San E.]
[Erase!]
[San E, out!]
[Eun Ji Won is also out!]
All the erasers are out?
[No mark chance.]
[Offense? Defense?]
[Blank...]
[While he was blanking out]
[Verbal Jint, out!]
[Right after, Yoo Jae Suk out!]
[Park Jae Bum is also out!]
[The hip-hop team
doesn't have a clue yet.]
[Jessi, out!]
- You won?
- What's with our team?
[The athletic club wins both rounds.]
What is this?
Someone wrote it here,
but someone else erased it.
Erasing is part of the game, so what?
[You still don't know
the rules of the game?]
Jessi and I were the only ones writing!
Where were you?
- I was erasing.
- But?
- Kwang Soo took my pants off!
- They're weak.
This game is so much fun.
Let's do it again.
[The winner asks for a rematch.]
A two point round.
We'll do this round with 3 points.
And Jae Suk has to kneel
down in front of Ha Ha.
Untie my laces, please.
You can tie his laces for him.
- I'm going crazy.
- Hurry up!
- What are you doing?
- This is...
Good job, good job!
Sorry, but I need to take a picture.
Record a video!
[How does a man kneel down...]
Jae Suk!
[Like this.]
[It's so easy to kneel down.]
[So easy thanks to Kkuk.]
It's not broken, right?
You can tie each other's laces,
it's normal.
Sorry, sorry.
[A bold close-up.]
[A strike on the head.]
- Do it properly!
- Who is it?
[They're scary...]
Sir!
I can't feel my feet!
- Do it quickly.
- And properly.
[Kneel down.]
I'm going to take a picture!
Jae Suk, lift your head up please.
- That's not your face!
- Why are you doing that!
- That's what he usually looks like.
- Hey!
[Summer of 2015... I won't forget...]
Ready, set...
This is worth three points.
If this team wins,
it will turn the game around.
Of course, of course!
Jong Kook!
No hitting!
- We're ready.
- Ready...
[Will the hip-hop club
turn things around?]
Oh my god!
Stop!
If you put that on my face!
[The athletic club is
using a 1 on 1 method.]
Gary!
[A perfect 1 on 1 system.]
[Of all times,
he runs into ace Blank Ji.]
[Guys I'm in trouble!]
[Ace Ji Hyo goes through
Jae Suk and starts attacking.]
[On the other hand,
there is chaos here.]
[Kkuk grabs two people in a flash.]
[Big Nose's incredible defense.]
[Thanks to a good defense,
Kwang Soo joins in on the offense.]
[He removes the only defense, Jae Suk.]
[Ji Hyo is at a no mark zone.]
[Chaos.]
[Blank Ji writes down names
without hesitation!]
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk, out!
[He can't get out even if he's out.]
[She's writing a Death Note.]
[She's writing the names of
the hip-hop club in a row.]
[What is this?]
[Jong Kook made a dog pile.]
Eun Ji Won, out!
What is this!
[Hip-hop club, all kill.]
[The athletic club wins the re-match.]
[Game over, in a flash.]
I was so hard-working!
[Instead of being sad about their loss]
[they're happy to be free
from the dog pile.]
- What is all this?
- What are you doing!
What's funnier is, didn't one
person write all of this?
Who wrote all of that?
[Do you want a re-match?
The whole team is untying their laces.]
[Angry.]
- Get in line!
- How about a 6 point match?
We'll give you 20 points!
We'll tie Jong Kook's
with our teeth first!
[We just need Jong Kook...]
Just you wait, in a month or so you'll
have a diss song written in your honor.
Especially you!
You'll have two!
Write one!
Okay?
- Jint, write one!
- I'll write one now.
- Re-match!
- Okay, okay.
The title should be 'shoe laces'.
[Rage.]
It's a good title!
I tied them today, shoe laces should I
tie them with my teeth, shoe laces.
[Just you wait...]
The winning team can pick two cards
out of the four numbers 3, 4, 5, and 6.
Just pick one and show us.
Nice.
Out of the signs there are
add, subtract, multiply.
Show us.
What is it?
Pick two cards.
[They picked sign cards as well.]
[The hip-hop club lost cruelly.]
[But the real winner is
chosen at the roof.]
[The game cards obtained so far.]
[Athletic club vs. hip-hop club.]
[Ready for period two.]
[The hip-hop club finally has
a chance to counterattack.]
[The Best High School Bluffer Race.]
[Period two, music class.]
There are a lot of musicians today.
[It's going to be a dynamic class.]
Feel, soul, my life!
Look at that.
I used to say that all the time.
[The three elements of music
would be rhythm, melody, harmony.]
[But Gary answered feel, soul, my life.]
Do you agree?
Oh, Gary said that?
[Ignorance or bluffing?]
I will find the soul of music
and come back soon.
Don't go to the snack shack
when I'm not there.
What's with this school?
Especially, the other
teammates shouldn't buy
anything while the rep does the mission.
The two teams aren't versing each other.
Is everyone here?
As you can see
you have to pick out
the keywords of the mission.
Each team figure out the
mission and pick one rep
who would best fit
for this mission.
While that person does
the mission as long as possible
the rest of the members will go
to the snack shack upstairs.
You each must buy something different.
While the rep is doing
the mission without failing
the rest of the members who buy
five different objects will win.
[If the rep gives up, the relay ends.]
Who would like to pick a keyword?
- Yeah! Go!
- The keyword is?
Chair.
You have to do a mission
related with that word.
- Isn't it a pylon?
- No way...
[I remember the pain from that day...]
Jay... you do this one.
Is it something weird?
[I feel like I shouldn't
sit on this 'chair'...]
- You're important.
- Jay, now is your time.
Jay will be our team's rep.
[Mission rep, Jay Park.]
Then I'll go.
- Really?
- Ha Ha!
Is it Ha Ha?
Why?
Can't it be me?
Isn't it 1:0?
Comparing visuals.
What are you saying?
This is the mission for the reps.
Invisible chair.
Each rep will wear pants with sand paper
and be in a horseback riding position
above the balloon with
a book on their lap.
Before the rest of the members
buy their objects
if the book on the lap falls
or if you sit on the balloon
that team will fail.
You've seen my lower body.
[The definition of lower
body is Dream's daddy.]
I'll do well, but just come quickly.
Everyone please go behind the desks.
You have to buy the objects
in the order I call out.
The objects you have to buy this round
are instant noodles
chopsticks
a can of tuna
chocolate
and water.
Memorize one each.
Ready, set...
Please get into position
when I blow the whistle.
[A teamwork mission with
the rep's lower body muscles]
[and the team members' quickness.]
[First mission, the electric chair.]
[Shove.]
[It's like a UFC match from the start.]
[Where did you learn such bad habits?]
Good job, Jessi!
I'm already so tired.
[Snack Shack Mad Max, Fury Hall.]
[The balloon will pop
at the slightest movement.]
Oh, good.
Please give me instant noodles!
Me first!
[Re-experiencing the
memories of snack shack.]
[Push.]
No!
[This is a competition.]
Keep it together, Jae Bum.
Hip-hop calves vs. Daddy calves.
[They are passing through the corner.]
Come on, Jessi!
[Baton pass, Jessi to Ji Won.]
Steal it!
[Stealing failed.]
[So close.]
[Ji Won is going to...]
[play dirty?]
[Kwang Soo, start!]
[I need a plan to close
the distance with Ji Won.]
Please give me some chopsticks!
[Ji Won received the chopsticks.]
[Grab.]
[Free hugs.]
[An eye for an eye,
a dirty game for a dirty game.]
This is unnecessary!
This is your loss, as well as mine!
[No, this is their loss.]
Do something!
- Jay, you got this!
- Just wait a little longer.
Jae Bum!
This is harder than I thought.
- What are doing?
- What are you guys doing!
Kwang Soo!
Ji Won!
Good job!
Is it hard?
Oh my god.
You can't let him steal!
You can't!
[Who has the chopsticks?]
[He stole the chopsticks.]
Guys!
Oh no!
- Hurry up!
- Don't fool around!
Hurry!
Don't fool around.
Ji Won!
Bite him!
[If they continue,
both teams might lose.]
He stole Ji Won's!
[Risky, risky.]
I can't, I can't!
[Giraffe, gets the chopsticks.]
[Doomed Ji Won.]
[This is dangerous.]
I guess I can walk now.
[If we're winning by a whole lap,
I can crawl.]
[Aren't you thinking about us?]
Jae Bum...
do you want to give up together?
[End of negotiation.]
Jae Bum, wait a little longer.
[This is hard...]
- Chopsticks!
- Again?
[Ji Won buys chopsticks again.]
I can walk all the way.
- What is this!
- You got your chopsticks?
Ji Won, hurry up!
[Second round of negotiation.]
[My betraying bum.]
Do I go?
[Hidden card, Verbal Jint.]
[A fast and accurate rapper,
Verbal Jint.]
[He will do anything for speed!]
[Elite rapper from S University,
his athleticism is different!]
[Attacking Verbal Jint]
[Will he be able to counterattack?]
[Trot, trot]
He's really slow.
[What's wrong with his running?]
- Why are you so slow?
- Hurry up!
He's so slow!
[Is he a snail?]
[Even though his legs are slow,
his hands are...]
[are even slower...]
Hurry up, hurry up.
What took you so long?
I've reached the limit.
[Instead of Big-nose brother,
his limitation has reached.]
[We're ahead of them,
what's with the fuss?]
[He just saw Ha Ha.]
[The athletic club passes the baton.]
[The hip-hop club passes the baton.]
I wasn't thinking about him.
[Thanks to him,
they're having a crisis.]
[Blank Ji is here!]
- Chocolate!
- Thank you!
Chocolate, here it is.
[The bouncy Grasshopper
gets the chocolate.]
Hold it for some more!
Don't think about anything!
- Wait, wait!
- Just hold on!
[Trying to break concentration]
Why did you bend so much?
Here she is,
now it's the last runner's turn!
Jae Suk!
[Baton pass]
[Blank Ji to Kkuk]
[Pratfall!]
You're over!
They're over!
[The athletic club fails at
the Electric Chair Mission.]
[My legs are numb.]
[Now it depends on the hip-hop club.]
Hurry up!
How many do we have left?
Jae Bum, hold on a second!
[They will complete the mission
when San E arrives.]
Jae bum!
You can do it!
[Yes...
I can do it.]
[I've played an active part
during the last game.]
[I could have been the MVP,
if my team won.]
[This time, Park Jae Bum will be MVP.]
[I'll show...]
[Oh! Please play again.]
[He failed when they were
really close to finish.]
[The Hip-hop club fails
at the Invisible Chair Mission.]
It's good.
They failed, too.
We could have won
if you hurried up.
I totally forgot about Ha Ha.
I forgot.
It was really tiring.
- Jae Bum!
- You need to massage your legs.
You did a good job!
You dirty bastard!
[Why are you stealing
other people's items?]
Kwang Soo is... really strong.
Wait, gather up, Team.
Why are you playing this game so clean?
- I played it well!
- Verbal, why are you so slow?
I thought you were a snail or something.
[Fumble Jint]
[I'm dying here...]
How come no one takes after Jae Bum?
It's okay, Jae Bum is strong.
Jae Bum, it's spacious.
Why don't you show us b-boying?
Can you please give me 10 minutes?
I'm sorry.
- You should take care of him first.
- I wanted make him a star.
Isn't this space perfect for b-boying?
[Park Jae Bum's 5 star rated
dance will be revealed soon!]
[Dance MVP Park Jae Bum's
Hip to the Hop!]
The keyword for the next mission is...
It's 'cup'!
[The second mission keyword: cup]
The keyword is 'cup.'
- Pick a player.
- It's going to be Verbal.
This time, Verbal will play.
- How about Running Man team?
- Ji Suk Jin.
Verbal Jint?
I'm Ji Suk Jint.
Verbal Jint versus Ji Suk Jint.
This game is holding a cup
around your mouth by suction.
Breathe and hold the cup.
The rest of the team members need
to buy things from the snack shack.
You need to face each other.
By the way, Jae Bum is wondering...
what makes this class a music class?
- We're just doing it in the music room.
- He's become sensitive.
The things you need to buy
during this round are..
Nectar, chewing gum
instant coffee, hot pepper paste,
energy drink.
Do you understand?
Get ready!
What?
[Oops!]
What's going on?
[The Hip-hop club fails
in three seconds.]
What's wrong?
[Ji Suk Jin drops the cup
while laughing.]
We'll do it again!
Rematch!
Are you serious?
- I can't.
- Maybe it's your beard.
[It's really easy.]
- You need to get rid of the air.
- You're not supposed to do it that way.
Look at his lips.
You need to make it tight at the bottom.
I can see the crack.
Put the rim tight.
[Pumped lips]
- It works, right?
- You did it.
[Shake, shake]
[He fails at it even after the lesson.]
He only studied for his life.
He's holding it with his lips.
You can't do that.
- He was holding it.
- I think you should do it.
Are you going to replace him
with Eun Ji Won?
Listen carefully.
Beverage, popcorn, insecticide,
cooking oil, and ice cream.
Eun Ji Won and Ji Suk Jin,
please face each other.
Release your hands
when I blow the whistle.
Ready, set!
[Grabs]
[I want your hair!]
Lee Kwang Soo, are you serious?
[He wants to collect women's
hair whenever possible.]
He's unbelievable!
- He's amazing!
- Beverage!
Give me the beverage!
[It's very peaceful here.]
- Was it chewing gum?
- No, it's popcorn. asdf
- Beverage!
- You can take it from the fridge!
[The Hip-hop club is a tad fast.]
[Free from all ideas and thoughts]
[They return at the same time.]
Good job!
[Guillotine choke!]
Jessi has a strong combat power.
[The hip-hop club arrives first.]
Here's the beverage!
[They're still very peaceful...]
[Oh, they can't really talk.
That's why...]
- Popcorn!
Popcorn!
Block him, block him!
What are you doing?
You should have put them
in the cup already!
[The gap is increasing again.]
See?
Gary is weak.
That's not it.
He was making it one by one.
[Popcorn artisan is upstairs!]
[Don't make me laugh!]
He was scooping popcorns one by one.
[Don't laugh!]
It's tiring!
Insecticide! Insecticide!
[The bouncy Grasshopper
vs. Dream's Father.]
Insecticide!
[While the hip-hop club
is still in the lead...]
[the masters are recovering.]
[The hip-hop Genius San E vs.
the athletic club's Ace Blank Ji]
Cooking oil!
[If the hip-hop clubs keeps
the lead, they can win!]
Cooking oil, please!
[San E increases the gap
and runs at full speed!]
- It's okay, Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo!
[Their cardiovascular endurance
have reached the limit.]
[San E to Verbal Jint.]
The last runner is Kim Jong Kook!
[Verbal Jint vs. Mr. Capable]
He's so slow!
[Verbal Jin is in the lead.]
It's so scary!
Out your head up!
Look up!
Just hold it for ten seconds!
- Wait a second!
- Just lean back!
It's good!
- Verbal Jint!
- Jong Kook!
[Who is the last runner
that comes first?]
[Mr. Capable is coming!]
[The athletic club turns
the table at the last minute.]
[The athletic club wins
at the Music Class.]
[Disappointed]
How can you lose?
[Crime reconstruction]
You can take it out yourself.
[The moment he grabbed one,
Mr. Capable caught him.]
[With the other hand,
he grabbed an ice cream!]
[He deserved to be Fumble Jint...]
[He doesn't have speed nor strength...]
[Verbal Jin is all wet.]
We had to take the ice cream
from the freezer.
I've seen people who are slow.
But he made me scared!
Therefore, the athletic club wins!
It's a complete defeat!
Every time I come on 'Running Man,'
I lose because I'm on your team.
It's not my fault!
It's Verbal...
we almost won but he ruined it!
[Thanks to Verbal Jin,
they had a good music class.]
The athletic club, please come forward.
[Picking out the cards]
Same as before, you will
pick one from three to six.
You need to show me.
[The first number card]
[The second number card]
[The first sign card]
[The second sign card]
At least we need to pick good ones.
[The first number card]
[The second number card]
[What about the sign card?]
[The first sign card]
Wow!
Please pick another one.
[The second sign card]
Even though we lost the game,
during this mission...
Jae Bum was really funny.
Verbal... you're like a new discovery!
You're the slowest person
in the entertainment business.
Let the viewers judge,
why are you...
Get out if you're not in my team!
[He's dissing him properly
as the captain of the hip-hop club.]
You're a member of the athletic...
[Summoned forcefully]
Record this!
You need to record this!
[Otherwise, I'm dead!]
- Let's see Jay's b-boying!
- Let's do that!
[Jay's break-dance time!]
This is a rare chance for us!
I'll start and...
Everybody dance now!
San E can do beat boxing, right?
[Okay, start the music!]
[It's show time!]
[The windmill!]
[Jay Park is awesome!]
[Freeze]
[The perfect finish!]
Come on!
[Who's going to challenge?]
[Roar!]
[I only know boxing moves!]
[He is the captain of
the athletic club indeed!]
Verbal!
[He's not very athletic,
but his Hip-Hop spirit...]
[Never mind.]
What are you doing?
How can you break
the mood like that?
Verbal Jint just crushed the mood again!
[He's still practicing.]
Just put down the cup already!
Stop it!
He'll be the master of
cup sucking in a year.
He will be preforming in the street.
On his album cover!
He might wear the cup
like a gas mask!
[Verbal Jint: You look nice.]
[Verbal Jint: You look suffocating.]
He won't need a mask.
Let's go!
[Let's go to third period!]
[The hip-hop club is in a crisis.]
[Will they be able to counterattack?]
[The acquired cards
after second period.]
[The last game before
the final mission on the roof!]
[What will be the game
they will play at the library?]
[You're stronger than yesterday.]
[The third period: free time]
Why did they put the mats on the floor?
You shouldn't run the games.
That's unfair.
It's good to be on a winning streak.
San E, Verbal, and Jae Bum...
Especially, Verbal looks
very disappointed.
He was highly motivated at first...
Look at San E.
He removed all his accessories.
They are useless.
This time, we will pick
the game for you.
The first game you will play is...
you probably know this game.
'The Stationery Throw.'
What?
What do you mean?
- Stationery.
- What is stationery?
It's fancy.
[He remembers fancy stationery shops.]
You're so old!
One representing member
from each team
will come out and wear a backpack.
Run to the line and bend your waist
to throw the stationery
inside the backpack.
We're not throwing them with hand
but bending our waist?
You're good at it.
We'll pick Kwang Soo.
[Powerful]
He's really good.
[Kwang Soo vs. San E]
What about you?
Good!
[The whole body rolling attack!]
He's good!
- Happy new year!
- Say good night.
Good night!
[You need to bend your waist
as if you make a deep bow.]
[The great humiliation]
[And his head is in the bag.]
Can you see?
- What was that?
- Did you see it?
You saw how I do it?
[Will Kwang Soo and San E
be able to do it properly?]
San E, let's go!
['The Stationery Throw,' 1st round]
Deux used to wear this kind of backpack.
Don't step on the line!
- Are you ready?
- Go!
You don't need to do it too hard.
[The future of the hip-hop
club is on this backpack!]
[Home Run!]
[The perfect bounce!]
[San E, nice shot!]
That was nice!
[It's an out-of-the-park homer.]
That's what he threw?
- That was nice!
- That's really far.
You can do it!
[How can I win...]
[Smile]
Start if you're ready.
- Kwang Soo, come on!
- Ready!
- Fight, fight!
- Set!
[Fly, fly away!]
We won!
[Giraffe's dramatic grand slam!]
He just threw it with hand.
[He's doubting.]
Did Kwang Soo throw it?
Check the camera now.
There's no way only one pen
could go that far.
It doesn't make any sense!
Don't you understand what bounce is?
I'm sure he threw it with his hand.
Of course, he threw it.
[He shut his eyes tight...]
[he holds the marker
in a scorpion-like position.]
[Then he casually throws the pen.]
[Then he acts like he's innocent.]
He must have done it.
[The fraud is exposed.]
I'm so sorry!
[What if you weren't caught.
Is saying sorry enough?]
- I'm so sorry!
- It's okay!
It's my fault!
I'm sorry.
[The hip-hop club gets one point.]
[The athletic club is disqualified.]
- Show us, Kwang Soo.
- Okay, I'll be serious this time.
Lets' go, let's go!
- It looks perfect.
- Let's go!
[No more dirty tricks...]
[I will reverse the game by fair play!]
Excuse me, Director...
[Sudden stop!]
[You need to experience the same.]
I'm sure I could have
thrown it really far!
All of a sudden, I thought about
something to tell to him.
- You just broke his concentration.
- I'm really sorry.
[I see how it is...]
Good luck, Lee Kwang Soo!
Ready!
[He hit his own face!]
It's pretty far!
- Did you get hit?
- I got a knee kick.
I saw stars!
- I really saw stars!
- At least, it went pretty far.
This game is too dangerous!
This game is not dangerous.
It's not supposed to be dangerous.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
If San E throws it further than that,
the hip-hop club wins the first game.
End this game, San E!
If you start talking...
- Stop it!
- What are you planning to do?
[Pretending and denying]
What did we do?
I'm not going to stand
and watch this time.
- San E, just do it.
- Do it even if they block you.
[The athletic club,
breaks into the field.]
What was that?
It's all for fun!
Do you think it's funny?
[A mud fight begins.]
[What do I do...]
That's how you play this?
[This is a war!]
[Scorpion Kwang Soo]
[His combat power increases.]
San E was kicking at the back.
Because he doesn't want to lose.
Don't just stand still.
Who was standing by?
Jae Bum, you didn't move...
Verbal...
- I'm not going to be standing here.
- You two are too timid today!
I'm timid today.
I didn't do anything!
What do you mean you're timid?
- What do you think timid means?
You don't have to be greedy about it.
Why do you want to be timid?
- What does timid means?
- You don't even know what it means.
I don't care!
[So she didn't know what it means.]
[She wants to be part of it.]
I'll see how you do, Jae Bum and Verbal.
Because we were in a fight!
So we can start acting up now?
No, we can't.
- We can block them though.
- I'm afraid you will cause a trouble.
Just stay calm, Verbal.
It's always the quiet ones.
Verbal, are you usually this quiet?
- Let's resume the game.
- Even if they block you, keep going!
- Really?
- Are you really going to?
- Let's go!
- Just do it!
Players should not...
[Rolling]
[It's an out-of-the-park homer again!]
That's right!
[San E's diving was rewarded.]
[San E's pen went further
than Kwang Soo's pen.]
This time, the hip-hop club wins.
It's just one game.
This time, you will play
'Indoor Slipper Ping-Pong.'
[Big-nose and Gary win at
'Indoor Slipper Ping-Pong.']
[During the free time,
score two points first!]
The game you're going to
play is 'Open the Book.'
You probably know this game.
One member from each team
comes out and opens the book.
If you see more people on the
opened pages than your opponent
It'll be lucky to have a history book.
[I should be brave!]
These are the books we will give you.
They're the same books.
Are there pages with no people?
Yes, and that'll count as 0.
Don't just ask,
'Are there pages with no people?'
Please do well on the game!
- You sound like Lee Sun Gyun.
- You only ask, you don't act!
I'll try and get the page
with the most people.
He drives me crazy.
He will impersonate him from now on.
The face has to show
eyes, nose, and mouth.
You can't lose, Ha Ha.
We need to get to the finals.
What are you looking at?
I can't see anything.
- This is how he plays it.
- Yes, this is how I play it.
Do you want to see how I play?
[He could go against the rules.]
These two have quick wits.
[Ha Ha will go first.]
One, two, three!
One, two, three, four, five,
and six!
- I think she's pregnant.
- And it's twins!
[Ji Won's turn.]
[He has to get more than six people.]
- One, two, three.
- Four people!
This is a rabbit.
[Ji Won gets three people.]
- Ha Ha is good at this kind of game.
- Just finish him, Jint.
Verbal, you need to win.
[The next runner is timid Verbal.]
When will I be able to win over someone
graduated from
Seoul National University?
Is it going to be today?
[The way he grabs the book
is out of ordinary.]
- He's good at handling books.
- He graduated the law school.
Verbal read a lot of books.
It's okay, he graduated low school
but you graduated high school.
I love school!
(An old social networking website)
This is old school!
[Feel the warmth of human
inside the book...]
I'll open it!
['Open the Book,' the second round]
[Verbal Jint: 15 people]
- There are 15 people!
- That's great!
There's a page with 30 people.
[Don't give up, Ha Ha.]
[Verbal Jint can smile now.]
Go, go, go, go!
- One, two...
- Hurry up!
['Open the Book,' the second round]
[Ha Ha: 4 people]
[The athletic club vs The hip-hop club]
[1:1]
[Verbal Jint's next opponent
is Mr. Capable.]
Jong Kook is not good at this game.
- Do you think he's not good?
- Not at this game.
- No, no, no, no!
You'll be surprised.
He will open a page with 100 people.
[Is Mr. Capable good
at 'Open the Book'?]
- Oh my god!
Three people.
[Mr. Capable gets three people.]
I think I can win.
We can't win over a Seoul University
graduate a single time!
I'll open it.
I think he dog-eared it.
Maybe he can do magic.
Stop, stop!
They're signaling him.
Come here and check if we can see it!
We can't see anything!
[One, two...
how I waited for this moment...]
[He couldn't even hold a cup.]
[He's got beaten by Mr. Capable
on the verge of victory.]
[But I'm not the boy I used to be!]
[This time, I must win
over Mr. Capable!]
It's one person.
And he's wearing a mask.
[It has to show eyes, nose,
and the mouth.]
['Open the Book,' the third round]
[Verbal Jint: 0 people]
[This must be a dream.]
We can't see the nose!
[The athletic club vs The hip-hop club]
[2:1]
[It's hard to defeat Mr. Capable.]
It's your turn, San E.
[Gary vs. San E]
Just one more!
If they defeat San E,
they will win the third period.
[Relaxed]
Good luck, San E!
- Going, going, gone!
- And I got it!
[Jackpot!]
- They're not human.
- We can't see their faces.
Jessi and Ji Won,
you need to let the viewers see this.
Go home and watch it later!
We're timid, what's wrong?
But I'm curious!
['Open the Book,' the fourth round]
[Gary: eight people]
- It's eight people.
- That's a lot.
We most likely won.
Hope you get nine people...
[Please...]
Don't distract him.
He did it!
[He catches a big fish!]
We won!
This can't be...
[The hip-hop club recovers!]
[It's definitely more
than nine people.]
- Did you switch the book?
- Of course, I did.
- This is the last round.
- Song Ji Hyo!
I'm afraid of her.
[You need to win this round
in order to pick good cards!]
I know this is the last round,
but stay back.
[Will the hip-hop club's heart
San E be able to win?]
- Do I need to open it first?
- Yes, it's your turn.
[The teams' futures depend
on how well Ji Hyo does it.]
[The goddess of fortune!]
- Song Ji Hyo!
- She's so lucky!
[Everyone in the picture is looking
straight and showing their faces.]
16 people.
[Lots of pressure]
Is that a record?
San E, open the same page
or else you'll die.
- Wasn't that 15 people?
- There was a page with 30 people.
- Ready!
- San E!
[Who will be...]
[the final winner?]
One, two, three!
[Huh?]
[This page is...]
The man with a mask again!
[The unclimbable fence of the mask]
- Ji Hyo, you are...
- Amazing!
[Sick and tired of
three consecutive losses]
We keep the winning path.
[Relaxed]
We were so close.
We did pretty well.
[The athletic club wins
during the third period.]
Pick two cards first.
[The winners picks
among 3, 4, 5, and 6.]
We can't see it, can we?
[The athletic club, the third period]
[The first number card]
[The second number card]
[The athletic club, the third period]
[The first sign card]
[The second sign card]
The athletic club, Please move back.
[The hip-hop club, the third period]
[The first number card]
[The second number card]
[The hip-hop club,
selecting the sign card]
[The hip-hop club, the third period]
[The first sign card]
[Pick this one.]
Up right, I have a good feeling.
This is what Verbal Jint picked.
Why?
[The curse of brave Verbal Jint]
[The Best High School Bluffer]
[The athletic club's 3 consecutive wins]
[Leaving only the final showdown!]
[The cards acquired during third period]
[The acquired cards in total]
[All high school feuds
end on the roof!]
[This is the final battlefield.]
What is it?
It's an outdoor film set!
You are finally at the roof.
The game to see who
the best bluffer really is
is a card fight.
We have collected six number cards
and six sign cards.
Each player will pick one
number card and one sign card.
Come up with the cards.
First, you will flip the number card.
Then you will flip the sign card
at the signal.
The one with the bigger number wins.
It's time to bluff.
We need to pretend.
The numbers that the
hip-hop club have are...
one, one, two
- Oh no!
- Three
three, and four.
1, 1, 2, 3, 3, 4.
And we're not going to
tell you the sign cards.
But we have a brain,
graduated from Seoul University.
These are the numbers that
the athletic club has.
Three, three, four,
five, five, and five.
But they're not to be
compared with us!
3, 3, 4, 5, 5, 5.
Now you can make combinations.
[The chances are against us...]
[What combinations will they make?]
Listen, they don't really have choices.
One and one, they're useless.
I think they will use
bigger numbers in a row.
We can win with our small numbers, too.
It's easy for us to win.
We will win when both teams
put useless cards.
I think they will use
the bigger cards at the end.
It'll be good for us if they use up
the big cards in the beginning.
We don't need to use
big cards in the beginning.
Let's use the small cards first
then we will win the rest.
We might even win the first one, too.
- We need to lose first.
- At once?
We need to guess
what they will use first.
Pardon me, but I'm pretty sure
they're in their glory now.
I think they will keep
the biggest cards till the end.
So they can win the game at the end.
I guess they won't use
big numbers in the beginning.
It's unfavorable for us,
so we need to take the bet.
Fortunately, we only have
two negatives.
We have pretty good sign cards.
We have a decided advantage.
- It's already decided.
- We are really smart.
[With resolute determination]
[Right here, right now]
[the showdown begins!]
You're having a hard time.
We couldn't win even once!
Do you think you will win this?
Maybe we will!
Ji Won will be the first player.
Our first player is Jong Kook.
Put the cards close to each other.
For victory, we need to win four times.
Or 3 wins and 1 tie.
We'll follow our plan!
- We will win!
- Crush them!
[Riding high]
[Poker face]
Have you ever seen a blue card?
Please flip the number cards.
One, two, three!
Just as we expected!
This is one of the big numbers for you!
Why did you use up the big one?
- It's not one but two?
- It hurts me.
You never know.
I think they put a useless card.
One, two, three!
[Revealing the sign cards.]
We won!
[The hip-hop club wins
at the first round.]
This is it!
I told you we can win with three!
Our plan is working!
[The hip-hop club starts by winning.]
[The second players, please come out.]
We have Ji Hyo!
We have Jessi!
- Jessi.
- This is an amazing battle of wits!
The second round, flip the blue card.
One, two, three!
- It's good!
- We never know!
[Both teams put out high numbers.]
- It's just how we expected.
- The sign card...
One, two, three!
[Revealing the sign cards.]
Just as we planned!
[They made the hip-hop club
to use their highest card.]
- Like I said!
- Wow, Dong Hoon!
[The hip-hop club has two wins
but a thorny path is waiting for them.]
We'll start the third round.
- Jay Park and Ha Ha.
- Flip the blue card.
One, two, three!
[Both teams revealed
the highest numbers.]
[Now, it's the sign card.]
Yeah!
It would have been better if we
switched the second and third round.
What are you going to do now?
They are playing a safe game.
They'll keep the big ones.
We should have won one more.
[There must be a solution.]
[Gary vs. Jae Suk]
Flipping the blue card...
One, two, three!
[Very big difference]
We know it's five.
[Relaxed]
The sign card, one, two, three!
[Revealing the sign card]
[A facile victory]
What a big difference!
[Suk Jin vs. San E]
Please make me win!
Starting with the number card,
one, two, three!
I knew it!
- We're going to take the bet now.
- The sign card, one, two, three!
[Maybe they will able to reverse...]
[What do we expect?]
[Three-peat!]
- It's annoying.
- This is fun!
[Even the last card is favorable
for the athletic Club.]
[Our plan will be successful!]
We're great!
They are in the palm of our hand!
This is the last round!
We won.
Kwang Soo will play.
Verbal!
- Really?
- A battle between an fool and a genius.
What are you talking about?
Who's dumb?
We have no choice.
It'll be a miracle if we win.
[We're giving our all.]
Flip the blue card, first.
One, two, three!
We did it!
If we win, we'll be tied.
- Yes.
- Yes, it is.
[I won't let you win that easily.]
The sign card, one, two, three!
[Will it be an easy victory?]
[Or will it be a draw?]
[The card has been flipped.]
[The hip-hop club's last victory!]
[Huh?]
[What is it?]
[They used the multiplying card
at the end!]
[The card fight ends in draw.]
- Hey!
- What do we do?
[Puffed up]
Start using your brain from now on!
The game is a tie now.
We'll use the sudden death method.
The athletic club won more games,
pick an additional sign card first.
They are exactly same sets.
You will use one of the number card
you already have.
Make a combination with
this new sign card.
Who wants to draw the last card?
It all depend on this card.
- And Ji Hyo is sitting there.
- She's really lucky!
- I did my best today.
- Yes, you did.
You did it, Ji Hyo!
Okay, very good!
[We won't lose so easily.
This is competition...]
[Jessi picks the last sign card.]
We have no other chances.
It's our destiny!
We did our best.
We did our best, too.
We'll flip the sign card now.
- Ji Hyo, flip it.
- Jessi, go ahead.
Why me?
- Ji Hyo!
- Please!
[1,000 percent nerve-racking!]
[I'm the goddess of fortune.]
[Please...]
One, two, three!
[The last sign cards reveal!]
[Half a second to the ultimate victory!]
[The last cards that will decide
the two teams' fortune!]
[They picked the same card!]
Wow!
[How could it be!]
[What an electrifying victory!]
[We missed it.]
Amazing!
We were close...
[Who knew they would have
picked the same card!]
It's just one point!
We did what we could.
[The goddess of fortune
blessed the athletic club.]
- Here is the prize for the winner.
- Wow, it's a golden snapback!
The golden badge is attached!
It's very stylish.
I still can't believe
we picked the same card!
[Bragging]
The hip-hop club should
have received this prize.
Thank you for playing with us.
Jae Bum, you've worked so hard.
Normally, guests on variety shows
appear to promote their albums.
'Running Man' doesn't give us
any opportunities to do that.
From the beginning, we start fighting.
- Why don't you promote yourself?
- It's okay.
Many people know me.
[He's bluffing now that
the race is over.]
It's the first time for me to
come on a physical variety show.
I tried my best...
but I'm so sorry.
From the beginning to the end,
he says sorry.
He keeps saying sorry.
I think I will practice cup suction
when I get home.
Thank you for your hard work!
[The summer blind date on vacation!]
[Hae Ryung, Ye Eun, Park Hana]
[Irene, Seo Hyun Jin, Hwang Seung Eon.]
[Mood maker, Do Sang Woo!]
[Extremely enthusiastic guys...]
[and extremely coy girls?]
You don't know how to party.
[Their shocking transformation starts!]
[Hot summer, cool vacation.]
[Will they be able
to handle the ladies?]
I want to stay with you tonight.
- Do you wanna me?
- Are you 'Wanname'?
'When We Go On Vacation.'
Subtitles by DramaFever