[The "Running Man"
mission box is delivered.]
What's this?
[Lively girl, Park Bo Young]
"Please bring a nostalgic item."
"The older the item is,
the more beneficial."
"However, you need evidence or someone
to prove the time period."
Do we need to film the evidence?
[Bingo]
Oh goodness!
Aren't I at a disadvantage?
The older the item...
No matter how old the item is
I was only born in the '90s.
This is a little troubling.
All my old items are back at home.
I need to go home.
[Who else got the mission box?]
[The classic wild card,
Lee Chun Hee.]
[What's this?]
[Blank]
What do I do?
[The weakling of villains,
Kim Hee Won.]
[What do you use this for?]
You want me to film
something with this?
I don't have any items...
[I can't just make up something...]
[All the Running Man members
got the mission boxes, too!]
We need to bring a nostalgic item.
I wish there was a
picture of Suk Jin and I...
[Think all the way back
with your special things!]
[What are their legacies?]
[The Legacy]
Today, there are three guests that
are sharing joyful memories with you.
Who are they?
Oh!
Who is it?
[Lee Chun Hee is here!]
It's still hot!
[Welcome!]
[Fashion point, leather jacket.]
Does every actor wear
clothes like this?
Kwang Soo, you look cool today!
- You're an actor!
- You've surpass the weather!
[The two fashion people are alike.]
- I see him so often.
- He's family.
Of course.
You've gotten a lot older.
You aged, too!
You look older than
when I saw you in the countryside.
How long ago was that?
It was seven years ago.
[Just then, the variety show
blue chip has arrived!]
[Weakling Kim Hee Won.]
It's going to be fun today!
[Let's give you a lift!]
He's that light?
[Lift! Lift!]
[He's as light as a feather!]
[This is his reputation?]
[Our cute brother.]
You're so weak!
He's paper thin!
He's so weak!
[Out of energy]
He's the weakest.
Weakling!
"Don't come!"
Go away!
[Please don't come here!]
"Don't do that!"
Why are you only cheating me...
It just means that we're close.
I only met you today.
[His grudge hidden
behind his weak side.]
We need to have an arm wrestling match.
That would be fun!
[Whose voice is this?]
[Park Bo Young is here!]
[Automatic seal clap]
[Oh my Bo Young!]
[They're treating her differently...]
[Refreshing]
You filmed a movie
with Kwang Soo, right?
- Yes.
- She's the lead role.
I'm a supporting role.
He's the lead role.
The fish head is the lead role.
He's been saying this
since last week...
Today's theme is
"The Throwback Legacy Race."
[Legacy?]
You'll be going to locations in Seoul
that are interesting and unknown.
And you need to gather as many
throwback legacies as possible.
Before you do that, you received
a mission last night, right?
We asked you to
bring a personal item.
- It was so hard.
- Me, too.
[They're revealing the
ten different items.]
- What's with the suit?
- This is 20 years old.
- Really?
- Yes.
I got it as soon as
I became a comedian.
One of my senior
comedians told me
"Now that you've become a celebrity,
shouldn't you at least have a nice suit?"
And it's a brand-name product.
[What is Jae Suk's memory?]
Hello, I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
Running Man told us
to bring a nostalgic item.
My item is 20 years old.
After I became a comedian
I bought it with my mother's card.
Was it ten months or 12 months
interest-free that I got it for?
I paid a small amount per month
for a really long time.
This is the suit that I got.
I used to wear a lot, back in the day.
This is my nostalgic item.
I will bring
this item.
[A 24-year-old suit.]
[Three-button suits were
the trend in the '90s.]
Hello, this is Park Bo Young.
I'm already at a disadvantage.
What do I do...
All the items that I've kept
are all back at home in Chungbuk.
And I don't have the
time to go back home.
So I'm at my newly moved-in house.
I still have unpacked boxes.
[Should I open my
memory-filled boxes?]
My fans have sent me those.
This is "A Werewolf Boy."
This is the film continuity book.
This is how it is drawn.
That was "A Werewolf Boy."
This is
"Scandal Makers"
it was actually called
"Three generation scandals."
This is probably the oldest one...
My album?
I have it...
[Let's see!]
[Eureka!]
Ta-da!
Do you see what's written here?
It says 1991, March 31.
That's me.
That is me.
Hi, Mom.
The picture of me that was
taken on March 31, 1991...
The baby in your arms
getting baptized
- is me, right?
- Yeah.
- That's me, right?
- Yes.
- Thank you, Mother.
- Of course.
I just called my mom.
That is me.
- An old photo?
- Are you getting baptized?
When she was baptized!
[One year old]
Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
I am back home
in Namyangju.
It's a traditional upper garment
I received from my Dad.
It's 2 in the morning
and because my Dad just got up
he will say a few words,
behind the camera.
Yes, so please explain this.
You wore that when you were born.
Your mom kept it...
The viewers are watching,
so please speak with honorifics.
Oops, sorry.
This is the first thing you wore
when your were born.
Please say Kwang Soo...
Oh, should I?
Are you Kwang Soo?
This is for the viewers.
Kwang Soo was
born on July 14, 1985
and this is the first clothing
he wore that day.
Mom kept it, well.
I want to thank my parents who
looked all over the house for this.
And I will bring this
precious item in this box.
Thank you!
[The traditional garment is 30 years old.]
[The first shirt Kwang Soo
wore as a baby.]
Next is Jong Kook!
- I brought...
- What's that?
- This is so old!
- It's a Walkman!
This is Aiwa!
Everyone had one of these.
[Fascinated]
It was such a
dream to have this.
This slim design.
- It's the new design.
- Why are you wearing it?
This made my hands free.
How did they make it so thin?
[It fits inside the pocket.]
[It's so fascinating to watch.]
- You can reverse it, right?
- Yes.
There's even a remote.
Wow!
This is awesome!
There's a remote!
This is so comfortable.
This is so nostalgic!
I listened to the demos
during my Turbo days.
[A 20-year-old Walkman.]
[Ha Ha's throwback item]
There is a toy in here that
I played with as a child.
My parents gave it to me as a gift.
Dream is playing with it now.
Dream, go over there.
Your feet are showing.
It's this one, right here.
It's quite old, but it's
filled with memories.
And now, it's Dream's toy.
This toy is my nostalgic item.
This truck.
Here, Dream.
- This is meaningful.
- This is super old!
[A 32-year-old toy
is now Dream's.]
Hello, I'm Lee Chun Hee.
The thing I find to be nostalgic
is one of my scripts.
I have scripts on this side.
This is my script for our
upcoming movie "Mutant."
[Eureka!]
This was my first movie, "Ice Rain."
How long ago was this?
How long ago was it?
[It was his first movie
with his aspiration.]
This is the evidence.
This was on November 23, 2002.
This is my schedule.
"Ice Rain" from 2002.
I found the script to "Ice Rain."
You can't throw this one away.
[His first movie script,
from 13 years ago.]
Hello, this is Song Ji Hyo.
I received the mission,
last night.
I found my nostalgic item while
I was talking with my siblings.
I will show it to you now.
It is this!
[What's her nostalgic item?]
[The nostalgic hero!
Bioman!]
Bioman!
[A hero series that dominated
children's video market]
[collaborated with
"Freshman" in the early '90s.]
[Everyone transform!]
Space warriors, to declare peace.
Aiming towards the Earth
to conquer the devil.
[The space heroes' show is over.]
So, he is my proof...
[Embarrassed]
as well as my younger brother.
- For the viewers.
- Hello.
Tell them how much we watched these
videos and how much we loved it.
She used to hit me a lot.
No, I didn't hit him.
Anyway, this is my nostalgic item.
Bioman!
[Bioman is love!]
[25 years old]
This is a throwback!
This is from when I won
"The Battle for The Strongest."
When we went to Europe...
Just forget about that already.
This is the oldest item!
It's 150 years old!
But you bought this.
Where's he proof
that it's 150 years old?
The store owner told me.
And I even texted the
main PD last night!
You have to count the year you bought it.
That's only two years ago!
Just say it's 50 years...
- We'll say 15 years.
- We'll compromise with 15 years.
15 years.
We moved a lot
so there wasn't much.
The year's written here, 2002.
[A hand printing of
his son, Hyun Woo.]
He got his hands printed
as soon as he was born.
You printed his hands?
- It's cute.
- It's amazing!
What is it?
It's picture of him
when he was young!
How old is this picture?
It was back in 1991...
I was in a musical from
April 27 to May 1s.
Peter Pan!
A children's musical.
[They got year-long hourglasses
equal to the time of their items.]
We'll give you hourglasses.
Please hand your items in.
There are four
one-year hourglasses.
[Team Bo Young, total: 119 years.]
[Team Ji Hyo, total: 101 years.]
We will win!
[Some crazy one-on-one missions!]
[No pride, no reputation!]
[They struggle to receive
the special legacies.]
[Starting now!]
I haven't seen this in a while.
Like the wind.
This is the first
mission of the race.
It's the popular old
commercial quiz.
- Yeah!
- Oh!
Nice, nice!
We will give a ten year
hourglass to the winning team.
And also...
The quiz is an all-kill method.
It could end with five questions.
This is great!
- This is the first category.
- Okay.
- Dialogue.
- Dialogue is hard.
- Me... really?
- You're pretty old.
[Really?]
[Mr. Capable, Jong Kook is first.]
Gary, Gary.
[Gary is first for Team Ji Hyo.]
[Wait... Gary's going up?]
Wait, come back.
I'll do it, come back.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
[The two men encounter
in the battlefield.]
[Who is this?]
[We meet again.]
[Hmph!]
[The battle for their
pride starts now.]
[Slap!]
[Once a rival, forever a rival.]
[If I can win, I'll chase you down
to the end of the Earth!]
One, two, three!
[Their battle starts now.]
I hate losing to him!
[I will win this time,
no matter what.]
We'll be precise,
since it's a dialogue.
This is the first question.
Who is that?
I know this ad!
You know this, right?
- I got it, I pressed it!
- They didn't even ask yet!
[What is Jun Ji Hyun's
final line in this ad?]
Okay, put your hands up!
She's pretty.
I know this one!
[They both rang the
bell at the same time.]
[Gary's hand]
[Gary's hand pressed it first!]
[Agitated]
I rang it!
[Will he get the right
answer on the first try?]
[I can't lose like this...]
"I get off here."
Pardon?
[I don't think that's it.]
Wait!
[Oh my!]
[This time Ha Ha rang the bell!]
Dong Hun, it's your chance!
"I'm getting off here."
[Is this the answer?]
- That's right!
- Okay!
[Ha Ha won!
Team Bo Young earned ten years!]
You got it wrong!
- What did Gary say?
- "I get off here."
It's their first encounter!
"I get off here" is so stuffy!
I would say that.
[Correct answer]
"I'm getting off here."
[Disappointed]
Gary!
That was close!
The next category are jingles.
That's fine, you know a lot of songs.
Jae Suk's going up!
[Shall I go up this time?]
He has the most
knowledge on jingles!
He knows too many.
He knows way too many.
Let's go!
You need to sing
this jingle, correctly.
This isn't easy!
This is the first one.
What are the lyrics
to this commercial?
He hits the wall!
This ad was popular with
Lee Duk Hwa's acting
and was remade by Kwon Sang Woo
and Lee Hyo Ri 12 years later.
This is the question.
You have to sing the entire
jingle from beginning to end.
Now, you came up to me
and call me.
[He's doing well.]
Stylish men, stylish women
Oh, "Torai"
(He changed it from "Try,")
[Will he get the correct answer?]
[Yoo Jae Suk got it correct!]
[Sad vs. happy]
[They both earned ten years.]
This is nothing!
I know all the jingles.
[I'm the master of commercials.]
- Did you only watch TV?
- Yes.
All I did was watch TV.
I didn't you would
be this specific.
The next category is
picking the odd ad out.
Bo Young, you go!
It's alright!
I don't know any of them!
I've only heard of the
"I'm getting off here."
I only know that line
- "I'm getting off here."
- Really?
- I didn't know any of the other ones.
- Oh no, Bo Young...
This is the next question.
What was this
commercial advertising?
Oh no!
[What was this
commercial advertising?]
I've never seen this...
I'm getting confused.
I know this one!
What ad is this for?
This is all of it?
Bo Young, press it!
- I don't know...
- Just try!
Mouthwash?
Mouthwash.
[Now, it's Jae Suk's try!]
I was a little bit confused.
Isn't this for a mobile carrier?
A mobile carrier?
[Will his winning streak continue?]
[Oh no]
[Good job, Bo Young.]
It's okay Bo Young!
[Team Ji Hyo earned 20 years.]
[How did he know that?]
[The correct answer]
[Why did my phone have to ring, now?]
[Punch!]
[Korea's communication channel,
Digital 011.]
[This is pretty nostalgic...]
I can't believe that watching
TV all my life paid off!
- Wow!
- How is he so good?
[My mom told me not to,
but it's helping me so much now.]
[Lee Chun Hee vs. Lee Kwang Soo.]
I'm going to win!
This is another jingle.
I wish there was one before
Kwang Soo was born.
Is it "From the sky"?
It's that one!
You know this one, right?
[We will show the
viewers the answer, first.]
Pick stars from the sky
pick the moon from the sky.
I put them in your hands.
Beautiful days
those lovely eyes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
From the beginning to end.
Start.
Pick stars from the sky
I gave them to you.
Wrong!
You were so cute.
[Is he trying to
serenade somebody?]
What song is that?
[Frustrated]
I know this one!
You know it!
Pick stars from the sky,
pick the moon from the sky.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
[That guy!]
[You can't skip half of the song...]
You haven't changed!
I gave them to you.
That's not it!
Pick stars from the sky,
pick the moon from the sky.
[Vocal twins]
Pick the moon from the sky.
How are you going to give it?
I give them, respectfully.
[A silly answer!]
[The jingle is going nowhere.]
They look like twins,
from the back.
[Innocent brain brothers!]
They're actually the old fool and young
fool on our SBS Sunday variety shows.
What do you mean fool?
[Old fool and young fool.]
You continued his
"Family's Outing" legacy!
No I didn't!
Kwang Soo!
You give it to them...
But where?
I give them in your basket.
I put them in your hamper.
Hey!
What do you mean hamper?
[There is too little to choose]
[between the fool duo.]
They understand each other!
Just tell them the first verse.
- In your hands.
- Oh!
Beautiful days
those lovely...
in your eyes...
Hey!
Lee Chun Hee!
Pick stars from the sky
In your basket...
pick the moon from the sky.
He doesn't know the rest.
I put them in your hands.
And then?
[Will he get it?]
[No way...]
Beautiful days
those lovely eyes.
That's right!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
[Lee Chun Hee wins!]
[Agitated]
Why do you like baskets so much?
[This is the old fool's potential!]
We lost to hamper.
[Am I the biggest fool...]
Go Hee Won!
[Kim Hee Won vs. Kim Jong Kook.]
[What's the dialogue in this ad?]
It's Fin.K.L!
Just drink some water.
I remember this!
That hurts!
It's not water.
The drink that fills me up
is when you are missing [blank].
I remember watching it,
but I don't know what they said.
Just say anything!
I will drink some, too!
[Oh my god!]
What are you saying!
"Let's eat together."
This is so frustrating!
This is more frustrating
than Chun Hee!
[I'm frustrated, too...]
"Do you only live on water?"
That's right.
This is right.
[Team Ji Hyo was exterminated
with Hee Won's loss.]
[Team Ji Hyo earned 30 points,
Team Bo Young earned 50 points.]
Currently, Team Ji Hyo has
a total of 131 years.
Yes.
Team Bo Young has
a total of 169 years.
[Find five legacies in Seoul.]
[Each team has to do missions
one on one and earn legacies.]
[The museum in the city is alive.]
[A war of legacy in an
area of history and tradition.]
[Which team will earn more?]
It arrived!
They sent the address.
Gongdeok-dong Mapogu, in Seoul.
I can already feel the tradition.
["B" rice cake shop, "Ch"
restaurant, "S" barbershop]
["J" tailor,
"Y" oriental medical clinic.]
We'll go the medical clinic
- and check our health.
- I volunteered.
[I need to get back in shape]
I knew it, but I waited a little bit.
I listened to that jingle a lot,
back in the day.
[You know I did that,
just for laughs.]
My family meets once a week
to sing that song.
Really?
Sing it now.
[He got caught.]
I'm already hungry thinking
about the rice cake shop.
I'm so hungry.
The rice cake shop that we're
going to is 44 years old, right?
It's probably really traditional.
Yes, I have it.
Thank you.
We're almost here.
Please stop over there.
[Wow]
I feel the tradition.
It looks like...
[Where's the mission site?]
[89 years of tradition, and was run
through three generations.]
This entire alley
way is traditional!
[It's like time stopped on the
inside of the building.]
We'll be heading in!
[The objects are telling
stories of the past.]
[This is Kwang Soo vs.
Chun Hee's battle site.]
Hello!
[Director Lee Nam Yeol, who is]
[the third generation
running the shop.]
This is like from a movie!
How old is this shop?
89 years old?
That's amazing.
- So, three generations?
- Wow, three generations.
Could we look around, first?
[Looks around]
This is a throwback.
This is it!
I used to wash my hair like this.
This is what I was talking about.
[It brings back his
childhood memories!]
Isn't this a briquette stove?
[It's rare to see this kind
of stove these days.]
[While they're at it,
the artisan shows his treasures.]
This is 100 years old.
This was cut before,
so I repaired it.
This is 100 years old?
We were using this since
the second world war.
It's that old?
It's better than
what they make now.
- You can't buy this any longer.
- No, they don't make it.
[A shop straight out of 89 years ago,
Sung Woo Barber Shop]
[They stayed in one location
through three generations]
[Bu Heung rice cake shop]
[Opened in 1972, and continued
for two generations.]
Since 1972.
[They still make rice cakes
the traditional way.]
[Ji Hyo and Bo Young arrive
at the historical rice cake shop.]
Hello!
This rice cake shop
opened in 1972?
Yes.
I wasn't even born.
[Delicious looking rice cakes catch
their eyes as soon as they enter.]
[They've stayed in one town
without changing the taste.]
You've been making rice cakes
for the whole time?
- No, my mom started this shop.
- Oh, your mother?
[Let's taste it first!]
[How will the traditional
rice cake taste?]
It's so good!
I love it.
They start watching
how the rice cakes are made here.
[The secret is to pound
rice cake in a stone mortar.]
You need to steady hands
to make it on time.
[Fascinating!]
[When the pounded batter goes in]
[it becomes bar rice cake.]
[A masterpiece with
44 years of history comes out!]
[Of course, they're eating it.]
[It makes her head tilt.]
I've been eating fake
rice cakes the whole time.
- Isn't this good?
- It's really good!
[Opened in 1972, the rice cake shop's
been in business for two generations.]
[A restaurant that's been handed down
through four generations, Cheong Jin Ok]
[It's known as the birthplace of
Haejang soup (hangover soup).]
[They can feel the history
at the entrance.]
[It opened in 1937]
You moved the location?
Did you take over your family business?
You're the third generation owner?
Can we come in?
[First time showing the kitchen
on a variety show.]
- It's an honor for us!
- Bones!
Is this for the ox bone broth?
Yes, they're ox bone, tripe, and organs.
And you boil it all the time?
We boil it for 24 hours to make broth.
[After 24 hours of cooking]
[the best hangover soup
with 78 years of history is ready.]
- I want to taste it now.
- Tell me some of your regular customers.
Mr. Kim Gu used to come.
Mr. Kim Gu?
(Leader of Korea independence movement)
[The soul of our Nation, Kim Gu]
And President Yoon Po Sun.
[and even the second
President of South Korea!]
[This place is like a witness to history.]
Amazing!
We need to take a picture.
This is the kitchen that
made food for Mr. Kim Gu!
[With their hangover soup,
they have mass customers for 78 years.]
[Meet the traditional hand acupuncture
at Yuil Oriental Medical Clinic.]
- The aroma of medical herbs!
- It does!
The whole street smells like it.
It's been 90 years.
Maybe it's soaked into the street.
[The only place that still uses the
traditional hand acupuncture method.]
Even the building looks like
it's historical.
[They fights against illnesses here
as same as 92 years ago.]
[At the very place...]
[they're experiencing
the hand acupuncture.]
[Stomping his feet]
I want to get
treated with gold needles.
What's that?
[A bigger and sharper needle
for Mr. Capable's muscles]
Oh no.
[It's more painful
than I thought.]
[You know how I felt now.]
What does it have to do with our mission?
For your health...
[A secret formula for good health
that's been handed down for 71 years.]
[The pride of 100 years of
experience, Jongro Tailor Shop]
[Jongro Tailor shop]
[100 years old. A thriving store
since the Enlightenment period.]
Hello!
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin arrive.]
- Are we at the 100-year-old tailor shop?
- Yes, you are.
Hello. Mr. Lee.
[Master Artisan Lee Kyung Joo]
- How many generations was it carried on?
- Three generations.
Will it be carried on
to the fourth generation?
Yes, it will.
- So your son is getting ready for that?
- Yes.
- Great-great-grandfather?
- My grandfather.
- And then my father.
- Your father.
- This is the picture from...
- When the store was first opened.
The location was here?
No, it was next to Bosingak before.
That's amazing!
Passing down the family business is hard.
It's been 100 years.
They should keep this store.
What Mater Artisan makes
are pieces of art.
[He can measure with his eyes.]
How about his waist?
What's Gwon Yeol's size?
It looks like 40 inches.
[Gwon Yeol's camera is shaking.]
I think he's right.
Can we measure?
- It's not 40 inches!
- Let's measure him.
He was on a diet to lose weight
but it failed and
he gained more weight.
- I do think it's 40 inches.
- No way.
[Measuring Gwon Yeol's waist]
What's your size, then?
Be honest and tell me.
- It's 40 inches!
- It's more than 40 inches!
Oh, it's exactly 40 inches!
Look!
Read the tape!
- What happened to you?
- No, it's not.
The measuring tape says it's 40.
What do you mean no?
40 is your size.
He just measured you!
The pants you're wearing
are actually too small.
[Anyway, Jae Suk and Suk Jin
arrived at the mission site, too.]
I didn't think you would
actually cut my hair.
Don't worry, I won't cut a lot.
I'll make you handsome.
I'm only trimming a little.
No one can tell.
When it's done, will I look like you?
No, you're not going to
have the same hair style.
- I'll get a taste of what's to come...
- I know, I know.
I'll come next time.
I want to come with my dad.
[Interesting]
Is this all my hair?
[Piled up]
It's not much.
[I can't even call it a haircut.]
Don't worry.
I need to keep this hairstyle
for my work!
[Surprised]
[He doesn't stop cutting his hair.]
You're the first celebrity
I'm giving a haircut.
It's an honor!
I'm serious.
I don't usually cut celebrity's hair.
You're the first one.
[He's even going to wash his hair!]
This is the best part.
[What is that?]
What's this?
It's apple cider vinegar.
Pardon me?
Vinegar?
It's a natural hair conditioner.
[Mr. Artisan...]
[You don't have to do my hair...]
[He's getting a shaving service instead.]
[He looks like a mannequin.]
Don't make him laugh, Kwang Soo.
[Getting the haircut was way better.]
Oh, it hurts!
- Excuse me...
- It takes less than 30 seconds.
Now, you can wash your face.
Thank you for your hard work!
You look different, Chun Hee.
[Ta-da!]
You look nicer.
It feels like I'm born again.
Of course, I have a personal preference
but I guess this
hair style is more popular.
When I was young,
I've always wanted to shave like this
- when I saw my dad doing it.
- He told me that.
You need to go against each other.
[Finally, the battle begins!]
The winner will get
92 years' worth of
79 years' worth of
44 years' worth of hourglass.
44 years' worth?
[It's a good chance
to add hourglasses.]
79 years' worth?
That's a lot!
Wait a minute, 100 years...
I think Suk Jin went for
the 100 years' worth match.
Jae Suk went there!
Oh no!
Suk Jin went to the place
that's 100 years old.
[At that moment, at the tailor...]
One, two!
[Ta-da!]
[They look like characters
from "Kington."]
They don't really suit us.
He's a master artisan
- but he didn't make these for us!
- Aren't these suits for someone else?
I can tell the owner of this suit
isn't that tall.
The pants should be little longer, right?
You're at the tailor shop
that's 100 years old.
Fedora, tie clip, and
cuff links, and shoes.
You're fully dressed up.
This is the first mission.
Starting now, take off
everything you're wearing.
[Take off everything?]
- Take off everything you're wearing.
- Take off?
This is what you do.
Take off everything except the
white t-shirt and underpants.
- What about the hat?
- You need to take it off, too.
From now on, take off everything.
Ger ready...
[This match is 100 years' worth!]
[I must win!]
Start!
[In a hurry]
[Jae Suk doesn't hesitate
to take his clothes off.]
[A button stuck to the tie clip.]
I finally got it off.
[Jae Suk is about to take off his shirt.]
Calm down.
Don't be in a hurry.
[When Jae Suk takes the lead,
Big Nose start playing dirty.]
[Of course, they start a messy war.]
I need to take 100 years!
[Hop, hop]
[Grasshopper takes off everything
with his hopping skills.]
[He only needs to push the timer.]
[I can't let you go!]
What are you doing?
This might look really strange!
[A disgraceful scene]
[Jae Suk is done undressing.]
The first round's winner is Jae Suk.
My opponent isn't Jong Kook.
What a relief!
[He's already exhausted.]
For the second round
- wear everything you took off.
- I knew it!
They're all over the floor.
This is really tiring!
Same as before, you'll start
when I tell you to start.
Ready...
[Two consecutive victories?
Or will it even the score?]
[The second round begins.]
Begin!
[He kicked Suk Jin's pants!]
[A nude battle]
[A battle of the century
to gain a century!]
[Let's go all the way!]
[All of a sudden,
they fight out of ring.]
You'll have to walk out
without wearing pants.
[Jae Suk succeeds at wearing pants.]
[And he's wearing his shirt.]
[Come on, pants!]
[He takes the pants
and walks out the door.]
[Going to an office right in front.]
Excuse me, can I leave
this here for a moment?
Where are my clothes?
Where's my jacket?
[It's at the office with your pants.]
It's outside?
[This is my chance!]
[Big-nose is using the timer
as a shield but fails.]
[He got caught by the wire.]
[I'll be right back.]
- Are you heading to the bathroom?
- No.
[I'm getting my pants back]
Hello!
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry.
This is the wrong place!
[Jae Suk is almost done.]
I think I'm done.
Where did one of my cuff links go?
[He found it at the corner.]
[I can't lose it again.]
[The only thing left for Jae Suk
is the hat.]
[If that's the case...]
This drives me nuts.
[He steals his hat.]
[Big-nose succeeded at it
by a hair's breadth.]
Since Suk Jin pushed the timer first,
he's the winner for the second round.
[Current score 1:1]
Don't tell us to take it off again.
[It's so hard to win 100 years' worth.]
What are we suppose to do now?
From now on, you'll start the mission
to win the legacy from this shop.
Pile the rice cake you just
cut as high as possible.
[Pile them?]
Seriously...
I was wondering why they
wanted us to cut them.
- Why did I cut like a food?
- Get ready.
You need to put them down.
I'm so sorry.
Ready, set, go!
[It begins openly and squarely!]
[Both of them start with
placing big pieces at the bottom.]
If you're an architect
that's watching this show
please don't forget that the
foundation work is really important.
So, the building won't fall.
With good materials.
[It's not so easy.]
[Shake, shake]
Can you please stand up for me?
I'm really desperate now.
Please help me for once!
I'm begging you.
[Ji Hyo's tower is getting taller.]
I'm in trouble!
Ji Hyo!
[Roaring of a lion]
[A scary attack with sound wave]
Ji Hyo.
[Please let me win once.]
[As soon as Ji Hyo's tower
becomes higher than hers...]
- Ji Hyo!
- Don't do that!
[A spurt at the last minute]
Oh, no!
I can't tell who won!
[They look pretty similar.]
We'll measure it.
It's eight centimeters.
Could you please measure that side?
That side is slightly higher.
[Whose tower will be higher?]
It's eight and a half centimeters.
Park Bo Young wins!
[Team Bo Young acquires 44 years.]
[In the mean time]
I can do this very fast.
In the basket, there are
100 pairs of spoons and chopsticks.
You need to sort them out.
Long time ago, I learned how from Gary.
I taught him how to sort
and put them in paper wrappers.
I used to do that really fast.
I learned from cleaning these
and everything else from Gary.
But he raised a tiger.
[What are you talking about?]
[Teacher Gary vs. Pupil Ha Ha]
The one to finish first will win.
[A battle between a teacher and a pupil]
[Teacher Gary starts
sorting out in a flash.]
[Student Ha Ha doesn't give an inch.]
[Neck and neck]
I can't lose this time, Ha Ha!
I've learned from you,
but I got really good!
I still work at my restaurant.
[I'll show you my reserved strength!]
[Ha Ha's new standing strategy.]
I'm almost done!
Oh, no a chopstick went the wrong way!
[While Gary made a mistake]
Gary!
See what I can do?
This is frustrating.
- Ha Ha wins!
- Yeah!
You know I changed my business...
and that's why it happened.
Let's do something like
pouring sauces in a dish.
- That's my expertise!
- Is that?
[Team Bo Young acquires 79 years.]
[Kwang Soo and Chun Hee's mission is]
Move shaving cream with your face.
[How can I move it
with my face?]
[Without using hands,
move more shaving cream and win.]
[Chun Hee starts first.]
[What are they doing?]
Wow, he's actually
carrying it with his face.
[I want to move even 1 gram.]
I feel sorry for him.
I'm sorry, Chun Hee.
Chun Hee, you're working
so hard for the movie.
I'll do it harder!
Kwang Soo, I want to win!
[His mouth is full of cream.]
[He's doing his best while crying.]
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- Don't eat it!
- I'm hungry.
[He's doing his best until the end.]
You can stop now.
You have a lot of cream
in your nose.
[Chun Hee's record is 26.5 grams.]
We're doing so much stuff
even more than a beauty show.
Haircut, styling
skin care, shave
facial wash with shaving cream!
It's like you're getting a whitening care.
[It's Kwang Soo's turn.]
Ready, set, go!
[I'm going to win,
no matter what!]
[I'm satisfying myself for the team!]
[He's amazing!]
This is Running Man, Master Artisan!
Thank you, Master Artisan!
The haircut
[and he gets a shaving
cream facial massage.]
Kwang Soo, that's enough.
You win.
I want more shaving cream!
[Time is up!]
[Spooky]
Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
[Kwang Soo's record is 75.2 grams.]
You moved three times more than him.
[I won, but I'm not that excited...]
- You've worked so hard!
- Chun Hee!
[We thought you'd use your chin...]
[Team Bo Young acquired 89 years.]
Since, each of you won once.
We'll start the third round.
Connect hangers
and keep them balanced.
You'll lose if the balance breaks.
[Rue: Take turns connecting hangers.
You'll lose if the hanger gets tilted.]
Until when should we continue?
If it reaches to the floor,
you can start a new one on the side.
[They'll lose if it loses
its balance for a second.]
This looks unstable.
[Jae Suk succeeded.]
[Suk Jin's turn]
It's an interesting game.
[Big-nose succeeded, as well.]
Start a new one...
[At that moment]
[Big-nose's hanger loses its balance]
I won!
[Team Ji Hyo, Jae Suk wins.]
[I can't believe this!]
That was so close!
I could have won this game!
[Team Ji Hyo acquires 100 years.]
The mission at the
Oriental Medical Clinic is
"Here is your herbal tonic."
Squeeze the boiled herbs
to get tonic.
The one who gets more liquid will win.
You know when you squeeze your laundry...
I lost against Suk Jin at arm wrestling
because I kept squeezing my towel.
[I will not lose today!]
[The mission begins!]
[Squeeze]
[I'm not the same old weak Kim Hee Won!]
[Unfortunately, his opponent
is Monster Kim Jong Kook.]
[Body vs. Mind]
[Their close match!]
[Victory is mine!]
[I will prove that I'm not a weak man...]
It's so hot!
[Even one more drop is fine!]
[With bare hand?]
That's a foul play!
Now stop!
[What will be the result?]
It's really hard to squeeze this.
- I think I won.
- No, mine is higher.
I'll put it on the scale.
Please move your hands away.
I have more, right?
It's 245 grams!
[Jong Kook won by three grams.]
I didn't think there would be
such a small difference.
[It's a reversal that he did
as good as Mr. Capable.]
[Team Bo Young acquires 92 years.]
[The winner gets a special
legacy from each place.]
[Team Bo Young acquires 304 years!]
[On the contrary, Team Ji Hyo
acquires 100 years.]
This is a rice cake
from a 44-year-old...
[Jae Suk acquires an old invoice
that was issued in 1940.]
This rice cake looks so delicious!
[Jong Kook acquires a scale for
medicinal herbs that's 92 years old.]
[Kwang Soo gets manual hair clippers
that's been used for 56 years.]
[Ha Ha gets a contract note
when they moved the restaurant in 1959.]
[Bo Young gets bar rice cake
that was made with their secret recipe.]
[At that moment]
[the members receive a message
about the final site.]
It's the final site!
National Folk Museum of Korea.
1-1 Sejong-ro, Jongno-gu.
[New - 37 Samcheong-ro, Jongno-gu]
[What mission is waiting for them?]
[National Folk Museum of Korea]
I'll tell you about the final mission.
"Capture the nostalgic legacy,"
and there are two ways to win.
One way is that you collect all the
nostalgic items your opponents brought.
Then you can put them in
your team's store window.
Let's find them all
and end the mission.
We need to find as much as possible.
I think there should be one in here.
- Gary, did you find any?
- I'm still searching.
[Team Ji Hyo is doing their
best to find the item.]
[The sound of a bell is approaching.]
I need to hide first.
There are two ways to win.
The other method is by eliminating
all the opponents' name tags.
Isn't this too obvious?
- What kind of rule is that?
- You're telling us to give up.
The attacking team will wear bells
and oust the opponents.
Each round is 20 minutes.
And you'll take turns attacking
for each round.
- Searching is a better plan, right?
- We can't even eliminate them.
[Team Ji Hyo is on defense first.]
There's nowhere we can hide.
- Look, there's no space!
- Let's get out of here.
[Whistle]
Let's go!
- You want to check the outside?
- They're scattered.
I think I'll check the outside.
See you!
- Enjoy!
- Good luck!
There's no space for them to run away.
Let's eliminate at least one.
[Team Bo Young is relaxed.]
[Whistle]
That's the sound of whistle, right?
What do I do?
[The real race starts.]
What's with the whistle?
Attacking team is on their way.
We're the attacking team?
No, the attacking team
is coming to get us.
[Big-nose starts attacking slowly.]
It'll be really frustrating
when they hear the bell.
Hey, I know you're frustrated.
- Bo Young, scream if you see anyone.
- Yes, Kwang Soo.
They're probably
searching for the items.
[Grasshopper and Gary
are quietly searching.]
Kwang Soo!
[I found them!]
- Kwang Soo!
- What is it?
- How do we get there?
- Where?
[Bo Young saw Gary and Jae Suk
through the glass wall.]
They saw us!
[Run!]
Don't go that way!
[Gary hides in the corner.]
Come near me!
[He's carefully hiding his VJ.]
[Kwang Soo passes Gary.]
[Bo Young passes, too.]
Are you sure?
[Bo Young is about to
search the auditorium.]
[Blank Ji and Chun Hee
are inside the dress room.]
Gary!
[Surprised]
[Her sweet and scary voice]
Gary!
[She's rushing to the dress room.]
[We've got caught!]
[They run out through the door
on the other side.]
Kwang Soo!
[What a loud voice
from a tiny figure!]
I'm going to catch them!
[Running at full speed]
It's Chun Hee!
[Mr. Capable was waiting
in front of the auditorium.]
- We need to catch him!
- Where did he go?
Wow, that was close!
[I'm going to catch them!]
[Time left until the shift]
[Elder Kim Hee Won
is searching for the items in the dark.]
[No nostalgic item will be here...]
This is it!
It's Suk Jin's item!
[It's Hyun Woo's golden hands.]
[He still needs to put it
in their store window.]
[Someone came.]
Where should I put it?
Should I put it in here?
This is safety zone.
[They can't enter the safety zone.]
Don't you need to put it over there?
[Yellow is Team Bo young's color.]
Bring it on!
Why would you want to
put your item there?
[Such a poor guy]
Come at me!
I can throw it, then.
[He's ready to block.]
[Bo Young came out to attack.]
- I'm not supposed to put it here?
- No, you should put it in your store.
He might start running all of a sudden.
Be careful, don't look anywhere else.
Just focus on Hee Won.
[Yoo Jae Suk appears at the moment.]
Jae Suk, catch this!
[He faked it.]
[He loses Ha Ha and Bo Young easily.]
This is upsetting!
I put one item here!
Jae Suk!
Let's take a break.
[Jae Suk enters the safety zone.]
It's so frustrating!
After 20 minutes, we'll be on offense.
This is the safety zone.
We can attack them after 20 minutes.
[Is he planning to stay here?]
I was just touching it.
[He might be the weakest,
but he's an expert teaser.]
[Ha Ha is under Hee Won's control.]
[Time left until the shift]
[Gary was hiding.]
[She must be gone by now.]
Are they gone?
[He's going back to search.]
We need to oust at least one of them.
He's coming this way.
Hide again!
[He's hiding from Mr. Capable.]
[He hides behind the garbage bins.]
[He's not going to come all the way here.]
Kwang Soo!
[Mr. Capable is looking for Kwang Soo,
but he's getting close to Gary.]
[You better hide.]
Is this area included, too?
[The scary sound is approaching.]
[He's not going to check
the garbage, is he?]
[He is!]
[It's suspicious...]
[I found you!]
[I caught you, Kang Gary!]
I just thought it's a good spot to hide,
and Gary is hiding here.
I'm sorry, Gary!
Gary is ousted,
Gary is ousted!
[I didn't think I would get
caught behind the garbage bin!]
Gary is ousted,
Gary is ousted!
[Team Ji Hyo found out
by the announcement.]
Our team member is ousted...
They'll be start attacking us,
when we have to shift roles.
- This is really tiring.
- We need to start hiding.
Bo Young, take a break first.
- We'll get going.
- Good idea.
We'll be in trouble,
if our time's up here.
I think Jong Kook...
[Whistle]
[Temporary pause]
[It's time to shift roles!]
- Temporary pause!
- We're in trouble.
[Mr. Capable stands still.]
Oh, it's our turn to attack!
[Switch offense an defense!]
[Offense-Team Bo Young]
[Defense-Team Ji Hyo]
[Offense-Team Ji Hyo]
[Defense-Team Bo Young]
We're in big trouble.
Let's eliminate one
that's near here.
We'll attack Ha Ha first.
Or Suk Jin, one of them.
[Team Bo Young has to
search for the nostalgic items.]
- Bo Young.
- Yes, Suk Jin?
[By the way, where did Kwang Soo go?]
Please come out, Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo is pretending
that he's one of the staff.]
How can you reveal my plan?
It'll be okay
if we stay together.
Wait for me, Ha Ha!
[Even Chun Hee has fierce eyes now.]
10 seconds before it resumes!
Bo Young, you need to open the door.
Even if they go inside,
we can still catch them.
[There's no permanent
fugitives or chasers!]
Two!
[The shifting roles race, starts!]
[Team Bo Young is running
away in outrageous speed!]
- This won't do!
- Come over here!
[It's their turn, but they're walking?]
[They seemed like
they would catch Ha Ha.]
[We have a plan.]
[Chun Hee, start the operation!]
- Hurry up, Chun Hee!
- Kim Jong Kook!
[Jong Kook is running away,
Chun Hee is chasing him!]
[And Kwang Soo is passing by!]
[Team Ji Hyo's only target Mr. Capable!]
[Jong Kook, I won't let you escape!]
[While Chun Hee is holding Jong Kook]
[Hee Won joins them.]
Hee Won, hurry!
He's off the wall now.
- Eliminate his name tag!
- I can't!
[Mr. Capable is not letting them
rip his name tag.]
[Will they be able to win
against Mr. Capable?]
[At that moment!]
I caught his name tag!
[Hee Won grabs Jong Kook's name tag.]
[Will he be able to eliminate
Mr. Capable's name tag?]
[He did it!]
[The weakling ousted Mr. Capable!]
We caught the big fish!
Kim Jong Kook is ousted,
Kim Jong Kook is ousted!
[Team Ji Hyo vs. Team Bo Young]
[4:4]
What's going on?
Kim Jong Kook is ousted,
Kim Jong Kook is ousted!
Kim Jong Kook is ousted?
[Oh my god, Kukk is ousted!]
[They lost Kim Jong Kook
during their first defense...]
Oh, no!
He has only one name tag!
[He has only one name tag!]
[One name tag?]
[What is he talking about?]
I'll explain how you can use
the hourglasses you've been collecting.
Each extra name tag lets you come
back to life in the next round
There's a name tag store at the back.
You can buy a replacement
name tag for 100 years.
[Each name tag will cost 100 years.]
[Handicap]
What do we do?
[It's favorable for us!]
You can choose any name tag.
One name tag costs 100 years.
You can get four, and you can get two.
If they buy four name tags
for Kim Jong Kook...
Then, they will have five Kim Jong Kook.
[Five Kim Jong Kook?]
[They laugh because they're relieved.]
[They laugh because it's absurd.]
[Starting from Team Bo Young,
they start name tag shopping.]
Which name tags
would you like to buy?
Kim Jong Kook.
I don't think we need to buy one for me.
Everyone except Kim Jong Kook.
Are we really going to do that?
I think that's a good plan for today.
[Because Mr. Capable will survive]
[they bought everyone's name tag
except him?]
[This is the result of the plan!]
Kim Jong Kook is ousted,
Kim Jong Kook is ousted!
What will happen to us?
We need to search for the items!
This is crazy!
[Put yourself together!
Mr. Capable's gone!]
[Running]
Park Bo Young is here!
Catch Park Bo Young!
[Thanks to Gary who's been ousted
Bo Young's location is revealed.]
[She goes into the auditorium
to hide herself.]
[Song Ji Hyo appears!]
[She looks like a rabbit
in front of a bear.]
- What's wrong?
- I'm so out of breath!
You know one of our
team member is ousted.
Just tell me
whose name tags you bought.
- Who has extra name tags?
- I'm not sure.
- I'm so sorry.
- I really don't know.
[I have no choice but to eliminate you
if you can't give me any information.]
Hang in there!
[A yellow giraffe came to save Bo Young!]
[Giraffe and Bo Young
vs. Ji Hyo]
You little!
[How dare you interrupt me?]
[If that's what you want,
I'll eliminate you first!]
[She blocks Giraffe with her arms,
and Bo Young with her legs.]
Run now!
[Jae Suk was passing by,
and he joins them.]
- Jae Suk!
- Run away!
Bo Young, run away!
[Her name tag is eliminated!]
[His name tag is eliminated, too!]
[Bo Young and Kwang Soo's name tags
are eliminated in a flash!]
Kwang Soo's ousted, too.
Wow, you're amazing!
[Park Bo Young is ousted!]
Park Bo Young is ousted!
Lee Kwang Soo is ousted!
[Wrecked]
[Park Bo Young is ousted!]
Park Bo Young is ousted!
Chase Ha Ha and Suk Jin!
[If they get Ha Ha and Suk Jin,
they'll eliminate everyone.]
[It's Song Ji Hyo!]
[Could it be here?]
Catch Ha Ha!
[Ha Ha encounters with Chun Hee.]
[He tries escaping,
but he's got caught!]
Chun Hee, wait!
No, no!
[Lee Chun Hee eliminates
Ha Ha's name tag!]
Ha Ha is ousted!
[The only surviving member
of Team Bo Young is Suk Jin.]
Please let me win once.
- I can't do that.
- You won over me at arm wrestling.
We're having a crisis.
We have a disadvantage.
How about an arm wrestling?
Let me go if I win.
[Hee Won will give one minute,
if Suk Jin wins.]
- Start chasing me after one minute.
- I see.
It's a single round match, okay?
[Hee Won and Suk Jin's arm wrestling.
That sounds familiar...]
Two years ago,
they had an arm wrestling match.
[It's a close game!]
Are you serious?
- Suk Jin?
- Is it for real?
[Big-nose brother won over him, really!]
[A victory that was like a miracle]
[A defeat that was like a nightmare]
[Today, right here...]
[Between the glory and embarrassment
of that day, what will be recreated?]
[These two don't yield
an inch against each other.]
[I won't be defeated again!]
[Victory will be mine!]
[It seems like it's a close game...]
Suk Jin!
[Goodness gracious!]
[He lost to Big-nosed Brother
again, seriously!]
[He's reestablished that
he's a weakling once again.]
Start running in one minute!
[I'm so fragile...
as always.]
[Time left until the shift]
Gary, come out now!
[Gary is already ousted.]
[Why did he tell him to come out?]
[When Team Ji Hyo visited
the name tag store]
Give us one name tag for Gary,
and one for Ji Hyo.
[They have bought extra name tags
for Monday Couple.]
- Are you sure this is okay?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Because the situation is
disadvantageous for us.
It's not going to change anything
even if we follow our guts.
[They're using Gary's
extra name tag now.]
[Since they're on offense,
Gary can attack now.]
[Team Bo Young's last
survivor Suk Jin is...]
[hiding in the dark,
but Ji Hyo finds him.]
Suk Jin is right here!
- Suk Jin is right here!
- Where?
[He runs away in super speed.]
[What a nice timing!]
[Big-nosed Brother got caught
by Monday Couple.]
[Suk Jin couldn't even fight back,
but his name tag is eliminated.]
[Ji Suk Jin is ousted!
Ji Suk Jin is ousted.]
We're all ousted.
[Team Bo Young's members are all ousted!]
We need to find the items.
Let's look for the items now!
- Ji Hyo!
- Let's search for the items.
[They're trying to find the location
before Team Bo Young respawns.]
[Where could it be?]
- Gary!
- Yes?
- Searching is harder than attacking.
- You can say that again.
[They need to find eight more
items out of nine items.]
I feel so bad that
we didn't buy Jong Kook's name tag.
[Who knew I would be eliminated?]
This is bad.
I think you'll get ousted
while you're trying to search.
Just focus on eliminating them
rather than finding the items.
Yes, let's do that.
During the defense,
just keep hiding.
I think that's better.
I know winning is more important,
but it's frustrating.
You know what I mean?
It's really important
to stick to the plan.
[Jingle-jangle]
We need to find the items
at a place like this.
[It's Jong Kook's Walkman!]
[He can't touch it
since his team is on offense.]
[Offense-Team Ji Hyo]
[Defense - Team Bo Young]
[Offense-Team Bo Young]
[Defense - Team Ji Hyo]
[Team Ji Hyo wears
a defense mark.]
[Their goal is to find
the nostalgic items now.]
[Where could it be?]
[Whistle]
Give us the bell, please.
This is upsetting!
I'm going to hurt them
even if it's just tiny bit.
What do you mean hurt them?
So upsetting!
[Te four members with extra
name tags are ready to revive.]
[Temporary pause]
[Team Bo Young is waiting
for the moment to avenge.]
[Team Ji Hyo is going to focus
on searching the items.]
[Offense - Team Bo Young]
[Defense - Team Ji Hyo]
Start!
[Both chasers and fugitives
are running at full speed!]
Where did Ji Hyo go?
I'll shout out if I find her.
[Team Bo Young's combat
spirit is higher than ever.]
[Only Kkuk without a name tag
stays alone in the jail.]
[Jae Suk runs like the wind.]
[He adds the Walkman
to the store window.]
[Jingle-jangle]
Listen, it's not the time
to walk like that!
- Jong Kook.
- Bo Young...
Oh, it was Bo Young....
It's you, Bo Young.
Did you say I'm walking?
That's too harsh.
Did you find anyone?
They're all inside the safety zone.
I think we need to do the same.
I couldn't find Ji Hyo though.
Bo Young doesn't really
say stuff like that.
She must have hated
the other team so bad.
Ji Hyo is right there.
- Where?
- Oh, it's not her!
[Team Bo Young is looking for
a chance to eliminate them.]
I start seeing things now.
Ha Ha!
You're not going to search for the items?
No.
[Their goal is to oust all of us...]
[Wait a minute!]
[Let me see...]
[There's Ha Ha]
[Big-nose]
[Bo Young and Kwang Soo.
[Only one person is missing!]
They don't have Jong Kook!
[He figured it out!]
[Which means...]
They don't have Jong Kook!
As I expected, the four except
Jong Kook revived!
[He's figured out their situation.]
We can attack them when it's our turn!
Bring it on!
[They made good use
of the safety zone.]
Kim Jong Kook is ousted!
No wonder!
Only four little fish were walking...
What?
Little fish?
He's not here!
Catch me if you can!
[The angry meter is going up.]
[I can't take it any longer!]
[He tries to eliminate
his name tag but fails.]
[Scream]
[I'm having so much fun!]
Ha Ha's going to go crazy, today.
Just wait 10 minutes!
- Think about how you've defeated today.
- Hooray!
[In the mean time, Chun Hee...]
[is wondering here and there.]
[The rest of them
are following the plan.]
Someone took the Walkman.
[Chun Hee doesn't know
Jae Suk already took it.]
[All of a sudden, he hides
himself on the floor.]
[Jingle-jangle]
[Does he think he's hiding?]
[What a windfall!]
No, no!
[Chun Hee is protecting
his name tag desperately.]
Please let me go.
What are you talking about?
Our team is all dead.
My bum is stuck!
What?
[Can you even come out?]
I don't think you can come out.
- My arm is stuck.
- Are you serious?
You should call the ambulance.
- I'll get you out.
- You're going to break my arm.
Try taking the hoodie off!
He's lying.
Take his arm out!
Who is it?
Who's this person?
[Three of them eliminated
his name tag together.]
We did it.
Let's go!
Next!
[Both parties are stubborn!]
They never over looked at me.
Lee Chun Hee is ousted.
[He's left with a sweaty face.]
[Big-nosed Brother runs away.]
[Blank Ji is chasing closely.]
Ji Hyo, stop it!
Suk Jin, I'm sorry.
You know I don't have a choice.
[Ji Suk Jin is ousted.]
Ji Suk Jin is ousted.
[I need to take a rest.]
Bo Young!
Ji Hyo!
[He was just checking his old spot.]
- It was a perfect spot.
- I got caught here.
You were hiding here?
Ji Hyo!
Don't shout, Gary.
It's not fair!
- Who's that?
- Come over here!
[Here comes Yoo Jae Suk.]
Isn't this unfair?
Two men want to attack me?
- I'm sorry.
- This is too harsh!
I'm sorry, Bo Young.
- I'm sorry, Bo Young.
- See you later.
[They've successfully eliminated
Park Bo Young's name tag.]
That's so petty!
Park Bo Young is ousted.
[Whistle]
[Ji Hyo and Giraffe are fighting again.]
[Attacking Giraffe!]
Ji Hyo, hang in there.
Hang in there, Ji Hyo!
[He's on defense,
why is he so brave?]
[Kim Hee Won has stepped
out of the safety zone!]
[But he's talking nonsense
if the situations gets bad.]
I'm sorry.
[While Hee Won and Ha Ha are fighting]
[Ji Hyo and Giraffe are still fighting.]
[Did you just bite me?
I'll bite you, too!]
[An eye for an eye
and a tooth for a tooth!]
[They're having a fist fight
and Jae Suk joined them.]
[It's like we're watching
a pro-wrestling match.]
If Kwang Soo eliminated Ji Hyo,
we'll be in trouble.
Let me save her first.
[Hee Won goes to help Ji Hyo.]
[Oh, no!
His name tag is in danger!]
[No way, he's not going to...]
[He's eliminated!]
[Gary came to help her.]
[He couldn't even stand up.]
Kim Hee Won is ousted.
[Did Kwang Soo eliminated Monday Couple?]
[He successfully eliminated
Song Ji Hyo's name tag.]
[He attacks Jae Suk right away.]
Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo and Gary vs. Kwang Soo and Ha Ha]
[What a mad house!]
Ji Hyo, what happened to you?
Ji Hyo...
What happened?
- She must have fought outside.
- Did you roll on the grass?
I had a fist fight with Kwang Soo.
[Incredible]
You've lived too long!
I'm satisfied because I eliminated you.
[They're still having a war.]
I'm holding Jae Suk's name tag!
Wait a minute, I'm going at it!
I'm busy, too!
If we can't eliminate him this time,
there won't be next.
We've turned the table so quickly.
I'm exhausted.
- I missed it.
- I'm on the ground, too.
Wait!
[He's going at Jae Suk's name tag.]
- No, Jae Suk!
- That was close!
[The time goes by while
they're holding each other.]
At this rate...
We need to eliminate them now!
[Team Bo Young tries to oust them.]
[Whistle]
Stay where you are.
[Total wreck]
What's wrong with you?
Humans change their mind so quickly.
What should we do?
- Would you accept our apology?
- No, I won't.
I'm so sorry.
[10 seconds before the pause ends.]
[Finally...]
[the winner of this race
will be concluded!]
The race start!
We need to hold it out for 20 minutes?
Just 19 more minutes!
[Ha Ha's name tag is eliminated.]
[Team Bo Young's last warrior
is Kwang Soo.]
How can I hold it?
[At last, his name tag was eliminated...]
Stop this nonsense!
- It's all over!
- Kwang Soo, it's all over!
It's all over.
[The intense battle is over...]
Thank you for your hard work!
Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
We won because of our strategy!
God helped us!
[Team Ji Hyo got over the
unfavorable conditions.]
The winner of this race is Team Ji Hyo.
["The Throwback Legacy Race"]
[Team Ji Hyo wins!]
[Everyone did their best!]
[The winning prize is a gold bar.]
It's gold!
Too bad!
It's been a while to see gold prize.
- Gary!
- Thank you so much.
Too bad for Bo Young.
[Thank you for being on the show,
Bo Young, Chun Hee, and Hee Won.]
Hee Won is almost dying.
[He's out of his mind.]
The winning team is Team Ji Hyo!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A top class limousine
and sumptuous feast!]
[Are they invited to a dazzling dinner?]
[A mysterious host invites
Running Man members to the maze castle!]
It makes me curious, though.
[Passing through the giant world
where everything is huge.]
[A mini-world that's hard
to walk or sit appears!]
[It feels like the world has been
upside down without me.]
[Their body and mind are
worn out with the endless maze!]
[Where's the exit?]
[The one chases
and the one watches!]
[Who in the world locked us up here?]
Next week, Running Man
"The Maze Castle."