[Unlock now!]
[The greatest battle of wits
in 'Running Man' history!]
[Guess the number and
unlock the locks!]
[Solve it again!]
[Their brains are in full activity mode!]
- Are you fools?
[Compete! Deduce! Unlock!]
[At Namsan Tower Observatory]
[The 'Locks of Love']
[At this place...]
[one man appears in an
inappropriate outfit.]
[He gets a secret message.]
[At an aquarium full of sharks...]
[a suspicious looking couple appears.]
[What are they here for?]
[In the coastal waters of Wolmido,
a mysterious creature appears.]
I've been swimming for 58 hours.
It's time to get results.
[This is a place of contact.]
[Perhaps... him....]
Aw! It hurts!
- Puppy!
- Bow-wow!
- Toad!
- Pardon?
What's this?
We're just starting!
- This is the worst thing for me.
[Agent Haroro, an acrophobe, is on call.]
I guess there's one more person.
[An overwhelming guy]
[A special agent with the
best combat power comes!]
[Stun Gun, Kim Dong Hyun]
- Dong Hyun!
[He was still overwhelming
against Kkuk!]
[The first fighter who entered
UFC attacks Running Man!]
[The strongest adventurer in history!]
- We're on the same team.
- Are we?
Kim Jong Kook!
Are you watching us?
- Jong Kook, see you later!
- See you later!
No, see me now!
We're on the same team, right?
No, you're independent agents.
- We're not?
- We're agents?
[Seoul Energy Dream Center]
Who is it?
[A new agent appears.]
Agent Sung!
[Diabolic voice, Sung Shi Kyung.]
[The brain of celebrities
undergoes 'Running Man' hazing.]
[A talk show MC learns the variety
show experience with his whole body.]
- What did you say?
- Agent Sung!
Why?
Sung Shi Kyung, Agent Sung!
Oh, Agent Sung?
It's awkward for me.
You usually sit down and
talk with Dong Yup.
I haven't been out.
You look like a thief,
when you're an agent.
- You don't look like an agent?
- Of course, I do. They wear coats.
Isn't that a robe from a hotel?
Agent Sung, that's too harsh!
[The best night errand boys,
are all called out.]
You're the member of the Dark Night,
the best night errand boys.
There's a secret request for you.
I can't see it well.
Acquire the secret key in a treasure
chest at the bottom of the aquarium.
Inside the aquarium?
Look at this, Gary!
- Are they talking about this?
- Look at that!
Red for Gary and blue for Song Ji Hyo.
There's a shark in there!
See? They actually bite humans.
How can we possibly avoid
the shark and find it?
What kind of a mission is this?
Do we even have to dive?
Find the 'R lock' among
the locks of love
and acquire the secret key.
Among them?
How can I find the 'R lock' from here?
There are so many locks!
This is too tough.
This is too...
Hi, Soo Hyun.
Are you well?
Acquire the secret keys in a gondola.
You can't get off the
gondola in the middle.
- Red box!
- Blue box!
Out of that many gondolas?
Plus, it takes about
three minutes per ride.
Open a lucky bag on the rock climbing wall
and acquire the secret key.
Are they talking about that bag?
Please hold a meeting before we film!
You mean me?
Stop filming! I'm serious,
you're talking about me?
Acquire the secret key from the
people who are in animal costumes.
- A red bag and a blue bag.
- A blue bag for me.
A red bag for me.
There are agents in
animal costumes here.
- I see them.
- True.
Are we getting guns?
Maybe taser guns?
[There are only two keys!]
Excuse me!
Wait!
- Excuse me!
[Agent Sung starts his investigation.]
Let me see!
You don't have it.
Watch out!
Giraffe! Wait!
What are you doing?
Are you Kwang Soo?
That person looks suspicious!
[Overreacting Rabbit]
- Look at that!
Shi Kyung!
He's so strong!
Is that Kim Jong Kook?
Is he here?
You see the rabbit?
- He's really strong.
- So what?
He's suspicious.
- He's just strong person.
- No, it's not that, Shi Kyung.
[Monday Couple Agents
are ready to dive.]
[In the deep ocean]
[along with a group of sardines]
[a big sting ray swims, too.]
[It's coming!]
[What an overwhelming scene!]
[They're floating for a while.]
[They pass the groups of sardines]
[and swim toward the
treasure chests.]
[I'll open and see!]
[It's empty?]
[Go to the next one!]
[It's empty again!]
[Where is it?]
[It's not easy to find a
key in the aquarium.]
[They wonder around
in the deep ocean for a while.]
[Agent Blank opens another one.]
[I found the key!]
[She's lucky even in the water!]
[Now, Gary needs to find the key.]
[There it is!]
[Agent Gary acquires the key.]
[The agents come back
to land safely.]
Success!
It's a whole new world.
Isn't it?
Yes.
It's so fun to be in the water.
I don't want to leave this place.
You've acquired secret keys.
Please keep it to yourself.
[What will be the reason that
they shouldn't show it to others?]
[Gary and Ji Hyo acquire secret keys.]
What number should we get on?
- Number 14 sounds good.
- Number 14?
Yes, it's the next gondola.
Let's get on.
- There's a box!
- There is! Number 14!
We're getting on number 14.
They're playing a sweet song.
- You need to come here with a girlfriend.
- Yes, it's for lovers.
[The big wheel starts moving.]
- Let's check this first.
- It drives me nuts.
Maybe the key is there, maybe not.
It's empty.
[The big wheel just started.]
- I'm sad.
Stop the music at least.
- It takes ten minutes.
- This is for lovers!
- It's the first time riding this, with you!
- It's the first time for me too.
I'm serious.
It feels really weird.
- It's my first time.
- Me, too!
- Kwang Soo!
- Really!
[The music doesn't
know how they feel.]
- The music is going to hit the climax soon.
- It's so passionate.
People write in here.
Someone wrote 'Jae Suk.'
That can't be Yoo Jae Suk.
Maybe...
A long time ago...
even before he met his wife...
That's possible! This has
been here for a long time.
[The ten minutes that felt
like an hour passed.]
- This is annoying!
- Thank you.
Stop playing romantic songs!
- There is!
- There's a box.
- Let's finish it this time!
- At least one of us!
I hope it was your key.
Let's get in.
I can't hear anything.
[Empty]
Another ten minutes in here.
[They don't want to admit it.]
Kwang Soo...
Who was your first love?
I think I was a high school student.
An older girl?
- It's always an older girl.
- You liked an older girl, too?
She's turning 60 soon.
[Are you well?]
[Haroro and Dong Hyun
fight with the rocks.]
- Please release my rope.
- Sure.
Try to raise your bottom.
Don't let your bottom stick out.
Get close to the wall.
[He climbs with his long arms.]
[Agent Haroro does his best.]
I think this is my limit!
I think I'm going to fall.
[He sure is the strongest guy!]
Dong Hyun!
- I got it!
- Dong Hyun!
I'll do everything if
you get mine, too.
- What are you going to do for me?
- Make you win.
Except that.
What do you want?
Are you going to hook
me up with a girl?
I'll give you my contact
on my phone.
- For real?
- For real!
I love you, Kim Dong Hyun!
[Then it's a deal.]
[He takes two lucky
bags and gets down.]
For real?
- I'll make sure to get you a woman.
- Don't forget.
- Kim Dong Hyun! Kim Dong Hyun!
[Secret keys acquired!]
[Namsan Tower]
- There are too many locks.
Was there a space to hook
another one?
Does anyone come back when
they break up with their lover.
Maybe they bring a cutter.
This is really tough.
How can I find it?
R!
- R?
['R lock' is right here.]
Oh! I found it!
How is it possible I found it?
What kind of a mission is this?
[Ha Ha, Dong Hyun, and Jong Kook
acquire the secret key.]
- I saw a giraffe.
- That's nothing.
I think the rabbit is suspicious.
- The rabbit?
- Yes, that rabbit. Look!
Rabbit, wait!
Wait, that person...
Shi Kyung!
[Let's pressed the siege.]
- See?
Come here.
Why is he doing this?
- He's here to exercise.
- Here it is.
[They got it.]
But this is mine.
A red bag and a blue bag.
- Blue bag is mine.
- And red bag is mine.
- What is it, then?
- Thank you.
Where do I need to go now?
- Wait!
[Agent Sung moves on.]
You should have told me.
- I'm leaving.
You didn't find it.
- I found what you found.
- I mean...
[Most of them are passive...]
Let me check.
[...but this sheep is actively blocking.]
Shi Kyung!
Wait!
- Shi Kyung!
[Give me it back!]
- He's not an average man.
[A strong sheep]
He's not the same sheep
from before.
Shi Kyung!
- Shi Kyung!
[Agent Sung comes back.]
This isn't the same sheep.
Seize him, Shi Kyung!
It's not him.
Here it is.
- I found it.
[Yoo Hyuk acquires the key.]
- Me, too.
[Agent Sung acquires the key.]
[Jae Suk and Shi Kyung
acquire the keys.]
How about 21?
Please!
[The eighth time riding it.]
I can't do it any more.
It has two boxes!
- What?
- Why two boxes?
There are two!
- Key!
- Finally!
We can finally escape!
- I'm happier than when I won.
- We're finally done with this mission!
[But...]
[They still have to wait ten minutes.]
- To get this key, I...
had to go through the hell.
We still have to stay in
the gondola.
Ah... that's right.
I'm cold!
[They were happy for a second.]
[They're depressed all of a sudden.]
[Everyone has succeeded at
acquiring their secret keys.]
[The Dark Night's temporary station.]
- What's the matter?
- Why so quiet?
- Hello!
- Night errand boys regular meeting?
Wow, regular meeting!
- Ji Hyo and Gary came!
- You're here, Ji Hyo.
Welcome to the night errand
boys' regular meeting.
- It's Jong Kook.
- You didn't want to catch a cold.
[He's wearing a muffler.]
- It's been cold.
- Why are you coming alone?
- I was by myself.
- You were? Really?
Why am I the only one?
You're here, Ha Ha.
What? Dong Hyun is here!
[Everyone is surprised
to see the UFC fighter.]
You're lucky, Ha Ha.
[The strongest night
errand boy, Dong Hyun.]
Please throw Jong Kook for me.
- Where were you today?
- We were rock climbing.
Were you able to do it?
That's why Dong Hyun helped...
- He did it for you?
- Yes.
You're still using honorifics with him?
How can I not?
He usually starts speaking
informal quickly.
- It's so cold.
- Hello!
[Jae Suk and Shi Kyung arrive last.]
- Shi Kyung!
- What brings you here?
I thought you're were
Jo Young Nam.
[He imitates him right away.]
What's the occasion?
- Hello!
What's with him?
Are you a pervert?
What are you?
[Everybody's judging his trench coat.]
You look awful today.
It's for my persona.
I think I have a chance
besides Dong Hyun.
- What are you talking about?
- Shi Kyung is really strong!
- You don't know anything about Shi Kyung.
[ I take it back.]
So, all of you acquired
the secret keys?
Yes!
We don't greet each other
or anything?
The whole nation knows
you're Sung Shi Kyung.
We don't catch up on our lives?
We start being night errand boys?
I think you've been in
the studios too much.
What is there to catch up on?
We see each other,
then we know we're alive.
No need for that.
- We're all well.
- I understand.
I'll announce today's race first.
It's the 'Hunter of the Key' race.
I'm offering the final
mission for you guys.
When you succeed this mission
you will get a huge dividend
and live in luxury.
To complete this mission
the secret keys you
acquires are critical.
[The secret key is critical!]
Before we start our final mission
we'll give you another chance
at getting an additional key.
Do you have any questions?
We don't catch up on
each other lives?
[Curious Shi Kyung]
Just say what you want to say
in front of the camera.
It's been a long time.
I'm his fan.
I didn't release a new album.
I'm not here to promote anything.
Then you'll do another mission
to get an additional key.
It's the race for the key.
Race?
We made a track shaped like a key.
Three runners will start.
Pick a person from each
zone and go to that person.
Throw the person down and
pop the balloon underneath.
And come to the finish line.
Then the first one to
finish is the winner.
There will be three rounds,
so three winners...
will go to the finals.
- That's right.
- It's an individual battle?
Yes. It's an individual battle.
My main skill is to block and throw.
I have a feeling that
he will come to me.
I'll challenge you today.
[Give him a standing ovation.]
- Please, defeat Jong Kook.
- Kim Dong Hyun! Kim Dong Hyun!
I'm just a singer!
There are many athletes out there!
No, you're not just a singer.
My fighter friends have
high expectations of you.
Just think of him as a
singer and an athlete.
- Who sings well.
- Just think of him as an athlete who sings well.
[Mission - Race for the key]
- Are you giving up already?
- We don't know yet.
Don't come to me!
- It won't be easy!
- I'll bite you all!
[First round:
Jae Suk, Shi Kyung, Dong Hyun]
- Help me.
- Bring it on!
- I'll go to Kim Jong Kook.
- Mark him, Dong Hyun.
I think Dong Hyun will come to me.
I want to stand in the middle,
because it's less painful when falling.
- That's not nice!
- Are you going to punch?
- It's not fair!
- Don't practice that!
- He looks strong.
- He's different.
Look at Jae Suk!
Get ready.
Ready!
How could it be so different?
I can't believe what I'm looking at.
Get ready.
Ready!
[Choosing an easy
opponent is the key.]
Bring it on!
He's fast!
Dong Hyun is fast as expected!
[Three men running at full speed.]
- He's coming at me!
[They're coming!]
- I'm sorry!
- He's coming at me!
I'm sorry!
[Get the easiest opponent first.]
- I'm sorry!
[Dong Hyun chooses Ji Hyo.]
Kwang Soo!
[Shi Kyung chooses Ha Ha.]
[Jae Suk chooses Kwang Soo.]
- Kwang Soo!
- With all my life!
[Shi Kyung throws Ha Ha quickly.]
- Kwang Soo!
- With all my life!
It's no joke.
Why is Shi Kyung so strong?
Are you serious?
What's wrong with you?
[Shi Kyung and Dong Hyun
run to zone two.]
Is he coming to me?
Jong Kook!
[Shi Kyung goes straight to
Suk Jin and takes him down.]
[Dong Hyun goes to Gary.]
[He chooses to win.]
[He pops the balloon first.]
[Dong Hyun finishes first.]
Good job!
Come here.
Come over here!
[Jae Suk passes zone one now.]
[Dong Hyun is a step ahead.]
[He gets the first place.]
[I missed it!]
Dong Hyun didn't go to Jong Kook.
He tricked us.
He won.
He's so strong.
- It's getting interesting.
- Come to me.
Ji Hyo!
[Come to me.]
- Me! Me!
Ji Hyo block them.
That's right!
There's only one open door.
[Race for the key, Second round.]
Get ready.
Ready!
This isn't fair!
We didn't even start!
Ji Hyo, make a cute face!
Dong Hyun will fall.
- I'll fall down.
- He said he will.
Wait for me!
Set!
[Their target is that one open door.]
[Open door, Jae Suk.]
You're mine, Yoo Jae Suk.
I have something to talk
to Jae Suk about.
[Shi Kyung and Dong Hyun watch them.]
Ji Hyo!
Wow, he's so popular.
I would go somewhere else!
Go for the empty spot!
[Empty spot?]
Ji Hyo!
[Kwang Soo tries an
empty spot, Dong Hyun.]
[A drop in the ocean.]
[Kwang Soo tries another
empty spot, Shi Kyung.]
[Who said they're empty spots?]
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo did it!
[Ji Hyo is leading solo.]
[Kwang Soo and Ha Ha are blocked
by the strongest wall.]
[She's the first runner!]
[Ji Hyo gets close to zone two.]
[Where should she go to?]
- I'll help you.
[Come to me.]
[She goes to Gary immediately.]
[As soon as Ji Hyo touches,
Gary falls down.]
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- That sure is a 'green light'
- Is that?
[Two men chase after her!]
Ji Hyo, hurry up and go!
[Ji Hyo is still the first
runner thanks to Gary.]
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo enter zone 2.]
[And these two men are here.]
[They obviously go to...]
Why me?
Go to Jong Kook!
That's horrible.
[In the meantime, Ji Hyo arrives
at the finish line.]
Ji Hyo goes to the finals.
Ji Hyo wins!
That's not fair!
[Their combination works
during the third round, too.]
Song Ji Hyo!
- Stop there!
- Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo!
[Come here, Gary!]
- Stop there!
- Ji Hyo!
[This time, Ji Hyo falls
down right away.]
[Gary passes zone 2 in a flash]
[and wins.]
[Ji Hyo and Gary,
the fantastic couple.]
Ji Hyo supports Gary.
When Gary gets close,
she opened her arms.
That was too much!
Jae Suk, I'll be Gary.
Recreate the scene.
- When did I do that?
- You did this!
What was that?
Are you getting back together?
Is this how we get back together?
Who is going to the finals?
It just accidentally happened.
[The final round.]
This zone will be really easy.
It's a basic level.
I'll run to that side.
- Dong Hyun!
[Nervous]
This is all about Dong Hyun
going to Jong Kook or not.
[I'll see you soon!]
- Look at Dong Hyun!
It seems like he's coming.
- I hope you have a head-on game.
- I understand.
With Jong Kook.
Don't think about winning.
Just defeat Jong Kook.
- Let's go!
- Ready!
Ready!
Having one more key is
very important.
We'll start.
Ready!
Set!
[The key is mine.]
[Running at full speed.]
[All three of them have taken down.]
[At the same time]
Hurry!
[In a flash, zone 1 is all cleared.]
Dong Hyun, you don't have
to do this much.
- They're coming!
[Tension in zone 2.]
Dong Hyun!
Go to Jong Kook!
[I'm coming, Jong Kook!]
[Come if you dare.]
Yes, they've met!
[Mr, Capable, indeed!]
[Gary is wrestling with Kwang Soo.]
[Ji Hyo had no choice but
to go to Shi Kyung.]
[She succeeds.]
- Ji Hyo!
[ A big reversal!]
[Goodbye, Ji Hyo...]
[Ji Hyo wins the Race for the Key]
- Don't look!
Don't look!
[Ji Hyo gets an additional key.]
- It's Ji Hyo.
- I blocked him!
Wow, Jong Kook held out!
- Good job!
- He blocked him.
He didn't win this race!
- Incredible.
[He feels sorry for Dong Hyun.]
It's better for us, if
Ji Hyo gets the key.
What if Ji Hyo wins the race?
[I'll see you at the final mission.]
Song Ji Hyo is the winner
so she can have another key.
I hope she'll get your number.
- What number...
- We can check each other's number, right?
Ji Hyo never loses a big game.
She always gets this kind of stuff.
I didn't expect her to get it.
- No, Shi Kyung helped me.
- Here's the key.
- You're getting it?
- I can see the number.
You saw it again.
- How can I possibly see it?
- You saw it!
With your hawk eyes!
[Ji Hyo gets additional key number seven.
What are the secrets of these keys?]
[Soon, the secret of the
key will be revealed.]
[A battle of wits to get the key.]
[And the plot twist!]
[Who will be the winner in the end?]
What's this all about?
- He talks like you.
- Why do you talk like me?
- I really don't know what it is.
- Are you taking us again?
- Again?
- We've just met!
- What is it?
- Not again!
- I'm lonely.
- Just follow them.
I've done nothing wrong.
Why don't you take Ji Hyo?
[The special mission for
the key hunters is...]
Night errand boys, I'll
announce the final mission.
Is this the final mission already?
The final mission is
'Maximize your dividend.'
From now on...
try and maximize your dividend.
Why did you have to...
Is it a golden hand?
Thank you.
We start with one gold.
We need to multiple it in order
to win.
So is this the dividend?
To maximize your dividend
using the secret keys you acquired
you should find a locker and open it.
- A locker?
[36 lockers are in this building.]
All of the lockers are locked.
Each locker has two locks.
Unlock one of the locks first.
Then you'll be able to get a hint about the
person who has the key for the other lock.
I need to find another person.
Find the person and open
the locker together.
Then you'll find a beneficial card
for maximizing your dividends.
Is there a hint about
how I can maximize?
The more you open, the
more you'll earn.
After certain amount of time
the exchange shop will open, and you can
exchange your coins with real money.
The one with the most
money is today's winner.
Someone might come for my key.
- I'm excited?
- We'll start the final mission now.
Ten, nine, eight
seven, six, five...
- four, three...
- This is my day!
two, one!
[The Dark Night's final mission is
to maximize the dividends.]
Where is the locker?
Find a locker for my key.
I have to find the locker quickly.
It's open.
I think there's one.
Is there none?
Yes, there is!
This is great!
It feels like I'm playing a game.
[Open!]
- What is this?
This would have been too easy
if it opened.
[He uses his height for a trick?]
[The hunter who has an advantage.]
- I have number one...
and number seven.
I have two keys.
Although I'm weak,
I guess I have an advantage.
It's right there!
[She can open it by herself if the
locker has the same two numbers.]
[Number one key...]
[Number one key fails.]
- No.
[Number seven key...]
[Number seven key fails.]
[While she's focusing on
looking for a locker...]
[Two hunters are watching
other hunters' movements.]
[Quickly find the locker!]
It's not in here?
[Shi Kyung runs for a while.]
This is fun!
I like it!
[He finds another one.]
Criminals...
Because we're doing this
in a closed building.
I feel like I'm here to
get some information.
[It's finally opened!]
Bruce Willis is a ghost.
Then it's 'The Sixth Sense.'
Six!
Okay.
What floor is this?
It's sixth floor.
It's the sixth floor, right?
[Jae Suk finally finds a locker.]
[Bingo!]
[What's the hint for the other lock?]
- A swan?
A swan...
Seriously...
That looks like number 2.
A swan means number two.
You didn't know I would solve it.
[If I can find a hunter
with the key number two!]
- Number 1.
- You have number 1?
- I'm looking for it.
- Aren't you 8?
Did you open?
- What's yours?
- What's your number?
Don't you have number 2?
- You have 2, right?
- Did you find the lock?
You have number 2.
Follow me.
- Why didn't you answer me?
- Tell me now.
[What's in the locker?]
This is it!
A swan.
[Jae Suk opens the lock.]
A swan!
Try opening it.
[Baek Bum - Kim Goo's pen name.]
- Kim Goo (nine).
[They open the locker.]
Choose one of the envelopes.
- One is beneficial...
- What is this?
[And the other is empty.]
You can pick the card
the way you want.
What is this?
So, you chose that one?
- Can I use my physical strength?
- Don't do it that way.
[He's ready to use his
fighter's skill.]
Do you want to switch?
Go ahead, please.
Choose one first.
- I want that one.
- This one?
- Here it is.
- Why are you holding two?
[It's either the golden card or empty.]
[Empty!]
[Why did I switch...]
- Multiply by three!
- What?
Thank you, Dong Hyun!
Three times as much!
Three times!
I'm so sorry, Dong Hyun.
What you chose was the right one.
- Yours is empty, right?
- No, it's not.
Wait, I'll read this to you.
[What is he doing?]
- Wait, I'll read this to you.
[There's another mission?]
[You can eliminate other
member's name tags.]
[Then the dividend will be transferred but
their keys and golden keys will lapse.]
[You can eliminate and
take their dividend?]
- Wait!
- You wait.
You wait, Dong Hyun.
[It's the happiest moment for him.]
[Jae Suk stayed in heaven
for three seconds.]
What are you guys doing?
Wait, Dong Hyun.
- Is it okay if I read it out loud?
- Wait.
You can't lose this bag.
Wait, Dong Hyun!
- This is not the time to eliminate.
- Is that so?
Can you tell me why?
Now?
When I don't do that...
This guy is...
playing this game in a hurry...
I'm very competitive.
Once I grab, I won't let it go.
- This is not a good time.
- Is that it?
Let's leave here first.
Why did you switch with me?
- Your name tag is on, right?
[He never loses his prey.]
- Then see you later.
- See you.
You're the richest person.
You don't know it yet.
- You go this way, and I'll go this way.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Dong Hyun.
- Sure.
I almost died there.
You scared me!
Why did you do that?
[I'm letting you go this time.]
Three times!
[He gets three gold coins.]
I think I can use him.
[Make a lot of money.
See you later.]
[No.5 Suk Jin and No.1 Ji Hyo]
Choose one of the envelopes...
One is...
[Getting the golden key card is crucial.]
Ladies first.
What do you want to pick?
Can you give me that one?
- You pick well.
- Take this.
- You want that one?
- No.
No? You want this one?
Then I'll take it.
I'll go somewhere else and check.
Did you open any?
- Yes, we opened one.
- Both of you?
- Really? Wow!
- Yes.
I feel so weird.
This is crazy.
[Empty]
Empty!
[His headache starts with this letter.]
- My head hurts.
Wow, Song Ji Hyo is
truly a lucky person.
[Queen of the Draw, Ji Hyo wins
even if she gives it away.]
[She acquires the doubling card.]
Double!
Double?
[Total two coins.]
Wow, that's great!
I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
[Will the Queen of the Draw
win this game?]
[Current status of the R coins.]
[Jae Suk has three coins now.]
[Running Man]
- What does 'Running Man' mean?
There's another locker.
[He's collecting the hints.]
Jupiter?
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter...
That's number five.
[He guesses the hints easily.]
Hodori (mascot for the '88 Olympics),
eight!
[He comes to the front.]
[Brain Shi Kyung guesses easily.]
- Fifth consonant, five!
[No.4 Kwang Soo and No. 7 Gary]
- I need to see this.
- You saw it, didn't you?
- No, I really didn't.
Then switch.
[Dud]
[Ah... I never should've swapped.]
[Earn 5 times the amount.]
Five times!
[Gary's current count - Five]
[Meanwhile, the muscle rivals,
Mr. Capable, and Dong Hyun...]
- That must've been your number.
- Then that must've been your number, too.
[Jong Kook- Six; Dong Hyun- Two.
The locker is opened.]
[They each grab a golden envelope.]
Dud!
Times three!
[Dong Hyun finds the 'Times Three' card.]
[Dong Hyun's current count- Three.]
I would've had six if I had
found this when I had two coins.
[You can start to eliminate
others' name tags.]
[But the key, and the coins they possess
will be eliminated along with them.]
[Should I get on the move, and
start eliminating some name tags?]
- Ji Hyo, what do you think we should do?
- What do you mean?
- Let's get one figured out.
- Okay, since I already owe you one.
Just tell me one of the numbers.
If it's right, then we'll open it together.
- Have you already opened one?
- Yes, I've already opened one.
Then let me ask you one.
Seven.
- I know who number seven is.
- Tell me who it is.
You're not going to tell anyone else?
You have to promise me.
[I wonder who it could be...]
- I'm number seven.
- Ugh, you're so annoying.
- I'm serious.
- I'm not doing this filthy show anymore.
[You can't trust anyone
in this world...]
On our show, you can't share
information like that with anyone else.
But know that I'm in hiding because
there's someone with a duplicate number.
- Someone with a duplicate number?
- I have two numbers right now, right?
I already know who has the same number.
You need the number seven, right?
Are you going by yourself right now?
- You haven't opened a single one yet?
- I just want to open one.
Where did it go?
I think it's right here.
[Will Shi Kyung's eight, and Ji Hyo's seven
open up this locker?]
[The locker is successfully opened.]
[Now it's time to make their selection.]
I've already opened one earlier,
so you can take your pick first.
Really? Then I'm going
to go with this one.
Shi Kyung, let's open them up
by ourselves.
[Ji Hyo flees the scene in fear of
Shi Kyung coming after her name tag.]
Then it means I can't open
anymore lockers with number seven?
[Blank Ji finds herself with a chance
to double her current amount.]
[The first locker Shi Kyung opens,
and he automatically ends up with a dud.]
Double!
[2 x 2= Four.]
I'm not sure if having these coins
is necessarily a good thing.
[Ha Ha is still frantically searching
for his first locker.]
[Finds his first locker.]
[Successfully opens the first lock.
What number is the other lock?]
[Turbo, Leessang, Bi-Bi.]
Okay, that's number two!
That means it's Dong Hyun.
[Wait... he knows that
Dong Hyun is number two?]
- Let's tell each other our numbers.
- Our numbers?
- Let's be honest, okay?
- Okay.
We'll just have you come in at first place.
First place is the way to go.
[Thus, Ha Ha (three) finds out that
Dong Hyun is number two?]
How were we supposed to find this
when they hid it all the way in here?
- It's not opening.
- You're number two, aren't you?
[The excitement of the lock opening
can be felt through the fingertips.]
I finally got one opened.
The one on the right was a dud earlier,
so this time, I'm going to pick this one.
[Early bird gets the worm!
Dong Hyun snatches up the card he wants.]
- We each get one?
- Is this your first locker?
I'm sorry, but I'm going to
get going now.
[Anyone can tell that Dong Hyun
is happy with what he just saw.]
[Ha Ha gets a dud
from the first locker he opens.]
Double!
- Thank you.
[3 x 2 = Six.]
- How many lockers have you opened?
- Me?
- I've only opened one locker.
- Me, too, and it was a dud.
- There's one in there.
- Where? In here?
- Wait for me. Let's look for one together.
- You've really opened only one?
- I'm serious, I've only found one.
- It's to your left.
- You've only got one, and it was a dud?
- Yes, it was a total dud.
Mine was a dud, too.
Did it open?
Yeah.
Did it open for you, too?
If you can open it, then do it now.
Are you number six?
Wow, this is crazy!
I had no idea that it'd be you!
- I don't know about this.
- What's in here?
[A celebratory dance for these duds!
One of them will get the golden envelope!]
- Do you want to switch?
- No.
- No? I didn't know you were number six.
- I don't want to switch.
- I didn't know your number either.
- Let's stick together, okay?
[Jong Kook ends up with the dud.]
[It's another dud, but I still can't
seem to stop from laughing.]
Double!
- Double!
[Rubbing it in.]
Thank you.
[Ha Ha- 1 x 2 = Two.]
Dong Hoon, I only have one right now
because I've only been getting duds.
So I think that I'm going to
have to take yours.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't just let you go right now.
I'll pay you back if I win the race.
I'm serious, I'll pay you back.
- I promise.
[No wonder he kindly led me in here.]
- I'm leaving.
- No, you cant.
[Rendered helpless.]
- Are you going to eliminate me?
- I promise that I'll pay you back.
- You can't eliminate me for a while.
- Yes, of course.
[I'll let you live.]
Even if I don't eliminate you right now...
Come on, just hand it over.
I finally have two coins.
Thanks.
- You seriously can't touch me, okay?
- Okay, I got it.
I promise.
I'm telling you that I won't touch you.
Be careful walking around, okay?
Do you see how worried I am about you?
[You'd better watch your back...]
[I vow to get my revenge...]
[Thus, Jong Kook successfully
gets himself another coin.]
[Another dud, Kwang Soo,
is purposely headed somewhere.]
- Have you tried this one?
- No, not this one.
[Giraffe is led to a locker in the
corner by Dong Hyun's lead.]
[It opened!]
[It's now time to make their selection.]
What is it?
It's a dud.
Why are there so many duds?
[He certainly lives up to his name.]
Why don't you open yours?
[Then mine has to be the good card...]
Why would they put this card in here?
I've been running around here for hours.
- What is it?
- Forfeiture of rights.
- What does that mean?
- It means to confiscate.
All the additional chips that you've earned
will be confiscated from you. (Minimum of 1.)
- Give me all the chips that you've earned.
- Yes!
[Hand over all the chips that
you've worked so hard to earn.]
I love duds!
I've been picking duds all day!
[His coin stash is
automatically reset to one.]
Dong Hyun, I'm going to go now,
and look for Jae Suk.
Since I just got this dud.
- How many do you have right now?
- I have two.
I only have two right now,
so there's no point in eliminating me.
But having two is better than
what I've got.
- Those are some hurtful words!
- Two is better than the one I have!
- What are you saying?
- Then just give me one.
I can give you one, but you're
acting like a thug right now.
- There are still lots of lockers left.
- Then just give me one.
- Do you want to lose two, or just one?
- What the heck is this?
- If I have to choose, then I'll choose one.
Give it to me while I'm still being nice.
[Please don't keep that innocent smile on
your face while saying those types of words.]
- Dong Hyun.
- Hi, Jong Kook.
[I'd like to wish you a joyous,
and a fruitful hunting experience.]
Enjoy!
- Should I finish it off?
- Sure! Have fun!
- Happy hunting!
- No need to say things like that.
It's like there are two Kim Jong Kook's.
- Thank you. I'll work even harder now.
- Yes, of course.
[I will make sure to
put this coin to good use.]
If I run into you again, then
I'll have to attempt an elimination.
- Please consider the help I just gave you.
- Okay, thanks.
- I'll see you later.
- Bye.
Even if I can't win the race today, I vow
to eliminate his name tag from the game.
[You just wait and see,
Kim Dong Hyun...]
Is it okay to take this from
him like this?
[You were fine earlier, so what
are you having doubts about now?]
I actually think that
this is a better method.
- Jae Suk.
- Are you number five?
- This is too hard for me.
- But are you opening up a lot of lockers?
Jae Suk, let's open one together.
Okay, let's find one and
open it together.
Let's go find one, and open it together.
Teach me how to play, and give me some
tips. You guys are awful to your guests.
- What are you talking about?
- No one's telling me anything.
I've been running around
all over this building.
I thought that I was forbidden from using
the elevator since this is 'Running Man'.
Why wouldn't you? You should
take the elevator when you can.
- Then that would be 'Elevator Man'.
- What are you talking about?
[Off to the elevators
on their search for the lockers.]
[A locker is found!]
[Attempting to open
both the locks by herself?]
[Blank Ji with both number one, and seven,
boldly attempts to open the locks by herself.]
[The number seven key is a winner.]
[Will the number one key also be a winner?]
This is awesome.
So awesome.
[Who knew that my keys would
open both of these locks?]
This is awesome.
Did you open it?
[What tangible fate between these two.
Mr. Gary makes his entrance.]
I have two keys.
- Then can I get one of these?
- No, you can't.
- Why not?
- You have to open the lock on your own.
And make sure to keep this in mind.
My two keys doesn't mean I get two lives.
- You only have one life, right?
- Yes, I only have one life.
My elimination would mean
that two keys will also be eliminated.
Then can you help me
open one of these lockers?
[Then he's going to find out
that I also have a number seven key.]
- I'm going to do this first.
[Turns down his proposal.]
[I need to remain extremely cautious.]
I seriously can't figure it out.
[Why doesn't anyone want my
number seven?]
[Ji Hyo gets a chance to double
her amount.]
Double!
- Thank you.
[4 x 2= Eight.]
[Ta-da!
A locker is opened.]
- That one? Are you sure about that?
- Yeah.
Are you sure that you
won't regret it?
[Gary with five vs Jae Suk with three.
A fierce mental battle.]
- Yes!
[Wait, did they both get
the chance card?]
I got a key card, too.
Dud.
Ugh, it's a dud!
[Gary was completely fooled
by the picture of the key.]
Double!
- Is this because I started off with three?
[3 x 2 = Six.]
- Is it right?
- Yes, I think this one is right.
[Grasshopper finally gets the hang of it,
and gets himself on a roll.]
- Double.
[6 x 2 = 12.]
- We won't know until we open it.
[But it isn't over yet!]
- There was one here?
- You were number one?
- Double!
[His winning streak takes him up to 24.]
[But Brain Sung attempts to give
the Grasshopper a run for his money.]
[Chases after the Grasshopper through
the use of deduction, and statistics.]
[Shi Kyung- 2 x 2 = Four.]
[I'm the one that'll
bring down the Grasshopper.]
[And almost immediately
opens up another locker.]
- Triple.
[4 x 3 = 12.]
[Finds a triple card before he even
gets a chance to take a breath!]
[Surpasses the Grasshopper, and
jumps to the current lead with 36.]
- Kwang Soo, let's go.
- Dong Hoon.
[The two coin donors gathers
to join their forces together.]
- Kwang Soo, do you have a lot?
- No, I only have one.
I had all of mine taken away from me.
I had no idea Dong Hyun would be like that.
Dong Hyun kept tempting me
to eliminate him in the elevator.
I opened a locker with Dong Hyun,
and I got another dud
and Dong Hyun got a forfeiture card.
The he wagged his finger at me,
and told me to come closer.
Let's go, Kwang Soo. I don't
even have a single coin right now.
- You don't even have one? I have one.
- No, I don't even have a single one.
This is a total lawless country,
or something.
- Do they know what century this is?
- The rules are in place for a reason!
Shouldn't the writers, and the producers,
step in and do something about this?
- Don't you think they're crossing the line?
- They need to be locked up behind bars.
Do you think that they're
better than us or something?
[The two herbivores' voices have
become louder as a team.]
What? Electroless innocence?
(Play on words)
I meant, separation of law
for the rich and the poor!
[The two herbivores set out together
in search for the lockers.]
[Dud]
[Hello, my name is 'Dud-Soo'.]
No, don't cry.
Wow.
[The current status of everyone's
standing will be revealed to you.]
[Knowing the current standing means
that I can target the winner's name tags!]
Let's just go for the one
that's in front of us.
[Even the Grasshopper, and the Tiger
are attempting to work together.]
- Where are you going?
- Why?
[The Grasshopper instinctively
attempts to flee for his survival.]
Wait, this is...
What is it?
Let's just tell each other.
Is it just coins?
[Jae Suk wins a chance to double
his amount.]
- Mine is a dud.
- Really?
[I have to flee in order to survive.]
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
[Since the Grasshopper isn't so easy,
let's just wait off on that for a bit.]
I should just monitor everyone first,
then figure out what to do from there.
[Barely escapes with his life.]
I feel nervous about this.
I don't think I want to have this many.
[Jumps to the lead with a total of 48 coins.]
[Ha Ha is being told the current status
of everyone's standing.]
Yoo Jae Suk has 48.
Sung Shi Kyung has 36.
Gary has 15, and Song Ji Hyo
has eight.
Ji Suk Jin has six.
Kim Jong Kook has four,
and Kim Dong Hyun has two.
Lee Kwang Soo, and Ha Ha...
only have one each.
- Ha Ha, do you know the count?
- It's frightening.
- What does it look like?
- You and I are on the same boat today!
You little scoundrel... I thought
you were hiding something from me.
I told you that I only had one.
I'm serious, we're in this together today.
- Sit down, and let's talk this out.
- Do you really have nothing?
You need to know this much.
You need to know this.
The current first place...
has 48 coins.
- Okay, you have to decide.
- Is it possible to have 48?
Yes, it must be possible.
Want to partner up with me?
- Yes, of course.
- Winning this isn't the issue for me anymore.
- If we don't get these 48 coins...
- Then it's all over for us already.
[Team Herbivore is now
Team Anti-48.]
- Wait, but you haven't told me who it is.
- That's our safety net.
[Meanwhile, 48 is clueless about
his identity having been compromised.]
Ha Ha.
[Of all places,
to get off the elevator here...]
- You've had a lot taken away, too, right?
- Yes, I have.
You're the last hope I have
to open the locker on the third floor.
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
- How's it going with you?
[Jae Suk can't be the one with 48, can he?]
- Don't lie to me!
- I only have one. How many do you have?
- Hey...
- Be honest with me.
- Let's talk once we're on the third floor.
- How many do you have?
Let's just talk
once we're on the third floor.
[The two are in a mental cat and mouse game,
with the Giraffe as the third wheel.]
Hey, if everyone had been open
about our numbers from the beginning
then we wouldn't have to
fumble around like this.
- Kwang Soo, where did you hide your coins?
- I seriously only have one.
Stop lying to me, and just
be honest with me.
I'm telling you the truth. Dong Hoon
knows everyone's current standing.
He also knows how many coins we all have.
Do you know how many first place has?
No, I don't know.
This is a secret, but 48.
[An explosion of fake acting.]
[Dud for luck, and dud for brains-
Giraffe is just striking out left and right.]
[In total acting mode.]
Double that would be 96.
I wonder who has the 48 coins.
- It's not you, is it?
- You know better than that.
[Trying to appease Kwang Soo,
and tells him that he's been hitting duds.]
- Let's not be like this to each other.
- You don't have anything either?
No, I don't.
But why don't I hear anything about
Ha Ha getting ousted yet?
[I know I told Ha Ha exactly
where to go...]
I will tell you everyone's
current standing.
[Haroro, in grave danger.]
Here, I'll show you the current standing,
and tell you why you shouldn't eliminate me.
[Offering whatever he can to help
preserve the survival of his own life.]
See? Jae Suk is in first place.
Eliminate him, and you'd take over his spot.
- You're going to help me?
- Eliminate him, and take over his spot.
- Okay?
- Should we go downstairs?
[Ha Ha and Dong Hyun join forces
to eliminate Jae Suk.]
- It's okay, Kwang Soo. Don't be scared.
- Why do you keep showing up everywhere?
- I was just heading downstairs.
- No, you can come with us.
- The three of us together?
- I'll pin down his arms.
I think Jae Suk just went into
the bathroom.
- You have to promise that we're a team.
- I'll show you how sincere I am.
- But you don't even have anything.
- I have one.
- So there's no use in eliminating you.
- I have two.
- How many does Jae Suk have?
- Dong Hyun knows how many Jae Suk has.
I've already told you how many. But
don't say that we're the ones who did it.
We'll just support you in your cause.
There he is.
[Just the person they've been looking for!]
[Attacked as soon as he's found.]
I've been told the current standing,
and he's in first place.
- You have 48?
- No, it's not me.
- You're the one with 48?
- Yes, he is.
I have no doubt about it.
I've been told everyone's current count.
[The Grasshopper is caught
between a rock, and a hard place.]
- Come on.
- Rip!
[The sound of absolute terror.]
[The person to eliminate Jae Suk
will gain his 48 coins.]
No, you can't do this to me.
[Whomever that eliminates Jae Suk
will jump into the leading spot.]
No, you can't do this to me.
[Kwang Soo eliminates Ha Ha's name tag!]
[What the heck just happened?]
Lee Kwang Soo, seriously...
You're not even a human being!
- Wow, seriously!
- Please listen to me!
[Dong Hyun, and Kwang Soo vs Jae Suk.]
- You have too many!
- You have to eliminate Kwang Soo.
- You seriously have to eliminate him.
- Dong Hyun, get rid of Kwang Soo!
[Alert the sound on Kwang Soo's betrayal!]
[What the heck is this kid doing?]
[The repeated moments of utter
humiliation throughout the mission.]
[You have shamed, and humiliated me.]
[I will repay you for all the humiliation
that you've given me.]
This is the only chance I have!
[Dong Hyun eliminates Jae Suk's name tag!]
[It's now one on one.
Kwang Soo vs Dong Hyun.]
Can we get a time out?
- There are no time outs.
- No time outs?
There are no time outs?
[Attack all the lower pressure points.]
[Betrayed Ha Ha's soccer kicks of rage.]
- Were you on my side?
- Yes, I was on your side!
Jae Suk, please!
You guys have to listen to me!
Please!
Please hear me out!
- Dong Hyun, please hear me out.
- You're a rotten jerk!
I was going to get Jae Suk for you!
[What a sad, and pathetic sight to behold.]
Please just hear me out.
- I will see you in jail.
- You just wait and see.
- Please hear me out.
- We're going to get our revenge.
You're responsible for this happening to me.
Everyone will be after you.
Jong Kook... he's going to come after you.
Jong Kook will be after you!
I'm sorry!
- I've never seen anything like that!
- What have you ripped off?
[The fighter's monstrous strength rips up
the strong fabric into shreds.]
[Raggedy as his jacket has become,
Kwang Soo is out!]
- I've even ripped up your jacket.
- Follow me!
No, you two can come with me.
- Gary, out.
- Is that Dong Hyun's doing?
[Maybe it's time for me to
start loosening up my muscles.]
The time has finally come.
It's time for me to get ready.
I bet getting ousted must be very upsetting.
What are the eliminated members doing?
- They're in jail.
- SBS has a jail cell?
It's our own makeshift jail cell.
- What is it?
- Are you ousted? Why did you get ousted?
- Who did you get eliminated by?
- I just came by to see how you're doing.
[Just came by to take a tour
of the SBS jail cell.]
- Just eliminate them all.
- When I think about Jong Kook...
then I'm reminded of Dong Hyun.
But when I think about Dong Hyun,
then I'm reminded of Jong Kook.
- Give me some helpful tips.
- You have to join forces.
You have to join forces with
Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo.
Join forces with Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo,
then eliminate them both after that.
No, you can't do that.
Here she comes right now.
[Just then, Ji Hyo walks into the jail cell.]
- Ji Hyo, have you been eliminated?
- She's just here to look around.
- Ji Hyo, are you ousted?
- No, I'm not ousted.
- Then help Shi Kyung eliminate others.
[Then what is she doing in jail?]
- I want to open one more locker.
- Do you remember our agreement?
We seriously have to try to open
the locker on the third floor.
We seriously have to open the locker
up on the third floor!
- Kiss her! Kiss her!
- Deep.
- But...
- You two need to join forces.
- We need to open the locker.
- Join forces, and eliminate the other two.
I'm too scared of those two right now.
[Will they be able to stop the beasts?]
He's coming!
He's headed this way!
[Where could Suk Jin be hiding?]
There he is.
I think I need to eliminate him.
[Big-nose is captured
by the fighter's radar.]
This won't do.
[I'm going to get caught if
I don't do something.]
[I'm pretty sure that
he's around here somewhere...]
[So that's where you've been hiding?]
[But I can still see you very clearly.]
We still have Jong Kook to deal with.
Aren't you going to fight Jong Kook?
Just pretend that I don't even exist.
[This can wait until everyone else
has already been eliminated.]
I'm telling you that Jong Kook is
over there, and he's headed this way.
- I didn't know that you were here.
- Jong Kook.
- Just head back downstairs.
- Okay, Dong Hyun.
[You can't steal my prey
away from me!]
Have a good time!
[Just then! Big-nose
launches an ambush attack!]
[He almost has him!]
[Fighter's animalistic instinct kicks in!]
[Big-nose is attacked as soon as
his ambush attack fails.]
Who fell?
Suk Jin, I'm so sorry.
It's okay, I just won't
watch your fights anymore.
[The fighter is reduced down to begging
from the unexpected grudge from Big-nose.]
[Big-nose's 18 coins
are handed over to Dong Hyun.]
You only gave me 17.
Can't I just keep one as a keepsake?
[Big-nose is eliminated with laughter.]
[Shi Kyung, and Blank Ji head down
to the locker that she saw earlier.]
[After the hint that she saw, she's
convinced Shi Kyung's eight is needed.]
[This could be the final locker
that they need.]
Mine is a dud.
[What's this?]
Where did everyone go?
I bet they're either on the 15th floor,
or on the main floor.
Tenth floor.
[The elevator is headed up
from the tenth floor?]
11... 12... I think it's still coming.
13...
[Verifies that the elevator stopped on 13,
and Kkuk heads down to the 13th floor.]
I'll head out first.
[Kkuk's guess is right on the mark!]
[These two remain clueless
of their imminent danger.]
- Let's get started.
- There's Jong Kook.
[I've got you now!]
What are you guys doing?
We have to get away from him.
Why are you guys running away
from me? Hey, let's talk.
[What do we do?]
Come on, let's talk. Why are you
guys sticking together like that?
Why are you guys together like that?
There's no need for that, is there?
I told him that I'd protect him.
You're going to protect him?
Shi Kyung, don't you want to
rip off her name tag?
- My fingers are itching for it right now.
- But we're going to come after you first.
Jong Kook, you can come after me,
or Dong Hyun.
[Let's just get out of here for now.]
I wonder if Dong Hyun's upstairs.
[The two run away with their hands
tightly clasped together.]
[Just then, Dong Hyun comes
onto the scene!]
I'll flush them out towards you.
[The two beasts team up together
to hunt down the remaining two.]
He's coming!
[Kkuk's net is starting to close in.]
[And the direction
they're headed towards is...]
[Peek-a-boo!]
What is this!
Fancy running into you here.
[Surrounded on all sides.]
- I can't believe this is happening.
- Let's separate these two.
[What's even more terrifying are
their cheery, and smiley faces.]
- You're seriously going to regret this.
- You think we're going to regret it?
Why?
I feel like I'm going to die just from
the sheer intimidation from these two.
You're aware that a lion doesn't let go
of anything once it sinks its teeth into it?
Have you forgotten that
you're a human being?
- Oops, I guess you're right.
- It's okay to forget once in a while.
[All joking aside,
they start to attack for real.]
[Successfully separates the two prey.]
[An extremely disadvantageous battle
for Blank Ji, and Shi Kyung.]
[Blank Ji is out! It's now down
to two hunters, and one prey.]
You're so stupid!
Don't you remember what I told you?
What!
You're so stupid!
Don't you remember what I told you?
- What! What is this!
- What happened?
[Reflect]
[Elimination reflection-
The eliminator is the one to get ousted.]
[That's why I told you
that you're going to regret it...]
[The final locker that Shi Kyung,
and Blank Ji had opened...]
[Shi Kyung earns himself a 'Reflect' sign
from the locker.]
So I'll just have to pretend
like I'm doing my best?
[So thanks to Shi Kyung's acting skills,
Kkuk fell for it completely.]
What!
What the heck is this!
[Even Blank Ji was unaware
of this truth?]
- Why is there an elimination reflection?
- Jong Kook!
I really wanted a big match with you.
I even had a plan for it.
I even had a whole plan for it.
Next time... I'll see you in the ring.
- I'll see you in the cage.
- Call me, and I'll meet you in the cage!
- I'll see you in there for sure!
- Okay, you got it.
[Unfortunately, the showdown between
the two hunters will be delayed.]
Good luck.
Kim Jong Kook, out.
[At last... the currency exchange is open!]
[Dong Hyun is in the current lead
with a total of 80 coins.]
[Instead of exchanging his currency,
he sits, and waits for Shi Kyung to arrive.]
[And watching this whole scene
in secret is...]
[Shi Kyung, with his 50 coins.]
[It's time to face the battle!]
[Ambush attack!]
[Fighter, Kim Dong Hyun vs
Brain, Sung Shi Kyung.]
[What will be the result of this battle?]
We will first reveal who the
final winner is.
Please lift up the money bag
on the count of three.
[The race of the golden key-
Time to reveal the winner.]
- Who's the winner?
- Three!
[Dong Hyun vs Shi Kyung.
Who's the final winner?]
[The Stun gun, Kim Dong Hyun, wins!]
[Shi Kyung's ambush attempt
is easily thwarted.]
[And is twisted into a compromising
position in an alarming speed.]
- No, this is so unfair!
- The world is an unfair place.
I can't carry a tune myself.
- Why do I...
- What did I tell you about the lions?
[A lion never lets go of its prey.]
[Sung Shi Kyung, out!]
[Complete humiliation]
[Winner, Kim Dong Hyun,
wins a total of 130 coins.]
[Wins a prize of 1.3 million Won.]
- This is awesome.
- I had so much fun.
The writers did such a great job
of setting up all the games, and scenes.
It really helps to put you in the mood,
and you really get into it.
- I'm bummed I didn't get to fight Jong Kook.
- You'll just have to come back then.
I'll see you in the cage.
[We'll wait to see your battle
inside the cage.]
Let's give our winner, Kim Dong Hyun,
a huge round of applause!
[We wish you all the luck
in the fighting cage!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Big-nose is having a winning streak?]
[Still so young at heart...]
[And they're young for real!]
[Kim Woo Bin]
[Kang Ha Neul]
[Jun Ho]
[The reality is a ticking bomb
waiting to explode?]
[The whole place is in an uproar
from all the energy and excitement!]
[The fearful, and quick footed youths...]
[I will protect my Big-nose Brother!]
[Next week on Running Man-
Protect the 20-year old Big-nosed Brother.]