[Uncovering hidden gems]
[Running Man finds gemstones]
[Unexpected outcome enough to sweep
the idol industries off their feet]
['O' Space Center in Incheon]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Running Man members have been
shooting for two days in a row.
We have a sore throat.
Please understand that.
They are wearing sunglasses
to cover their faces.
Reveal it!
I think it's because they ate something
before they went to sleep.
I think he needs to go see a doctor.
Seriously.
I don't know who the guests are
but they're all dead meat.
[This song sounds familiar.]
Isn't it Super Junior's song?
[Is Hee Chul going to be here today?]
[A man is running towards
the members with a sign.]
[A Super Junior member
is on Running Man!]
[The perfect visual, Si Won?]
[The well-grounded guy, Hee Chul?]
[Or the leader, Leeteuk?]
[Which member came to
visit Running Man?]
[Huh? Is he...?]
[Super Junior's Ryeo Wook]
[He pushed out the usual members
who appear on variety shows.]
[It's rare to see Ryeo Wook
on variety shows.]
[He's fully dressed as if he's going to
perform on the stage.]
- Am I overdressed?
- You look nice.
Why are you carrying your name?
This is my concept.
[First guest is a rare guest
to see on variety shows.]
[What's the theme today?]
We have more guests, right?
4Minute!
[Someone is in a hurry]
[A member from 4Minute?]
[Could it be Hyuna?]
[4Minute's leader, Ji Hyun?]
[Get ready.]
Hello!
[4Minute's Kwon So Hyun]
[Seeing the guests...]
[One of the top girl groups,
4Minute's youngest member.]
[It seems like she's on a
variety show for the first time.]
[So Hyun is 22 years old now.]
- You're already 22?
- How old are you now, Ryeo Wook?
- I'm 29 yeas old.
Is the age difference between
Kwang Soo and you only one year?
- No, it's two years.
- Am I older?
[How can you say that by
looking at Kwang Soo's face?]
- He looks very young.
- You look young, not him.
Who's next?
[Today's theme seems like...]
[The song is...]
BEAST!
[Amongst the BEAST members,
who would it be?]
[Talented guy, Ki Kwang?]
[Hot-blooded leader,
Yoon Doo Joon?]
[The BEAST member
that came to Running Man is...]
[BEAST's Son Dong Woon.]
[There was a rumor about his wit.]
It’s very rare to see him
somewhere other than a stage.]
Dong Woon is an ambitious guy.
[He wants close-ups.]
[He showed his ability to pick
the right spot on music programs.]
[The ambitious guy,
Dong Woon.]
- That ambition hasn't been revealed yet.
- He's handsome.
[He was hoping for others
to recognize his ambition.]
As I see the guests
coming out one by one
I can tell what kind of theme
we'll have today.
[They are the members of
popular groups but...]
[He can't really say it out loud.]
I have a feeling.
I know why they are
holding the signs.
I was doubtful when I saw Ryeo Wook
and So Hyun
but I'm pretty sure now
that Dong Woon came out.
They're not really
representing their groups.
Ryeo Wook thinks it's the
youngest members special.
He's saying we could be wrong.
[So Hyun and Dong Woon are also
the youngest of their groups.]
Let's see if Ryeo Wook
is right or if we're right.
[Youngest members' special
or the unnoticed members' special?]
[Let's see who comes next.]
[Infinite's song?]
[He's overacting
the moment he steps in.]
[I think we're right.]
[Infinite's Jang Dong Woo.]
[I'm the hidden gemstone of Infinite.]
I really like Infinite, but I've never
seen you on variety shows.
[He debuted five years ago, but it's his
first time on a Sunday variety show.]
- Are you the youngest in your group?
- No, I'm the second oldest!
[So, the theme is not
the youngest special.]
Are you the second oldest?
I'm the second oldest.
I'm the second oldest, too.
I'm the second child of my parents.
He's witty.
See? He has ambition.
[Today's theme is indeed,
the unnoticed idol members special!]
This is a really good idea.
There are lots of idol members but
we don't get to see them very often.
That's right.
We had no opportunities!
You should have been on variety shows
countless times already!
I wonder who will be the next?
[Girl's Day's song is being played.]
[Her ambitious
and cute dance moves.]
[Girl's Day's So Jin.]
[The leader of Girl's Day,
So Jin.]
[Now it's time to take
the lead on variety shows.]
I can feel the thirst
of all these idols.
[Their thirst for variety shows.]
- It's my first time seeing So Jin.
- Me, too.
I never knew there was such a pretty
and bright member in that group.
And we never saw her on variety shows.
I thinks she's the prettiest
Girl's Day member.
She is really pretty.
[It's a mystery that she hasn't
been on a variety show before.]
- Look how pretty So Hyun is.
- Thank you.
In 4Minute, there's Hyuna...
- Hyuna, Hyuna...
- Hyuna, and Hyuna.
In Super Junior,
there's Si Won, Leeteuk, Hee Chul...
No, no!
There's Ryeo Wook.
In Beast, there's
Ki Kwang, Doo Joon.
And Ki Kwang, and Ki Kwang.
In Infinite,
there's Sung Kyu, L, Sung Kyu.
In Girl's Day, there's Minah,
Hyeri, Minah, Hyeri.
- So Jin is right here.
[But I'm the leader.]
Now's the time to turn the tide over!
You know what today's theme is.
- We have more guests.
- We have more?
[Rare idols on a variety show,
the rarest idol is coming.]
- It's Teen Top!
- Niel is coming.
[He seems pretty chill.]
[Teen Top's Niel.]
Ryeo Wook and So Hyun
are very upset.
Because Niel is too
famous to be here.
He doesn't fit in.
He's the main vocalist.
He's not thirsty!
[Still, it's his first time
on Running Man.]
Teen Top is not that famous yet,
I want to promote my group.
[They've performed in 20 countries.]
[Teen Top is more popular
in foreign countries.]
[And Niel plays a leading part.]
He's somewhat similar to Kwang Soo.
People always say it to me.
Why are you glaring at me
when you say that?
Niel and I were
in a TV commercial together.
[They were in a beverage commercial.]
He may look like Kwang Soo
but he's different.
- Thank you.
- What do you mean thank you?
They're all looking good.
[This time, a weird
gemstone is coming.]
[The overly ambitious, Eric Nam.]
- Ah, it's Eric Nam!
[He's even more excited.]
[Eric Nam]
[He's a great singer who was
a contestant of an audition program.]
[He's broadened his career as a reporter
especially for foreign celebrities.]
I know Eric (A Shinhwa member) though.
Ah, you were a contestant
of an audition program?
Yes!
I'm sorry but I've never
heard his song before.
I've heard his name a lot,
but not his song.
- He looks mature.
- I'm 28 years old.
[Someone is running
with lightning fast speed.]
[Which group is he from?]
BtoB!
[Is he dancing to the song 'Beep Beep'?]
[He's ambitious, too.]
[BtoB's Min Hyuk]
[BtoB's rapper
and a very athletic idol.]
He's really good at sports.
You can see him twice a year.
[Field day specials are on
New year's day and Thanksgiving day.]
I'm getting teary here.
[There aren't many opportunities
for them to show their talents.]
[The last guest]
[From the way he walks,
he looks unique.]
He's the leader of VIXX, N.
[The hottest group
amongst idol groups, VIXX!]
[I lead the way of VIXX!]
VIXX is the hottest group
amongst teenagers.
You're praising yourself?
[Very ambitious introduction.]
- We know VIXX.
Let's welcome them.
Welcome!
[They are rarely seen
on variety shows.]
[Finding the Hidden Gemstones Race.]
I'm actually in charge of
variety shows in my group.
Is that true?
I've been DJ'ing for a radio show
for more than three years.
And I've been MC'ing on a cable channel
for more than a year.
You have?
- He's the Yoo Jae Suk of cable TV.
- Is that so?
Just how many Yoo Jae Suks
are there on cable channels?
That's why I can't air
on cable channels.
Because there are too many
Yoo Jae Suks?
When you arrived here,
did you get the feel of today's theme?
- Yes, I did.
[It's an ambition special.]
So Hyun, who made you
think that the most?
When I saw Eric Nam.
I'm Eric Nam.
Please treat me favorably.
I envy you.
So Jin, who do you think fit
to this theme the most?
Ryeo Wook.
[He's shocked.]
[I'm sorry.]
She's older than me.
- Really?
- Are you serious?
- How old are you?
- I'm thirty.
[It doesn't make sense.]
So Jin is 30?
She looks so young.
She looks like she's 23.
[The new icon of baby face, So Jin.]
- This is the beginning.
[The warming up is over.]
Why are you covering me?
I should be on the screen
as much as possible!
Why is everyone so sensitive?
I'm sorry.
[Everyone wants to be on screen
as many times as possible.]
Be confident, everyone.
You are the true gemstones
of variety shows.
What you're saying
makes us feel smaller.
[Agreeing.]
Why would you say that?
You said this is
a hidden gemstone special
but I'm already becoming a jewel...
[N's whimsical reply.]
[We can tell he is prepared.]
He needs to change his name from 'N' to
'This guy' as in 'What's with this guy?'
- And I'm the leader of my group...
- You're the group leader?
the best dancer, a pretty good singer,
and also in charge of sexiness.
Is he a narcissist?
It's true. I'm also in the drama
'The Family is Coming'.
- With So Jin.
-That's right.
- Then you should know each other well.
- We have a love connection.
N is very proud of it
and So Jin seems to be shy.
It's because I'm not divorced yet.
[She feels awkward admitting their affair
since she's a married woman in the drama.]
[How would their relationship be
on Running Man?]
[Managers]
[Idols]
[Team Red] [Team Pink]
[Team White] [Team Blue]
The missions for
the 'Job Well Done Race' are
the games that are picked
by the guests.
They picked the games from the previous
races of Running Man earlier.
- We met earlier.
- Really?
According to the result of each mission
you will get a gold bar
with a 'Job Well Done' stamp.
The team that gets the most
gold bars will be the winner
and only the winner can
actually take the gold bars.
Managers, please help your
team members.
[We'll now start the Finding
Hidden Gemstone Race!]
What do you usually do
when you're home, Dong Woon?
I stay in bed.
- I like to light up a scented candle...
- A scented candle?
It's my healing therapy.
Not that I need it...
Even before you debuted...
So Hyun says she's 22 now.
Didn't you debut when you
were 16?
I was 16 when I joined 4Minute.
- Were you doing something before then?
- I was on SBS's True Game once.
I don't think you remember me
because I was in elementary school.
[A kid from a dance competition grew up
and became a member of 4Minute.]
Ryeo Wook, you're not very active.
I'm better at talk shows.
I told Hee Chul and Dong Hae
that I'm going to be on Running Man.
But they didn't believe me.
So I said 'It's real!'.
Then Dong Hae said "Why you?"
- Dong Hae should come, too.
- We need to introduce Dong Hae, too.
There are so many people
we need to introduce.
[Arriving at the first mission site.]
What game is this? It looks like
we're in the middle of a rice field.
- What is it?
- Is it the mudflat?
[It's in the middle of winter.
It can't be a mud game..]
[Shiny mudflat on a winter day.]
[Who picked the game
that will be played here?]
- Let's get out.
[They're smiling upon arrival.]
[They're smiling upon their arrival.]
You can go that way.
[How will their first
experience at a mudflat be?]
[It's their first time seeing wetsuits.]
Eric, pick a pretty one quickly.
There are name tags on them.
- Do I just wear one?
- Yes, Ryeo Wook.
[Rule no.1 :No one's going to help you.]
- Where do I put my shoe lifts?
[Rule no.2 : Boots are a must,
shoe lifts are optional.]
Remove your mic.
[Rule no.3 : Remove your mic.]
- You know what it means?
It means your whole body
will get wet.
I've never worn this before.
Niel, I told you
not to make a scene like this.
[The Managers know
it from their experiences.]
[Finally, it's time to get in.]
- Gather with your team members.
- Eric, Niel!
[It's hard to make a move for them.]
- Come on, guys.
- Ryeo Wook!
Try and get the close-up scene.
They love the mudflat.
Thanks to Min Hyuk, we're all here.
Thank you, Min Hyuk.
[At the meeting earlier,
Min Hyuk wrote mudflat game.]
The first game will be
'One Heart and Mind on the Mudflat'.
All four team members
will start running at the same time.
When you hear a loud pop,
huge work pants will shoot out.
You should try and grab the pants,
then all four members get in the pants.
You see the flags with an R mark?
There is a rubber mat at the finish line.
All four of you have to be
on the board.
Ryeo Wook doesn't exercise.
And he doesn't understand
the game instructions.
Managers, please explain the game.
Go to the starting line, everyone.
[The first mission has begun.]
Can I help you, So Jin?
[Giraffe is reaching out to help her.]
Do you have a boyfriend, So Jin?
He's flirting over there.
What are you talking about?
- Anyone can tell.
- That's what I'm saying.
- I'm a bit nervous all of a sudden.
- Why?
- Don't be nervous!
- Be nervous!
I won't blow a whistle
but you will hear the pop.
Then you will see a pair of
pants shoot out.
In a bit, another pair of pants will shoot
out, and there will be 4 pants in total.
Get ready!
[First round of 'One heart
and mind on the mudflat'.]
[First pair of pants are flying.]
[Surprised.]
[Running at full speed for the pants.]
[Min Hyuk grabbed it.]
[Three team members
are chasing after the pants.]
[Indoor style entertainer Ryeo Wook
hasn't adjusted to the mudflats yet.
[Min Hyuk is dodging pretty well.]
[This is the proper way to play.]
[Right then, the second pair
of pants shoot out.]
[All four team members
follow the trace of the pants.]
[The work pants come first.]
[She's learning the game
with every fiber of her body.]
[Third pants shoot out.]
It's right there.
[Team Red and Team Blue
are after the third pair of pants.]
[In the meantime, Team Pink gets the pants.]
[Team White is starting to wear one.]
[Team Red and Team Blue
are still fighting over the pants.]
[The last pants shoot out.]
[Niel quickly grabs the pants.]
[All the teams get one pair of pants each.]
[They need to wear them
and get to the finish line.]
[All other teams are starting
to wear their pants.]
The first team to wear the pants
and stand on the board wins.]
[Slapstick comedy happens more
when they're in a hurry.]
[Pink team is wearing the pants
without any interruptions.]
[We can't let them wear it so peacefully!]
[Jae Suk and Dong Woon attack them.]
[Kwang Soo is interrupting his own team.]
[While the three teams struggle...]
[Team White is advancing.]
[Team Pink is after them.]
[First team on the mat wins.]
[The winner of the first round takes a
break when this round is over.]
[Team White wins.]
[First round winner, Team White.]
Everyone lost their energy
only after one round.
[I envy them... they are
escaping from the mudflat.]
[The winner of the first round can
sit back and watch the others.]
Min Hyuk is certainly fast.
Min Hyuk, why did you pick this game?
It's so cold here!
It was a good choice!
An excellent choice!
[The three teams go back
to the starting line.]
We're empty-handed.
They're not here any more, so
we can show what we can do now.
- Our team has good members.
- So this is how the mudflat is.
So this is how the mudflat is.
I'm very happy and satisfied.
I had enough fun.
I hope other people can feel
the happiness now.
- We can take a break now?
- Let's watch them now.
- It's all because of So Hyun.
- Why?
By the way, Niel...
Your face is too clean.
You're even cleaner than So Jin.
[Running Man members are teaching
him what a variety show is about.]
[Exploring the mudflat with Niel's face.]
[He gave up his beauty for his team.]
Niel, you're going to make
Teen Top famous today.
[If I can promote Teen Top...]
You have the most clean face
in your team now.
- It's all dried up.
- Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
[Washing up his face with mud.]
[Styling his hair with mud.]
[He's having a mud feast.]
[Team Blue is playing
the human domino chain.]
[Niel is perfectly adjusted
to the mudflat.]
Are you okay, Niel?
He's doing a good job.
[The fairy of the mudflat,
why did you come so late?]
It feels refreshing.
I didn't know it would be
nice out here in the winter.
-I know, right?
- I thought it would be just cold.
Ryeo Wook, how would you feel
if you were standing there?
It would be frustrating.
I guess I felt refreshing because we won.
Now I can enjoy the sight.
Now you know why people like
mudflats so much.
[Second Round]
- Dong Woon!
- Yes, Captain!
Let's do it!
[The winning team
will be able to take a break.]
We don't know when it will start.
[Get the pants as quick as you can
and get to the finish line.]
[Dong Woon catches them
as he dives into the mud.]
[The other team members pounce on him.]
[The second pants shoot out.]
[Niel's nice catch.]
[But he gets thrown right away.]
[Big-nose was on his way
to help him but blocked by So Hyun.]
[In the meantime,
N could get the pants easily.]
[The last pants shoot out.]
- It's right there.
- It's like we're watching a football game.
[Wherever the pants land,
it turns into a madhouse.]
[Team Pink gets together
to wear the pants.]
[Stop the Team Pink.]
[Niel is on his way.]
[He was on his way for a
slapstick routine.]
It's so funny.
Who is this game for?
What is this?
You can't even see the
faces of the guests.
Are you sure this game
was picked for idols?
[No matter what, I will be
the main character today!]
I never knew that pants were
that stretchy before.
They don't rip.
[So Hyun gets the pants.]
[Team Pink is almost done
wearing the pants.]
[Eric Nam is blocking it
with all his strength.]
[Stop Team Pink.]
[Those two in front passed
the finish line.]
[They tried to stop N and So Jin.]
[Team Pink finally pass it.]
Team Pink won.
- Mommy!
[We miss our mothers at times like these.]
Who was it?
Who picked this game? Min Hyuk!
[Who... are you?]
This time, it will be a real mud fight.
Only one team will be left.
I might be swearing.
Bear with it.
We're really upset.
We have the first and second winner,
so only the third place is left.
Big-nosed Brother, aren't you cold?
I'll give you a muffler.
It's much better.
This is so warm.
Thanks, Jae Suk.
Who's that?
[Who are you?]
[An organism resembling
Eric Nam is approaching.]
[We find another one who might be Niel.]
[The first and second winners
are watching them together.]
[The final round]
[Team Red vs. Team Blue-
Who will be the last winner?]
[Two pants shoot out at the same time.]
[Struggles for both pair of pants.]
It looks like a war
when I watch it from here.
I was doing that?
- It's so much fun to watch.
- They don't look like humans anymore.
[Kwang Soo takes the pants
and runs away.]
[How far are you going to go?]
Why are you running so far?
Just stop it!
You will go all the way to China.
[He's about the cross the West Sea.]
I don't want to live this way!
What are we doing in the
middle of winter?
[Just come back.]
Kwang Soo, I'll go first.
[Where are you going?]
[Let's go together.]
[Endless duel of the two men.]
Jae Suk, you need to hurry back!
Wait for me!
[He's showing what variety is
about with his whole body.]
Wear your pants!
[Both teams start to wear the pants.]
[Who's faster?]
[The team who gets first
is the last winner.]
[The finish line was so close.]
[Team Blue wins the third round.]
[Exhausted]
[The red team lost by an inch.]
Don't look!
[Kwang Soo's pantless fashion
will be remembered forever.]
[Team White gets three gold bars.]
The second winner gets two gold bars.]
- Get off!
- I'm Niel.
[He camouflaged to get
the gold bars.]
[Team Blue gets one gold bar.]
[The first mission is over.]
[Running News
Niel, trades his looks for his talent.]
[So Hyun's desire for winning
surprises Mr. Capable!]
We'll include washing up
as a special mission.
The team who washes up the fastest
will get a gold bar.
[He is Eric Nam (not a beast).]
I'm not a monster.
Do they have a shower
for everyone?
[It's time to get myself back.]
Do you have a change of clothes?
Stop filming!
That's enough!
I've been looking like this
the whole time?
[After a short while...]
[N came out first.]
[Gary came out second.]
- N!
[All the members have to
get in the car.]
- Jong Kook!
- So Hyun!
[Ji Hyo is looking for the other members.]
- Ha Ha!
- Where are you?
So Hyun!
Let me do the make up for you!
- Girls don't answer at all.
- Seriously?
- So Hyun!
- No one replies.
[We can't get in.]
- So Jin!
[Dong Woo returns as a flower boy.]
- Where is Dong Woon?
- I haven't seen him.
Why are you blocking the way?
- Are you leaving now?
- Of course, I am.
- No, you're not.
- Move your car.
How come I don't see any of my team members?
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- He's here!
Stop him!
- Get out!
- Are you going to date me or not?
[Gary's playing hard to get.]
Where do I need to go?
[All the members of Team Blue are here.]
[Team Red tries to get in the blue car.]
[Right then, all the
members of Team Red arrive.]
- Is Team White here?
- Hey, you're team is all out.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
[Dong Woo is carrying Kwang Soo
on his shoulders and taking him away.]
[N is interrupting Team Red.]
- Jae Suk!
[Kwang Soo gets in the car
without one of his shoes.]
Team Blue wins!
Feel! Sense! Niel! Eric! Cross!
[Team Blue gets an additional gold bar.]
Think how hard it was to get a
gold bar at the mudflat.
[Kyeyang Library in Incheon]
- What is it?
- Hello!
I think it's the name tag elimination.
It looks like a prison cell.
It's the name tag elimination.
[They've heard a lot about it.
Worried and excited at the same time.]
[Team White, Ryeo Wook is pretty slow.]
[Today's name tag elimination is different.]
[There's no hidden spot.]
Before we start, I have something to say.
Kwang Soo stole one of our gold bars.
I understand he wanted to take it
but stealing is wrong!
[This is what Kwang Soo stole.]
That gold bar belongs to us,
why are you hesitating so much?
- Say, 'please'.
- What did you say?
- Then don't.
Give him.
What are you doing?
[It seems very important.]
[The case is terminated peacefully.]
By the way,
please don't let Gary wear pink.
[Gary in pink makes people's eyes hurt.]
- Please, don't.
- I'm depressed all day long.
I have to play the name tag elimination
but I don't look strong at all.
Amongst all the guests, Dong Woo,
Dong Woon, Eric Nam, and N
wanted to play the name tag
elimination game.
This time, the name tag elimination to win
against Running Man will be 1 versus 3.
Each team has a representing
team member.
Yoo Jae Suk, Kim Jong Kook,
Lee Kwang Soo, and Gary.
- These 4 people are the representatives.
- Suk Jin is not?
I expected to hear my name.
[Big-nose spirit:
Always greedy for positions.]
We picked the representatives
by their winning rate.
Yoo Jae Suk, Kim Jong Kook, Lee Kwang Soo
and Gary are the representatives.
Let's say the three members
except Yoo Jae Suk
pick another team's representative.
If they pick Kim Jong Kook,
they have to play with Kim Jong Kook.
If they succeed eliminating
Kim Jong Kook's name tag
depending on the time it takes,
the fastest to succeed wins.
Three of you can do it, so be careful.
If Kim Jong Kook eliminates
all three members' name tags
this team will be ousted.
It's very difficult to eliminate
three name tags.
We'll draw from the team
who arrived first.
We have no choice.
I'm getting nervous.
Pick one.
- Pick one...
- But they are not good at it.
- But Ji Hyo is good at it.
-Yes, you have Ji Hyo.
[Min Hyuk picked one.]
- You guys have one Running Man member.
Then let's see
who Team White picked.
[Kwang Soo? Jae Suk? Gary?]
[Gary]
[Gary of the Pink Team is chosen.]
Song Ji Hyo's on that team.
[Fate's cruel joke?
Monday Couple to face off.]
Ji Hyo always texts me
after the show.
- These two are really...
- When did I ever do that?
[Really?]
- Ji Hyo being on that team...
[How long will it take to eliminate Gary?]
White Team is pretty weak when
you take Jong Kook out of the equation.
[Rule- The representative of each team
is unable to participate in the game.]
- Ryeo Wook, you have to do a good job.
- Fighting!
- He kept saying he'll get it done quickly.
[Ryeo Wook makes Jong Kook nervous.]
[Gary vs Ji Hyo, Ryeo Wook, and Min Hyuk.]
Take it easy, okay?
- We're getting started, right?
[These two seem extremely nervous.]
- Gary, you may get started.
- What do we do!
What are you going to do?
He's no joke as an opponent.
- He's really scary, isn't he?
- That's right.
[Gary goes up to the second floor.]
- Gary is up on the second floor.
- Gary will go up to the third floor.
- There he goes right now.
- It's instinctive to go up to the top.
He says it's instinctive to go to
the end. He's so scary.
[Looking for a place to hide.]
- Rather than getting caught while hiding...
[Decides to wait in the stairwell between
the second and the third floor instead.]
[Ryeo Wook and Min Hyuk test out their
walkie-talkies for the first time.]
- You'll get started in 15 seconds.
- Can you hear me?
I can't hear anything.
Do I press this button?
You have to press down
on the button while you talk.
[With the big battle looming ahead,
they get a quick lesson from Blank Ji.]
- Okay, I got it.
- Can you hear me?
- Ryeo Wook is really weak in strength.
He couldn't even rip off the name tag
of his own strength.
- Seriously, he couldn't rip it off.
- They're like a flock of sheep.
[Gentle sheep full of fright...
Will they be able to get the job done?]
[Gary vs White Team.
Start the name tag elimination!]
- Let's go up to the third floor.
- I'm going up to the third floor.
- Hey, you can't leave me alone like this!
- Just start searching for him.
I'm going to get really scared
if I run into him on my own.
[Fearful Ryeo Wook gets startled by the VJ.]
- Why is he so fearful? This is bad.
[What are you doing, Ryeo Wook?]
[Gary is waiting in the stairwell
by the third floor lobby.]
What's this?
[Gary is discovered!]
Ji Hyo!
[Gary is found! It's only a matter
of time before he's surrounded.]
[Gary is surrounded by all three
in the third floor lobby.]
- Ryeo Wook is chasing after him.
- Gary shouldn't be running away.
Ryeo Wook, don't go after him.
Ryeo Wook!
[Gary vs Ji Hyo.
All eyes are on the fight.]
Let's grab him.
[Instead, Gary is the one to
grab Ryeo Wook!]
[Luckily survives the attack
with Ji Hyo's help.]
- Focus! Just stay still.
- Wow, he's amazing.
Why aren't you focusing?
[Busy taking care of
high maintenance Ryeo Wook.]
- Ji Hyo's acting as the commander.
[White Team's commander, Blank Ji.]
Why is Ryeo Wook standing so far away?
[Scaredy cat, Ryeo Wook, stays far away.]
- What they're doing isn't easy.
- The clock is still ticking.
[The clock keeps on ticking...]
- They got him!
You have to grab him!
[But Gary quickly escapes
from their clutches.]
- Wow, Gary's good.
- This isn't easy for Gary, either.
[Muscly Min Hyuk desperately attempts
to maintain his grip on Gary.]
[But he almost loses his own
name tag in his attempt.]
How are we going to eliminate him?
Someone has to grab him
even if one must be sacrificed.
- They have to go against him.
- They have to grab his arms.
Wasting their time like that is useless.
[Successfully pushes Gary into a corner.]
[Min Hyuk pins down his arms!]
[Ace Ji Hyo jumps in!]
[White Team successfully eliminates Gary.]
- Kang Gary.
- I was seriously terrified.
[How long did it take the White Team
to eliminate Gary's name tag?]
Ugh, I'm tired.
[The time it took for the elimination
will soon be revealed.]
- Gary, it was like something out of a movie.
- Wow, that was great.
Gary, you did great.
Guys, you did great, too.
You did better than I had expected.
I thought you'd get eliminated instead.
I thought you guys were
going to be eliminated.
You guys did much better
than I had expected.
It's time to determine whom
the Blue Team will go up against.
- One member can come up and choose.
- We get to draw?
- It'll be Ji Suk Jin...
- I'll go and draw.
- This team won't be easy, either.
- Choose wisely, okay?
- You'd better not choose Jong Kook, okay?
- He already made his selection.
- Hand me what you have chosen.
- It had better be Jae Suk.
I have a feeling that it's Jong Kook.
[A fifty-fifty chance.
Yoo Hyuk vs Mr. Capable.]
- Please let it be Jae Suk.
- I think it's Jong Kook.
[Despair]
[Kim Jong Kook vs
Suk Jin, Niel, and Eric Nam.]
Since they're all males,
at least I don't have to be careful.
- Ugh, what a relief.
- It's such a relief.
I'm going to show everyone
what I'm made of.
[Is that right?
Then shall we get started?]
[Mr. Capable vs Suk Jin, Niel, and Eric Nam.]
I'm not even kidding when I tell you
that Jong Kook is seriously no joke.
[Don't fall for that easy going smile...]
- We're determined, too.
- Yes, we're very determined.
[Blue Team, fighting!]
Since there are three
males on the Blue Team
they're more difficult as an opponent
when they're on the defense.
But Jong Kook is the most difficult
target to attack for any team.
It really is a battle of
strength this time.
I really can't stand how Jong Kook is
strutting around like that and acting cocky.
I know what you mean.
His overconfident strut, right?
[One man's fearless stroll.]
There's nowhere to even hide.
[Then how should I do this?]
You can't help but want to flee
when you see Jong Kook.
- Should I not run away even if I'm alone?
- Run away if you're alone.
Scream out his location
as you run away from him.
But if two or more of us are together,
then we have to attack him.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, Suk Jin.
- This is no joke. This is for real.
- This is really happening, isn't it?
- You're facing off with Kim Jong Kook.
- Why did I draw that slip of paper?
[Time to let go of your regrets...
and face the battle!]
- Just pin down both his arms.
- His arms?
- Ready, go!
- Let's go!
[Jong Kook vs The Blue Team-
Start the name tag elimination.]
[Mr. Capable is waiting for them
at the top of the stairs!]
[Come and get me.]
[Why is he using the walkie-talkie
when they're all standing together?]
[You're not getting past me
on these steps.]
- They're running up to him.
- There they go!
Why aren't they going?
- I bet that's really scary.
- They can't keep stalling time like that.
He's using the elevation
to his advantage.
Being in a tight and elevated spot like that
could be advantageous for Jong Kook.
But they have to
push their way in right now.
- There you go!
- There they go.
[Chooses to face off with
Jong Kook head-on.]
[The imminent face-off.]
Running away isn't going to
do us any good right now.
[Decides to forge ahead
under Big-nose's orders.]
[Mr. Capable is surrounded
on all three sides!]
[A tight battle of strength.]
Battling three at once
isn't easy even for Jong Kook.
[All eyes are focused on
the action scene on screen.]
Don't back down.
[Big-nose attacks,
but is thwarted to attack Eric Nam.]
[Okay, my name tag is still
on my back.]
[The name tag]
- He ripped off Niel's tag!
[In the blink of an eye, Niel is ousted!]
- What just happened?
- You just got ousted.
[One shot, one kill.
This is the power of Mr. Capable.]
He just ousted Niel.
[It is now one vs two.]
Don't let him get his hands on you.
[Big-nose gets his hands
on Jong Kook's name tag!]
[Will Big-nose succeed in
ripping off Mr. Capable's name tag?]
[Big-nose rips it off!]
[Big-nose successfully eliminates
Mr. Capable's name tag!]
- Wow, he did it!
- Wow, he eliminated him!
Suk Jin ripped it off!
[How can this be?]
Big-nose did it!
I pretty much had him.
- But I was caught by the door.
- Okay!
[Just how long did it take The Blue Team
to accomplish their mission?]
[A standing ovation.]
- Wow, Suk Jin.
- Destiny is meant to be changed.
[It's been a long while since the victor
and the loser has swapped roles.]
- I eliminated him rather quickly.
- Wow, that was impressive.
- Why aren't you cheering for me?
- I can't believe that just happened.
[Big-nose, you did an amazing job!]
You pretty much sacrificed Eric Nam,
and eliminated Jong Kook on your own.
[Bait, Eric Nam and Big-fish,
Big-nose's perfect teamwork.]
- I thought I had this one in the bag
- I thought we had this one, too.
[Overconfidence led to his loss.]
Then we'll be facing off
against Jae Suk, won't we?
- Then I have to go in?
- Fighting.
[Yoo Jae Suk, fighting!]
- Fighting!
[I will get that gold bar.]
[Yoo Jae Suk vs Ha Ha, So Jin, and N.]
[Runs up to the library
on the second floor.]
Come in.
Ready, set, go!
[Jae Suk vs The Pink Team.
Start the name tag elimination.]
Where is he?
Where did he go?
We have to find him.
I wonder if he's up here?
[Number one common mistake by newbies-
Staying together in a group.]
Is he hiding?
I'm going to check upstairs.
[Ha Ha goes off to the third floor.]
I doubt that he'd be in here.
[Number two common mistake by newbies-
Not searching thoroughly enough.]
So Jin!
So Jin, come on.
He's not here.
[What do you mean, I'm not?
I'm right here.]
Let's go up to the third floor.
[What a bunch of newbies...
passing right by Jae Suk.]
[Eric Nam checks the bag...]
[But the gold bar is missing!]
[Who stole it out of our bag?]
- Who took it?
- It wasn't me.
- Come on!
- I already gave you one!
- What?
- This is going over the line.
- It wasn't me!
- It really wasn't me.
[Suspects Gary of being the culprit.]
- Did someone take their gold?
- I told you that it wasn't me.
- Someone wiped them out?
- I'm telling you that it wasn't me.
- Who stole our gold?
- This isn't allowed, is it?
[Let's forget about the gold for now,
and get back to the name tag elimination.]
- He's in the manager's office right now.
- They still haven't found him yet?
What's taking them so long?
They have to find him!
He's doing a great job
of dragging out the time.
- Where is he?
[Where in the world is he hiding?]
[In the meantime, Jae Suk
moves on to the supply room.]
[Jae Suk's plan is to drag out the time
by fleeing from his opponents.]
- Hey, what are we going to do? Let's go!
- He's dragging out the time.
What if he's upstairs in the library?
[Pink Team heads back to
the supply room on the second floor.]
- Let's check the library.
- It's over here.
I'm sure he's moved again
to somewhere else by now.
Search every corner of this room.
There he is!
[There he is!]
[Get him!]
- Okay, I see him.
- Come here and corner him over there.
[Where did he go?]
[They finally get their hands on him!]
We have to rip off his name tag!
[Must rip it off vs Can't rip it off!]
[The bloody battle of name tag elimination.]
[Jae Suk's counterattack
is definitely at a disadvantage.]
[So Jin, out!]
- Wow, Jae Suk is so strong!
- I think Jae Suk actually has a chance.
- Wow, I think we might win this.
- What if he ousts the other two?
- Why is Gary kneeling down?
- Because I'm frustrated.
Gary was good at dragging out
some time himself.
What are they doing?
Please let go!
We don't have any gold.
You guys have no idea
how desperate we feel right now.
[Running Man's hidden Mr. Capable,
Power-Yoo.]
The grip he has on his teeth...
He lasted on the grip
and the venom of his teeth.
[How long did it take
the Pink Team to oust Jae Suk?]
Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- That was no joke.
[Yoo Jae Suk is the best!]
- It's up to us now.
- You guys have to do well.
[The Red Team will have to go up against
the king of trickery, Giraffe Kwang Soo.]
[Will they be able to eliminate the name tag
without a single RM member on their side?]
One, two, three!
[What are these guys doing?]
- Ten seconds left before you start.
- Ah, ten seconds?
[Giraffe-Kwang Soo's once famous
fast hand moves.]
[Kwang Soo vs
So Hyun, Dong Woo and Dong Woon.]
He's not on the third floor.
[Dong Woo and Dong Woon are
searching through the second floor.]
Dong Woo, what if he's not
on the second floor?
- I wonder if he's on the third floor.
- I think he's on the third floor.
It's okay, it hasn't been that long yet.
They remind me of Dumb and Dumber.
I told them not to stick
together like that.
- You guys startled me.
- Is he not up here?
[They're unable to find Kwang Soo
up on the third floor.]
- I wonder if he's hiding in a locker?
- Where could a big man like that be hiding?
[That big man is hiding out
in the reading room.]
[The Red Team heads back down
to the second floor.]
[Unable to decide where to go.]
[Dong Woon heads into the reading room.]
- Where do you think he went?
Why is he nowhere to be found?
[Where is he?]
[Finally comes out of hiding.]
[Starts running up...
then turns to run away!]
[Why is he running away?]
Guys!
[I vow to eliminate Dong Woon
from the game!]
Where are you?
No, wait!
[Retreats up to the third floor.]
We got it.
You got it?
Wow!
[Dong Woo eliminates Kwang Soo
of his name tag.]
[All the representatives are eliminated-
What is the result of their times?]
We have the final results of the
Running Man name tag elimination game.
When Yoo Jae Suk went in
as the representative of his team
- he went up against the Pink Team?
- Yes.
- Your time was 4 minutes and 43 seconds.
- But that won't be the determining factor.
Thus, the Pink Team came in at last place
and failed to earn any gold bars.
In third place, with the time of
2 minutes and 57 seconds...
- Do you think it's going to be us?
- I wonder who it is?
- I really have no idea.
- It's Gary's opponent, Kim Jong Kook's team.
- We're in third place?
- Yes, your team came in at third place.
[The White Team earns one gold bar,
which brings them to the total of four.]
In second place, with the time
of 2 minutes and 43 seconds...
[Second place- 2 minutes and 43 seconds.]
It's the Red Team,
who just eliminated Lee Kwang Soo.
[Red Team earns two gold bars,
which brings them to a total of two.]
And in first place...
[Kim Jong Kook's opponent, the Blue Team,
comes in at first place.]
With the record of
1 minutes and 42 seconds.
[1 minute and 42 seconds.]
Big-nose's time is finally here!
[Disappointed]
[A ninety degree bow.]
- Didn't I tell you that I had a good feeling?
- Yes, you did.
- But someone took one of our gold bars.
[It wasn't me.]
I really don't know who took it,
but why don't you kneel down before us?
- And apologize to us that way.
- What's so hard about that, Jong Kook?
If that's how it works,
then give it to us.
[Kneeling down is no big deal.
Please give us a gold bar.]
Then let's do it this way. Show us
the gold bars you have right now.
Then even if you have more later,
we won't count those.
Show us the gold bars you have now,
and tell us how many you have.
The ones we have right now?
Okay, we'll do that.
- You're really just.
- We had no idea you were like that.
- He's really just.
- Show us what you have now.
- What if they pull out three?
- You have two.
Even if you have more later,
we're not going to count those.
Kang Gary has another one.
[He has a gold bar in his sock.]
[Mr. Gary, the actor.]
It's mine!
I'm telling you that this is mine!
[I'm not giving you my precious gold bar!]
I picked this up!
I'm telling you that I found this!
Wow, you really are something else.
I really found this one.
I found it on the floor.
[Running Newspaper-
Scared Ryeo Wook- 'I'm so sorry!']
[Son Dong Woon-
'Running away was the easiest method.']
We've really come a long way today.
[First place in hand pushing game-
Earns three, now with a total of five.]
Coming in at first place is really exciting.
- I had faith in you guys all the way.
- Me, too.
- Did we do a good job?
- You guys are the best.
[Blue Team's current gold
bar count- Six.]
I don't feel bad about having given
one of our gold bars to the Red Team.
- Yes, I don't either.
[Gave one gold bar to the Red Team.]
We have the most number of gold bars,
we won a game, and even did a good deed.
It's really all over if we
win the next game.
- Winning is the most important thing.
- What if we don't win?
- If we don't win, then we're...
- Then it's over for us.
Then everything that we're saying now
isn't going to get aired at all.
Then everything will become meaningless,
and we'll get mud in our faces.
- This is the last of it.
- That's kind of disappointing.
Let's turn the game around.
[SBS' open hall in Dongchon.]
Come on, let me find just one.
[What are they all searching for?]
I've always seen the members
finding things in lockers like these.
[What are they all searching for?]
Today's final mission-
fulfill 10kg of gold.
Find the gold bars hidden in this hall,
and in addition to the ones you already have
you have to fulfill a total of
10kg of gold in weight.
Each gold bar weighs 1kg.
Each team's platform will indicate
the total weight of gold in possession
and your aim is to fulfill 10kg in gold.
Those teams with less gold in weight
will have to find the additional amount here
or you're also allowed to take them
from your opposing teams.
The platform where the scales are
placed is your safe zone.
You can't steal from each other in
the zone. You may get started now.
[Find the hidden gold bars,
and fulfill 10kg in gold!]
[Gold rush- Start!]
- Is it in here?
[Grasshopper searches the rehearsal room.]
[Yes! He strikes gold!]
[His sharp senses earns him his first
gold bar within the first minute.]
[Rushes over to the safe zone
to drop off his gold.]
[Red Team adds another gold to
their scale to get a total of 4kg.]
They already found one.
They went from three to four kg.
[Even the Blue Team with their current lead
of 6kg cannot put their guard down.]
[Big-nose starts searching through the kids'
pockets in his sense of desperation.]
[Get the gold and run!
Ryeo Wook rushes off with the gold!]
[Get him!]
[Everyone rushes over to see
what the fuss is all about.]
- Kwang Soo!
[Total chaos.]
[Blue Team's Niel eyes his chance...]
[And successfully steals it away!]
Min Hyuk!
[And makes it over to the safe zone.]
[Add another gold bar-
Blue Team now with a total of 7kg.]
Ugh, I lost it.
[Finding it is one thing, but delivery
of it is the key to this final mission.]
[Ace Blank Ji finds her gold.]
[Welcome!]
[White Team is in danger once again
of having theirs taken away from them!]
[The scent of gold
is wafting through the air.]
- No, Jae Suk!
- No!
[The Grasshopper shattered my dreams!]
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
[Red Team brings their total
up to five with another steal.]
[That's too bad...
It was Ace's gold.]
- Out of my way.
- You startled me.
I said, out of my way.
[Drops off the empty box.]
[What are you going to use the empty box for?]
- I really can't find any.
[He falls for it!]
- I don't have anything.
[One fisherman looking for a catch.]
[He fell for it!]
Hey!
There are duds?
There are empty boxes?
I just saw Jae Suk throwing it away.
[Short-legged Haroro
searches through all the chairs.]
[It's real gold!]
[There he goes again...]
[The luck of the boy who cried wolf?
Safely enters the zone without any trouble.]
Wow, I was so nervous!
[Pink Team with a new total of 6kg.]
[Find 10kg of gold!]
Suk Jin!
[Nice catch, Big-nose!]
- Help! Come and help me!
- Sorry, So Hyun.
Sorry, So Hyun.
[Your partners... are busy doing this.]
[Big-nose successfully steals it away.]
No!
Hey, Niel!
That's mine!
Niel, that's mine!
Help!
[The Blue Team puts up a good defense line
against So Hyun's screams for help.]
Hey, that's mine!
I found it, so it's mine!
[How is he going to get out
from under this mess?]
[Makes a sly pass over to Big-nose.]
[While Niel uses himself as bait
to lure the others away...]
[Big-nose rushes over to the safe zone!]
[Is he safe?]
[So close!
But both feet weren't in the zone.]
[Had the gold stolen away,
and thrown down on the ground.]
- Give it back to the rightful owner!
[The never-ending battle for gold.]
[Everyone's starting to gather around
the possessor of gold.]
Get him!
[You're saying that you're
going to get me?]
[A participant of 2014 Idol Athletic Battle.]
[An unbelievable record of
60m in 6.40 seconds!]
[This is the man that broke the record
to bring home the gold medal!]
[I'm that 'Idol Bullet', Min Hyuk!]
Let's return it back to its
rightful owner!
[Will he be able to surpass this obstacle?]
[Easily gets past one obstacle.]
[A quick fake in the direction
safely lands him in the zone.]
[This is the power of
his 6.40 second record.]
- But I found the gold.
- He's like a beast.
[White Team brings up their total
to 7kg with Min Hyuk's help.]
- Great job, Min Hyuk.
- Wow, he's really fast.
- I found it.
[Just remember that I found the gold.]
Ugh, seriously.
That was unbelievable.
I've always wanted to play
the treasure hunt game.
[Searches through every nook and cranny...
but the gold is nowhere to be found.]
I can't find any!
There aren't any.
I don't see it anywhere.
[Finally discovers a gold bar
hiding bashfully on the door ledge.]
- Hey... N, come over here.
[Recruits her tall partner over for help.]
Hurry.
[Quick and safe delivery is crucial.]
[Pink Team currently has 6kg. Add
one more, and they have a good chance!]
- I don't have anything.
- You're acting suspicious.
I really don't have anything.
I don't have any.
- I really don't have any.
- Check his back pocket.
[Yoo Hyuk searches the stadium.]
- I thought I saw something earlier.
[It's gold!]
[Red Team was in last place,
but suddenly already up to 6kg!]
[Ambitious Eric Nam searches
through the MC waiting room.]
[There it is!]
[Hides it deep within his coat
and heads over to the safe zone.]
[Gets caught by Mr. Gary
while rushing off to the zone.]
Dong Hoon!
[Not who he was calling out for,
but Big-nose rushes over instead.]
[Big-nose's unreliable assistance.
Making his escape is a better chance!]
[The gold hyenas starts rushing over
at the scent of gold in the air.]
[N takes advantage of the chaos
and rushes off to the safe zone.]
[In life, timing is everything.]
[Pink Team brings up their total to 7kg.]
[Over here is still a chaotic mess.]
- I don't think he has anything.
- No, I'm sure he has something.
It's in the right inside pocket.
[Thank you for that important information!]
- Why would you say that out loud?
[All seven hands starts digging
for his right inside pocket.]
Here it is.
[What a steal!
Did the Red Team get the gold?]
Who is it?
Did you get it?
[While everyone is lost in confusion,
Eric slides over to the zone.]
[Just what is going on here?]
- What just happened?
- He didn't steal it from me.
- This was a fake?
Here it is!
[The real gold was in his left pocket!]
- Wow, Eric is no joke!
- Wow, that was such a smart move.
- That's not the one, it's this one.
He put the fake in his right,
and the real one in the left pocket.
[After all his hard work,
he almost put it in the wrong scale!]
- We just need to find two more.
- We need two more.
[Blue Team's total- 8kg.]
[So Jin continues to search the ledges.]
[Bingo!]
[Off to make the delivery.]
[So Jin discovers her second bar
with her hawk-like eyes.]
[So Jin is in the groove.]
- Over here!
[Blue Team's Ace, Eric, spots So Jin.]
[So Jin is in extreme danger.]
They're perverts!
Perverts!
- Perverts!
- We're not perverts!
[The Pinky Brothers rush over
at So Jin's sign.]
[Is this the site of perverts' admonition?]
Give it to Gary.
Run!
Run, Gary!
[Bulldozer Kang Gary vs
Sticky handed defensive line.]
- Let go of him!
- Gary!
[He drops the gold!]
[Haroro rushes over to pickup
the gold that fell onto the ground.]
- You did great, So Jin.
- So Jin, don't feel nervous!
[Just trust me...
I will find them all for you.]
[Checking every tiny nook and cranny.]
I wonder if I'm searching through
too many useless...
[Calms himself down
to start over his search.]
Eric!
[What did Niel just see?]
[Five minutes ago.]
- I feel like my head is going to burst.
[Ha Ha enters the Green Room
after sending Eric Nam away.]
[Discovers the gold that would bring
their total up to 9kg.]
[Makes their move while pretending
to be still on the search.]
How may kg do we have so far?
Gary, we need one more.
We just need to find one more.
[They only need one more?]
[Hawk-eyed, So Jin, finds another gold bar
and adds it to the goal.]
[Treasure hunting goddess, So Jin,
brings up her team's total to 9kg.]
- We just need one more.
- One more?
[In that case, Ha Ha's gold bar
could be their winning ticket!]
[And Niel had just witnessed
this whole scene.]
- Stop them!
[They must be stopped!]
Hurry, Min Hyuk!
[We can't let them beat us like this!]
[Will it be the Pink Team's victory,
or the Blue Team's great line of defense?]
[He makes it into the zone!]
[The Pink Team takes the victory!]
They found another one?
[They steal the victory!]
[The final ceremony
to ring in their victory.]
[10kg of Gold Rush Race-
Pink Team wins!]
[Mommy, I won!]
[The Pink Team takes home the win!]
[Wins the gold as their winning prize!]
If you're disappointed with the loss, then
come back on the show a few more times.
Then I promise to help you
win next time.
Let's just go out to dinner sometime, okay?
Let's just go out to dinner
since you like to eat.
[What great times we had
in our treasure hunt!]
Thank you to everyone who came on the
show to participate in our games.
[Thank you to all our guests who came on
the show to shine like bright jewels!]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle.]
[Over the mountains,
and across the waters...]
[After searching through
every corner of the country...]
[All kinds of delicacies
that they got to enjoy...]
[Find the true master of taste,
and the freshest ingredients...]
[The finest foot critics will come to judge!]
[It's time to get past the
borders of Korea.]
[The cooking tour takes them overseas
to Hong Kong and Thailand!]
[Through land, sea and air...
Past all imagination, and experience...]
[The ultimate recipes that they'll receive
from the local master chefs!]
[2015 New Year Cooking Competition-
Who will be the ultimate cooking chef?]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle]
Subtitles by DramaFever