[The hottest freshmen are coming!]
[You know how to party!]
[A powerful student orientation begins!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[March... spring begins.]
[At the start of a new school year,
the campus is full of excitement.]
[On the stage, where the
drama club's sweat is steeped...]
[a group of freshmen
await for a special stage.]
[Challenge... passion...]
[and fluttering...]
[are all in here.]
[Only guy members are on the stage.]
- I don't see Ji Hyo here.
- I guess it's a good thing for us.
- It gets my hopes up.
Except for Gary,
we're anticipating our guests.
Are they coming now?
- We're ready to welcome them.
- I want to see them!
[The student orientation has begun!]
[The girls that returning students
are waiting for.]
[Extremely focused]
[Who will be the first freshman?]
[Hani of EXID]
- It's Hani!
[Returning students are wildly excited.]
- Hani! Hani!
[Hani is on 'Running Man'!]
['Up and Down' is her group's song.]
[Korea's in love with Hani right now!]
[Hani opens the first
gun of Running Man!]
Up, down! Up, up, down!
[They mimic in front of the original.]
[He's just happy.]
Hello! I'm Hani of EXID.
I'm excited to be here.
Up, down! Up, up, down!
Hani came out first.
How about the ones still waiting?
How are the other guests?
They're the best!
[Bravo!]
Who is it?
[The next freshman comes out.]
[Actress, Nam Ji Hyun]
Hello, Ji Hyun!
[The child actress,
Nam Ji Hyun is now a lady.]
[The young 'Queen Seon Deok']
[has grown to take the main role
of the weekend drama.]
It's Nam Ji Hyun!
I thought you were one of the idols.
Look at her outfit.
She doesn't look like an idol.
- That's right. Idols don't wear coats.
- It's a college student's fashion.
You're a lady now.
You were a little girl when you
were in 'Queen Seon Deok'.
Just be careful not to
be paired with Ji Hyo.
Okay, We have Hani and Ji Hyun.
Who's next?
[Everyone is waiting for
the third freshman.]
[Who is the lady with
these beautiful legs?]
- Actress Jung So Min?
[Actress Jung So Min]
You have such a small face!
[The fresh and lively,
Jung So Min.]
[She was known as
Yoon Eun Hye's doppleganger.]
[Now she's become a top actress.]
First time meeting you!
- She's so pretty!
- Gary's fallen for her.
It's the third time for me.
Hello, I'm Jung So Min.
I'm pleased to be here.
It's great.
Let's greet the next guest!
[Who is the fourth freshman that
will make the mood even better?]
[Student of an engineering college,
Yoon So Hee.]
Wow, she's also pretty!
What a beauty!
[A student of KAIST who graduated
early from a science high school]
[and fell in love with acting.]
[She fills the stage
with her freshness.]
So Hee reminds me of Go So Young.
- Thank you.
- She does look like Go So Young.
- How can everyone be so...
- I can tell by the members' faces.
- It's rare...
- Another one's coming!
- Who is it?
- [Who will be next guest?]
- She's from G-friend!
- G-friend!
[Is she a member of G-friend?]
Their name will go down
in idols' history.
[Yerin of G-friend.]
[They debuted seven weeks ago.]
[The groups' image is pure.]
[What we dreamt of
when we were students.]
[They have the image of a girlfriend.]
- Hello! I'm Yerin of G-friend.
- She does look like a girlfriend.
[She's cute.]
She speaks cutesy for her image.
It sounds very cute.
[Proudly walking, the
last freshman Blank Ji.]
- Song Ji Hyo...
[He doesn't care.]
You don't care about me at all!
Don't discriminate against me!
Please welcome me!
Don't expect anything from us.
What do you want from us?
Thank you for joining us.
[Hani, Nam Ji Hyun, Jung So Min,
Yoon So Hee, Yerin]
March is the start of a new
school year.
You'll be student couples for a day
and play in the 'Greatest Love Race'.
Do we have to love again?
I'll announce the couples.
Hani...
and Yoo Jae Suk.
[A dance for the victory.]
- You look like you're dirty dancing!
[Good riddance.]
Nam Ji Hyun and Kim Jong Kook
are a couple.
I'm worried for you.
He's very naggy.
The nagging father-in-law.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun couple]
- I'm a little nervous.
- There are three couples left.
Jung So Min and Gary
are a couple.
What is this?
I can lose the draw then?
[He's happy.]
[Am I the loosing ticket?]
- Why Gary?
- Gary waited for Ji Hyo.
Yoon So Hee and Lee Kwang Soo.
[I like him, too.]
- You look good together!
- You're lucky, Kwang Soo.
- Don't give him your phone number.
- She's Kwang Soo's type.
- What are you talking about?
- It's nothing like that.
- It's true!
[Only Yerin and Ji Hyo are left.]
- Yerin and...
- Yerin and?
- She's a lot younger than me.
- Ji Suk Jin are the couple.
[Suk Jin and Yerin couple.]
[Ha Ha automatically loses the draw.]
Congratulations!
What have I done to you?
[This couple looks awkward.]
A girlfriend and... a principal.
You look like a high school girl
and a principal.
Look at them. They look so happy
seeing the beautiful guests.
- We're very happy.
- Even their laughs sound different.
[Look forward to seeing this combination!]
For the Greatest Love race
each team will receive a
token of love.
The winner will be the couple who
puts the token in the best spot.
You will get a chance
to switch the token
when you win the missions and
also get a hint for switching it.
You'll pick your token first.
- It's okay, pick anything Hani.
- Just don't pick the 'corn syrup'!
[First-come-first-serve!]
Fighting, So Min!
Why are you taking off your shoes?
Why are you taking off
your shoes, So Min?
[So Min is a lot more
enthusiastic than she looks.]
Start now!
[The real race hasn't even started, but
they're having a physical brawl.]
[Kids these days...]
[How will the tokens be used?]
- I've never seen a woman sliding before!
- Seeing that almost turned me off.
[They have chosen their tokens of love.]
[Get to the mission site.]
- Do you know how to drive?
- Yes.
- Are you good at it?
- Well...
- Should I drive?
- Yes.
Don't make things awkward.
- I think Kwang Soo likes you a lot.
- I like him, too.
Hope you enjoy the ride with him.
- Watch your head.
- Okay.
I hope it goes well with her.
- You always ruin everything.
- She's from KAIST.
Just let it be.
- Sister-in-law!
- Don't do things like this!
[She doesn't mind
Ha Ha's awkward jokes.]
[It's their time alone.]
- Did you go to KAIST?
- I still go there.
- Still going?
- I took some time off before.
- Wow, it's not a joke.
- I'm not all that great.
- What do we have? A marble?
- Yes.
When you think about the component...
for example, oil won't unite
with water.
- Water won't unite with wax, either.
- You're different.
- No, isn't that how we play?
- You're analyzing the component.
Chili oil won't mix with water.
[That sounds relevant
but they're in a fog.]
You're the best!
Fighting!
It's the best 'fighting' ever.
Is that so?
Fighting!
[What should I do?]
Last time I saw EXID was...
- It was right before we debuted.
- That's right.
'Shinsadong Tiger' introduced you to me
saying that you would debut soon.
The group name is 'EXID'.
Hello! We're EXID!
That's right.
[She takes out something.]
[Is that a hair comb?]
I think it might take a while.
Go ahead.
- My hair is not fixed.
- Isn't it uncomfortable?
It is. I wouldn't do it if
I had a small forehead.
[She finally takes out a hair roller!]
The bangs stick flat on the
forehead if you don't do it.
- It'll be like this.
- Yes.
It looks like seaweed.
It's not easy to be in a girl group.
Seriously.
- It is boring...
- No, I'm fine.
Don't lie to me.
The weather is perfect for sleeping.
I'm fine.
[But her eye lids move up and down.]
[She's in a deep sleep.]
[Her neck is in 90 degrees angle.]
[That's right.
I'm on 'Running Man'.]
[She pretends nothing happened.]
I thought you were dead, Hani.
I try not to fall asleep,
so I spray this.
[She sprays breath freshener.]
[She opens the window and blows out.]
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
I just burped.
You're amazing!
[Hair roller + Sleeping + Burp]
[What an unaffected personality!]
[Field day for the freshmen.]
We're going to race.
We're the first team.
[The huge ad-hoc stadium awaits
Running Man]
[with hurdles, acupressure mats
and a special pull-up bar!]
[What will be the mission?]
- It's the 'Bungeoppang' team.
- Why?
('Bungeoppang' is a quiz show
with celebrities and their kids.)
This is the one-sided love team.
- Gary has a crush on her.
- She's very feminine.
I thought she might be a tomboy.
I asked why she likes snow,
and she said "It's high in scarcity."
She said that?
It's been 12 years since
I heard the word 'scarcity'.
I said, 'Are you good
at self-management?'
and she said, 'We need to
strengthen self growth.'
[So Min's character
is high in scarcity.]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee have arrived.]
- Did you talk a lot?
- Yes, we did.
- You're Kwang Soo's ideal type.
- Seriously?
[So Hee is Kwang Soo's ideal woman.]
It's true that I like...
[As usual, (only) Kwang Soo is truly...]
I think they're trying to
put us on the spot.
[Kwang Soo's heart is pounding.]
- Sister-in-law, he's real.
- He'll spend some money.
- What are you talking about?
- Kwang Soo will go broke today.
I heard you're very smart.
She goes to KAIST.
She was accepted through
the rolling admission.
- Were you the first in the whole country?
- No. Not at all.
I went to a 'Gwa-go'
(a science high school).
You went to 'Gwa-geo'?
(civil exam in Joseon dynasty)
- Science high school.
- Oh, I thought it was the civil exam.
That makes her a person
from the Joseon era.
Seriously.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun have arrived.]
- Didn't he nag a lot?
- No, he didn't.
No way.
That's not possible.
Wait 'til you start playing.
Yes, he will start nagging then.
He'll nag until the night comes
if you don't play well.
I must try very hard.
[Jae Suk and Hani have arrived.]
- What's wrong?
- You're very late.
Hani was dead for a while.
I told her to sleep
but she kept saying no.
Then she started humming.
[He wants to share
Hani's charm with everyone.]
I took the long way.
I'm sorry.
We'll start the first game,
'Knight on a Horse'.
The couples will race on the
acupressure mat in their bare feet.
On the first stage, the guy runs
while carrying the girl.
Then they throw the girl
over the hurdle.
For the second stage, the guy
carries the girl on his back
and runs to the pull-up bar.
Then the girl should eat the biscuit.
After that is the last stage.
The guy can put the girl down on
the mat and then throws a ball up
they both turn around, hug
and catch the ball.
Keep in mind that there
are only four balls.
It's a foul if you use your hand.
I love these kind of games.
I suffer from 'Cold Extremities'.
(Cold hands and feet)
[First time hearing 'Cold Extremities'
on Running Man.]
A 23 year old girl using
the word 'Cold Extremities'?
- She's 27.
- She's 27?
[First round, 'Knight on a Horse'.]
- Fighting!
- The winner can take a break.
Ready!
- Will you be okay?
- I'll be okay.
It's not that you're heavy.
Set!
[Which couple will get through these
difficulties first and win?]
[The winner of this round
is the first place winner.]
[The guys are still smiling.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun
get to the hurdle.]
[They go through the hurdle at once.]
[Right after Jong Kook and Ji Hyun]
[Gary and So Min get through.]
Get on my back!
[On the other hand...]
[These freshmen haven't
stopped growing yet.]
[They must start from the beginning.]
[Jong Kook, Ji Hyun, Gary, and So Min
are on the acupressure mat.]
[They scream in a high pitch
with every step they take.]
[They get to the pull-up bar
around the same time.]
[Now it's the girl's turn
to eat the biscuit.]
[Their feet hurt and
they're getting tired.]
I ate it!
[Ji Hyun succeeds at once.]
[They get to the final spot.]
Hold me higher.
I still can't!
[They're the ones who still can't.]
[The three teams struggle
with the first stage.]
I can't throw you!
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo succeed.]
[They quickly run to the pull-up bar.]
- Just throw me!
- Okay!
[He succeeds at throwing.]
[They're showing off
pro-wrestling tricks.]
[They might end up
staying in the first zone.]
Let's go!
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun take
the challenge at the final stage.]
[It's important to keep
in step with each other.]
[Don't just hug each other!]
Hold on a second.
- Did you eat it?
- It's done?
[Gary and So Min join the final stage.]
[They can win as soon as they
catch the ball.]
[Kwang Soo, So Hee, Ha Ha, and Ji Hyo
try eating the biscuit.]
[It's almost there...]
[They're still doing some pro-wrestling.]
[Your dad,
I mean... your brother is sorry.]
[Thanks to the mission,
they get free hugs.]
[My hands are slipping.]
- Did you eat it?
- Should I eat it all?
[Kwang Soo and So Hee
get to the final stage.]
['Bungeoppang' couple didn't
get to see the biscuit yet.]
It's okay.
You never know.
[The three teams are
competing at the final stage.]
[They're in a hurry, but
the ball keeps bouncing.]
[It's the first time hugging
and getting stressed.]
[We just want to touch the ball.]
[They are the strong
winning candidates.]
[Gary and So Min calmly throw the ball]
[and keep their focus.]
- We did it!
[They succeed at catching the ball.]
[Gary and So Min couple,
the first winners.]
[The first winner gets a strong hint
and a ticket to switch the token.]
We were almost there.
[These people stayed at the
hurdle for the whole round.]
[We've put a lot of effort...
but this... we can't do.]
- We can't do it.
- Give us an advantage!
Our partners aren't as light as them.
[And we're different in strength.]
I beg of you! Please lower our bars
two inches lower than the others.
Our partners aren't the same
as the others.
They're too long
so their legs get caught.
[Giraffe quietly makes Jong Kook
and Ji Hyun's hurdle higher.]
- What are you doing?
- I'm doing it for you.
Are you crazy?
[He gives the most powerful
couple a disadvantage.]
That's only fair!
Ji Hyun will get hurt if she
gets thrown from that high.
[Mr. Capable's chivalry.]
What a joke!
You don't even care
if we get hurt?
You've never treated us to
a meal if even you win.
We saw how you've thrown
Ji Hyun today.
[The first winning couple
can sit back and watch.]
[Second round, 'Knight on a Horse'.]
[The second winner
will get a hint and a break.]
Set!
[There are three balls.]
[We can take a break if we win!]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun get
through the hurdle first.]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo get
through the second.]
Amazing!
That's incredible!
[Mr. Capable is using all his strength
and gets to the pull-up bar first.]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee]
[Jae Suk and Hani]
[have passed back to back.]
[First time walking on the
acupressure mat.]
Jump over!
[Trying a new method.]
Hurry!
[Operation Human Bird succeeds.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun succeed
at eating the biscuit first.]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo succeed right after.]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee join them.]
[The second round is a tight match.]
Just like that.
I'll throw the ball.
[Catch the ball
and be the second winner!]
[This is a very difficult mission.]
That's not easy at all.
[The same people in a different stage.]
[Hani succeeds.]
Eat it, please!
[Yerin succeeds... almost.]
[She gets the acupressure therapy.]
[The last stage,
four teams and three balls.]
[Lucky!]
[The first step for this mission]
[is to steal the ball.]
[Three teams are aiming for one ball.]
Throw the ball!
[Throw it quickly.]
Move away!
[Jae Suk and Hani succeed!]
[The couple's victory ceremony.]
It was great!
[They are planning a strategy
before the third round.]
Kwang Soo is acting like
a serious man today.
[Actor Lee Kwang Soo, in a long time.]
You don't act like the
Running Man today?
You're not the Running Man Kwang Soo?
[He shows off his male beauty
by doing the clap push-up.]
Kwang Soo looks cool today.
[This is all for you.]
I feel sorry for the girls
who met the weak partners.
Why is he standing over there?
That guy just throws everything high.
- He can't even control his strength.
- Do you want me to throw you?
[The last round for
getting the benefit.]
[The last round, 'Knight on a Horse'.]
Ready, set!
[The winner will get a ticket
for switching the token of love.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun,
Ha Ha and Ji Hyo succeed.]
[Suk Jin and Yerin,
Kwang Soo and So Hee fail.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun
get the lead again.]
[Operation Human Bird, again.]
[Fosbury-backflop,
the Human Bird evolves.]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee
pass at the same time.]
[There's no time to stop!]
[All four teams are
at the biscuit stage.]
[Ji Hyun succeeds in a flash.]
[So Hee eats it
at the speed of light.]
You're almost there!
[There are only two balls
for this round.]
[Interruption is in Giraffe's nature.]
- The ball hit Ji Hyun's nose!
- Are you okay?
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo vs. Suk Jin and Yerin.]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee
vs. Jong Kook and Ji Hyun.]
[The biscuit is mine]
[but it isn't.]
[That should be mine.]
[The biscuit plays hard-to-get.]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee, Jong Kook
and Ji Hyun. What a tight match!]
[They wrestle whenever possible.]
We've got to steal the ball, So Hee!
[Each team has the ball.]
Throw it!
[They throw it at the same time.]
[There's only one ticket left.
Who will be the last winner?]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee
win by the split of a hair!]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun
fall a step behind.]
- We caught it, too!
- Are you okay, Ji Hyun?
[This person never
touched the ball.]
Kwang Soo hit my nose!
- I'm sorry.
- Why would you hit her nose?
Are you okay?
[The first mission is over.]
Everyone, stay where you are.
- Who won third place?
- We did.
Please come forward.
[The pitapat couple made
a good combination.]
So Hee doesn't mind
Kwang Soo at all.
This ticket is for third place.
[Token switching ticket lets them check
the tokens and switch the tokens.]
Can we switch another team's
token, too?
[Switching Ha Ha and Ji Hyo's corn syrup
with Jae Suk and Hani's chili oil.]
They don't even know what's good.
They don't have any hints.
So Hee made a deduction.
They have a brain.
You know So Hee goes to KAIST.
[Second place, Jae Suk and Hani]
[come out to the tokens frivolously.]
Two tickets are inside
this envelope.
Try not showing it to others and look.
[The Greatest Love - A love like a glass
bead cannot be the greatest love.]
The chili oil is clear in color.
The one I had in my 'Stir-fried
Glass Noodles' was red.
What are you talking about?
They were switched.
[Hani thought the corn syrup
was their chili oil.]
Let's switch with this one.
[Switching Jong Kook and Ji Hyun's candles
with Jae Suk and Hani's corn syrup.]
They're just switching it
but they don't know anything yet.
Don't speak if you don't
know what's happening.
I know what's going on!
You're just guessing
and it's wrong.
Don't spill the water.
[Candles belong to
Jae Suk and Hani.]
[First place gets a strong hint
and a token switching ticket.]
[The Greatest Love - Being hot is better
than being sticky (attached) for love.]
Isn't this the one?
- This can't be that simple.
- Right. That'll be too easy.
I want to 'keep' it (as in storing
the liquor bottle at bars for later).
'Keep'?
You're really weird.
Why would you want to keep it?
She wants to keep it as if she's
storing a liquor bottle at a bar.
[So Min uses words
that are 'high in scarcity'.]
So Min, it's not soju (liquor)!
Just drink up!
[Switching Gary and So Min's water
with Ha Ha and Ji Hyo's chili oil.]
The first game is over.
You'll go to the next location.
Let's go!
[Group-bonding underwater
activities for the freshmen.]
['O' Water Park, Namyangju]
- It's Pop-up Pirate.
- The game with the flying pirate.
- It's amazing to make it this big.
- They made it so well.
The second game is Pop-up
Pirate as you can see.
You're going to play
'Pop-up Miss Pirate'.
- Wow!
- What's going on?
[The freshmen are in a panic
and the returning students cheer.]
Just let us fly!
[Running University isn't
the easiest place.]
The female students from two teams
will sit on the flying chair
inside the barrel.
We will draw the Running Balls
to pick a number, then the
male students
will take turns sliding the sword.
If the number on the barrel
slot matches with the ball
the girl flies into the water.
You'll play 'rock-paper-scissors'.
The winner will decide
who will play first.
You can pick your own team
if you want.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo win
'rock-paper-scissors'.]
[The Goddess of fortune, Blank Ji.]
One of the two teams will fail
and that makes it harder
for the team to win.
Please pick carefully.
I don't like some of the teams.
[He moves instinctively.]
Why are you looking at us
when you say that?
You like Hani, don't you?
Do you want to play first, Mister?
- Do you want to play now?
- We'll do it later.
We pick the blue team.
[Jae Suk and Hani.]
You should see Hani's dance first.
Are you ready, Hani?
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
Now scream!
[The freshman's dance time!]
[Hani's original dance
of 'Up and Down'.]
[Up, down, up, up and down.]
[Ji Hyo sways her arms.]
[Kwang Soo dances, too.]
[Judging.]
[The legendary pelvic thrust.]
That's great!
[Her partner Yoo Hyuk dances, too.]
[Don't pick us for the first round!]
Cancel!
[The designation is canceled!]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee try next.]
[He changes suddenly.]
[Awkward dance]
It's how everyone dances
these days!
[Ji Hyun appeals with her dance moves.]
[It's unsatisfying...]
That was a nerdy dance.
- She dances like us.
[The 90's style dance.]
[The judges feel great
satisfaction over her dance.]
[The mix of club dance and
Korean traditional dance.]
[The last dancer is the
youngest freshman.]
[Let me finish up the stage.]
[She takes up the stage of variety!]
[Yerin's freestyle dance.]
[A new gunfire dance of
the 21st century.]
[The powerful finish!]
[She hit her nose with her knee...]
Are you okay, Yerin?
She just hit her nose with her knee.
The mood totally changed.
[She quickly changes her
style for her own song.]
[She turns to a fresh young girl.]
[She acts like an idol
all of a sudden.]
[He smiles like a father
looking at his child.]
G-friend!
[She was scary one second ago.]
[She's very cute... huh?]
[She changes her character
in two seconds.]
[Freestyle Yerin, go!]
[Discovery of a rare species
on variety.]
[Hey, come on!]
[200% of powerful energy!]
[Culture shock.]
[A strange and powerful dance.]
[Everybody's dancing.]
What are you doing?
Do you call it a dance?
[Bring it on!]
[A b-boy showdown for
the strange dance.]
[Will you have any strength
left for the game?]
[Good job, Yerin!]
[They decide on the teams
for the first round.]
[Yerin will be exempt.]
- Can we tell them now?
- Yes.
The first team will be...
the blue team!
[Even after the 'Up and Down' dance.]
The second team will be...
the gray team!
[The awkward dance team!]
Do you hate us that much?
It's nothing like that.
['Pop-up Miss Pirate']
[Kwang Soo and So Hee
vs. Jae Suk and Hani.]
We now begin the game.
I'll pick the number
and keep it with me.
What number will it be?
[He dances like an executioner.]
[Go away, Kwang Soo!]
[He's into the sword dance.]
- Do you need water?
Of course, I need water.
[A variety executioner?]
[He's scary...]
[He gets a head start.]
Number eight!
[Chances are one out of ten.]
[Safe!]
[Watching makes them nervous.]
[It's Jae Suk and Hani's turn.]
[Now Kwang Soo's doing
Yoo Hyuk's sword dance.]
Do you need water?
[He directly shoots!]
[One more sip.]
[The human water gun.]
[Yoo Huk's choice is...]
Number two!
[Chances are one out of nine.]
[Safe!]
Number one!
Number four!
No, pick number one.
Number one!
[So Hee picks the number,
what will happen?]
- Okay!
[Chose wisely.]
[As the chances of being dunked grows,
their level of nervousness also grows.]
Was Jae Suk in the water?
[Courtesy of the human water gun,
Kwang Soo.]
- Number nine!
[Jae Suk and Hani choose number nine.]
[The nerve wrecking feeling-
Number nine is safe.]
Yes, we're fine.
Wow, that was scary.
- What number should we go for?
- Number ten.
[Remaining numbers.]
- Number ten... go for number ten.
- Number ten!
[So Hee's firm about her decision-
Kwang Soo and So Hee go for number ten.]
- Okay!
[So Hee and Kwang Soo choose wisely again.]
[Remaining numbers.]
[Number five is chosen.]
[Nervously exchanging looks.]
[His heart may burst out of his chest.]
[On the other hand, brave Hani
seems to enjoy the thrill of the game.]
[25% chance with remaining numbers.]
There are only four left.
Only four remaining numbers.
- Number six!
- You're wrong. Should go for number three.
- He's totally wrong.
- He's going to get it wrong.
[Did Kwang Soo make the
wrong selection?]
- He's wrong!
- He's not wrong?
[He passes again!
Number six was a safe number.]
[The masters of the game are
showing extreme longevity of life.]
- Only three numbers left!
- How are you guys still alive?
[The burden of having to choose-
Feels as if their heart is about to burst.]
- Number four.
[Confidently chooses the next number.]
[Hani confidently chooses number four...]
[33.3% chance of being
thrown off into the pool.]
[Hani safely chooses number four.]
[Yoo Hyuk is about to drop dead.]
[I can't handle it anymore!]
[Feeling defeated.]
[Only two numbers now remain, and
one of the two are guaranteed to go in.]
Kwang Soo will choose the number,
and you'll both stick it in together.
- Three, and seven are left.
- I can't believe it's come down to this.
[The final face-off.
One will be thrown off into the pool.]
Jae Suk, what number do you want?
Hani, which number do you want?
[I'm not going to tell you that.]
[Big-nose brother chooses three!
He says lucky number seven isn't the one.]
[So, Kwang Soo chooses to
go with seven.]
Jae Suk will have number three.
[It's going to be one of these two!
Who will get to save their partner?]
Okay... one, two, three!
[The climatic end...
Who will be the ultimate winner?]
[Jae Suk and Hani win the game!]
[Sorry, So Hee...]
- So Hee, are you okay?
- I thought it was lucky number seven!
[The PD shows off
the fateful number to the camera.]
I think So Hee's angry.
[The angelic So Hee has lost her smile
since being thrown off into the pool.]
[Angelic So Hee's first experience
with the water dunk.]
Okay, who's going to go next?
[- Suddenly starts to rub his eyes.
- Pretends to be doing something else.]
[Averts their eyes.]
[Avoids the team selection process.]
Do you see the depth
of water being 0.9 meter?
This is only going to be for the men.
[Automatically gets up.]
- No, you don't have to.
- No, let's just do it!
Do you see the waterslides over there?
We're going to see who gets there first.
Ready, set, go!
[Kkuk chooses to go the pool route...
and the rest goes up the stairs.]
[Quick footed Ha Ha
is the first to slide down.]
[But Giraffe stands in the way.]
[Eliminated Giraffe is determined
to take someone down with him.]
[Middle aged Big-nosed Brother's
final spurt, and he unexpectedly wins!]
- Who got here first?
- It was me!
Then I'll go up against Ji Suk Jin.
[Fooled you, didn't I?]
[So... this is what this place is like?]
[Eliminated Kwang Soo will choose
the next number of elimination.]
Wouldn't it be funny
if it was the first number we chose?]
[Which number did Kwang Soo choose?]
- I'm going to go for number one!
- Number one?
- Yes, number one.
- Why?
- What about number one?
- He doesn't know.
- I drew the number.
[But Suk Jin doesn't seem to care...]
What happened?
Did she get stabbed?
[Her explosive reaction.]
- Are you okay?
- There's a pattern to the act of crime.
I doubt it'll be number seven again.
Number seven!
- Send her flying into the water!
- She passes!
[Number seven is safe.]
[Kwang Soo is the only one who knows
what the elimination number is.]
[Shares the number with
his partner, So Hee.]
Which number?
Number eight.
[It seems as though Big-nose has
mastered the art of Chinese language.]
[Back to being Jae Suk and Hani's turn.]
I bet it's really nerve wrecking.
[And of all people, it's Jae Suk,
with the pea-sized heart.]
- Being eliminated is actually better.
- Number three!
No, number four.
[They're not on the same page at all...]
- Five!
- Four.
It would be really funny if I
were thrown into the water now.
Four!
[Follows Hani's wish, and chooses four.]
[The sword is in!]
[Hani selects very wisely,
and is deemed safe once again.]
How is the game lasting for so long?
- 2, 3, 5, 6, 9, 10 are left.
- I think this is the moment.
- Ten!
- How about number ten?
- I like it.
- What about number nine?
[Number nine?]
- I'm going to go with number nine!
[Goes against Kwang Soo's advice.]
I don't trust you.
Number nine!
[How can this be?
Nine was the actual number!]
[Welcome to the pool.]
I told you that it was number nine!
Why didn't you believe me?
[What have I done?]
- That's two wins in a row!
- Why don't you believe me?
[Kwang Soo selects number nine
as the next number of elimination.]
Yerin's face looks different now.
- Doesn't Yerin look different?
[She's definitely the free-spirited child
of the idol world.]
[Jae Suk and Hani maintain the win
with three teams still left remaining.]
- Let's play the noonchi game.
- What?
- One!
- Two!
[Kkuk is chosen as the next player
from having been too slow on his feet.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun
vs Jae Suk and Hani.]
[Being quick thinkers brings Gary
and Ha Ha to at least the third place.]
[Number three is the next
number of elimination.]
I'll let the other team go first.
Can I stab Yoo Jae Suk with this?
Two.
[A light start to the game-
Two is a safe number.]
Jae Suk's lasted long enough.
I bet Hani is a nervous wreck by now.
Ugh, I feel like I'm going to
die over here.
- The suspense is killing me.
- Eight!
[Jae Suk and Hani chooses eight.]
[Eight is another safe number.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun continue
to avoid the elimination number.]
- One!
- Ten!
[Clears numbers one, and ten.]
[Both teams are doing a good job
of avoiding the elimination number.]
- They're both doing a great job.
- Yoo Jae Suk...
Three!
[At last, the elimination
number is selected!]
[A refreshing dunk in the water.]
[Guaranteed at least a third place,
and moves onto the fourth round.]
[Thrown into the pool with her long
hair flowing in the air.]
[Wait, this picture is...]
[The young maiden ghost from
all the creepy legends!]
My lashes are still on.
[Happy that all her lashes are still on.]
[Gary and So Min vs Jong Kook and Ji Hyun.]
- It's okay.
- You choose the number, So Min.
- Just choose the first number for me.
- One.
- One!
- I hope someone gets eliminated right away.
[Shouts out the number with confidence.]
[Wait, did we seriously just win?]
Seriously?
Is this for real?
[Completely flabbergasted.]
[The elimination number
that had just been drawn.]
[Flying high into the air... and dunked.]
[This has to be a dream.]
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun are
easily moved up to the play-off round.]
Stop spritzing!
Are you running a pest control
inside your mouth or something?
[A total variety package.
Like peeling back an onion...]
[The final round-
Ha Ha and Ji Hyo vs Jong Kook and Ji Hyun.]
[Who will be the Greatest Love's
ultimate couple?]
[Which number will determine
the fate of the winning couple?]
- Which number should we go for, Ji Hyo?
- Let's just go with whatever.
- I'm really nervous right now.
- Then I'll just go in order.
Two!
[Selects number two.]
[Will it be?]
[Ha Ha chooses a safe number.]
[Even the crowd of onlookers
seem extremely nervous.]
[Whew... what a deep sigh of relief.]
- I've never seen Ji Hyo so nervous.
- Should we go in order, too?
Or should we just go for it,
and choose number four?
- I really don't care.
- Okay, I got it.
- You guys are looking very close.
- It's nice to see.
She's going to go for it,
and wants number four.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun choose number four.]
[Number four has never been
the elimination number yet.]
[It should be okay, right?]
[You can trust me.]
[Did Ji Hyun make the right selection?]
[Game over-
Ji Hyun is thrown into the water.]
[Flying high.]
[Ji Hyun fails to select the right number.]
[It doesn't matter...
Flown high into the air.]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo win the game!]
[The unarguable lady of luck!]
Let's not play these sort of
games anymore!
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun win
second place.]
[First place winners show off
their dance moves with Hani.]
[Who cares what you look like?
You just won first place.]
[Token of Love- Time to make the exchange.]
When we get to the end, we're going to
do an experiment with these six tokens.
The outcome of that experience is going to
determine who wins the entire race.
[They all take their guesses on
what the experiment is going to be.]
Third place winners, step forward.
[Gary and So Min to make the
first exchange.]
[Current- Chili oil.]
Let's swap this out for this one.
[Swaps out Kwang Soo and So Hee's
marbles for Ha Ha and Ji Hyo's water.]
[Their plan is to throw off Ha Ha and
Ji Hyo's chance at a win.]
[Second place winners are given a hint,
and a chance to make an exchange.]
[A chance to ask one
'yes' or 'no' question.]
What is your question?
- Is it related to fire?
- The answer is...
No.
[Q - Is it related to fire?
A- No.]
We're going to swap it out like this.
[Jae Suk and Hani's candle
for Jong Kook and Ji Hyun's corn syrup.]
- Congratulations.
- This is the setup?
Inside, you'll find your hint,
and a chance to make your exchange.
[Ask whatever question you'd like, and
we'll tell you one mission-related answer.]
Let's ask this one.
You said we're going to do an experiment?
- What are we going to be experimenting?
- That's a very good question.
- Hurry up.
- No need to beat around the bush, right?
Here's your answer.
It's an experiment related to density.
Did you just use the word, density,
in front of Ji Hyo and I?
Isn't this what 'density' is?
Like texture of some sort?
[I think 'density' means...]
[Swaps out their marbles for
Jong Kook and Ji Hyun's candle.]
- I don't think that's right.
[They seem unsure of their exchange.]
No, you can't change your mind.
You must return to your spot.
Remember when the producers
explained the rules to us again?
They said something about being in the
greatest spot means the greatest chances?
That's right!
You really are smart.
[So Hee guesses that 'Greatest Love'
is referring to being in the highest spot.]
They even dyed the water in the shade
of blue to make it look like corn syrup.
They put that dye in the water
on purpose.
So once everything is mixed together,
the one on the top is the winner.
With the difference in their density
the heaviest ones
are going to sink to the bottom.
[Density?
As in the clue that was just given out?]
From my knowledge,
I'm sure the candle will sink, too.
- But oil floats, right?
- Yes, oil floats.
- That's why it's the liquid candle.
- Yes, you're right!
[Kwang Soo and So Hee guess the greatest
token of love to be the candle.]
[Did these two manage to guess correctly?]
Hani, I think I've figured it out.
I think it's the boiling point.
Isn't it usually 150 degrees?
[What's the 'boiling point'?
Is it something you eat?]
I was on a one meal a day diet.
- But you've been eating nonstop.
- There's usually one free day.
I really do think that it's
related to the boiling point.
- What happens when you win?
- They gave out a diamond ring once.
[How many baked goods
can I buy with a diamond ring?]
[They finally arrive at
the final mission location.]
[An army of teddy bears?]
- I'd suggest that you run over here.
- Is it a first-come-first-serve basis?
[The quicker they arrive, the better off
they'll be for the final mission.]
The third and the final mission
is 'The Love Confession Stair Quiz.'
[Final mission of the day-
The Love Confession Stair Quiz.]
[A meeting of a love confession and quiz
for this group of newbies.]
[Stairway of Suffering
at 'D' University in Seoul.]
- See the 'R' flag on top of the stairs?
- Yes.
The girls will go and stand by the flag.
You may go up there now.
[The girls will go and wait by the flag
at the top of the stairway.]
[Just what is the mission about for
us to start suffering like this already?]
Here are the rules.
You will be given a question down here.
You will run up the steps
with one of the stuffed teddy bears.
Remember the question that I've posed,
and ask your partner waiting for you up top.
- The first team to correctly answer...
- It's just one?
- You just need to answer one question.
- We can do this.
[Answer the question incorrectly,
and you must run back down the steps.]
Look, it's a teddy bear!
It's so huge!
It's totally cute.
The poor teddy bears are getting wet.
[The girls are excited at the prospect
of getting a teddy bear.]
- The teddy bears got soaked in the rain.
- They're really heavy!
Why is this teddy bear so heavy?
The song, 'Wish List' by Byun Jin Sup,
which was very popular back in the 80's...
- Fill in the blank in these lyrics.
- I totally know this one!
- Go!
- But Yerin was born in 1996.
[Will Yerin even know the song?]
[Big-nose's personal wish list...
Winning first place and earning a hint.]
Yerin!
He's carrying the teddy bear up here.
So cute!
[The girls are eagerly waiting
for their own teddy bear.]
Yerin!
If you get this question wrong,
then I have to go back down there.
Really?
Then I'll get it right.
- Listen carefully, okay?
- A traditionally played marble game...
It's a marble slap game, right?
But it's also referred to as, __ game.
Which means, a sound made by a half empty
glass bottle. What is this other name?
Go.
Here he comes.
- Soo Hee, here.
[Hands off the teddy bear to So Hee.]
- Do you know who Byun Jin Sup is?
- Yes.
[Will they be able to win first place?]
- Do you know the song, 'Wish List'?
- Yes, I know the song.
- That's way too easy!
- You know the song?
- Fill in the blanks in the lyrics, okay?
- Okay.
'As you stare into my silent eyes...'
'A woman who __.'
'A woman who matches into the jeans'?
What are you talking about?
How can you match into jeans?
[Correct answer- Vision.]
- Did she say, 'Matches into the jeans'?
- You think the song is about a dry cleaner?
- I'm so sorry!
Do you work in a dressmaker shop?
Why would you match into some jeans?
[He must now go back down the stairs to
receive a new question to ask his partner.]
- I feel so bad!
- You can't do this to me!
[The bear must also be taken back down.]
- This is so heavy!
[Gary and So Min arrive in third place.]
So Min, you must go up the stairs,
and Gary, pick up one of the teddy bears.
[So Min is sent up the stairs
as soon as she arrives.]
[What is the question
that will be posed of Gary?]
In the popular letter grading system
for school academic grade standing
'Ga' represents the lowest
letter grade.
What do you think that represents?
Go!
How are we supposed to know
what that letter means?
Doesn't the 'Ga' means
that we're already ruined?
Fighting!
So Min!
Why has meeting you meant
nothing but endless suffering for me?
- Fighting!
- You know that we have to win this, right?
[Please... let's just win this right now.]
- You need to answer this correctly.
- Should I give you your question?
- No, you can give it to me in a little bit.
- What's 'Fidget slap'?
- What did you say?
- Fidget slap.
- Fidget slap?
Was she close?
You know the letter grading system that's
used by schools to grade your academics?
But that's not the question.
But in that grading system, 'Ga'
represents the lowest grade, right?
- So what does 'Ga' mean?
- What the heck is this!
- I think it's a Chinese character.
- What does it mean?
- 'Su' would mean, minus...
- Yes, it's along those same lines!
It's the lowest?
Wait a minute...
Is it like telling you to go away?
Like telling you to go away with
your bad grades or something?
Or does it mean that
you're on the brink of failing?
[Answer- Shows potential]
- Why did you tease us like that?
- Ugh, you guys are too much!
[Go away back down to the bottom,
and get yourself another question.]
You're making this love confession
way too hard!
Can't you just allow us to
love each other?
The bears are getting heavier by the minute
because they're getting wet from the rain.
- I know, it's getting really soggy.
- It's getting wet and soggy in the rain.
- They've got the bear again.
- I bet they're really cold.
The Greek mathematician, Archimedes,
figured out the principle of buoyancy
while bathing and shouted out these words
in excitement. What did he shout out?
'Tears of the Moon', which is a type of jewel
that Cleopatra mixed into vinegar
to drink for beautifying effects...
What is the name of this jewel?
He looks so defeated already.
- He's deflated of his energy.
- The ladies can go up right now.
- You can do this, right?
- Okay, let's get this done.
- The Greek mathematician, Archimedes...
- Yes?
He became so excited when he figured out
the principle of buoyancy while bathing
- that he shouted out these words...
- Eureka!
[No way!]
[But I just got here!]
[Is it right or wrong?]
- Can you ring that again?
- Okay, let me ring that again.
Come on, do it right!
[Correct answer- Eureka]
- My team was the first to get here.
- Who wouldn't know the answer to that?
Who else would know it?
- I just said it in the shower this morning.
- What a laugh.
[Gary and So Min win first place.]
In the worldwide popular novel series,
'Harry Potter'...
the usage of this magical tool would
determine the students' dormitories.
- What is this the book is referring to?
- I don't know this either.
Usage of this magical tool to determine
the students' dormitories?
What is this magical tool?
The magical tool...
[The bear is so heavy,
and my knees are starting to hurt...]
- Yerin, we have to get this right.
- You can do this!
We have to get this right.
I feel so bad.
Cleopatra mixed this into vinegar
and drank it to keep herself beautiful.
What is this thing that was also called
'Tears of the Moon'?
- Isn't it pomegranates?
- Pomegranates.
- What could it be? I have no idea.
[Answer - Pearls]
Why are you struggling
so much with it?
[The joy of having come in at first place.]
- Yerin...
- Is it an easy question?
- You've seen Harry Potter, haven't you?
- No, I haven't.
[Thus, the second attempt is also a failure.
Answer- Sorting Hat]
A couple that's constantly stuck to each
other is said to look like a pair of these.
In Spanish, it means, 'La cucaracha'.
What is it referring to?
Cockroach.
[No way...
Could that be the right answer?]
- Seriously?
- Yes, it's cockroaches.
Don't act like you're smart.
You've gotten all the previous ones wrong.
- Seriously?
- You kept asking me all the tough questions.
Yes, 'La cucaracha' means, 'The cockroach'.
- Yes, that's what it means.
- Yes, that's correct.
- How did you know that?
- You didn't know?
'Cockroaches, cockroaches...
the name is so beautiful.'
Is that what it really means?
- We came in at second place!
[Kwang Soo and So Hee in second place.]
This place was named after the best
strategist during the Joseon era
- who was also infamous for his virility.
- I don't even understand the question.
What is the name of this place,
which is popular amongst the young people?
Jung-ja-Dong.
[Would Ji Hyo know this answer?]
'Wile staring into my silent eyes,
she matches my __.'
- Is it two letters?
- Circle lenses!
[Correct answer- Vision.]
- 'While staring into my silent eyes...'
- She stares into the whites of my eyes.
- What do you mean, whites of my eyes?
- What else would she look into?
[My woman... she stares
into the whites of my eyes.]
- My face!
- My... eyes? I'm sorry.
I knew you'd be like this from the moment
I heard you snoring in your sleep.
[No need to go too far.
Just go back to the base of the stairs.]
- Someone already got second place, right?
- Yeah.
- Who was it?
- Kwang Soo.
[Must come in at least third place
in order to gain some sort of a hint.]
This part of the body is thrusted out in
greeting when greeting someone in Tibet.
Which body part are they referring to?
This is like army training all over again.
- When you drink...
- It's about drinking again?
- Yes, but in Joseon era...
- Joseon era again?
No, it's not about the Joseon era.
We have to correctly guess this hotspot
that the young people in Joseon would go to.
- Is it related to the past?
- I think so.
But you need to tell me
the name of the place!
- You have to guess what it is, you fool!
- That's way too easy!
- Ten, nine, eight, seven, six...
- Ahpgujung-do!
[Correct answer- Ahpgujung]
[Seriously?
That's the correct answer?]
[This is going to be game over.]
[You heard the answer, right?]
[Seeing the expression on everyone's
faces, the answer must be...]
- Myeongwolgwan!
- What!
Ji Hyo, are you kidding right now?
['Myeongwolgwan' is the hotspot
for the young people?]
- That's a barbeque place.
- Forget it.
[Ten years shaved off of his life.]
People in Tibet thrust out this part of
their body when greeting someone.
- Tibet?
- Tibet.
- I think I know.
- People in Tibet, okay?
- I know this. This is too easy.
- This is the people in Tibet.
I think 'Thrust out' is the hint.
[Think about what you can thrust out.]
The tongue?
Come on, let's hurry.
[Correct answer- Tongue.]
Who knew that would be the answer?
We got it!
[Jae Suk and Hani come in
at third place.]
[The final mission is now over.]
- Who knew that would be the right answer?
- Is it over?
[It can't be over, can it?]
[But we were the first ones to get here...]
- Yerin, is the game over?
[The early bird...
is the first to get tired out?]
- Is it all seriously over?
- We've got nothing.
We have to continue to
remain clueless in the race.
[The only thing that remains is the
final chance to make an exchange.]
[Which of these tokens will
indicate who holds the greatest love?]
Wow, look at all this fog.
Yerin, this is called, smoke.
It's not fog.
- Ugh, I'm so disappointed.
- I really had higher hopes for today.
[Token of love's current standing.]
Yoo Jae Suk, who came in at third place,
please step forward.
[They can make the exchange
without being given any hints.]
The previous first place winner...
had the candle, right?
Don't you think that it has
something to do with the boiling point?
Doesn't it take a long time for
the oil to reach its boiling point?
- Yes, it does.
- I bet it has to do with the boiling point.
[Guessing that it has something to do with
the boiling point of the chili oil.]
The candle would be the first to melt.
It can't be the candle.
- I think it's either this one or that one.
- It's one or the other.
- It has to be one or the other.
- Want to go with our first choice?
To be honest, I'm not really sure.
[Jae Suk and Hani choose the chili oil.]
Lee Kwang Soo and partner,
take the card and make your exchange.
It must be so nice to be able to
earn a hint, Kwang Soo.
Don't let anyone see the card.
No, You have to stand behind the display.
No, stand in front.
No, hold it over like this.
[What's wrong with you?
Haven't you ever seen a hint before?]
- This is the first hint I've earned.
- Really?
Lee Kwang Soo, isn't Yoon So Hee
going to do it by herself anyway?
- How can you even say that?
- You just look so clueless.
How can you even say that?
We're figuring this out together.
We're in on this together.
There was going to be a love connection,
but I see now that she's refusing it.
There is an underlying love connection.
[What hint did they receive?]
[Lee Kwang Soo, and Soo Hee are currently
in one of the top three standing.]
Then what we have...
is one of the top three contenders?
[Water is one of the top three contenders?]
They purposely dyed the water blue to
differentiate from the corn syrup.
[The water was purposely dyed blue to
tell it apart from the corn syrup?]
[Separating the soluble, and the
one that floats on top is the winner?]
[So Hee guesses that the Greatest Love
is related to the density of the soluble?]
Oil floats, doesn't it?
- Jae Suk just swapped his out.
- But that's what we want, too, isn't it?
Which one should we go with?
Ugh, I'm about to go crazy.
- I haven't been up there at all today.
- I'm so curious to see what it looks like.
- These two are totally up to fate.
- Corn syrup is all I got to see today.
- I've only heard that there's others.
- I don't even know what's up there.
The other ones that we are thinking are
going to sink to the bottom anyway, right?
- Is it the candle?
- No, candles don't float.
They don't float in water or oil.
So it's not the candle?
[What will Kwang Soo and So Hee choose?]
[Kwang Soo and So Hee choose
the chili oil.]
[Don't touch our candle.]
[Gary and So Min are given a top hint,
and a chance to make an exchange.]
- You two are looking awfully close.
- Even slapping each other like that?
You're thinking that you're close
to winning the race, is that it?
[What is the hint that they've been given?]
[Gary and So Min are
currently in fifth place.]
This is the top hint you have for us?
[With their recent hint, they know
that their corn syrup isn't a winner.]
Let's just go for what we
were thinking.
I think the thing about being on top
is what's most important.
- Like floating on something?
- Something with very light density?
Yes, I think that's what is it.
Something that would float on top.
[Gary and So Min also guess
it to be related to density.]
[Everyone seems to be leaning
towards the chili oil.]
Okay, it's time to announce the results
of the final mission.
The team that is standing in the top spot
will be the ultimate winners of the race.
A cylindrical measuring case
will be brought forward.
Place your team's token of love
inside that cylindrical vase
and the team with the token that floats
on top will be today's winner of the race.
[Token of love's current standing.]
The first team to go...
- Yoo Jae Suk and his water..
- Water is a given.
- That's going to be the bottom.
- Sorry, but how about our marbles?
[Their marbles are going to be
submerged underwater.]
Maybe our peanuts
will have a chance of floating to the top.
[Dumps in the water into the cylinder.]
It's definitely not ours.
Next, Ji Suk Jin.
Dump your peanuts in there.
[Second to go are Suk Jin,
and Yerin's peanuts.]
Can we do it later?
I've dumped a lot of peanuts into my drinks,
and they sink down to the bottom.
[Peanuts are dunked in.]
[Peanuts sink way down to the bottom.]
- Kwang Soo, dump your corn syrup in there.
- What about the chili oil?
The chili oil should be dumped in first!
- What if this melts in the water?
- Sorry, but what about our marbles?
Let us just dump it in there.
Dump it in without getting any of it
to stick on the walls of the cylinder.
[Where will the corn syrup sit?]
The corn syrup can push
the peanuts up to the top.
[No way!]
[The magic of density!
The peanuts are pushed up to the top!]
The water and the peanuts
are pushed up to the top!
[The peanuts are pushed up to the top
thanks to the corn syrup's heavy density.]
Time to dump in the marbles.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyun's turn
to dump in their marbles.]
[Will the marbles show an unexpected result
just like the peanuts had?]
- Dump the larger one in there.
- Be careful not to crack the cylinder.
[No chance of that happening.
The marbles clunk down to the bottom.]
- I guess it's not going to be us.
- Candles don't float in water.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo's candle.]
You know those floating candles?
They usually have something on the bottom.
Melted wax would float though.
[Wait, it's floating!]
Ji Hyo, they're floating!
Don't put anymore in there.
[The candles are floating just fine
on their own!]
- What do we do, Ji Hyo?
- I told you that the candle is the winner.
- Ji Hyo, we could actually win this!
- My peanuts are still floating, too.
- My peanuts are floating, too.
- Look at the peanuts.
[Current standing-
Candles vs Peanuts.]
- Peanuts shouldn't be floating, right?
- Pipe it down.
And finally... dump the chili oil in there.
[The only token left remaining
is Gary and So Min's chili oil.]
[What will be the outcome of the chili oil?]
- Is that floating?
- Stay up there.
Stay up there, my candles.
[Just who... will be the ultimate winner?]
Come on, candle!
Let it be the candle!
[The chili oil is floating
back up to the top!]
Float to the top, peanuts!
Come on, peanuts!
[The peanuts are slowly
starting to sink to the bottom.]
[The peanuts are sinking
to the bottom of the chili oil.]
- The candle is still floating!
- Everything is under the oil.
[Will the candle really be the
final winner?]
[The candles are still remaining on top!]
[Floating on top are
Ha Ha and Ji Hyo's candles!]
[Ha Ha, and Ji Hyo are the final winners
of the Greatest Love!]
[The magic of density-
Candles take everyone by surprise.]
Oh my, I can't believe this!
I seriously can't believe this!
[Even the candles are enjoying their
moment of victory from the top.]
- Ji Hyo's luck is seriously unbeatable.
- When So Hee heard of this game...
she figured out the game when she heard it,
and was talking about the density of it all.
She kept talking like she was so smart even
as I kept telling her that it was the candles!
She kept asking how I could not
know about their density!
- I told you that it was the candles!
- I'm so sorry.
- I really didn't think it was the candles.
- Myeonwalgwon ended up winning.
- I seriously can't believe...
- Ugh, this is hurtful to my pride!
- Then peanuts aren't it?
- No, not the peanuts.
But the peanuts did
give a run for their money.
[But at a closer look,
one peanut is still floating up on top.]
- The peanuts did stay up there.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
The peanuts aren't up there anymore!
Ugh, that's so spicy!
[What a piece of work...]
- Give me some water!
- Did you not see the chili oil in there?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Fiery spirited fairies are here!
Kim Seo Hyung, and Yeh Ji Won.]
[Tons of laughter, and overflow of talent!
Keeps the RM members on their toes.]
[Off on a public transit trip
to welcome in the spring air.]
- The water bottle!
- Where did it go?
- Water!
[Obtain the water of mystery.]
[The unexpected two faces
of these fairies!]
[The fairies turn without a
moment's notice!]
[Which of the two fairies will help
clear up the world's supply of water?]
[Next Week's Running Man-
The Race of the Water Fairies.]