[Running Man's fifth
anniversary special, part one.]
[The special stage of the legends!]
[The festivity of Korea's
million album sellers!]
[An extreme Running Man makeover
will be revealed now!]
[The Million Seller Race]
['E' Club in Chungdam-dong]
[Running Man's
fifth anniversary special]
[Our first part starts with
fresh beats in the club!]
[The club is filled with excitement.]
[But why are they here?]
[The Running Man members
were invited by surprise.]
What's this?
[The club is full at 11:40 a.m.]
Why did you make us wear these?
There are so many people here!
- What is it?
- What's the theme for this week?
- This is amazing!
- This is awesome!
[They lose themselves to the rhythm.]
How are there so many people,
this early?
To the stage, to the stage!
[They're clubbing before noon...]
Hello!
- What's with our clothing?
- Why did they give it to us?
[They don't know who it's for,
but it's party time!]
[They go on stage without
anyone telling them to.]
[I don't what the occasion is,
but it's fun!]
[Let's party for now!]
[As soon as the members go on stage]
[the beat gets faster.]
What's this?
[The rhythm magician is here!]
What is it?
Hello, everyone!
[Huh? That sounds familiar!]
Nice to meet you, I'm your DJ for today.
I'm Koo Jun Yup from CLON!
[What a surprise!]
[Koo Jun Yup from CLON]
['Kung Tari Shabara'
from CLON's first album.]
[We're going to have a blast!]
['First Love' from
CLON's fourth album.]
[This dance comes out naturally!]
[Kwang Soo,
this must be a gift from the Gods!]
Everyone!
Ore ore o!
I keep smiling now!
Just thinking about you!
[Everyone has fallen into
the trance of ore ore o.]
Ore ore o!
[An unexpected but amazing
performance by CLON.]
[Things got heated, fast.]
DJ Koo!
[Everyone, scream!]
DJ Koo, DJ Koo!
[The club is heated to the max thanks
to the world-class DJ's appearance!]
[The party just started!]
What is it?
It's g.o.d!
[The second guest is here!]
[The Nation's idol, the cryogenic
patient, and a new husband]
[the cheerful fella!]
[Park Jun Hyung from g.o.d]
['Friday Night' from
g.o.d's second album.]
[This moment right now,
is a Friday night!]
[The original nation's Idol,
g.o.d's eldest brother.]
[The return of Bro Jun!]
Everybody say! Tonight's the
night, tonight's the night!
Hey!
Ho!
Tonight's the night,
tonight's the night!
Pump it everybody say
tonight's the night,
tonight's the night!
Ho! Ho! Ho! Ho!
Tonight's the night,
tonight's the night!
[The second guest,
Bro Jun's performance is over.]
[And before they can even reflect,
the third guest has come!]
[It's our bro!]
[Instead of a black cat]
[we have a black tiger!]
['Black Cat Nero'
from Turbo's first album.]
[The dance makes our hands and feet
go in a zig-zag with the Euro-beat.]
[The flashy dance moves,
and the high pitched voice!]
[The unbeatable Turbo!]
[Jong Kook is the third guest
for the party!]
[Now, the official party starts!]
Let's scream!
[His special stage for his
fellow Running Man members.]
[He adds more fun
to the surprise party!]
[He couldn't help himself
but even rap as well.]
[Turbo's fan, Ha Ha intrudes on stage!]
['Twist King'
from Turbo's second album.]
[I touched Turbo!]
[DJ Koo dances, too.]
Shout out, everybody dance!
Don't worry about life.
Leave your body to the music!
Twist King, yeah!
- Who is it?
- Who's next?
[Wow! It's summer!]
[The official song of the summer!]
Yeah, come on!
['Woman On The Beach' from
Cool's 3.5th album.]
[Lee Jae Hun from Cool]
[Grasshopper jumped on stage
instead of the ocean.]
[He got held back by fans.]
[A tune that gives a refreshing
sensation by the mixed group, Cool.]
We loved each other.
[A magical song that makes
you refreshed just by listening.]
['Destiny' from Cool's third album.]
I anxiously searched for
my destined other half!
One, two, three, four!
[The megaton range hit song that
made Cool exist today.]
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
Where were you all those times?
[An expert's performance
that engages the audience.]
It's so fun!
This is great!
[He can do the dance perfectly,
Peter Pan Jae Hun.]
[The audiences fall
into the dance as well.]
Now, I can't keep both of you.
[The unstoppable retro brothers.]
Only the females!
I wish I were a man
at a time like this!
[A perfect ending
that satisfies women's hearts!]
[There have been four
guests already...]
[Where does this party lead?]
- This is awesome!
- There's more!
- Today's the best!
- This is the best day ever!
This is amazing!
[It's finally come!]
[The song that turned
this club into a tour bus!]
['Dances with DOC'
from DJ DOC's fourth album.]
It doesn't matter how old you are!
Everybody sing with me, just like this!
[Lee Ha Neul from DJ DOC]
[Now that the atmosphere is heated up]
[let's go for the real performance!]
Everybody, puts your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
One, two, three, four!
['Run to You' by DJ DOC's fifth album]
[The party's at its peak
with this dance!]
[A magical song that controls
all the clubbers!]
Bounce, bounce!
I'll run to you,
I'll even fly to get to you!
I'll hold you,
I'll give my all to you!
[A devilish song that makes
the entire nation jump!]
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce!
[It's the best!]
[The fifth party guest's
performance is over.]
[The members' energy is running low.]
[It's not over yet!]
[The voice that sends shivers.]
- This is crazy!
- Oh my god!
[The guest that will conclude the]
[fifth anniversary party is here!]
Aw, Kim Gun Mo!
[This is today's climax!]
[The last legend appears!]
Oh my god!
[Kim Gun Mo]
[The singer who represents Korea
in the Guinness Book of Records.]
Scream!
['Wrongful Encounter' from
Kim Gun Mo's third album.]
[The legends' synchronized dance!]
['Wrongful Encounter' first introduced
techno music in the country.]
[The beautiful collaboration of a
masterpiece and the beautiful voice!]
[Ours is a great encounter.]
[Everyone became one as
they greet the legend!]
It seems like you're more interested
in my friend than me.
You push me farther, after the day
[This has become the best
concert anyone will ever see!]
[He obtained both
a popular appeal and musicality!]
[South Korea's legendary singer,
Kim Gun Mo!]
I cried saying
this wasn't possible!
I had to throw away both
my love and friendship!
[The club became a
concert hall all of a sudden.]
[Today's fancy finale!]
Do the ending!
The dance!
[You mean, this?]
[The original techno dance!]
[Everyone's dancing!]
[The legends' collaborated stage
finalizes the performance!]
[The Running Man fifth anniversary
surprise party was a success!]
[Both thumbs up!]
[The heat in the club doesn't die out.]
[A slightly annoying gesture.]
What are you doing?
Why you?
[What have you contributed...]
It was such an amazing night!
This is the first time
I've sang this song before noon.
[It's also their first
collaboration concert!]
I thought this was a dream!
They're the same as back then!
Please introduce yourselves.
- It's an honor!
- It's such an honor!
The fact that they're
all here, together.
How many albums have
they sold altogether?
I think it's around 20 million!
They're the one that reflect the '90s.
Suk Jin and I were doing
the military service together.
- That's right.
- We were together...
I trained him.
He was really nice to me.
Was he hard-working?
You should've gotten beaten up, back then.
Why?
I tried really hard.
[It's the first time
seeing him so obedient.]
Today's race is
'The Million Seller Race.'
All the guests, including Jong Kook
have a record of
selling millions of albums.
He holds the Guinness record.
You will be divided into teams and
collect albums during missions
to get a total of
ten million albums to win.
The total amount of the
three million sellers' highest
selling album number
will be your initial score.
[It's an advantage if they have
a higher amount of sold albums.]
I'll announce
the Running Man team, first.
Yoo Jae Suk, Gary, Song Ji Hyo
are on one team.
And the betrayal club is a team.
[Which teams will the legends go?]
- Kim Gun Mo!
- Come here!
Look at all of them!
Jong Kook looks so nice.
I just want to say something.
[He sits like a lamb.]
I used to accompany these
people back in the day.
I was the youngest one
in the waiting room!
More than anything,
the thing we're most curious about
is the number of albums they sold,
which was incredible.
I think Kim Gun Mo sold the most.
He sold the most albums!
- The Wrongful Encounter!
- My third album sold 2.8 million!
- That went on the Guinness, right?
- Yes.
- The sale of a single album?
- If you include the black market...
- It should be around 3.5 million!
You sold so many!
[Poker face]
- What about g.o.d?
- g.o.d.'s second album!
Third album, 'Lie.'
Oh, right, 'Lie!'
'No, no!'
It was 2.3 or 2.4 million...
The second, third, and fourth
album sold the most.
- Which album did you sell the most?
- It was either second or third...
- 'Love is'!
- 'December'!
- Did it surpass one million?
- All of Turbo's album did.
He's so at ease!
We couldn't pass a million for the
last album, but all the other ones did.
What about DJ DOC?
I think, 'Morphy's Law'
sold the most!
I think it was the third album?
It passed a little over two million.
- That's right.
- That's probably right.
What about CLON?
Our first album sold the most.
I think it was either a million
or slightly under a million...
While we talked about the number of
albums, his voice got a little smaller.
[The singers before me
were too strong...]
To be honest...
I thought, 'should I
just say 1.3 million?'
But I thought I would get caught...
So I said slightly under a million.
- He's the original Hallyu star!
- He's the original muscle-man!
Jong Kook is kind of like
a fake version of Jun Yup.
I was the first celebrity with a tan.
Where did you get a tan?
On the roof.
I did it at the tanning shop.
We thought he got tanned
the same way we did, but.
- He owned a tanning machine at home!
- At home?
I was cheated...
I bought it because of him.
What do you mean?
A newer machine came out,
so I bought a new one
and sold the old one to him
saying it was the new model.
I laid down for an hour and half,
and still didn't get tanned!
- It was just a fluorescent light!
- You have to replace the bulb!
I didn't know that...
[What about Jae Hun's record?]
I didn't really calculate the numbers.
I just tried my best.
[He claims he remained
distant from commercialism.]
Didn't you say
you sold 2 million earlier?
- The thing is...
- This watch is also a voice recorder!
- From a million to 2.8 million...
- Wow!
- How much have you sold?
- Ten thousand?
- How about you?
- 2400 albums.
[Depressed]
[They're choosing
which legend to pick.]
[The blue team's first choice is]
Kim Gun Mo!
[They choose the most
beneficial person first.]
We're good to go!
One, two, three!
Bro Jun!
[It's more beneficial if they have
a higher number of albums sold.]
Lee Ha Neul!
I don't want to be on that team
with Gun Mo!
Then, we pick... one two three!
Jae Hun!
And Jun Yup!
[The red team is Jae Suk, Gary, Blank
Ji, Bro Jun, Jae Hun, and Jun Yup.]
[The blue team is Big Nose, Ha Ha,
Kwang Soo, Gun Mo, Ha Neul, and Kkuk.]
They're nothing without Jong Kook.
What?
- Ha Neul said you guys are soft!
- Like jelly!
Kim Gun Mo's third album,
released in 1995
sold 2.8 million.
[He entered in the Guinness
Book of World Records.]
DJ DOC's third album, released in 1996
sold 1.95 million.
1.95 million?
Turbo's third album, released in 1997
sold 1.4 million.
Your starting point is 6.15 million.
[They're already happy
before they even started.]
CLON's first album, released in 1996
sold 1.12 million.
Cool's third album, released in 1996.
- Third?
- 2 million?
Sold 1.07 million.
[They have a lot, too...]
g.o.d.'s third album, released in 2000
sold 1.85 million.
Your starting point is 4.04 million.
The difference between
the two teams is 2 million.
[They're heading to the first
mission site with the legends.]
- The best street, back in the day!
- It's the Rodeo street!
- Did the hamburger place disappear?
- There was a hamburger place!
- Over there!
- It's the main street!
There's a bakery down the alley.
If you see towards the right,
there was a cart full of CD's.
The place that sold
most pirated tapes, was here.
- Yeah, over there!
- At the time, when our album came out
we would bring it to the seller
and ask him to play our music.
- I'm getting flashbacks!
- It was so lively, back then.
- There was music in the street...
- It's illegal to play music in public.
[Only the hottest music
was played on the Rodeo street.]
[Even if they were stars, they asked to
play their music at the cart-stand.]
Here's the first mission.
You will be going to the Apgujung
Rodeo Street that you mentioned.
The mission you will do first is
'Relay the song with the citizen.'
The citizen has to continue
the song you sing.
You have to find a citizen that
will participate in the mission.
One of the million sellers will
start singing one of their songs.
Then, you have to pass
the mic onto the citizen
and they must perfectly sing the next
phrase without making an error.
You will receive 50,000 albums
per succeeding citizen.
You have 30 minutes for this mission.
The million seller has to
sing their song.
- G.o.d!
- I have a good feeling about this!
Jae Hun, what's yours?
- Mine's 'Destiny'.
- Sing it!
Why did you appear in front of me, now?
It's a weird pass.
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
Where were you all these times?
[She got that part wrong, too.]
G.o.d!
When you're tired and exhausted
- lean on me.
- Kwang Soo, sing it.
I will always be by your side!
I don't think you can sing this part.
I'm the rapper!
I did the rap part!
When you're feeling down and out.
Climb the nearest sky and
yell as much as you want.
[The combination of wrong
lyrics and cheesy vocals.]
[Was the song always this cloy?]
Scream out loud!
Kung Tari Shabara Shapapapa!
(Kung Tari Shabara Papapapa!)
[The original singer is shocked.]
'Kung Tari Shabara Shapapapa!'
- Call me when you feel lonely.
- What is the problem?
Call me when you feel depressed!
[Original lyrics: You
know what I want.]
I need you, I want you.
I wanna, I love you!
(I will run to you!)
- It was weird, right?
- 'I wanna, I love you.'
This time, 'Destiny'!
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
Where were you all of these times?
I always want to give you my love.
(Being lonely, I made a girlfriend.)
Today is the day
that we'll have our first kiss!
[A new era of a freestyle song.]
To be honest,
I don't really know the lyrics.
His freestyle is out of this world.
You can do pop songs, right?
- Pop songs?
- Yeah.
When I find myself in times of trouble.
Mother Mary comes to me.
Speaking words of wisdom, let it be.
I know the lyrics.
[I know the lyrics.]
[He always does the opposite
of what you expect from him.]
[While they laugh and talk]
[they've arrived]
[at the Apgujung Rodeo Street.]
- We'll have to do...
- Good luck!
- I can't do it!
- Okay!
['Relay the song with
the citizen, ' start!]
[An intense welcome!]
Who wants to go first?
[Let's see... the Apgujung people!]
[Welcome to Apgujung!]
Let's start on the main street!
[We're looking for fans of
Kim Gun Mo, DJ DOC, and Turbo.]
We need to hurry!
We need to run!
Sir, sir!
Excuse me!
Just help us once!
[Street-casting the first citizen]
Please help us out!
Call me when you feel lonely.
What's the problem?
[The chorus came from
the side of the street!]
Okay, let's go here!
One, two, three, four!
Call me when you feel lonely.
What's the problem?
You know what I can do!
- That was so close!
- 'You know what I want!'
You only got one part wrong!
[She hummed along,
and now she's put to blame.]
I don't even know this part.
[Stare]
Let's just ask, because she's pretty!
Because she's pretty!
[Dazzling, dazzling]
[The Goddess of Apgujung]
[Thank you, Apgujung...]
[Run to you]
[Surprised]
- Do you like DJ DOC?
- I don't think she knows our song.
Do you like Kim Gun Mo?
[Shy, shy]
Bounce with me, bounce with me.
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce.
[Huh! She knows?]
Call me when you feel lonely.
What's the problem?
She's got the problem.
[They can challenge
three times per citizen.]
I had to throw away both!
[Self-resignation]
She doesn't know.
[I don't think Gun Mo will
forget about this humiliation.]
Gun Mo!
- There's a lot over there!
- Where?
- Over there!
- Come over here!
Wow, it's been a while...
[It's been 13 years since a
road mission with citizens.]
We used to film a lot in Apgujung.
We used to do a lot of road missions.
You can tell by someone's eyes
if they want to participate or not.
When we ask and they look at
us slightly, they don't mind.
If they look away right
away, it's a no.
- That person didn't look away.
- Who?
[Wide open]
We found one, her eyes are alive
and seemed glad when she
encountered our filming crew.
Do you, by any chance
need to be broadcast for some reason?
I just got my hair done...
See?
She's got her hair done.
- Did you want to...
- Wow, you're beautiful!
Oh, Song Ji Hyo?
[A surprise praise]
[Smile]
I'm a fan!
- What do you do?
- I quit my job...
and I'm preparing
to go study overseas.
Back then, we used to ask these
kinds of questions all the time.
Then, shall we start?
[The first runner-up is Jae Hun.]
Why did you appear
in front of me, now?
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
[Will she know...]
Where were you all those times?
Being lonely, someone next to me
now became my girlfriend.
['Relay the song with
the citizen, ' success!]
We did it, we did it!
[This is fun!]
Thank you so much!
She seemed like
a long-lost friend.
She casually asked, 'did I do well?'
'Did I do well?'
She's a five-year member at heart.
Thank you very much!
This is what a street
mission should be like!
When you're tired and exhausted,
lean on me.
I will always be by your side.
So when you never feel
like you're alone in this world.
So when you never feel.
I'll be right beside...
Oh man, Jun Hyung.
[You seemed full of energy,
we trusted you...]
[Dizzy, dizzy]
I do know the song!
I can sing all of it at karaoke!
I love Cool's songs.
Ready...
Why did you appear
in front of me, now?
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
Where were you all those times?
Being lonely, you weren't there.
She makes a mistake every
time she looks at me!
['Coolly' depressed]
She's so full of energy...
[Dance, dance]
[Unfortunately, they failed this time.]
What about the policemen
in the police car?
[They must listen to the radio
often when they're on patrol...]
I'm sorry to bother you
during your patrol!
Sir, do you have a little bit of time?
Sorry to bother you.
It'll be over soon.
We'll start!
Why did you appear
in front of me, now?
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
Where were you all those times?
[She knows!]
Being lonely...
[They failed the third round.]
[Cool's pride just tumbled down...]
[I'm sorry we can't
be 'cool' about it.]
It was almost there!
I almost sang along!
Anyway, thank you!
- Can you take a picture with me?
- No!
[Oh, my!]
She asked to take a picture and
the officer next to her said...
No!
[Thank you to the two officers
who contributed their help.]
Let's try the car!
Bounce with me, bounce with me.
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce!
- Call me when you feel lonely.
- What's the problem?
You... I want!
Open the window!
- Window, window!
- This time, it's Gun Mo!
I cried saying, this wasn't possible!
I had to throw away both
my love and friendship!
My other friend tapped my shoulder.
And told me to forget,
but I don't think I can!
[The mystery girl in the
backseat, succeeded!]
[They currently have
6.2 million albums!]
We did it!
Help us once!
[The lady in the leopard print got cast.]
[Since she's in leopard print,
let her sing the Tiger's song.]
Everybody dance,
forget everything and just dance.
Forget all the worries...
I don't know!
I cried saying this wasn't possible...
I've warmed up.
I had to throw away
both my love and friendship.
My other friend tapped my shoulder
and told me to forget,
but I don't think I can.
[They've succeeded twice in a row!]
Thank you so much!
Will you give us a hundred thousand?
How is it possible?
- We will.
- You will?
You never know!
Thank you, thank you!
Try it!
You never know.
You promised you'll give us
100,000!
One, two!
One, two, three, four!
I cried saying
this wasn't possible.
I had to throw away
both my love and friendship
[How will this attempt that'll count as
100,000 albums turn out?]
Hello!
Hello, I'm alive and well!
Oh, he doesn't know the song.
- Thank you!
- Bye!
[It was fun.
Hope you have a good trip!]
[They have 4.09 million.]
Hello!
Hello, Ma'am.
Please come over here.
- How long has this shop it been opened?
- Eight years...
This shop must be popular.
Yes, this shop looks famous...
Where did you go?
Please, do not go too far from the mic.
Do you have regular customers
that are celebrities?
Jun Ji Hyun and Ko So Young...
[Suddenly looking around]
We came here not knowing
it's a popular shop among stars.
Alright, then we'll start right away.
- Here, he's Cool.
- I like Cool.
[Sweeping her hair up]
I think she's emotional like a girl.
Did you see how she swept her hair?
[She's doing it again.]
We'll start now.
Why did you appear
in front of me now?
You were nowhere when
I searched for you.
Where were you all those times?
Where were you, really?
Why did you appear in front of us now?
She was only in the fashion business.
It's regretful.
She might know Clon's song.
When you're feeling down and out.
Go to the mountain and try mmm!
[Try mmm?]
Go to the mountain
and eat something good?
Go to the mountain and try mmm!
Thank you so much!
I remember passing by
many celebrities on this street.
It's easier to see them here
than in the broadcast stations.
[But how come we're
the only ones here?]
Here's a famous designer!
[A famous designer?]
[This person is?]
[The shoes designer and an entertainer
Hwang Young Rong.]
She made her shoes out of gold!
When you're feeling down and out.
Just stop what you're doing
and take a trip!
[Why does it sound so natural?]
- I think you want to take a trip.
- Yes, I really want to.
Why did you appear in front of me now?
Hi-yah!
She's featuring!
You were nowhere
when I searched for you.
Where were you all those times?
Being too lonely...
when...
Hi-yah!
[What's wrong in Apgujung?]
Her hand movement was good.
- I want to help you but...
- You're wearing high heels?
Just film the torso of me.
Thank you so much!
[The red team fails.]
- Thank you!
- Goodbye!
Come to think of it...
it's really hot, but it's so much fun!
[My heart flutters!]
[The lady with the long straight hair
suddenly appeared.]
That lady...
[All the guys fell for her long hair.]
Excuse me!
Excuse me, wait...
[He's definitely a guy!]
Nice to meet you.
We fell for your looks and chased you.
I've experienced
this kind of situation a lot!
He smells like shampoo!
We couldn't help but chase you.
Please, forgive us.
Can I ask what's your occupation?
I work at a bar.
Are you getting ready for work?
Then, we'll start right away.
When you're feeling down and out.
Go up to the mountain and shout!
Open your chest like
me and shout.
Kungtari Shabara Papapapa!
[After a while, the red team
succeeded for the second time.]
- Thank you so much.
- You're so beautiful from behind!
- You're beautiful!
- You're handsome!
[Goodbye, the fairy of shampoo.]
Ba Ba Ba, everybody, dance,
forget everything and just dance.
Forget all the anxieties
(worries)...
It's fine.
[Kim Gun Mo moves out!]
My other friend tapped my shoulder
and told me to forget,
but I don't think I can.
[They achieve 6.3 million.]
[Kim Gun Mo is love.]
[Would this gentleman know this song?]
[He knows!]
And told me to forget,
but I don't think I can.
[The blue team achieves
6.4 million.]
[4.14 million
vs. 6.4 million.]
[4.19 million
vs. 6.5 million.]
[The 30 minute competition
is almost over.]
[How will it turn out?]
Both teams have succeeded 13 times.
[Both acquired 650,000 albums.]
Those 650,000 discs
will be give at the next spot.
Where you're going next is...
the restaurant of your choice.
- Any restaurant?
- Yes.
- I know a good place.
- Where is it?
It's a Chinese restaurant.
They make good black bean noodles.
- Do we you decide it just like that?
- Let's eat something cold.
We all want to eat
buckwheat noodles...
Cold buckwheat noodles!
It's right here.
[The red team arrives to a restaurant.]
Back then, I wished I'll park
my own car and eat here later.
- That's right.
- Right here, park my own car...
and go inside and eat
as much steak as we want...
Go inside and drown your sorrow.
- They have a good sausage stew, too.
- That's right.
[A sad story of Grasshopper...]
This is the place for the Yoo Jae Suk's
long-cherished desire.
We went to the restaurant
in the summer.
But the steak was too expensive.
We couldn't order
enough stew for everybody.
So, we ordered ramen
and put it in the stew.
I went there with my colleagues
but I was poor back then.
We were going to chip in
but I didn't have money.
I was eating but worried...
'You need to carry some money around.
Are you a beggar?'
- Oh, my!
- Oh, no!
At the time, I cried...
- It was hurting.
- In the middle of eating...
[For the eight years
he was an unknown...]
[he was sad and poor.]
[He was at the back corner.]
[So, I cried...]
[So, I laughed a lot more.]
[At long last, he's back here...]
You can order, but...
Let's not say 'but.'
You need to pay for the food
with the album count.
[They can pay with the album count.]
Each 10,000 won is worth
100,000 discs.
That's not fair!
Then, Jae Suk can't eat the steak!
[The tragic dish
that Jae Suk couldn't eat.]
This is 60,000 won and
it equals 600,000 discs!
- Six hundred thousand discs!
- He came back after so many years!
It's been ten...
no, 20 years!
Now, we have to order the
same thing you ordered.
Just like Jae Hun said, we need
to order a stew for three people
and some ramen noodles.
This drives me crazy!
Jae Suk, let's just order the steak.
We can do better at the next game.
That assorted grilled meat platter
is good, especially the sauce!
You need to eat well,
so you can do better.
[What will the Grasshopper's
decision be?]
[The blue team decided to
get the cold buckwheat noodles.]
We'll take away 100,000 discs
per 10,000 won.
That's too harsh!
It's not that expensive here.
50,000 won is
500,000 discs?
If it's 36,000 won, we'll round up
and take four hundred thousand discs.
- How much is the noodle?
- The cold noodle is 7,000 won.
Six times six is 36,
so it's 40,000 won.
Let's eat that first
and then see how it goes.
Wait, 40,000 won means they'll
take away 400,000 discs.
- We can earn it back.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I'm sorry...
but let's order a pork cutlet.
- Don't say that!
- It's an extravagance!
Ha Ha, dumplings are better.
[Do you want me?]
- It's 5,000 won for six dumplings!
- It's perfect for six people!
It's too expensive.
- We need to save.
- They take away the same anyway.
We all work in order to eat.
Ha Neul, if we resist,
we can get the golden disc.
We should not waste here.
I don't eat dumplings anyway.
We won't be running
for the next game.
This is too harsh.
I really want to eat the dumplings.
We need to save.
Did you decide?
Yes, we'll only order
six buckwheat noodles.
- Then the price will be 42,000 won.
- Get some radish Kimchi.
400,000 discs.
Then, we'll accept
the majority decision.
I think we should eat what we want.
And do our best later.
- How about you, Gary?
- Same, everyone sweated a lot.
We'll do our best!
- What about you?
- The best!
Excuse me, can we get
the assorted grilled meat platter?
[Unanimity]
I'm so touched.
Everyone wanted to fulfill my desire.
My team all agreed
to order it for me.
We'll use the discs.
We'll have assorted meat platter.
Please give us a free steamed rice!
- Then sausage stew...
- Sausage stew!
Also, one sausage stew, please.
- Then how much is it in total?
- 680,000 discs!
[They're about to spend 700,000 discs.]
What year did you come here?
- When you couldn't eat the steak.
- It was 1991.
1991?
This is the tearful steak.
[Here comes the steak!]
[The platter arrives.]
I really wanted to eat this!
- In 1991, I...
- These onions!
She gave us a lot!
Thank you for the generous servings!
Jae Suk, take the first scoop.
- Help yourself.
- Eat a lot, Jae Suk.
Thank you!
Thank you, everyone!
I won't forget this.
I'll have this first.
[I never knew I would eat this
after 20 years.]
[What a rich flavor!]
[His dream comes true.]
Try some.
[DJ Koo tries.]
[Jun Hyung likes it, too.]
It's good.
- Isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
This is the taste of memory.
[Love follows the grilled meat.]
Even kids will love this.
[While the red team enjoys
the luxurious meal...]
- This looks so good!
- It was a good choice!
This is perfect for the weather.
Eating dumplings on top of this
will be too much.
Let's take a picture first.
What is it?
[Here comes the dumplings.]
Is it on the house?
- Thank you so much.
- Excuse me.
Did they order the dumplings?
[Of course]
We ordered this?
How much is it?
- We ordered this?
- It's 10,000 won for a dozen?
Who ordered it?
Let's just eat it.
I think Kwang Soo made a mistake.
[Kwang Soo's mistake, you say?]
Please give us six
cold buckwheat noodles.
Go order the dumplings.
Go to the next store
and order the dumplings.
Just ask how much they are.
How much are the fried dumplings?
- It's 5,000 won.
- 5,000 won?
Can I have two servings?
10,000 won worth.
[The blue team has
6.3 million discs.]
Why did you do that, Kwang Soo?
You told me to order them.
- I wasn't going to say it!
- I was joking!
It's good though.
Don't fight when you eat.
[The red team's hearty meal.]
You ordered the grilled meat platter
and four servings of sausage stew.
We're in the middle of eating.
Two servings of stew for two tables
and four bowls of rice.
So, it's 96,000 won.
It's same as one million discs.
[One million?]
I should be nine hundred
sixty thousand, not a million.
Gun Mo sold 2.8 million discs.
If he comes here and eat twice.
He'll lose everything.
[What an rip-off!]
Let's go get some dessert!
- It's coming!
- Thank you!
[Two red bean shaved ice
cost 16,000 won.]
- You know, let's do our best...
- And win!
- What's that?
- It's on the house.
Thank you so much!
- How much does it cost?
- It's 11,000 won.
That's a hundred thousand.
We haven't eaten it yet.
- It's a free treat.
- We can't throw this out.
Give it to the production crew.
[We're not going to eat it?]
But this is really good...
[Looks juicy]
Kwang Soo, wait!
- I can't help it.
- Just think about it one more time.
You already know how it tastes like.
Honestly, I've never had it before.
How about playing rock-paper-scissors?
We'll give you 10,000 won
if we lose.
- You won't charge us, if we win.
- That's a good idea.
Can we do that?
Be our rep, Gun Mo.
- Take out five hundred thousand.
- What for?
So, we can buy the
shaved ice for everyone.
He wants to be generous.
[But that's not your private money.]
[The magnanimous, Gunsour]
(Like Mansour bin Zayed Al Nahyan)
You're too much!
What's wrong with you?
We don't know him.
- Red bean shaved ice...
- Kim Gun Mo is ousted!
[Kim Gun Mo is ousted!]
[An unwary victim]
He's enjoying it.
- Shall we do it?
- Either a hundred thousand...
It'll be a single round match!
You'll lose, if you don't throw.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Rock-paper-scissors!]
[He saw it.]
[He threw it after he saw his.]
[It's piece of cake.]
[The PD realized it too late.]
- That's foul play.
- No, it's not.
He threw it on time.
The PD is too naive.
[Frustrated]
How are you going to
live in this harsh world?
[This tastes fantastic!]
[I can't let the mango leave...]
Then, let me have a bite.
[He couldn't contain himself.]
It's funny he asked for a bite.
[The blue team even
had a free dessert.]
- That was a good meal.
- It was delicious.
Aw... thank you, Ji Hyo.
[The have a lot less discs,
but they feel more rich.]
How many discs did we use?
Probably, 400,000 to 500,000 discs.
- We heard you ate a lot.
- Yes.
You don't have that much money.
Please, buy us a cup of coffee.
- How much is it?
- 10,000 won equals 100,000 discs.
Honestly, we started off...
Right, we had a lot less
discs from the beginning.
[Negotiations under the table]
[The album tycoon, Gunsour]
If you're going to give it to her.
Let's hear her saying 'I dreamed of you.'
[Oh, no...]
'I dreamed of you,
I dreamed of coffee.'
[Laugh]
Just do it.
I dreamed of you,
I dreamed of coffee.
I had a poop, a diarrhea poop.
I'm cuter!
I'm cuter than you!
[What's with him?]
I'm really bad at this!
[They successfully tricked Blank Ji.]
[6.05 million vs 3.69 million]
[At last, it's the final mission]
[The red team is far
behind the blue team.]
We filmed our version of Avengers here.
And the real Avengers
was filmed here, too.
[Running Man and
the millionaires enter.]
What's that?
[It's a special music studio.]
They're vinyl records!
It's Turbo!
Wow, there's Turbo's album!
- g.o.d.'s album!
- Ji Suk Jin's album is here, too!
[Ji Suk Jin's debut album, 1991]
[Ha Ha's debut album, 2001]
It's Ha Neul when he has hairs!
[He had lots of hair when they
had their third album in 1996.]
Just look at my album!
- How did you get this CD?
- It looks cheesy.
A student designed it
for a part-time job.
He's wearing dress pants.
Ah, he kind of looks cool.
- He suddenly looks cool.
- He plays piano really well.
Gun Mo is the best.
[Even Blank Ji's heart flutters.]
Hello, nice to meet you.
Wow, he's awesome!
Anytime, he can...
Take his towel away.
Ji Hyo is...
the only woman for me.
Cannot get enough of you
my only...
[Grabs]
- Is this your wedding ceremony?
- Thank you.
I never expected Gun Mo
would sing for our wedding.
[A magical voice that
ignites the dying fire of love.]
Illuminating the dark
and sinister world
Ji Hyo.
[The warm and comforting lyrics]
I couldn't even buy you
a dress all this time
[Cough]
[His sense of humor
burst out at the climax.]
I got goose bumps
because it was touching!
[He changes the mood.]
[It's party time!]
Isn't she lovely?
Isn't she wonderful?
I never...
I don't know the lyrics.
I know the lyrics.
[Let's just go with the flow.]
I never thought
through love we'd be.
Making one as lovely as she.
But isn't she lovely
made from love?
[The perfect ending.]
['Class is permanent.']
- Did I do okay?
- You've completely warmed up.
Everyone, the blue team
collected 6.05 million discs.
- 6.05 million?
- Yes, it's 6.05 million discs.
And the red team has
3.69 million discs.
Three six nine, three six nine!
- Oh, no.
- You must have eaten a lot.
- The gap is too big.
- At this spot, you'll pass ten million.
Basically, you see
the game board over there?
You'll play the game
by flipping the number.
On top of the game,
there are variables today.
You have two chances.
- Do you see the screen over there?
- Yes.
That's in Shinchon.
Pardon?
[Shinchon?]
[♪ At the same time, Shinchon]
[The street of youth]
[In the middle of the street]
[there's a capsule noraebang!]
We've installed
a single-room noraebang.
They're singing right now.
[It is broadcast simultaneously.]
You don't know them?
- Did we cast them?
- No, they're passersby.
So far, a few groups
have sang in there.
[Anyone can use the noraebang.]
[The nostalgic noraebang
with million sellers.]
Outside, it has the sign
'the nostalgic noraebang.'
Inside the box, there are posters
with the song list of your songs.
Therefore, inside the singing booth
of the busy street of Shinchon
if they pick one of your songs and sing
the team will get 500,000 discs.
- 500, 000 discs?
- Awesome!
We're confident!
- Someone's singing.
- Is the score recorded?
If anyone sings one of your songs
the alarm will sound and
you'll get 500,000 discs.
This chance will be effective from now
until someone passes ten million discs.
[The nostalgic noraebang
will be the key to winning.]
[The victory might be
decided by the citizens.]
[The exciting hip-hop sisters]
[The pleasant trot duo]
[The sad ballad trio]
[The serious solo]
[We welcome everyone!]
The second chance is...
'I miss you, my friend.'
From now on, you can call
one singer friend.
Just one person.
If the singer completes
the mission with you
top album sales of
the singer will be added.
Who should we call?
- It has to be one person.
- We need to discuss it first.
Who should we call?
Jae Suk.
How about H.O.T?
Their album...
Hee Jun, let's call him.
Hello.
I'm filming 'Running Man.'
I'm in the middle of filming it.
- Ask what's their top sale?
- What number is the most sold album?
Their fourth album sold 1.48 million.
What are you doing, Hee Jun?
Are you filming?
You're practicing for the concert?
Wait a moment.
- Talk to him.
- Hee Jun.
It's Jae Suk.
I'm sorry.
Can you come here for 30 minutes?
Tell him he can wear a mask.
They're in the middle of practicing.
So, it'll be hard.
That's too bad.
I see, Hee Jun.
H.O.T sold 1.48 million.
That's too bad.
How about Jo Sung Mo?
I'll talk to him.
His phone's off.
It says Kim Jong Suh's second album
sold more than a million.
- Let's call Jong Suh.
- Yes, do that.
Hello, Jong Suh?
Your album...
a single album sold a lot, right?
Where are you now, Jong Suh?
You're in Daejun?
[Disappointed]
I see, Jong Suh.
Where are you now?
We're filming 'Running Man.'
You need to come here.
Just for 30 minutes.
But you need to come to our team
for 30 minutes.
Thank you so much!
Come quickly!
[They've succeeded at casting.]
- 1.58 million sold.
- The score will be similar.
Call Sung Soo of Cool.
[What? The Sung Soo I know?]
[We're filming 'Running Man.'
Can you come?]
That'll do!
[Stood up]
It's Jae Hun.
It's weird here, don't come!
Come, Sung Soo!
[He's not that cool.]
If you don't come, I'll
write you a letter.
Tell him you'll write a letter
and make it song lyrics.
Jun Yup is upset to hear that.
[Why do you keep
talking about letters?]
- Please calm down.
- We didn't do anything.
All of a sudden,
they dissed us in their song.
They said we had
a voice of a dog seller.
He was a real gangster back then.
We're nice to each other now.
Thanks to him
'Show Me the Money' started.
Sung Soo, come quickly.
- Is he coming?
- Yes!
Okay, that's the end of it.
- But you don't know who we called.
- Who did you call?
[He's sending a text message.]
[In a moment]
[Another million seller
came for the red team!]
[The one who could reverse the result!]
For those of you
who are tired and hungry
we've prepared a snack bar
behind the monitor.
If you see the menu
there's a price list.
But whatever you want.
Ice is priced for 50,000 discs?
A bottle of juice is for 100,000.
Bag of popcorn is 10,000.
I 'll never be able to eat it.
Are you buying it now?
[Gunsour and his bodyguards
came to spend.]
Don't use it just to by funny!
He wants to eat something!
I just want to buy a pack of gum.
It's just 50,000 discs.
50,000 discs?
I only sold 2,400 discs!
[Come again, Gunsour.]
Pay us 10,000 discs for a piece of gum.
Ji Hyo, he gave you 10,000 discs worth.
Ha Neul is getting a phone call.
- It feels weird.
- Just answer it.
[Kim Sung Soo]
Ha Neul...
- Yes, Sung Soo.
- My child is alone, I can't go.
My child is alone, I can't go.
[All of a sudden?]
[Jae Suk sent Sung Soo a message
telling him not to come.]
[My plan worked!]
[The blue team is
in a state of emergency.]
- She's big!
- Bring her with you!
[It's like they're having a party.]
Sung Soo, is this how it is?
Give me the phone.
Give us 100,000 discs.
We'll make him come.
What's going on?
Are they gangsters or what?
Give us 100,000 discs.
We'll make him come!
- Are you sure he'll come?
- He'll come for sure.
[Gunsour is already preparing
100,000 discs for them.]
[They receive 100,000 discs first.]
- That's sneaky!
- Call him now.
[He's calling Sung Soo right away.]
100,000 is not that easy to make!
Call them right now
and tell them you'll go.
[Will Sung Soo leaves
at one call of Jae Suk?]
Wait, Sung Soo's calling.
Just don't come!
Good job!
[The controversy about Kim Sung Soo
reversed again.]
- Call Tae Woo from g.o.d.
- Answer the phone.
You'll play rock-paper-scissors
and pick a number from the board.
Gun mo never lost.
You'll lose, if you don't throw.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Jun Hyung wins.]
[The red team can
choose the first game.]
It's fine.
- Ten!
- Ten?
This game is for 500,000 discs.
[The classic zero game]
Pick three reps.
You know how to play the zero game.
Call our a number.
If the number matches,
the person will escape.
The team that all the
members escape will win.
[Gun Mo, Ha Neul, Kwang Soo vs.
Jae Hun, Gary, Ji Hoon]
The sneaky brothers will play it.
Old and new sneak members.
The team that all the
members escape will get 500,000 discs.
That's a lot!
Let's get something to eat,
if we win 500,000 discs.
Ji Hyo, first.
- We'll start now.
- Zero!
[Lift]
[Ji Hyo could have
escaped, if not Jae Hun]
Let's just call out 'pang'
instead of 'zero.'
Just call it 'zero.'
'Pang' is a bit weird, I guess.
From Kwang Soo.
I'll call it now.
[Nervous]
Kwang Soo's turn.
Six!
[It was five.]
- Please do not move your lips like that.
- Why no?
- Don't say it like that.
- That's okay.
It's habit.
- Please call out 'start.'
- Start!
Zero!
Gary.
[It's Gun Mo's turn.]
- Is it you?
- It's my turn.
Zero!
This is how you play this game!
You need to do it suddenly!
After I say 'start.'
Why does he have to be the judge?
He's the famous MC,
but he doesn't have to be the judge!
[It's Gun Mo's turn again.]
Two!
[This time, Gunsour
succeeded without cheating.]
[If Ha Neul and Kwang Soo escape,
they can get 500,000 discs!]
[Gunsour escapes, Gary resumes.]
Four!
[It was close.]
Two!
[Ha Neul succeeded at his first try.]
[Kwang Soo's the only one
left in the blue team.]
Three!
Start!
Two!
Please, make it clear, Gary.
It's because my finger is like this...
[He's imitating
'One Ear' from the movie 'Tazza']
It's Jae Hun's turn.
- Start!
- Zero!
Zero!
[Lift]
- Good job, Kwang Soo!
- Gary!
Two!
- Ji Hyo!
- One!
[Ji Hyo's sudden attack worked.]
- Wait!
- You said Ji Hyo, instead of start!
Start and the name are the same thing.
[Everyone is extremely sensitive.]
It'll be either start or the name.
- Start!
- Six!
It's hard to succeed with six!
- Kwang's misfortune continues?
- I'll do it this time!
Start!
This is perfect.
Three!
[Jae Hun perfectly escapes.]
[My finger just moved...]
[Tell you finger to move properly!]
[Why am I the last one?]
This is all planned out!
We planned to leave one person out.
[Gary vs. Kwang Soo]
It's Gary's turn.
Start!
Two!
[This can't be...]
[The red team wins the class zero.]
[Kwang Soo's misfortune
continues today...]
You should complain.
You're older than him.
What's wrong?
They're having fun.
It's fine, it's fine.
Just give them 500,000 discs.
We're still winning.
[5.9 million vs. 4.29 million]
[The simultaneous broadcast]
[In Shinchon]
[Two guys are singing
Kim Hyun Jung's 'Bruise.']
[They must have hurt a lot.]
Pick a number.
[The winner picks the second game.]
Number one, please.
I hope it's worth 2 million.
It's Ddakji Othello!
Ddakji?
Jong Kook should play.
You know how to play
Ddakji Othello Game, right?
Three reps will come out.
And try to make your team color show.
[The reward is 500,000 discs.]
Suk Jin, Jong Kook
and I will play it.
Jun Yup, Gary and I.
You should play it.
The first reps are...
[The blue team's rep,
Ji Suk Jin]
Ji Suk Jin and Koo Jun yup!
Suk Jin, it's blue.
- Well, I don't think I lost.
- You're nervous.
Take your Ddakji!
What color should I make it flip?
Blue.
I'm good at flipping but
I don't know what color I should.
- Just hit the red ones.
- Blue ones are ours.
- So, what color should I hit?
- Red.
Except the Ddakji and the players,
nothing should be on the mat.
Please get outside of the mat.
This is also to get 500,000 discs.
We really need to win this.
Ready, start!
[You know who I am.]
[I'm the king of Ddakji, Ji Suk Jin!]
[No one expected he would win.]
[He's also stronger
if the game is bigger.]
[The sound of the
scream is still vivid!]
[I'll let you hear it again!]
[You already forgot about me?]
[He's the original muscle monster.]
[He showed off his strength
in front of Kim Jong Kook before.]
[Power!]
[Experience, skills, and strategy?]
[I'll crush them with my power!]
[The war of nerves between two men.]
[Who will be the winner
of the first round?]
- Just hit the red ones!
- Red ones!
Hit the blue one.
- Lee Ha Neul, your knees are on.
- You're petty.
[Judge Yoo is even more picky now.]
- Ready.
- Can I start here?
No, you should start from there.
I like that Ddakji in particular.
You can't touch each other.
Just hit Ddakji only.
Why not?
You shouldn't touch each other's body.
[It's all because of you, Jong Kook!]
Start!
[The Ddakji Othello, the
first round starts!]
Why is he so slow?
[Suk Jin flipped it!]
[Ju Yup flipped one, too.]
[They both flip one of each.]
[They're getting faster.]
[Jun Yup's powerful play.]
- Continue!
- Flip one more if you have time.
[Jun Yup's continuous success.]
[Huh? Did he just flip the blue one?]
[Why does Big-nose keep
flipping blue ones?]
[What's this?]
[Tap]
[Huh?
He made it red.]
[This is the bad
example of sneaky play.]
[This player keeps\flipping
the wrong ddakji.]
[You need to flip the red ones!]
The red one!
[Oh, you mean the red ones?]
[6:14]
Great!
Good, Jun Yup!
Jun Yup, go!
[Big-nose tries to chase
him from behind]
[but the game is over.]
[Koo Jun Yup wins the Ddakji Othello.]
Amazing!
Why did you flip blue ones?
[He's no use even if
he's the king of ddakji...]
It's frustrating!
It was such an exciting game!
Suk Jin!
Can I play for the second round?
[Please take a rest.]
You look tired, already.
Can I buy a glass of water?
I'm so thirsty!
You need to hold it.
I wouldn't be so mean
if you didn't hit our ddakji.
I was going to make you kneel,
but I'm being generous.
Jong Kook has gotten a lot nicer.
He's gotten a lot calmer now.
[At that moment]
[the alarm rang!]
[Someone in the nostalgic noraebang]
[is singing one of the
million sellers' song!]
[The original singer
of the song they picked]
[will get 500,000 discs right now!]]
[Who's the original singer?]
Bounce, bounce!
[The blue teams gets 500,000 discs!]
[The bounce started in Shinchon
has come all the way here.]
Yeah, baby!
Bounce with me, bounce with me!
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce!
See?
That's my song!
We'll give you 500,000 discs now.
[It's like as if they've won a game.]
[6.4 million vs. 4.29 million]
[They look relaxed again.]
Jut hit with the edge.
[It's okay even if we lose this game.]
Or just drop it.
Just like this.
Drop it like this.
Phew, I can't play it right!
This is upsetting!
It gives us energy!
[The last mission continues.]
[The second round of Ddakji Othello]
[Ha Ha vs. Gary]
Good job!
A song is picked!
[It adds 500,000 discs again!]
[The red team's songs in a row!]
[But the true battle begins now!]
[The comedy competition
that will go down the history!]
[The plot twist reverses the result!]
[No one can tell who'll win the race!]
He's here!
[He's here?]
[Huh?
Isn't he...]
[Finally, the red team's
singer has arrived!]
[Who will this man's identity?]
[It'll be revealed next week!]
[Running Man's fifth
anniversary special, part two.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
['Please, Find Me!']