[Case Number: 150913-2]
[Daejeon, Korea]
[Everything started from a request!]
[And a mysterious client 'X'
is behind the case.]
[The mysterious client gathers the
greatest detectives of the century.]
[A battle of dueling mysteries,
by the greatest detectives!]
[The one to reveal the identity
of client 'X' will win!]
[The greatest detectives
have gathered.]
[The legendary quick-witted
detective Yoo Jae Suk.]
[And two other detectives arrive.]
[The experienced,
detective Sung Dong Il.]
[And another who
looks suspicious.]
[The passionate detective,
Kwon Sang Woo.]
[I will solve this case!]
[It has been a while!]
I've seen Dong Il on other programs.
But Sang Woo, it's been a while!
Wow, it's been so long!
Nice to see you!
We're filming in
Sang Woo's hometown!
Oh, Daejun is his hometown!
It's my first time in
this neighborhood.
Oh really?
Where did you live?
- In Doonsan-dong.
- Oh, Doonsan-dong?
[The song of Daejun has returned.]
[Daejun is my homeground.
Everyone, follow me!]
[The extraordinary
investigation story.]
[He's still a little nervous.]
It's been a while since he's
been on a variety show.
Jung Jun Ha always talks about
Sang Woo and So Ji Sub.
We were really close...
[Clearly stated in the past-tense.]
We were really close,
but it's a shame.
Today, you are the detectives.
Including Yoo Jae Suk, you
will be the team leaders.
- Oh really?
- Team leader?
So our subordinates
are over there?
[That's how it works?]
Can we abuse our power?
[It's going to be fun today.]
[The expert,
Detective Sung is here!]
[He's the best at investigating and
his sense of humor is the best.]
[I will solve the mystery and make
people laugh throughout the show!]
- They're downstairs, right?
- Yes, they are.
- The employees will now...
- We need to pick well.
You will need to pick them,
but they're on a stakeout.
Oh really?
['J' Gold theme park.]
You will do a detective
hide-and-seek to test you on your
stakeout skills and
your adaptation skills.
In a short while,
detectives will come look you.
If you are detected by a detective and
get your name tag eliminated
you will become part of
that detective's team.
Can you see me?
You can't, right?
Is it okay if I hide behind this?
Don't tell anyone!
- Can you see me?
- Yes.
- You can?
- Of course...
Is there anywhere I can hide?
- Can I hide somewhere?
- In the booth.
So a detective might not
necessarily eliminate
our name tags?
They might tell me to go away.
[What if no one takes me?]
The person you eliminate
will become part of your team.
- Can't we do it alone?
- It's not mandatory to eliminate, is it?
[The detectives are picky.]
The important thing
is that there are three of you
and six of them hiding...
Wait... there are six, right?
How many years have you done this?
Shouldn't you know by now?
- He only cares about me.
- The most powerful.
'The most powerful.'
This is why everyone
talks about you.
Stop it!
So, you might assume that you will
each have two members
but it isn't like that.
The more you eliminate,
the larger your team becomes.
- I like doing things alone.
- He's like the lonely chief...
- You know, like in the movies?
- There are characters like that.
I don't really think the members
will really be of any use...
- Kim Jong Kook.
- If there's anything physical, maybe.
Let's go Dong Il, Sang Woo.
- We just go?
- Yes.
- Variety shows have gotten simpler!
- We just go.
- One person might end up alone...
- That's possible.
- Didn't you hurt your Achilles' heel?
- I'm going to catch Jong Kook.
That's right, catch Jong Kook!
Is Jong Kook fast?
[He's fast and strong.]
I met Jong Kook in a sauna
five or six years ago
and he was in the hot spring, alone.
But at that sauna,
there were only two of us.
- That must have been awkward.
- I awkwardly said hello
as I walked in, and we silently
bathed together...
[Meanwhile, the detectives are waiting.]
I'm going to go up one more floor.
I'm going to be at an
un-guessable floor.
I always say this, but don't go to
the basement or the top floor.
Because that's where people
want to go, first.
So it's best to hide on
an un-guessable floor.
I've given you a tip.
I'm actually pretty confident when
it comes to running away.
I've been doing it for five years.
This is a great hiding place.
This is perfect if I can open it.
[Just then, the team leaders arrive.]
- Should we get out?
- Yes.
Start!
[When a name tag is eliminated,
that person becomes part of the team.]
I was going to run a lot today.
But I got hurt while
playing soccer yesterday...
It's been a while since I've been
on an SBS variety show.
He was hired by SBS
on their first recruitment.
Oh, that's right!
In the year 1991.
- He was hired by SBS.
- Yes.
- What's with this treatment?
- There's no red carpet, but...
I'm so bored.
[Haroro is still relaxed.]
[But what's with this atmosphere?]
Are they here?
[Oh my!]
[Jae Suk's VJ, Kwon Yeol.]
[Runs away]
[When you meet them, run away.]
Well, good luck getting
your teammates.
Teammates?
We just look for them?
Let's go!
- We can take off our sunglasses, right?
- Yes.
It's so dark.
[Handsome appearance]
You're handsome!
I don't think it'll be easy.
Wow, this is a nice auditorium.
[Team leader Sung is looking
around the auditorium.]
[He found something?]
[He got candy!]
There's no basement.
Where will they be hiding?
Not in here...
A criminal knows
the mind of a criminal.
They're not criminals...
[They're automatically a criminal
because he's chasing them.]
You should have seen
me playing golf.
[Tiger and Giraffe are
in the elevator.]
Ha, ha, ha.
What are you doing here?
Are you here to golf?
- I have some work here.
- You guys can talk.
I don't think this is a place for me.
Hold on, I think...
Wait, hold on!
[Kwang Soo's on Jae Suk's team.]
[This time, he tries to get Tiger.]
- I think...
- Why?
- Sir!
- What?
- I'm allowed to eliminate!
- Eliminate what?
[Team leader Grasshopper
takes Giraffe.]
I'll see you later!
- Don't bump into me!
- I won't.
So you're on one team now.
So what can I do?
Can I eliminate?
You just follow me around!
- Am I your shadow or what?
- Just follow me.
I'm also flustered.
[I need to avoid that team.]
Why were you there...
I went to the roof,
but I hid too well.
You hid too well?
[Current situation]
[Surprised]
What's with this company?
- The people are only golfing.
- It's a guest!
[Big Nose hasn't seen who it is, yet.]
I'm going to run!
[He chases.]
[He forgot about his injury.]
[Runs]
He saw me!
[Stops]
[He wouldn't see me here, right?]
[Grab]
Oh, my!
[He saw him under the stairs.]
No!
[Who are you?]
Oh, it's Kwon Sang Woo!
Thank you!
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I hurt my Achilles'
heel yesterday.
I thought I couldn't run, but...
- Am I the first one?
- Yes.
Race start!
I will take you.
Please, follow me team leader.
He really is... handsome...
I don't normally...
I don't normally take pictures
with the guests, but...
[It's photo time as soon
as he's on the same team.]
- Can I upload it on my social media?
- Yes, of course.
[Is this a fan meeting?]
[He will be of use, right?]
You know what made me feel bad?
Jong Kook has gotten
so much weaker.
He's gotten so weak!
I almost cried.
Impala's over there.
Let's just pass by.
[They're trying to catch Kwang Soo.]
- You caught him?
- Oh my gosh, hello!
- I was going to catch him!
- I got caught!
You got Suk Jin?
I am Sang Woo's left Achilles' heel.
Today, I am Sang Woo's
left Achilles' heel!
Wow, in the middle of
this Savannah meadow.
- You got Suk Jin!
- I will be his left foot.
- Kim Jong Kook's around.
- I need to catch him.
[And another man who
is aiming for Mr. Capable.]
[Jong Kook, where are you...]
That's Sung Dong Il!
Who is that?
[Are you... Kkuk?]
[It's you.]
[I found him!]
Let me give you a hug.
Dong Il!
I need to give you a hug.
[Mr. Capable is on Dong Il's team.]
- It's been a while!
- It's been so long!
- How were you?
- Good!
- You lost so much weight!
- I need to live.
No one gets cast if they're chubby.
You're like a coach.
- I was practicing golf.
- Here?
- You can rest.
- Where do you want to go?
Should we go eat?
I only need you.
Having you is like having 100 people.
- Dong Il...
- I don't need anyone else.
[The only members left are
Ha Ha, Ji Hyo, and Gary.]
It doesn't look like me, right?
[Haroro's hiding
with the audience.]
Who is that?
[Ji Hyo's on the ground.]
It was a false alarm.
[The experts of escape vs.
The passionate detective.]
[Careful, careful]
- Where?
- They're there!
[Sang Woo's heading directly for
Gary as soon as he sees him.]
[Suk Jin, block that side.]
Please save me!
What is this?
Don't do this!
[Gary's on Sang Woo's team.]
- Gary's the best.
- I wanted to catch him.
- He's Mr. Random Capable.
- I'm your fan.
- Since 'Honey Family.'
- He's so handsome.
Who did you get?
- We're going now?
- You're part of our team, now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[Current situation]
Did you catch on?
I didn't get Jong Kook, on purpose.
[What is he saying?]
- Jae Suk...
- I didn't...
I don't want to be on
the same team as him.
That's why I didn't eliminate him.
When Jong Kook pushed you earlier,
that's the fastest I've seen you.
[The only detectives left
are Ha Ha and Ji Hyo.]
[Oh no, they're here!]
[He's managing his expression.]
[Nervous, nervous]
They're actually golfing, here.
[Huh?]
[It's a little suspicious
over there.]
Team leader!
He's over here.
- Oh, sir!
- You're so casual!
You couldn't find me?
- I was here the whole time!
I was so lonely!
I was here the whole time,
but no one found me!
He couldn't have been more casual!
[Team Leader Yoo tries
to get Ha Ha right away.]
I want to see the guest!
[Punch, punch]
[Rip]
[Ha Ha is on Jae Suk's team.]
- Why couldn't you find me?
- I almost passed by.
If it weren't for Kwang Soo,
I wouldn't have found you.
Look for Ji Hyo, we would be the
strongest team if we find her.
I don't know who
the detectives are.
He got an injury
playing soccer yesterday.
We found her!
We need to get her!
Why is she so fast?
- Why is she so fast?
- What about your Achilles' heel!
[Ji Hyo, who ran as
far away as possible]
[was eventually caught by
Sang Woo, with his injury.]
[Rip]
- Oh my god!
- I got Ji Hyo!
Wow, Ji Hyo's so fast!
We have four members!
How can you run so
well with your injury?
I was so surprised!
[He successfully
recruited three members.]
[It's the start of the battle.]
[Mysterious client 'X'
has brought them here.]
[Who will be the greatest
detective to find client 'X'?]
What's this?
Is it bowling?
It looks fun!
Before we head over
to the mission site
we will decide the order.
We'll take it slow.
- No problem.
- It's hot, anyway.
Dong Il doesn't care
about winning.
It takes the burden
off my shoulders.
Usually, it gives me
a lot of burden.
I just follow you.
This is what you will have to do.
Everyone will have to
blow with their nose
to knock the pins down.
The team to knock the most
pins down can depart first.
We have Big Nose!
- The points add up together.
- We're at an advantage!
[Sang Woo's team is advantageous.]
[Blow]
Kwang Soo's blowing his nose
and it sounds like a spray.
- Like a spray.
- I did it with my mouth.
Can you spray some on my hair?
It's getting flat.
So I can style it.
[Spray]
It's so strong!
One, two, three!
- Wow!
- Four?
[He got three.]
[His nostrils get bigger
as his eyes get smaller.]
[Jae Suk: Three pins.]
It's the amount of
pins knocked down!
- Can I have a re-do?
- Count the pins.
[Second member, Kwang Soo!]
Ready, set!
[Knock]
[What are you doing?]
[How dare you!]
Wait!
- I just got hit!
- Detective!
We should disqualify him!
We can just try again!
Then I can just keep
knocking them down, too!
- And also...
- Don't touch!
Just let him do it!
Go over there!
[He seems so nonchalant
about winning before...]
- What's wrong with you?
- What are you doing?
It's not about winning,
he just can't stand injustice!
- Sir!
- What do you mean, sir?
You can't emcee well, nowadays.
I've never seen
someone so worked up!
Go away!
Okay, start.
Don't push with your hand!
One!
[He only got one pin.]
- Okay!
- I'm so dizzy.
- Ha Ha!
- You won't fall over like this.
Kwang Soo, lie down.
He's feeling slightly dizzy.
- Can I blow from this side?
- Anywhere is fine.
- His nostrils are big for no reason!
- He's dizzy.
- Be careful, you might get dizzy.
- Let's go!
Seriously.
[Third member, Ha Ha!]
The end!
[Immobile]
[Kwang Soo: One pin.
Ha Ha: Zero pins.]
[A total of four pins.]
What are you guys doing?
Next team!
Are you out of your minds?
There was a
psychological burden, there.
You guys go first because
we only have two people.
Let's not talk a lot.
Just sit, and blow.
[First runner up, Sang Woo!]
Challenge!
I hope his nose
boogers come out!
I hope his nose boogers come out!
[Jae Suk's immature
psychological attack.]
It's done, it's over!
That doesn't count!
[He double checks his nostrils.]
I hope a big one comes out!
Hey, that would be so funny!
- Hey, that would be so funny!
- Hey? Are you crazy?
Yeah, it was funny!
[He's ready to launch with his nose.]
- Okay, one more time.
- If his boogers fly, we're framing it!
And displaying it for a week!
[Blow]
Get out!
[Get out!]
[Team Leader Kwon got zero pins.]
[Why doesn't it work?]
What are you doing?
It's so hard!
[Second member, Gary!]
Gary's good because
rapper's do this.
[Beat box]
I can't do that...
- Beat box!
- One, two!
I got a runny nose!
You're gross!
I said I was sick!
I have a cold!
It was like spray!
Gary, you did nothing
but blow your nose!
What are you doing?
[The third member is Suk Jin.]
- It was like a spray.
- He just blew his nose!
Why is mine so... short?
It doesn't work!
How do you do it?
It's because Suk Jin
shrank his nostrils.
It doesn't work!
- Now, Suk Jin!
- Should I go?
Let's go!
Ready!
Be quiet!
[Struggle]
[What was that?]
[Why did his nose speak?]
[They currently have zero
pins knocked down.]
[The only one left is Ji Hyo, the ace.]
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo surprisingly
has big nostrils.
- We're relying on you!
- Her nostrils are as big as mine!
- Is it here?
- Yeah, that's perfect.
- You look so weird right now!
- Ready, set!
[Blow]
That's it.
[Even the ace didn't get any.]
- You were pretty!
- She's cute.
[Sang Woo's team didn't get any pins.]
This is impossible!
- We have four people!
- We may end up winning, right?
[Jae Suk's team is in the lead.]
- Can we try again?
- No way.
I need to see which
way the wind blows.
He needs to see, first.
You need to get good balance.
[Team Leader Sung challenges.]
- He said this game was childish...
- But he's so hard-working.
Then should I not do it?
[Team leader Sung is
immersed in every moment.]
- Good balance.
- At most, he'll get two.
[He got four in an instant!]
Old people do this
kind of stuff well!
- He got four!
- Four!
How did he do that?
[Direction: Good
Power: Good]
[Nice shot, team leader Sung!]
If Jong Kook doesn't get any
then it'll be a rematch.
He can't do it.
- If his nose is even strong...
- I've never seen someone like this.
We can do well in other missions.
- Don't touch him!
- It's a mask!
Don't stop in the middle!
[Kkuk also got four pins.]
He's so annoying!
Cultured people can't
do stuff like this.
Ha Ha got really
upset for a second.
It's not because we didn't win,
but because the other team was annoying.
- We did well.
- We told you already!
[Will they be ahead of
everyone else, later on?]
- We're departing first.
- Yeah, we should go!
There's something in here...
an envelope.
It's like a wedding invitation.
Do we pick one of the
five places we want to go?
There are different missions
in each location.
As this race is about picking
the greatest detective
when you get there, we won't
tell you what the mission is.
- Oh...
- Then?
You have to solve the mystery and
guess what the mission will be.
If you do the mission properly,
we will give you a hint.
For example, there'll be a glass of water
and no one will tell you what to do.
- You have to drink it.
- Right.
If you drink it, you could get a hint.
Or you might have to spill it.
- This is like an education program!
- Exactly.
It's not as random as that.
There are going to be hints telling you
exactly what you have to do.
[Saemaeul Mural Village, Expo Park,
Daejeon Station, Chungang market.]
[Find out the mission
in each location.]
[You will receive
hints on client 'X.']
This is close by.
- Isn't it right there?
- Oh, really?
Okay, so we can go here first.
My mom told me not to go
to far away places when I was young.
Because I might get lost.
I'm going to follow what she says.
[Jae Suk's team
follows right after!]
- We could surpass them!
- For sure!
['S' bakery]
[Saemaeul Mural Village, Expo Park,
Daejeon Station, Chungang market.]
[Complete all five missions first.]
There's dumplings!
- Where should we go?
- Dumplings.
- We're going to Expo Park.
- Why?
- Guys, you need to wake up!
- Okay.
Let's go to the bakery!
- No, Expo Park.
- No, bakery!
Let's take a vote.
The closest location
is Expo Park.
- Let's go to the bakery.
- Listen!
Attention, rest, attention!
- This is Expo Park!
- He was surprised we didn't do it.
You thought we would do it?
Go be on another team!
- Attention, rest, attention!
- That's right!
We are going to Expo Park.
Is that clear, soldiers?
To Expo Park, let's go!
The dumplings must be good...
[Departure to Expo Park.]
[Dong Il's team is
heading to Expo Park, too.]
- It's the closest.
- Yup, to Expo Park.
A long time ago,
Joon said his school was
going somewhere to play
a game like on "Running Man."
Kwang Soo coached him, in person.
He gave him tips on what to do.
And Joon came back.
I said, "What happened?
Uncle Kwang Soo gave you tips, right?"
He said he did what Kwang Soo
told him to and got eliminated first.
[He was the first one ousted.]
[Why Kwang Soo of all people?]
That's the Saemaeul Mural Village.
- Let's follow the direction.
- Bakery?
- Or the dumpling restaurant?
- Dumplings?
- Should we go there?
[They are headed to the
dumplings restaurant.]
Team leader Kwon is from Daejeon.
We're nearing the
University I attended.
- Oh, it's here?
- Really?
- What is your major?
- Fine Arts Education...
- People are really...
- You're an arts student!
Oh my god!
He's a handsome arts student!
When I went to school, I did sports
or drew.
It was one or the other.
Girls would have fallen for you!
When he's sweating while playing sports,
like absorbed into something.
I really loved drawing!
I was always drawing through
middle and high school.
You look so different!
When I see actors or other
people drawing and stuff
I really want to do it, too...
But it's still not the right time...
[Departure]
[Expo Park]
[Dong Il's team is at the
entrance of Expo Park.]
This is the Expo Park.
Go and solve the mission.
I have a feeling the
mission's over there.
Right?
[Everything you see
could be a clue.]
Why would we have come
to Expo Science Park?
There should be something there.
Can't we just stay in the shade?
- This is supposed to be fall...
- It's hot, right?
We need to search
in this large area?
- I think it will be...
- That tower!
This is the biggest thing here.
There are clues.
So we'll check the
closer areas first.
- And then, over there...
- If I build a big house
I want one of those
sculptures in the garden...
- Like that?
- The kids would love it, too.
- What's around here?
- Science museum.
[The two detectives look manly.]
But this place is too big.
Is this program always this hopeless?
[He's getting sweaty.]
We're slowly narrowing it down...
- Are we really narrowing it down?
- Yes, we are...
[Expo Park]
[Chungang Market]
[Sang Woo's team's target
is the dumpling store.]
- It's been such a long time!
- You've been here before?
There used to be
a famous theater near here.
I watched a lot of movies there
when I was young.
I was in elementary school.
I think it was Chungang theater.
Let's go find a clue!
[Is this mystery game and
a trip down memory lane?]
I visited this market
when I was really young.
My mom took me to this market
and we ate some sausage.
I remember that time.
- Chungang Market!
- Yes, it's Chungang Market.
- I think it's been 30 years.
- It's the market..
- 30 years?
- Yes.
[In the area he used to
visit 30 years ago]
[how will he solve the mystery?]
- Where's the dumpling store?
- It's right there.
[They arrive at the mission site.]
- Wow, it's fried dumpling!
- Do you always have them?
- Can we eat first?
- Let's get in.
- This seems suspicious.
- Let's get inside first.
They look so good!
[Welcome to the dumpling zone.]
[What mission awaits
them at this place?]
I can't wait any longer!
[Everything you see could be a clue.]
[Menu]
[The rules are self-service.]
- The rule is self-service?
- Is this related?
- We need to do something, right?
- Right.
[They need to get to
the final site by 4 p.m.]
Maybe we need to make some...
within three minutes.
[It's a three-minute timer.]
What could this be?
- I think you're right.
- We need to make dumplings.
Start the timer.
Let's make it.
- Hurry up!
- Making dumplings, how many?
I haven't made dumplings before.
What do I do?
I hope we're wasting our time.
Sprinkle lots of flour.
Maybe this is not it.
Should we eat them instead?
Maybe we need to eat certain amount of
dumplings within three minutes.
No, this can't be.
It says the rule is self-service,
not water.
There's no hint here?
Oh, maybe it's this!
Dumpling, dumpling, dumpling!
Oh, that's the dumpling game!
Let's do it, dumpling, dumpling,
dumpling!
Wrong!
[What's hidden in this dumpling store?]
It's Expo Science Park!
- It's been such a long time.
- It reminds me a memory.
I like dumplings but
you can't miss this place.
Hey, team members!
Don't you think we should come here?
This is a nostalgic place!
[He's emotional.]
This place reminds me the old times.
- It's Kumdori!
- I had the toy!
[Long time no see, Kumdori!]
- Let's solve the mystery now.
- What could it be?
They didn't appoint any place?
Where should we go?
Maybe we need to combine
all the mission sites.
Dumpling, pastry and...
That song sounds familiar!
- Do you remember?
- This is the 'Citizens' Exercise!'
[They casually start exercising.]
Let's go check where
the music comes from.
That's the part for side stretch.
Why would they play this song?
[It's not like people exercise here.]
[There are people exercising!]
[Kkuk Dong Il appear.]
[What are these people doing here?]
They think this is the mission.
Even his back is annoying.
Wait, could this be the mission?
It's possible.
[They can't just leave.]
[Music stops.]
They did wrong!
- We'll challenge!
- Don't bother us!
This is our spot, so
go over there and do it.
He's even more hysterical today.
Don't copy us!
We're just doing what we remember.
We were going to do this any way.
We'll do it in front of the tent.
Begin!
Let's stand apart.
- Do you think this is the mission?
- Yes.
[Because the music stopped
when they were wrong.]
This reminds me of the old times.
During the assembly...
[Arm exercise!]
[Their body moves by his command.]
I remember my school days.
This makes me think back
on my school days.
- Back stretch?
- Is this how you do it?
[The good example of the back stretch.]
[The exercise fairies aren't
making making a single mistake.]
I remember the exercise.
My body moves to the song.
That's right!
This part sounds like Ben-Hur!
- That's right!
- We all said it sounds like it.
Everyone becomes serious
when this part comes on.
This is the most dynamic part.
Skipping!
One, two, three, four!
Oh, it's the foot shake.
You need to shake it nicely.
[You shake off the dirt on your soles.]
Breathing!
[Inhale and exhale]
Phew!
[The breathing sound means
it's near the end.]
- Great, I can do it now.
- It almost made me cry.
[The Gymnast Brothers have
finished the exercise.]
I think we did it.
[Didn't we complete the mission?]
[Was the mission at the Expo Park
This is the 'Citizens' Exercise'?]
We've completed the mission.
[They've succeeded.]
Let's go to the next site.
- We can't do it.
- We give up!
This is too difficult.
We'll do another mission.
- There's another mission?
- Yes, there is.
We've already finished
two missions here.
You should do the mission
at the observatory!
- Go up to the observatory!
- At the observatory?
I just hate every single word he says.
He's temperamental.
Leg exercise!
They said we'll get a
hint on the phone.
They'll send us?
On the Pictalk.
[The hint will disappear
in 10 seconds.]
There's a buddy called client.
[Blue striped shirt]
Blue striped shirt?
[Dong Il's team acquired
the first hint.]
[What does this hint mean?]
It disappeared.
Where should we go next?
Check the map.
Let's go to a restaurant,
so we can eat, too.
[Sang Woo's team hasn't
figured out the mission.]
[Kwon Sang Woo started to move!]
[Grab]
This is the restaurant's menu?
- Yes, it's the restaurant's.
- No, wait.
Ma'am, does this belong here?
It doesn't!
Let's check what's on the wall!
[Empty]
Maybe I'm wrong.
Wait...
- It's suspicious.
- This comes off too easily.
Suk Jin, maybe we should
eat them by the order.
[Blank Ji's suggestion:
Eat the dumplings on the menu.]
- Maybe the ones in the picture.
- I figured it out!
- Is she right?
- This is it!
- Eat them by the order?
- No, that's not it.
Isn't this finding the wrong spelling?
- Vegitable?
- That's right!
[He found 'Vegitable kimchi dumpling.']
Steamed mugwort Pun!
Not bun!
Buttercup squash...
We found two.
Meat, meat!
It's should be fried meat dumpling.
But here, it's 'Fried meet dumpling.'
- How many did we find?
- Let's combine the letters.
[What do they need to do?]
There are three wrong letters.
We should eat them!
[He actively agrees.]
Eat them!
Let's eat it one by one.
Give us a vegetable kimchi dumpling
fried meat dumpling
and steamed mugwort bun, please.
Water is self-service.
[They're eating up a storm.]
I think we're right.
[Isn't this the mission?]
Drink your water.
They're not telling us.
Maybe they didn't expect
us to get it this soon.
If you're right, you'll
get a hint on the phone.
[If they succeeded at the mission,
there will be a hint on the phone.
[Client]
[Backpack]
It's backpack!
Is this the hint?
We need to remember this.
- What color is it?
- It's blue.
[Sang Woo's team
completes the mission.]
- Did it disappear?
- Yes, 10 seconds passed.
We got off on the right foot.
[Will they be able to
get the next hint?]
Thank you.
My friends, let's exercise
in front of Hanbit Tower.
My dear friends will remember this.
- Follow us.
- Do you remember the music?
Can you put the music louder?
Start the Citizens Exercise!
Repeat after me.
- We're doing it for real.
- My friend...
you must be in your 30s or 40s.
What are you doing?
Section Chief Kim, get up!
Department Chief, you too!
[Let's take a trip down memory lane
with your stiff joints.]
I didn't think I would
enjoy it this much.
[He looks like he was electrocuted.]
[It's cute when you make one mistake.]
Many years passed,
but we still remember.
[His movement is fast.]
A student who's good at this
used to come forward.
That's was me.
Jae Suk.
Side stretch!
One, two!
My body just moves itself.
[Kwang Soo stretches at double speed.]
My arms move naturally.
Yes, my body remembers the moves.
[After the side stretch,
it's the back stretch.]
One, two!
[Do you remember
the highlight of the back stretch?]
[Everyone screamed
while they stretching their back.]
Full-body exercise!
- It's the Ben-Hur music!
- It's grave!
I'm getting emotional.
We need to make a serious face.
I used to do that with my friends, too.
[Help your friend
tone their sphincter.]
[When they hop in their place,
they kick each other.]
[Kicking each other's lunch bags]
[After touchy touchy exercise time]
[doing the easy arm and leg stretch.]
- This is amazing.
- I remember the whole exercise.
It's automatic.
[Finally, the breathing at the end]
All the viewers are crying by now.
[Ah... it's nostalgic...]
Five, six, seven, stop!
[They stopped moving,
but can't stop crying.]
- Did we pass it?
- You passed it.
[They've completed
the mission at Expo Park.]
How have you been doing, my friends?
Rose, rose, Rose of Sharon
is the national flower!
[He starts singing the children's song
that everyone knows.]
We've received the vital force
of Mt. Jungbyung.
- Isn't it your school song?
- Yes.
We've receive the pure
vital force of Mt. Insu.
[A sudden school song battle]
Didn't you received the
vital force from something?
- I think they use vital force at schools.
- What is it anyway?
We've receive the pure
vital force of Mt. Insu.
We've receive the
vital force of Mt. Suri.
- Wow, every school received it.
- A mountain
and the vital force are
mandatory in school songs.
We've completed the mission.
I'm surprised I remembered it.
Even the details like this.
[Jae Suk's team acquired
the hint, too.]
It'll disappear in ten seconds.
Blue striped shirt.
Let's go to the dumpling place.
- Dumpling or bakery?
- What's next?
- It's up to you.
- Let's look at the map.
Don't pick the other place.
Let's just go to Chungang Market.
- The Mural Village is the closest.
- The rest are all close to each other.
Do you think it's
faster going this way?
- Or that way?
- Give up this one, and go to the rest.
Let's just not go there.
We can still get four hints.
I know you're hard working person.
But let's be smart, Yoo Jae Suk!
- Use your brain!
- I'm the team leader!
Who wants to go to the bakery?
Dumpling place?
Mural?
You can go there by yourself.
Give him 20,000 Won.
(20 dollars)
Let's go now.
[Runs]
Jae Suk!
[Give us the car key!]
[They're about to be
grounded at the park.]
No!
Oh, it opened.
[They were able to get in the car.]
I see, I'll accept your opinions.
I'll go there, then.
We can go right after we eat dumplings.
What's the most popular pastry
at the bakery?
- It's either croquette or pineapple bun.
- That sounds good!
I'm okay if we go to
the dumpling place first.
Will they have dumpling soup, too?
My team members must be
really hungry by now.
They're pretty close to each other.
Pick either of them, Team Leader.
- Yes, go ahead.
- Just trust me.
- Today, we have the same fate.
- We're one.
- That's right!
- We're one!
One is just one, it's not two.
Two are just two, not three.
La-la-la-la la-la-la-la
La-la-la!
We're here.
- Let's get off.
- Look, Jae Suk.
- I'm excited.
- Dong Hun, look at the dumplings.
[Dumpling or pastry,
what's Grasshopper's decision?]
I'm so hungry.
[Isn't that a mural?]
There's... a mural...
Wait a second.
This isn't the dumpling place?
You've arrived
at Saemaeul Mural Village.
[Welcome to Saemaeul Mural Village!]
What's wrong with him?
- He's a swindler!
- What do we do with him?
You said you'll pick one of them.
You should have discussed with us!
At least, we should have
gone to the bakery!
You said trust you!
Why didn't you discuss with us?
We'll finish it quickly
and go somewhere else.
I should have protected
my name tag from him.
Let's go, everyone!
[Daejeon Station]
Wow, the station is so big!
How do they clean up?
The color of the backpack was blue.
The sign is in blue.
It's suspicious.
It's blue.
[Sang Woo thinks they might find
the clue from a blue object.]
[Everything you see could be a clue.]
Let's brainstorm if anyone
finds anything.
There should be the 'R' sticker...
[Gary is searching near payphones.]
Maybe Gary found something.
I found it.
Am I getting a phone call?
Why?
Answer the phone.
It's ringing?
I'll give you a question.
You need to solve the problem
in order to acquire a hint.
- Getting a call on a payphone?
- It's real!
Is he serious?
What color are the sneakers
that PD Yim Hyung Taek is wearing?
He's asking the color of the sneakers
that PD Yim Hyung Taek is wearing.
- Who?
- Seriously?
I was with him but I don't remember.
Who looks at other people's sneakers?
- Let's just guess, blue!
- White!
- The backpack was blue.
- Say it on the phone.
It's blue.
- You're wrong.
- No, I mean white.
- Hello!
- Did he hang up?
- Is this a joke?
- No, I really received a phone call.
- Did the bell ring?
- Gary did receive a phone call.
- Then they will call us again.
- Let's wait.
Who's working with PD Yim?
Can you contact anyone?
I think it was white.
Black, green, red!
I think it's red!
Since this is the mission,
I don't think it's ordinary color.
We can only guess.
No one's going to tell us.
It's ringing.
We're in trouble.
What color are the sneakers
that PD Yim Hyung Taek is wearing?
Try mumbling it.
- It's... color!
- Please, say it clearly.
- It's the color!
- Did you see PD Hyung Taek's sneakers?
- Wrong answer.
- I didn't say it yet.
He hung up.
Are you sure?
- I see, Julie!
- Did anyone see it?
Are you sure?
Are you sure it was orange?
I told you it could be red!
- Is that your stylist?
- Yes, she saw them.
I said it's close to red.
[Sang Woo's team might be
able to get the second hint.]
We got help from the stylists.
He's wearing something
that stands out today.
It's ringing!
Talk confidently.
What?
[That's too confident.]
- The sneakers of PD Yim..
- Are you asking what color it is?
He's very confident.
- They're orange.
- Is that correct?
The message came.
Great!
- They were orange.
- It'll disappear in ten seconds.
Sunglasses!
Sunglasses, backpack, jeans.
- Isn't this an outfit for a trip?
- It's a trip!
[What are the hints for?]
Let's go!
Come over here.
This is the mural village.
He's a dictator!
Take these Polaroids with you.
[Everything you see could be a hint.]
Wow, they're all murals.
This one's pretty!
The whole village is covered by murals.
- Team Leader!
- Yes?
- Let's separate, there're three roads.
- Wait a second.
I think we need to
separate from now on.
- Isn't he a little scary?
- Why are you doing that?
Tell him not to push himself forward.
Don't push yourself forward.
You go that way, you go this way
and I'll go this way.
- Let's separate!
- Let's do that.
Wait!
What's wrong?
There's a camera.
[Is that all?]
- Jae Suk!
- Why?
- Remember, the blue-striped shirt?
- Yes.
A tiger with blue stripes.
Tiger means Kim Jong Kook.
He's annoying.
No? I thought it was an associating game.
But you pointed out blue stripes.
That's pretty sharp.
- I admit it.
- Wait!
What is it?
There's writing on the road.
[Jae Suk ignores Ha Ha.]
Sung Yong, you need to film me!
Sung Yong, just follow me!
I have sharp eyes!
Quickly, three, two, one!
Withdraw!
Gwon Yeol, take his camera!
I'm the team leader!
Sung Yong, hurry up and come back.
We don't have time to waste.
[Ha Ha found a suspicious mural?]
Sung Yong!
Ha Ha!
I'm going to take a picture!
Move aside!
I'll be the first one.
[The tyrant team leader takes
everything that looks decent.]
Jae Suk, lower your position.
There are antennae here.
Grasshopper gets wings!
- It's a good picture?
- Did it come out okay?
The next member, Ha Ha.
This is a brilliant idea.
- You need to open the lens.
- One, two!
Ha Ha looks cute.
I will hold a pose like...
- Now, withdraw!
- Yes, Sir!
We don't have time to fool around.
That's unfair!
Wait, wait!
Look at shi!
Come over here and look.
Did you think this was a butterfly?
- This is not a butterfly.
- Kwang Soo!
[He's being philosophical.]
Take off Ha Ha's microphone.
Look, there's an 'R' sticker!
[Ha Ha found an 'R' sticker.]
Team Leader Yoo, stand in line!
Attention! At ease!
You can look at it first, Kwang Soo.
There's an 'R' sticker!
Team Leader Yoo, pay attention!
Open your eyes wide and search!
I don't think he's suitable
for a team leader!
- Carry this for me.
- Yes, Sir.
Look closely.
- Why do you think there's an R sticker?
- Why?
- We need to take a picture here.
- All three of us.
- Let's take a picture together.
- Please take a picture of us.
We need to take it ourselves.
- We need to take a selfie.
- He has no idea.
Team Member Yoo, pay attention!
I like how you try to work hard.
But you need to use your brain.
Your method doesn't work on this game.
This is upsetting.
- I'll take it.
- We need to be in the picture.
One, two, three!
[Will they succeed?]
[Team Leader Ha and employees.jpg]
- Wow, I found this R sticker.
- How did you find it?
I should have found it.
- Did we get a hint?
- No.
Then, this is not the mission.
It was a good picture, though.
Then... maybe we need to
find more R stickers.
Think, why did they give us three cameras?
- Why three cameras?
- Because we're three people.
Find two more stickers!
- Are there more R stickers?
- That's correct.
We need to take a
picture of R stickers!
[Where's Dong Il's team's next spot?]
Let's get in first.
The chairs are the sets.
I guess we need to do something here.
Look at the flour.
We need to do something.
I think we need to make dumplings.
Do we just make dumpling?
I think there should be
guideline of some sort.
'Rule is self-service.'
It says 'Rule is self-service.'
Oh, make dumplings ourselves?
Oh, could it be this?
Ma'am!
Can I get some water?
- Water is self-service.
- Self service?
- Yes.
- She said it's self-service.
Can I still get water?
- Two glasses of water, please.
- No, it's self-service.
Maybe we need to persuade her
until she gives us some water.
I don't think that's it.
She could bring us some water.
She's too firm.
Let's see...
'Rule is self-service.'
instead of 'Water is self-service.'
Maybe there are some other words
that are misspelled.
Eureka!
You agree on everything I say.
- Your reaction is too...
- No, you're right.
I think there might be
typos or something.
Oh, this one's wrong!
Vegitable!
[After 40 minutes of their deduction,
they've found a typo.]
Vegitable is wrong!
Should we order
vegetable kimchi dumplings?
Mugwort Pun?
- Isn't this bun?
- It should be.
That's wrong, too.
Fried meet...
It's fried meat dumplings!
I thought it was Japanese!
Please give us one serving
of fried meat dumplings.
- We're pretty smart, Dong Il.
- Not bad, not bad.
We've guessed it right.
Yes, it's obvious we
graduated high school.
[Dong Il's team acquired
the hint 'Backpack.']
[Jae Suk's team
is still collecting R stickers.]
- That R sticker is...
- Wow!
Did you find one?
Team Leader Yoo!
- Team Leader Yoo!
- Are you still walking?
You're too slow.
Run!
I was just passing by
and it's just there.
Take a picture of it.
Hurry up and take it.
Now...
One green, one red...
It's rainbow colors!
- Let's hurry up and find them.
- We need blue.
Blue... get the color of the sky!
Did we find the red?
- We found it.
- Let's scatter and search!
- Where did we find it?
- Wake up, Jae Suk!
We need blue, yellow...
Come over here, Team Leader Yoo!
Team Leader Yoo!
Why don't you run over here?
Five, four, three!
You're still not running!
Team Leader Yoo drives me crazy.
Take a picture.
Take this one.
I'm doing extremely well today!
- This is not blue.
- Team Leader Yoo!
- Yes.
- Come over here and search.
Both of you should be able to see it.
Try finding it in ten seconds.
- It's right there.
- Seriously?
- What are you doing?
- You're amazing!
This is blue, and this is navy.
- How did you find it?
- What color are we missing?
- We need a yellow sticker.
- Run!
Move, move, move!
I'm the team leader.
I want to save face.
[Why can't I see it?]
Team Leader Yoo!
- Team Leader Yoo!
- Did he find another one?
No way!
[He found the last one, too?]
- I've already checked it.
- Did you check it or not?
- At ease!
- Attention, at ease!
- Did you check it or not?
- I checked it.
[He's carrying his head high.]
Did you take off your glasses?
- I was wearing them.
- Find it in five seconds.
[Arrogant]
It wasn't here.
- It wasn't here before.
- Did you find it or not?
I felt something weird
when I passed this picture.
- Check the phone.
- We've got the message.
Wait.
Why are you checking?
It lasts for ten seconds.
Black baseball hat?
Black baseball hat
blue-striped shirt...
Okay, follow me.
[He's back to normal.]
Team Leader Yoo, are we going to
eat dumplings now?
- Thank you, Team Leader.
- Sure, follow me.
[Ha Ha's active performance
was buried like that.]
[Where is Dong Il's team headed to?]
Let's get off.
[Sungshimdang bakery is famous
for their fried pineapple buns.]
[Dong Il's team acquired
blue-striped shirt and backpack.]
[What's the hidden mission
at this bakery?]
This bakery must be really famous.
- This is bakery?
- It's amazing!
[Fried pineapple bun
is famous in Daejeon.]
- They opened in 1956.
- 1956?
What's this?
I think this monitor is suspicious.
We need to type it here!
- Let's answer the question.
- 'F.P. means... friend pineapple...
- bun.
- That's it, press enter.
[It appeared on the screen!]
Check the phone.
- Did we get the message?
- I think Jae Suk is calling.
Don't answer it.
[Sang Woo's team enters the bakery.]
Jong Kook is here!
I didn't know that
such a good bakery existed.
He knows the bakery.
We ate here when we were filming.
('Detective: The Beginning')
[It's time for Sang Woo
to come into his own!]
[He starts solving the mystery.]
I think we need to write something.
Look, they started making
fried pineapple buns May 20th, 1980.
That's the birthday
for this famous bun.
[There's R sticker!]
- What's this R?
- That's for Running Man!
[As they found the sticker,
a mysterious command appears.]
[1980, F.P. OnebiteAh]
- Maybe we need to feed someone.
- I think so.
F.P. One bite Ah!
[He's willing to do anything!]
That's not it!
[Now, they're feeding the citizens.]
They're looking for someone.
- Is there anyone who was born in 1980?
- Oh my god!
One bite Ah!
[They confirmed her birth year.]
Yeah!
[Sang Woo's team acquires 'Jeans.']
Are they finished?
They're done.
Is there anyone who was born in 1980?
You were born in 1980?
Take a bite, please.
[F.P. One bite Ah!]
- You were born in 1980.
- That's right.
Thank you so much!
[Dong Il's team acquires 'Jeans.']
It's the Citizen's Exercise!
Forward!
To the side!
Wow, I remember the exercise!
We did it!
[Sang Woo's team acquires
'Blue-striped shirt']
[At the dumpling place...]
[Detective Ha Ha
found the typos right away.]
Can we have vegetable kimchi dumplings
fried meat dumplings,
and steamed mugwort buns?
[Is that it, really?]
[Jae Suk's team acquires 'Backpack.']
Good job!
- Didn't we take lots of pictures?
- We took that one, too.
I'll check the murals on this side.
Check the other side.
I need reading glasses,
they want me to play hidden object?
We don't have time.
We should just go to the final site.
Wow, fried pineapple bun!
That looks so good!
On the screen, it says
'1980, F.P. OnebiteAh.'
- Just one of them is 'F.P. Onebite.'
- OnebiteAh, OnebiteAh, One bite.
1980, F.P. OnebiteAh,
could it be 'take a bite?'
I think that's it.
[Detective Ha Ha is burning!]
- I think it's as simple as that.
- Wait, Team Member Ha.
Team Leader Yoo, just take a bite.
- I know you've solved some clues.
- It was all, not some.
Just take a bite.
I think someone who was
born in 1980 should take a bite.
I think Kwang Soo should eat it.
Is there anyone who was born in 1980?
- Born in the '80s, anyone?
- Were you born in 1980?
- When were you born?
- I was born in 1983.
You were that young?
[You look older...]
Weren't you born in the '70s?
[Detective Ha Ha found a VJ!]
He was born in 1980!
You were born in 1980, right?
Take a bite.
He took a bite.
Do you have an ID with you?
See?
He asked for his ID!
Team Leader Yoo!
If you get this one, too...
he needs to be credited
for this mission.
This should be it.
Why would they check his ID?
See?
Team Leader Ha, who found R sticker?
Who trained you?
I found the sticker here!
No sticker, no message!
[In the middle of a childish fight,
they acquired 'Jeans.']
Did you see that?
[The final mission site,
National Science Museum]
[Three groups of detectives are
gathering in the situation room.]
Dong Il, please take a seat.
See?
We need to find the client among them!
I've never been wrong once today!
[What are the purposed of CCTV?]
It feels like a disasters headquarters.
This is the final mission of
the 'Detective Race.'
Each teams have different
amount of hints.
That's right.
You need to find a person
with a matching clue for
the final mission.
You can find a person
through CCTV from here.
Check if they match with your clues
and where they are.
The thing is
You're not going out all at once.
One of the member will
go out at a time.
And take turns according to your plans.
You got it, right?
When you think you found the client
you can go to the booth with them
that we installed on the ground floor.
And we can check
if you're right or wrong there.
But we can only do that once.
- We have only one chance.
- We should decide carefully.
Each groups might have different clues.
But we're all looking for
the same person, right?
What are they doing?
Are they recruiters?
[They come close to
Sherlock and Watson.]
They look like they're looking for
a baseball player to train.
[They've done discussing their plan.]
Are you going to go out
first, Team Leader Yoo?
No, I'm the team leader
and Ha Ha will go first,
Just listen to me.
- Go ahead.
- Team Leader Yoo will go.
- You need to pocket your pride.
- I'm the leader, Ha Ha.
Hurry up and go.
I think Ha Ha should go first.
[Jae Suk's team's first agent
will be Ha Ha.]
In my opinion...
- Think carefully, Team Leader Kwon.
- Ji Suk Jin...
took a good rest.
[Maybe, you will be more
helpful that way.]
Jong Kook has more know-how.
He will go first.
You don't have any other team members.
[Are you looking down on us?]
Didn't you see how we
played the whole day?
It was really annoying.
[Trying to keep it calm.]
We were listening to classical music
when we were on the car.
[We will keep detective's dignity.]
But they might find it quickly.
Of course, we'll know
if they person pass by.
[The final mission of
the Detective Race begins!]
[The clues that they
acquired by foot.]
[Combine the clues
and find client X!]
[Three levels, 27,000 SQ.
About 300 suspects.]
[And client X is hidden
amongst the suspects.]
[The only things they can trust
are the clues and their senses!]
[Which team will find the
client X and win the race?]
[Catch me if you can!]
Can you hear me, roger?
Yes, I can hear you, roger.
Pay attention on the screen.
[The first runners: Ha Ha, Suk Jin
and Jong Kook]
Let's just finish the mission quickly!
I guess the color of the
stripes are important, too.
It's really confusing.
So many of them
are wearing similar items.
We'll tell you when we
find someone suspicious.
[Team members can help them by radio.]
[All of them are wearing a mask
to hide their faces.]
I think the last clue was the mask.
Everyone of them are wearing them.
[Matched] [Unmatched]
There are so many suspects!
Calm down.
Team Leader Yoo,
quickly check the screen!
I see, don't worry about it.
We're looking at the other levels.
Search on that floor.
[Team Leader Kwon found
a very suspicious person.]
Lower floor.
Go down stairs.
This person has the matching
all four items we have.
[Matched] [Matched]
I'm going downstairs!
Around the booth?
I don't think that person is here.
But we can't tell the color
of the backpack.
- I know, right?
- Team Leader Yoo!
We couldn't find the right one.
Some pretend they are the clients.
- But there are so many of them.
- I still think the same person is.
The floor with the booth.
- It's confusing.
- I can't see all four of them.
I don't think the client is here.
So confusing!
- Is it confusing?
- It's really confusing.
When I think I found the person,
one item doesn't match.
[Team Leader Kwon found a person
walking to the other side.]
I'm on the second floor now.
We don't even know if the client
is a man or a woman.
Just run for the suspect!
I need to find the person
then match the clues.
It's not him.
[Matched] [Unmatched]
[Unmatched] [Matched]
The color of the stripes...
[Team Leader Yoo
is on the second floor.]
This makes me dizzy!
Everyone is wearing a striped shirt!
This is confusing.
[Matched] [Unmatched]
[Matched] [Matched]
I found someone near me.
Can you see me?
[He thinks the stripes are blue.]
Black hat, jeans
and striped shirt...
[But the stripes are black.]
[Team Leader Sung keeps following her.]
I think you're right.
The woman with long hair.
[Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo
are on the scene.]
[Kwang Soo found a prime suspect.]
[Detective Sung finally
meets her face to face.]
Excuse me, can you
go to the booth with me?
[Blank Ji starts an investigation.]
[She found a key suspect
that matches the clue.]
Excuse me, could you go
downstairs with me?
[Huh? Ji Hyo caught her?]
What do you think?
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
found the prime suspect.]
[What's going on?]
I'm downstairs.
[She's showing the suspect
through the CCTV.]
- That person?
- Do you see us?
Is this person correct?
Wait a second.
[Confused]
Look over here!
[Is she client X?]
Downstairs!
I think the color of
the backpack is light.
What about the hat?
- No hat?
- Hat is not one of our clues.
[They didn't acquire the clue of hat.]
I don't think so.
Get go to the booth with her.
[A suspect without a
hat starts running.]
Could it be her?
She's wearing backpack and sunglasses
but no hat.
I think I'll take her then.
[Blank Ji abandons the prime suspect.]
[Now is the chance!]
Blue striped shirt
Black baseball hat
[To find the one and only!]
Backpack!
[They've investigated
by all the senses.]
[All the clues point at her!]
Jeans
Let's go.
Please help me once.
[Detective Giraffe pulls
hand of the suspect.]
I think I found her!
Show us!
Just take her to the booth.
- Take her.
- Where did she go?
[In the meantime, Kwang Soo takes
the suspect to the booth.]
[They only have one chance!]
[They will succeed at the final mission
if she's client X!]
I'm sure it's her.
She has all the matching items.
Okay, great.
Go up with her.
We're here!
Black baseball hat,
blue-striped shirt, jeans
and backpack, she has everything.
Don't say everything out loud.
[Is she the real client X
the detectives were after?]
[Jeans]
[Blue striped shirt]
[Backpack]
[Sunglasses]
[Black baseball hat]
[What's the result of
the final mission?]
[Matched!]
[Jae Suk's team succeeded
at the final mission!]
It was her!
The one I caught a minute ago!
[We did it!]
[My friends, not all the detectives
are the best!]
[The identity of client X
will be revealed in a moment!]
[It's so hard to be a good detective.]
This is incredible!
[The Detective Race:
Jae Suk, Ha Ha, Kwang Soo win!]
Client X, can you please come forward?
[The mysterious client X appears.]
[Who are you?]
The clues you achieved are
look at her.
Black baseball hat
blue-striped shirt, backpack
- sunglasses
- There were sunglasses?
And jeans.
She's the only one with
all the matching items.
Thank you so much!
She has a beautiful silhouette!
Can we see her face, too?
Do we know her?
[Excuse me for a second.]
[Who is client X?]
[Client X]
[who suggested a brain
game to the detectives.]
[What's her identity?]
[Ta-da!]
[Shocked]
What?
- Oh my gosh!
- Tae Young!
[Client X is Kwon Sang Woo's wife,
Son Tae Young]
You didn't recognize me?
You didn't recognize your wife?
[Oh no, I got decoyed...]
[How will I face the music?]
Wait, wait!
I thought she was
one of the celebrities.
I honestly thought she's my type.
[It's match made in heaven.]
I thought she has nice skin.
- I wanted to see her face.
- It's too late.
[It's always the timing.]
You're supposed to recognize
your wife by a hunch.
[This won't do.]
I've experienced something like this.
One day my wife came back
from a photo shoot with a magazine.
I was waiting for the
elevator on the ground floor.
She was on the elevator.
- What are you talking about?
- Whose house did you visit?
[He pushes himself into a corner.]
I was zoning out.
When the elevator opened, I thought
a beautiful woman lives in my building
without recognizing her.
You're a good actor!
[He's showing the best acting
to make her feel better.]
- That's why she loves you.
- In a way...
I didn't know it was you.
I thought she was the one.
When I grabbed her arms,
we almost fell.
I was thinking about
going the other way.
I thought she would follow me
if I run away.
So I just walked with a man.
She was walking with a man?
I told you not to go
out with other men!
I always stay home otherwise.
[She talks funny.]
She's a good entertainer.
Shouldn't you give her a hug?
She came all the way for your movie.
- I don't really like touchy touchy.
- She hates it!
[Love returns.]
Her face is so dull.
[Embarrassed]
As if she's riding a merry-go-round.
When did she join?
From the beginning?
- Last week.
- Are you serious?
You haven't said anything since then?
He was in the States.
Why did you breed disbelief
between husband and wife?
They've just settled down
with two children.
Thanks to 'Running Man'
my heart fluttered again
when I saw her standing right here.
That's enough!
- That was the funniest moment!
- You didn't even know it was me!
What are you talking about?
I mean it.
You're so sly.
He's good!
I want to sing with him once!
Will I turn like this
when I get married?
We need to learn from him!
[Your marriage life depends
on the husband's attitude!]
[Jae Suk's team gets
the winning prize.]
[What is it?]
[Golden magnifying glasses!]
You should give it to him.
He has bad eyes.
[They must be happy.]
Thank you for being with us,
Kwon Sang Woo and Sun Dong Il.
Sun Dong Il?
Someone called him Sun Dong Yeol.
(Retired baseball pitcher)
He was really disappointed.
Don't call him Sun.
Let's give a round of applause
for these three!
[Thank you for being on 'Running Man'!]
[No one comes here.]
[A deserted island]
['Running Man' members are
trapped with no reason.]
[They can escape only if
they complete their name tag.]
[The escape mission with
the smartest celebrities.]
[A survival game that
awakens their reserved nature.]
[Another key to escape from
the island are the citizens!]
This is real!
[But that's not all?]
[Someone is carrying out
a secret mission?]
[Do not trust anyone on this island!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Next week, Running Man]
[The Escape]