[The most beautiful brides
have arrived!]
[But! These brides are shocking!]
[Dangerously charming!]
[Dangerous Brides]
[The most amazing moment of your life.]
- There's even a marriage officiant.
[A wedding full of blessings]
- Who is it?
Who will be my partner for today?
[Please consider me a groom today.]
[Who is...]
[Jae Suk's fiancee?]
- Jessi!
- Jae Suk!
[The first bride of
Running Man wedding.]
- I feel awkward.
- I'm Yoo ssi, you're Jessi.
[A female rapper with
strong combat power.]
I have something to say.
Who are you to judge me?
We're not a team.
This is a competition.
[Today, I came to conquer Running man!]
[She's bright and cheerful.]
- Jessi!
I'm so happy to be partnered with you.
Are we going to get married?
Jessi and me?
Oh my back?
Jessi, let's go!
Yo! Yo!
Hip hop, yo!
You're Jessi and
I'm Yoo ssi (surname)!
[An embarrassing rhyme
in front of a pro rapper.]
- Hello.
- Who is it?
[The second bride and groom.]
She's beautiful.
She is beautiful!
Yoo Ri?
You're Kim Yoo Ri, right?
[Kim Yoo Ri, who made
a grand slam of dramas.]
[Chick and elegant, Yoo Ri!]
[2015's most noteworthy actress.]
[The wedding hall is brighter
as she enters.]
- Wow!
- She's beautiful!
- Why didn't anyone cheer for me?
- Hooray!
Today is my day!
He's happier now
than at his own wedding.
I went to his wedding.
He looks happier now.
I feel like I'm sending
my daughter off.
Yoo Ri's face says it all.
For her, it's just acting.
Just business.
- That's not true.
- Oh my god!
Suk Jin is genuinely happy.
I thought she was a cyborg.
It's her first time on a variety show.
She's not!
She came in like a robot.
- I'm very nervous.
- She's actually happy on the inside.
- I thought she was a zombie.
- What are you talking about?
Do I wait for my partner here?
- I'm curious.
- Who is it?
Unbelievable!
She's pretty, she has a small face.
[Gary falls in love in 0.1 seconds.]
- Her face is hidden with her hair.
- She's pretty, she's pretty.
She has a small face.
- Isn't that Seo Ye Ji?
- Seo Ye Ji!
[The innocent-look of this generation,
Seo Ye Ji.]
[Her face stirs up
the protective instinct in men.]
[She's more known as...]
[Kim Soo Hyun's partner
in a commercial.]
I don't know how
we're supposed to walk down...
[A heart name tag on Gary's back!]
I'm so shy...
[He almost fell,
but he's still happy.]
[He can't hide his smile.]
Hello!
You know that today's
a group wedding, right?
[I feel a hot stare...]
[Really obvious stare.]
[The light footsteps
of the third bride!]
[His mouth drops open.]
[Who is Ha Ha's bride?]
- AOA!
- It's Choa!
[She is the definition of sexy.]
[The original cat dancer!]
[With a look that captures
everyone's attention.]
[Immediately takes Ha Ha.]
[As well as Big Nose.]
- Choa is a beauty.
- Thank you.
So is Ye Ji, and Yoo Ri.
- Ye Ji, Gae Ji, and Jessi!
- Why is everyone so pretty?
- What about me!
- You're pretty!
I'm really sorry, but
your wife looks tough.
But Jessi was a lot prettier
before she got her eyes done.
Be quiet!
I know when she used to be Jessica H.O.
- Jessica H.O. was a lot prettier.
- You were so pretty.
Be careful.
You're gonna get dissed.
Just wait.
- Hello, everyone!
- It's Kwang Soo!
[Gentle-mode Kwang Soo.]
- You look much better in person.
What are you doing?
[Who will be Kwang Soo's bride?]
Please come out!
- Who will it be?
- Who is she?
Kwang Soo is nervous.
It's Ji Hyo!
It's Ji Hyo.
There comes the dud.
She's the most beautiful.
There's no romance at all with Ji Hyo.
[No way.]
Am I really with Ji Hyo?
Why, you don't like me?
- No, it's not that...
- Just come.
Ji Hyo's pretty today.
Don't lie, Jae Suk!
- That's a wedding dress?
[Slightly disappointed.]
Ji Hyo's really pretty today.
The one who exposed
his ankle bones is here!
You can look forward
to meeting your partner.
- Why are his pants so short?
- Can I get my hopes up?
[She is!]
[Powerful walking]
- Do Yeon!
Please trample on Jong Kook.
[The comedian with great force,
Jang Do Yeon.]
- How long are her arms?
[With a model-like looks.]
Does she have four legs?
[She created a unique gag style.]
- She's so cool!
[This is the great force,
Jang Do Yeon's style!]
[Approaches Kkuk without fear!]
- The perfect partner for Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook is feeling uncomfortable.
Let's go, Honey.
[I like her.]
[She is definitely tough.]
- Oh, you came.
[Greeting the invisible guests.]
- Jong Kook feels awkward.
- He can't look at her.
Sir, you came?
[He is also embarrassed.]
- You know him?
- Do Yeon!
[Showing off her talent!]
[Bizarre.]
[Unique.]
[Grotesque.]
- Look at her!
[She captures everyone's attention.]
I don't know if you know
but Do Yeon actually...
debuted from
'The Truth Game Show'.
- That's right.
- Really?
She was on the show as
fake Park Jung Ah.
I've been criticized from that...
You were really funny.
[They do look alike.]
We will now have the
bride and groom's wedding vows.
It's a group wedding.
I don't want to marry him.
I will ask the grooms first.
- Do you...
- Just say yes.
swear to love your bride 'til the end
even when your name tag
is ripped off?
- Of course!
- Yes!
- Yes.
Sir!
He didn't answer.
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry.
Now, I will ask the brides.
Even when you're receiving
your punishment
will you swear to love
your husband forever?
I do.
[Hesitates]
- Why aren't you answering?
- Yes!
I didn't understand.
If anyone is against this marriage
please step forward.
Are there any?
There are none!
What is this?
- What?
- I'm scared!
[Why are they eliminating
the name tags?]
[Emergency situation.]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon's attack.]
Why?
[What kind of situation is this?]
[Tremble.]
[Everyone got attacked
without preparation.]
[Shock and fear hit everyone quickly.]
- We got all of them!
- There's something?
- We're done!
- It's a mission!
[Why on earth did they attack?]
[There is something.]
[What is their secret?]
[One hour ago...]
We haven't had a
one-on-one meeting in a while.
Why are there two chairs?
Is there someone else?
Your soon-to-be bride
will be here shortly.
A bride?
[The entrance of a random foot.]
Honey.
[Kkuk and Do Yeon's first meeting.]
These days, I work with
many female comedians...
Does your energy get sucked out?
What are we doing today?
Out of all the couples
getting married today
you are the most dangerous couple.
[Touch for no reason.]
[Too much pressure started
from this moment.]
There will be a
group wedding today.
A group wedding?
You said group wedding,
I thought of the wedding night.
- What's wrong with you?
- Sorry, that's inappropriate on SBS.
Kwang Soo's mine today!
What's with the heart!
It's embarrassing!
There's going to be five other
couples at this group wedding.
You're Jessi,
yo, I'm Yoo ssi.
You must oust all five couples.
Pardon?
- As soon as we start?
- How?
We have to oust them
during the opening?
- As soon as we start?
- Yes.
What does he mean?
Shall we do some karate?
There will be a marriage officiant.
He will let you know
when to start eliminating.
He will start the ceremony,
then say...
'If there is...'.
If there is anyone
who is against this marriage
please step forward.
As soon as you hear this
you need to eliminate
everyone's name tag.
[All five couples are attacked.]
[Carrying out the name tag
hunting mission.]
[None of the members knew.]
[Mission complete.]
- Bravo!
It's a mission!
- Thank you.
- Good work today.
- The filming is done today!
- What is this?
It's done, we won.
It's the dangerous couple race.
Your final mission is the wedding.
Before you even started it
you've been ousted
by the dangerous couple.
Oh, we filmed the ending first?
You're upset, right?
Right now...
we are going to go back 10 hours
and carry out the mission
to decide your wedding hall.
You will be doing the other missions
and pick a wedding hall.
There is an A hall and a B hall.
You must go to the hall that
Jong Kook and Do Yeon are not in.
When the final wedding
starts again
the couples who choose the hall
that they're not in, will win.
What if we make all of them
come to our hall?
If all the couples meet
in one hall like now
this will happen again.
And the dangerous couple will win.
Should we look at this one first?
Oh, they're mixing up the cards
to tell us where to go.
We'll need to see where they go,
and then decide later.
- To be with them.
- Right!
- Then, should we just leave them?
- Yeah.
[For now, they will keep an eye
on the other missions.]
[A hall is everyone's destination now.]
[Go back 10 hours
and change the future!]
[Earn the chance to change
the destination through other missions!]
Have you watched Running man?
Sure, I've watched at home.
- It isn't your first variety, is it?
- It is.
- It's your first?
- Yes.
I feel like it's my first filming ever.
- Oh, like your first drama?
- Yeah.
- Like when you...
- Yo! You want some disses?
- Yo grasshopper!
- I'm not grasshopper, he is.
- But grasshoppers are green.
- This color is for grasshoppers.
We are Jessi, Yoo ssi.
You're Ji ssi, Kim ssi.
Oh my god.
How many cc is your engine?
- Rhyme?
- He's kind of good.
- He's not good!
- Yesterday, I had 500 cc of cola.
[Stop now...]
- Jessi!
- This is a competition!
- This is a competition.
- We're not a team.
Say something, Yoo Ri.
Where are you going?
Oddly, the weather's always nice
when there are pretty guests.
The weather's really nice today.
Doesn't it smell like cologne?
- From you?
- I put on some cologne.
Suk Jin and I shared some cologne
because there are female guests.
Let's go!
The weather's nice and I feel great!
- Choa!
[Their behavior makes them
look like a young couple.]
It won't be that easy today.
It's not a great situation for us
so it's best not to say anything
like if we switched the cards,
or whatnot.
We need to make them think
that everything is out of order.
We need to match our mouths (words).
[Feeling embarrassed
for no reason.]
I'm feeling great today.
[All of the couples are
feeling great today.]
- We should go.
- Let's go!
[The first mission to the safe hall.]
What is this?
- This is a competition.
- We're not a team.
The first game of the
dangerous couple mission is
the eggs...
of love.
Yes, it's the 'Egg of love.'
The males of each team...
will hold one egg in each hand.
And you can't let it crack.
The females of each team...
must protect their partners
from other couples
or have to attack them
to crack their eggs.
If you crack both eggs, you win.
If both of your eggs crack,
then your team will be ousted.
Can I take my jacket off?
- It's hot.
- Stop trying to start a fight.
- Her tone is like that.
- It's hot, it's hot.
She said it like
'can I take ma jacketoff?'
[Yoo ssi, 100% synced with Jessi.]
She sounds like she's from
the country and not America.
It was like 'can I take ma jacketoff?'
She can't speak very well, so be nice.
Jae Suk!
It's her tone.
[Don't be mistaken, everyone.]
She's actually very nice, everyone.
You sound the same.
While everyone is laughing,
Do Yeon is very anxious.
Why are you anxious?
I should have done that.
- Don't think about that!
- To form a competitive composition.
[Look forward to seeing Do Yeon!]
Everyone take two eggs.
- Wait.
- What?
If you hold it tight in your fist,
it doesn't crack, they say!
Right, it doesn't break.
- Really?
- Try one, for practice.
Try one as practice.
- Sorry.
- Wow!
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
It does crack!
Out of everyone, it's Jessi.
I'm really okay.
I'm going to take
a shower anyway!
I watched Running man very often.
This is a real competition.
Jae Suk, trust me.
That tall woman?
Keep dreaming!
The tall woman?
She's Do Yeon.
You need to grab
one of their arms first.
Oh my, it feels nice.
Jong Kook's weakness is women.
He might just give up an arm.
When they come,
just kick them.
Just keep kicking.
Kick as you walk.
Yeah like that.
[Choa's high kick.]
Don't go!
Come here!
They're easy.
If anything, we need to win
the games.
So what do I do to crack
someone else' egg?
You need to put your fingers inside.
- Ready!
[The egg of love.]
Stay next to me.
[Jessi is confident.]
Oh my god,
Oh my god!
[Yoo Ri comes from behind.]
[An attack without any defense.]
Oh my god!
They're fighting!
[They're throwing themselves!]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo attack Suk Jin.]
Crack it!
[Gary and Ye Ji,
Ha Ha and Choa join in.]
[While Jong Kook and Do Yeon
are the opponents they need to attack.]
[Everyone's fighting except for
Jong Kook and Do Yeon.]
Yoo Ri, don't do this!
[Choa attacks Big Nose.]
She's really tough!
They're really tough!
[Running away is the
best option for survival.]
[Hello, Giraffe.]
[Giraffe doesn't realize
he's being chased.]
Wait!
[Ye Ji breaks one of Kwang Soo's eggs.]
[One shot. One kill.]
- I did it!
I only have one left!
Wait!
Where's Jae Suk?
Ye Ji!
No!
[Being thrown out.]
[The brides' target, Gary.]
[The Piranha Brides Corporation.]
Don't do this!
Help me!
[Surrounded by five women,
charming Gary.]
Jessi, it hurts!
Jessi's beating up somebody.
[They're hiding and watching them.]
- No!
[Yoo Ri vs. Ye Ji.]
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
They're really tough.
They're so tough!
[I have to protect my other egg.]
[Egg-stremely shocked.]
[The sudden attack of the tall woman.]
[Please help me, my legs.]
Ye Ji!
[Right in front of them is Jessi.]
[Caught you!]
One of mine already cracked!
[The hip hop Pacquiao's
deadly punch.]
No!
This is competition!
[I will protect my man!]
[Choa joins them.]
Choa here, here!
It's here, that one cracked already.
[Ye Ji can't help him any more.]
- Do Yeon, Hurry up!
Do Yeon!
- Did it crack?
- Yeah.
If both of your eggs crack,
then your team will be ousted.
- Gary and Ye Ji are ousted.
- Bye, bye!
You did well.
I'm really sorry.
[Out of energy after the first game.]
Ye Ji...
I'm so tired.
I think I underestimated them.
Think of them as men.
- Hey!
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin!
Think about this carefully.
Ha Ha, come.
If we continue like this,
Jong Kook will win.
- Not now!
- It's a meeting!
- It's a discussion.
- To be fair, let's crack one.
What do you mean?
Hey!
- Hey!
- Jong Kook...
It cracked!
[The hip hop Pacquiao's accuracy.]
- One of them cracked!
- Jessi uses her fist!
- It hurts!
- She doesn't understand we...
Jessi, you don't know what's going on?
- We're a team!
[Piggy back.]
We need to get to Jong Kook first.
Help me, any one!
No, you can't go!
- Do I hold on?
- Yeah.
I'm holding her, I'm holding her.
[Gulp.]
Say ah.
[Spit it out!]
[Will he survive?!]
[Abrupt.]
[Finger attack.]
He lost it!
[The egg cracks.]
[Big Nose's humiliation.]
Okay, we got one.
She's a monster.
[You win!]
Jessi!
You, Jessi!
Go away, Jessi!
[Greatest fighter, Jessi.]
- Jessi's the best.
I think they're a team.
What are you going to do?
No, no.
Kwang Soo if you don't win,
you're dead.
You need to eliminate Ha Ha.
Go, go!
Jae Hyuk, go!
I'm not Jae Hyuk.
- I'm not Jae Hyuk.
- Jae Hyuk.
[Choa's target is Jae Suk.]
[Reverse.]
[He escapes from Choa.]
[Thud.]
[Trip, fall...]
[and crack!]
Ha Ha!
I tripped, and fell.
I'm so upset!
I tripped and fell!
I tripped on that.
[It doesn't count.]
I succeeded!
Choa, tell them please.
I tripped and fell.
I wasn't even planning on attacking.
But you fell, so I lightly
pinched your egg.
Oh, he fell and cracked it?
This narrows it down a lot.
[Three teams are left.]
All the strong couples are eliminated.
But Jong Kook is hard.
Let's do it again!
What do you mean again?
Yoo Ri has pale legs
you seem like you don't
go out that much.
You don't exercise much, do you?
- She's quiet.
- I do one!
I breathe.
But...
I have bits of your egg in my nail.
The yolk.
Your spit.
My spit isn't yellow.
It's from the egg.
Ye Ji seems to enjoy
watching today.
- I never got to hear your voice.
- I'm sorry Ye Ji.
I'm Jae Suk, not Jae Hyuk.
She keeps calling me Jae Hyuk.
- Who's Jae Hyuk?
- My manager.
Your manager?
- What are you doing?
- Go Do Yeon!
That's good!
Keep going!
Ji Hyo!
Where?
Where are you?
Ji Hyo, it's here!
[The one who wants to protect vs.
the ones who want to crack.]
- Ji Hyo!
[You must be in the top two]
[to select your wedding hall.]
- Bite him, Ji Hyo!
Kick behind his knees!
[Hip attack.]
Ji Hyo! End it!
[Time to go out.]
- She keeps hitting my bum!
- I'm sorry!
She's chopping my bum!
[Suddenly...]
- Hurry!
- Ji Hyo!
- Now, now.
High kick, high kick!
Would you help me out?
Can I borrow your hoodie?
Let's go together.
I will be back soon.
[Transformation into a dad.]
[Slowly into the war zone.]
[Already close behind.]
Kwang Soo's behind you!
[I'm Back!]
[Attacks Ha Ha.]
Come here, little girl.
[I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.]
Ji Hyo, we need to crack this.
[The tall woman's incredible power.]
[Choa's super kick.]
Ow!
[Thrown out.]
[What just...?]
Oh my, I'm really sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
[Sorry, we couldn't protect you.]
I'm really sorry.
If you feel unjust, hit me.
No, I'm not going to hit you!
[Jong Kook, Do Yeon vs. Ha Ha, Choa.]
- What happened?
- Why is no one attacking him?
Choa, kick his calves!
[One arm, knock down.]
[Do Yeon, mount-position.]
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, we won.
[Game over.]
[Jong Kook, Do Yeon 1st place.]
Wow, it's no fun at all.
You did well.
Let's have round 2!
Round 2!
This store needs to operate, too.
Don't you think?
When she said round two, Yoo Ri said
'Don't you think the store
needs to operate, too?'
[The true meaning
behind the elegant words...]
She doesn't want to do round two.
[Jong Kook, Do Yeon 1st place.
Ha Ha, Choa 2nd place.]
[It's time to choose
their wedding hall.]
Ha Ha and Choa, please come forward.
You must be happy!
We need to be second place at least.
Put it down.
Let us see that!
[Check your invitation first
and choose a wedding hall.]
It depends on luck at this point.
[They're all in the A hall.]
They didn't spend much time changing.
I think we're all the same.
[They need to analyze
Jong Kook and Do Yeon's mentality.]
Should we stay here?
[Changing to B hall.]
If the dangerous couple wins a game
they can check and change
all of the couples' destinations.
- We should have ousted them!
- We shouldn't let them win.
You should have told us that
from the beginning!
[Bickering and blaming]
We'll change them all.
[They need to put
everyone in one location.]
[We will repeat 'the future' again!]
[The opening wedding ceremony
where everyone was ousted.]
[Will this future be
repeated in eight hours?]
[The tall woman
who threw out herself.]
[Open your eyes!]
[Gentleman tries to be quiet.]
[He sits quietly...]
[and the tall woman wakes up.]
Are we leaving now?
- You were sleeping.
- Yes.
Are you tired?
- We started filming really early.
- My, my...
[Will she be able to keep it up?]
[Six hours before
the dangerous wedding.]
- Boxing.
- Is it a boxing ring?
It's a boxing ring.
What is this for?
- It's a ring!
[Couple of trays are a bonus.]
We arrived early.
- Is it a ring?
- It's boxing?
Is this for a game like
'Look this way'?
Why are my fingers hurting?
You put them in Suk Jin's mouth earlier!
[She attacked aggressively
and she forgot already.]
- When she cracked the egg?
- Yes, she's really something.
You know what Jessica H.O is?
Her name is Ho Jessi.
- Her surname is Ho.
- Stop making fun of my name!
- It's her real name?
- Her name is Ho Jae?
- It's Ho Hyun Joo.
- Yes, Ho Yeon Joo.
- It's Hyun Joo!
- Ho Hyun Joo!
- Is there a surname 'Ho'?
- Yes.
There's 'Lady Ho Ho.'
(Korean title for 'Mrs. Pepperpot')
[What are you talking about,
Mister Ha Ha?]
Are there any celebrities
with that name?
Honaldo.
(Cristiano Ronaldo)
I don't know anyone.
Ho Dong.
(Kang Ho Dong)
- His surname is Kang.
- Just call me Jessi.
- So funny!
- Jessi Ho!
- Ye Ji's here.
- Let us hear your voice.
I haven't heard you talk yet!
I talked to her and found out...
- that she never dated anyone.
- Don't lie!
Ye Ji!
You fell for it?
How can he fall for that?
You know near the Han River...
she said she goes there at 1 a.m.
She told me that.
You thought she was hinting at you?
I thought of going
somewhere else with her.
He fell for it again.
- I can meet her there at 1 a.m.
- Stop believing it!
- Was I fooled again?
- Of course!
Compared to these people,
my partner is a gentle lamb.
She's so graceful.
You should know that
she's the best wife material.
But she's single now.
She's pretty and family oriented...
- Don't you have a boyfriend?
- No, she doesn't.
- They say so but...
- I'm sure she has one!
[She must be very sure of it.]
[In a firm tone...]
- I'm sure she has one!
Don't you have one?
[The outspokenness just started.]
Why don't you talk about me?
What did you talk about?
Before we left the last mission site...
she was sleeping.
She didn't talk a lot.
I pretended to sleep.
But he didn't come in.
What did you expect?
No, she was sleeping like a baby.
Where were you heading?
No, I was waiting in the car
so we can talk together.
I didn't want to bother her.
Do Yeon debuted as
Park Jung Ah's doppelganger.
You look like Jung Ah?
I insisted, but I look more like
Koo Bon Seung.
That's right.
She looks like Koo Bon Seung.
I thought she looked familiar.
[She even dances like him.]
She does look like Koo Bon Seung.
What is this?
This game is 'Tell Me Something.'.
Each couple picks a sentence
that you need to hear from your partner.
You will sit inside the ring
facing each other.
Make your partner say the sentence.
The fastest couple
will be the winner.
It's too difficult.
I'm really bad at this.
We play it with our partners?
I'll announce who will go first.
The first couple will be
Jae Suk and Jessi.
Show me, Jessi!
Let's finish it quickly.
- Jessi and... what?
- You'll play with me.
[She didn't understand the game.]
[Jessi is like me.]
- Only Jae Suk needs to know?
- Yes.
He needs to hear it from Jessi.
It's impossible!
- Okay, explain it to me.
- Just respond to what I say.
Please sit on that chair, Jae Suk.
Jessi can sit on the other chair.
Why do we have to start this?
I'm nervous!
Can I practice once?
We can't practice.
It's too difficult.
We can't be the first couple!
- Just do it!
- I'm ruined!
But his explanation...
for example...
[Should I take a nap?]
- Is it one word or a sentence?
- It's a sentence.
That's even harder!
We'll lose.
- Just do it!
- When are you going to start?
We won't lose.
Yoo Jae Suk won't get hit.
I want to explain then!
Would you just start playing the game?
Just follow what they tell us!
- This is a competition!
- It's too difficult for me!
Let's just start, Jessi.
Until when are we going
to do this?
Okay, let's start!
Get ready.
Ready!
[Who are you to judge me?]
- You need to learn how to rap.
[Disappointed.]
- Oh my god!
- You're not supposed to listen!
I don't mean it!
Don't be sad, talk to him!
You need to talk back.
Don't be upset!
You need to learn how to rap
from the beginning!
You know what I'm saying?
- Tell him something.
- You're ugly.
That's not it!
[You're ugly!]
She's driving me crazy.
- She just wants to say it.
- Time out!
Wait, she doesn't understand
the game at all.
[At least she know you're ugly...]
- Correct answer!
Viewers need to know how ugly he is.
I couldn't think of anything.
Can we do it again?
Try responding to what he says.
- Respond to what I say!
- Okay.
I know you're good at rap.
Just listen to this carefully!
Is it going to be different this time?
It's the same sentence...
For example, what do they mean?
Just do it later!
Stand up!
- It's is upsetting!
- They can't do that!
I need to see other people play.
- It's upsetting.
- She's so funny!
Jessi is driving me crazy!
Can we go first?
The next couple is supposed to be
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
Lee Kwang Soo needs to solve it.
[What's the sentence?]
Kwang Soo needs to say...
[You're like an angel.]
I know you're a good rapper.
You should think why I said it.
Then what do I say?
I'm good at it!
I'm far better than you!
Something like that.
Or you could say,
It's not even funny!
- Don't lie to me.
- Oh, I see!
You need to explain those.
You said 'say what I want to say.'
Excuse me, I think Jessi is drunk.
I think you're drunk.
- Where are you hitting me?
- There's nothing there!
What do you mean there's nothing?
Look how she talks!
[Let's just be nice.]
- No one knows about it.
I got mad for a second.
We don't know about it.
Do we need to perform a doping test?
Watch carefully, Jessi.
Ready!
You have five minutes.
[Let me see.]
Sorry for the interruption, but
is Jong Kook a gangster?
- He looks down on us.
- He even has a stick.
What's wrong with you?
He has a medicated patch on his knees.
It's not even Summer yet
but he's wearing shorts.
What are you doing?
And his smile...
It's really unpleasant!
Do you want to see me for a second?
What do you mean?
- You want to see me again?
- Seriously.
[You...]
[You little...]
[Attention!]
What are you doing?
You're a lot older than him.
You're ten years older than him!
The age difference is
not even a year or two!
You shouldn't be intimidated.
- You could even spank him!
- Nothing happened.
Don't let me catch you!
Isn't that too much?
Are you threatening him?
I won't let you catch me.
Then it's okay.
[Ji Hyo needs to hear...]
[You're like an angel.]
Kwang Soo, what type of person I am?
- A cool-headed woman.
- Give her a true answer.
[Actually, you are...]
[I've seen you for five years...]
A bit annoying.
[A bit annoying!]
[Thank you, Giraffe.
I'm only 'a bit' annoying.]
What was that?
[Culture shock!]
[Blank Ji expected to hear she's an angel
but it turns out that she's annoying.]
I guess you just say
what you're really thinking.
Because I don't know the answer.
[She tries new strategy.]
- What's your ideal type?
- Not too tall...
- Not too tall, and pretty...
I can't even say this?
I was just saying my ideal type!
Kwang Soo has been seeing
girls like that in the past.
- A short person.
- A short and glamorous person.
Do you like someone like Park Na Rae?
[A match made in heaven]
She's the shortest celebrity
after Jeon Won Joo.
- Na Rae is cute.
- Yes, she is.
Her height is about 148cm.
- In the sky...
- It's difficult.
I think I know what it is.
[Quick witted Jong Kook
seems to know the answer.]
- There are stars...
- and the moon...
- and the sun.
- the sun and?
[In the sky...
then it should be the answer.]
I want to have you!
[What is he talking about?]
- You want to have her?
It's all because of Jessi!
Everybody is turning into Jessi!
When you want to have a girlfriend,
we say we'll get her a star.
What's my family name?
I mean my real name.
- Chun...
- Yes!
Chunsa (angel) like girl...
I hope for a girl like an angel.
And who is that?
Who's that?
I hope you're a girl like an angel.
I can't do this any longer!
- It hurts to much!
- It sounds good!
- Yes, it sounds nice.
[Only if he didn't say 'I hope.']
What kind of a girl am I?
You're a girl like an angel.
Correct!
- I think it took a long time.
[It took 2 minutes and 51 seconds.]
- It's too difficult!
- You can do it, Jessi!
Jong Kook solved two in no time.
A little like a shaman...
- Where should I go?
- He's really quick.
I wonder how he catches things so quick.
Jessi, do you want to do it now?
No, I'll watch another couple.
- Little later?
- Yes.
The next couple is...
It's Gary and Ye Ji.
Now it's getting interesting.
We'll finally hear Ye Ji's voice.
[He totally fell for her.]
She's attractive.
[You're really random.]
Mister, please give me a lot of it.
You're cute.
How much is this much?
[She's trying to explain the 'really' part.]
You can take all of me.
She smiles a lot.
She's Gary's ideal type.
If a girl smiles at him
he thinks about her at night.
- My mom is trying to give...
- He'll be seeing six of Ye Ji's faces.
Is that so?
- Mom, please give me a lot of...
- Gary is just happy.
- He wants to keep looking at her.
- Do you want something?
- Did you see Gary?
- Don't you want to drink some coffee?
She has a charming voice.
She sounds like Park Jung Ja...
What is the water
and what is the sky?
[Park Jung Ja has a very deep voice.]
One of them will answer
your question.
Where is the land
and where is the sky?
- We were going to do something before.
- It's a kind of sexy voice.
You're really cute!
No!
Oh, it's not me.
This drives me crazy.
Give us seven minutes.
I'm not going to get it.
[They're ready to do it all night.]
But I understand him.
- 'R'ear. (for random)
- He's just enjoying it.
What's with the rear?
[Wake up!]
Gary doesn't care about
winning this game.
The first letter is from the rear.
And then apple...
('r' and 'a' from random)
- What are you doing?
Are you just trying to be cute?
You're supposed to play the game.
No, I can't do this.
- It's too hard.
- You said it before.
- Was that 'really'?
- Yes.
- And then?
- You're really a mess!
[Huh?
What just happened?]
Isn't it too much?
[The tray knows how
variety shows work.]
We'll manually drop the tray.
Until 'really' is correct, right?
My rear is like an apple.
You're really random!
Hit him!
Correct answer!
[He hit him when he got it.]
[I didn't know that was the answer.]
Kwang Soo, that's the answer!
That sounded pretty hard.
You tried to give me
the letters, right?
[It took 2 minutes and 34 seconds.]
By the way, I can tell Gary
fell in love with Ye Ji.
I thought he couldn't get it,
but he actually got it.
I didn't know she kept trying.
The word random is hard to explain.
[You're flexible like a squid.']
- I have ten legs.
What is she doing?
She can do that?
You're freaking awesome!
Freaking awesome?
- I have ten legs.
- You're like a rare creature.
- Why ten legs?
- I have ten legs.
- A squid!
- Right.
You're really...
You're flexible like a squid.
That's right.
- Correct answer.
- I did it?
[It took 1 minute and 4 seconds.]
- Isn't that too easy?
[That's incredible.]
Jong Kook and Do Yeon.
['Oppa, Marry me.']
- Are you ready?
- Yes..
I'm going to give all
my money to my wife.
- Marry me.
- Did she get it?
- It has to be precise.
- Would you marry me?
You need to call me first.
How would you address me?
Honey.
I said it when I met you.
I'm sorry but...
please tie his arms for me.
[He's too competitive.]
He doesn't hit women.
You need to address me...
Oppa, marry me!
Correct!
[It took 2 minutes and 40 seconds.]
- I was giving a hint...
- Look at him!
The next couple is
Suk Jin and Yoo Ri.
Do you want to go first?
- I'll challenge.
- Yes.
- What did she say?
- Do you want to go first or later?
- She said she'll challenge now.
- I thought she said she'll control now.
Ready...
It's up to you.
set, go!
[Who are you to judge me?]
- Jessi.
You're just... not.
- You...
- Get lost!
- It's not that, Jessi.
- Jessi is upset, look at her!
Her face turned red.
You're not supposed to
perform a rap.
You need to start from the
beginning all together!
Do your job properly as an MC!
[Do your job properly as an MC!]
They're just fighting!
Is this a diss battle?
- That's not it.
- Is this a freestyle rap battle?
[The previous teams were
not really good examples.]
- She's driving me crazy!
- You're doing a good job!
Jessi, your rap is wrong
from the first note!
That's not how you do it!
- Freestyle rap?
- He's bad at explaining.
I don't know what the answer is
but I think it's your fault.
I could guess all the answers
easily but yours.
[Jessi and Yoo ssi are about the same.]
- Unpretty Rap Star?
- No, it's not.
- You can't swear!
- I'm sorry.
- Make it easier.
- I see.
I think you're better at dancing!
- Or try singing slow songs.
- I know what it is.
- I don't think you should rap.
- Answer it in English.
[I can give the answer in English?]
- JYP!
[Why did she mention
him all of a sudden?]
I think we should do it later.
Doesn't JYP say stuff like this
on K-pop star?
Just come here, Jessi.
I'm sorry.
Can you give us another chance?
Just once!
- What are you going to do?
- Please give us one more chance!
[Another sentence is given.]
- This time, Jessi will be asking.
- She can explain?
Come on, I'll answer it quickly.
[Are you crazy?]
You can talk.
Am I crazy?
- It hurts.
- How can I explain this?
- Say something.
- This was right.
- It was?
- Okay?
- Don't talk.
- I'm crazy about you.
I'm going to get crazy!
It drives me nuts!
This is upsetting!
[What did I do?]
- How do I explain it?
It's so easy!
You're driving me crazy!
Wow, he's really bad at this!
Try again, Jessi!
- Look at me!
- You!
Yes.
I'm going to wrap it up!
How can you not see it?
What is that?
There's no other way
you can explain this.
- I can't say it.
- Try explaining with words.
- You're supposed to get it.
- You know it.
- Hey...
- No, not that!
You make me go crazy.
Seriously, you...
- I'm fed up with you!
- Keep going!
Say that in Korean.
- He was saying it in Korean!
- He's been speaking in Korean!
Say that in English.
Correct!
[It took 3 minutes and 8 seconds.]
You should have told me that earlier!
Why is only my question in English?
[We didn't think it was a big deal.]
Only if you said if it's in English.
We're the last ones.
Speak for yourself.
You were worse than me.
- What is she saying?
- Just step back, I'm embarrassed.
Let's do it!
Yoo Ri hasn't done this before.
I've never done this, either.
Look at her face!
She's pale!
[You have multiple
personality disorder?]
[She cries all of a sudden.]
[Suddenly happy]
I don't know what to do.
The weather is nice today
and I like you very much.
- I want to keep it touch with you.
- I'd like to go out with you.
[Wake up!]
He means it.
It's time to answer.
She's scary.
[Big nose is dumbfounded by her acting.]
Do you think I'm Yoo Ri?
You're out of your mind!
Oh, she was in that drama!
Oppa, peace!
(A line from 'Kill me, Heal me.')
- What is this?
- It's multiple...
Are you multiple?
- Give me your phone number!
- I can give it to you.
[After a long while...]
- You're...
a person with a case of
multiple personality disorder?
- What?
- That's too long.
- You almost got it.
- You...
have a case of multiple
personality dis... disorder?
- What was that?
- Why?
- Wait.
- The last part is weird.
- He's done.
- Kill Me, Heal Me!
You said you watched
'Kill Me, Heal Me'!
- It's not weird if you say it fast.
- He's too much!
You said you saw the drama!
You watched 'Kill Me, Heal Me'!
You have multiple personality disorder?
- Correct!
[2 minutes 58 seconds passed.]
A case of multiple personality disorder.
- That's what we usually say.
- No, we just say it like this.
I'll have to win over him.
The second winner, please come forward.
Can we only see our wedding invitation?
I think we can win at sports-like games.
I'm still not good at Korean.
Yes, open it like that.
[Checking their own invitation.]
What should we do?
Should we go there?
Jong Kook changed it
for some reason.
Or should we change it?
It's by luck, I guess.
He smiled.
Yes, change it.
Put it down and go back.
[Gary and Ye Ji changed
to 'A' wedding hall.]
- You need to win at least twice.
- That's right.
Then you can tell if
we're all in the same hall.
We know what to do.
We'll open it casually.
We changed to this before.
[Jong Kook didn't change it?]
Wait a minute.
[They're surprised to see
it's still the same.]
- Does it mean he didn't change it?
- No, he didn't.
- It's the same as we changed it.
- Yes, it's the same.
This is confusing!
Why would he do that?
It's really confusing!
He wouldn't have imagined that
we would win the second game again.
Maybe that's why he left...
I think...
- I think we should just stay here.
- Okay.
- Don't you think so?
- Yes.
We'll stay at 'B' hall.
I was confused but
I think you're right.
Just like you said.
[Will their choice change...]
[their miserable future?]
[Three hours before
the dangerous wedding.]
[A specially prepared field
surrounded by cherry blossoms.]
[What is their final mission?]
- What is this?
- This looks like...
- What is it?
Looks like it's related to water.
We need to win this.
A few teams never saw
their own invitations.
- We haven't seen ours.
- Us neither.
Jessi got scolded by
her manager, Jae Hyuk.
- I got scolded.
- She uploaded her picture on her SNS.
Her agency told her
not to upload more pictures.
I was next to her.
And she said
'Jae Suk told me to upload it.'
'Don't do it again!'
'I see!'
'I won't do it again!'
- Gae Suk...
- I'm not Gae Suk.
She calls him Jae Hyuk and Gae Suk.
She's unique!
You're the best!
It was fun!
[Someone gets nervous, every time
Jessi makes everyone laugh.]
Do Yeon, you look tired.
I'm very happy.
Thank you for inviting me
on this show.
Why did she get old all of a sudden?
- Were you sleeping?
- I'm Do Yeon's aunt.
[Do Yeon's grandmother might
come at the end of the game.]
I hear she can impersonate Jessi.
- Try acting like her.
- I heard she's good at it.
- It's funny for others but...
- Don't do it!
- Please, do it!
[It won't be easy to impersonate her.]
I did it at a comedy show.
There's a famous scene.
Everyone's sitting here
and sharing opinions.
Wait a second.
I need to talk.
[This scene is from...]
[Not that long ago,
this made Jessi 'the legend of diss.']
[She becomes Jessi herself.]
[Charismatic!]
Did I do that?
During the past ten years being
a rapper, today is the worst day.
[The way she talks and walks...]
[and even the facial expressions
are the same.]
[Very detailed]
That's my habit!
My lips actually cracked doing this.
Who are you to judge me?
[Her never ending diss!]
Hey, you ugly!
Why are you frowning?
[Kwang Soo becomes an ugly kid.]
I'm the C.E.O.
And the rest of you are wallflowers!
[She's even more like Jessi.]
[It's going to the climax!]
[I'm Jessica D.O.]
[Birth of a legendary impersonator.]
Good job!
I feel so much better!
Now Do Yeon can go home and sleep.
You would regret if you didn't do this.
Jessi, was she good?
No.
Only her tongue is the same as mine.
- Why do you do that?
- It's just my habit.
This is the last game.
The original game is from Australia.
They had an idea from seeing
a drunken husbands at a bar
and his wife was dragging him home.
They made a game and
we changed it a little.
Brides will drag their grooms
by holding their feet.
The couple who pass the finish line
first including their head, is the winner.
Who will win this game
can change the future.
That's possible.
We need to join up with each other!
This is a physical activity
like you wanted to do.
- It's raining, though.
- Stop your nonsense.
Just think about it in your head.
I was worried about
cameras getting wet.
Stop, Suk Jin.
[The race in soapy water.]
I didn't know it was you!
- He took off his glasses.
- He's ugly, isn't he?
Yes, I'm the ugly one from before.
This is a competition!
Don't talk to me!
I don't know you.
We need to win this race.
It's a competition, okay?
- You're ugly!
- He's really ugly!
We need to work with each other!
Joining up doesn't change anything.
You need to win.
Let's try and grab their feet.
He doesn't move!
[It's hard to stand up on the track.]
Wait!
It's so cold!
[Bulls-eye!]
[Jessi wakes him up and
makes him competitive.]
Ready!
[We need to win and
end this race here!]
[We won't let you win!]
Ready!
[The combination of dragging...]
[and moving is important.]
Don't use elbows!
[Three teams run fast.]
[Jong Kook uses his abs.]
- One, two, three!
[Jae Suk moves like he's skiing.]
[Kwang Soo looks like he's upside-down.]
[Every couple moves in a different way.]
Jae Suk keeps using his elbows!
Ye Ji!
[He's so heavy.]
[They moved 15cm in 5 minutes.]
Ye Ji, hold them tight!
Keep moving backward!
[At that moment!]
This is not the time for this!
[She avoids the Tiger couple
but attacks the Giraffe couple.]
What are you doing, Choa!
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon keep moving.]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo move again.]
[While she attacks,
her partner stays at the back.]
You're too heavy!
Ha Ha!
Stop Jong Kook!
[Jessi attacks the Tiger couple.]
[She steals their towel.]
Jessi, it's better for us to keep going!
Please listen to me!
[The two teams are close.]
He's so heavy!
[But she doesn't give up.]
[Yoo Ri is ready to
give up on the father.]
[They're almost at the finish line.]
[The first one to pass will be
the winner of this round.]
[At the same time...]
[Don't let Jong Kook and Do Yeon win!]
[Kwang Soo, please!]
[They passed it almost same time.]
[The result is...]
Lee Kwang Soo wins!
[Kwang Soo's head passed it first.]
[Kwang Goo and Ji Hyo
will get to choose the hall.]
[They stopped Jong Kook
and Do Yeon from winning.]
Good job, Kwang Soo!
It was so hard!
As long as Jong Kook
is not the first winner!
No, we can't let that couple
be the second winner.
- What's our score?
- You said you're good at physical activities.
It's slippery here.
It's supposed to be slippery!
Do well this time!
And you moved like this.
Get ready for the second round!
- This won't do.
- Wait a second!
Try holding here.
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon
have to win this race!]
Stop the red team!
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon
are fast again.]
[Jae Suk and Jessi are
right behind them.]
[The rest three teams are
desperate this time.]
[Yoo Ri is dragging her father home.]
[Jae Suk and Jessi]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon]
No, Ye Ji!
Pull harder!
[The second groups chase them after.]
- It's good!
- Okay!
No, Ye Ji!
Not here!
[Her hidden energy comes out!]
[While the three teams chase...]
[the two teams are still
leading the race.]
[One of the teams will have
a chance to change the location.]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon
are one step ahead.]
[No!]
- Jessi!
[What are you doing?]
[While Jessi falls...]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon win!]
[Jessi loses the chance
by attacking other couples again.]
I can't let him win the race!
I can't let him!
It was very close!
What do you mean you can't let him?
We should have won it, then.
Jong Kook and Do Yeon are
not the first winners.
You can come forward and change
other people card first.
- Please hurry up changing them.
- It's either my team or Jong Kook's.
Now?
Are you sure we can do it here?
Please move back, everyone.
It doesn't really matter for us.
Can't we just watch it?
Let us watch it!
- Watch it on TV.
- It doesn't even matter if we see it!
I always watch it on TV.
I think we were close to winning.
That's why.
I'm already getting ready
for next week's race.
- We're not winning this week.
- We lost already.
- Wait, Jessi.
- It's all because of you!
- A tall woman?
- A tall woman and a big man.
- A tall woman and a muscle man.
- A tall woman.
[They check that Gary and Ye Ji
changed to A hall.]
- It was like this.
- Are you surprised?
- We were right.
- They're changing our invitation.
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo...
I'm sorry but please
step back, everyone.
- If I were him, I would take the risk.
- But it's risky any way.
[Should we have to change
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo's invitation?]
[They leave it as B hall.]
- Hurry up!
- We don't have any choices.
[It's over.]
[Their future will be the same
if it stays like this.]
They're all done.
- Decide quickly!
- It's fifty-fifty.
You can only look at your invitation
and change it.
Cover it well.
[A real battle of wits begins.]
- Hurry up!
- It doesn't matter to us.
[It's B hall...]
[Then...]
[How will Kwang Soo
and Ji Hyo react to this?]
[They would naturally
change it to A hall...]
[but what if Jong Kook
is aiming for that?]
[Will they simply change it to A hall?
Or stay in B hall as Jong Kook planned?]
[Their dangerous wedding
is about to start.]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon
successfully gathered four couples.]
[Will Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo be able to
avoid that future and win this race?]
[It's finally 6 p.m.]
[The dangerous wedding begins!]
[The fortune of the six couples
will be revealed here.]
[Jae Suk and Jessi checks
their wedding invitation.]
- B hall.
- B hall?
Let's go.
- It's on the fourth floor.
- Let's go.
- Will a miracle happen?
- It's okay.
How much do you think it is?
Wedding halls?
I think it's expensive.
Are you going to get married soon?
Call them when you're
going to get married.
[They're in front of B hall.]
Let's go in, Jessi.
[They walk into B hall.]
Did we come here in the morning?
It smells like food here.
[Unfortunately, it's the same place.]
It's all because of you!
It's all because of me?
[The second couple,
Suk Jin and Yoo Ri's turn.]
It's a good thing,
if no one else is there.
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
will decide the result.
This is the battle between
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo...
Jong Kook and Do Yeon now.
- It's all over!
- Oh, no!
I hoped we were the only ones here.
It's over.
If Jong Kook enters here,
that's the end.
No, it depends what Kwang Soo
did after Jong Kook changed them.
[Gary and Ye Ji enter.]
[By chance?]
[Gary and Ye Ji's location was changed
by the dangerous couple.]
Why did you come here?
Hope we're the only ones.
[Ha Ha and Choa hope, too...]
[Hello, friend!]
Look at that.
It's over.
Now, we'll see who comes next.
Kwang Soo or Jong Kook.
That's the result.
If Kwang Soo enters next,
we all lose to Jong Kook.
Because Jong Kook planned it.
[The fifth couple,
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.]
[Their invitation is in front of them.]
We already know what it is.
[Will they avoid the dangerous couple?]
- We'll win if there's no one else.
- Yes.
This makes me nervous.
If we see other people,
then that's the end.
If Jong Kook enters next,
it means Kwang Soo's couple wins.
That's right. It means Kwang Soo's
couple chose A hall.
[Hopes no one is inside...]
I trust your instinct.
You never choose wrong.
You're always lucky for
this kind of stuff.
If Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
come here...
it means they lost
at the battle of wits.
[Everyone will be ousted at the wedding.
Will the future be repeated?]
[In the beginning, Jong Kook and Do Yeon
put everyone in A hall.]
[After the first game...]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon
put everyone in B hall.]
[After the second game,
Gary and Ye Ji moved to A hall!]
[And after the final game...]
[Jong Kook and Do Yeon
put everyone in B hall again.]
[But Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
were to choose after that.]
[Would Ji Hyo have changed
B hall to A hall?]
[This is the moment of destiny.]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo enter...]
[The couples in B hall
are nervous, too.]
[Someone entered!]
[No one's here!]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
chose the empty hall!]
[After the final game...]
[Ji Hyo changed to A hall.]
[Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo win!]
- Seriously? No one's here!
[That means in the B hall,
Jong Kook and Do Yeon entered!]
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo won!
[Kwang Soo isn't here!]
- Kwang Soo won!
- I told you!
- That's incredible.
Ji Hyo's luck worked again?
She's unbelievable!
[The dangerous couple
came so close to victory.]
We won!
[They came to B hall to brag.]
[Disappointed]
[Forward roll ceremony for Jong Kook!]
Being partnered with Ji Hyo
makes you win.
- A man's life is depends on his wife!
[He holds up one million Won.]
Take the money from him!
You're incredible.
Why did you want to change it?
I didn't think much.
I just thought
I'm going to change it.
[Suddenly tired]
Miss Jang.
Can you impersonate Jessi again?
I'm the C.E.O.
And the rest of you are wallflowers!
[Swing her firsts.]
This is exactly like Jessi.
[Icy Jessi]
Can't you please tell me
that I was funny?
- You were funny.
- I'm happy.
Today's winners are
Song Ji Hyo and Lee Kwang Soo!
It's time for the wedding march!
I think they'll divorce
right at the door.
You'll be a battered husband!
They'll divorce for sure!
I think they will divorce, too.
[We hope Song Ji Hyo and Lee Kwang Soo
will live happily ever after!]
Subtitles by DramaFever