[Rival: A person who you are competing
against in the same area.]
[The history of Running Man
is a history of rivals.]
[Finally, today!]
[To make the rankings clear,
there will be a Rival Big Match.]
[Put aside all the past victories.
At the final battle today...]
[The winner takes all!]
[The most intense match
in Running Man history!]
["D" Fitness Center in Mapo-gu, Seoul.]
Today is the Rival Big Match.
You will be having
a match with your rival.
I don't know if
Kim Soo Hyun has any time.
Pardon?
Kim Soo Hyun and Lee Min Ho.
I think they are my rivals.
I don't know if they have time.
I'm Kim Soo Hyun.
[His rival appears!]
[I am Kim Soo Hyun.]
[Grasshopper from a Star.]
I am Lee Min Ho.
[Grasshopper over Flowers.]
What is this!
- Hold on a second...
- Unbelievable.
Your rivals are Kim Soo Hyun
and Lee Min Ho?
- What?
- You're out of your mind!
[Kkuk's rival is Yoo Hyuk.]
[Rival report]
[The beginning of history.]
Why are you here?
[The two prominent
members of Running Man.]
[The number one, Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Mr. Capable Kim Jong Kook]
Let's be fair.
I'll see you later.
[They can't avoid fate.]
[From being a spy to a leader,
he's always at the center.]
[Mr. Capable, who always overcomes
a situation with his strength.]
[From name tag elimination to Ddakji
matches, they've faced it all.]
[They're ending this rivalry today!]
Why are you here?
Why are your rivals
Soo Hyun and Min Ho?
He can't do anything
besides use his strength.
- What did you say?
You're unbelievable!
[Anyone can tell that they're rivals.]
Honestly...
- What are we doing?
- What is it?
Putting aside your age,
height, and weight
it will be based only on victory.
The winner becomes
the big brother.
And the loser becomes
the younger brother.
I don't really want to
call him "Big Brother".
He has nothing to lose.
I'm older anyway.
But I don't want to
call you "Big Brother".
I'm older anyway, but you
don't want to call me "Big Brother"?
I have to spend an
entire day calling you that!
I think this is a little too much!
Choose a game that you're
confident in playing.
I can't compete with him in strength,
what are you talking about?
Why didn't you just tell me
to call him younger brother?
What do you mean leg presses?
Let's see who can
stand longer on a gym ball.
My goodness.
Are we in the circus?
[Gym ball palm slap game.]
Let's do that.
Let's play one round.
- Just one round?
- Of course.
Let's try it out first.
Wait, this isn't easy...
You have to take your feet off.
[Huh?
Did he lose already?]
This is it!
It's done.
He already treats me
like a big brother.
[Kkuk is a man of action?]
Go on it.
[Gym ball palm slap game.]
[Start]
[Frustrating...]
[Ugh]
[I can't stand the sight of him!]
[You hit me?]
[Why not?]
[They're also rivals
for being childish, too.]
I can't stand him!
[Rival report]
[The records of physical fights.]
[Their matches were always intense!]
[From name tag elimination
to mud fights.]
You'll pay for this!
[They always eliminated, got eliminated,
chased and were chased.]
[Who will be the winner
of this rival match?]
Or let's do this.
You put this near the head...
The person who drinks it in
a shorter amount of time wins.
- If you spit it out, you're out.
- Isn't that obvious?
- Put your legs here.
- Okay.
- Put your feet here.
- Okay, okay.
I've never drank water
like this before...
- I don't know either.
- I'm just doing it but...
is this even possible?
- I'll take a look first.
- Since I suggested it.
Let's start.
- We'll be starting.
- Yes.
[The vibrating belt machine.]
[Vibration]
[It's intense as soon as it starts.]
[What is this?]
[Warning: ugly.]
[You might be in trouble if you
get caught by the health trainer.]
[He drank it all!]
That hurts!
That really hurts!
My neck...
Just try it.
My neck hurts.
[An important match that
will determine their ranking.]
Ready, set.
[Vibration]
[He spit some out!]
[Where am I...
and who am I?]
You spit some out!
[I can't do this!]
[The hardest workout
is the belt machine.]
[Yoo Jae Suk won!]
I feel so good!
- Why did you make me laugh!
- What?
You can't make me laugh!
I feel so good seeing him
spit the water out.
According to the match, Yoo Jae Suk
will be on the Big Brother team.
And Kim Jong Kook is on
the Younger Brother team.
Now you have to
call me "Big Brother."
You must call him that,
and use honorifics.
And you need to
call him younger brother.
It's my first time calling
him "Big Brother"
in the ten years I've known him.
- It's very humiliating.
- Let's go, muscle man.
[Silent]
Answer me!
Say something.
Start talking!
Say "Big Brother"!
I need some time to think.
Let's go Jong Kook!
Yes, Big Brother.
[He's looking elsewhere.]
- I did it!
- All right, follow me.
[Big Brother team - Yoo Jae Suk.
Younger Brother team - Kim Jong Kook.]
[They're headed where
the other teammates are!]
[He's getting in the back?]
I'm sorry, but you
have to sit beside me.
- What do you mean?
- Why did you sit in the back?
I will sit wherever I want to.
[He's the younger brother
and a driver?]
Can't I just sit where I want?
[It seems like it's
going to be a long day...]
["J" Internet Cafe in Mapo-gu, Seoul.]
[Someone gets out of the car.]
[Who is this man?]
[The legendary pro-gamer,
Lim Yo Hwan.]
[Rival report]
[The Emperor of Terran, Lim Yo Han.]
[The only pro-gamer that was allowed
to use "The Emperor" as his nickname.]
The winner is Lim Yo Han!
[He won many trophies with
his amazing strategy.]
[Annual income: 200 million,
The Emperor of Terran, Lim Yo Han.]
[Lim Yo Han signed up for a
contract for 780 million for 3 years.]
[With his skills
and handsomeness]
[he takes over]
[variety shows and ads.]
[The living legend of Korea e-sport,
Lim Yo Han.]
[There's only one person
who can fight against him.]
[A hand that never stops moving.]
[He doesn't lose focus.]
[Who's the rival that will
be fighting with him?]
Why are you working so hard?
[It's Hong Jin Ho!]
I knew it was him.
We're not rivals anymore.
[Rival report]
[The Storm Zerg, Hong Jin Ho.]
[The outset of constant
attacking Zerg, Hong Jin Ho]
[He's always given his rival Lim Yo Han
first place at every important match.]
[His second place jinx
continued on Running Man.]
[Will he be able to
get out of it today?]
[Kkuk and Jae Suk came
to meet the second group of rivals.]
- Who's that?
- Jae Suk's here.
[Huh?]
- Hi, Jin Ho.
- Hello.
[Hong Jin Ho and
Lim Yo Han are together?]
This is the real rival match.
They're actual rivals.
Jin Ho told me that...
he's won before,
but he won small games...
And he always lost the
big games to Yo Han.
Let's just put an end to this today.
[Lim Yo Han vs. Hong Jin Ho.]
[Lim Jin War,
The story that will never end.]
[Their 15 years of rivalry
started with "StarCraft."]
[They will put an end to this
with "StarCraft" today!]
[The legendary rivalry,
Lim Yo Han vs. Hong Jin Ho.]
[Who will be the Big Brother?]
There's a lot of tension.
[The start screen that everyone
recognizes pops up.]
- Can I sit comfortably?
- Yes.
Both of them changed
as soon as it started.
The Emperor of Terran
and forever second place.
He's the Storm Zerg.
To everyone who is
a fan of pro-gaming.
To everyone who loves Hong Ji Ho and
Lim Yo Han, this is an intense moment.
This is nerve-wracking.
[With the countdown]
[the two players go back in time.]
[Lim Jin War, start.]
We aren't professionals, so our
commentaries are insufficient.
Aside from not being professionals,
Jong Kook has never played this game.
I've tried twice.
We can still... explain.
- The robot is gnawing.
- What are you saying?
He's digging up something.
It's digging resources.
[Lim Yo Hwan controls Terran units.]
Look at them.
Their fingers move so fast!
Even if you don't know the rules,
you can tell that their fingers are fast.
Wow, that's really fast.
You need to mine lots of minerals.
You can build a lot of things
with those resources.
When they finish building
their battle station
you can attack the opponent's station.
Then, your enemy will be "pwned"!
- Did you just say "pwned"?
- "Pwned", "Pwnage"!
- Don't use that word.
- If you grind them, you win.
- So it's a grinding game.
- Yes.
- They're very fast.
- They aren't saying anything.
They are incredible.
[His screen turned off!]
- What happened?
- I pressed the wrong button.
It's been a while.
He makes a lot of small mistakes.
I was surprised that
his screen turned off.
- It started!
- They're at war?
Zerg sent a few troops over.
- Oh, look at that!
- There's a moth looking thing.
Moth... you don't know
anything about the game!
Don't comment,
just bring water or something!
[The moths are moving in perfect order
with Hong Jin Ho's command.]
We're very sorry to everyone
who enjoys this game.
We don't really know
this game too well.
[Hong Jin Ho attacked
Lim Yo Han's camp with moths.]
They're entering his camp.
- That's what's happening?
- Yes.
Terran is also attacking.
- Really?
- Yes.
Terran sent his troops.
They're really cute,
they're toddling.
Don't say things like that...
- Why?
- What do you mean toddling?
They are cute.
[Name: Marine]
Zerg is sending attacks consistently.
Terran is defending, calmly.
Zerg is blocking.
He came through.
Terran got in.
[The Emperor's eyes.]
- They're fighting!
- The bugs have joined in.
There is another kind of bug!
- Just stay quiet.
- A bug with a tail!
- Their attack...
- What's that?
- He turned into an egg!
- Just be quiet!
- What do you mean an egg?
- He turned into one!
He's here!
Terran is here.
- He's attacking.
- Terran brought a spaceship.
They keep sending their troops to battles
[They aren't losing their focus.]
This is insane, it's so much fun.
Some things that look like
crabs are flying around.
They're not crabs!
[This time he laughed.]
- They don't even have wings.
- How can you call them crabs?
- How can they fly?
- He's here!
[The match continues.]
Look, it's amazing!
It looks like Zerg is on defense.
There's something
coming out of the eggs.
[Laugh]
[Unbelievable!]
You really don't know anything!
A creature's coming
out of the eggs.
Terran is attacking full-scale.
[Hong Jin Ho surrendered!]
[He seemed calm,
but now he's celebrating.]
[2015 Lim Jin War,
Lim Yo Han's victory.]
Why did you end it
so suddenly, Jin Ho?
It's pretty familiar.
I guess you had the
same situation before.
It happened a lot before.
So Lim Yo Han will be on
the Big Brother team.
And Hong Jin Ho will be on
the Younger Brother team.
Let's go.
I feel like the day
is already over...
This is a good start to the day!
[Big Brother team - Lim Yo Han.
Younger Brother team - Hong Jin Ho.]
[They're on the way
to meet the third group of rivals.]
[Looks around]
Where are they?
Is Yo Han's car in front or behind?
- He's right there.
- Oh, that?
Wake up...
There's an aftereffect
when I lose a game...
[I have to call
my rival big brother...]
[They arrive at a cozy looking cafe.]
Where are we?
Is it an Audrey Hepburn themed cafe?
They have yummy things.
[The hottest pink girl, EXID's Hani.]
[The third rival big match:
Hani vs. Ji Hyo.]
[Rival report]
Does it even make sense?
- How can she sleep over there?
- She's amazing!
[The expert of sleeping
and napping, Ji Hyo.]
[She changed the paradigm of sleep.]
[The Goddess of sleep, Hani.]
[How will their rankings clear up?]
- What is this?
- We were about to start our game.
Younger Brother!
Please move the jackets over there.
The younger ones are
supposed to do these things.
You need to win, Ji Hyo.
This is just a reverse hierarchy game.
Younger Brother!
Go get a menu.
[Upsetting]
Hurry up!
Go with him, why are you sitting?
I think one person can get a menu.
I'll go get the food later...
Jin Ho gets Yo Han's!
You get mine!
[They have to run errands
as soon as they lose.]
We'll start the match
between Hani and Ji Hyo.
What is this?
It's a pitch-pot game.
Whoever gets it in will win.
Ready, set.
[Ji Hyo goes first.]
[Her first try was so close.]
Don't throw it towards the floor.
What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with you?
- It keeps going down.
Wear comfortable pants.
Don't throw it towards the floor.
[What is she doing?]
Grab the front.
Take care of yourself!
[Throw]
That was better.
Grab where?
It's not like he knows
about this game.
The back?
Oh, the front.
This is really hard, right?
[Is it really hard?]
Please throw it more carefully.
Carefully.
Throw it carefully.
[I want to try, once more.]
Ready, set.
[Kick]
No more!
[Upset]
We need to show them who's boss.
He nags so much.
Darn it.
[Her remark is like
a middle aged man.]
[Song Ji Hyo won.]
Wow!
Why are you guys
happier than Ji Hyo?
Because it's Ji Hyo.
She's a member of Running Man.
Ji Hyo's on the Big Brother team.
[Hani's on the
Younger Brother team.]
[Big Brother team - Song Ji Hyo.
Younger Brother team - Hani.]
[Other rivals are waiting
at SBS in Sangam.]
[Super Junior's leader, Lee Teuk.]
Hello.
I'm so tired.
[Super Junior's Kim Hee Chul.]
Hello, it's been a long time.
[The big match
Lee Teuk vs. Kim Hee Chul.]
There's a Rival Big Match today.
[The two eldest in the group
who lead Super Junior.]
[However, they're very
different people.]
[Hot-blooded Hee Chul vs.]
[serious leader, Lee Teuk.]
[They're so different.
What will their rankings be?]
I'd rather be the younger brother
because he holds grudges.
He'll never call me Big Brother.
We're not rivals
but we're so different.
To be honest, we're not rivals...
We just don't click.
We're polar opposites.
Even our clothes...
he's so plain and he loves white.
We used to live together
a long time ago.
I love the color red
so my side of the room was red.
And his side of the room was white.
And to be honest...
it's my first time being
on TV with him.
[It's their first time being on TV
without the other members.]
It's so awkward!
Is this "Passing Journal"?
Ten years, and this is the first!
[Thankfully,
the other members arrive.]
Hello!
[Noisy Hee Chul.]
[Lee Teuk takes is a step back.]
Hee Chul and I are the same age.
Teuk isn't older?
We're the same age.
Our birthdays are nine days apart.
Oh, really?
They're really rivals.
No, we just don't click.
What game will they be doing?
I suggested a game.
Because we know a lot of people
from various events
we can text a female celebrity,
and whoever calls first wins.
- It's simple.
- Single round match!
I was going to text Hani,
but she's here.
You have to choose someone
you both are close with.
Yoona?
Yoona.
- Let's go with Yoona.
- Okay, Yoona!
- Ready...
- Press send at the same time.
I'm very fast at typing.
This is Yoona's number, right?
- Yeah.
- It's been a while since you called?
Let me just put an emoticon.
[That's not allowed.]
You can't use an "item."
It's supposed to be sincere.
No emoticons?
One, two, three.
[The text message has been sent.]
We'll wait.
This makes us anticipate.
Yoona has to see this...
If she doesn't, there's no point.
Yoona is always on her phone, though.
Hello?
[Hello?]
[Did he get a call already?]
Oh, never mind...
- His random comic sketch.
- We don't click!
[Why?
This is so funny.]
[Just then!]
No way!
Just blur out the number.
[He really got a call from Yoona.]
Yoona!
[Jealous]
- She didn't read mine...
- Congratulations, Yoona!
Pardon?
Hello?
What is this?
You must have got a text
from Lee Teuk and Hee Chul.
[Upset]
You saw both of them, right?
Between the two...
do you know who I am?
- She knows.
- Who are you?
You have to introduce yourself!
I was in a hurry.
I am Yoo Jae Suk.
Hello!
Yoona!
You probably got a
text from both people.
- Yes.
- Why did you call Hee Chul first?
I love you, Yoona.
Please tell us honestly.
I got Hee Chul's text first, so I called.
And then I got Teuk's text.
- She's kind.
- I thought "is this for TV?"
So you knew it was for TV,
and you still called Hee Chul first!
[Yoona, I'll be good...]
Hello?
Teuk!
You wanted me to call?
She's speaking formally!
Hello, I'm Yoo Jae Suk,
who was listening to your conversation.
Yes, hello.
I only heard a little,
but you don't seem very close.
They don't seem close.
Here, you can talk to Teuk.
Yoona's in big trouble.
Teuk holds grudges.
- Teuk!
- Yes, Yoona.
You're already upset!
[Bingo]
[Yoona,who knows he gets mad easily,
is one of Teuk's best friends.]
Was I obvious, Yoona?
I'll call you later, love you!
[Yoona, thank you and I love you too.]
So Hee Chul's on
the Big Brother team.
And Lee Teuk is on the other team.
Jong Kook!
[Big Brother team - Kim Hee Chul.
Younger Brother team - Lee Teuk.]
[Gary and Ha Ha were tired of waiting
and start the mission themselves.]
We can say "follow me" and see
how many kids gather around.
They'll obviously go to you.
You're Haroro.
It's been so long since Haroro.
But these guys were probably
like three back then, so they know.
Please bring glasses.
Do you have the
Dragon Ball costume?
[Who will the kids pick?]
Let's play tag, I'm going to run away!
See if you can catch my butt!
Catch me if you can!
Guys, come here!
It's so fun!
I'll give you something yummy.
Let's play choo choo train.
Choo, choo, train.
[The kids are already
in love with Haroro.]
Catch me if you can!
He has a kid at home!
Who wants to ride the slide?
Let's go!
[I'll fail at this rate...
I need a solution...]
Let's go!
I'll buy you
black bean noodles later.
[Black bean noodles?]
[This is working?]
Two, four, six... I'll order 30 dishes.
- Please deliver it to the kindergarten.
- Will 30 be enough?
- Black noodles and sweet and sour pork.
- 500 pizza...
I'm going to give them.
Children always pick
the last thing they hear.
You don't know how it will be
until you open the jar.
Maybe your jar will be opened.
(Pun: you'll be upset.)
I see, I see.
[Easy and composed]
- Children, come to me!
- Children, come and eat black noodles!
Come to me!
[A crowd of children
go toward Mr. Black Noodle.]
In front of Ha Ha,
there are eight children.
In front of Gary, there are 15 children.
[Gary won!]
Yeah!
- Black bean noodles!
- How come?
[As he promised to the little angels,
the food was delivered!]
[Thank you so much for
your cooperation.]
Your team members are decided.
There's something you must do,
when the team is decided.
Each of you bow to your own big brother.
Come over here.
He's older than me,
but this is irritating.
One by one!
Say "Big Brother" when you bow.
Yes, Big Brother!
Good!
- I've never seen this before!
- Take care.
It's funny, Jae Suk is older any way,
but he seems so happy.
It's been a while since I've seen
him smiling so brightly.
I'm going to do it quickly.
[It's Jin Ho's turn.]
Do it slowly.
Big Brother!
It seems he doesn't really mind.
It looks natural.
Teuk's face turned red!
Teuk must really hate to do that.
Big Brother!
Listen to what I say, Brother!
- Jong Kook!
- It's fine!
It's fine.
There's something different
for Gary and Ha Ha.
- They're real rivals.
- What if I had to bow!
There's a war of nerves between them.
Attention, when you bow to elders.
Look!
Gary's so serious.
In front of elders, you need to
take off your hat.
[This is upsetting!]
- Call him Big Brother.
- Big Brother!
[Yes, my dear brother.]
[All the members are appointed.]
It's heartwarming.
[Big Brothers are in red.]
[Younger Brothers are in blue.]
[The real battle begins now!]
[Ranking positions didn't end yet!]
[A boiling ranking war
between the rivals!]
[It begins now!]
[Yeouido Hangang Park]
[All the members are arriving together.]
- What's that?
- I wonder what's that for.
It's huge!
Isn't that a board for the game of yut?
It's game of yut!
You're right,
is this a human version?
There are yut sticks over here.
- We cast them on the stage?
- We need to cast inside the circle?
Big Brothers!
I'm so glad you're still in good shape.
- Don't just say it, like you mean it.
- Yes, Big Brother!
- Long life to you.
- You, two, bow.
Yes.
[Stiff]
Younger Brother team
might like this mission.
Maybe it's favorable for us.
The winner of this game
will become Big Brother team.
Plus, lunch will be treated
by Younger Brother team.
[Enthusiastic]
We need to win this.
Don't lose this game!
Of course!
What game is this?
You're looking at the huge yut board.
It's yut name tag game.
You can play the game of yut.
Maybe we'll be ousted
by name tag elimination.
One player will cast yut.
The rest will be the tokens.
You can play name tag game when
you meet each other on the same station.
Isn't this too disadvantageous for us?
Of course, Jong Kook
will be the first token.
He's the first token!
I'll be the token no matter what.
Of course, of course.
Maximum three tokens
can be on the same station.
Then, when we're three,
we can rip Jong Kook's name tag.
Three to one...
Is that enough?
[A strategy game on the yut board]
[Will they be able to defeat
the impregnable Jong Kook?]
[Yut Name Tag Game, start!]
- Fight!
- Cast it, Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo and Hani will cast yut sticks.]
- It's yut!
- It's gae. (2 steps)
- It's geol! (3 steps)
- No, it's gae.
Gae means Gary.
Too easy to be chased.
This is getting interesting!
Gae, gae, gae, gae!
Please!
[Let's get Gary!]
Hani, pick it up and throw it down!
It's "mo!"
(advance 5 steps & extra cast)
One more throw!
Throw it higher!
You're doing a very good job!
- Good!
- It's "gae!"
Let's catch Gary!
Why?
[He'll get caught from the beginning.]
Why did you take off your jacket?
[In order to catch you!]
I'll take your jacket.
Why did you take off your jacket?
[Relaxed]
This is fun!
- Gary!
- Don't do this to me!
[There's no one to help
and nowhere to go!]
Look at him!
He's too strong!
[I feel sorry...]
Gary
[When they lose their name tag,
they have to go back to the start line.]
[Rip]
[Mr. Capable wins.]
Kim Jong Kook!
- Cast again?
- Yes, we caught them.
- We didn't use the "mo" yet.
- Then you should just go.
Please give Gary's name tag back,
he needs it.
- Good!
- Let's take off jackets!
Let's put another token with "gae"
then put another for "mo."
- Advance five steps!
- We need "geol." (3 steps)
- Cast it, Ji Hyo!
- If you cast gae, it's over!
I'll throw it now!
What if she throws "gae"?
Hope she doesn't throw gae...
It's do! (one step)
You can finish it
with "reverse do." (one step backward)
Hope we'll get reverse do next time!
"Geol" is good, too.
[It's Hani's turn again.]
Hani, anything is fine!
- What is it?
- It's geol.
Geol!
(3 steps)
[Should we move the two
and make three move together?]
[Or should Lee Teuk move alone?]
(He can take the shortest course.)
[They choose to let Lee Teuk advance,
so he can finish it soon.]
[Big Brother team is feeling urgent.]
I'll cast!
Why did she do that?
Its' gae!
[Should a new token fight
with Jong Kook and Ha Ha?]
We need to go.
We have no choice,
I need to go.
Hani, cast it.
Ji Hyo didn't get more than gae so far.
Anything's fine!
Geol!
[She threw another geol.]
Kwang Soo, catch Suk Jin!
If I have no choice,
I'd like to fight with Hong Jin Ho!
I fought with Kwang Soo so many times.
That's right!
It's not fun any more!
I'm worried if Ji Ho might
feel pity on Suk Jin.
[You might be hurt, if
you look down on me.]
Jin Ho, their team is on a cliff.
[Suk Jin vs. Jin Ho]
Will Hong Jin Ho win second place?
Suk Jin, you need to regain your honor!
- You have nowhere to go.
- It's suspenseless.
[Jump]
[A pro-gamer's suspenseful jump!]
What was he doing?
[They grabbed each other's
name tags at the same time!]
[And Big-nosed Brother eliminated
Jin Ho's name tag first!]
[Hong Jin Ho was ousted so easily...]
- Jin Ho!
- You were this bad?
[Anyway, Big-nosed Brother
defended his station.]
Are you okay?
If we get geol, should we combine them?
- We should.
Geol!
If they have do, try eliminating
one of their name tags!
Why do I have to carry you?
- Anything!
- Yes!
Get do!
Cast it higher, Hani!
You're doing a good job.
Just ignore him!
- Gae!
- Good job!
Let's combine!
- Isn't he ousted?
- No, he can go again.
[They already have Kim Jong Kook.]
[Why do they all want to be together?]
He's hurt.
[Big Brother team needs to
run away from Younger Brother team.]
- What is it?
- It's gae.
[They run away.]
Get them next time!
Gae!
- Is that yut? (4 steps & extra cast)
- It's geol!
Geol!
[No way...]
Do, gae, geol!
(We can get them!)
[I can't believe it!]
[The big brothers are caught by
the scary younger brothers.]
This drives me crazy.
[The worst case possible
actually happened.]
How could we be so unlucky?
[Sorry!]
Why don't you wear your jackets?
Why don't we attack Jae Suk together?
You guys attack one of them first.
[They're so confident.]
- We need to stick together!
- Good, good!
- Just grab one of them.
- Don't waste your time!
[Jae Suk is busy protecting
Big-nose and himself.]
They're doing well!
[It's tighter than we thought!]
Hong Jin Ho,
come over here!
[He's planning to get
rid of the weakest.]
Is Hong Jin Ho the queen
who needs protection?
Rip it, Jin Ho!
Quickly!
[While Ha Ha is holding Jae Suk]
[Jin Ho's attack succeeded!]
[Rip]
[What a perfect revenge!]
[He must be really happy...]
[Big Brother team goes back to zero.]
Anything is good!
[At that moment, Hani cast mo.]
(five steps and extra cast)
She must be the god of yut!
Cast it one more time!
- We have mo and...
- She's good.
Come out, Kwang Soo!
- How many steps?
- Two!
[The tokens can be
combined up to three.]
You can go two steps first.
Then, go five more steps for mo.
I have to take the longer course.
That's better than getting caught.
Let's go!
Do, gae, geol...
[Trip]
[The icon of misfortune...]
Is there any spot that's not flat?
- That's too cheesy!
- I'm tired of seeing you fall.
I fell for real!
It hurts!
- I'll cast!
- I'm bleeding!
I'm sick and tired of it, Kwang Soo!
[What a tough journey
to become an old brother!]
[While all Younger Brother team
members are on the board]
[Kwang Soo and Lee Teuk
are close to the finish.]
What is it?
It's geol.
Get in, catch them!
What's going on?
No, they can't.
Teuk, you can go out this turn.
Anything's fine!
Reverse do?
[Gae]
Finish!
[Lee Teuk finishes it first.]
Mo, do!
Ji Hyo, please get mo and do!
- Mo and do!
- It's not going to be easy.
[Gae, again!]
[Slowly, they move two steps.]
[Mo that big brothers wish for
are allowed to younger brothers.]
[Yut expert Hani]
We can't do anything.
We can't beat them.
There's no way.
[And they even get
the geol that they want.]
Use geol first to take the shortcut
and exit with mo.
We can do that!
Wait, then Kwang Soo
will be left alone.
[They're worried about Kwang Soo
since he's so clumsy.]
You should exit.
You can use mo (5 steps), and exit.
You'll let him use mo?
[He only need one step.]
What are you thinking?
It's mo.
Why would you waste it?
If we can catch Kwang Soo, we might win.
[Big Brother team hopes
Kwang Soo will be left alone.]
To catch Kwang Soo,
they need yut (four steps).
So far, Ji Hyo never cast
more than two steps!
Let's get out first.
We'll give you a chance, Kwang Soo!
- We'll exit.
- Time-out!
They exited.
[If they can't catch Kwang Soo now,
the game is over.]
Ji Hyo, there's only one way.
We can only live if you cast yut,
otherwise, it's over.
[Pressure]
Unless it's reverse do,
I'll exit next time.
If we get yut, we can attack him.
- Ji Hyo, please throw yut!
- I'll cast now!
Please, please, please!
[Yut]
[Wow!]
[We caught Kwang Soo!]
She just put them down.
Even if you put them down,
it's hard to get yut.
Try and see if it happens.
[Demonstration]
See?
You can't get it like that.
[Giraffe is caught one step
away from the finish.]
I'm sorry that we are three,
but Kwang Soo is tall and strong.
- We're in trouble.
- He can do it.
Kwang Soo, it's okay even if you lose.
Why does it only happen to me?
[His first target is Hee Chul.]
Good, Kwang Soo!
Great!
[Kwang Soo's having a close game
with three opponents.]
- He's good!
- He might win!
Give up, Kwang Soo!
[Run[
[He was going to attack Hee Chul,
but he failed.]
Thank you for the hard work,
Younger Brother.
[I should have gotten out
when there was a chance.]
[Kwang Soo's third round]
- Nice, it's do!
- You can't change it now!
It's fine.
Mo!
[Thanks to God of Yut, Hani,
they're on the right track.]
One more cast!
It'll be perfect if we get gae.
Geol!
- You have to go around.
- It could have been short.
It's okay, you can go around.
[Again, he's taking the detour.]
Do, gae...
If he doesn't get caught here,
it'll be fine.
[Thanks to Hani,
he's advancing pretty fast.]
Maybe getting do is better.
Do!
[They can take the shortcut
and make a turn.]
[Finally, there's a hope
for Big Brother team.]
I hope we get yut!
Hani, I need to exit!
It's not that easy to get yut.
- What is it?
- Gae! (two steps)
That's nice!
I'm almost there!
- I'm getting nervous.
- This is more exciting than I thought!
Gae is okay.
It's gae.
[It's so close!]
[From now on, just one movement
will decide the winner.]
This is so much fun!
- Gae!
- Gae?
If they get more than three steps,
Younger Brothers team will win.
If they get two steps,
we will fight each other.
Here we go!
Please!
[Don't throw gae!]
Gae, gae, gae!
[Yut is thrown!]
That's right!
Gae!
[No way, is that real?]
[Is that an infinite loop
name tag game?]
[One more stick is flipped!]
[It's geol!]
[Younger Brother team wins!]
[We're going to be big brothers now!]
[Younger Brothers team wins the
game of yut by a whisker.]
[Oh, no...]
[We couldn't have been treated
as big brothers properly yet.]
It's amazing.
How come she throws mo so often?
- She's incredible.
- We could've won.
We almost won.
- As I said before...
- We're the big brothers now?
As soon as the red team says
big brother, you will be.
Let's hurry up.
[Most of them are actually younger.]
This is ridiculous.
We'll do it together.
- One, two, three!
- Big Brother!
- Square face, come over here.
- What did you say?
- Square face.
I got cut!
Making fun of appearances
isn't the right thing to do!
[Do you want to feel
how sharp my bones are?]
I'll hit you with my face.
I'm sorry, Big Brother.
I was too upset.
I'm so sorry.
[SBS Broadcasting Hall,
Deungchon-dong, Seoul]
[The final site for the battle!]
[The place where we will
make rankings clear!]
[A special stage, the octagonal ring!]
[The Rival Big Match]
Hello, I'm Lee Byung Jin, the caster
for Running Man Rival Big Match.
Hello, I'm Game Caster Jeon Young Jun!
From now on, we'll start the
final mission of the Rival Big Match.
Please enter the ring!
The players are entering now.
What?
It's an octagon!
[Amazed]
Hello, I'm the Yoo Jae Suk
of the game world, Jeon Young Jun.
What brings you here?
[An octagon ring and casters?]
[Everyone's surprised to see
the blockbuster level game setting.]
Are we going to
play pro-wrestling?
You know what the octagon is for.
- It's a battle!
- That's right!
Cutthroat competitions waiting for you.
I hoped it was an actual
cutthroat competition.
[What's wrong with him?]
It seems they're ready
for the game already.
Is there any way we can stop him?
Seriously.
The Rival Big Match.
What will happen in this octagon?
We will reveal them now.
You can check them on the screen!
Six matches will be held.
They're on the screen.
First, Kim Hee Chul and Lee Teuk
will play picking out 33 cards.
Forehead Basketball,
for Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook.
The third round will be Thumb Long Jump
for Gary and Ha Ha.
The fourth round, Ji Suk Jin and Lee
Kwang Soo betrayal rock-paper-scissors.
The fifth round is amazing.
Song Ji Hyo and Hani, Sweet Dreams.
The first one who falls asleep wins.
[The Rival Big Match]
The sixth round,
Lim Yo Hwan and Hong Jin Ho.
[The first-ever sleeping game
on a variety show!]
Finally, you picked something
Ji Hyo's really good at.
- Hani, too, falls asleep easily.
- How can I sleep when they record?
I've cast all sorts of matches
but I've never cast sleeping before.
Are you going to cast, too?
We've discussed about that round
with the production crew.
We can't make it for
winning two out of three.
You can't wake up someone sleeping
and make them sleep again.
- How many hours did you sleep?
- Last night... two hours.
- Two hours?
- How about you?
I think she only slept for 15 hours.
She hasn't started her hibernation, yet.
Ji Hyo can sleep 23 hours a day.
The sixth round is for Lim Yo Hwan
and Hong Jin Ho, Arcade Tetris.
As a game caster, I'm telling you.
In Lim Jin War, Lim Yo Hwan always wins.
Think about betting for Lim Yo Hwan.
He's strong on practice.
- Have you played Tetris?
- Not really.
But, I can win over him!
I can win this.
Trust me.
[I'm going to overcome
the curse of Lim Jin War today!]
The important thing is
that you can bet your
points for each round.
The points that you can use
for all the rounds are 250.
You can use all the points
for the first round, too.
- All in?
- We'll do that for Sweet Dreams.
Let's use 240.
[You're the real Ace!]
How much points you've used
is kept secret.
When all the rounds end
we'll reveal how you divided
your points at that time.
Let's start the game now!
We'll start the first round
of the Rival Big Match!
[The Rival Big Match, start!]
[In the octagon, only my
rival and I are standing!]
[I bet everything on this battle!]
[You will gain all!
Or lose all!]
[Who will laugh at the end?]
[The Rival Big Match]
The first round of the Rival Big
Match is "picking out 33 cards."
Lee Teuk vs. Kim Hee Chul.
Picking out 33 cards.
They need to quickly pick out
33 cards in order using one hand.
- It won't be easy to pick out quickly.
- That's right.
Lee Teuk and Kim Hee Chul.
Let's look at the players.
Their fans know about it
and they've also talked about a fist
fight they had in Inchon on a talk show.
The rivals in the group.
Officially, Lee Teuk is the Team leader.
And Kim Hee Chul is the Sub Leader.
We can see the two players
are rivals from looking at the profile.
- You can't have two suns.
- Of course not.
They can't be rivals forever.
They need to make it clear someday.
And that's today!
Please write down how many
points you will bet for the first round.
- Don't feel too pressured.
- I think I can win.
You think so?
I think we can put a lot
of points for Lee Teuk.
I think he can win.
I'm a lot faster than Teuk at typing.
I can move my fingers really fast.
How about betting 70 points?
I'm worried...
Hee Chul went to a technical
high school, so he's dexterous.
He built a lot of stuff.
He's dexterous.
I'll leave now!
Let's shout together!
Good luck!
Have fun!
The players finished the practice.
Kim Hee Chul appears first.
I think you'll win this.
No matter what.
Don't waste your energy.
Lee Teuk and Kim Hee Chul.
Lee Teuk was exercising on
the bar when he entered.
That's just wasted energy.
He might be too tired later.
- That was unnecessary.
- That's right.
Just do as you're used to!
Time matters for this game.
It's important to pick out 33 cards fast.
I wonder how fast
Lee Teuk can pick them out.
Just relax, Teuk!
[Super nervous]
I'm feeling uneasy!
- Lee Teuk, fight!
- I'm so nervous!
[The introductory game
of the Rival Big Match!]
[Picking out 33 cards]
Don't listen to them!
Are you ready?
I'm ready!
The first round!
[I will beat my rival today!]
This makes me nervous.
It's okay, Teuk!
The game starts now!
[He makes mistakes as soon
as he starts playing.]
[Oh, no!]
[Nice, he made a mistake!]
[He's speeding up to
make up his mistake.]
At once!
He's half way!
If you make mistakes,
you lose a lot of time.
[Go, Lee Teuk, go!]
You're doing a good job!
[He's almost finished.]
Finish!
[Lee Teuk's time will be revealed
after Hee Chul's play.]
[Good job!]
It's okay.
[I think I can do it.]
Lee Teuk made a few mistakes.
That's where you lose the time.
Playing slower but steadier
can reduce the loss of time.
Hee Chul, rather than being fast,
keep it steady.
This game makes me so nervous.
Kim Hee Chul is pretty sharp.
He's setting the cards at an angle
that's comfortable for him.
It's important to set it at an angle,
so it's easier to pick.
- Kim Hee Chul!
- Ready!
Keep it calm!
- Kim Hee Chul!
- Start!
He started!
- He's fast!
- Four, five, six...
Good, good!
Don't do it too fast!
You never know...
[Super-focused]
Slowly, slowly.
[He makes up the mistake he made
in the beginning and speeds up.]
Great, great!
[Flawless card picking!]
[Using his snaps, he's
advancing at a high speed.]
Finish!
[He's sure of his victory.]
He's good!
[Bitter]
He picked the cards so easily!
[He's still dexterous!]
How can you be so fast?
Kim Hee Chul's snap was good!
The distance from the card
and his hand was short.
Right on top of the cards,
using his snaps
he minimized his motion.
You didn't move much,
and that's how you won!
[What will be the result?]
Lee Teuk's record is
16.95 seconds.
I think Teuk's record
is less than 10 seconds.
Kim Hee Chul's record is
[Which team will get the point
for the first match?]
13.24 seconds!
[Kim Hee Chul wins the first round
of Running Man Rival Big Match.]
Hey, little brother!
[In two seconds of announcing
the result, he acts like a leader.]
[Welcome, Champion!]
It's okay.
[We'll win the next match!]
[Let's keep this upturn!]
As Kim Hee Chul from Younger Brothers
team takes the first victory
Younger Brothers is
leading the match now.
But we shouldn't forget about how
much points they put up for this round.
More important than
winning is how you use the points.
If they didn't put a lot
of points for this round...
Through winning the matches,
it's about how many points you'll get.
You don't know until all the rounds end.
They need to get ready
for the second round now.
The second match is Forehead Basket.
Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook
will be playing.
The first one to score five points
through the hoop on
the opponent's forehead will win.
Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook
have had death matches numerous times.
Yoo Jae Suk is the number one
figure on Running Man
and Kim Jong Kook has
an eye on that position.
[Number One vs. Mr. Capable]
He's raising a tiger.
He's seen the tiger's claws
during the mud battle.
Yoo Jae Suk was smashed into the mud.
At another match with Kim Jong Kook,
the curve on his bottom was exposed.
It was horrible.
His position as a national emcee
has been weakening.
Kim Jong Kook who has an
eye for the number one position
and the national emcee,
Yoo Jae Suk's match for the position.
[I'll put the period on
this tiring relationship!]
The game of diamond cut diamond!
The confrontation of pride
between two men!
Jong Kook will do his best.
[Burning with passion]
Take off your glasses, Jae Suk.
Both players are ready.
- Fight!
Go, Yoo Jae Suk, go!
The second round, Forehead Basket!
We'll start now!
[The Rival Big Match,
Forehead Basket, start!]
- I don't care who starts.
- Go ahead, Jong Kook!
Jong Kook's shooting form
isn't that good.
[Jong Kook's weak at ball games.]
Arc!
[Goal in!]
Succeeded!
[Hooray, Tiger!]
Kim Jong Kook!
With score of 1:0,
Kim Jong Kook is leading.
[What did he just do?]
[This is feeling better
than scoring a goal!]
Don't be irritated by that!
[Upsetting]
He aimed for it!
He wasn't aiming for a goal,
but he aimed for Tiger.
This is more of a provoking.
Yoo Jae Suk is taking off
his glasses now.
He's ready for Tiger's counterattack.
Just ignore it!
[Wait and see.]
I feel so good, even though I missed it.
[Will he avenge?
Will he score?]
Good job!
[Eye for eye, tooth for tooth,
psychological warfare!]
The path of the ball
is getting lower and stronger.
It's more like a fast ball.
You did it!
[A strong and fast ball!]
[Good riddance!]
[He forgets about the match,
and keeps making fun of Tiger.]
He's having fun,
and he will be able to score next.
- Yoo Jae Suk is smart.
- It's like a jab.
Don't be swayed!
[I'll remain calm.]
This hoop is in the way.
[Mr. Capable is focused on the match.]
Throw it hard!
Aim for the "R" mark.
[Goal in!]
[Yoo Jae Suk vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[1:1]
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Grasshopper becomes competitive.]
I'm swayed because of you.
(AOA's song)
[That was close.]
You just need to
get the hang of it.
Aim for the "R" mark again.
[Yoo Jae Suk vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[2:1]
[Praise Yoo Jae Suk!]
Yoo Jae Suk reversed!
It's two to one now!
After he's gotten hit twice,
he's swayed.
Don't worry, you can reverse!
[Goal in!]
[Yoo Jae Suk vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[2:2]
Please lower your head.
They're rivals.
[Yoo Jae Suk vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[3:2]
[Younger Brother team is
one step closer to their goal.]
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Tiger is aiming for the hoop.]
He missed it.
His mind is weakened!
Yoo Jae Suk is controlling the game now.
[Sabotage]
Yoo Jae Suk!
Goal in!
[See?]
[He ignores the opponent's
sabotage easily.]
Four to two!
It's the fourth goal!
It's a match-point for Yoo Jae Suk!
The game only began, Jong Kook.
The ball will fall from up to bottom.
Up, down, up, up, and down!
He did it!
He's careful.
The difference is only one point.
Kim Jong Kook is right
after Yoo Jae Suk.
[Jae Suk needs one more point!]
[Please, please, please.]
You need to finish it now.
[Nervous]
Please put your head down.
It's good now.
[Being sensitive about
the hoop's location.]
He's got the feel of the
angle and the path of the ball.
It's about controlling strength.
He made it!
[Goal in!]
The goal went in!
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Yoo Jae Suk vs. Kim Jong Kook]
[5:3]
Since he earned five points first
the winner of the second round
is Younger Brother team.
They've won twice in a row!
Kim Hee Chul, and Yoo Jae Suk's victory!
[Complicated]
Two consecutive victories
for Younger Brother team!
They have a good flow of the game.
[Younger Brother team keeps their
upturn with consecutive victories.]
It was a close game.
It was really close!
Kim Hee Chul and Yoo Jae Suk's
consecutive victory!
The two players who want
to be the leading figure!
Of course,
Yoo Jae Suk protected his position.
We just finished the second round.
[The Rival Big Match]
[Jae Suk: win. Jong Kook: lose]
[Gary wins over Ha Ha
at the third round.]
They're feeling urgent
because it's 3:0.
They'll do their best to win this round.
By the way, if I lose this time.
We might lose at two rounds.
Our team spirit might go down.
I wonder how they divided
up their points.
I think they put a lot
of points on Hani.
We can win at the three rounds.
Then it'll be three to three.
I don't think they put
a lot of points for early rounds.
They must've put a lot
of points at the end.
We will win from now on,
no ones knows how it'll be.
Betrayal rock-paper-scissors, a battle
between Ji Suk Jin and Lee Kwang Soo!
It's about who can lie better.
The players will say what
they will throw before.
Will they keep their words or betray?
If they keep their words,
they earn two points.
That's right!
When they keep the promise,
you get double points.
The icon of betrayal, Giraffe!
Once, he set up a giant maze
and tricked all the Running Man members.
Ji Suk Jin, 178 cm and 73 kg.
With Lee Kwang Soo, Feel! Touch! Cross!
They've been acting together
by using their senses.
The icon of Betrayal, Kwang Soo betrayed
him and they started to fall out.
Ji Suk Jin, by the way,
with the golden key...
He betrayed everyone!
When I was watching the show on TV,
I knew he would do that.
Is he showing his true colors?
Currently, Younger Brother team
has won three rounds.
Kwang Soo has to cut the stream now.
You're feeling in a hurry
because you've lost three times.
[So much pressure]
Go for it!
You can do it, Kwang Soo!
[Big-nose is using the situation.]
Good luck!
I'll make you go down today!
- Let's go!
- There's nowhere to retreat.
Younger Brother team has
won three times now...
Kwang Soo has to win
this match no matter what.
[The one who wants to
fight back to the ropes!]
[And the one who wants to put a period!]
[The Rival Big Match]
[Betrayal Rock-paper-scissors, start!]
Their team spirit is already low!
What are you going to throw?
[First attack!]
Don't tell him first!
It's okay, it doesn't matter.
I'll throw paper.
- I'll throw scissors.
- Then you'll win.
I'll throw scissors, seriously.
Please, help me once.
- How?
- Just lose for once.
Beg on your knees,
he's older than you any way.
[He doesn't care by fair means or foul!]
What's the score now?
He's begging him to throw paper!
You don't know if that's real.
That might be his trick.
Let's go!
- I'll throw scissors!
- I see.
Trust each other,
even though we're enemies.
That looks really nice.
[They make a verbal contract.]
Get ready!
[They agreed to be true.]
[Will their agreement come to fruition?]
Rock-paper-scissors!
As expected!
[They're in a draw.]
[Their betrayal DNA!]
- It was all lies!
- Right!
At the end of the continuous lies,
if one true statement comes out
they'll score two points.
At a critical moment,
they have to be truthful.
I see how it is.
He knelt, but he was still betrayed.
They're betrayers after all.
Both of them are...
I'll throw paper.
- Paper?
- Yoo, too, throw paper.
Paper to paper!
[Thinking]
- Aren't you putting off too much time?
- Scissors!
He said it as he was throwing rock.
He did throw rock with his hand.
[Saying one thing, doing another.]
Wait a moment.
- Why are you...
- It's what you did.
Are you going to throw scissors?
I'll throw paper.
I was going to throw paper.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[With a truthful statement,
Kwang Soo earns two points.]
[I've been tricked!]
Lee Kwang Soo earns two points!
Who knew they would both
be truthful this time?
What an amazing battle of wits!
It was a skill of God!
[The Rival Big Match]
- Just one more step.
- You're on your own.
It's an important moment.
[Anxious]
[Self-awakening]
[It hurts!]
Didn't you hit too hard?
Too bad, he must've been KO'd by that.
[What do you hate me so much?]
Kwang Soo, you're almost there.
Just relax.
Kwang Soo's battle of wits!
Kwang Soo's the one
controlling the game.
Scissors.
- Are you going to throw it?
- Yes.
Suk Jin, I lied.
I won't throw scissors.
I say I'll throw scissors,
but I don't do it.
Then, it'll be either rock or paper.
Since you're not going
to throw scissors.
Then, I won't lose if I throw paper.
I'll throw paper, then.
He's smart!
He said scissors
and then he said he lied.
He's making it more complicated.
See?
Kwang Soo is controlling the flow.
He's offensive.
Ji Suk Jin is agitated now.
Was rock-paper-scissors
this kind of game?
I didn't really expect much for
the fourth round, but it's so exciting!
[What will these two men choose?]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[I've been tricked again!]
[Lee Kwang Soo wins the
betrayal rock-paper-scissors!]
You did a good job, Suk Jin.
[With Giraffe's effort,
Big Brother team is revived.]
This is upsetting!
I'm sick and tired of it!
Don't cry!
You did such a good job!
Scissors, scissors, scissors!
- The scissors!
- He only threw scissors, but he won!
Scissorhands Lee Kwang Soo!
He made a turning point for his team.
It's their team's first victory.
He brought their first victory
during the fourth round.
Big Brother team grabs
their first victory
and started chasing their
opponent with the score of 3:1.
They're still in the hunt
to win this battle
if they put a lot of points
for Lee Kwang Soo.
Is that a bed?
They're bringing in mattresses.
The mattresses for a sound sleep...
I debuted 26 years ago
and I've never thought I'd
cast someone's sleep.
Look at the beds!
We have beds for a Running Man set?
What kind of game is this?
For the fifth Big Match
Hani and Song Ji Hyo are getting
ready in the waiting room.
What are we supposed to do?
[What are these machines?]
It's not going to vibrate
or anything like that?
No, it's not.
They can pretend they're asleep.
Using medical equipment,
we'll be testing.
The sensor will show their brainwaves.
It's like a lie detector.
How can I possibly
fall asleep like this?
They might have bet a lot
of points for this round.
The viewers of Running Man have seen
Song Ji Hyo sleeping countless times.
Recently, Hani was sleeping
in the car with a bent neck.
- Her eyes were rolling.
- In the car, in front of cameras.
When Yoo Jae Suk was right next to her.
That's why both teams might have
bet a lot of points for this match.
This is a bet of trust.
- We need to bet a lot.
- No, no!
Hani will be actually sleeping
when they cover her eyes and ears.
- That's right.
- She's too strong.
I think they will bet a lot for Ji Hyo.
There's no reason for us
to bet a lot for this.
- Even if we win, it's okay.
- They'll lose their points.
We need to start whispering, too.
According to the judgment
of the sleep therapist
we'll stop when one of them falls
into the second stage of sleeping.
The goal is the second stage of sleep.
The fifth round battle begins now!
We'll start the battle now.
- Do we lie down?
- Yes, please.
Feel free and lie down comfortably.
This is so unfamiliar!
Song Ji Hyo is on the left,
Hani is on the right.
They have different methods of sleeping.
Song Ji Hyo covers her
face with the blanket.
She didn't use the eye mask.
Covered in a blanket, without a pillow.
Ji Hyo could fall asleep
within three minutes.
She can sleep no matter
how bad the road is.
Can you keep it down?
[Big Brother team is also quiet.]
[Fascinated to see
the brainwave graph]
[Silent]
Wearing eye masks.
The graph is showing on the screen now.
If it looks like a straight line,
then it means they're sleeping.
They have different method of sleeping.
Hani puts her hands on her chest.
On the screen, we can see
the graph for both players.
Since they're still awake,
the graph keeps moving.
It'll change later.
You can only see a blanket on the left.
That's Song Ji Hyo.
Both of them are known as good sleepers.
They're always feeling tired.
Celebrities usually lack sleep.
There is much attention towards
the two players who sleep a lot.
Both of them are sensitive now.
They might be sensitive to sound,
or people next to them.
One of the players seems uncomfortable.
Of course, this is different from usual.
Eye masks could give some pressure.
So, she decided to
take off the eye mask.
A little light is bearable.
On the left, it's Song Ji Hyo.
Her graph has more highs and lows.
Hani should open her mouth,
in order to sleep.
That's still okay.
Darker...
At this moment
the sleep therapist says
Hani is closer to sleeping.
If it looks like a straight line,
then it means they're sleeping.
Song Ji Hyo is moving.
Maybe she can't get to sleep.
Her graph moves up and down.
On the contrary, Hani's graph
is pretty steady.
It's pretty calm.
Her graph looks almost straight.
Now, both players' graphs
look almost the same.
Song Ji Hyo is a good sleeper, too.
Hani's graph seems more
like a straight line.
[Hani fell asleep.]
Hani is getting close to
the second stage of sleep.
Hani is leading.
[Ji Hyo's special skill
has to be applied!]
[Lift]
Hani wins.
[Hani wins the match.]
Hani won!
She's awake!
[What's going on all of a sudden?]
[Half sleep, half awake]
Big Brother team earns another point!
It's three to two now!
They're chasing Younger Brother team.
Did you sleep well, Hani?
One of the players is puzzled.
She's not sure if she's still dreaming.
She's still trying to wake up.
Ji Hyo fell asleep, too.
Hani is not fully awake, yet.
Wow, Hani!
Ji Hyo usually falls asleep
when she covers her face.
I saw her opening her mouth slowly.
It was obvious when she
took off the eye mask.
- She seemed sleepy.
- She was ready.
I can't believe Ji Hyo lost at sleeping.
It's nonsense!
Hani has a puffy face.
It was less than 10 minutes.
I didn't want to wake her up.
She was already asleep.
Good job!
[The dark horse in the world
of sleep wins over Song Ji Hyo!]
She adds another victory to her team.
Big Brothers has two wins,
and Younger Brothers has three.
Because we don't know
how they bet their scores
we can't say one of
the teams are leading.
- Yo Hwan.
- You need to win.
[Pressure]
[Big Brothers has hope now.]
It's all up to Jin Ho now.
- So much pressure!
- You can do it!
This match is for you!
It's a drama all for you!
If you win this time...
I think I'm going to cry!
The last round!
Only one round is left!
Please introduce the players for the
sixth match of The Rival Big Match.
Today, it's not a StarCraft match,
but a Tetris match.
Let me introduce two players now.
Hong Jin Ho and Lim Yo Hwan,
please enter!
This is the last game.
Hong Jin Ho needs to get rid of
his "number two" tag today.
He could remain as number two.
Good luck, Lim yo Hwan!
[The relationship
as rivals for 15 years!]
Lim Yo Hwan wins!
Their faces are the same as
when they had StarCraft match.
Don't be nervous!
This isn't going to make you number one.
I never thought this music
could sound so heroic.
I think they're betting
a lot on this, too.
The one who loses this loses the race.
Get ready!
We'll begin the sixth round now!
One, two, three!
Good luck, Hong Jin Ho!
Hong Jin Ho is on your right
and Lim Yo Hwan is on your left.
They need to get rid of
12 lines for this round.
One by one...
Tetromino is falling.
Nine lines left.
[He made a mistake.
[Nervous]
Five more lines!
Eight lines for Lim Yo Hwan!
There is a three line gap.
Hong Jin Ho has five lines left.
One more!
And three lines!
Three and six, Hong Jin Ho is leading.
Only two lines for Hong Jin Ho!
One less!
The last one, finish!
[I defeated Lim Yo Hwan!]
[Hong Jin Ho scores one point.]
[Bitter]
Stay calm.
The second round begins now.
This time, it's 15 lines.
Go, Hong Jin ho, go!
They're setting the foundation for now.
Lim Yo Hwan is calm.
Obstacles are appearing!
Lim Yo Hwan is leading now.
The game looks very good.
[It looks like a high-rise building.]
[One small mistake can ruin the game.]
[Everyone is nervous.]
He got rid of two lines.
[Lim Yo Hwan starts playing faster.]
Eight lines to six lines!
[Nice!]
Lim Yo Hwan is doing well this round.
There's no reverse!
Five lines to ten lines!
Lim Yo Hwan only has three lines left!
And two lines now.
Lim Yo Hwan needs to
clear one more line!
[And the "I" appears!]
[Lim Yo Hwan wins the second round.]
[I can't believe it!]
[Relaxed]
The score is one to one.
It's a tie.
[The third round begins.]
Jin Ho looks like he's
playing StarCraft.
[The pro-gamer's instinct revives.]
They need to clear 15 lines.
Oh, it's a good one.
[What a well-matched contest!]
One more line is cleared!
Lim Yo Hwan is fast in the beginning.
Same score again.
Reverse, tie!
This is such a close game!
Current situation for Hong Jin Ho is...
[He put the 'O' in the wrong spot.]
He made a mistake!
[You can do it!]
Just one line gap!
It's too early to give up.
Four more lines for Lim Yo Hwan,
Six lines for Hong Jin Ho.
[An 'I' appears.]
[He scored a lot at once!]
Just one more line!
[Two 'I's in a row,
he reversed it in a breath.]
Just one more line for Hong Jin Ho!
[I won again!]
[He defeated Lim Yo Hwan twice!]
Match-point!
[He can't control his face now.]
[Lim Yo Hwan vs. Hong Jin Ho]
[1:2]
He's really nervous.
He's feeling pressure.
[The fourth round starts.]
[This time, they need to clear 18 lines.]
18 lines this time.
Lim Yo Hwan needs to stay calm.
17 to 17.
It's a tie!
Lim Yo Hwan got rid of two lines.
He's playing it fast.
[He puts 'O' in a pile.]
Slowly, Hong Jin Ho
is waiting for a strike.
Hong Jin Ho!
[He makes a mistake.]
[Now is the chance!]
It's fine.
[One mistake makes it rise high.]
Hong Jin Ho needs an 'I.'
Not a good situation.
You got an 'I!'
[My savior, 'I!']
Two lines and two lines.
[Jin Ho turns it around.]
It's so close!
A tie!
[The lines they need to get rid of]
Lim Yo Hwan, six!
Hong Jin Ho, five!
The difference is one line!
Five to four!
[Super nervous]
[Neck and neck]
Four to one!
It's the last line!
The game ends here!
[I did it!]
[Lim Yo Hwan vs. Hong Jin Ho]
[1:3]
[Hong Jin Ho wins at Arcade Tetris!]
[Finally, I defeated him!]
[Dejected]
This was a lot more thrilling
than StarCraft.
More than any finals,
I was most nervous.
[The only thing that's left
is to check the betting.]
We'll check the betting
score for the first round.
How many points did both teams bet?
- Please!
- Show us!
- The first round!
- They bet 50 points?
They bet that much?
50 out of 250?
That's a lot.
They bet 100 points?
[Big Brother team
lost 100 out of 250.]
[Because Lee Teuk lost.]
[They trusted Teuk too much!]
The match between
Lim Yo Hwan and Hong Jin Ho.
Reveal the betting point!
[Younger Brothers bet
40 points for Lim Yo Hwan.]
It wasn't too much.
[Big Brother team bet 70 points.]
[Younger Brothers vs. Big Brothers]
[50:70]
That's a big number.
The second round, reveal!
- They only bet 20 points?
- For the number one?
Big Brother team bet 50 points.
[Big Brother team bet
50 points for Mr. Capable.]
They won, but they've
only earned 20 points.
[The fifth round, Ji Hyo vs. Hani]
[How many points did they bet?]
[Big Brother team bet
10 points for Hani.]
[For winning the game of the century,
they earned 10 points.]
You thought we would've
bet a lot for Ji Hyo, right?
[Are they making fun of us?]
I kept saying I'm not confident.
[No one knows who will win.]
Just 10 points?
Only two rounds are left.
[Younger Brothers vs. Big Brothers]
[70:80]
We'll reveal the third
and fourth rounds at once.
Please show us the
third and fourth rounds!
[The Rival Big Match Race]
[What will be the result?]
[We're at 90% now!]
We won with a good strategy!
[Big Brother team earned
10 points from Kwang Soo's victory.]
It's a complete victory!
[How could it be?]
140 to 90!
[Younger Brother team won the race.]
The games were tight, but
the betting decided the winner.
We managed our score
really well and won!
[We did a good job, too.]
Jin Ho looks so happy.
I'm satisfied now.
- Jin Ho cried when he won.
- I did cry for a moment.
Of course, you need
a trophy at a competition.
I'm sorry, we won the race.
[They're bickering until the end.]
The Rival Big Match!
Younger Brother team won!
Thank you for your work!
[Early winter in 2015.
Han River, Seoul]
[Gary is stuck inside
an unfamiliar cube.]
[Where am I?
Please come and take me out!]
[He can only make phone calls!]
[He needs to tell them what he sees!]
[Lost in Seoul.]
[From now on, use all your senses!]
[As time goes, the location of the cube
becomes even more confusing.]
[A vast conspiracy over a diamond!]
[Where is Gary?]
[Where is the diamond?]
[What?]
Wait, move it slowly!
[Next week, "Lost in Seoul."]