[The Big Bang package has arrived!]
[Big Bang returns after three
years ready to compete!]
[The greatest idol stars of variety!]
[It starts now!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Korea, 2015]
[Two mysterious vehicles
appear in the light.]
[Break!]
[Smoke billows out
with a thunderous noise.]
[And...]
[Out of the smoke,
six Roman gladiators appear.]
[Global fashion leader, G-Dragon]
[The charismatic T.O.P]
[The swag Tae Yang]
[The seductive and dangerous Seung Ri]
[The pillar of idol variety, Dae Sung]
[Mr. Capable and Big Bang]
[By the way, from the other side...]
[Six wealthy merchants from
the Joseon Era appear.]
[The two historical teams clash in 2015!]
I started clapping as soon as I saw them.
Why didn't you call me?
Why are you personally greeting them?
Nice to see you.
[It's been three years.]
Get in line.
Why didn't you greet me?
It's an honor to see you!
He's gotten mean!
They would look great even if
they we wearing this costume.
Ha Ha envies GD the most.
[Thank you.]
Who doesn't envy GD?
I don't envy him.
He's a great man.
Be my son's godfather.
[Embarrassed]
Make him just like you!
- He wants to make his son like GD.
- Start training from now on!
- Dae Sung, you look the same as before.
- That's right.
I was getting too handsome.
I wanted to go back to my original style.
Is he serious or what?
His persona is going to be changed.
What's your new persona?
Ugly man, I have to go back.
He's showing his forehead
and discouraged.
When he had those bangs,
everyone said
that he looks handsome
and rejuvenated.
I've covered up half of my face
and they said my face
is brightened up.
- Unbelievable.
- What is it today?
- Are we from the past?
- Back to the past?
- Where are you from, GD?
- We're from Rome.
[Why does he look so awesome?]
He's so cool!
What about you, T.O.P?
We're from Lome.
I had a recording with T.O.P,
and he's changed.
- Like what?
- He talks in a less deep voice now.
- He doesn't talk in very deep voice.
- Really?
As you can guess from your costume
you're big merchants from the Joseon Era
and gladiators from the Roman Era.
What are you?
Are all of you Hong Gil Dong?
- What did you say?
- We do look like him though.
Move aside!
You're covering Big Bang.
- What?
- Why are you wearing a skirt?
- Move aside!
- Don't look down on this sword.
This is for beating up.
To go back to the past that you're from
you need to win
the Time Track Race.
Let me explain
the rules for the race.
What you need to do to win is...
There's only one 'Back-To Car'
that will let you go
back to the past.
Only the final winner can get on
the car and go back to the past.
When you complete a mission first
you will be able to choose
the gates of the final relay.
There are two missions to complete.
At the final race, the team who gets on
the 'Back-To Car' is the winner.
Isn't this place familiar to you?
Yes, I know this place.
Ha Ha and I did a racing game.
Here?
- You might have an advantage.
- What advantage?
- How?
- He said so!
- Why are you doubting?
- Why is it to your advantage?
- Do you remember the course?
- It's in my mind.
- Go to the first mission site.
- Let's go!
[Was Big Bang too quiet?]
[They have thrown themselves!]
[Bite, run...]
[throw themselves and strip!]
[Total variety gift set!]
[Everything about Big Bang!]
[Let's go!]
[It looks like the gears are spinning.]
Oh, okay!
[Curious]
[Where are they?]
Those aren't acupressure mats, are they?
What is it?
[What is the gear set for?]
Is that a gear?
What is it?
[A special outdoor set
for the time travelers.]
[The super-sized gears in the clock.]
They're wagon wheels.
- What is it?
- Oh, they're gears?
- They're moving.
- Oh, the ones inside a watch?
[He's curious and nervous.]
[Different sizes, different locations]
[What mission will they be
given on these gears?]
What is this for?
Do we have to put our face in?
The first mission is
'The Cuckoo Clock Goes Cuckoo.'
- What's that?
- We will tell you the time.
Remember what time it is...
[Suddenly, the gears start moving!]
- That's really fast!
- They're fast!
[Each gear moves in a different speed.]
- It's so fast.
- Look at that!
You need to go through the gears
and get to this cuckoo clock.
Then break the plastic wrap
on the clock with your face.
Say 'cuckoo' as many times
as the presented time.
Just like a cuckoo clock.
It'll be difficult at 12 o'clock.
The person who succeeds at it
will leave the clock.
The first team to succeed
will win the first mission.
In short, this is an agonizing game!
As more members leave the set,
winning will happen, but it'll be hard.
[When and who leaves
can change the situation.]
I've become handsome,
my fans might leave me if I do this.
Don't they need to do
something like a mud fight?
I don't know it might be the costume...
but Dae Sung looks like he's
dressed like a foreigner for a skit.
Isn't he one of the foreign actors
in 'Mystic TV Surprise'?
Look at his hair!
You look like a Westerner.
GD was in one of the
toughest races ever.
At that time, GD smelled like a frog.
We haven't played that game since.
[No one has played the game since then...]
I think we can win this game.
On the way, Jong Kook said...
he will make everyone fall
in the worst case scenario.
I said, you pass out sometimes.
But we edit the scenes out.
[I'm lucky to be on his team.]
- I'm nervous to play against Big Bang.
- Very nervous.
I don't want to lose.
We'll start the first round,
ready!
[The gears start moving.]
- Why so fast?
- How can we go through these?
[Will they be able to
make it through the gears?]
The time is...
- The first person at the clock...
- Sing 'cuckoo.'
We can drag each other, too.
[Break through the plastic wrap,
and sing cuckoo!]
[It's 9 o'clock!]
[GD passes the first gear
with a forward roll.]
[Tap dancing on the gear]
[Wobble, wobble]
[Hop, hop, hop]
[Chaos]
[Despite the ruckus, Jong Kook
and T.O.P are in the lead.]
[Break the plastic wrap,
and sing nine times!]
[But why can't I break it?]
[The floor is still rotating.]
[Looks like a rice ball.]
[Tae Yang is spinning on the gear.]
[Tae Yang has escaped from the gear.]
[Now everyone arrived at the clock.]
[Their tops and bottoms are
in different situations.]
[Are you really the T.O.P we know?]
Go back!
[Jong Kook is a human barricade.]
[GD is sacrificing himself.]
One, two, three!
Break it!
[His hair is back to normal.]
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo
cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo!
- Okay!
- He did it!
Good job!
Kim Jong Kook can't do that!
He blocks us from getting in.
Isn't that foul play?
I wanted to give up in the middle.
The wrap was hard to break through.
[The reminder of the horrible work]
This is an exciting game!
We need to get inside first because
Jong Kook is blocking for us.
We need to stop Jong Kook.
- Don't let him go there.
- Go to the clock first.
[T.O.P leaves the clock.]
I played one game,
why am I so tired?
- We need to keep running.
- Yes, run sideways.
My feet got twisted.
The plastic wrap is very tough!
- Let's go!
- It's important to finish first.
Big Bang's team has fewer members now.
Right, it's going to be easier for us.
Ready, it is...
[The gears start moving again.]
[11 o'clock!]
[They are faster than before.]
[Tae Yang and GD are in the lead.]
[Tae Yang runs fast...]
[and knocks his head!]
[The Pink Alien]
[Dae Sung is tap dancing again.]
[An alien is about to be born.]
What time is it?
Wait!
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo...
[Stop Tae Yang!]
[But Jong Kook, the barricade
doesn't move a bit.]
He's biting my arm!
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo!
12 o'clock?
No, it's not!
[Tae Yang, the cuckoo is wrong.]
Don't bite me!
[Bite]
- Keep going!
- Get in!
[GD comes out of the hole
Tae Yang made.]
What time is it?
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo...
cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo,
cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo!
[GD cuckoos the right amount of times!]
- Wow, you're the best!
- Did he make it?
- How many times did you say it?
- 12 times.
Why?
[After two rounds,
GD lost all of his energy.]
I couldn't think when my
mouth and head were covered.
It's hard to run and block
Jong Kook at the same time.
Can we not run through the gears?
- Please stop the gear!
- We can't block him anyway!
Ugh, I got bitten so much!
I'm covered in bite marks!
You're lucky, Ji Yong!
He went into the hole very fast.
What are you doing?
Let's think of a plan.
This is a physical game.
Let's block Jong Kook
and let them go.
We need three people to hold him.
Or all of us can attack
Jong Kook's head!
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and Gary
are the strongest among us.
Block him, and let Ji Hyo go first.
- We need to break through it fast.
- The three of you go.
I think they are
trying to make you succeed.
Otherwise, they can't win this.
One or two of you who can
work with me stay until later.
And the rest should get out first.
Even if they get there...
You and I should get out first.
- Dae Sung can stay.
- Because you're strong.
- Do you exercise?
- Yes, I do.
He's stronger now!
People like you and me
need to exercise.
That's the only way to survive.
We need to keep our body fit.
[The half-closed eyes brothers,
unite together.]
Tae Yang!
How does your hair stay moist?
I put some water.
What are you doing
in the middle of the meeting?
- Don't be jealous!
- Concentrate!
Is this a fan meeting?
Put some water.
[He puts water in immediately.]
It's going to dry soon.
- You look...
- Look at him.
Did you get a back shower?
You look like you played it really hard.
[Ha Ha styles his hair like Tae Yang.]
You two look similar...
from neck to toe.
Let's play it again.
If you're ready, we'll resume.
You're getting close to me?
Three of you?
They don't look at me
but they're standing next to me.
It's weird.
Look over here.
I don't think we will lose,
even without me.
- Just tell us it's 1 o'clock.
- This time, we will make it!
Six of the merchants
and four of the gladiators are left.
- Seriously.
- Ready!
Fight!
[The gears start rotating again.]
The time is...
[6 o'clock!]
[Three of them block one tightly.]
[Tae Yang runs fast.]
[Catch Tae Yang!]
[Dae Sung and Seung Ri
run to help Tae Yang.]
Tae Yang is fast.
[Tae Yang's specialty, the header!]
[The pink alien is back!]
[The four of them are united!]
- Do something!
- My arms are numb!
We need to do something about it!
[Tickle, tickle]
[The merchants are interrupting Tae Yang.]
[In a hurry, wearing plastic wrap
on his head...]
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuck...
[Stop the singing!]
- Cuckoo!
- How can we lose again?
[Tae Yang calmly succeeds
at singing cuckoo.]
What are you doing?
6 o'clock.
Tae Yang bit him?
[I got bitten.]
[Things like that happen
when you play games.]
[Ha Ha, Ji Hyo, and Seung Ri succeeded.]
I'm so frustrated.
He keeps blocking us
and doesn't let us do anything.
We should make him leave.
- How can we do that?
- We can't unless he sings.
Can we stop them from
singing by hitting the side?
It'll sound like 'Ugh koo!'
[Try it if you can.]
It's four vs. two.
If two gladiators succeed, it'll be over.
Ready, set!
[5 o'clock.]
[Jong Kook is the fastest!]
Get in!
[Dae Sung, we'll be set
if you get in now.]
[Wait for me, Jong Kook!]
Wait, Jong Kook!
[Where are you Dae Sung?]
Get in, Dae Sung!
[I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
It might take some time...]
Dae Sung!
Dae Sung, get in!
[Dae Sung barely escapes...]
[and tries to get through their legs.]
Dae Sung!
[Meanwhile, Jae Suk and Gary
try breaking through...]
[Easy Brothers knocked
Dae Sung on the gear.]
[Jong Kook keeps holding the clock.]
[Dae Sung manages
to escape from the Easy Brothers]
[and going in from the bottom again.]
I'm in...
[What chaos!]
[While Jong Kook blocks
Gary and Jae Suk...]
[Dae Sung watches the rotation.]
[When he's near the clock,
Dae Sung starts tickling them.]
Dae Sung, hurry up!
I'm in!
[Where are you going?]
Dae Sung!
[Gary is thrown.]
[Big-nosed brother replaces Gary.]
[Who are you?]
[Two Suks under one roof.]
They might do it!
What time is it?
Cuckoo!
I don't know what time it is.
I forgot!
5 o'clock.
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo!
[Jae Suk succeeds at it.]
Good job!
Dae Sung, you should have gotten in.
[He went in...]
[He got back out after a moment.]
My body feels like...
as if I went inside a cage full of dogs.
What should we do?
[Who will block Kim Jong Kook now?]
We need to get rid of Jong Kook...
Hey, that's little too much.
Get rid of me?
- Let me go this time.
- No, let me.
No, let me leave.
They don't want to be the last one.
- Let me leave.
- I should.
Do you want me to face a
tricky ride at this age?
Maybe you're shameless
at that age.
I need to keep my dignity.
Three people left.
I like what I'm looking at.
When was the last time
you were nervous?
Ready!
[The winner will be able to choose
the first and second gate.]
Set!
[3 o'clock, starts!]
[Jong Kook and Dae Sung get
to the clock at the same time.]
[With just his face,
he has become a variety wonderkid]
It's over!
[He's screaming for losing his fans!]
One, two, three!
Dae Sung!
Jong Kook!
Who grabbed my feet?
Hurry up, Dae Sung.
[When Dae Sung gets in,
the barricade Jong Kook starts blocking.]
[That face... is more like art.]
[They try to stop Dae Sung...]
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo!
[The barricade Jong Kook
succeeds at blocking.]
I'm done!
Look at them.
They're watching
the game in peace.
Because they know they will win...
I will protect Big Bang!
[Hooray, Jong Kook!]
Let's do our best.
Now, it's about who will betray first.
I'm dizzy.
I'm about to throw up.
Hurry up!
We'll attack him at the same time.
Are you ready?
[Jong Kook is surrounded by them.]
It's better if you let me go.
At least, one person will remain.
[If Jong Kook succeeds,
The Gladiators will win.]
[6 o'clock, starts!]
[Mr. Capable's full power.]
[We can't lose like this!]
[After the running...]
[Horror!]
[We're lucky that he's on our team.]
Beat him on the side!
Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo,
cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo!
[Jong Kook easily succeeds.]
We won!
[The Gladiators win the first mission.]
[They can choose the first and
the second gate of the final race.]
There are two options
for the fist gate.
Look at the options,
and decide now.
They might pick a bad one.
This one.
[Water]
[Carbonated drink]
- This one is better.
- Of course!
This is easy to pick.
- Okay, give it to us.
- What is it?
Carbonated drink?
Maybe we need to drink and whistle.
Okay, we'll take it.
We wanted to pick this one
from the start.
We have Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo and I can drink soda fast.
I can drink it fast, too.
You're giving us the second gate, too?
Let us pick first!
[Straight]
[Curve]
This kind of stuff...
This one.
But we never know...
They're so happy.
Anyway, the final race will be a relay.
Pick this one.
Dae Sung is smart!
That's right!
Give it to us.
T.O.P is laughing a lot.
You must have picked a good one.
What is it?
[I'm so happy.]
- It's good.
- Okay!
They must have picked 'straight.'
Maybe the curve is a good one.
[How will this card
influence the final race?]
Was this game okay for you?
Yes, it was fun.
You've only gone once.
You say it was fun?
We haven't even started yet.
I was going to give up
in the middle.
You came back out few times,
and we pushed you back.
I thought I couldn't make it.
I couldn't break through the wrap.
If we win the second game too,
we'll be able to pick all the gates.
What would be 'straight'?
I think it's about driving.
I think we will drive
since we're here.
- Then is this for a track?
- I wonder if we'll drive cars.
I wonder if they will
give us tricycles.
[It won't be anything simple...]
Maybe they will tie our legs
and make us race?
[They're making all kinds of guesses.]
There's got to be something.
In any case, 'straight' is
better than 'curve.'
It's so hot today.
Hot air comes from the outside.
[He looks at something...]
It's pretty hot, right?
I turned on the heating.
Why did you turn it on?
I was wondering why it was so hot.
It was strange.
It's hot summer!
[The merchant team is
having fun on the road.]
[Silent]
[Here, sleeping...]
[there, sleeping]
[Everywhere sleeping...]
[They've only completed one mission,
but are totally exhausted.]
We're here.
[Opens their eyes.]
[His eyes look bigger.]
[Where are we?]
[A cool valley with a nice stream.]
[What is the next mission?]
Let's get off.
We're here.
This is the main dish, but we've
wasted our energy for the appetizer.
[Half-asleep.]
I'll give you the rules.
Across the ages and in all countries
people enjoy this ball game.
- A ball game?
- Foot volleyball!
Dodgeball!
That is basketball.
[Basket ball?]
A red flag warning
is issued in Yeongnam.
Now, it is expanded to
Jeonnam and Kangwon.
Today is the hottest day...
[Are you serious?]
In the water, you will see the
basketball posts on both sides.
You will play with a special ball
that becomes heavy when wet.
Five players for each team.
[Big Bang and Running Man's
epic performance.]
[Water basketball.]
[Are you ready?]
[They've changed into uniforms.]
[Naive look]
It's been such a long time
since I've seen Dae Sung like that.
He's back to his old image.
He looks the same
as in 'Family's Outing.'
Look at GD, he's wearing
the towel differently.
Don't do that!
How did you do that?
Why are you so fashionable?
Why did he tie it differently?
It's not like you'll
look like him anyway!
Why not?
We'll be the same if we do that.
We can all be GD,
if we wear it the same way.
We can't be GD.
[A trendsetter and a village foreman.]
[Do you have to be handsome
to be fashionable?]
Will Running Man
get the ball first?
- Yes, we will attack first.
- No, let us!
Let's start with a jump ball.
[The Gladiators team
gets the ball first.]
[Kkuk and Yoo Hyuk are on the bench.]
[GD's miss pass.]
Pass it!
[Kwang Soo's crisp pass]
Suk Jin!
[Big-nose's shot!]
[Big-nose, scoring the first point?]
[T.O.P's blocking!]
It's so cold!
[Seung Ri's long pass]
[Slam dunk!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[1: 0]
He's my brother!
Dae Sung dunked it.
[The Basketball Man, Dae Sung.]
You looked awesome!
I'll show you what I can do!
[The Merchants get the ball now.]
[Ha Ha is hiding behind the Gladiators.]
[I see you, got it!]
[Home Run!]
[Ha Ha is shorter than I thought...]
[He gets the ball in the face.]
[He passes it to Tae Yang.]
[Clean shot!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[2: 0]
[That was amazing!]
[Glance]
[Ji Hyo, I can do it, too.]
[The series of attacks
by the Gladiators.]
[Gary intercepts the ball.]
[Let's go, Merchants!]
[Gary's lightspeed attack!]
[Are you watching me, Blank Ji?]
[You're awesome, Kang Gary!]
[An ugly lay-up shot.]
[Are you dancing a ballet?]
I messed it up.
[The Gladiators' counterattack.]
[Let's go!]
[Dunk!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[3: 0]
[Big Bang is love.]
[Depressed]
[The Merchants were put in a corner.]
[They barely steal the ball.]
[Steal]
[Gary intercepts again.]
[This is a great chance
for a fast break.]
[We'll finally score one!]
Kwang Soo!
[He fails at a behind-the-back pass.]
[No matter how good of a skill you've
got, it's no use if you fail at it.]
[The ball is passed to
the Flame Shooter, Tae Yang.]
[He runs by himself...]
[and makes a shot?]
[All I can see is the hoop.]
[Goal in!]
[His aim is deadly.]
[Fantastic baby!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[4: 0]
It's frustrating!
That's great!
[The Merchants, changing the players]
[I'm too frustrated to watch.]
[Who's going to switch with him?]
Suk Jin, switch with me.
[Big-nose brother is substituted
and Captain Yoo is added.]
What were you doing, Suk Jin?
I played pretty well.
Big Bang, Big Bang!
[Big-nose is sullen
and cheering for Big Bang.]
[GD's interception.]
Writers, can't you keep it down?
You're so noisy every time
GD gets the ball.
[A loose ball situation]
[GD and Kwang Soo's
struggle for the ball.]
[I can't let it go!]
Hurry up!
Ji Suk Jin!
[I'm not helping.]
[Hurry up and go!]
Ji Suk Jin!
[The king of cheating.]
[It's a loose ball situation again.]
[He casually catches
the ball and passes it.]
[Hand of God, Big-nose]
[He passes the ball to Ha Ha
who was close to the post.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[4: 1]
- You can't do that!
- My hands did it.
- Apologize then.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, that's how it is?
Because I don't control
my hands, either.
My hands did it.
I don't know.
[The Gladiators are
unrelenting in their attacks.]
[T.O.P passes it to Dae Sung.]
[Shoot!]
[Kwang Soo hits the ball
after it went inside.]
He caught it after the ball went in.
[The ball is passed to Ha Ha.]
[Haroro's dunk shot.]
Ha Ha!
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[4: 2]
[What a thrilling moment!]
You can't hit the ball
when it's inside the hoop!
Okay, I see.
Okay, I apologize.
[You're going too far...]
Can I switch?
[Mr. Capable makes a charge.]
I'll block the other team
while you pass the ball.
Like a football.
[Don't be so scary...]
[Pass]
Get in, get in!
[Solid rock defense]
[Is he a human being
or a pitcher plant?]
[This is the football-style basketball!]
[Goal in!]
[Dunk with two hands.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[5: 2]
[Giraffe is helpless
in front of Mr. Capable.]
[You dominate a game
by controlling the rebound.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[6: 2]
Good, good!
[What am I going to do
with that monster?]
[What is there to do?]
[Giving him a scalp massage
with a sponge ball.]
[And shoot!]
[Goal in!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[6: 3]
Did you hit me?
Sometimes, it happens during a game!
I apologize!
I'm really sorry!
[Is anyone doing the laundry
with a battledore?]
[It led to a bench-clearing brawl.]
[Time-out!]
[Giraffe throws
a punch of revenge.]
[He elbows him, too.]
[Just pretend you're hurt...]
[Dae Sung passes the ball to Tae Yang.]
[And he passes it to T.O.P.]
[Run!]
[Shot?]
[Alley-oop!]
[It was a pass even though
it seemed like a shot.]
[They performed like
professionals from the NBA.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[7: 3]
- We need to cheat.
- You should go one-on-one.
We should pass it high for him.
Within his arms reach.
But the ball is pretty heavy.
Try running!
We need defense.
It's important.
People who remember me
from 'Family's Outing'
Didn't I improve?
I'm not who I used to be.
I'm not as clumsy as I was.
I improved.
Did you see the alley-oop?
We need to cheat.
[Skills... or strength...
We're not a good match for them.]
[We don't really have a choice...]
Let's do it!
One, two, three!
Fight!
Will it change anything?
He's annoying.
I'll punch him in the face
when I turn 80.
[The second half of the game begins.]
[Just trust me.]
[Dunking is easiest thing in the world.]
[Dae Sung turns out to be the ace.]
[Should I start now?]
We need to guard!
[Let's go!]
[The ace makes a charge.]
[Will he show us another fancy skill?]
[He enters the water in a fancy manner.]
['Class is permanent.' - Bill Shankly]
[Throwing himself to pass the opponent.]
[Will they be able to make
a goal our of the pass?]
[Goal in!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[7: 4]
[Old habits die hard.]
[The Merchants are on the upturn.]
[It's their turn to attack again.]
[This is my second chance!]
[Welcome back,
Dae Sung the comedian.]
[It's beyond my control.]
[Pass]
Kwang Soo!
[An out-of-the-park homer]
[GD and Kwang Soo's
second ownership dispute.]
The water is deep!
Good job!
[Don't worry,
we will use it for good things.]
Get it, Ji Yong!
[Wrong shipment]
[My ball!]
[Their third battle]
Push his head down!
[Ji Yong is a good kid who listens.]
It's deep!
Where are you going?
- Save us!
- It's too deep for us.
[The rivalry between GD and Kwang Soo,
to be continued.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[10: 9]
[Yoo Hyuk's outside shot!]
[Goal...]
[It hits the rim and it bounced.]
[Big-nose's under-the-basket shot.]
[It failed.]
[T.O.P's fantastic pass.]
Ji Yong, you should score!
[It's a good chance
for a fast break!]
[He finishes it with a dunk.]
He reacted quickly!
His legs gave way.
[It's all because of Giraffe.]
Time-out!
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[11: 9]
[The Merchants need
a special arrangement.]
[How can we beat out this monster?]
Did you catch it?
[He catches the ball
from less than a meter.]
This is our last chance!
Dae Sung!
[Stop it!]
[Their rivalry starts again.]
[All-or-nothing war]
[Mr. Capable can handle that.]
Let go of me!
Don't take my pants off!
Do not take off my pants!
[That is...]
[the first stage of their tactic
for blocking Mr. Capable.]
[Na na na boo boo.]
This is it!
It's the chance!
[This is a very special arrangement
for victory.]
Where are my pants?
['Search for the owner.']
Take off his pants!
[The Merchants steal
their pants shamelessly.]
[This is how you play
when you're in a valley.]
Take off his pants!
[Beautiful legs.]
[Goodbye, pants!]
[I don't think I can
stand up for a while.]
We can't get out of the water!
[The savior, Dae Sung appears.]
Take it!
[Thank you!]
[Send it to the moon!]
[At this rate, we will lose the game.]
[Then, I have no choice
but a sudden attack!]
This isn't our post!
[He almost scored in his own goal.]
Kwang Soo!
[Dunk]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[11: 10]
[Sing a song comedian.]
- Time-out!
- Two players go over there!
[What time-out?
It's time for a fashion show.]
[I look good in red.]
- Hurry up!
- We tied the two top scorers' feet!
[A red flag warning is issued today.]
[You'll feel less hot.]
Take off T.O.P's pants, too!
[I'm really sorry.]
[Steal]
[Running at full speed.]
We need to stop him!
Stop him!
[Damn it, my weak legs...]
Please help out Ji Yong!
[Tae Yang gets his pants back
and joins the battlefield.]
[He can only watch it.]
[Pass]
[Go, GD!]
[Grasshopper's blocking]
[As soon as he lands,
he's rushing to the goal.]
[He beats out T.O.P]
[and a sharp drive in.]
[finishing up with a dunk.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[11: 11]
Ugh!
[From a defense to a fast break...]
[I am YooBron James.]
Just you wait!
I'll strip you till you're naked!
I'll make you naked!
You're on bent knees!
Are you admitting your sin?
You've made too many mistakes to us!
You little!!
- Take that!
- Won't you look at me?
We will forgive you now!
- It's no use to regret now!
- We're debt-free now.
- You rascal!
- Let's go.
I'm sorry.
[Gets up]
[The beast has escaped.]
[Beefy legs.]
[His legs look scary...]
[That style...
makes him look stronger...]
[Spartakkuks is back in the game.]
[He can't jump yet...]
[We're not in good turn.]
[After the good defense,
it's a good chance for a counterattack.]
[Will he be able to break through
T.O.P's defense?]
[Fake]
[Pass]
[Dunk]
[Perfect teamwork!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[11: 11]
[Two points to victory.]
[This is a critical moment
for the Gladiators.]
Let's attack all together!
[Giraffe's blocking skill, spider hands.]
[Why don't you keep
holding your hands up?]
Time-out!
[The Giraffe shield has collapsed.]
[Tae Yang's shot!]
[Goal in!]
[The Flame Shooter Tae Yang
and Tiger's team play!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[12: 13]
[Yahoo!]
What are you doing?
[The pitcher plant is back!]
[While Jong Kook blocks
the three players T.O.P rushes.]
Gary, it didn't go in!
[Goal in.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[13: 13]
- I see how it is!
- Sure.
We'll make you stay in the water!
Then, I'll make this valley
as a bath house.
[Both teams need to score two points.]
- Ji Hyo, catch it!
- Good job!
[Nice catch, Blank Ji!]
[Pass]
[Dunk]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[13: 14]
[The Merchants need one point]
[the Gladiators want
a quick-strike fast break.]
You're crazy!
[The final stage of blocking Mr. Capable.]
[Oh my god...]
[Giraffe wants to share
the information.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[14: 14]
[It's fun to play in the valley.]
You better stay in the water.
You're crazy!
[What's that gray fabric
he is holding?]
Give it back!
He's Tarzan!
[Are you enjoying a party
or filming for the show?]
[Pure naked Kkuk]
[Sitting like a girl.]
- You don't have your underwear?
- No!
[In a loud voice]
Give his boxers back!
Are you insane?
Are you willing to trade
this game with this?
You're crazy!
Why would I?
Why my underwear?
Just give it to me!
[Don't be too kind!]
- We need to dry them first.
- Give me back!
I need a clothesline.
Bring it lower.
- What are you doing?
- It's too wet.
[He likes this kind of boxer...]
- What are you doing?
- Wear it.
Go ahead.
He won't be able to come out.
Jong Kook is crying.
Give him some Kleenex!
[I won't forget this humiliation.]
[One day, when I stand up
I'll have my revenge...]
[I'll be back.]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[14: 14]
Each team needs one point.
One shot and it's over!
[Pass]
Oh no!
[Steal]
[What a great opportunity!]
Take it!
[Be calm and score one point...]
Alley-oop!
No!
[GD puts his heart and soul.]
Throw it!
[Steal]
[Goal in!]
[The Gladiators vs. The Merchants]
[14: 15]
[Haroro's decisive steal
leads to their victory.]
[Pitiable]
He's the fairy from
'A Fairy And A Woodcutter.'
Jong Kook is the fairy?
Why are the writers
all wearing sunglasses?
Do you want to take
a good look at Jong Kook?
[Bingo!]
[It's time to appreciate Spartakkuks.]
[The water basketball is over...]
We won by force.
Hey, GD...
You acted like you
weren't interested at first.
- T.O.P and all of you!
- It's not even funny!
So, we're allowed to do this?
- What are you talking about?
- No one saw you.
Mind your manners and get dressed.
We're on TV.
He exercised a lot.
I guess he wants to show off.
[Wait and see!]
Should I make you naked, too?
It was a great strategy!
Pick an option for the third gate.
- We should pick 'Short.'
- Why?
What if it's like chopsticks?
- Long and short?
- This one is difficult.
We wouldn't have
known what to pick, either.
We should pick 'short.'
- Take the 'long.'
- Okay.
And for the last gate.
- Big.
- Let's pick 'small.'
We picked 'short'
so pick 'small.'
- Should we keep consistency?
- No, just to be safe.
What if it's something huge?
Pick 'small.'
- Should I pick 'small'?
- Pick 'big.'
- Why?
- I have a feeling.
Small is good.
Big things are not
good for speedy games.
You've picked for all the gates.
Now you only have the last mission,
which is the racing.
As you decided...
[What are they doing?]
[Oops]
As you decided...
Why did you make them miserable?
They're doing laundry next to me.
You have only one mission to do.
Let's go!
[Go to the last mission site
of 'The Time Track Race.']
Jong Kook, you look...
- Shut up!
- I envy you, Jong Kook!
[The long-awaited final mission
of 'The Time Track Race.']
[The Gladiators enter the racing circuit.]
Why do they look so cool?
[They get a head start
from the beginning.]
You're not that cool, Dae Sung.
Please tell me I look cool.
The last mission of
'The Time Track Race'
'is 'The Running Car Race.'
Racing?
From the first to the fourth gate
you will travel in the cars.
You will get out of the car
for the missions and keep going.
We can't go back if we don't
complete the missions.
We can't go home?
[Dae Sung, focus!]
The sun is setting...
All day long, we've tried
to go back to the past.
You've picked the options for each gate.
- Water and carbonated drink.
- Straight and curve.
Short and big.
We have small and long.
- Are you showing us now?
- I think short is good.
[The options are revealed.]
Listen carefully.
The fist mission is
'Drink and flip.'
All of you will participate
at the first gate.
Everyone must get out of the car.
According to the options
water and soda will be served.
- Drink it first.
- Taking turns?
We need to flip the cup
so it's upside down.
The next person repeats.
When all of the cups are upside down
get back in the car and leave.
At the second gate,
you'll be doing 'The Abacus racing.'
- Like in-line skates?
- One person will pull in front?
Just one member will get out of the car.
And you'll see abacuses.
Get on the abacuses and
complete your courses.
One person gets out and finishes
the curved course on the abacuses.
Your feet need to stay on the abacuses.
At the third gate
you will play
'The Flagpole teamwork.'
Five people stand in a circle
Switch spots in one direction
until you're back to the original spot.
- Then 'long' is better.
- We have 'long.'
The flagpole should
not touch the ground.
When you're done,
get back to your car.
We picked the good ones.
At the last gate
You need two people here
to play 'Win the knapsack.'
You will see two walls are built.
You need use your body
to break down the walls.
When the knapsack drops,
pick it up and get in the car.
So, it's good if we picked 'big'?
When you're all done
stop the car at the start line.
We'll find the 'Back-To Car.'
When everyone gets in
the car and closes the doors...
We might bump into
each other and fight, right?
Do whatever you want.
What do you mean?
You need to say 'no.'
What if they take our pants off again?
I guess, it was traumatic for Tae Yang.
Don't do such things!
You understand the last mission?
Get in the car!
- Do you decide now?
- Yes, now.
Who will walk on the curved course?
The first one is for everyone,
so it doesn't matter.
The next one is for two people.
- Two and two?
- Two and one.
Who is a fast runner?
[The experienced and skilled Merchants.]
- For the five, everyone except me...
- Why?
So, I can drive right away.
Will you be able to...
do the abacus one well?
[The hottest idol cares about looks.]
We made good choices.
- They're not bad.
- All good except the last one.
Should we win?
Of course we should!
But we picked bad ones.
It's okay.
We can do it.
- Someone who's good at running...
- But abacuses are unstable.
They have the straight course.
Don't smile so cute, GD!
T.O.P's profile looks very handsome.
[T.O.P's intense gaze.]
You must be happy.
Should I wear the hairstyle?
You're already wearing it.
Your hairstyle is the same as his.
[The same hairstyle,
different impressions.]
[Ji Yong is about to take a photo.]
GD is taking a photo of us!
[V!]
[Snap]
Are you going to upload on your SNS?
[I shouldn't have taken it.]
Don't, because I'm not in the picture.
[Even you...]
Don't upload it.
- Follow me!
- Make sure you upload it!
[I just wanted to
commemorate this moment.]
[The final mission starts!]
I like the sound of it.
It's very awesome!
[For the real car racing...]
[Everything is set!]
[Everyone is holding their breath
on the racing circuit.]
[The lights start to signal
the start of the race.]
[Super-concentrated.]
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's win!
[Racing starts!]
Let's go!
Go, Jae Suk, go!
[The Gladiators started off faster!]
What's going on?
[The Gladiators pulled ahead.]
[We're faster!]
[We'll go ahead!]
We were fast!
[After the first straight course,
they enter the first corner.]
[This is a battle for control!]
[A smooth cornering.]
[A semi-professional race car driver,
Yoo Hyuk uses the apex.]
Jae Suk!
[He started a bit late,
but he's catching up at the corner.]
[The Gladiators secure the line.]
Drive properly!
[Jong Kook is pretty good at racing.]
[Driver Kkuk's fantastic driving skill.]
It's like a real car race!
[Finally, it's the hairpin section!]
Slowly, slowly!
Now speed up!
[They experience the
professional-class cornering for free!]
[They slowly feel motion sickness.]
[Consecutive corners.]
Put on the gas!
[Jae Suk has the most
serious face in a year.]
[The Gladiators don't let
the Merchants get control of the line.]
Defense! Defense!
[You're the best, Driver Kkuk!]
Get ahead!
[The Merchants have chased
right behind the Gladiators.]
[They look like they are
on a pirate ship ride.]
[Are you enjoying
in an amusement park?]
[Will they cast them behind?]
[They're right next to us!]
[At about the same time,
they arrive at the first gate.]
We're almost here!
[They arrive at the first gate
as they catch up!]
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Don't stop running!
[Drink and flip]
Drink it!
Wait until everyone is out of the car.
[Soda vs. water.]
Is it one person drinking them all?
It's not that easy.
Jae Suk!
[T.O.P succeeds at it.]
[The second runner Kkuk
drinks it all at once.]
[At that moment, Yoo Hyuk finishes it.]
We need to widen a gap here.
[Mr. Capable flips it easily.]
[While Tae Yang drinks...]
[Big-nose is suffering
from the carbonic acid.]
[Tae Yang flips it in one go.]
[Big-nose flips it on his first try, too.]
No, the other way.
[The Gladiators are a lot faster.]
[A fizzy attack!]
[The fourth runner, GD completes it.]
[Dae Sung and Seung Ri
are the only ones left.]
Pretend it's beer!
[Dae Sung, his finger is too tight.]
You almost did it!
Why can't I do it?
Ji Hyo!
Please!
[Dae Sung succeeds at it.]
[The last runner, Seung Ri.]
[Is there hope?]
Kwang Soo!
[Seung Ri did it on the first try.]
[The Gladiators complete
the first mission.]
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
- We have more games left.
- What the next one?
- Are you okay?
- Fasten your seat belt!
Bye!
[Envy]
- We won.
- It feels nice!
Very good!
It's a good start.
Can we get the car ready?
[The last runner Ha Ha, succeeds at it.]
This is crazy!
[As soon as they get in,
the chase resumes!]
[Stop there!]
It's right there.
[The second gate is at the end
of the straight section.]
Ji Yong?
Ji Yong will do it.
['The Abacus racing']
Just one person needs to get out.
Run, Ji Yong!
[Finish the straight course
on abacuses!]
[Wobble]
They just arrived.
Are they finished and leaving?
[the Merchants arrive
at the second gate.]
Get out, Gary!
Are they here already?
Fight!
[Good luck, GD!]
Fight, Gary!
You can do it!
Faster!
[Huh?]
[He's fast!]
Wow, Gary is really fast!
[Are you looking at me?]
- You can do it!
- He's winning!
[He crosses the finish line
and displays his showmanship.]
Get in!
[Again, the Gladiators pass
the second gate first.]
What's next?
Is that for five people?
Isn't the next one for five people?
They are blocking us!
Good job, Gary!
[Gary's finishing spurt with his scream.]
You're almost done!
[The Gladiators make
a detour and depart.]
- Please, Gary!
- Just a little more!
[The king of abacus
finishes at the second gate.]
[They didn't go that far.]
Gary, you caught up a lot.
Let's go, let's go!
- We're good!
- This is very thrilling!
This is in manual mode,
what's wrong with it?
It changed to manual shift.
Will it stay on the second gear
from now on?
[Can we trust Jong Kook?]
I need to change, it's on drive now!
[While the Gladiators
are in confusion...]
[He drastically makes a sharp curve.]
[He skillfully passes
the s-shaped course.]
[The Gladiators arrive at
the third gate first.]
Who should get off?
[At that moment]
[They've caught up.]
Everyone, get out except Jae Suk.
[They will be able to turn
the game around.]
Let's go!
['The Flagpole teamwork']
Long flagpoles are ours.
We have short poles, right?
What are we supposed to do?
Grab one of each.
- Which direction should we go?
- To the right!
To the right!
We'll go to the right!
I grabbed it.
- Calm down!
- One, two...
One, two, three!
- They're too short!
- Fight!
One, two, three!
[Five times straight?]
Kwang Soo!
Move the pole for the next person.
One, two, three.
[They did it for the first time.]
[This is nice!]
[Second time!]
It's very nice!
Tilt the pole!
- Very nice!
- We can do it!
Don't leave your hand
until the very last moment!
- That's it!
- We did it!
One more time!
One, two, three!
[We know how!]
- One, two, three!
- We can do it!
Focus!
[They need to do it
two times straight.]
[Acrobatic move.]
One more time!
- Calm down.
- Focus!
Last one!
[Both teams need to
succeed one more time.]
[Win or lose?]
[Their last jump.]
[Which team will depart first?]
[They fail.]
One, two, three?
[What about the Gladiators?]
[Grab!]
We did it!
[They did it five times straight.]
[The Merchants have to start over.]
Concentrate on it!
Okay, we did it!
[They're lucky because
the Merchants picked 'short'.]
It's so tiring.
[Good luck.]
One, two, three!
We still have time!
What happened?
[They are at hairpin section again.]
[Jong Kook, don't push it too hard.]
[I'll show it to my brothers!]
[A flowing parabolic cornering.]
- Very good.
- We're almost here!
That's the wall?
They look very thick.
- Just two more!
- Very good!
One, two, three!
[They managed to finish
it five times in a low.]
[Busy, busy!]
[There's no time to lose!]
[He immediately accelerates the car!]
[They arrive at the hairpin section.]
[The car gets a brush with the bumps.]
[Yoo Hyuk's bold handling.]
[He drives like an expert.]
Do we have to break it down?
How?
[They bump into the wall.]
[It's not shaky at all.]
It doesn't move at all!
[To drop the small knapsack,
they need to repeat is numerous times.]
Do they need to make it drop?
Let me do it, T.O.P.
[At that moment, the Merchants
arrive at the fourth gate.]
It won't be easy!
What do we need to do?
[It's not too late!]
You need to break it down.
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo, go!
Get in the driver seat, Ha Ha.
[Maybe it's easier for the big knapsack.]
[Kkuk attacks the bottom.]
[Both knapsack didn't move a bit.]
[We will win!]
[Tiger's second charge!]
It dropped!
[The small knapsack drops first!]
[I'm sorry, T.O.P!]
- They did it!
- Hurry up and get back!
[The other wall collapsed, too.[
Hurry up!
Kwang Soo, hurry up!
[In a rush]
They picked theirs up, too.
Ha Ha, take the bundle from him.
Give it to me and drive.
Just throw it!
Let's go!
[To the last mission, go!]
[Speed up!]
We need to get in the 'Back-To Car.'
[What a fierce chase!]
- What's the last one?
- This was the last one.
Oh, the five people...
we need to get in the small car
and travel though time!
[The Speed Race, the last mission!]
[All the team members
must get into the 'Back-To Car'!]
[The Gladiators are ahead.]
[But the Merchants are behind them.]
[Maximum speed]
Drive faster!
Where do I need to go?
What's wrong with the road?
It's almost over.
It's just a car race.
[I see them!]
[After passing this curvy course,
there's the last gate!]
[The Gladiators enter into
the last straight section.]
[The Merchants chase them fiercely.]
That car over there!
We're here!
We need to get in the car!
Get ready to get out.
[Every second counts!]
[Which team...]
[will arrive at the fifth gate first?]
[The Gladiators get there first!]
Get out!
We'll get out first!
Let's go!
[Now, it's a running contest by foot!]
[After being the passengers the whole time,
everyone is running all of a sudden!]
[All the team members get in the car,
this car goes back to the past!]
[The Gladiators preoccupy the good spots.]
[Are they playing
'Ring Around the Rosie'?]
Push them out!
Open the door!
[No way!]
Get in!
[Five members of the
Gladiators got into the car.]
[They can go back to the past
only if Dae Sung gets in.]
- What about me?
- You can't go!
Jae Suk!
[In the confusion, Yoo Hyuk
grabs an opportunity.]
[Now, five members of the Merchants
are in the car as well!]
[Only these two are left out!]
[Inside the car, a fierce battle
for seats broke out!]
[A bloody fight for
going back to the past.]
Dae Sung, come to the driver's seat!
Dae Sung shakes off Kwang Soo
and finally gets in the car.
Go away!
[Giraffe's clinging strategy.]
[Giraffe's clinging tactic.]
Wait!
He's like a leech!
[Push!]
[Go away, Kwang Soo!]
[I want to go back to the pas...]
[Bye!]
Close the door!
The Gladiators are the winners!
[The Gladiators win
'The Time Track Race'!]
[Now...]
[Go back to the past!]
Let's go back to Rome!
[Let's go to the Gladiators'
hometown, Rome!]
Sparta!
[Are they really leaving?]
[We have no idea...]
[Back To The Past!]
Wait for us, we'll be back!
[That's how Big Bang
went back to the past...]
[Let's pretend they left, and
now they're back to the present!]
It's been three and a half years since
we've been on a show together.
It was really nice having fun together.
I was happy to be on a Korean TV show.
- What are you talking about?
- Are you a foreigner?
[They've been busy overseas.]
- Thanks to Jong Kook...
- Don't mention it!
I will protect Big Bang!
It's been a long time being
on a variety show.
I had so much fun
seeing my friends again.
Visit us more often.
I thought we were filming
'Family's Outing' for a second.
Invite us again.
I had so much fun.
I'll be back if you invite me again.
[Thank you for being with us
Team Big Bang!]
[We hope you keep on rolling!]
[In a village out of a fairy tale,
the real couples appear.]
- Honey!
- She's at her husband's work.
[Their life is a musical,
Kim So Hyun and Son Jun Hoo.]
- I can't watch it any longer!
- Brother in law!
[Byul, who came to get back
at her husband's enemy.]
[So Hyun is lost in between
her husband and his enemy.]
[A movie-like telepathy
between the real couples!]
- This is all fake!
- You never know what will happen to you!
[And the three men visit!]
[Song Joong Ki, Jo In Sung,
and Im Joo Hwan, ]
She likes him more!
[Love and War]
Subtitles by DramaFever