[Seoul Mannamui Gwangjang]
(the place of gatherings)
[A clear blue sky.]
What lovely weather!
It's autumn!
Please have a wonderful Thanksgiving!
We've invited guests that are
well suited with Thanksgiving.
- Who are they?
- Who came?
[Who will enjoy the day's amusement?]
Is it an idol?
[It's hard to tell.]
[The first guest is...]
[Eunhyuk.]
[Eunhyuk from Super Junior.]
[He's a notable idol and
an MC in the variety business.]
It's been a long time!
You got discharged, right?
[You got discharged?]
I'm going to the army, soon...
- Sorry.
- You confused him with Lee Teuk!
[He confused him with Lee Teuk...]
I'm so sorry.
I'll start my service in a month.
[He should have stayed quiet.]
- You're finally going.
- Yes, I'm going.
[He's going to the
army on October 13th.]
This is going to be my
last broadcast before I go.
I'll ask Eunhyuk.
All the guests today are supposedly
well suited for Thanksgiving.
Please tell us why you are
As a Thanksgiving gift,
people give anchovy gift sets...
[A national idol that
looks like an anchovy.]
It's Joo Hwan!
Introduce yourself
before coming out!
Why did you come out like this?
[The handsome and kind Im Joo Hwan,
the hottest actor.]
[His dramas are always a hit
when he lands the lead role!]
[From taking on the role
of a cute boyfriend]
[to acting as a
possessed murderer.]
Why are you well suited
for Thanksgiving?
I'm like a chestnut...
Chestnut?
- A chestnut?
- Chestnut?
What about a chestnut?
The more you peel...
[Runs]
[Who is this acting like
she's in a spy movie?]
[She charges]
Uh-uh!
[She is so charming.]
She scared me!
[The trot fairy, Hong Jin Young!]
[The pretty singer with a powerful voice!]
[And her charm is a bonus!]
[The Queen of Performances!]
- Jin Young, you!
- You!
Jong Kook can't really stand
stuff like that, do it for him.
- Which one?
- Jong Kook, you!
Jong Kook, you!
He acts like he doesn't,
but he likes it!
[Did I do well?]
Good job!
Jin Young is good.
[A human vitamin,
better than herbal medicine.]
It's done!
We're good.
Chestnut, anchovy,
and a real Thanksgiving gift.
[They're the perfect guests
for Thanksgiving.]
Jin Young needs to take
the chestnut and anchovy
and advertise.
As Thanksgiving is
just around the corner
you know how it is
to travel during the holidays.
- And there's traffic congestion.
- Traffic congestion!
The rest stop on a blocked highway
is like an oasis in the desert.
The first mission of the
"Thanksgiving Gift Set Race"
is the "Rest Stop Specialty Food Tour."
[Rest Stop Specialty Food Tour.]
- We'll eat something tasty?
- Udon!
- Udon, udon!
- There're so many dishes!
We'll take the Yeongdong Expressway.
That's one of my favorites.
You have a favorite?
There are a lot of tasty
dishes in Yeongdong.
Yes, there are.
There are specialty dishes
at each rest stop.
We will show you
five choices of dishes.
- That we can eat...
- Thanksgiving...
- Oh, it's Yongin Rest Stop!
- What's famous at Yongin?
There's a lot to eat there!
[Stone pot brown rice bibimbap
with soybean paste]
[Number one Bibimbap dish]
[picked at the 2013 dish contest.]
[Absorbed]
There are a lot of
people who stop by Yong-In.
Deok-pyeong is famous!
[Specialty dish at
Deok-pyeong rest stop.]
[Beef rice soup]
That's really good!
[The number one selling dish
in the whole country.]
[A popular dish that sold
369,000 bowls in one year.]
[You have to eat this
at the Yeoju rest stop!]
Homemade pork cutlet!
That's so good!
- This is really good!
- It's so good!
[The fried batter, the meat and
the sauce are a perfect harmony.]
[It calls for 70,000
people every year.]
It just looks so appetizing.
- Hoeng-seong!
- It's premium beef!
- Isn't it rice soup?
- Premium beef!
[Grilled short rib patty steak.]
[The softness of the beef and
the aroma of the bell flower root.]
It's Premium beef
and bell flower root!
This is so good!
I've tried it!
[Grand prize award at
the 2009 dish contest.]
- It's Pyeong-chang!
- In Kangwondo!
- Oh, this is good!
- This is so delicious!
[Shiitake mushroom and pond snail
soybean paste soup.]
It depends on each rest stop!
[The mushroom and pond snail
steals your appetite.]
You have to pick one
out of the five.
And you just have to
go and eat the dish.
Really?
As you can see, there are only
three meal tickets per dish.
First, line up behind the
dish you want to eat.
Really?
I can't decide...
- I want to eat the rice soup.
- You can take a look.
What should I have?
[The grilled short rib
patty steak is popular.]
[Five people chose it.]
This looks good,
but this also looks good...
I'm going crazy!
Pork cutlet is also really good.
Jong Kook, come here!
Let's eat pork cutlet!
[Why did you pick
the one he doesn't like...]
[She controls him with strength
when it doesn't work with words.]
Just eat pork cutlet!
I can't eat alone!
- Should I go alone?
- I don't eat pork cutlet!
- Let's eat it!
- Eat pork cutlet at Namsan!
I'll slice it for you!
[She launches her charm.]
[They automatically smile.]
Okay, okay.
I'll be your match-maker!
[He jumps in every time
he senses a romantic vibe.]
It never works out when
there's someone like him!
It won't work out!
Please go away!
I'll make sure you'll be too shy
to stare at each other's faces!
[Not doing anything
is being helpful...]
Even when you see lock eyes
by chance, I'll make you look away.
[You're so silly!]
We can't see Eunhyuk
because you guys are too tall!
Take care of Eunhyuk!
He'll be gone in a month!
Come here, Eunhyuk!
I need to be on TV, a lot.
Let's eat, the three of us.
[The team Kwang Soo went to
is Kkuk and Jin Young's team...]
You are so dull!
If Kwang Soo joins, it's over.
Kwang Soo needs to stay.
I was the third wheel
in this group all along!
What are you saying?
[He's getting angrier the
more he thinks about it.]
The three of us had meals before!
You invited me because it was awkward
with just the two of you?
There's something fishy!
Did you use me?
I thought you liked me!
[He's getting ahead of himself...]
Jin Young, you're too much!
As I said, there are
only three meal tickets.
Hong Jin Young and Kim Jong Kook
can take the first two.
Take one each.
Jong Kook's eating pork cutlet!
That's the power of love.
[Shy, embarrassed]
You need to play rock-paper-scissors
if there are four people.
Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Gary played scissors, by himself.]
Yeah!
You're disqualified.
- Pardon?
- That's a shame.
[He was the only one
who played scissors...]
He won by himself!
[The only one who plays
something different loses.]
- I want to go there!
- Gary, let's eat pork cutlet.
[Glare]
It's been five years
since Jong Kook did this!
[His first glare in five years...]
I don't want to go!
I'm so scared!
People think it's real!
It was too scary!
Gary, go to Yong-In!
So, Gary picked Yong-In
to eat the stone pot Bibimbap.
The four of you, please play
rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Oh my!]
[This can't be real...]
Is it Eunhyuk?
[I won, but I feel weird...]
Did you see him get
surprised after winning?
[They're having fun teasing him.]
[Eunhyuk is disqualified.]
Eunhyuk, let's have pork cutlet.
I do want to eat it...
Come, come, come!
How can he go when you're so scary?
[It's obvious that you
don't mean it...]
[Scratch, scratch]
Come on, come on.
[He wanted pork cutlet,
and he got permission.]
- You're so dull...
- What's wrong with you?
I'm not dull, but...
[It's my last show,
but it's so hard...]
Ji Hyo, can't you come with me?
- Can't I take Ji Hyo?
- I'll eat with Gary.
What are you guys doing?
- I can't eat alone...
- I was deciding between the two.
[Maybe it's because it's
the place of gatherings...]
There's love everywhere.
[The teams have been decided
for the Rest Stop Food Tour.]
[Ring, ring]
Hello?
- Jong Kook's wife!
- Sister!
Where are you, Jong Kook's wife?
Ha Ha and I talked about it,
but we support it.
Me, too!
Congratulations,
you've passed the audition!
You've passed the difficult
Kim Jong Kook audition.
Congrats!
Can I speak to Eunhyuk?
Hello?
Today's mission for you is
"make Jin Young
and Jong Kook fall in love."
I don't think I have to do anything...
Jin Young is very forward.
How's the atmosphere, there?
I feel like I'm third-wheeling.
Eunhyuk, when it's awkward
play the telepathy game
ask them questions like,
"do you like winter or summer?"
Should I try, now?
Goodbye, for now.
Okay, summer vs. winter?
One, two, three!
Summer!
[They got the same answer!]
The ocean vs. the mountains?
One, two, three!
- The ocean.
- They got the same answer!
Again?
[Telepathy match!]
Last one, black-bean noodle
or spicy seafood soup?
They got the wrong answer.
You guys can order both!
Jin Young can feed him!
[Yong-In rest stop.]
[Gary and Ji Hyo arrived first.]
Toast!
Croquette!
Should we eat everything?
It's going to be so delicious!
I was going to go on a diet,
from today.
No, you can't.
Stone pot brown rice bibimbap
with soybean paste!
- We need to eat that.
- Hello!
We don't do any missions, first?
Do we just eat?
There aren't any missions?
Yes, just eat first.
[For free, without any missions?]
That's suspicious...
You have to let us eat it,
without worry.
- Just have it, without worry!
- Really?
We'll the the famous...
Two stone pot brown rice bibimbap
with soybean paste, please.
[The perfect combination of fresh
vegetables and a warm stone pot.]
[A unique bibimbap with a
spoonful of soy bean paste.]
Gary, look!
[This is it!]
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
[Looks around]
Do we really just eat?
[This is unusual...]
Is it really okay?
I'm a little nervous...
Let's just eat, Ji Hyo!
Wow!
Is it good?
It's so good!
Should I try some?
- It's good, right?
- I can add more.
This paste is really good!
The soy bean paste is really good.
[How's this for your way back
home from Thanksgiving?]
But this soy bean paste
is incredible.
It's fits so well with this paste.
With the vegetables.
[Deok-pyeong rest stop.]
Let's go!
[Big Nose and Ha Ha
are ready to eat]
[the beef rice soup.]
Wow, it's amazing!
It's wonderful.
It's this!
It has "best" written next to it.
We need to eat the best!
[The rich flavor of the beef.]
[And some delicious toppings
for an appetizing texture.]
[One of the five delicacies
of the season.]
[They try it right away.]
How is it?
- It's rich.
- I can't wait!
[Wow!]
It's better than the
ones in the market.
- It's true.
- It is.
Okay, now
the highlight is the meat.
[Add the rice and meat,
half and half.]
And then add the radish kimchi.
To be honest, if this was sold in
my neighborhood,
I would eat it every day.
There are lots of times when you see
a fake reaction on TV and
end up disappointed, right?
Look at our real reaction.
This is 100 percent pure.
[Munch]
[An explosion of flavor.]
Don't overreact!
[The most honest
reaction in the world.]
[Feasting vs. spiritual possession]
- I got the shivers.
- What kind of a reaction is that?
You try.
I don't overreact!
- I didn't overreact.
- I don't overreact.
[Forget overreacting Ha Ha,
Big Nose is going to show you.]
[This taste is!]
[What is that?]
[They can taste the cows'
life force inside their mouth.]
[They're experiencing a whole
new world with the rich flavor.]
[This is a miracle...]
This makes you crazy...
Wow, I'm not overreacting.
[They act like nothing
happened after all that...]
I'm so embarrassed...
[The spiciness added to the broth,
the best food is born.]
[Yeoju rest stop.]
Let's go!
[Kkuk, Jin Young, Eunhyuk
came to eat pork cutlet.]
- What would you like?
- Pork cutlet.
Homemade, homemade,
homemade pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlet?
- Yes, please.
All three of us will have it.
[Not frozen pork cutlet,
but freshly fried.]
[The harmony of the crunchy
texture and the sweet sauce.]
[One of the five delicacies
of the season.]
Wow, that looks delicious!
The pork cutlet looks amazing!
[Let's see, the spoons...]
- Do we just eat?
- Thanks.
[She takes care of his spoon.]
Do we just eat?
[What about me?]
- I said I would slice it for you.
- No, it's okay.
I will slice it for you!
[Is my sincerity nothing to you?]
I'll do it!
Is this yours or mine?
Yours.
[We got married vs. I live alone.]
[She carefully takes a piece...]
Say ah!
[So charming]
Jin Young...
[Cute, cute]
I'm okay.
[It's okay, I'm not going to look...]
It's really good, right?
- Isn't it good?
- It is.
The reason why it's so good
is the generous quantity,
first of all.
And the meat is really thick.
[And with the sweet sauce, the rest
stop's popular pork cut let is born.]
[She's very frugal in putting the
leftover sauce on her last piece.]
She eats really well.
I'm curious on what
we're going to do now...
[We're curious...]
[on when we're arriving...]
[They haven't even arrived yet.]
[The team that went to the closest
rest stop already finished eating.]
I'm so full.
If you are a couple, there's a role for
the boyfriend at times like this.
[He gets up without saying a word.]
[Then he pours water
that they'll drink.]
[And the water must not
be too cold or too hot.]
[Then hand her the glass, casually.]
[Then she says, in return...]
Gary!
You drank some on the way!
No, I didn't!
It's only half full!
[If there's too little,
she might misunderstand.]
Thank you for the meal.
- Did you eat well?
- Yes.
So starting now,
we will explain the rules.
- The rules?
- Yes.
As Thanksgiving is
around the corner
we told you that there's the
"Rest Stop Specialty Food Tour"
and "Thanksgiving Gift Set Race."
You need a team for the
"Thanksgiving Gift Set Race."
- Yes.
- That's right.
You need to choose your teams.
You mean the members?
You need to choose your own teams.
The members that have selected
the same rest stop will
be the primary team.
And until the next mission which
is in Gangneung, Gyeongpo Beach
you have to make a team of five.
You need to make a team of five.
While you travel, you might throw away
a member or be thrown away.
You could be thrown away.
If you are thrown away, there aren't
any other methods of transportation.
So you can hitchhike
to the next stop.
Really?
In a random car?
I'm shy with strangers!
But, even if you hitchhike
other teams can pick
you up on the way.
Why are you explaining that to me!
I'm just explaining, because you
said you're shy of strangers.
I am shy of strangers...
The three of us, at least...
shouldn't betray one another...
Okay, the three of us
shouldn't betray each other.
- It's five people, right?
- Yeah.
The three of us won't
betray each other!
This is how everyone
starts out, right?
Everyone?
Let's not betray each other.
Let's not do that.
Let's not separate.
Don't throw me away!
I can't trust you...
All of a sudden?
After having this together?
It's me!
[Come on, brother!]
- Yoo!
- Boo!
Cross!
- Rice!
- What?
- Soup!
Cross!
We met through rice soup.
The pure heart of Korean people!
The strength of Korea!
The ancient mystery!
Inside Grandma's arms!
Friendship!
We will never separate.
If you pictured us separating,
you are mistaken.
There's something thicker than blood,
and it is the rice soup!
- Rice!
- Soup!
Cross!
[The Yeoju rest stop team
are making a teammate recruiting list.]
Gary and Ji Hyo won't separate.
They're together, right now?
- They've kissed already.
- Really?
- At a performance, on stage.
They're pretty official, now.
- Really?
- For real?
They're real now...
Ha Ha's calling!
- Jong Kook.
- Why?
- Have you eaten?
- Yeah, I did.
I ate as well.
Did you hear about the rule?
Yeah, I heard.
What should I do?
Sorry, but I don't think
you guys are of any help.
I'll be straightforward.
If Suk Jin and I are together,
it won't be of any help.
But if one of us goes,
it'll be helpful.
[Disloyal Ha Ha is at it again...]
- Just you?
- Why do you think it's both of us?
Then you can come!
I'll go to Yeoju!
- Okay then, we'll wait for you.
- Yes.
- Bye.
[What is Big Nose
doing at this time?]
[Big Nose is also calling.]
Suk Jin!
How many of you are there?
Have you eaten?
We're still on our way.
We're going to Hoeng-seong.
- Still?
- Yes.
Anyway, after you eat,
there will be more to talk about.
I'll call you later!
Okay!
Bye.
There's something going on!
[What's happening around us?]
Jong Kook's calling me.
- What's going on?
- What is this?
Hi, Jong Kook!
Where are you?
We're still on our way.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Well, enjoy your meal.
You know that I always want
to be with you, right?
[Why is he confessing
all of a sudden?]
Jong Kook, what's going on?
Just eat, and we'll talk again.
- Okay, I'll call you back!
- Okay.
Bye!
What's going on?
There's no detail.
[They're curious after
the phone calls.]
I don't feel so bad...
Why is everyone calling us?
What is it?
[The Monday Couple are
having a rest stop date.]
- Do you want to play baseball?
- Yeah.
- Ah, oh my!
- Just hold the bat!
- Just hold it!
- It's too fast!
Hold the bat!
You can do it!
Just hit one!
Wow!
- Just hit one!
- I hit it!
- Again!
- Wow!
[This time, it's basketball!]
Go, go!
[The ball is my friend.]
[I am not lonely
as long as I have a ball.]
Wow!
Ji Hyo, I have a cramp...
Really?
Ow... ow...
- I don't have it.
- Ji Hyo...
She changed.
If it was a long time ago,
she would have given me a massage.
[The touch of an angel.]
An ugly guy like me
with no game
met a pretty girl...
Yes, have some.
[I want to have some
coffee and talk a while.]
[Maybe we can get closer, today...]
Knock, knock!
[Here's your coffee.]
[Can I come closer to you, today?]
[Lock]
Ji Hyo!
[Locked the door]
[What is this situation...]
- Ji Hyo!
- I just locked the door.
Ji Hyo!
I don't know what to do now.
Who are you calling?
Ji Hyo!
[The faces of betrayal,
Big Nose and Ha Ha.]
[Five minutes ago]
It's so hot!
[Her phone rang
when she was by herself.]
Ji Hyo!
Yes?
Are you on your way with Gary?
He's in the bathroom...
Oh... just come by yourself!
Really?
Where to?
Let's meet at the Yeoju rest stop.
- Do I just go?
- Yes, just come.
Ji Hyo, don't think about it!
The Gods have given you this chance!
And then you can
meet up again, after.
It'll give Gary the chance
to be filmed more.
He's here.
Lock the door!
Hurry!
[She eventually falls
into their trap...]
[Shut the door.]
Ji Hyo!
I locked the door.
[She fell into our trap!]
- I locked the door.
- Yeah.
Then get in the driver's seat.
Wait.
Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, don't joke around!
You're so silly!
- I got in the driver's seat!
- Good job!
That's amazing!
It's like a scene in the movies.
[He still doesn't
understand the situation!]
- Are you going to drive?
- I put my seat belt on!
You're amazing, Ji Hyo!
No, don't pull it!
If you betray me...
I'll have no one left to
trust in this world...
[She's so moved...]
[but the pedal was also moved.]
Song Ji Hyo!
[Is she really running away?]
Open it, let's go!
Ji Hyo, let's go!
[She's not joking!]
Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo!
[Newest member of
the betrayal club, Song Ji Hyo.]
[Don't go, Song Ji Hyo!]
I actually left him, for real!
I really drove away!
Come to Yeoju...
Do you want to come to
the Deok-pyeong rest stop?
Where are you?
I'm at the Yong-In rest stop.
- How long does it take from there?
- 11 kilometers!
Hurry up!
Come to Deok-pyeong!
- Okay!
- Okay, bye!
I came without Kang Gary...
What do I do?
[Desolate future]
[He got back stabbed by Blank Ji.]
It's a new feeling being
betrayed by her...
Then I have to hitchhike!
I've only seen this in the movies!
What do I do...
[The Kkuk-Hong couple and Eunhyuk
are at the Yeoju rest stop.]
The three of us aren't
betraying each other, right?
- Of course!
- Let's not betray each other.
- Yes.
- Of course!
There's no reason to betray
an ace like Eunhyuk.
I really like this team.
I think we're perfect...
- Really?
- I really like the three of us.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I think we should be careful...
Ha Ha's calling!
[Ha Ha said he would
come without Suk Jin...]
- Yeah?
- Right now...
We have Suk Jin, Ji Hyo,
and I as a team.
So we're waiting for Ji Hyo.
She only has 2 kilometers left.
Okay.
If you decide quickly,
we can make the perfect team.
Let me just let you know
that you're on speaker phone.
Why would you put
me on speaker phone?
I instinctively did it...
[There's no place like here.]
- Ha Ha!
- You have no manners!
Yes, Jong Kook's wife!
Ha Ha, don't do that.
Jin Young...
- Are you on speaker?
- Do something with Eunhyuk...
Ji Hyo's here!
[Betrayal Blank Ji enters
Deok-pyeong rest stop.]
- Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo, you did well!
- Here, get in here.
- What do I do?
Jong Kook!
Ji Hyo just arrived!
- Ji Hyo is with you?
- Yeah.
- Okay...
- We'll go to Yeoju...
Okay, just come here then.
Okay, bye.
This is no joke!
Their teamwork is awesome,
but when they start shooting...
I can't trust "Running Man" members...
The three of us won't
betray each other.
Okay, Eunhyuk?
You're the most suspicious!
You're a "Running Man" member, too!
No, the three of us
will never turn coat.
For real.
- Wow, I just...
- Why?
Honestly, I want to
go to the bathroom...
but I can't leave your side.
I really want to go but...
It's so scary.
Since you came to join us,
our plan is
to take Jong Kook and Jin Young
and ditch Eunhyuk..
Then, it'll be five people.
Period.
Hurry up.
Do you want to get in this car?
Wait, I'll get some stuff.
What do I do?
Kang Gary looked really puzzled.
[A betrayal newbie Blank Ji
can't forget about Gary.]
Ji Hyo, do you want to go now?
[Just the two of us...]
Lock the door.
[Haroro...]
[What are you going to do?]
Do you have a phone?
[Team Leader Ha's getting ready to...]
We bought a lot of stuff...
What's going on?
It shouldn't be...
[Yes, it should be.]
Look at you two!
Suk Jin, It took...
less than five seconds.
Wait, wait.
Suk Jin...
It didn't even take me five seconds.
Ji Hyo, look!
I was getting some pastries for you.
Wait.
Seriously...
Come on!
I know it's funny.
It's very fun.
[The taste of betrayal.]
It's very fun, I know that.
You know, betrayal is...
- This is funny!
- I'm Ha Ha.
- What should I do?
- Ji Hyo, wait.
If we leave Ha Ha here...
It'll be five people
if we two of us go to Yeoju.
Yeoju?
We can go to Pyeongchang, too.
- Will it be five at Pyeongchang?
- Either Yeoju or Pyeongchang.
We can go anywhere.
[Where should we go?]
- I was going to give this to you.
- Dong Hun...
Now that I think about it...
It'll be complex if we let you in.
If you don't get in,
we'll be set for either teams.
Get out!
[Quick-witted Haroro
gets ready to move.]
[Big Nose and Ji Hyo in on the way.]
Hurry up, hurry up.
We need to go to Yeoju.
[Haroro's speedy race
to Yeoju Rest Stop.]
Seriously...
- Dong Hun?
- Listen, Jong Kook.
I was betrayed while
I was changing cars!
What?
I'm all by myself.
I was betrayed!
Just include me in your team.
It's no joke.
"Running Man" members are scary.
It took me five seconds
for me to change the car.
I was getting my phone...
then they locked the door.
I'm going there by myself.
I'll take Gary, too.
Let's just make a team of five.
Can you promise me?
- Don't refuse me!
- It's perfect.
I didn't betray them.
Don't refuse me, Jong Kook!
- I see, are you coming here?
- Yes, I'm on my way!
Okay, I see.
- Okay, I love you, Jong Kook!
- Okay.
[Wait and see...
How dare you betray me?]
[Hoengseong Rest Area]
Thank you for the driving!
[While the others are
busy betraying each other]
[Jae Suk's team arrive
at the rest area they chose.]
[Let's taste grilled
short rib patty steak!]
You'll have to wait about three minutes
before the food is ready.
I'll tell you why others
keep calling you.
Why is that?
You'll select your own team member.
If you make a team of five,
that'll be your final team.
[That's why they kept calling us.]
You might throw away
a member or be thrown away.
If you are thrown away, you need to
hitchhike to get to the next mission site.
Hitchhiking?
[I thought it was a food tour,
but it's a war!!]
[I should keep my mind clear...]
[I don't want to "hitchhike."]
[Just like this.]
Do you go to Yeoju Rest Stop
by any chance?
[He's busy looking for
a car in the street.]
Are any of you going to Yeoju Rest Stop?
[Kang Gary's hitchhiking.]
[Please, please, please...]
Do you go to Yeoju Rest Stop
by any chance?
Can you drop me over there?
[Nod, nod]
Are you sure?
Thank you so much!
[Honking]
I'm sorry!
Let's get in!
Thank you, thank you so much!
You can start driving.
I'm sorry.
[Thank you for letting us in!]
Thank you so much!
You know Song Ji Hyo...
betrayed me and left me here.
[It brings me tears again.]
I never knew she would
betray me like this.
I don't have money...
[He feels a bit awkward...]
I should be the one driving...
but I can't drive other people's car.
- Because there's no insurance.
- You mean this car?
No, I mean the insurance doesn't cover
the other person driving.
[He feels awkward and
hears things wrong.]
It's such nice weather for driving.
Yes.
I'm so sorry...
[Hitchhiking., It's different from
what I've seen in the movies.]
[Jae Suk's team is about to eat now.]
It's here!
Thank you so much!
That looks good!
Oh, my!
They give us soup, too.
Isn't that nice, Jae Suk?
More than anything...
thank you for the food!
[Fantastic visual]
It looks somewhat nostalgic.
This soup is good!
It's incredible!
Wow!
Try eating it with kimchi.
[You can enjoy steak at a rest stop.]
[Jong Kook's team is
waiting for others to arrive.]
It's about time for them to get here.
Let's wait a bit longer.
I feel listless since we ate.
Do you want to take a nap?
Are you okay?
- Take a nap.
- No, I'm fine.
You're going to leave me
when I take a nap.
No, it's not that.
No, we need a woman in the team.
Why would I want to leave you?
- They're here!
- Are they?
Gary's here.
- He's here.
- Gary!
She abandoned me!
I heard about it.
Are you alone?
- I was abandoned.
- Where's Ha Ha?
He's on the way, too.
- How many cars do we have?
- I can do anything today!
- Let's just go by our car.
- I'm serious!
Today, it's Kim Jong Kook
and the boys again!
It's been a while.
- What's that, is it Ha Ha?
- How does he have a car?
Why do we have so many cars?
- Maybe he ditched them.
- No, he was ditched.
Where did you get the car?
I brought my team's car.
Ji Hyo was next to me
but she kept going.
She must have talked to Jae Suk.
Oh, Suk Jin went in Ji Hyo's car?
- It's simple, let's make a team.
- It's five people.
Wow!
We made a team!
I'm in, seriously!
Eunhyuk couldn't
even go to the bathroom.
Let's just go to the bathroom together.
Hold your hands like this.
Seriously?
You can stay outside
with me over there.
I wanted to go to the bathroom, too.
Don't go anywhere!
I was getting some snacks for the team.
Oh, you were getting the snacks?
Yes, I took it from the car,
then the door was locked.
Ji Hyo, we're a team now.
We can go to Gangneung now.
Let's go to Gangneung!
To Gangneung!
[Five vs. five]
[What will be their next mission?]
[Pyeongchang to Gangneung]
[Gyeongpo Beach]
[The final mission
site, Gyeongpo Beach]
The cloud looks like a cotton candy.
That looks like a picture!
It's so beautiful!
[Jae Suk's team arrives
at Gyeongpo Beach.]
Geongpo Beach is famous for pine trees.
[They're wearing a uniform.]
Let's get out!
- Let's go!
- We have a good teamwork!
The wind is nice!
It's so pretty.
Look at the color of the ocean!
It's been a long while
since I've been to Gyeongpo Beach.
It's beautiful!
[Under the high sky of autumn,
it's an emerald sea.]
It's really nice to be here.
It's so pretty!
- I love it!
- It's perfect weather, too!
It just looks like a picture!
Don't put the food in direct sunlight!
- Because I'm going to take them.
- I really want it!
Avoid direct light!
Look at the ginseng!
Dried persimmon!
[Korean beef, ginseng,
dried yellow corvina, and on.]
They even have ginseng!
All the gifts on the table
will be given out at this site.
[The gifts on the table
will be given out at this site.]
Not all nine of them are games.
There's a bonus in there.
It's a surprising gift.
Tell us what letter you want to flip.
A gift is written on the back.
Then, you will have
a match for the gift.
Suk Jin wants to choose first.
It's Korean beef rib gift set!
From the beginning,
we have everyone's favorite!
It's big!
The first game is
"Steal the full moon."
Two reps will face each other
and put a tube in the middle.
On my signal, you can pull the tube
until you reach the line at the end.
Isn't this unfair?
We won!
[It's a power game!]
[Mom, we'll have
Korean beef for dinner!]
[We love Korean beef, too.]
Eunhyuk is good at playing sports.
- Isn't it more of a power game?
- He's thin.
You know, people play
with tubes at the beach.
[Im Joo Hwan, Song Ji Hyo, Lee Kwang Soo]
[Kim Jong Kook, Hong Jin Young, Ha Ha]
["Steal the full moon"]
Begin!
Runners, please come forward.
[Im Joo Hwan vs. Kim Jong Kook]
I knew it.
[From the first round,
it's a big match!]
- Joo Hwan, don't try to win.
- Just give up, if you can't.
You're not our wild card.
[Don't forget to stay healthy!]
I think he'll try.
[I can't give it up that easily.]
Don't push yourself too much!
He doesn't give up easily.
The possibility of you
winning the game is lower.
The best thing possible is
that you can pick up the tube
in a flash and run with it.
It'll be fantastic, if you win.
You need to do it fast!
Get ready
[I've been hiding all along]
[but deep inside my heart,
I'm really competitive.]
[The seal is broken!]
[Im Joo Hwan vs. Kim Jong Kook]
Start!
[Mr. Capable is dragged.]
[Unbelievable!]
[Power!]
I can't believe this!
- Joo Hwan!
- What's going on?
[Why is he so strong?]
[I told you, the seal is broken!]
[Mr. Capable, I'll defeat...]
[Oh snap!]
[Joo Hwan drags Mr. Capable again.]
[Neck and neck]
- Wow, Joo Hwan is so strong!
- With Jong Kook...
[The unsealed desire for victory,
give me strength again!]
[Today, I'll defeat Mr. Capable...]
[He enters into combat mode.]
It's been a while seeing
Jong Kook doing his best.
Joo Hwan!
[No, I can't lose like this!]
Joo Hwan, you're wearing pink!
[Pink underpants!]
Bury your feet in the sand!
[His legs gave way
while he laughed away.]
[The power of pink gets
rid of his desire in a second.]
He has a cramp!
- You have a cramp, right?
- It's fine, now.
Wow, Joo Hwan is strong!
I told you not to push yourself.
[If my underpants were not pink...]
It's embarrassing!
Don't try to win!
Jong Kook seemed surprised.
It's been a while.
He was really ambitious.
I could feel it while I was playing.
Ha Ha and I should've been the players.
Jin Young is not an easy opponent.
We'll only win if
Jin Young wins this round.
Don't put so much pressure on me!
Don't do that!
Isn't this too close to that side?
It's too close.
Measure it by walking.
Chan Hee is right here.
It should be here.
No, it's right here.
[Cameraman: To the right.]
[Right there, okay!]
- He said okay.
- No.
The cameraman said it's here!
[Go away!]
[Don't stop me!]
He said it's here.
Why are you...
[You can see something like this
when people play "Go stop."]
Let's just believe in Ji Hyo.
[They've changed the location
of the tube for the second round.]
- Get ready!
- You should win, Ji Hyo!
I've only slept for two hours.
Ji Hyo only slept for ten hours, too.
Compared to her regular habits,
it's like she pulled an all-nighter.
Do you study these days, Ji Hyo?
She has insomnia.
Ready, set, go!
That's good, Jin Young!
[Jin Young strikes first.]
No, Ji Hyo!
[She gave everything from the beginning.]
[But it's not that easy to
win against the Ace.]
- Very good, Ji Hyo!
- It's a close game!
It's nip and tuck.
Good, pull Ji Hyo!
[She doesn't miss the chance
and uses all the strength she has.]
No, it won't do!
[The Energizer takes a firm stand.]
Ji Hyo is so strong!
Ji Hyo is really strong!
Wait, wait, brother, mommy!
[The absolute power manages
to put the young spirit to sleep.]
You never know.
[The second round:
Song Ji Hyo wins!]
Ji Hyo's so strong!
[I'm sorry, Jin Young.]
Thank you.
- It's fine.
- It's not that you're weak.
- Ji Hyo never disappoints me.
- You're a bull, Ji Hyo.
She only slept for ten hours.
The Song of "Song Ji Hyo"
is for "Songaji." (calf)
- Ji Hyo is really strong!
- Awesome!
Next players!
We'll win this!
It's Kwang Soo and Ha Ha.
- Kwang Soo!
- Good luck!
- What strategy could he have?
- You can do it!
Think about the Korean beef set!
- Kwang Soo, lower your position.
- Play it fair, Kwang Soo!
Ready, set, go!
[Hops]
[Ha Ha's sudden jump]
[He puts his body inside the tube
and go forward.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Watch your hands!
[What are they doing?]
Kwang Soo, just run!
Just run!
[They're spraying their saliva.]
Stop it!
It's disgusting!
If you keep doing it,
we'll take away the gift.
[They stop their match.]
- Warning, warning!
- They spit on each other.
Ready, set, go!
[The rematch starts.]
[Ha Ha jump into the tube again.]
[I won't be fooled by the same trick.]
That's good!
[The last match for the beef rib set.]
[We can't lose!]
Why are you doing it to that extent?
- It's over!
- Rib!
[That rib is mine!]
Just endure it!
Kwang Soo wins!
[Jae Suk's team acquires
the Korean beef rib set.]
- They did their best.
- White team gets the Korean beef set.
Let's get it all!
- Pick a letter, please.
- Get it from the first row.
- "Jeul"
- Dried persimmon!
What's the game?
The second game is "The Radish
Full Moon on Your Forehead."
You put a pickled radish on
your forehead and eat it fast.
We've played it before.
- Do we all play together?
- It'll be a relay race.
It's a relay?
Who's good at it?
Ji Hyo, you want to go first?
Ready!
Do I put it over here?
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
Ready, set, go!
[The Radish Full Moon, starts!]
I'll hold the hat for you.
[Mr. Capable eats it in three seconds.]
He already ate it.
He's good at everything!
Ji Hyo, it's okay.
Don't do it in a hurry.
Slowly, slowly.
It's okay, just do it bold!
[Ji Hyo succeeded.]
[Big Nose is the second runner.]
Suk Jin, good!
[Frowning]
Squint your eyes!
This is so hard!
It's caught by his big nose!
[Big Nose succeeded.]
Don't stick out your tongue!
Lower your head!
Seriously, this drives me crazy!
[Eunhyuk becomes the black hole
of Jong Kook's team.]
Bend your brows!
[Will he be able to do it today?]
[He fails again.]
[He passes it to Gary for now.]
Eunhyuk didn't do it.
[It's easy if you give up your image.]
Gary's face!
- It's working!
- It's there!
[Yum]
It's almost there!
It's done!
Next!
It's a tie!
[He's still handsome.]
[He finished in a flash.]
Last one!
- Victory is ours!
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
Hey, Kwang Soo!
Be bold!
Why is he so slow?
[While Kwang Soo is struggling]
[Eunhyuk successfully gets it.]
You're almost there!
Go!
[Both teams are on
their last player.]
[We can't let them win, now!]
[Jae Suk's team won
the Radish Full Moon.]
[Jae Suk's team won twice in a row.]
[That radish...]
[Triumphant]
Give it to them!
It's fine!
[They won the dried persimmons.]
Aren't we giving him
too much stress?
He bags are all the way down...
Eunhyuk...
We've never won this much with
Jong Kook as our opponent.
Overpowering.
[Uncomfortable]
It's like a tsunami of victory
just crashed into our side.
We're just so overpowering!
- It happens once in a lifetime.
- Okay, I got it.
[Enjoy while you still can.]
[Jong Kook's counterattack
has begun!]
[Save the flag in the sand castle.]
Nice, nice!
[Jong Kook's team got
their first victory.]
[Multi-vitamins]
[The Giant Hoop game.]
[Thanks to Jin Young's
active participation]
[they won twice in a row.]
[I can't let them just win.]
[Knocking down cans,
wearing a yo-yo on the can.]
[Joo Hwan got them all, in a flash.]
[Jae Suk's team is
in the lead once again.]
[They're opening the last letter.]
[Giving my gift, while smiling.]
Okay!
- Here, take it.
- With both hands!
Please!
Kwang Soo, you give it.
[Here you go.]
[Awkward smile]
He's smiling!
[Pat, pat]
[They got the dried
persimmons, anyway.]
That's the joy of sharing.
It's really nice,
being able to share.
We won't be playing any more games.
But we did bring those
to give them out.
Should we go one last
round with all of those?
One last round with all of those!
With everything!
- Let's just do all of them!
- With the remaining sets!
[Deal]
You can play rock-paper-scissors,
or whatever you like.
[With this game]
[we're taking all of that?]
Let's see who can
kick their shoes far!
That's a good idea!
- Let's do that.
- That's a good idea!
Let's kick it far!
Start from this line.
- Do you want to bet all at once?
- Yes!
- At once?
- Just do it at once.
Okay!
[There's Korean beef left.]
Let's take turns!
We'll do it now.
Why don't you go first, Jong Kook?
[Kick your shoes
as far as possible!]
This is the last chance
to win the prize.
You're not going to
complain about it later, right?
Of course, winner takes it all.
- Let's do it!
- I'll do it first.
- Gary!
- I shouldn't take off my socks.
I'll do it now!
[The team who throws a shoe
the farthest can win all of them.]
[Gary's shoe flies in an arc.]
You should fly it in the beginning.
[Gary strikes it first.]
[Jae Suk's team's
first runner is Jae Suk.]
It's too high!
[He's throwing it high.]
[The mental attack!]
They're attacking us with reactions.
That's how you play it?
I see.
[Jong Kook's team's
third runner is Ha Ha.]
[It flies and lands right
next to Gary's shoe.]
[Ha Ha and Gary have
the highest score.]
Kwang Soo!
We should've played
this kind of game before.
Kwang Soo, go!
You need to throw it low!
He's so ugly.
[Stops]
You've been always ugly.
Don't be surprised.
Look at the long stride.
I hate it.
That's right!
[It's stopped by the camera.]
Oh, no!
There's a camera!
[Unfortunate]
What's the camera doing there?
Who put the camera right there?
[Maybe it's the God of Variety...]
The camera was there
when we played, too.
[That's the part of the game!]
- It was stopped...
- Why did he throw at it?
Pay for the camera!
I think it could have
gone 20 meters further.
I think it could have gone to Seoul.
That's absurd!
Take it easy, Eunhyuk.
Just think of it as if you're
going to break the record.
I'll do it!
[I've waited this moment...]
[In no time, he was regarded
as a game black hole]
[at the Radish Full Moon game.]
Do it one more time!
[I will recover from
a losing position.]
[I suggested the
game that I'm good at.]
[I'll show you why
I picked this game now.]
[Fly!]
[It flew beyond the line.]
[A shoe missile divides the beach.]
[He's absolutely the winner.]
- Oh my god!
- Incredible!
Yes!
[Devastated]
[Thanks to Eunhyuk, Jong Kook's
team is close to the prize.]
You can be skilled at it?
Don't think about it.
Just throw it.
Suk Jin looks like
he's here for a picnic.
He's awful.
Can is this possible?
It looked like a butterfly.
My shoes are covering my ankles,
so I'll use a sandal.
[He's wearing indoor sandals.]
- Is it okay?
- Sure, no problem.
[What do we do?]
[It might land on the moon.]
- Fight!
- Hope it goes over the line!
I'll do it!
[Let's go to the end of the beach!]
[It goes up vertically.]
[Oh, no!]
[An eagle shot]
[Their reactions!]
[It's pay back time for
the reaction attack.]
[Ah, so refreshing]
[Why did you wear the sandal?]
[They're the most talented
at laughing at other people.]
[Jong Kook is the
third from the bottom.]
Wow, all those cheeky people
are gathered together.
We won't regret it even
if they take the prize.
I feel so relieved.
Seriously, I love Gyeongpo Beach!
What a nasty word!
We won the game anyway.
Joo Hwan didn't play it yet.
Joo Hwan!
It's our last chance.
Everyone's focused on you.
[The seal is broken again.]
[I'll defeat Eunhyuk]
[and finish the game.]
All the camera is shooting for you.
You've won other prizes, too!
If you defeat Eunhyuk,
it'll be the jackpot.
[Let's go!]
[I'll finish this gam...]
[We won!]
[They don't care about
the score any longer.]
[With one shoe,
everyone's cracking up.]
[Farewell, my desire for victory...]
[Shake, shake]
[What's wrong with him?]
Oh, my stomach hurts!
[He made everyone laugh
and fails to be the winner.]
It was so funny.
Therefore...
Jong Kook's team won!
We did it!
It was so funny.
[Phew... I made it.]
["Class is permanent!"]
How about Jong Kook vs. Joo Hwan?
I feel so relieved.
Thank you so much!
The prizes are on the table.
It's good to be Thanksgiving.
We didn't win many games
but we have so many prizes.
Is this it?
Put them on the truck.
[Is this really over?]
Kwang Soo!
[While everyone is dreaming
of a happy ending...]
We have more than enough!
There are a lot of
big ones over there.
[Coming soon]
[The secret mission is
put in front of them.]
I'll go over there,
you go over there.
[A surprising plot twist!]
[The criminal is among them!]
We caught them!
[The amazing plot twist]
[is starting now!]
[They're heading to the next site
with a a load of gift sets.]
We got a lot more though, right?
We got less,
but ours are more expensive.
[Quality over quantity!]
We lost, but we still got more!
[Thanksgiving should be
abundant with food.]
The sunset is so pretty!
[The sun is setting
on Geyongpo lake]
[just like a painting.]
[The members are entering
the mysterious mission site.]
There's another game?
I think there's
something at the end.
[An empty, spacious area.]
[What mission will they do here?]
[He's getting ready.]
Something's going on...
- I think we need to start running.
- Should I unfasten the seat belt?
Do we have to get there first?
I have no idea.
You only need to go back to Seoul.
You only need to go
home with your gifts.
But since drowsy driving is a
problem these days
so you can rest a bit before
you make your way back.
You can take a nap until 7:30 p.m.
[Take a nap?]
[The mission is to sleep?]
- You can sleep until 7:30 p.m.
- What time is it, now?
- It's 6:30 p.m.
- For an hour.
You want us to sleep?
- Where?
- In this car.
We have other cars in case
you're too squished.
If it's too squishy, you can go to
the cars parked beside you.
Really?
- We just sleep?
- Why?
Do we lose if we don't sleep?
The mission is to sleep?
We are giving you an hour to nap.
Then, we are shutting
the cameras off now.
- What's going on?
- We'll stop recording!
One, two, three!
[All cameras are off for an hour
except for the cameras on tripods.]
[Have a good nap!]
Does this make sense?
[Confused]
Eye patches?
[There has got to be something...]
I'm going to take a nap.
[Big Nosed Brother doesn't hesitate.]
[Goddess of sleep, Blank Ji
gets ready to take a nap.]
[They put away their suspicion]
[and go to dreamland.]
[They don't know
what will happen next...]
[It's getting dark slowly...]
[Nap time is over!]
[The current time is 7:30 p.m.]
[We're carefully checking
if everyone's asleep.]
[Everyone's in deep sleep.]
[An alarm is going off.]
[It's coming from here...]
[Opens his eyes!]
[At 7:30 p.m.
Im Joo Hwan gets up on time.]
[Kwang Soo and Jae Suk in the
same car wake up at the same time.]
[Blank]
[The camera is recording...]
[Are we supposed to do something?]
Do we run away?
I think so.
[They're getting ready to run?]
[Shh!]
[The other members
are still asleep.]
[Come here.]
[They put the other
members behind.]
[And go to the secret rendezvous,
without knowing anything.]
What is it?
What's this?
Why are there so many cars?
[What's with the secret rendezvous?]
I will give a secret mission to
the three of you who woke up on time.
[A secret mission?]
You have two choices.
You can steal all the gift sets
to take for yourself,
while everyone else is sleeping.
Or you can wait
until they're awake
and you can share it, altogether.
Are you going to run away
with all the gift sets?
[Tempted]
[What will their choice be?]
We'll do that!
[We don't have time to hesitate.]
- Gwon Yeol, where are you?
- Right here.
[Getting ready to run away]
There's a carrier service
within Gangneung city.
Find a box from the first site,
and ship it out at the second site.
If you go in the right order,
you can take all the gifts.
Hurry up and bring the gifts.
[When successful,
they can take it all.]
[Without delay,
they're headed to the gifts.]
- Can we get them all at once?
- No, there are too many.
We need to be quiet.
[Jin Young is asleep.]
[The Thanksgiving thieves trio]
[They steal the gift without a hitch.]
[Eunhyuk and Ha Ha are asleep, too.]
[We've stole everything.]
[Shall we move them now?]
[They stole everything at LTE speed.]
[It's their first collaboration]
[but they're a great match.]
What is all this?
Kwang Soo!
What is happening?
[Let's get out of here first!]
[The thieves are running
away without delay.]
Do we ship it out?
So if we ship it to Seoul,
we can have it all...
I think so.
So if the others wake up, find us,
and rip our name tags... we're out.
We have to run away...
I hate being chased!
I'm usually a chaser!
[They picked it,
and they're complaining.]
It is easier to chase...
[Let's wake up, first...]
[Current time: 7:45 p.m.,
five minutes passed.]
[Red alert!]
[What's this sound?]
What's going on?
[The siren is letting them know
of the thieves' runaway.]
[Wake up]
[He comes out without
knowing about the robbery]
[that happened five minutes ago.]
What is it?
[Why isn't anyone in that car?]
[Ha Ha suspects something,
and heads over to the car.]
They took it all, and ran away!
[The truck is empty.]
Jae Suk
Joo Hwan, and Kwang Soo are gone.
[They didn't even leave
a single speck of dust...]
They ran away!
Jin Young!
We got robbed!
[What do you mean, robbed?]
- We got robbed, Gary!
- What?
The people in that car?
The ones who woke up on time
ran away to ship out the gift sets.
There's a tracker
installed in that car.
So who ran away?
You can see their location.
What happened?
Catch them and eliminate them
and they won't be
able to keep the gift sets.
Thieves!
Let's be on our way.
Eunhyuk, Eunhyuk!
[You shouldn't be sleeping!]
Yes?
[Why is it so noisy?]
- Someone stole our car.
- What?
I mean, not the car.
Let's take two cars.
Don't you have another GPS unit?
[He's in peace.]
[What's going on?]
By two sedans?
Yes, just drive sedans.
I can't even sleep peacefully.
I can't trust these guys.
I knew it.
I was wondering
why they told us to sleep.
Guys...
Let's go catch the thieves!
"Thou shalt not covet."
Don't they know it?
Let's call each other.
Is it near Hansol elementary school?
Where are they now?
[Let's go!
Let's capture them all!]
[At 7:50 p.m.]
[They start chasing out of anger.]
What if they scatter around
and wait us at each site?
They're moving.
Where are they going?
They are on... Gangneung Bridge.
Gangneung Bridge?
I thought something was suspicious.
It wakes me up.
Did the three know from the beginning?
- No.
- That's not it?
They probably took the offer
when they got up at 7:30.
We should have woken up at 7:30, then.
[This is tiring.]
They're all supposed
to wake up at 7:30.
[They we didn't need to
betray them at all.]
So, that's what
Kwang Soo's character is like.
Yes, Kwang Soo's always cheeky.
[He looks cheeky even though
they're on the same side.]
[Currently, 8:05 p.m.]
[They're arriving at the first site.]
- Is it here?
- It seems like it.
They will meet a dead end
if they stay on that road.
We're pretty close to them.
Why don't you pick a place nearby?
There's Ojukhun Rest Stop.
They're near Ojukhun Rest Stop.
They're near a dead end.
They've stopped here.
Which means, they got out of the car.
They probably need to do something.
Oh, they're doing their mission?
[The thieves are arriving
at Gangneung artists' village.]
I'll check this side.
Okay.
Where should I go?
This side is large.
Let's search this side together.
Kwang Soo and I are really bad at this.
[The two skilled thieves are
bad at finding the 'R' box.]
I'm not even joking.
We're the worst members for this.
I'm terrible at finding 'R' marks.
There're so many boxes!
[Giraffe is also panicking.]
R mark...
[Joo Hwan is struggling
finding the box all alone.]
[We need to find the box
before the chasers arrive.]
- It's not in here.
- Is it going to end here?
[They're one kilometer away.]
They're still not moving.
They're doing something.
Maybe they need to box it up.
- We're so close!
- Are we?
- Look!
- We're here.
We've almost caught them.
It's exciting!
- Break their arms.
- This is what Running Man is like.
Make a left here.
Yes, the navigation shows
that I have to make a left.
Make a left here.
[What are the thieves doing?]
It'll be over if our name tags
get eliminated.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- Did you find it?
- No.
There are so many boxes
but I can't find the R box.
I searched them, but couldn't find it.
We'll get caught here.
[But, It ain't over 'til it's over.]
[The enthusiastic thief Joo Hwan
keeps searching and searching.]
[He finds the R box.]
[There're wrappers and tapes inside.]
[I did it!]
- Where did you find it?
- The room full of boxes.
- I checked that room, too.
- It was on the top shelf.
[Now, let's move to the final site!]
[At 8:15 p.m.]
[The thieves acquired
wrapping materials.]
[At that moment...]
Isn't that the car?
- That car over there?
- That's it.
They parked in the shade.
[We're here to capture you!]
The car parked over here.
- Where?
- That one in the front.
They're here!
That's the car!
They're here, they're here!
[The thieves were
able to get in the car.]
- I should block the car with our car.
- Catch them!
Wait, don't get out!
- Eliminate their name tags!
- No, don't get out!
Get back, get back!
[The chasers are chasing them again.]
They'll be caught soon!
The destination, destination!
[Changing direction all of a sudden]
[To the final site,
they start the chase again.]
I should have blocked their car.
[VJ: What are we supposed to do?
How can I follow them?]
[They left the filming staff behind.]
Soon, a three-way intersection
should appear.
They started moving again.
- Are they following us?
- Yes.
There's another car over there!
[The chaser team two]
Oh, they're right here!
We got them!
Wow, incredible!
Jong Kook's car is right there.
- Isn't that the chaser two?
- Yes, it is.
[They're surrounded by the chasers.]
Block them from the front!
We would have blocked them
if we were in a movie.
But..
We can't go over the line.
Hey, thieves!
We're surrounded.
Should we eliminate your name tags now?
[You're scaring me.]
Why did you do that?
You took the holiday gifts?
Don't look at them.
Just ignore them.
Pretend we don't know them.
Just lock the door properly.
[They're in a hurry, but they
follow the traffic signal.]
They're still there.
Unbelievable.
They came right next to me.
Did we catch them too early?
It's not that easy to
find them this quickly.
They went far away in an area
that we don't know.
I like our teamwork,
and Korean GPS devices.
I was wondering
they must be near us...
but they just pass by.
We can find them with
a GPS device alone.
Is there any way we can drop them?
We're limited even
though it's a chasing.
We can't really do it like movies.
We still need to follow
the traffic act.
I wish it was different than this.
There's only one way.
We need to keep driving
until they don't have any more gas.
What kind of a chasing is this?
You follow the speed limit
and traffic signals.
The thieves follow
the traffic signs well.
If we let them go here,
we'll lose them forever.
That must be the final mission site!
- It should be!
- The stadium?
The lights are on.
It's right here!
They need to stop here,
no matter what.
They're supposed to come here.
It's right here.
They'll end up coming here.
Let's hide here.
I'll park this car somewhere else.
I don't think all three of us
will be able to stay alive.
While the car is running...
one can get off and run to the site.
That's right.
That's the only way.
- We need to act fast.
- Run and block them.
They'll be surprised if
we run all of a sudden.
I'll be ready to run.
Joo Hwan, we'll get the prize
if you write all of our names.
If you can trust me,
I'll run to the spot.
Kwang Soo, we need to block two cars.
I think one person will get off
and the rest will stop us.
And the other will run.
Eunhyuk, you should run.
And catch the person
who runs with the prize.
Where's the site?
Is is inside the stadium?
Jae Suk, on your left!
Courier service!
They might figure it out,
if we go near the truck.
[Okay, they're finally here.]
They're coming in.
We need to stop them
while you write the invoice.
I wonder if I'll have enough time.
Maybe they will ship it
through the window.
One is going to run.
Should I carry
the prize and get off?
I'll take the dried yellow corvina
and get off.
- Should I catch him?
- I think they're giving up on him.
[Here's dried yellow corvina set!]
Put it in our trunk.
- Run to that side.
- Then, I'll start running.
Eunhyuk, don't fasten
your seat belt, yet.
Do not close the door
and put it in out trunk.
Right now.
Run!
[This is our only chance!]
[Run!]
[Running at full speed.]
He's running, Eunhyuk.
[The chaser with hot blood!]
Eunhyuk is chasing him!
[Blue: Ju Hwan]
[Pink: Eunhyuk]
[Joo Hwan arrives at the truck first.]
[Only if he can write their names...]
[Ji Hyo who was in ambush
tries arresting him.]
[The siege is all around him.]
- It's insane!
- They all got off.
[Will the thieves get the prizes?]
[Or will they be arrested?]
[What will be the result?]
[Joo Hwan's name tag]
Im Joo Hwan is ousted!
They're here.
I was surprised!
[The thieves are chased by Jong Kook.]
What should we do?
Ji Hyo and Suk Jin were
hiding right next to the truck.
Jae Suk, I don't want it
to be ended like this.
Joo Hwan is over.
Joo Hwan is over?
What should we do?
They're here.
Let's stop them right here.
- Block them!
- Come over here, Jae Suk.
Hello!
[Their fantastic teamwork]
Get off, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo...
It's too painful.
Is this the end for us?
Why did you get so greedy?
You shall not steal others'.
Should I put something
small in my pocket?
I'm going to take one, then.
Let's eat some dried persimmons.
Let's have a dried persimmon.
[Struggle, struggle]
It's in the trunk,
and I can't reach it.
[The chasers are convincing them.]
One of you step out!
- We won't catch you!
- Kwang Soo!
- Just one of you!
[How did we end up like this?]
Please stop!
No more!
We'll stay afar.
We'll step back,
but just one of you get out.
What do you want, the meat?
Kwang Soo, you get out that way.
Get out, that way.
[He's trying to sneak to the truck.]
I will block them with the car.
I'll get out!
[Will they succeed this mission?]
[With the car door slightly open,
he approaches]
[and catches him.]
It's over now!
[Kwang Soo's out in a flash.]
[Mr. Capable's speedy catch,
in the blink of an eye.]
- I'll get out!
- Get out!
[Big Nose is gathering
all the gift sets.]
I'm getting out!
[He takes out the invoice.]
Suk Jin, what are you doing!
Suk Jin!
[He tries stealing all of it.]
[The employee is also flustered...]
[What are you doing?]
[Ji Suk Jin, out!]
[Big Nose, who was blind
by the gift sets, is out.]
What kind of person are you?
[The atmosphere has gotten
looser thanks to Big Nose.]
[This is my last chance!]
Jae Suk, Jae Suk!
[He goes for the final plot twist.]
[It's still possible for
them to have it all.]
[What will their fate be?]
[Yoo Jae Suk, out!]
You caught him?
[The chaser win the final mission.]
[The thieves have a miserable ending.]
Get on your knees!
You guys are really...
They prepared the
gifts for Thanksgiving!
I can't live like this!
What's all this?
We're innocent people!
[At that moment, Big Nose is
heading to the truck again.]
[Big Nose tries, once again.]
You've been eliminated!
He wants to take it all!
I can't trust anyone anymore.
- This is so funny!
- Wow, you're unbelievable!
You're unbelievable!
The invoice I gave,
is going to be shipped, right?
The mischievous ones
who stole the gifts.
[That's a little...]
Everyone, except the three of you
and Ji Suk Jin who got eliminated,
will share the gift sets.
I knew it would turn out like this!
I can be eliminated?
Am I out?
[People need to live kindly.]
And honestly
it wasn't even fair.
We have to obey the traffic rules
and obey all the laws.
That's why, during the chase we said
"they stole the gifts,
but they're obeying the traffic rules?"
We had to!
We wanted to block you,
but we were prohibited!
We wanted to, so bad!
[He's concluding, all of a sudden.]
- Thanksgiving...
- You're pretending to be nice, now?
[They don't appreciate him pretending
to be nice all of a sudden.]
"Fellow viewers..."
We will not steal
others' belongings.
And live, kindly.
Please have a
wonderful Thanksgiving!
I'll be heading home, now!
[The chasers take
a load of gifts home.]
- Goodbye!
- Thank you!
- Have a good Thanksgiving!
- See you in two years.
- Oh my!
- Okay!
[Eunhyuk, we hope you will
be back manlier in two years!]
- Goodbye!
- Okay!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[They've been invited
to an unfamiliar place.]
[A 24-hour, unanimous race.]
[If you fail, you have to
leave after 24 hours!]
[Keeping an eye on the Running Man cast
for 24 hours in an abandoned building.]
[Just stay here for 24 hours?]
[There's only one way to escape!
Unanimously succeed the challenge!]
[If you fail, it's hell!]
[Running Man Special: Consensus]