Running Man
Episode 231
[There are no guests today.
Thus, marks the start of the mission.]
[The seemingly impossible mission
of the day...]
[And that day's mission becomes history.]
[The birth of Yoo-ames Bond.]
[Eliminates every member
with one single water gun.]
[The first Yoo-ames Bond mission
that became history in the making.]
[And after a whole year...]
[Yoo-ames Bond makes his return.]
[The mission becomes even more difficult.]
[But... Yoo-ames Bond evolves.]
[With his improves skills, he
successfully eliminates all the members.]
[Not just once... but twice.]
[The members' shock and rage.]
[The second Yoo-ames Bond mission
shows off his elite spy status.]
[His impressive resume
gets filed into the past...]
[And today...]
[Yoo-ames Bond returns
in his perfected form.]
[Yoo-ames Bond returns better than ever.]
[And... something completely unexpected.]
[Today will go down in history.]
[January 6, 2015 - 1 PM.
Taekwondo Stadium in Mooju.]
What is this?
Why are you doing this to me?
I just got here!
[Blindfolded the moment he walks in.]
Seriously.
What are you blindfolding me for?
Something must be happening today.
[Feeling nervous.]
[Where is he being taken to?]
[After walking for a bit...
his blindfold finally comes off.]
Here?
What is this?
What is this all about?
[Wait, this is...]
Is this the day?
[Now that we think back,
this is how it's always been.]
[Being summoned to a secret room
to receive a secret mission.]
[Next, the assigning of the weapon.]
[And the second secret room
becomes even more upgraded.]
[Thus, Yoo-ames Bond's missions
always began from a secret room.]
- Mr. Yoo-ames Bond.
- Yes?
- You've always performed well for us.
- Yes, that's true.
- We've designated a successor for you.
- What do you mean, my successor?
[A successor?]
- Your successor will soon be joining us.
- So?
Hand your water gun over to your successor,
and order that person to eliminate everyone.
[Hand over my water gun?]
- Who said I want a successor?
- And as for you...
You have to teach your successor
all of your spy skills
and help that person successfully
become the second Bond.
[The second Bond?]
You know how quick witted Blank Ji is?
She asked me earlier this morning
if it's going to be a spy mission today.
You have no idea how tight the
competition is amongst those guys.
Having me be the spy is one thing,
but having someone else become the spy?
[I'm not going to be the spy, but
there will be a successor in my place?]
[A successor...]
Who's going to be my successor?
I can only think of one person.
To be honest, even though he's older
than me, he's actually my junior.
Suk Jin... He's actually two years
my junior in this business.
[Possible successor one - Suk Jin.
Older in age, but a junior in experience.]
[No one can beat Big-nose
when it comes to enthusiasm.]
Ji Hyo.
[Possible successor two - Ji Hyo.]
[The undisputed Ace of Running Man-
A true hunter in form.]
It can't be Jong Kook. He thought
he was Rambo with the water gun.
[This man is more like a mercenary
rather than an agent.]
Kwang Soo.
[Possible successor four- Kwang Soo.]
[Traitor instincts down to the bone-
The icon of betrayal.]
As for Ha Ha and Gary...
[Possible successor five - Ha Ha.]
[Haroro, always has a trick up his sleeves.]
[Possible successor six - Gary.]
[One of the strongest members-
Mr. Random Capable.]
- I don't know who's coming, either.
- Really?
[Who could it be?]
[Unable to even fathom a guess
as to who the successor is going to be.]
If you find yourself in danger, or
feel that your successor isn't performing
then you have the authority to
eliminate that person.
Your successor will soon be here, and
we ask that you be kind to that person.
Ugh, I wonder who's going to show up.
[Just who will show up as his successor
to become the second Bond?]
[Big-nose]
[Kkuk]
[Kwang Soo]
[Ha Ha]
[Ji Hyo]
[Gary]
[It doesn't matter who it is...]
[I will be the one to determine
who becomes my successor.]
[Yoo-ames Bond]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Gary]
[Ha Ha]
[Ji Suk Jin and Lee Kwang Soo]
[And Yoo Jae Suk]
[Yoo-ames Bond - The Successor]
[The same morning at 8 am.]
[Taekwondo Stadium in Mooju.]
[The room they're secretly entering
with an alarm clock in hand is...]
[none other than Running Man
members' rooms.]
[The ultimate morning call service.]
[What is this?]
[What noise is this so early
in the morning?]
[Mommy, five more minutes...]
[Oh, you're not my mommy.]
How do I turn this off?
You're stopping it with your hand
instead of turning off the alarm?
[Kkuk wakes up by choking
the mechanism off the clock.]
Ugh, you startled me awake
from my sleep.
[Still half asleep.]
[Barely manage to pull themselves awake.]
[Handed their mission for the day
as soon as they open their eyes.]
'Please find me' race?
You have currently lost your identities.
As your name tag states,
you are not yourself at this moment.
- You're not Song Ji Hyo.
- You're not Ji Suk Jin.
My back is blank right now?
What is this?
[Their name tags are blank.]
[Checking to see their blank name tags.]
Am I just a spirit?
[Getting used to the idea of
having become a spirit.]
[Big-nose's face is quite
swollen from his sleep.]
Ugh, I slept without my shirt on,
and now I feel all congested.
My face is really
swollen right now, isn't it?
[Checking himself out in the camera.]
I really have lost myself.
I'm not myself right now.
If you want to get your identity back,
then hurry over to the taekwondo studio.
[Please Find Me Race- Start]
[On their way to the taekwondo studio.]
What is this?
This is so tacky.
- Is it a competition of some sorts?
- Are we the White Team?
- You're spirits.
- We're spirits?
Because we've lost our identities?
- All our name tags are blank.
- Let me see.
[The members have lost their identities,
and all that remains are their spirits.]
Do you remember the movie, 'Please find me'?
There's a twist at the end.
- Yes, you're right.
- I'm wondering if this is a spy race.
- You're on that already?
- Are you getting started already?
[Current time- 8:30 am.
Long before Jae Suk received his mission.]
You're talking about spies already?
- We're spirits today...
- I've always been tricked by spies.
- That's why I need to be alert.
- Gary's not saying anything.
You know how I am.
- I can't figure Gary out anymore.
- No, I don't know how to read Gary anymore.
- Kwang Soo won't be the spy.
- Why not?
You make it too obvious.
What nonsense to talk about
so early in the morning.
There's no need to talk such nonsense.
[Entering the taekwondo studio...]
Have any one of you seen my body?
My physical being has disappeared.
- You're blindfolding us?
- What are you guys doing?
What are you blindfolding me for?
[All the members are led off to
different locations while blindfolded.]
[They all arrive at their respective spots
and take off their blindfolds.]
Ugh, you startled me.
Who are you?
[Who are you?]
[They take off their blindfolds to find
mysterious doctors in front of them.]
Hello.
Your physical body is hidden
somewhere within this building.
The moment you stepped into this building,
your physical being has started to disappear.
Quickly complete your mission,
and recover your body.
[They must complete their mission and
recover their bodies before they disappear.]
I have to find and recover my body
before it disappears completely?
- Okay, I understand.
- You have to find your body.
There are many locked rooms
inside this building.
You have to search through those rooms
and find the one that's housing your body.
[Find the room that's housing their body
amongst the numerous rooms.]
I understand.
- Can I get going now?
- Wait.
[Pocket of life.]
There are five jewels in here?
[Five Jewels of Life and a yellow key.]
[The key will open only a few of the
numerous locked rooms in the building.]
[Inside those rooms are a variety
of different missions that await them.]
Once you succeed a mission,
then you'll be given another key.
[Succeed the mission
to receive a key to the next level.]
[Then the key received will get you
to the next level's gateway.]
[Must succeed a mission from each level until
the room that's housing their body is found.]
So I have to find the room
that can be opened with this key
and succeed the mission within that room
to move onto the next level?
I have to give up one of my jewels
every time I fail a mission?
You'll be given another jewel
when you succeed a mission
but you'll have to give one up
when you fail a mission.
If you lose all your jewels,
then your body will disappear completely.
Which means,
you'll be eliminated from the game.
- Fighting.
[Off to start the missions.]
You must go and get started!
There's not much time.
Can you let me see your face?
[Excessively dramatic doctor.]
What's wrong with you?
You must live in order for
me to live, too!
[I must successfully complete my missions
in order to save the life of my doctor.]
He's really funny.
[Time to start the 'Please Find Me' race!]
Here's a yellow door.
[Discovers a yellow room that matches
the color of the key received.]
[What sort of a mission will
he find inside the yellow room?]
[Attempts to open the lock
with his yellow key.]
[It's not opening.]
Just because the door's yellow,
it doesn't mean that they all open?
[Only a few of the yellow rooms
can be opened with their yellow key.]
[First step in the mission is to find
the room that their own key will open.]
There are so many rooms!
[While the members are getting started
on their mysterious mission...]
[Just then...]
[Yoo-ames Bond is about to receive
his secret mission.]
Your successor will soon be here, and
we ask that you be kind to your successor.
[Yoo-ames Bond's mission- Eliminate the rest
of the members with his successor.]
[Waiting in hiding for his successor.]
[Who could it be... Who could it be?]
[Who could it be?]
[His successor enters the room.]
[Just who could it be?]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[A secret room?]
[Elated at the thought of possibly
being asked to be a spy.]
I really want to enjoy this moment.
This moment makes me feel so happy.
What is it?
What is this about?
[The wall is opening!]
[Making his appearance from behind
the wall, is Yoo-ames Bond.]
[Oh my goodness! I can't believe
I'm witnessing this moment!]
You can't come into the secret room!
[I was here way before you came in.]
- I'm Yoo-ames Bond.
- Yes, I forgot.
- Can't you tell by looking at this?
- What's going on here today?
[Can't be...]
[Yes, today is the day.]
- Have a seat.
- Aren't I the star of this episode?
- Am I not the one?
- You're nothing until I decide to take you.
You're just...
a tall guy...
with the face of a dog.
Have a seat.
[Yoo-ames Bond sits down to relay
the rules to his possible successor.]
Today...
will go down in history.
Do you know how many Yoo-ames Bond
episodes today makes?
- This is the third episode.
- Yes, it is.
It's the most successful theme
in the history of Running Man.
No, it's not to that extent.
Who says that it is?
Every single viewer out there
awaits my Bond episodes.
This is that day.
But...
You and I will become a team today.
Today...
- I won't be the one to shoot this water gun.
- Me?
- You'll be the one to shoot it.
- But why are you talking to me like that?
- Get out.
- No, come on.
[How dare you!]
- If you don't want to hear it, then get out.
- I was just asking.
- You can call me whatever you want.
- Okay.
[Calms down to carry on
with the mission message.]
The reason why I called you in here
is because...
if you successfully complete your mission...
then as of today,
you will officially become an agent.
Your final test before you
become an agent
will be revealed to you once all the other
members have been ousted by the water gun.
Only when you and I are the only ones left,
will you be given your final test.
- A test?
- That's right.
I have to pass the test
before I officially become an agent?
You have to eliminate everyone else first.
You're looking at me like that again.
You're looking at me
like you don't trust me.
I can see your traitorous instinct
starting to rear its ugly head.
- Are you really going to be like this?
- No, I'm not.
Can I shoot you, too?
Not that I want to do that.
- I'm just asking out of curiosity.
- That's why I'm telling you the rules.
- Listen carefully.
- Okay.
You can shoot this water gun
only when we're both together.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Which means, this.
During today's Yoo-ames Bond episode
I will act as your mentor.
Think about how many times you've ruined
big secret missions like this in the past.
I've never ruined anything.
As the viewers are watching
with such high expectations
there have been numerous occasions
where you've totally ruined the outcome.
- I know that things didn't go well...
- That's what I'm saying.
[Fascinatingly enough, the bigger the secret,
more obvious Kwang Soo made everything look.]
That's why I'm going to take care to pass on
all my knowledge over to you during this.
- Is this like Batman and Robin?
- No, it's not.
We're Don Quixote and Sancho.
Young-Gu and Daeng-Chil.
There you go, now you're getting it.
Only when the two of are together,
will this water gun have any effect.
- Do you understand?
- Only when we're together?
[While the two are formulating
their plans together...]
[The other five members are busy
trying to find the right rooms.]
My key is going to get worn out.
Like my heart?
[Kang Gary, the man of persistence.]
I can't believe that
none of these doors are opening.
There's even a black room.
A black room?
I wonder if there's going to be
some monsters again today?
That one's black, and this one is red.
Yellow...
Aren't those taekwondo belt colors?
Those are the different level colors.
These are the different levels.
It is, isn't it, Yoo Suk?
Red belt, black belt...
They're belts!
Taekwondo belts.
Yellow, and the blue over there.
[While the members are slowly
getting one step closer to the truth...]
[These two are still only
talking about their mission.]
You need to pull yourself together.
We have to get our acts together, got it?
Okay, then...
[Yoo-ames Bond's symbolic water guns.]
[Unable to believe his sight.]
[The water guns that
he's only seen from afar.]
Did they really have to
hang that picture up there?
- Why is it only about Jae Suk?
- This is my special episode.
- I can understand the water guns...
If you succeed your mission today,
then I'll sign this picture for you.
- No, it's okay.
- You can hang it up in your room.
- I'm telling you to hang it up in your room.
- Choose one.
- I don't know which one to choose.
[First water gun selection
of Kwang Soo's life.]
- Should I go with the big one?
- No.
Then pick one for me if you're going to
disapprove of my selection.
- Then choose one for me.
- The elephant and the alligator are popular.
- You have to be very careful with it.
- Should I keep it in my pants?
- There are different colored solutions.
- This is...
The color disappears after a minute,
and doesn't leave a trace.
Your current situation from
when I first started out
is extremely different.
You're really getting spoiled.
Are you aware of that? The world
has become so much more convenient.
What if you spill?
I feel like I'm in a movie or something.
No, what are you doing?
- What if it leaves a trace?
- Don't be such an amateur.
Do you not believe in today's technology?
[It really did disappear!]
- What do you think?
- It disappears right away.
If you really get to the final stage
as we discussed earlier
then you will be honored
with a new name.
What will my name be?
- There's a very famous investigator.
- Who?
Mr. Choi Bul Ham.
Since I'm Yoo-ames Bond,
how about 'Kwang-Buram' for you?
[Not getting a very good feeling about this.]
He has solved countless crimes,
and are you disrespecting his role?
No, I'm very honored by the name,
and I respect him greatly...
You think only foreign names
are cool and good?
- Your name will become your identity.
- I will succeed and become Kwang-Buram.
You will be Kwang-Buram.
There's this, too.
[Yoo-ames Bond's other symbol-
The gold bracelet.]
[If others discover the gold bracelet,
then they fail the mission.]
[Bond himself puts the band on Kwang Soo
so that it's not caught by others.]
What if only one of us gets caught?
Then can I eliminate the other members
by myself without Jae Suk?
- What are the rules on that?
- What is it that you're trying to do?
What are you saying? Are you
saying that you'll do it on your own?
[Kwang Soo's still unable to move on from
the dream of being the sole star of the show.]
Okay, let's go.
[Time to start their secret mission.]
- Kwang-Buram.
- Yoo-ames Bond.
- Good luck on the mission.
- Thank you.
[Will Yoo-ames Bond be able to
pass down his legacy?]
[Yoo-ames Bond and Kwang-Buram's
start of the mission.]
Jae Suk, you have your
water gun, right?
- It's not showing, is it?
- No, it's not.
[Kwang-Buram is following
in Yoo-ames Bond's trail.]
- My clothes are soaked.
- Why?
- I think my water gun is leaking.
- Let me see.
No, it's okay.
It's rubbing alcohol, so it doesn't matter.
[Yoo-ames Bond, at his best.
Always being cautious.]
There's more up there.
[The other members are still
searching for their rooms.]
[Will this door open?]
This one fits!
This one actually fits!
[Finally enters the first mission room.]
[Each room holds a different mission.
Which mission waits in this room?]
[30 seconds on the clock with five chances-
Catch five balls or more with tongs to win.]
Successfully complete the mission to
win the key to the next level door.
[Rule- Must bet one Jewel of Life
for each mission.]
I have to catch five of these balls
with these tongs?
I can't use the paddle at all?
Okay, I'll do it.
[Will receive the Jewel of Life,
and clear for the blue level if he wins.]
[But if he fails the mission,
then he loses a Jewel of Life.]
[Discovers his prey, Ha Ha.]
Jae Suk, I have to catch
the balls with these tongs.
- That's pretty much impossible.
- Okay.
Let's do this!
[Yellow Zone- Catch the table tennis balls.]
You should've caught that one.
How could you not have caught it?
[Now that he's actually doing it,
it's not as easy as it looks.]
[Catches one of five.]
[But the balls keeps bouncing
off of his tongs.]
[Rage filled full swing.]
That's too bad.
That would make me angry, too.
Ugh, I'd get angry, too.
I'm getting aggravated just from watching.
[Yoo-ames Bond continues to
further agitate Ha Ha.]
[Only one ball successfully caught so far.]
[Fails the first attempt.]
Ugh, I'm so aggravated.
[Wait...]
[This is when I'd normally
be targeting his back...]
Only when the two of us are together
can you shoot your water gun.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
[But he can only pretend to be doing
the mission since Kwang Soo's not with him.]
Since I'm already here,
can I try this mission, too?
- Only once Ha Ha's finished.
- Then I can do it?
Yes, but you have to bet
one of your jewels.
- Huh?
- Why are you acting like you don't know?
- Because I've already lost one.
- Really?
- You have to bet a jewel, okay?
- Okay, go!
[Yellow Zone Mission- Second Attempt.]
[This time, Ha Ha grabs the tongs
in a different direction.]
[Mission accomplished.]
[He's already succeeded the mission,
but he continues to go for the record.]
[The tongs are now
an extension of his hands.]
[Isn't catching the balls
with the tongs so easy?]
- What the heck? 17...
- I did it!
[Ha Ha successfully clears the mission.]
- He just saw how I did it.
- Challenge accepted.
Challenge.
[Ha Ha's Jewel of Life
is returned back to him.]
I get my jewel back,
and I also get a blue key!
- Okay, buddy.
- Okay!
- I'll watch you play before I go.
- Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Which way is it coming?
[His skills are so...]
Ugh, this is aggravating.
Oh, I got one!
[The balls continues to bounce
off of his tongs.]
[Is he purposely not catching the balls?]
Jae Suk, you have to stop letting it
bounce off the tongs.
[Ha Ha doesn't suspect Jae Suk of being
a spy, and gives him advice.]
- That's right.
- Like this?
- There you go.
- Ugh!
I don't know what to tell you.
I'm going to get going.
[Unlike the confidence he started with,
fails the mission.]
[Pretends to be enraged.]
[Imitates Yoo-ames Bond's movements.]
- I didn't do that. It was my first attempt.
- Goodbye!
Ugh, this is so aggravating.
[Ha Ha leaves in search for
the blue level mission.]
Ugh, this is so aggravating.
I'm all set.
You can stop doing that now.
[No need to pretend anymore
since there aren't any eyes watching.]
You can calm down.
Since some have moved on to the next level,
shall we start eliminating them one by one?
I think I'm going to go and check
to see what my pupil is up to.
Then we will start the elimination process.
[Starts hunting mode with Kwang-Buram.]
[Kwang-Buram, on the other hand...]
What are you doing?
[Just like Yoo-ames Bond predicted,
he's mingling with the other members.]
- Are you able to go to the red rooms?
- Only one person at a time can find it.
Only one person at a time
can find their bodies.
[Slowly starting to feel the pressure
with the members' succeeding their missions.]
[They must be eliminated,
but where's Yoo-ames Bond?]
[Yoo-ames Bond exits
the yellow mission room...]
- I succeeded the mission.
- Nice.
[Yoo-ames Bond pretends to have
succeeded the mission to avoid suspicion.]
- Jae Suk, did you succeed?
- Yes, I did.
- You have four left? You should get going.
- I have four missions left.
I have to go to the bathroom first.
[Kwang-Buram follows in
Yoo-ames Bond's footsteps.]
You have to remain covert
and shoot without hesitation.
You can't hesitate at all.
- And you have to keep it covert.
- Okay, I'll do it quick.
Check and make sure
that your water gun is full.
It doesn't need to be completely full,
but make sure that it can shoot.
You have to make sure
to get it with the first shoot.
- Don't be nervous.
- Okay.
Just trust me.
Pull yourself together.
I said, pull yourself together.
The moment you lose your focus,
then you and I are over, got it?
[The two spies' secret meeting
in the bathroom.]
- Don't let me see you having doubts again.
- Okay.
The moment I see you having
doubts again...
I'll just end you myself.
- Pull yourself together.
- I'll shoot at your signal.
I'll be right out, okay?
[Yoo-ames Bond leaves after leaving
behind some of his wisdom.]
[The nerves are making his stomach...
He takes after Jae Suk in this matter, too?]
- Please!
- It's not going to work.
I got it to open.
Bye!
[Gary finally succeeds in entering
the Yellow Mission Zone.]
Bye, Ji Hyo!
Find 15 things that are different between
the two rooms and explain what they are.
- 15 of them?
- Yes, 15 differences between the rooms.
[30 seconds and five chances to find
15 differences between the rooms.]
Ready, set, go!
[We invite all the viewers to
join us in the mission.]
[Spot the difference between the rooms.]
[Mr. Gary scans the two rooms.]
Cup, books, shoes, umbrella....
[Time over- Time to state his answers.]
- The cup is different.
- How are they different?
- You have to be more detailed.
- One is short, and one is tall.
[The size of the cups.]
And the book in the middle is different.
They're different colors.
One is green.
The clothes are different, too.
This stack is missing one.
The slippers.
The socks are different prints.
The umbrella colors are different.
The hanger is different,
and the time on the clock is different.
[Different times.]
And... and that's all I
have for now.
[12 differences are spotted so far,
and only three more left to find.]
The round peg on the clothes rack
are different colors.
[The color of the nail on the coat rack.]
Wait a minute...
[Only two more differences are left to find.]
Only two are left, right?
Okay, it's all over!
First, it's the doll.
One is missing a shoe.
[The shoe on the doll.]
And the baseball bat.
One has a black tape wrapped around it,
and the other one doesn't.
[All 15 differences are spotted.]
[Gary clears the mission.]
[His Jewel of Life is returned back to him.]
I want to go and find my being again.
[He earns the key to the blue level.]
Okay, it's off to the blue level now.
[Two of the members are now
off to the blue level.]
Okay, let's go.
Things are going pretty well.
Shall I go for the win today?
[Gary is now on the search
for the opening blue door.]
I hope one opens right away.
Come on, let's find an opening door.
[I'm going to find my missing body.]
[Find the mate- Find the matching
fruity scented hand cream.]
[A total of seven chances,
and onto his sixth attempt.]
[Successfully finds the banana pair.]
[Fails the sixth attempt.]
I thought that I had that one.
[Final seventh attempt.]
Ugh, I'm ruined.
I'm in big trouble now.
[Two pairs still left to match.]
I can open one at a time?
Okay, I'm good.
I've succeeded.
Okay, I've succeeded.
[Jong Kook succeeds his mission.]
I like this one.
Banana.
[At ease enough to put on some hand cream.
Mr. Capable is a man who looks after himself.]
This is the key that will allow you
to enter the blue zone.
Thank you.
[Yellow zone mission-
Find the key within five seconds.]
[Find the key from the bowl of hot stones.]
[Ouch, that's hot!]
[Finds the key right away!]
[Big-nose succeeds his mission.]
Today is my day.
Ouch, that's hot.
[The heat of the game lingers on.]
Okay, off to the next zone.
Okay, I've still got five lives left.
- You are now upgraded to the blue level.
- Okay.
I have a good feeling about today.
Listen to me carefully.
What we do from now on is what matters.
What you're doing right now
and the slight smile or expression
you have on your face
when you go around the other members is
what will get you suspected by others.
- But I don't know how to hide it.
- I know.
The movement you start to deny it,
that's when they'll get suspicious of you.
But if I don't say anything, then
they get suspicious of me being quiet.
Forget everything that I just told you,
and everything we just talked about.
You're just here to find a key
like everyone else, and that's it.
- The key finding mission.
- That's right.
Just think about that mission,
and not about the water gun, okay?
[I'll make sure to remember.]
[Even though he told him
and told him again...]
[That's the look of reassurance
on his face?]
[It's as if he's announcing to the world,
'I'm on a secret mission!']
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo.
Where did Kwang Soo go?
Call him and see where he's at.
What is he doing?
What is he up to by himself?
[Kwang Soo... you haven't been
caught already, have you?]
We have to find the room first, right?
[Must find a blue zone room
that the key fits into.]
[Mr. Gary is showing the most enthusiasm
for finding the room at the moment.]
I found it.
[Gary is first to enter the blue zone.]
[Just then, Yoo Hyuk is seen
heading towards Gary's direction.]
- Are you in the blue zone?
- Yes, the blue zone.
- Want to play a game with me?
- Where?
- What's in here?
- I don't think Suk Jin can do it.
[Must endure being tickled longer than
your opponent with the recorder in mouth.]
- No, I can't do this.
- Why not?
You know that I can't stand
being tickled.
- You know I hate being tickled!
- Come on, why?
- I'm weak when it comes to being tickled.
- Let's just play a practice game.
[Playing a practice round to
determine whether to play it or not.]
[Jae Suk to take the first turn.]
- You have to spread out your arms.
- No, I don't need to do that.
[Gary just grazed Jae Suk's side...]
[Jae Suk is one very sensitive man.]
Why don't you give it a try?
- Gary's good at enduring things like this.
- I feel like I'm being tickled already.
- Wait, I'm not ready yet.
- But Gary's good at things like this, right?
[Already feeling the tickles even though
the game hasn't even started yet.]
Ready, set...
I'm not playing this mission.
- I'm not playing this game.
- You guys are neck and neck.
- You should do it.
- Okay, let's do it.
[The two weakest players are
deciding to take on the mission.]
- Okay, this may not be bad.
- Okay, let's do this.
[Putting one of their life jewels on the line
to play the mission.]
[Only the winner of the mission
will get their jewel back.]
- It's whoever can last longer?
- This is much more fun than watching TV.
I'd better take off my glasses.
Pay close attention to him, okay?
He really is so ugly.
[Even though I may be ugly,
I have to stop Gary from succeeding.]
[The recorder blows loud and clear,
as soon as the mission starts.]
[A guaranteed win.]
- How long was it?
- I'm guessing it was 0.13 seconds?
- It was 0.18 seconds.
0.18... then I need to
end Gary by 0.17 seconds.
This is kind of hard.
I have to get going myself,
but I'm too entertained by this.
[Now, it's Gary's turn.]
It's not even a second.
You just have to last 0.18 seconds.
Okay, that 0.18 seconds is a very
important time in my life.
I just need to long enough
for that important time.
Okay, everything is hanging
on this moment.
[Already feeling the tickle even
though it hasn't even started yet.]
What are your hands doing
there already?
This is the spot.
Get him on his sides.
[I have to somehow win this game.]
You won.
Kang Gary wins!
[Gary's record- 1.17 seconds.
Gary wins!]
- Am I losing my jewel?
- Yes, you've lost it.
[Only Gary gets to keep the jewel
for having won the mission.]
- Congratulations, Gary.
- Thank you.
[Yoo-ames Bond is unable to stop Gary
from moving onto the red zone.]
Since you've succeeded,
you'll be given a key to the next level.
[Gary wins a key to the red zone.]
Can I get going then?
Thank you.
Kwang Soo.
[Kwang-Buram finally shows up after
having wandered around aimlessly.]
We needs to start eliminating them.
[The members are climbing through the levels,
but they haven't ousted anyone yet.]
Jae Suk, what are you doing?
[Suddenly pretending to be getting
a drink of water.]
Are you getting some water?
- Suk Jin, did you succeed?
- No, I didn't.
- Jong Kook is in the blue zone already.
- He's in the blue zone?
Are you still in the yellow zone?
Gary's in the red zone already.
- Really?
- Gary's in the red zone.
- What's after the red zone?
- It's the black zone.
- Red zone is the third one?
- Yes, he only has two zones left.
[All the red games must be
played with three people.]
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- You should play this game with Ha Ha.
- Let's play a game.
- Good, I've been waiting.
Would the rest of you like to watch
an entertaining game?
What is it?
[Kwang Soo slyly follows into
Jae Suk and Ha Ha's yellow mission zone.]
You're good at things like this.
[More mats of your color must be flipped up
at the end of the minute to win the mission.]
Should I play this or not?
- Ha Ha, do you want to play it with me?
- You're not a blue zone yet.
You're still in the yellow zone.
Should I play this or not? Play or not?
Ugh, I really can't stand you sometimes.
- What are you doing?
- Should I play it or not?
[What's wrong with him...]
- One, two, three, four.
- Should I play it or not...
Should I do it or not...
- What are you doing?
- That's really weird.
- You should've done it with us.
- It's actually pretty fun.
- It's just because you're jealous.
You need to come here and do it.
[Finally steps back behind Ha Ha.]
- One, two...
- Are you ready?
- Let's do it with some feelings this time.
- Okay, like this?
[Kwang-Buram... are you
still looking for your water gun?]
[What are you doing!]
[Something... is off?]
Ugh, seriously!
[He checks his own stash of jewels?]
- Ugh, seriously.
- I startled you, didn't I?
[Is this how Yoo-ames Bond's
dream will come to an end?]
- You're trying to steal from me?
- What?
[Huh?]
[Haroro mistakes Kwang Soo
of stealing his jewels.]
- There are five.
- No, I only have three right now.
- Give it back.
- Why did you do that?
- I seriously didn't do it.
- Just give it back.
[Hands over one of his jewels.]
- Why would you do that!
- What are you doing?
[We're just lucky... that it's Haroro.]
- Come on, let's just do this first.
- I'm not playing it!
[The leaky water gun is shoved down
the back of his pants?]
- Let's just finish this mission first.
- You guys are too scary.
- It's because I don't have any jewels!
- Then go out and get some on your own.
Why would you steal!
- Jae Suk, you should apologize.
- I'm sorry.
- Should I sue or not?
- Should I do it or not?
[Problems will be shoved aside
for a little dance time first.]
- Seriously, don't do it again.
- Okay, no more.
- Are you allowed to steal?
- He had the bag open.
[He almost just got caught,
and he's rifling through again.]
You're going to steal from everyone?
You didn't steal any?
Why did you take mine earlier?
- It's because of you. He started it.
- People like you...
- Why am I...
- It's because you started it.
This is all because you started it.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't ever do that again.
[I vow to get it done this time!]
Okay, let's do the dance.
[Ready to eliminate Haroro.]
[A direct hit on Ha Ha's name tag.]
Should I do it or not...
[It's a success.]
[Now that Ha Ha's been shot,
it's time to really dance it out.]
[Haroro has no idea
what had just happened to him.]
[This is almost sad...]
I'm not going to do this.
You're going to win this.
- You'd win this.
- Then I'm not playing it either.
I'm not playing.
[There's no more reason
to be around Haroro anymore.]
- You should go do your missions!
- Okay, I'll be back.
[Kwang-Buram awkwardly
takes his leave.]
I can't be standing around
here like this.
[They finally eliminated one member...]
Ugh, you seriously startled me.
I told you not to hesitate with it.
You have to be quick.
Hurry up and get to the yellow zone.
[Senior spy is feeling apprehensive
about his successor.]
[The mark on his back
has already disappeared.]
Where's a blue zone member?
- Ha Ha, I succeeded.
- Which one?
[Huh? How is he still walking around
when he's been shot with the water gun?]
Find an open door and call for me.
[Just then, a doctor comes
onto the scene.]
I have much that I need to ask you.
[So that's how it happens...]
Doctor.
[The doctor is leading Ha Ha
away somewhere.]
[Ha Ha has no idea what's going on.]
- Please come in.
- What is this place?
[What is this?]
What is this?
[The place that he's been taken to..
is jail.]
What is this?
[So confused.]
Is there a spy?
[Still unable to grasp the situation.]
It's Ji Hyo, isn't it?
Like this... let's not spread it around.
[Find four metal marbles
and find the secret code.]
[All four marbles are discovered.]
In that case...
Yellow one is 'one',
and the blue one is 'five'.
Red is 'seven', and black is 'eight'.
It's 1578.
[Secret code- 1578.]
I got it.
[Upgraded to the blue zone,
and earns the key for entrance.]
I had to dig through the dirt.
Ugh, that was tough.
Freedom!
- Miss Blank, did you win something?
- I just finally succeeded.
- What did you succeed in?
- I had to dig through the dirt.
- Wow, this is awesome.
- I don't know what's happened to him.
- Are you in the blue zone?
- Yes, I'm in the blue zone.
[Yoo-ames Bond and Kwang-Buram
are back together again.]
[Now that I look at the situation,
we're back together again?]
Let's get to a blue zone mission,
and move onto the next level.
- One of us three has to move on.
- I think it's over that way.
[Ji Hyo is our next mark.]
We can't go that way.
[Kwang Soo readies his water gun.]
[Quietly sneaks up on Ji Hyo's back.]
[Target locked.]
[A direct hit on her name tag.]
Where is it?
[Hides his water gun away
as soon as his mission is over.]
Someone must've done something.
- What if they're just in the room?
- There they are.
[They just need to make up an excuse
and flee from Ji Hyo's side.]
- Kwang Soo, you can't go in there.
- No, you can't go in there.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
[Kwang Soo... that was perfect.]
- Please follow me.
- Me?
Why do you need me?
I have to get to the blue zone.
You'll know once you follow me.
[Okay, two members have
been ousted...]
[But their biggest concern still remains.]
Ugh, I'm feeling so nervous
and anxious.
Ugh, stress!
What is this?
[Blank Ji is following the doctor's lead
without even knowing what's going on.]
- I think you've been disqualified.
- Why?
I think it's Jae Suk.
- I'm out?
- I think I'm out, too.
Was he going after your jewels at all?
[Still trying to figure out
how they've been ousted.]
I need to get this mission done
before someone else comes up here.
[Gary is already onto the red zone.]
[But he hasn't been able to
open up any of the rooms yet.]
[The first person to untie and take the belt
from their opponent wins the game.]
I'll help you.
[Kwang Soo is getting ready
to face Big-nose.]
I think you tie it like this.
[The water gun!]
[Swoops down to pick it back up.]
[Yoo-ames Bond starts acting funny
from feeling flustered.]
Just help him instead.
What are you trying to pull here?
What are you trying to do?
[Seriously!]
I'll stay right by your side,
so don't worry about anything.
He's treating me like a total idiot.
We both started Running Man
at the same time.
[Kwang-Buram was feeling so confident...]
[I can't believe that he's my successor.]
- I need to get to the red zone.
- I need to get there too.
[Since we're already in this mess,
I'm just going to do this myself.]
[Hands it off to Yoo-ames Bond.]
[I'll shoot.]
[Then I'll grab him.]
[They're now ready to oust Big-nose.]
- The winner of this game will go with you.
- Okay.
Ready, set, go.
[Kwang Soo vs Big-nose.]
Suk Jin's stronger than he looks.
[Now's the chance...]
[Kwang Soo, keep holding onto him.]
[Jae Suk, now's our chance.]
[Closes in on Big-nose's name tag.]
[Opens fire.]
[Since I've already got it out,
one more shot.]
[Bulls eye on Big-nose's name tag.]
[We got it!]
[Big-nose still has
a cheery look on his face.]
That's pretty impressive.
It's like a UFC fight.
The winner gets to come with me.
Okay, that's how you play the game.
[A meaningless move by someone
who's already been ousted.]
[Kwang Soo succeeds the mission.]
[Loses the game,
and shot by the water gun, too.]
Wow, Suk Jin's really strong.
[Only two more left to eliminate...]
I must be needed for
something important?
[Kwang-Buram, seemingly
nervous about something.]
The solution keeps leaking out.
[Almost didn't even get to oust Suk Jin
from the lack of solution in the water gun.]
[Startled by the smallest bit of noise
in his agitated state.]
[The water gun newbie even struggles
to get the solution in the chamber.]
I think that should be enough.
[Gary and Jong Kook are the only two
left to eliminate.]
[But why does it have to be
the two strongest opponents?]
[Will be he able to safely
complete his mission?]
[Jae Suk marks Jong Kook as his
next target and follows him in.]
Since we're allowed to tackle each other,
let's make this entertaining.
Wait, are you trying to turn this
into a physical battle?
- Listen, I'm in a dire situation right now.
- I'm in a dire situation myself.
- How many do you have?
- I have to move on to the next level.
- How is that important?
- The number is very important.
- Why?
- Tell me what you have right now.
- Let's just do this and move up a level.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Okay, bet a jewel.
I'll take the blue panels,
and you can take the red.
- Seriously...
- Wait.
- I'm blue, right?
- That's right.
- Hey, did you pass?
- No, I can't find a room.
Then wait here for a minute.
- I'm going to beat him, and come with you.
- The winner of this game can come with me.
- Okay, I will.
- Okay, that sounds good.
Set, go!
[A forceful body check
as soon as the game starts.]
[Jae Suk...]
[Yoo-ames Bond is held tightly
in Kkuk's embrace.]
[Strong as a bull, Kkuk, is playing the game
with Jae Suk wrapped around his waist.]
- Help me, Kwang Soo.
- How am I to help you with that?
Kwang Soo, help me!
What are you doing to him?
This is really wounding my pride.
Kwang Soo!
Jae Suk, there are still four left.
Gather up your strength and do it.
[There are only four more
red squares left.]
Jae Suk!
Jae Suk, you look like a baby
that's been painted with white paint.
[Utter insult.]
[The winner has been already determined,
but Kkuk is going for the record.]
[Ten seconds left on the clock.]
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo!
[Time's up.]
[Even though Kkuk is his enemy,
he's still impressed.]
- Okay, it's over.
- That was the perfect game.
[All blue.]
[Kkuk, with the perfect win.]
- Ugh, I'm so aggravated.
- It's over.
- Congratulations, Jong Kook.
- Thanks.
That Kim Jong Kook...
[I will get my revenge with
the water gun.]
Thank you.
[Jong Kook wins the key to the
red zone with his victory.]
He's on a different level from us.
[This frightening human being...
Must oust him before he gets any further.]
[All three step out of the room.]
Where did Suk Jin go?
He's not in the red zone yet?
That's strange.
Something feels very strange.
Kwang Soo's acting really strange today.
He kept staring at us while
we were playing our mission.
- I was going to go with the winner.
- Are you a spy?
What game is it that you want to play?
You're acting really weird.
- I haven't found a room yet.
- Then why do you want us to come with you?
I was going to wait for the winner
to go and find the room together.
- Have you found any rooms yet?
- Yeah, I just found one.
- Where is it? What's the mission?
- He's acting really strange.
- Or is he just that strange all the time?
- I think you're overly sensitive right now.
- Am I being too suspicious?
- You tend to be that way.
- I'm really not that strange.
- I never realized that about Kwang Soo.
But when you mentioned that
he was strange...
[Yoo-ames Bond tries to distract Jong Kook
from the suspicion that he's feeling.]
- Gary's found a room.
- Really?
[Who will be the one to enter
the black zone first?]
- What's this?
- I wonder what it could be?
- It looks like Gary's office.
- What is this?
- I think we can do this.
- What is this? Why are our name tags here?
- What is it?
We have to rip off the name tags
without the use of our hands.
- You can't utilize your hands.
- No, of course not.
- Please hand over one of your jewels.
- I feel like Gary's already checked this out.
You've already practiced this, haven't you?
- Can I play this? I can't, can I?
- You're still in the blue zone.
You can't play when
you're not even on our level.
[How dare the blue belt even try!]
Why did you come here
when you're not even on our level?
Just watch us play the game.
You can sit in the viewer's gallery.
[I'm actually here to take you down.]
- Why don't we all start here?
- Okay, let's start here.
[It's yet undecided as to who will
enter the black zone first.]
As I'm sure you've all guessed already,
your own name tags...
Ugh, seriously.
You're such a dirty player!
He just asked me to rip it off for him.
- What are you doing?
- What are you trying to do here?
[Red Zone Mission-
Self-name tag elimination- Start.]
[Oh?]
[Kwang Soo is using the ledge
of the TV stand.]
[Just then...]
Okay!
[Huh?]
[Already?]
[Kkuk runs over to the door wall
as soon as the game starts.]
[Sticks the name tag between the crack...]
[In one swoop... wins the game.]
[Wow, he really is something else.]
Can't you just do it normally
like the rest of us?
You were just going to
scratch it off on the ledge?
The moment he did that, you
guys looked like a bunch of cavemen.
You know what that means, don't you?
The skills you were using compared to him...
He's the advanced sort, while
you're still using caveman methods.
[Caveman methods.]
- Then is he going off to the black zone?
- He just won the key to the black zone.
[Jong Kook wins the key
to the black zone.]
[Black zone is the final level
in his attempt to save himself.]
[One of the black doors is the room
that's housing their sought after bodies.]
[The moment Jong Kook finds that room,
the race ends with Jong Kook's victory.]
The moment one of the members finds the
room and their body that's contained within
then the race will come to an end,
and both of you will lose.
- You win as soon as you find the right room?
- That's right.
[Jong Kook must be ousted before
he finds the correct room.]
I hope that you get eliminated
the moment you open the door.
Why are you saying that?
Why are you saying that to me?
If this door opens, then
he immediately wins the race.
I don't think this one will open.
I saw much bigger doors than this earlier.
[The two come around to
surround Jong Kook.]
[Pretends to be checking out the lock.]
Something feels very strange here.
[Mr. Capable smells
something fishy going on.]
Jae Suk, pull your hands
out of your pockets.
Come here, Jae Suk.
[Have I been caught?]
[Jong Kook is attempting to
check his pockets.]
- What are you trying to do?
- You really are too much.
[The water gun is thankfully
in Kwang Soo's pocket.]
Something's not right here.
Check my name tag.
- There's nothing on there.
- Is it okay?
Jae Suk is acting really strange.
I was trying to open the door...
then when I caught him
looking at me...
[After hearing Jong Kook's story,
Gary now has a suspicious look in his eyes.]
- Does that makes any sense to you?
- No, it doesn't.
[Yoo-ames Bond and Kwang-Buram
are in extreme danger.]
- Then he suddenly started looking elsewhere.
- Is there something in here?
[Jae Suk, what are we going to do?]
- What's going on here?
- Why did you look into the keyhole?
- Why is your hand in your pocket?
- I'll be honest with you.
[Is he honestly going to
tell them about their secret mission?]
I was trying to steal your diamond.
- Why are you doing that!
- Because I don't have many left.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Okay, mine are still here.
- Hey! Don't be like this, too!
- I'm not trusting anyone anymore.
[Mr. Gary lets go of his suspicions
and just goes on his way.]
- Ugh, seriously.
- Why are you acting like this?
- I'm sorry, but you still have five!
- No, I only have four.
- I only have two left.
- We don't have many left.
- Just give us one.
- The rule says that I can't give you one.
But I was told that stealing is allowed.
[Being shameless is the way to survival.]
- That's right, stealing is allowed.
- Just keep going.
We don't know what we may
end up needing them for.
I wish I could give you one, too.
[The newbie successor's expression
is frozen on his face.]
Jae Suk, find the blue zone room,
and finish the mission there.
But I have to find a room that unlocks first.
What if I end up losing another one?
- Hey, if I end up losing another jewel...
- You can come and see me then.
Come and see me when you only
have one jewel left.
- If I lose another one, then it's over.
- Come see me when you have one life left.
- I pretty much gave you that red mission.
- Okay.
Come and see me when you only have
one life left, okay?
[This is the time to take down
our most formidable opponent.]
[A direct hit on Kkuk's name tag.]
[Shoots the water gun,
and an obvious blank look on his face.]
- I'm going to search for my room.
- Okay.
But where did everyone go?
Why haven't I seen anyone around?
- You're really...
- There's a big black door on the 4th floor.
I'm going to go and check that out.
Keep checking down here.
I hope about ten taekwondo masters
fly out and put an end to you there.
- Let me know if you find anything here.
- Okay.
Kwang Soo, come here.
[Elimination of Mr. Capable had the
two shaking in their shoes.]
I could smell the alcohol in the solution,
and I was scared he'd catch that, too.
We could've been in big trouble earlier.
- Why do you hesitate so much?
- But that was Jong Kook!
We still have Gary left to eliminate.
- Gary's the only one left.
- Yes, we just need to eliminate Gary now.
Gary can't even move on
to the black zone anymore.
If it hadn't been for Ha Ha earlier,
Jong Kook may never have fallen for it.
- Heaven is looking out for us.
- You're right.
We have to win this.
If it hadn't been for Ha Ha's attempt earlier,
I would've been at a loss for what to say.
Wow, I can't believe he
fell for that story.
How did you even think to
say that though?
[Still trying to figure out
how he was ousted.]
[Loading the chamber with
the final hunt looming ahead.]
Okay, Gary's the only one left to go.
I just need to eliminate him to win.
[Once Gary is eliminated, then the
successor's mission is complete.]
[Mr. Gary has somehow survived
long enough to become the last target.]
[After having lost the previous game,
he's on the search for another red room.]
[Just then, Kwang-Buram is seen
walking towards the red zone.]
[Opens the door with the master key.]
[Going along with Jae Suk's plan
to lure Gary over to the room.]
It's the chair race!
I'm really good at this game.
Three players must be seated in
each one of the chairs
and the first person to cross
the finish line wins the race.
[Huh?]
[What are you doing?]
[The water gun newbie is playing out
a scene during a crucial moment like this?]
[I see you've been wanting
to do this for a long time...]
[Playing out the agent game
to his heart's content.]
What are you doing?
[Just then, Mr. Gary enters the room.]
- Why didn't you call for me?
- Where have you been, Gary?
I've been looking all over for you.
- Why didn't you call for me?
- I just walked in here.
You were trying to do something
by yourself, weren't you?
[If it had been anyone else but Gary,
then he would've been totally caught!]
- It's the chair race.
- Seriously?
[Awkward Kwang-Buram... How is he
to become the successor like this?]
I haven't even seen Ji Hyo around.
- Hey, what is this?
- Did you pass?
- I just passed.
Come on, let's hurry.
- This mission is too hard.
- What is this?
[The two spies are in a hurry to
finish the game and win the mission.]
- It's tough to win with these chairs.
- Is Jong Kook searching for the black room?
- I don't know.
- Why isn't anyone else around?
- Suk Jin was the last person I saw.
- I haven't seen anyone around.
That's what I'm saying.
- You have to bet a jewel.
- Do you know anything?
No, I don't know anything.
You know I can't hide things
like that.
I'm seriously not hiding anything.
[Jae Suk is now pretending
to be checking Kwang Soo out.]
You each have to bet a jewel
before you can play this mission.
- We can't touch the floor with our feet?
- Make sure that Kwang Soo doesn't cheat.
- These chairs are tough.
- Let's not go over the line.
I'm not going over the line.
Ready, set...
[Will Gary's body be found first,
or will they oust him first?]
[Chair race- Start.]
[All three are racing toward
their own personal goals.]
I think I may be able to win this.
[Jae Suk takes the lead.]
[Just then... Gary suddenly takes the lead.]
[Gary is in the clear lead.]
[Kwang-Buram stays close
on Gary's heels.]
[We can't let you win the game!]
Push me.
You have to push me!
I said, push me!
[Will Gary win the black key,
or will the duo win the mission?]
[Gary wins the mission!]
Hey, what's wrong with you?
That really hurts.
- My butt really hurts!
- That was a brutal game.
Gary, that was a really brutal game.
Hey, why couldn't you have
played better?
You should've pushed me
towards the line.
Give me back my jewel.
I may be able to win this.
Okay!
[Gary wins the black key.]
[We can't let him walk away like this...]
Sorry.
[Gary rushes off to the black zone.]
- We're right behind you.
- Wait for us.
- Why didn't you shoot him?
- I don't have any solution.
- Why didn't you reload?
- It keeps leaking.
[He used it all up while playing out
his agent scene earlier.]
You're driving me insane.
Why don't you carry the solution around?
- Hurry up and reload.
- Ugh, seriously.
[Jae Suk ends up reloading for Kwang Soo.]
You're a total mess.
I would've ended it a half hour ago.
- I know that I made a slight mistake...
- No, you even dropped the gun earlier!
- Gary's the only one left.
- This is our last one.
- Let's get this done.
- I know that this isn't easy.
This is really hard.
I don't think the water gun is my style.
The moment you hesitate,
that's when you die.
There's no need to go that far.
[The teacher and the successor
aren't a very good fit.]
[Off to get their last target, Gary.]
It's all over the moment
you and I eliminate Gary, right?
- What did you say?
- After we oust Gary...
Are you planning on betraying me?
You still have one final test left to go.
[If Gary can clear the black zone mission,
then he wins the race.]
Why isn't anyone around?
[Sees a black door!]
[Either his body awaits him, or a
mission waits behind these doors.]
[It opened!]
[What will he find inside?]
What is this?
Memorize the boards on the monitor
Move from the start to finish mark
in the order that is shown on the monitor.
- You're only going to show it once?
- Yes, just once.
Are you kidding me?
What are you guys doing?
[Must go in the order shown.]
I think I can get it in one try.
[Fumbling through his memory
and taking it one step at a time.]
[Onto his fifth step already
without any mistakes.]
Ugh, I'm starting to get confused.
[A safe step.]
[Next is his seventh step!]
[Fails the first of three attempts.]
Ugh, this is too hard.
[They must oust Gary
before he succeeds.]
Where's Gary?
Since I got that one wrong...
[Fails the second attempt.]
[It's a battle against time.
Who will end it first?]
What could it be?
[Victory is right in front of his eyes!
Starting his third and final attempt.]
- Did you succeed?
- Did you?
[They must shoot before
Gary succeeds!]
[There's no time!
Get out the water gun!]
[He only needs to shoot!]
- What's wrong with him?
- What are you doing!
Why are you ruining my game!
[Gary has no idea what just happened,
and is actually happy for the help.]
- I'm sorry, Gary.
- What's wrong with you!
- I know what to do now.
- Sorry, Gary.
Wait a minute.
Don't come near me!
- Gary.
- I know what to do now.
[A chaotic self-congratulatory ceremony.]
Wait, I know this one!
[Gary's unaware of what's happened,
and celebrates his win.]
That could've been big trouble.
Thanks, Jae Suk and Kwang Soo!
[Falls through even the last hole.]
- Gary, thanks so much.
- Thank you, Gary.
[For what?]
- I'm sorry, Gary.
- Didn't I just win?
Why can't you recognize this?
[Reveals the water gun.]
[What is this?]
We had it out in the open,
but Gary still didn't notice it.
[Feels even worse because
Gary is so oblivious to it.]
Again?
Come on, don't do this!
- Where did you get me?
- It's already disappeared.
[I thought I was going to win today!]
- What's he supposed to be?
- My pupil.
I'm Kwang-Buram.
- When I'm so close to the end?
- Yes.
[So close to winning!]
- Had we been a little later...
- Why is this happening to me!
I seriously thought I was going to win!
- Sorry, Gary.
- Don't do this to me!
Gary, I'm so sorry.
[Final member, Gary, is ousted.
Yoo-ames Bond and Kwang-Buram win.]
Okay, let's take these off.
[But this isn't the end!]
As of today, you will officially
become an agent.
The final step, which is another test...
only when all the members have been ousted,
and you and I are the only ones left...
that's when I'll reveal
the final test to you.
[What is the final test
that he'll have to face?]
- Is it all over?
- No, there's one final step left.
- There's a final step?
- Kwang Soo.
Rip off my name tag.
I want you to take off my name tag.
[Why does he want him to do that?]
Listen to me carefully.
The moment I hand this water gun over to you,
you have to immediately make a decision.
You can't hesitate.
If you shoot my name tag on
the count of three
then you'll be doing the water gun specials
all by yourself from now on.
But... if on the count of three...
No, wait.
No, hear me out first.
Hear me out, Kwang Soo.
[He can't help his instincts
from coming out.]
If you don't shoot on the
count of three...
then we will continue on as
Yoo-ames Bond and Kwang-Buram.
We can continue on with these specials
with the two of us as partners.
- I'll do it alone if I shoot.
- Yes, you alone.
Then I'll become a part of history.
Yoo-ames Bond and the water gun is no more.
[The shooting of the water gun will be
a forever farewell to Yoo-ames Bond.]
Wait.
[You need to think about this first!]
On the count of three, okay?
Have you made your decision?
- Yes.
- You need to think about it.
Here.
Take the water gun.
It'll be on the count of three.
[Time to determine their fate.]
[Will it be the two together,
or Kwang Soo on his own?]
[The end of this water gun's barrel
will determine the fate of history.]
I have faith in your decision.
I don't wish for Yoo-ames Bond
to come to an end.
[Just what will he choose?]
[The water gun backfires.]
[How did this happen?]
[About 30 minutes ago, while Gary and
Kwang Soo were waiting for the chair race.]
[Jae Suk chooses a water gun
from the ammunition room.]
This will determine whether Kwang Soo and I
will continue to work together or not.
This is his final test.
Let's go.
[This was the final test that
Yoo-ames Bond had put in place.]
[Traitor, Kwang Soo, fails the final test
just as Yoo-ames Bond had predicted.]
Just as I had predicted.
You're finished.
I, alone, will continue with
the water guns.
- You're finished.
- What is this?
If you hadn't shot the water gun,
then both of us would've won.
But since you shot the water gun...
You, traitor.
You cannot be changed.
You cannot become a secret agent.
[Kwang-Buram self-terminates.]
- Wait...
- The original Bond.
Me!
And the second Bond...
- Will forever be...
- What are you doing!
I'm Kwang-Buram!
Yoo-ames Bond makes his return,
and alone, he shall remain.
- Am I finished?
- Kwang-Buram... goodbye.
What is this!
- But I eliminated everyone!
- Yoo-ames Bond will live on.
- Coming soon!
- Kwang-Buram is finished?
No!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Great to see you, my friend!]
[Running Man members'
best friends are here!]
[A trip down the memory lane
with their best friends.]
[Their friendships,
that seemed to be forever...]
[The gold key presents
itself in front of them.]
[Will their friendships be tested?]
[Will it be their friendships or the gold?
The display of their true friendship.]
- I'm so happy.
- What's wrong with you?
- Am I too old?
- Yes, you're too old.
[Next Week on Running Man-
Gold or Friendship?]