Subtitles by DramaFever
[2015 Blockbuster Variety Show]
[A match between the police and
Mafias who lost their memory!]
[Jang Yoon Joo, Jung Man Sik.]
[Hwang Jung Min]
[Are you the police or the Mafia?]
[Starring Yoo Jae Suk]
[Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook]
[Ha Ha, Lee Kwang Soo]
[Gary, Song Ji Hyo]
[Hwang Jung Min]
[Jung Man Sik]
[Jang Yoon Joo]
[What's this?]
[After regaining consciousness]
[there are people
scattered all around.]
[I now realize...]
[I don't know who I am,
or where I am...]
[wriggle]
What is this?
[They don't remember anything
before they blacked out.]
- What is this?
- What's that?
[Handcuffs?]
[A police badge?]
Save me!
Save me! Help!
[Why is he there...]
What are you?
Who are you people?
Save me! Help me!
- Save me!
- Who is he?
[They start waking up one by one...]
Who are you?
Are you the one who did this to me?
- You look vulgar!
- What?
Who is he?
[A man and a woman who seem to have]
[lost their memory together.]
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Why am I here?
They sent a nymph from above.
Who are you?
[Unrecognizable faces]
[There are suspicious
objects laying around.]
- What's that!
- Don't come any closer!
- Don't come closer!
- What are you doing?
[What happened here?]
- What's happening?
- What?
I can't remember anything!
[That's a little too much...]
I'm the police!
[The objects are the only clue]
[to find out who they are.]
[Meanwhile...]
[The same thing happened next door.]
[There's a person in here, too...]
[Jang Yoon Joo]
[Handcuffs?]
[And a police badge?]
[I don't remember anything...]
[There's someone else coming
out from a warehouse...]
[Jung Man Sik]
[He also does not remember anything.]
[And then...]
[A man who hasn't woken up yet...]
[Smoky air...]
[An unfamiliar office...]
[Where is this place?]
[A police badge...]
[What does this have to do with me?]
[Hwang Jung Min]
We need to act, so don't say anything!
- There's someone here!
- Who?
[It's already chaotic,
who else is here?]
Please untie me!
Who is it?
What's Jang Yoon Joo doing here?
[Everyone's sensitive
due to memory loss.]
How have you been, Yoon Joo?
[There's more!]
Congratulations on your wedding!
[Man Sik is here as well!]
How did you get here, Man Sik?
[They lost their memory but
are happy to see each other.]
[Wow!]
[The brother's visit.]
[What's with him?]
- Bring it on!
- Bring what?
You guys bring it on!
Why is everyone wearing black?
[Everyone who has lost their
memory is in one place.]
Where are you going?
[Giraffe's echo from faraway.]
Kwang Soo, you'll still be in it!
The cameraman can get you.
[Then, that's okay.]
Do you have to do this?
Wait, am I the police?
I have handcuffs, too.
[There are only objects to tell
them who they might be.]
This is the 'Find Your Identity Race.'
Between the 10 people
there's a mix of police and Mafias.
[The Mafias and police are mixed!]
[A few hours ago]
[There was a large-scale plan
to arrest a Mafia family.]
[However...]
[That's how they all
lost their memory.]
Find your identity with the hints
and if you are certain
that you are the police
You have to arrest the Mafia and stop them
from smuggling gold at the final mission.
If you are certain
that you're the Mafia
you need to avoid the police and
smuggle the gold to your boss.
What do we do with someone
that already looks like the Mafia?
[Huh? Me?]
He looks like the Mafia.
Then, how about the detective finds
the gold and gives it to the Mafia?
[His role in the movie 'The Unjust.']
Oh my god!
What are you going to choose?
Yoon Joo keeps asking me what I am.
[Just pick whichever you want.]
[The objects can be hints.]
I don't think the handcuffs necessarily
mean you're the police.
I had both the handcuffs and the badge.
- You're the police.
You're the Mafia!
[Did the police wrap the
Mafia with duct tape?]
You were just sleeping.
You're just a duct tape.
He's so funny!
My hair was being pulled by Ji Hyo,
maybe it was before the arrest.
Right?
Man Sik said Gary looks like a husband
who was caught gambling.
[You went gambling?]
[Sorry...]
He probably lost the
deed to house gambling.
That's right!
If you get caught, you die.
[Find Your Identity Race, starts!]
[Ten people lost
their memory within seconds.]
[Am I police? Or the Mafia?]
[Find your identity and
complete the final mission!]
[Find Your Identity Race.]
[They've split off into two cars
based on their assumptions.]
So, we lost our memory
The Mafia just needs to
smuggle the gold and leave.
- Before that the police must stop them.
- We have to find our identity first.
The most important thing is
that the proportions are the same
between the Mafia and the detectives.
And we don't know if there are
more of Mafias or detectives, yet.
But usually there are more detectives.
There are more Mafias.
There are more thugs.
They pick thugs randomly, and you have
to take a test to become a detective.
[The king of logic.]
They pick thugs randomly!
And detectives need to take a test.
Nobody here knows if they're
the Mafia, or the police.
- We don't know yet.
- We don't know.
And it's a game, so it has
nothing to do with your image.
But I still think you're a Mafia.
I wish it was based on my image.
I don't want to think about it,
I wish I was the Mafia.
[Just then, the other car
drives up next to them.]
Jung Min really looks like...
Are you the police?
- Are you going on a picnic?
- Jung Min, you look like a prisoner!
- He's scary...
- I feel like...
- Oh my!
- He spat!
[He dominates them with
his method acting.]
Did you see that?
That's when the drunk guys says...
Is he your father? Huh?
[He attacks back
with his method acting.]
[Stop, criminal!]
[The police's chase of rage
in order to stop crime.]
[Driving fast and carefully is
an important skill to have.]
[That's why we prepared this mission.]
- I remember this!
- Three-wheel bicycle?
- It's a race!
- This is so old!
The first mission of the
Find Your Identity Race
is the chase of rage.
Because there is always a chase.
You ride the three-wheel bicycle
and you have to get to the finish
line avoiding the obstacles.
First to fifth place
winners' memory comes back partially.
- I have to win this one.
- I have to win.
We might never know who we are?
- We will never tell you.
- Really?
We have to live a full day
without knowing who we are?
With these tight clothes?
This tight, light blue shirt?
This keeps getting stuck in my armpits.
[The chase of rage track.]
[Pass the slope.]
[Cross the puddle in a U-turn zone.]
[A banana field]
[A steep, elevated road]
[A continuous S-shaped course
over a muddy road.]
[An automatic car wash]
[And lastly, a secret passage.]
[First race group, Jung Min, Ha Ha,
Yoon Joo, Jae Suk, and Man Sik.]
Isn't this unfair?
Jung Min's on the inner track...
- That's not important!
- Be quiet.
[Yoon Joo and Jung Min switch
places because of Ha Ha.]
You're dead now,
I'm going to drown you!
- We will bring you the shoes later.
- Yes!
I'm going to start later.
When they struggle up ahead,
I'll just cycle past.
- Ready...
- Good luck!
Ready, set!
[The chase of rage, round one!]
[Yoon Joo is speeding past!]
[The guys are struggling on the slope.]
- Ha Ha's short.
- He's too short.
[Man Sik is barely getting past.]
[Yoon Joo's in the lead.]
[Whoosh]
[Yoon Joo and Ha Ha
enter the U-course.]
[Whoosh, whoosh]
[They are all fighting
for third place.]
Jung Min, push Jae Suk away!
[You want me to push Jae Suk?]
[Splash]
[Did I do a good job?]
Fine!
[Run, run]
[Stop, there!]
[An unexpected triple-axel
on the banana field.]
[Jung Min is ready to
attack the leads.]
Why... why?
What are you doing?
Why me?
- He's a Mafia!
- Mafia!
[Go away!]
What are you doing!
It fits him so well.
[Within five minutes, he
became the king of cheating.]
It's so natural!
[There's no way he's a cop.]
[Run, run]
[Why is he here?]
[I don't know anymore.]
[Don't speed going downhill.]
They have nothing to do with victory.
- They look like they're having fun.
- It looks fun!
[Bring it on!]
[He moves their bike in the meantime.]
[Don't go without us!]
[A forceful banana pack for his skin.]
[Yoon Joo's already heading for
the car wash while they fight.]
[Dolphin scream]
[She arrives at the last
course after the car wash.]
[Man Sik arrives at the car wash, too.]
What is this?
It's cold!
[Somewhat miserable]
Man Sik, hurry!
Let's go down together!
Are you okay?
[The car wash stole his hair...
it's a man's dignity!]
Hurry up!
Man Sik, hurry!
His father's here.
[Man Sik went in, and
out comes his father!]
Where did he go?
[Struggle, struggle]
[Yoon Joo and Man Sik
finally completed the race.]
[First place, Yoon Joo.]
Did you fall?
[Second place, Man Sik.]
The car wash.
Are you okay?
[Do I look okay?]
Don't come closer, please.
You told him to hold me down, first!
[I've warmed up, I'm ready
for the next round.]
[Consolation race, Jung Min, Ha Ha,
Suk Jin, Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Gary.]
[Round two, Ji Hyo 1st
place, Jong Kook 2nd place.]
- Why am I here?
- They are dirty players.
[Their name tags are muddy.]
We haven't eve begun yet!
- They're so dirty!
- I've never seen actors do this!
[The number one cheating candidate.]
Are there any rules, anyway?
- Well one person's going to win...
- It's going to end somehow!
Two people get to go to the finals.
Go ahead, first.
Ready! Gary, move back...
- Go back.
- I'm so nervous.
We're starting!
[They all cheated at the same time.]
[It's too perfect as
if they'd planned it.]
No one can go! No one!
It'll never end!
Just then, Jung Min speeds ahead!
[Kick]
[Jung Min goes bare feet.]
[But Jae Suk's in the lead in a flash.]
[Where are you going!]
[He holds his bike and walks.]
[Ha Ha whooshes past
without getting caught.]
Catch Ha Ha! Hurry, catch him!
[Jung Min chases him with bare feet!]
[Come here!]
Look, he's doing it again!
He's a troublemaker, that boy!
[Dive]
Grab Jae Suk!
Fine, be like that!
Grab Ha Ha!
You have to catch Ha Ha!
[Push, push]
[Splash]
They're starting the neverending game.
[The neverending war of cheating.]
[Ha Ha and Gary take this
opportunity to speed ahead!]
[Jung Min's bicycle!]
He's miming!
[He's miming a three-wheel bicycle.]
[Ha Ha's already at the see-saw.]
[He jumps down
the see-saw by himself.]
There's one more left!
[First place, Ha Ha]
[The neverending fight
for second place.]
[Hwang Jung Min is angry!]
[I want to go forward!]
[Bring it on!]
[He was a really scary person...]
[Jae Suk is in the lead
for second place.]
[Where are you going!]
Take his bike!
Please!
Please, my butt!
He's such a dirty player.
Let's all start at the same time.
- Wait.
- Bring your bike!
My bike is here.
[While Jae Suk steals his
bike back from Kwang Soo]
[Gary and Jung Min race ahead.]
[The last round of a
crazy cheating war.]
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin join in.]
[Just then!]
Go down!
[Kwang Soo locks Gary
and Jung Min's bikes.]
[Right then, Jae Suk
brushes past them!]
[He wins an advantage
from a difficult situation.]
What is this?
[Second place, Jae Suk]
[He's more happy than
an actual victory.]
I finally got away from this hell!
[Ha Ha and Jae Suk get to the finals.]
[Suk Jin, Gary, Kwang Soo,
and Jung Min fail.]
[At least we don't have
to play this anymore!]
[It's not over, I have a lot of
cheating skills left to show...]
[Finals, Man Sik, Yoon Joo, Ji Hyo,
Ha Ha, Jong Kook, Jae Suk.]
- He's the king of cheating!
- He really is.
He won because you grabbed our bikes!
Jae Suk, I kind of helped...
There were all sorts
of cheating involved.
Only five people get the hints, right?
- Only the last person...
- Just don't be the last one!
Everyone else is an enemy except me.
[Finals, starts!]
[Yoon Joo and Man Sik are in the lead.]
Just don't be last!
Yoon Joo's going!
[Just then, Ji Hyo speeds past.]
[The expert of three-wheeled bicycles.]
- Catch her!
- It's because she rides bikes often.
[Ji Hyo and Yoon Joo are too fast.]
[But Man Sik is easy to deal with.]
[The last spurt of the lower ranks.]
You have to catch Man Sik!
- Don't come!
- I have to catch you!
Don't come!
[Stop there!]
[Ji Hyo is still in the lead.]
[Man Sik lost all his energy.]
[Tiredly falls]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook
take this chance.]
[The side effect of his tight shirt.]
It's so cold!
[First place Ji Hyo and second place
Yoon Joo enter the car wash.]
[Unique ladies, the power
of the lead group.]
[If they both get on the see-saw together,
they'll at least get second place.]
[The rest of them all
enter at the same time.]
Just wait a little bit!
Let's go!
[The ladies enter the
final course together.]
[First place Ji Hyo,
second place Yoon Joo.]
[Third and fourth are
Jae Suk and Jong Kook.]
Who's third place?
[Third place Jae Suk,
fourth place Jong Kook.]
This is so meaningless!
[Now the only thing left is the loser.]
I feel like I'm dragging someone.
[Bingo]
[Man Sik's father is back.]
He ages on the way back.
[The loser doesn't get any hints.]
Should I run faster?
This guy... you're making me sorry!
What are you doing?
I'm really embarrassed, but...
[What should I do...]
[I can't give up...]
- Your hand...
- No...
I don't think I'll ever
hold hands with you.
We could be colleagues!
[Slide]
[Now's the time!]
[The final spurt!]
[Who will be the loser]
[that doesn't get the
hint after all this?]
[Fifth place, Ha Ha]
[Man Sik gets last place.]
[Father...]
You must be hurt...
Man Sik... just sit there.
Don't get up.
[I'm sorry.]
You match with the bike!
It's so fitting!
The color is the same!
I'll just be here, casually...
[Ji Hyo got first place
and regained three memories.]
[Handcuffing someone's hand]
[A police hat, and police car]
[Two hands that opened a
cabinet with gloves on.]
[Then, that means...]
[Yoon Joo regains two memories.]
[Two hands that were handcuffed]
[Two hands holding a
treasure with gloves.]
[My identity is...]
[Jae Suk also regains
two memories.]
[A call from Boss]
[A wanted poster]
[Then am I...]
[Jong Kook only regains one memory.]
[A text message by the
Boss, giving an order.]
[Then my identity is...]
[And Ha Ha regains one memory!]
[A secret ledger
with transaction information]
[Then I am...]
[There's always a line you
mustn't cross at a crime scene!]
[The line only police can cross.]
[Do not cross - Police Line]
[That's why we've prepared
the Blockbuster Police line!]
This is the second mission.
This is an important
mission for cops.
Cross the police line!
There are two people in
each police line zone.
You have to start behind the line
and when I whistle, you need to cross
the line and take out the flag.
So one person will fail each time.
It's really cruel!
I already had a taste of hell,
this is even more hellish.
It's only going to end
when someone collapses.
Different from the previous mission
You have a chance of
calling a secret agent.
- This is nice.
- You can ask them questions.
That's amazing!
Man Sik said that even if his team wins,
he doesn't want to be the protagonist.
- Why?
- He always has a supporting role.
It doesn't work that way here.
- You can be the protagonist today.
- No, no...
You might be the protagonist today.
- You were the protagonist earlier!
- In reverse...
Whoever stands beside me
can be the protagonist.
[A kingmaker for the true protagonist.]
He's so cool.
It'll be hard for Man Sik...
it's a little tight.
What about you?
You're both the same.
[Cross the police line, round one.]
So we go in pairs?
[Who will be the first one to fail?]
I'll show you what cheating is...
[They're all worried
they'll be cheated.]
Nice, nice!
Ready, set!
[My secret identity...]
[I will find the hint here!]
[Scream!]
[Automatic screams as
soon as they start.]
[Everyone's crawling?]
[They all crawl together...]
[Yoon Joo who still hasn't
gotten used to the cheating]
[Finally starts crawling.]
[Un-decipherable]
[Welcome, cheaters]
[Gary and Man Sik pass]
[Where are you going!]
[Jung Min uses addition
cheating skills.]
[Jung Min got the last flag!]
It's hurts so much!
[Yoon Joo is last.]
I was hit six times!
I actually tried crossing the line...
[I've never seen such dirty players...]
Everyone crawled...
Jang Yoon Joo is eliminated.
What were you thinking?
[He's the king of cheaters.]
I'm with Man Sik,
so it gets narrow at the end!
We can't go out at the same time!
We were stuck!
Yoon Joo, please go to the side.
Yoon Joo, it's okay!
Don't talk to me!
- Don't crawl!
- I crossed normally!
You can't just let everyone pass!
Only one has to drop!
Don't leave him alone!
- What are you doing?
- Let's make a pair!
- Where are you going to go?
- This way...
- There are three people here!
- Do you want to fail with me?
- I see.
- Don't crawl!
- This side might be easy.
- Yes, let's cross it quickly.
Let's cooperate!
- You know that, right?
- I know.
We'll help each other.
It's not my fault if you get hurt!
- Me, too!
[They're still intense over here.]
[Cross the police line,
second round starts!]
[They're violently entering]
[as if they're doing
a field inspection.]
It hurts!
It's tight!
[Everyone is screaming
in the overpopulated side.]
[It's easier for Jung Min.]
[Who created this game?]
[It's still very hard for him.]
[What an advantage
to stand next to Big-nose!]
[Jong Kook and Jung Min pass first.]
[Come on, Big-nose!]
[Total wreck]
[Two flags for Suk Jin, Gary,
and Kwang Soo!]
[I want to get the flag!]
[I want to find out my identity!]
[Three cornered battle for the flag]
[Who's going to win?]
[Kwang Soo and Gary
acquired the flags!]
[Oh, my brother...]
Suk Jin, come here!
This isn't even funny!
- We came together...
- In the same car...
Did you block Jung Min?
I couldn't because he
might have elbowed me.
He doesn't look back.
He actually hits me
when we film movies.
And that hurts a lot!
- Let's go through together.
- Okay, okay.
[For the third round, he proposes
an alliance with Ha Ha.]
There are three people
who didn't get any hints.
[It'll be easy again.]
[Cross the Police Line!
The third round starts!]
[Jung Min goes first
and Ha Ha follows?]
[Giraffe crawls again.]
Don't crawl!
[Where are you going, Giraffe?]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook
pass at the same time.]
[Right before Giraffe goes out,
he gets caught!]
[Jung Min and Ha Ha...]
[Headlock?]
[I thought they put arms
around each other...]
[In the meantime, Ji Hyo passes.]
We shouldn't fight
with each other!
Both of you can survive!
What are they going to do?
[Since their alliance broke,
he doesn't want to let him go.]
Let me go!
There's only one flag!
Hook him with your legs!
[Will Jung Min end up
losing because of Ha Ha?]
[I can't let you go!]
[Did you think
our promise was a joke?]
[Brother... this isn't right...]
[The dirty legs...]
[He lost them!]
[My paramour is gone.
My beloved paramour is gone.]
[Ha Ha grabs the last flag!]
[I can't believe
Ha Ha tricked me.]
[He was careless with Ha Ha.]
[And Ha Ha strikes Jung Min
on the back of his head.]
[Why did I team up with him?]
- It's like a movie!
- Jung Min hgas no hint!
[Hwang Jung Min drops
out of the third round.]
We need to win two more rounds
to get a hint.
Jung Min and I won't
figure out our identities.
- I'd rather not know it.
- We'll still be able to find it.
[All of a sudden, music starts.]
[Running Man members
start dancing automatically.]
It's so funny!
[He's adopted right away.]
[Everyone is dancing now.]
[As if they're having
a party on the meadow]
[but they start the fight
at the sound of a whistle.]
[The fourth round starts
all of a sudden.]
That's scary!
[The flags are getting less,
their combat powers move up.]
[In a hurry]
[After Jong Kook and Ha Ha]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
acquire a flag.]
Look at Ji Hyo!
[The police line supports me.]
[Ji Hyo crosses it like Agent Smith.]
Is it Man Sik who failed?
Brother Man Sik!
Where did you get caught?
- Man Sik!
- He's sitting on a hammock.
He's on vacation.
I just want to get some rest.
[Do not cross! Police Line]
[Ji Hyo fails at the fifth round.]
I'm sorry.
Are there anyone who'll get two hints?
- Jong Kook.
- Jae Suk, Jong Kook and Ha Ha?
[The informer can only answer
yes or no.]
[The information they can get
is up to the questions they ask!]
- Hello.
- Yes, Yoo Jae Suk.
The place that I get my pay check is...
the boss?
The answer is... no.
[As he hears the answer,
he remembers something.]
[A police badge under his feet!]
[Two hands that put
a wanted poster.]
[Answering a call
from 'the boss.']
[He remembers it all at once...]
I'm sure now. I'm the police.
[Is he really a police man?]
The hint I have from before,
has the word 'task.'
Is this 'task' something illegal?
Yes, it is.
[As soon as he hears the answer,
he remembers...]
[a lead pipe and a pair of
handcuffs near him.]
[A message from the his boss
about his job.]
Through the questions I asked,
I cleared confirmed my identity.
I'm a Mafia.
- I'll ask a question.
- Yes.
Am I a government worker?
Am I being chased by someone?
Yes, you are.
You're not a government worker.
[Ji Hyo grabbed Gary's hair.]
[The handcuffs under Ha Ha's feet.]
[The ledger that Ha Ha remembers.]
I'm sure...
I'm a Mafia.
Mafia.
[Are Gary and Ha Ha really the Mafia?]
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Yes, hello.
Did I...
do anything wrong?
No, you didn't do anything wrong.
I'll hang up now.
That's not what I meant. Wait!
[The conversation is over.]
Hey... hey!
[Anyway... let me gather up
the fragments of memories.]
[I was covered by duct tape]
[and I did nothing wrong...]
[That means...]
[I'm a cop?]
[The third mission of
Finding The Identity Race]
[The highlight of police tasks,
the undercover duty]
[Right here, right now]
What do we need to do here?
[a very special stakeout
will be played.]
[The car for the stakeout.]
[The hideout is in front of
a convenience store?]
[What secret does
this empty store have?]
You know, I have no idea
how to play this mission.
- We need to go there secretly.
- Without getting caught?
How is that possible?
From those guys?
How is it possible?
There are so many people.
It's those guys?
- It's impossible.
- They're living their own life.
Each one has a role.
[Is that a camera?]
They're aiming for us.
[Who are these men with cameras?]
How do we do this?
- Inside, we should...
- I think that's more difficult.
This is the last mission
that can help finding your identity.
[Five minutes ago...]
The third mission is
'the undercover shopping
at the convenience store.'
[No one's excited over shopping...]
- There's a convenience store outside.
- Yes, I saw it.
There are four judges with cameras
inside and outside.
You need to buy the appointed items
and go back to the car
while you avoid them.
We shouldn't be photographed.
The mission doesn't just end
when they take your picture.
You keep doing the mission
until you go back to the car.
Each photo is counted as five seconds.
In that case, even if
you finish the mission fast
the total time can be long
if they've taken a lot of pictures.
This time, we'll also give out
the hint to five people.
Two people will carry the mission
so it's one on one battle.
Who you're against
is very important.
Man Sik seems he'll be
on their camera easily.
Look at his face.
He looks like he's absentminded.
- Is it very tough for you?
- A little.
[A little tough]
[Putting on a prim air]
[I should have stayed home and rested.]
The first pair are...
- Kwang Soo and Yoon Joo.
- Us, together?
If one of us comes back,
only that person passes?
Yes, that'll happen.
I can't lock the door.
- Can I?
- You can't lock the door.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
- Are you going to get out?
- Let's get out.
But my door is facing that way.
- If I get off, then...
- I really don't know.
[I'll get going first.]
[An eye like a hawk]
[Figuring out the
judges' pattern is a must!]
They move in a pattern.
[This is all about timing!]
When he goes back this time...
[Let's go!]
[Startled]
[At the moment he was going to go]
[Athlete Jang runs out.]
[She scared me!]
[A cute landing]
[It's not cute at all!]
Make a right!
She's on your right!
[Turns] [Anxious]
[Challenge! Super(market) model.jpg]
[The model was caught
in the camera first.]
[The judge turns away
after taking a photo.]
[This is good timing!]
[Giraffe finally escapes
from the car.]
[Turns]
[You cold-hearted man,
I'll follow you.]
[Struggle.jpg]
[Athlete Jang enters the store.]
[Yoo Joo's shopping list]
[Baby wipes, Shrimp ramen, Iced water]
[Crab chips, Underwear]
[The crab chips are right there!]
[Grabs]
[Crab chips]
[I can't lose!]
[Giraffe advances.]
[Giraffe is cornered.]
[I'm on the way to meet you!]
[Giraffe's crisis!]
[Smile, Giraffe.]
[He turns around and goes back?]
[Giraffe is missing.]
[Where did Giraffe go?]
[Ta-da!] [The god of petty
tricks found a shield.]
[I'm not afraid of anything anymore.]
[Turns]
[Unhidden.jpg]
[Even a part of the body
is counted as a picture.]
[Kwang Soo enters the store.]
[Greetings.jpg]
Please, give me a pair of socks.
You can't do that!
You're a bad guy!
- Did you just call me a bad guy?
- How can you do that?
[Athlete Jang only needs iced water.]
Help me, where's the Pocky?
[Kwang Soo's shopping list]
[Black bean ramen, Socks, smoked eggs]
[Banana milk, Pocky]
Where's the water?
Do you have smoked eggs?
[I just need to avoid
getting photographed.]
Ma'am...
[Slowly walking]
I think I'm photographed.
[Walking table.jpg]
[Why don't you just put it down?]
I'm sorry.
Can you go to another side?
Why are you...
[She finds her last item.]
Could you pack them in a bag?
- Yoon Joo!
- It's so unfair...
I'd like to cancel this one!
[He's trying to cancel Yoon Joo's item.]
- I want to cancel it.
- Can you take care of my stuff first?
I was here first!
[Yoo Joo is avoiding the camera.]
You're really a bad guy!
[Nothing's going to stop me!]
[The angry cash-out.jpg]
- Put this away!
- I won't do it again!
[It feels like I'm naked!]
Please give it to me.
Ma'am, where's the Pocky sticks?
[Athlete Jang's done shopping.]
[She just needs to go back to the car.]
[Escaped!]
[It wasn't bad.]
[I'm going to finish up
by going back to the car!]
[A powerful bow!]
[Her items are dropped!]
What's going on?
[I feel more embarrassed than hurt!]
[I guess she's buying lots of things.]
[Embarrassed]
[Jang Yoon Joo completes
the undercover shopping.]
[Kwang Soo's done shopping.]
[I need to avoid to getting
photographed at all costs!]
[Escaped!]
[I forgot!]
[Giraffe in grief.jpg]
[Go away!]
[Giraffe completes
the undercover shopping.]
You see the tent over there?
You can go there and watch other people.
You can go now.
[Athlete Jang vs. Giraffe]
[Who will be the winner?]
[Yoon Joo's photo collection:
The woman never stretches her back.]
[Kwang Soo's photo collection:
It's not a sin to look ridiculous.]
[Kwang Soo: 4':38"]
[Yoon Joo: 4'12"]
[Kwang Soo: 5':13"]
[Yoon Joo: 4':37"]
[Jang Yoon Joo wins.]
[Undercover shopping, the second round]
[Hwang Jung Min vs. Grasshopper]
- They're going back and forth.
- Yes, we need to go
when he turns away like that.
But the other one stands up.
At that moment,
we need to hurry up and go.
Yes, it's about time.
After he passes...
[I have no hints.
I'll win over you, Grasshopper.]
[Move!]
[Hwang Jung Min vs.
Grasshopper starts!]
[Wrong way.jpg]
[Actor Hwang and Grasshopper
are cornered.]
What's going on?
[Knock and enter.jpg]
Why did you come all the way?
[He turned around,
it's our chance!]
[Perfect aim]
[Bring it on.jpg]
[Yoo and Hwang enter the store.]
Wait, where is it? Where is it?
[Should I come forward?]
[I can't let Actor Hwang
acquire any hints.]
[The Grasshopper's
antennae are working!]
[He found it!]
[Pantyhose]
[A dangerous moment!]
[Perfect hiding. Jpg]
[The one who conquers
the convenience store]
He keeps taking pictures.
[Keeping hiding.jpg]
- I'm done.
- Where's razor?
[Grasshopper finishes shopping.]
Razor?
Where's the lollipop? It's here!
[Better than nothing.jpg]
Thank you.
[He finished paying.]
I can't find it.
[Escaped]
[Feeling free and refreshed!]
[Aw... he took my picture.]
I think I got photographed a lot.
[Grasshopper completes
the undercover shopping.]
I got photographed a lot.
Is Jae Suk done already?
He's so annoying.
He's good at games.
I've bought everything right.
[How is Actor Hwang doing?]
This is tiring.
[He avoided... not!]
[Okay, another one.]
[Stop taking photos
when I ask nicely.jpg]
[Wobble]
[I was surprised but
I don't bend my back.]
Jung Min is getting
photographed a lot.
He gave up.
He looks like a housewife
who's grocery shopping.
[Relaxed]
What is he doing?
[Hwang Jung Min's visit
to a convenience store]
- He's not good at games at all.
- He's just like me.
He's not a Running Man expert.
[Grasshopper's photo collection:
The flying Yoo Punk.]
[Actor Hwang's photo collection]
[A star's normal daily life]
[Jae Suk: 3':31"]
[Jung Min: 4':09"]
[Kwang Soo: 3':46"]
[Yoon Joo: 4':59"]
[Jae Suk wins.]
- We'll be back!
- Good luck!
Let's go, Ji Hyo.
[Kkuk vs. Blank Ji]
He's going to turn right...
Should we go?
Jong Kkuk, wait.
[Hide well...]
[Hide!]
[We're just friends.jpg]
What's Jong Kook doing?
[Kkuk and Blank Ji rush to the store.]
[You've got caught!]
[Short trackers.jpg]
He's right there.
I found apple juice!
[Careful, careful]
[The temptation of ramen.jpg]
Where's the red bean jelly?
Oh, it's here!
[I don't eat junkfood.jpg]
- Jong Kook will...
- Be eliminated!
I hope so.
I really hope he fails.
I hope so, too. He's too good.
[Everyone hope for Kkuk's failure.]
Jong Kook! Hurry up!
[Escaped!]
[Another shot when she's careless.]
Is this the one? Oh, my!
[Handsome butt.jpg]
[I bought them all!]
Ten seconds left.
Three, two, one!
Eliminated!
[Time exceeded.]
Kim Jong Kook is eliminated.
[I should have gotten
familiar with snacks...]
[Kkuk is new to convenience store.]
[Stakeout suits Blank Ji.]
[Undercover shopping, the fourth round]
[Gary vs. Ha Ha]
They're coming! They're running!
They're going!
[Nervous]
[Calm down and wait
for the right moment.]
[Wrong timing!]
[Octopus and squid.jpg]
[Even their faces look funny.]
They look like
they posed for a picture.
They caught us!
- The poncho is right here.
- Where's the tooth brush?
[Ha Ha keeps finding his items.]
How come you don't
have smoked eggs?
[He found toiletries.]
[We found Ha Ha.]
I bought them all!
[We caught Ha Ha again.]
[Not Ha Ha.jpg]
[Ha Ha goes back after shopping.]
[Gary's having a photo
time by himself.]
[He looks like a Hallyu star.]
Hurry up, Ma'am!
[Gary's done shopping
in a flood of flashlights.]
[Gary's photo collection:
Clean, clear, and under control.]
[Gary... .jpg]
[Gary likes corners.jpg]
[Ha Ha's photo collection:
The mystic to the core.]
[Ha Ha...  .jpg]
[Ha Ha is handsome.jpg]
[Ha Ha: 3':43"] [Gary: 3'58"]
[Ha Ha: 4':08"] [Gary: 4'43"]
[Ha Ha wins.]
[Undercover shopping, the fifth round]
[Jung Man Sik vs. Big-nose]
This is a war.
None of us has hints.
We can't back down!
- Should we go together?
- Should we?
- We could be nice to each other.
- Let's go together.
[Let's break through
the siege together!]
[Peek]
Do you want to go first?
[Goodbye, Big-nose!]
He just leaves.
[Faster than anyone]
[Nice timing!]
[Man Sik goes straight?]
[He got caught by the judges outside.]
[New record!
Three pictures upon arrival.]
[Man Sik is visiting
the convenience store!]
[Big-nose comes in the store.]
[Snap!]
[Who will end up getting a hint?]
I have no hints!
Ramen, ramen!
[A flood of flashlights]
[Are they really trying to
avoid the cameras?]
[I'd rather be enjoying it,
if I can't avoid it.]
[The dream of stars,
being in a flood of flashlights.]
[Experiencing the admiration of an
awards ceremony at a convenience store.]
[2015, The Convenience Store
Art Awards Ceremony]
[Wow! Actor Jung.jpg]
Man Sik keeps getting photographed.
Man Sik is funnier
when he doesn't talk.
He's one of those.
[Simple and naive, Actor Jung]
Where can I find an underwear?
Where can I find underpants?
[Man Sik and Big-nose
finish shopping.]
[Big-nose escapes
first in a flashlight.]
[Man Sik goes out of the store.]
[Big-nose vs Man Sik,
what's the result?]
[Man Sik's photo collection:
Almost a crime scene]
[Big-nose's photo collection:
The ultimate poverty]
We've added it up, and by one minute...
The winner is...
- Ji Suk Jin!
- I can't believe this!
- Man Sik, don't worry.
- He gave me the game.
There are two people
without any hints.
[The two actors have to guess
their identities without a clue.]
- Veteran!
- What are you going to do, Veteran!
What kind of a hint will it be?
I'll show it to you all.
Take a look at this information.
This time, we can't ask questions.
[The Police-Mafia ratio
is five to five.]
[Two of the Mafia's Surnames
start with 'J']
- Who are they?
- It's me.
- Are there three people?
- Yes.
- Yoon Joo knows.
- Ji Suk Jin, Jang Yoon Joo
- and Jung Man Sik.
- Oh, I see.
Now it's confusing.
[Who am I?
And Who are my colleagues?]
[The police and the Mafia
that lost their memories!]
[To win the final mission,
you need to find your identity!]
[Who am I?]
[What will be their choices?]
In front of you, there is
the police badge and leather gloves.
You'll pick one of them
and leave for the final site.
You'll carry out a task
according to the decision.
Decide whether you're
a police or the Mafia
by the memories you recovered
through the hints.
Then leave.
With the hint I've received...
I'll choose the police badge.
I'm a...
Mafia.
My background is... the Mafia.
This is mine.
[The police: Song Ji Hyo, Yoo Jae Suk]
[The police: Song Ji Hyo, Yoo Jae Suk,
Lee Kwang Soo]
[The Mafia: Kim Jong Kook, Ha Ha, Gary]
[The Mafia: Jang Yoon Joo]
You know I only know
the last two hints.
[The Police-Mafia ratio is 5:5.]
[Two of the Mafia's Surnames
start with 'J']
Ji Suk Jin, Jang Yoon Joo
and Jung Man Sik.
I... will pick the more probable one.
[The Mafia: Ji Suk Jin]
You don't have a lot of information...
I have no information!
What information?
If I were to think
through the situation
I was in a foul-looking office...
so I thought, am I Mafia?
And then on my desk,
was a police badge.
[But there was a police
badge on the desk.]
[Confused]
With your sixth sense, guess if
you're the police or a Mafia?
[When I first woke up,
I came out of a dusty place...]
[Helpless]
[Was I being chased as a Mafia
or was I chasing as a cop?]
I can't say that I'm a cop
just because of the badge...
My...
[What was I?]
[Man Sik picks Mafia.]
[The Mafia: Jung Man Sik]
But... I believe in the
police in our country...
As a veteran, I want to pick this one.
- Please take your badge.
- Okay.
I can't just wear the badge.
[The only thing left
is the final mission.]
[The ratio is supposed to be 5:5,
but the ratio is 6:4 at the moment.]
There could be a Mafia here.
[Something's not right.]
[Did everyone]
[make the correct decision?]
[The final match location.]
[The secret hiding place of
the Mafia Boss is here!]
[Everybody's here in one place!]
[The Mafias arrive early.]
- Please get out.
- Yes!
[There's someone here that
made the wrong decision...]
Before the police arrest you,
you need to find...
Let's stay together.
The five briefcases
of gold bars in this factory.
Load all five briefcases in this SUV.
You need to move them to the hideout
where the Boss is.
You'll win if you succeed in doing so.
Let's find them
before the police arrives.
[Where is the briefcase?]
Man Sik, if you get caught
in the middle of searching
I'll try and earn some time.
- Run away and look for them.
- Okay.
In the end, the police
special forces will come.
- Then you'll be rounded up.
- SWAT team?
Before that happens,
hurry and find the briefcases.
Where is it?
Is the police here?
They're not here yet, right?
[At that moment,
the police are entering the factory]
[We're here to arrest the Mafia.]
The police will wear
this bell on your shoe.
Arrest all of them and
seize the gold bars.
If the police win, you'll be
awarded with the gold bars.
It's been a while.
They're already
carrying out their mission.
Should we attach the bell?
Then, they'll know where we are.
- That's why we attach it.
- Oh, is that so?
[Mafia mopping-up
operation has begun!]
Why are we running all the time?
Ah, it's 'Running Man.'
It's tiring!
[They're here!]
[We should move carefully.]
[I think I'll suffer from
auditory hallucinations again.[
[They're searching the gold bars
more discreetly.]
[Looks around]
What is that?
[A briefcase with the 'R' sticker!]
[The gold bars!]
There's another one!
They're really heavy!
[Moreover, there're two!]
[Perhaps, in here?]
[Bummer]
[Man Sik chose the Mafia
without a hint.]
[He looks like a thief.]
[The briefcase of gold bars!]
[And there are two again!]
[Now the Mafia team
found four briefcases.]
- Where are they?
- I found two here!
- I found them, too.
- Did we find three?
[I hear something]...
Where's our car?
[They decided to put
the briefcases in the car.]
[The boss is impatient.]
[Hurry up and find five briefcases
and send them to the boss!]
[It's about time to find them...]
- Is the trunk open?
- Yes.
- Wow!
- The other way.
I'll protect them here.
- Do we need to find one more?
- Yes.
[We need to find one more briefcase
then we can go to our boss.]
Where were they?
Were they hidden very well?
I was always bad at scavenger hunts
when I was young.
I don't think it's here.
[Chills]
- Let's get out.
- Sh...
[The police is near.]
Did you find anyone?
Do you want to go to the car?
[He checks the outside
and stepped out.]
Jae Suk!
[Catch the thief!]
[Forget your colleagues.
Run for your life!]
Is that Man Sik?
[He's faster than he looks.]
[Is this Jung Min?]
[He senses the situation outside]
[and chases the Mafia
at full speed!]
[This is the true character
of a veteran detective!]
[Grabs]
I eliminated him!
[He arrested the first Mafia!]
- Man Sik!
- I almost missed him.
He caught me in the movie
and he even caught me on 'Running Man.'
He was hiding here.
[You should have
chosen to be the police.]
[But did they really chose
the right identities?]
[Startled]
[It's Blank Ji!]
[She was going to
hide in the blind spot.]
[Blank Ji was surprised, too!]
[Yoon Joo is stuck.]
Please give up and go!
[The enthusiastic detective
is on the move!]
Jung Min, don't this to me!
[You were here?]
[Jae Suk joins them.]
Oh, no! Don't do this to me!
- Jae Suk, take care of her!
- Yoon Joo!
Don't do this!
Jae Suk...
Jung Min, look inside the car!
There's someone inside the car!
Suk Jin is inside the car!
[Wriggle, wriggle]
[Big-nose was right in front of them.]
Catch him! Don't catch me!
[Were you waiting for me
to eliminated you?
Suk Jin!
[The end of the Mafia
who ratted on her colleague.]
Why did you tell them?
- Let's just die together.
- What are you...
You're not supposed to hide there.
Why did you tell them?
You drive me crazy!
[Only three Mafia members are left!]
[We just need to find
one more briefcase...]
[How could we lose the police?]
It might be tiring for you,
but I'll run slowly.
[He caught three criminals.]
[Captain Hwang is enjoying arresting.]
[Gasp]
[Throbbing]
[What was that?]
[Did he find me?]
[Ha Ha, with a guilty conscience
starts running!]
[It worked!]
[Were you there, Ha Ha?]
[Why did he come out?]
Jae Suk, Ha Ha is running!
- I'm right here!
- Corner him!
For my colleagues,
I need to hold out until the end!
- Finish him!
- It's over!
I need to drag on...
[Ha Ha dragged on for five seconds.]
There are two left!
[Smile]
[He arrested four Mafias.]
[The best cop!]
[Gary and Jong Kook
are the two survivors.]
Stay behind me.
[How can I avoid them?]
Come over here, to the back.
Come, we'll get caught
if you keep going that way.
It's good.
[He's immersed in the Mafia's role.]
[He really wants to win today.]
Oh, it's right here!
[He found the last briefcase!]
[Wait for me, Boss!]
Where's the car?
[He successfully arrives at the car.]
[They can go to the boss's hideout!]
[Wait, Jong Kook is still...]
[Should I just go or not?]
- It's Jong Kook!
- Kwang Soo saw me.
[He's finally detected!]
Bring it on!
[The fateful meeting
with the original.]
He's politely asking you
to bring it on.
- I'm not going to do it.
- Come on, Jung Min.
[Blank Ji attacks.]
Wait, Ji Hyo!
[The car with gold bars
leaves the site.]
[Kkuk is in a
confrontational situation.]
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
[Gary, It's too late for me.]
It's Gary!
[Yoo Hyuk finds Gary!]
Catch him!
Jong Kook!
[Where are you?]
[I'll delay it as long as possible!]
Ji Hyo!
[Mafia Kim Jong Kook is arrested!]
How is it possible?
[There's only one left.]
[Gary, go to the boss!]
[Jong Kook, I'll finish this!]
Jae Suk, the car is moving!
Catch him!
- Did he run away with the car?
- Yes!
Hurry up!
Still, the Mafia team wins.
In the end...
[Gary gives police
the slip like that..]
[and moves to the boss's hideout!]
[If he delivers theses five briefcases
to their boss...]
[This is the boss's hideout!]
Boss!
I brought all the gold bars, Boss.
[The identity of the Boss]
[Lee Dong Jun]
The real boss is here!
[The boss was Lee Dong Jun?]
Good job!
By the way, did you find
these all by yourself?
No, I brought them at the end.
But we all worked together.
Is that so? That's amazing.
Thank you. I admire you, Boss!
You've won the world Taekwondo
championship three times.
- Three consecutive years of winning!
- And?
- That's what I know!
- That's what you know?
- Who's he?
- The real boss is here.
What were you doing?
You couldn't even find them!
[Gary, you did it!]
Where did you find it?
You've worked so hard.
We found them together!
[Not all six of them are Mafias.]
I'll show my loyalty!
Let me see...
Who is this bastard?
[Is Big-nose the bastard?]
He's not one of our members.
That can't be true.
I worked for you today.
- I've never seen you before.
- You must be wrong.
I haven't seen you before.
- Drag him out!
- Boss!
[Big-nose is not the Mafia?]
- Goodbye!
[Suk Jin thought he's the Mafia.]
[But his real identity is...]
[the police!]
Therefore, today's winning team
is the Mafia team.
[Jung Min was a detective!]
[Man Sik also chose
his identity correctly!]
Jung Min ran really hard today...
Yoon Joo's pants were provided.
She has to buy because he made a hole.
Thank you Man Sik, who makes us laugh
even if he doesn't talk.
Thank you for acting as the boss,
Brother Lee Dong Jun.
Thank you! I'm a fan of yours!
Today's winners are Gary and the Mafia!
[The true actors of Korea!]
[Good luck with your movies!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Lee Yo Won is like
a fresh breeze of summer.]
[Cha Ye Ryun who has
the image of a city woman.]
[We've decided to throw
a casting competition.]
[We've never seen an
actress like this before!]
[The recreation of masterpieces
with citizens!]
[We bet everything on this casting!]
[Who will be the main actress
of this casting?]
I'm tired.
I can't do this any more.
[The actress casting call competition]