Running Man
Episode 230
[Flower boy of the new generation-
Seo Kang Joon.]
[The tough man of the new generation-
Hong Jong Hyun.]
[The devil that stole
the hearts of all women...]
[The intellectual super rookie-
Choi Tae Joon.]
[The gentleman that we want for ourselves-
Nam Joo Hyuk.]
[The gentleman of all gentlemen.]
[The new standard for all gentlemen-
Seo Ha Joon.]
[And saving the star for last...]
[And the leader of these men...]
[Asia's Prince, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Specialty- Turning his everyday life
into one for the pages.]
[Hobby-
Enjoys reading letters from his fans.]
From, Ga Young.
I want to be the Big Dipper
that shines brightly in your heart.
Okay, I'll call you my very own
Big Dipper from now on.
Ah... and please tell Jae Suk
that I really love him?
Ga Young, you're out.
[The super rookies that'll sweep
2015 by a storm.]
[Lee Kwang Soo and the Boys.]
- I notice that Kwang Soo isn't here.
- I bet he's assigned another role today.
- I bet he's up to something else.
- You're the seniors at Running High School.
- We are?
- We're the seniors?
How many years have we been seniors for?
I don't know who they are,
but I feel bad for our juniors.
- I wonder who they could be?
- They should just transfer their school.
- There they come.
- I see them coming.
Hey, Kwang Soo's the captain.
[An entrance of all the hottest
rookies of 2015.]
[Super rookies have landed.]
- Kwang Soo looks like a squid.
- He looks like a squid next to those guys.
- I'm the leader.
- How are you the leader?
- It's great to see you guys.
- Ugh, I feel so embarrassed.
[Safely putting some distance
between them.]
[Their looks are too perfect
for anyone to stand next to.]
- Look at how happy the writers are.
- Yes, they seem way too happy.
- Song Ji Hyo looks happy, too.
- This is great.
Hello, my name is Hong Jong Hyun,
and this is my first time on Running Man.
[An extensive resume list from
dramas, movies, to variety programs.]
[A widely talented entertainer.]
Hello, my name is Seo Kang Joon,
and I'm a rookie actor.
[Seo Kang Joon, the new icon of flower boys,
and one of the hottest men of 2015.]
Hello, my name is Choi Tae Joon,
and I'm also a rookie actor.
[Made his initial debut in 2001-
The mid-grade rookie actor, Choi Tae Joon.]
[An actor who can make any woman's
heart go aflutter with his charm!]
Hello, my name is Nam Joo Hyuk,
and I'm also a rookie actor.
I hate men like him.
Men who are tall, yet still cute.
Yeah, I agree.
[An impressive height of 188cm,
with the charm of an innocent boy...]
- Hello, my name is Seo Ha Joon.
- Wow, he looks and sounds so masculine.
[Worthy of being called his new nickname,
'The king of the living room.']
[We are Lee Kwang Soo and The Boys.]
- Are we their seniors?
- Yes, you're the seniors.
- The six of you are the school's seniors.
- Hello, Seniors! It's great to meet you!
Happy New Year to all of you!
What are you doing? Bow down!
[Flustered and unsure of what to do,
they all drop to the ground for a grand bow.]
What are you doing?
Why are you bowing down to me?
There will be two teams of six members each,
with a team of Seniors and a team of Juniors.
Today's special winter episode is called,
Investigating the life of male students.
You will play a variety of missions that
are crucial to the lives of male students
to earn the clues you'll need to correctly
answer the question at the final mission.
We have prepared a mission based on
what male students are most curious about.
Figuring out what girls want is what
male students are most curious about.
You have to figure out what the number one
answer is from a list of top ten answers.
That's hard.
That's not going to be easy.
Before we get to that big question,
we have a list of other survey questions.
Yes, so this is a list of survey questions
that were given out to female students?
- Yes, these are the questions.
- It's good to know these things.
- You need to know these things.
- I'm curious to know what they are.
We need to know what women want.
This question is in regard to
the dating life of teenagers.
I remember those days.
- I really remember those days.
- Some of you are dating right now, right?
- Yes.
- You just agreed to it, didn't you?
Congratulations!
[Naive Joo Hyuk falls for Jae Suk's ploy,
and attempts to remedy his mistake.]
Want to send your girl a video message?
- No, I'm not dating anyone.
- Really? Okay, fine.
Fine, we'll let you slide.
He admitted to it without realizing it,
so it's too late to correct his mistake.
Question- One day, you suddenly find
yourself interested in your friend.
- When do you think you'd realize that?
- When you see your friend all dressed up.
- When she's wearing a skirt.
- Once in a while...
you find yourself questioning it
when you see her smile.
Who are you referring to?
- Who's the girl that you're referring to?
- Oh, it was when I was still in school.
- He's denying that it's now.
- He got himself out of that one.
I was getting really excited
thinking that he was going to tell us.
- Don't say anything.
- I'm feeling nervous about it.
- When she gives off a maternal vibe.
- What?
- When she feels maternal?
You must like older women.
- Tell us the truth.
- You've dated older women before, right?
- Yes.
- You have, right?
- I could tell by the way he said it.
- A lot of men like older women.
What about you?
When have you felt that way?
When the girl touches me without thinking
because we're already friends.
- When a girl touches you without thinking?
- That's when you feel it?
- That's the number one answer!
[The number one answer!]
[The moment when you suddenly look at
your friend as something more?]
[When the girl grabs your hand or brushes
your hair back without even thinking.]
That's when a guy is suddenly
made to wonder.
- The head...
- In that case...
[We'll pass on Kwang Soo's answer.]
You have to give me a chance
to answer, too.
- That's Kwang Soo's Achilles' heel.
- What is?
- When a girl caresses his hair.
- Is that right?
I don't know who Kwang Soo
will get to meet in the future...
Why would you tell everyone out there
what my weak point is?
I'm sharing Kwang Soo's weakness
with our future sister-in-law.
It's when you slightly ignore him,
then absently start caressing his head.
- This is what he likes.
- This is what we're talking about.
Kwang Soo tried doing that to me before,
and I bashed him in the ears for it.
- Yes, I saw her do it.
- Stop it!
We don't know who it'll be,
but let us reiterate it once again.
When Kwang Soo touches you on the head,
know that he's putting his moves on you.
No, that's not the truth.
I'm just an affectionate person by nature.
Our race for the day is to find the answers
to these sorts of questions from our viewers.
That's not as easy as it sounds.
Here's the dating question that our viewers
are most curious to know the answer to.
What was the most difficult moment you've
experienced while crushing on someone?
This is what our teenage viewers
are most curious to know about?
This question that you just heard
is the big question of the day.
- We already know the answer to that.
- Isn't the answer obvious?
- Isn't it when the girl likes someone else?
- That has to be it.
It's when the girl likes
some other guy other than yourself.
[Time to reveal the multiple choice answer.]
One- Purposely ignoring me while
being aware of my crush on her.
- Yes, it hurts to be ignored.
- No one can be that mean.
- While knowing that he has a crush on her.
- There are girls like that out there.
- What's the second option?
- Drawing the line at their friendship.
[Two- Telling him that he's a good friend,
and cutting off any hopes for more.]
I'm sorry to tell you this, but I've never
once thought of you as a man.
Three- Waiting around for her to call me
while not having the courage to call myself.
- Yes, I totally know what that's like.
- But you can't call the girl first.
Even going to bed with
the cellphone clutched in your hands.
But I don't think it's nice for
the girl to leave the guy hanging.
Four- When she expresses an interest
in my friend, and asks to meet him.
What are you supposed to do then?
[Five-
When that person is too popular.]
[Six- When she's all I can think about,
and I can't seem to do anything else.]
[Seven- When she asks me for dating advice
because she's in love with someone else.]
- There are seven possible answers.
- Yes.
- Find out what the number one answer is.
- Of those seven possible answers?
Yes, you must find that out.
- Only one is the correct answer.
- But I agree with them all.
- They all sound painful.
- I think number two is the answer.
They're still teenagers,
so I think we need to think simple.
- They're more mature than you think.
- Really?
Have any of you personally experienced
any of the aforementioned scenarios?
- Have you?
- Have you experienced any of it?
Have you? No, I doubt it.
These guys wouldn't know about it.
[What's a crush?]
I've experienced every single
one of those scenarios!
I don't know why I even bothered asking.
These guys wouldn't know about it.
None of these guys.
[Only one of the seven is the real answer-
Which team will get the correct answer?]
[The most difficult moment
while crushing on someone?]
I doubt any of those guys have
ever had an unrequited crush on anyone.
- I'm sure they have. Everyone has.
- I once had a crush on someone on the bus.
- Really?
- I had a crush on a girl that rode my bus.
- She rode the same bus as you did?
- Yes, for three years.
You two rode the same bus
for three years?
Do you remember when Chae Yeon confessed
that she used to have a crush on you?
A guy with good enough manners to
get concerned and see her home
is the type of guy
that most girls go crazy for.
Is it the type of guys that acts protective
of the girl while walking down the street?
The guy that walks on
the outside of the sidewalk.
- Throwing out a protective arm, right?
- I do things like that all the time.
Yes, you do things like that a lot.
Jong Kook is always wagging
his tail in front of the girls.
No, I don't!
When have I tagged my tail?
When have I ever wagged my tail?
If he had been a girl,
then he'd be the conniving type.
- How am I conniving?
- You're totally the conniving type.
- Yes, he'd definitely be like that.
- Stop being so conniving.
Yes, stop trying to confuse us.
I wonder what it could be?
We have to think like teenagers.
They surveyed teenagers,
so we have to think like them.
But for me, I feel better and put in place
when a girl tells me that we're just friends.
I see, you feel more settled?
Don't you think not knowing and
keeping my hopes up would be even harder?
But having her put you in your place
can make you feel more at peace.
You know what I think I'd struggle with?
To have her tell me that
she has feelings for my friend.
Friends are very important
in a teenager's life.
Then you could lose both your love
and your friend at the same time.
Do you know the song,
'Tested friendship?'
[That song came out
when I was ten years old...]
I think I'd struggle with having her
come to me for dating advice.
To have that person come to me for dating
advice when I have feelings for that person?
When that person comes to me,
and asks me for different date ideas
then I'd have to tell that person
the things that I'd like to do with them.
Yes, you're right.
That would be so cruel.
- Having to tell her that...
- You sound very experienced.
No, I'm not.
And teenagers don't know
when to give up.
Since Joo Hyuk is the closest
to the teenage years.
- Yes, you're right.
- I've had a crush before.
- Really? How old were you?
- I was in third grade.
- Really? When you were in third grade?
- I had that crush for three years.
- Do you want to get beat?
- It was a very serious crush.
- Then we ended up dating.
- Really?
It just kept on progressing
until things worked out in the end.
- Like a one track mind.
- I'm sure that's how most teenagers are.
What about you, Kang Joon?
Have you ever had a crush?
- Yes, when I was in high school.
- So everyone's had a crush before?
- Did you end up dating her?
- No, I didn't.
- So it never worked out?
- No, I couldn't even talk to her.
I'm betting everything
I have when I say this.
I bet if you told her you liked her,
then it would've ended up working out.
All of you could've gotten
the girl you wanted.
[What is he saying right now?]
I'm only saying it because I've
had a crush that never worked out.
['O' hotel swimming pool in Soochun.]
Pull yourselves together!
[Flower Boy Crush Report-
Their first research topic is?]
[Are those mats on the water?]
- Did you guys get to talk on your way here?
- We got to talk a little bit.
- They've all crushed on someone before.
- Really?
But here's the important thing.
You all got your girls in the end, right?
- Yes.
- See? This is what I mean.
- That's not a real crush.
- That won't happen even in our next life.
- They all ended up getting their girls.
- I've had a crush for three years.
- We've had a three year crush, too.
- Who?
- Joo Hyuk.
- You had a crush for three years?
- When I was in third grade.
- So did you get the girl in the end?
His crush started in third grade,
and he got his girl in sixth grade.
- That's not even a crush.
- But I really did love her.
- Really?
- So how long did you two last for?
- 50 days.
- Wow, you're something else.
[A three year crush...
comes to an end after only 50 days.]
- No, she dumped me.
- Seriously.
Sometimes, the real thing isn't as good.
- Has that ever happened to you?
- Yes, I used to like Kyung Rim.
- Why did you all like older girls?
- All guys like older girls at some point.
Okay, this is your first research topic.
This is not just your physical test,
but it's to test your sense of balance.
This mission is, water relay race.
One member from each team will run on
the mat towards the platform in the middle.
Once on the mat, you can push
your opponents off into the water.
The team with the most members
remaining on the mat in the end, wins.
Please decide the order of your players.
[Choosing the right order of players
could be key to winning the mission.]
- Jong Kook should go last, don't you think?
- He needs to throw everyone in the water.
Jong Kook needs to throw
everyone in the water.
So the first person on the mat
can push the opponents in, right?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Kwang Soo's the leader, isn't he?
- Yes, I'm the leader.
- What a sad leader.
- He's our captain.
- They're the ones who chose me.
- Really?
- They're so nice to make you the captain.
- You have no idea.
- You're older by how many years?
If we're going by looks,
then he's about 13 years older.
- How do I look that much older?
- No, you do look that much older than them.
[All the seniors are busy
warming up their bodies.]
Are you going to date me or not?
[The juniors follow in their footsteps,
and start their own warmups.]
We're competing against them?
[With Captain Kwang Soo as their leader...]
Aren't you supposed to warmup
your upper body first?
The first player can go
at the sound of my whistle
and at the sound of my next whistle,
the second player can go.
[Getting ready to start the race.]
Don't stand in the order you're going.
You have to confuse them on the order.
- We're going to start the first round.
- Okay.
Ready!
[Experienced Team Seniors vs
Youthful Team Juniors.]
[The first round with
their pride hanging on the line.]
Jong Kook, we're just going to relax
and hang out in the back.
Ready!
[Water relay race- First round.]
[Ha Joon vs Mr. Capable.]
[The two aces battle of pride.]
[Dumped into the water.]
I'm sorry, Ha Joon!
[Welcome to your first
Kim Jong Kook experience.]
[Second player, Tae Joon-
Runs full speed ahead with gritted teeth.]
[But...]
[Tae Joon is also met with the same fate.]
[Next player for Team Juniors-
Youngest player, Joo Hyuk.]
[I will get revenge for my brothers!]
[Add one more to the mix.]
[Attacks with a loud scream...]
[And runs full speed ahead
into the water.]
Hey!
[He practically flew into the water.]
[Full speed ahead.]
[Laughs out loud until he realizes...]
[That he's up next.]
What is this?
[Current score-
3:0 with Team Seniors in the lead.]
Take them down with you!
[With Captain Kwang's advice,
how will Kang Joon fare?]
[A 360 degree turn plunge.]
- What is this?
- This isn't even a match.
[Team Seniors are
the only surviving players.]
[In this disadvantageous state,
Jong Hyun runs out for his turn.]
[And for Team Seniors,
it's Big-nosed Brother.]
[But...]
[Jong Hyun arrives at the platform.]
[Oh?
He ambush attacks Ha Ha!]
[Could Jong Hyun be Team Juniors' savior?]
[But he falls victim to Gary's shoving.]
[Captain...]
[I'm Captain Kwang...
and my teammates are watching me!]
[Guys... I'm here to join you.]
[A polite 90 degree bow
even to his younger brothers.]
[A total win for Team Seniors.]
- What is this?
- What was that?
- We've never played this before.
- We've never played this before, either.
[And Joo Hyuk was just a passerby.]
[A slight act of revenge
to recoup his damaged pride.]
[Too easy of a win for Team Seniors.]
- Can we count this as a practice round?
- What are you talking about?
Beg the seniors right now!
Please give us a chance.
- Please let that one be a practice round.
- What are you talking about?
[They all follow Captain Kwang's order,
and bow down on the ground.]
- We'll have Suk Jin go first this time.
- Yes, but let this be a practice round, too.
Please!
We're all still young.
We're still learning.
Please do us this one favor.
- Okay, we'll do that.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Seniors!
[Thank you, Seniors.]
- Thank you!
- You guys are very weak players.
We may have been at first,
but we'll do better this time.
You guys are way too weak.
I think you guys need to work out.
We're just getting started!
Sorry!
[Just then, Big-nose exacts
his revenge for Jae Suk.]
[An eye for an eye, a dunk for a dunk.]
- Big-nose won't let you get away with it.
- Captain.
[Unable to get used to the scene of
Kwang Soo being referred to as 'Captain.']
I really love that.
- I've never been called that before.
- Captain?
I've waited five years to hear that.
[First time hearing that after
five years of being the youngest member.]
- Let's do this before Jong Kook comes out.
- They're talking about Jong Kook.
[An emergency meeting on what they
should do before Jong Kook comes out.]
- Should I go first?
- Yes.
- You? You're going to go first?
- But you're our ace player.
- No, you can't go first.
- What is this?
We have to keep our hidden card for last.
[Look at how happy he is.]
Can you say that stuff to me
a little bit more?
You look like Terius right now.
(A hero in a comic book series.)
[Comparing his wet look as that of Terius.]
[Checks himself out in the camera.]
[The first game was a practice round,
and back to playing the first round.]
- Ha Joon used to play rugby.
- Really?
Well, Suk Jin plays the stock market.
[First players-
Rugby player vs Stock market player.]
[Big-nose isn't the easy target
as they all assumed he'd be.]
[Ha Joon attempts to throw
Big-nose into the water.]
[But Big-nose doesn't let Ha Joon go,
and takes him down with him.]
[Second players- Tae Joon vs Gary.]
You have to take him down with you!
[An impressive battle of their strength!]
[The whistle blows for the third players.]
[What?
He tackles his own teammate, Tae Joon?]
What are you doing!
[A feisty battle of two on two?]
[Gary and Tae Joon fall in simultaneously.]
[Next- Kang Joon and Jae Suk.]
[Kills two birds with one stone!
Jae Suk and Ha Ha are both eliminated!]
What are you guys doing!
[This will no longer be tolerated!
Mr. Capable is on the move.]
[Mr. Capable... falls into the water!]
[But what is Kang Joon doing?]
[Clumsy Kang Joon also falls into the water.]
[Blank Ji is the only surviving
member of Team Seniors.]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hyuk vs Blank Ji.]
[Monday boyfriend's hair pulling?]
[Oh, Captain... My Captain.]
[The unspeakable agony.]
[Ace Blank Ji will not go down
without a fight!]
[Joo Hyuk attempts to
take Blank Ji down with him.]
[Joo Hyuk and Blank Ji falls down,
and Kwang Soo is the last one to fall in.]
The winner of the first round is,
Team Juniors!
[Team Juniors wins the first round.]
[After their first complete failure,
Team Juniors show a new side to them.]
[Team Seniors:0 vs Team Juniors:1]
I must be getting older.
I couldn't handle them.
This is the determining round.
We have to make sure to win this.
[With the end of each round,
Team Juniors gather together for a meeting.]
What are you guys whispering about?
We need a little bit of time.
These newbies don't know anything.
- Sorry, but give us a little bit more time.
- What are you guys whispering about?
[Kwang Soo bows down,
so everyone else bows down.]
I can hear you whispering
something about Jong Kook.
One person can hold Jong Kook down,
and another person can push him in.
- You guys are exhausted, aren't you?
- No, we're not.
- We're just getting started.
- I heard someone saying that he's tired.
- Who's saying that he's tired?
- Whoever's tired, get out here!
- Not me!
These jerks...
- What?
- What did you say?
[He was definitely
looking in their direction...]
The little jerks.
Little?
Then you must be talking about me.
[Why, I ought to just...]
Now that you're all ready,
we'll start the third round.
[Current score- 1:1.
Third round.]
Ready!
[We're not falling for your fake moves.]
- He must be going first.
- Why are you making it so obvious?
[Joo Hyuk's awkward at whatever he does.]
Ready.
[Round three- Start!]
[Joo Hyuk starts off very delayed.]
Joo Hyuk, you have to stay in there!
[Team Juniors' plan is to stick it out
for as long as they can.]
[Their plan succeeds and
Gary is dragged into the water.]
[Second players- Tae Joon vs Jong Kook.]
[Tae Joon's lightning fast takedown.]
[Impressive! Tae Joon withstands
Mr. Capable as his opponent.]
[Next- Rugby player, Ha Joon vs Big-nose.]
[Ha Joon successfully shoves
Mr. Capable into the water.]
[Team Seniors are in danger!]
[A fierce battle between the two teams.]
[Jong Hyun doesn't hesitate to
get into the game.]
[With four people already on the platform,
Kang Joon and Ha Ha run in.]
You have to take Ha Ha!
Take Ha Ha!
[A fierce battle between all the players.]
[Add the last two players into the mix.]
[In the midst of all the chaos,
Ha Ha and Kang Joon are shoved in.]
[Blank Ji and Kwang Soo
are next to get shoved in.]
[Jong Hyun and Ha Joon
vs Jae Suk and Suk Jin.]
[Just then...
Jae Suk attempts to shove them all in!]
[But Little Mr. Capable, Ha Joon,
withstands the attack.]
[Somehow, the two oldest players...]
Who's grabbing me by my throat?
[It's your own teammate, Big-nose.]
[Even attempts to tickle his opponent,
as taught by Kwang Soo.]
[Just then, Jae Suk counterattacks.]
[The final battle ensues!]
[Big-nose lands in the water!]
[Jae Suk is the only one left to eliminate!]
[Just then, Jong Hyuk grabs Jae Suk
and drags him into the water with him!]
[After the fierce battle,
Team Juniors wins!]
[Team Seniors 1: Team Juniors:2]
We take back giving you that break.
[The seniors are aggravated at having
counted the first round as a practice round.]
Everyone gather around.
Just look at you guys!
[Team Seniors are humiliated after not
having taken their opponents seriously.]
Hey, Rugby.
Get in line over there.
[Ordered to stand in line.]
[To all the seniors in the country-
Please do not act like this at home.]
Since we gave you a break initially,
we're going to play one more round, got it?
In that case, if we win this round,
then give us the seniority status.
- Okay, fine!
- Filthy bastard.
[A never before seen moment of insult
in the history of Running Man.]
We'll accept your offer
if you'll give us the seniority status.
But if you refuse to do that,
then we won't accept the offer.
You can take it.
- Then we'll take the seniority status.
- Fine.
[The never-ending scene of insults.]
You're not the seniors yet!
We haven't started yet!
- It's only after you've won this round.
- I thought our new status started now.
Did your mic fall out?
[Angry Yoo Hyuk's slapstick revenge.]
[Captain, just let it go.]
[Nice! Captain Yoo
lands one on Captain Kwang.]
[Captain, you need to cool off.]
I'm sorry.
Fine, this is for the seniority status.
If we win, then the seniority status is ours.
- Okay, fine.
- Okay, then let's do this.
- We're their seniors by how many years?
- Don't they know their place?
- Seriously!
- I just got dissed by those guys!
I have to get them back for this.
[Their status aside,
this is a battle for their pride!]
This is war!
We have to figure out who'll go first
because I think Jong Kook will be first.
[Both teams are getting very serious
for this one last battle.]
[Their rarely seen competitiveness
makes its appearance.]
Let's shout it out four times.
Fighting, fighting, fighting, fighting!
- Let's give it a rest.
- Fighting, fighting, fighting, fighting...
[We'll take your ten 'Fighting...']
- Okay, let's do this.
- Ugh, they're so aggravating.
[So aggravated!]
[This is going to be a close battle!]
Fine, we'll show you how scary it can be
when you don't know to fear your seniors.
Let's beat them one more time.
[We'll show you our robust youth vs.
We'll show you to fear your seniors.]
If we lose this round,
then it'll be the end of us.
[Mr. Capable is getting ready?]
- You're going first?
- Wait.
Do you really think that we'll have
Jong Kook go first?
It's no fun to have Jong Kook go first.
Ready!
[Mr. Capable goes in!]
[To have Mr. Capable be their first player?
Team Seniors must be feeling nervous, too.]
[Second players- Tae Joon...]
[And he's also knocked off
in just one attempt.]
We're sorry, Seniors!
Please forgive us!
Come on!
[Ha Joon rushes in towards Mr. Capable.]
Stick it out!
You have to stick it out!
[Little Mr. Capable, Ha Joon, knocks off
his center and battles three on his own.]
[Next players- Kang Joon vs Big-nose.]
[Kang Joon falls back onto the mat
with Mr. Capable's shove.]
[And Ha Joon is the target
of everyone's attack.]
[But...]
[He maintains his grip on Mr. Capable,
and takes him down with him!]
[On the other hand, Kang Joon still
can't even get on the platform.]
[He barely manages to pull himself up,
when Ha Ha knocks him right off.]
[Next is Jong Hyun, who always
managed to pull his own weight.]
[It's 4 vs 1.
The odds are stacked against him.]
[Time for the last players to go in.]
[But...]
[Did my eyes just make a mistake?]
[Blank Ji falls in with her arms
wrapped around Jong Hyun's neck.]
Are you kidding me?
[Blank Ji is romantically eliminated.]
[It's currently 4 vs 2.]
- Come on up here.
- Come up here.
[Here they go!]
[Their numbers may be few, but Kwang Soo
and Jong Hyun put up a good fight.]
[Just then, Ha Ha pulls Kwang Soo
into the water with him.]
[Jong Hyun is Team Juniors'
last remaining hope.]
[Jong Hyun gives it his all
until his very final moment.]
[Jae Suk and Gary work together
to shove him in.]
[Team Seniors 3: Team Juniors: 2.]
[After a long end, Team Seniors wins!]
Team Seniors wins the first round!
[We've managed to win...
but we're now drained of our energy!]
Okay, I need everyone to gather around.
- You did win, right?
- Yes, of course.
[They barely managed to win
thanks to Kkuk's role in their victory.]
Even though we won, it's embarrassing
how much we had to struggle to win.
- I feel a little embarrassed.
- Yes, I feel the same way.
[A little embarrassed to look
their juniors in the face.]
I've been watching Kwang Soo for five years,
but I've never seen him like this.
[Captain Kwang's never before seen image.]
He's the type that'll definitely
let his power go to his head.
[I am Captain Kwang.]
Go to the room on the right
once you leave the pool
and you'll find the hint that you're seeking.
Okay, let's go take a look.
See you later, Juniors.
- See you later.
- Yes, Sir.
[They all salute their seniors.]
[What is the first hint that
they've earned?]
[Two TV monitors?]
Please take the bag.
- Don't let them see it.
- Okay, don't let them see it.
[Takes a look at the card in the bag.]
[A chance to look at the dual monitors.]
Your mission is to correctly guess
the number one answer
to the question, 'What is your most difficult
moment when you're crushing on someone?'
This is your chance to ask a group
of women right here in the city
that exact same question through
the use of your monitors.
Okay.
The winners will get to ask a group of
teenage girls at an art school.
[The winners get to ask a group of teenage
girls gathered together at an art school.]
[The other team will get to ask a group of
women in their thirties in a chorus group.]
The winning team can ask both the groups
of women directly through the monitor.
The loser team can listen to the answer
of only the group in their thirties.
- Get ready to ask your question.
- I can't let them see me like this.
[First up- The group of teenage girls.]
[Team Juniors can't hear with their
headphones on in the back.]
- Hi.
- Hi, girls!
Listen, girls...
[Team Juniors steps forward
to take a look at the monitor.]
Seo Kang Joon!
[The teenage girls' focus has already
shifted onto the group of flower boys.]
We have a question to ask you.
- Okay!
- Have any of you ever had a crush?
- Me!
- They all have.
Tell us what the most difficult part is
when you're crushing on someone.
When he doesn't pay attention
to the text message I send him...
and you know that face thing...
the online face page?
[Ah... Facebook?]
When he updates his Facebook status
and doesn't respond to my text.
- Then it must be the ignoring part.
- Okay, I see.
- How about an answer from someone else?
- What about the girl standing next to her?
- What is your answer?
- We're all artists here.
But the guy I like asked me to draw
a picture of him with his girlfriend.
[Ouch, that sounds heartbreaking.]
[It must be this situation.]
How about an answer from someone else?
I let the guy know that I like him
but he still remains so obtuse and stupid
and doesn't even acknowledge it.
That's Kim Jong Kook.
- When he doesn't like me.
- When he doesn't like her...
When he doesn't even like me.
When he knows that she likes him,
but when he doesn't like her back?
[When he doesn't like me back.]
So he draws a clear line?
How about someone else from the back?
Someone else from the back?
When I confess my feelings to him,
but he says he just wants to remain friends.
- All the answers are here already.
- All the answers are similar.
- They're all on the list.
- All the answers are very similar.
Does anyone have anything
that they'd like to say to their crush?
Don't be like that!
- You're going to end up regretting it!
- Stop talking about me behind my back!
- I'm going to succeed!
- I'm going to meet someone much better.
If you had to pick the number one answer,
then which answer would you pick?
- What would be your number one answer?
- When he just wants to remain friends.
- Yes, I agree.
- That's so true.
- When a line is drawn?
- Who currently has a crush on someone?
- Me!
- It's always that one.
[The ranting and raving of one
grudge-filled teenage girl.]
- Why such a long crush?
- You have to. Love has no boundaries on time.
[A refreshing answer from a lively girl.]
- Thank you!
- Wish us luck on our exam.
Good luck on all your exams!
[Good luck on all your exams!]
[They've earned a quite a few hints
from the group of teenage girls.]
You can take off your headphones
and listen in on the other conversation.
Please turn on the monitor.
- Hello!
- You look like you're still in your twenties.
- Yes, you do.
[Everyone still looks young and fresh.]
- Have any of you ever had a crush on someone?
- Yes.
They've all had a crush on someone.
What have you found to be
the most upsetting moment?
- When before you go to bed...
- When a sad song comes on.
Then I think about him when I eat,
and at every other moment.
[Something that they've all experienced.]
- When he's all they can think about.
- What other experience have you had?
There was a guy that I liked,
but no one knew that I liked him.
Then a close friend of mine told me one day
that she had feelings for him.
[A similar situation to this one.]
I couldn't even say anything, and I just
got those two together the very next day.
I remember just crying my eyes out
for several days afterward.
[A sad memory of getting the other two
together and crying by herself for days.]
- Everything that we're hearing...
- Is the same result as the survey results.
What is the one thing that you found
to be the most painful thing?
Is it when you cut off all communication,
or is it when they ignore you?
Or is it when they tell you
that they like someone else?
When they like someone else.
- It's when they like someone else.
- When they like someone else.
It's when jealousy makes its play.
- That's what they remember.
- That's the most painful aspect of it.
Thank you for your help,
and happy new year!
[Thank you for all your honesty!]
Are those the same answers as
the teenage girls' answers?
- No, they're not.
- I told you that they're not.
[They're not falling for it.]
[Flower Boy Crush Report-
Off to the next mission site.]
I should've had Tae Joon
and Ha Joon sit up front.
No, we all did a great job.
No, not Joo Hyuk.
Kwang Soo, I did good in
the second round.
- I think I took four of them down.
- You flew off of there like a feather.
- No, I hid from them.
- Of the thirties group...
What is the answer that we
heard from them?
When they can't stop
thinking about them at night.
- But that's a given.
- They're already in their thirties.
When they feel melancholy
after hearing a sad song.
- I don't think teens would feel that way.
- I agree.
When they can't stop thinking about them.
Wasn't that one of the answers?
- When they can't stop thinking about them?
- But I don't know if that's a crush.
That encompasses everything.
It's like that when you love someone, too.
I don't think you can single that one out.
[Different answers from
the women in their thirties.]
[Some answers are things that
teenage girls haven't experienced yet.]
I think it's this one. Feigning ignorance
while knowing of their crush on me.
Yes, that one is harsh.
When they know of the crush?
I think it's either feigning ignorance
or asking for dating advice.
I think it's when they ask for you
to hook them up with someone else.
When they want to be
introduced to someone else?
What about when a third person
comes into play?
There's a high chance that
it'll be one of those two answers.
Yes, those two situations come into
play a lot during teenage years.
Yes, I think that's the age for it.
Hey, you know that number one answer
that the teenage girls chose?
- Drawing the clear line?
- Yes, I think that could be it, too.
That's what those high school girls chose.
When your crush tells you that
they just wants to be friends with you.
- That would be tough to hear.
- I had that happen to me in my twenties.
That's a very likely thing to happen
when you're in your teens.
Since that would happen while in school,
you'd still have to see them all the time.
I once told a girl that I was lying
just to save my face.
- Because you were embarrassed?
- To save face?
[Trying to save face out of embarrassment.]
I'd say, 'You're mine, so let's date.'
Then she'd respond, 'No, I'm not.'
To which I'd say, 'I was just lying.'
- I've done that a few times.
- You're so pathetic.
- That's seriously so pathetic.
- Didn't a girl once tell you to get lost?
- Yes, I've heard that.
- I remember that.
I think she was about
two years older than him.
Yes, I totally remember that.
You were still in your twenties.
- I think she was a little drunk.
- He was trying to put on his cool act.
- Can I call you mine?
- Get lost!
Trying to act cool never works
when you're confessing your feelings.
[Remembering all their bygone memories.]
I only said that to cover up
the nervousness that I felt.
[Off to the next location
while lost in their cloud of memories.]
[A small park in the middle of a pond.]
[Team Juniors are the first to arrive.]
[Must win this round in order
to win the top clue.]
- I see a start mark over here.
- What is it?
- Should we run there?
- I see an 'R' marked flag.
- This already looks difficult.
- Maybe I should take off my coat.
Is this a relay race?
I think it's a relay race.
Look at all the 'R' marked flags
placed here and there.
[What is the second mission
that awaits them here?]
- Welcome, Seniors.
- Hello, Sirs.
- Hello, Sir.
- Hey, guys.
- Who are you guys?
- We're the newbies.
- Hello, Sir.
- I'm the youngest of the bunch.
[Looks the oldest, but
claims himself to be the youngest.]
Here's your second mission.
Your next mission is,
Suncheonman Bay Relay.
You're here at Suncheon Lake Park.
They say that this park embodies
the essence of this town.
As you can see, this embodies the mountains,
the lakes and the city of this town
and everything has been built
to reflect that essence.
The relay will be divided into six parts
and the final runner will have to run up
to the mission zone up at the top.
The final runner will finish the mission,
and the winner of that mission wins the race.
- That's how this mission will be played.
- So it's not just a relay run?
You have to win the final mission
to win the race.
If the final runner fails the mission,
then everyone has to start over.
- Then the mission will start over.
- Start over from the beginning?
- From the start line?
- Yes, all the way back to the starting line.
[An ominous feeling that this is
going to be a never-ending relay.]
The final runner's mission
will not be known here
and it'll be given to only the person
that gets up to the mission zone.
Then the final runner should be someone
who's very smart and clever.
Yes, you only have one chance.
Only one chance will be given
to successfully complete the mission.
- I bet they're fast runners.
- It's okay, here's how we'll go.
[Gary- Ha Ha- Suk Jin- Jong Kook-
Ji Hyo- Jae Suk.]
If you fail the mission,
then we're all going to finish you.
[Feeling the pressure.]
[Team Junior is figuring out their plan.]
The younger one will probably
think faster on his feet.
[Youngest member, Joo Hyuk,
is feeling the pressure.]
- No, I feel confident.
- If you fail, then we'll have to start over.
[No matter how fast they run, failure to
succeed the mission means starting over.]
If he fails, then let's all give him
a smack in the hand.
If he fails the mission, okay?
That's the starting line.
[Everyone to their stations.]
[They're starting to realize
the true scale of the course.]
We're going to have to run
like Cristiano Ronaldo.
- I think we'll be good at the running part.
- You're all fast runners, right?
- I'm confident in my running skills.
- You're a fast runner, aren't you?
- We have to win this.
- I agree.
- We have to win at things like this.
- We have to be resolute.
Who's the third runner over there?
Who's their third runner?
[First runners- Gary vs Kwang Soo.]
Please stand at the starting mark.
Don't you think that you're
being too mean?
[Second runners- Ha Ha vs Tae Joon.]
- This is where we'll have to start over?
- Yeah.
When the second runner comes up...
Watch yourself because I may shove you.
[Fourth runners- Jong Kook vs Jong Hyun.]
You seem really strong.
I'm afraid that you're going to
hurt me even while running.
[Will we see the monstrous strength of
Mr. Capable during the relay race?]
What do you guys do for fun
when you're in your twenties?
- I like playing video games at home.
- You like playing video games?
Kang Joon.
[Crucial final runners-
Kang Joon vs Jae Suk.]
- Team Juniors, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Team Seniors vs Team Juniors-
Second battle with their pride on the line.]
[Suncheonman Bay Relay- Round One.]
[Starts off at a dead run
at the sound of the whistle.]
- Wow, he's so fast.
- This is good!
Wow, he's so fast!
[The two runners are already closing in!]
[Fast footed Gary is almost
to the second runner, Ha Ha.]
[Formidable opponent, Kwang Soo,
runs full speed ahead on his long legs.]
Take it easy!
[Kwang Soo hands off the baton to Tae Joon.]
Here, Dong Hoon!
[Gary also hands off his baton to Ha Ha.]
[Team Juniors is in the lead
by the split of a hair.]
They're the second runners
and they're headed over to us.
- This is like a blockbuster movie.
- No, that's not the way!
[The two runners are neck and neck!]
[Already handing it off
to the third runners.]
[Big-nose fails to grab the baton
in his attempt to delay Ha Joon.]
[Ha Joon takes this moment
to get a lead on Suk Jin.]
[The gap is growing between the two teams.]
He's fast.
[Ha Joon defies gravity to run,
and Big-nose defies his age to catch up.]
It's already over.
[Ha Joon already hands the baton
over to Jong Hyun.]
[Jong Hyun takes off like a bullet
as soon as the baton is in his hand.]
[Big-nose finally arrives and
hands the baton off to Kkuk.]
[The gap is ever growing...]
[But Mr. Capable is on the run,
and it's too early to give up.]
[Jong Hyuk uses his long legs for speed.]
[Kkuk unleashes his full power mode.]
[Jong Hyun arrives at Joo Hyuk's position.]
[Ji Hyo succeeds in her attempt
to interfere in baton hand-off.]
[Mr. Capable arrives in the meantime.]
[Joo Hyuk's vigorous run.]
[But Ace will not let the twenty-something
beat her down!]
[Final runner, Kang Joon, gets the baton!]
Start running!
[Ace comes in right behind.]
[Jae Suk also gets on his way.]
[The final mission zone.]
- I hope Kang Joon succeeds.
- If he succeeds, then we win.
[Kang Joon is first
to arrive at the mission zone.]
[But Jae Suk is right on his tail.]
[Starts the mission almost simultaneously.]
[Catch the five gonggi pieces in one swoop.]
In one try?
- It's whomever succeeds first.
- You have to catch them all together.
[Kang Joon wrongly grabs the pieces
in his haste.]
[Team Junior may have been fast, but
they're slow at understanding the task.]
Jae Suk will go first.
[Jae Suk takes the first turn.]
[He must first get all five pieces
on top of his hand.]
[Jae Suk fails.]
[It's now Kang Joon's turn.]
[Successfully gets all five pieces
on top of his hand.]
[Now he must catch them all
in order to succeed!]
[Kang Joon fails.]
[Both teams must get back
to their starting lines.]
Ugh, this is so disappointing!
- We have to go back?
- I had no idea it'd be gonggi.
- I had no idea it would be that.
- You failed?
[We have to run again?]
I wasn't able to flip my wrist.
Hey, you just needed to catch
the five gonggi pieces to win the mission?
Yeah, just catch the pieces.
Do you want to do it?
- Okay, I'll do it.
- I think we can switch the order.
I know that Suk Jin
doesn't want to run again.
Come up here, Suk Jin.
Jong Hyun, do you want to do it?
Can you handle it?
- I'll give it a try.
- Okay.
Tae Joon, do you want to go first?
We need a fast start.
[Leader Giraffe gives out the orders.]
- Is everyone ready for the second round?
- Yes.
[Getting ready to show off
their skills once again.]
- Fighting!
Ready!
[Gary and Tae Joon's alarming speed.]
[Suncheonman Bay Relay- Round Two.]
[Gary's explosion of speed.]
Wow, he's so fast.
[Tae Joon also takes off running.]
[An explosion of a 25 year-old's energy.]
[Full speed ahead Gary is
already closing in at 'R2'.]
Do you guys have motors on your feet?
Wow, he's really fast.
[Tae Joon hands off the baton
to Kwang Soo.]
[Ha Ha receives the baton
almost at the same time.]
Ha Ha's quick.
[A close competition!]
[Team Junior touches off first!]
Wow, Running Man is no joke.
- Running Man's stamina is no joke.
- Your stamina improves on the show.
[Being on Running Man is no different
than hitting the gym regularly!]
[Ha Joon's alarming speed...
and Grasshopper's impressive spurt.]
- They're really fast.
- They're almost here already.
[Ha Joon's powerful dead run.]
Wow, you're really fast.
[Kang Joon touches off.]
[And Jae Suk hands his off to Kkuk.]
[Once again, Kkuk is in full power mode.]
- Fighting!
- Kang Joon!
Jong Kook's really fast.
Fighting!
[The two runners don't even seem to
notice the curved path in front of them.]
[Touches off almost simultaneously.]
Good, Jong Kook closed down the gap.
We have to succeed the mission this time.
[22 year-old's enthusiastic run.]
[But Ace is catching up
even while in a skirt!]
- I'll get this done!
- Let's finish this, Jong Hyun!
[Team Junior starts off.]
[Team Senior starts off.]
- Ji Hyo's so quick!
- Go!
[Team Juniors is once again first to arrive.]
[Arrives to do the final mission.]
[But it's not the same mission!]
[Thought that the mission
would be the same...]
[That's why the final runners
were chosen the way they were.]
[Smack the book and flip the coins
over twice in a row.]
[While Jong Hyun gets the book ready,
Big-nose also arrives.]
- Please.
- Did they switch up the mission?
[If they fail again, then they'd
have to go back to running.]
I hope they succeed this time.
[Still getting ready.]
[Big-nose immediately launches his attempt.]
[Big-nose immediately succeeds
his first attempt.]
[Even though he was first to arrive,
he's still busy getting prepared.]
[Jong Hyun takes his first attempt.]
[Jong Hyun also succeeds his first attempt.]
[Please succeed the mission.]
[Only one more coin left to go.]
[What will be the result?]
I think they did it.
They did it?
- I think we did it!
- But that's Suk Jin's voice.
We did it!
We won!
[Team Senior wins
Suncheonman Bay Relay Race.]
Didn't we get there first?
But we got there faster.
[Jong Hyun fails.]
[Big-nose succeeds.]
[Big-nose successfully flips
two coins over in a row.]
[Why won't this work?]
You did great!
[Neither of them can believe
the outcome of their game.]
[These youngsters can't accept
their failure.]
How are you supposed to do this?
[Team Seniors wins
with Big-nose's performance.]
We won!
Hey, Hong Jong Hyun!
Where's the baton?
We have to spank him.
[Jong Hyun needs to be spanked.]
[Please forgive me...
I thought it was going to be gonggi.]
[Just keeps slapping away at the book.]
[Can we do it over with gonggi?]
[Big-nose is greeted with fanfare.]
[Big-nose mentality plays on.]
- What are you guys going to do?
- You guys aren't even a match for us.
- Are you guys even good at anything?
- We thought it was going to be gonggi again.
- You guys don't look too happy.
- We thought we were going to win.
[Off to receive their next hint.]
[Time to hand out the clues.]
- 60 seconds in the answer room?
- We've got 30 seconds. Not bad.
There are a total of 10,000 notes of
surveyed answers in the room.
It's all the answers that we've received
from the survey that was conducted.
Which means, the number one answer has
the most number of pages in the room.
And there's another very special clue
that's hidden amongst the notes.
There's only one note that is chosen
as the Lucky Eraser Chance.
The team that finds this note will
be given one correct answer.
[Team Seniors will go first.]
I'll take half of this wall.
[The answer with the most amount of notes
is today's correct answer.]
We have to look for the erasure chance.
[Only one of these numerous notes
is their erasure chance.]
[The feelings of these teenage girls
is so confusing to receive.]
It's either being ignored,
or not even being acknowledged.
[Only ten seconds left on the clock,
but there are 10,000 notes on the walls.]
- I don't know which has the most.
- What about the erasure clue?
- It's not being acknowledged.
- How are we to figure this out?
[Which of the answer has
the most number of notes?]
Wow, there are so many in there.
There are way too many.
I'll call you my senior
if you can find the erasure.
- There's no way they're going to find it.
- Let's give it a try.
[Only 30 seconds on the clock.]
[Team Juniors turn.]
[Not even any time to take in the shock.]
[Telling me their feelings for someone else,
and asking me for dating advice.]
- See which one is mostly the same.
- There are too many up here.
I think that has the most.
- It's not being acknowledged.
- We needed more time in there.
- No, that's not the one.
- I'm telling you that it is.
[Everyone offers a different answer.]
- I saw not being acknowledged.
- I saw liking someone else.
18 seconds.
I see wanting to be friends
more than anything else.
I see being invisible
[All their opinions are differing.]
It's the erasure!
[Kwang Soo discovers the erasure clue.]
[A one in 10,000 probability!]
[That's a lie.]
Because Kwang Soo's
the first one that said it.
Kwang Soo was the first one
to have said it.
[Kwang Soo pulls off a miracle.]
I'm your senior!
- This is the erasure chance.
- You actually found it?
[Gains seniority after finding his clue.]
- Where?
- You found it?
- He really did.
- It was on the bottom.
- I can't believe you actually found it.
He saw a lot of wanting to be friends,
and he found a lot of being invisible.
They saw something different from ours.
Wanting to be friends is what I saw.
[Off to the final mission site.]
I looked through two different walls.
I saw liking someone else the most.
I saw that and being invisible,
and I saw being invisible the most.
I only saw what was in front of me.
I saw asking for dating advice the most.
It's either asking for dating advice,
or not being able to get in touch.
- Don't you think?
- I think it's liking someone else.
[Team Juniors runs into a group
of teenage girls by a chance.]
- How old are you?
- 15?
- She's 15 years old?
- Wait.
Have you ever had a crush on someone?
You have? Then at which moment
did you most struggle with?
- Which one of these?
- This one.
- How old are you?
- When he's too popular?
[Ha Joon's received response-
'When he's too popular.']
- Have you ever had a crush?
- What did you find to be most difficult?
- When I couldn't get in touch with him?
- When she couldn't get in touch with him.
They all have different answers.
- When you had to wait around?
- Yes, I think that was the toughest.
- Waiting around is the toughest part.
- That really is.
[The teenage girls' number one answer-
Having to wait around.]
[Really?]
- I really am curious now.
- Thanks for your help!
[Thanks for all your help!]
- What do you think?
- Should we try figuring it out?
I think it's being ignored when
they know that you like them.
- What do you think, Tae Joon?
- I really have no idea.
What if you had to pick one?
I'm going to go with what she said.
'When he's too popular with others.'
I think it's asking me for dating advice
because he likes someone else.
- Me, too.
- I agree.
I think that would be the toughest part, too.
- Wow, this is really hard.
- I feel even more confused now.
[A few moments later.]
[Everyone seems to be
searching for something.]
[What could they be searching for?]
How am I supposed to find it
in this large space?
Here's your final mission of the race.
I told you that you needed to correctly
guess the number one answer to the survey.
You'll have to find a beach ball
that contains the contents of the answer.
There are a total of seven beach balls
with the possible answers written on them.
You have to find the beach ball
and score it in the goal
in order to win the game.
There's a goal post on the first floor
and one on the second floor,
totaling two goal posts.
If you throw in a ball with
the incorrect answer written on the ball
then the person who threw the ball
will be eliminated from the game.
Team Juniors used up
their one chance, correct?
- What did you use it on?
- It was a huge help to us.
- What we thought was the correct answer...
- It's when they want to be friends, right?
- No, it's not that one.
- It's not? Okay, thanks.
[Why did you have to tell them that?]
- No, that's not what I was saying...
- Just stop talking!
- He said it's not that one.
- Tae Joon...
- I made a mistake.
He says he made a mistake.
[Find the woman's heart- Start.]
Wow, this really is Running Man.
I wonder where the ball is?
No, there's nothing in here.
- I just wanted to try doing that.
- Yes, I knew you would.
- Where...
- Is the beach ball?
[Where's the beach ball?]
[Meanwhile, Joo Hyuk is...]
I found it.
[Immediately discovers
one of the beach balls.]
[Gets a beach ball in his hands.]
['You're just a friend.'
Puts the person in the friend zone.]
- Isn't it better to be put in your place?
- Yes, I think that would actually be easier.
I think I got the best one.
This is a dead-end.
No matter where I go...
I try to look cool,
but I don't think I can pull it off.
[Yoo Hyuk and Jong Hyun search
through all the lockers.]
[Telling me that they like my friend,
and wanting to be introduced.]
[Makes a run for it.]
[Jae Suk, where are you going?]
[They all must think that
Jae Suk's beach ball is the right answer?]
Jae Suk, I'm coming!
What is it?
[Ha Joon intercepts.]
[Runs off with the beach ball
to the nearest goal post.]
[Runs off at a dead run.]
Look to see what it says first!
Ha Joon!
What is it?
What does it say?
[Telling me that they like my friend,
and wanting to be introduced.]
No, that's not the number one answer.
[Could this be the answer?]
- This is the special clue that you found.
- Okay, what is it?
[Team Juniors receives their special clue.]
[Finds out which one
is the incorrect answer.]
This is the number four answer?
I suddenly feel so lost.
- Are you sure that's the same one?
- This was the number four answer.
No, this isn't the number one answer.
That's not the one.
Wait, that's my ball.
I was the one that found it!
You can't toy with us!
Run, Tae Joon!
You have to run!
[Tae Joon runs away with
the stolen ball in his hand.]
Where's the goal post?
[Tae Joon, you're not thinking of
throwing in the ball, are you?]
[Wait...]
Tae Joon!
Where's the goal?
[He looks like he's about to
slam-dunk the ball!]
Where did Tae Joon go?
[Used up their chance to check
one of the incorrect answers...]
I suddenly feel so lost.
[No, that can't be the ball
that Tae Joon has in his hands.]
[But if this is the correct answer,
then Team Juniors could win the race.]
[Slam dunk!]
[Saying that they like my friend,
and wanting to be introduced.]
[Could that be the correct answer?]
- I put it in there.
- I don't think that's the right answer.
No, that's not it.
I don't think that's the right answer.
- Choi Tae Joon, out.
- Yes!
[Tae Joon eliminates himself.]
Choi Tae Joon, out.
[The reason why his teammates
seem so frustrated.]
I told you that wasn't the correct answer!
[Huh?]
You still dunk it in there even after
the hint told you that wasn't it?
[The incorrect answer that they gained
after using their erasure chance...]
[Number four answer- Wanting to be introduced
to one of your friends instead.]
[Even after knowing that's incorrect,
he still dunks the ball in the goal...]
What were you thinking?
We already knew that wasn't it!
- That's the hint we were given.
- Seriously?
- I didn't realize that was it.
- That's the erasure chance we were given.
- Who just got ousted?
- Was that really the fourth answer?
That's the wrong answer that we saw
as the erasure clue.
- You threw that ball in there?
- Yes.
- Why would you do that?
- I thought that was the correct answer.
[Tae Joon ousts himself out of the game.]
[Even Team Seniors thought
that was the number one answer.]
- I thought that was the answer.
- No, it wasn't.
- That's why he was eliminated.
- I think it's having to wait around.
I think it's either that one,
or something else very simple.
Just the fact of crushing on someone
could be a painful thing.
So I think it could be
having to wait around for them.
[Jong Hyun's still searching for more balls
even with one already in his hand.]
[Discovers another beach ball.]
[Unable to call first,
and just having to wait around.]
[Should I just keep waiting for
others to score more balls?]
[Kang Joon is also on the search
for the beach balls.]
[A beach ball is found.]
[When that person
is all they can think about.]
[Hides the ball away under lock and key
so that no one else can get it.]
Oh, what's this?
[Gary also finds a beach ball.]
[Finds his own team's
number one estimated answer.]
- I found the most crucial one.
- What is it?
- Gary, I'll put it in there.
- Dong Hoon!
- What is it? I think it's this one.
- I think this is very important.
- Asking for dating advice?
- I think this is the one. Put it in there.
- That's the one we were thinking.
- I told you that this is the one.
[Asking me for dating advice.]
There are a lot of notes on
asking for dating advice.
[The dating advice notes
were most commonly seen by Ha Ha.]
I really saw the most on
asking for dating advice.
- Please let this be the correct answer.
- This is the answer we were thinking of.
[If that really is the number one answer,
then they win the race.]
That would be so cruel.
That has to be it. We won.
Ha Ha, out.
[We were thinking that was too easy.]
- What could be more cruel than that?
- That's not it, either?
I really thought that was it.
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo seem visibly nervous
at the announcement of Ha Ha's elimination.]
[Now remaining are 5:5.]
[Flower Boy Crush Report-
What could be the survey's number one answer?]
This one...
I don't think this is it, do you?
- No, I don't think so.
- I don't think so, right?
[The ball that Kang Joon recently found.]
Try putting it in there like that.
What are you trying to do to me?
What are you trying to do to your leader?
I don't think this is it.
This one doesn't make sense to me.
- Trust me on this, this isn't it.
- Then put it in there.
- We'll trust you if you'll put it in there.
- I'm telling you this isn't it.
But you still want me to put it in there?
- But what if this is the correct answer?
- How am I the leader right now?
- You're not the leader anymore.
- Have you guys been toying with me all day?
What if the other team puts this in,
and they win the race?
- What if the other team wins with this?
- I'm positive that this isn't it.
Seriously?
How about we make someone else
put this one in there?
How about Suk Jin?
[Gary is chosen as their sacrificial lamb.]
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
No, I don't want to!
Jong Kook, help!
No, I'm not doing this with my hand!
- Lift him up there.
- No, I don't want to!
[Gary is forced to score
the ball in the net.]
My hand didn't even touch the ball!
Gary, out.
[Captain Kwang Soo's dirty play.]
[Team Seniors loses another teammate
after first losing Ha Ha.]
Ugh, I'm seriously so aggravated.
This is seriously...
I'm not going to forget this one.
[Only four more left to go...]
If we hadn't found this one, then the other
team has too high of a chance at a win.
If it's not this one,
then it has to be the other one.
- Waiting around?
- It has to be waiting around.
The toughest part has to be left
wondering and not knowing anything.
Even if you don't like the answer,
it's better to know where they stand.
- I have to know whether I'm it or not.
- That's right.
It's really annoying when
you're constantly left to wait around.
That actually happened to me once.
They told me everything about the CF shoot
except for where it was getting filmed at.
I knew the date and the time
the CF was going to get filmed
and they told me they'll see me in three days,
then I never heard from them again.
[Totally left hanging.]
[Some frustrating times...]
I was going to search through every single
studio in Gyungggi-Do district.
I'm serious.
[Joo Hyuk continues to search through
every nook and cranny.]
[Discovers another beach ball
in the freezer.]
When they completely ignore me
while knowing of my crush on them.
I think I'm doing a good job
of finding these balls.
- What's that?
- There's a ball coming your way!
Joo Hyuk has the ball!
[Score the ball with the number one answer
to immediately win the mission!]
[There's no one by the goal post
on the first floor.]
I think it's being ignored when they know
that I've got a crush on them.
- That's what you think?
- That's what I think is the answer.
[Kwang Soo's number one answer.]
[Could it really be the number one answer?]
[Dunks it in before he can change his mind.]
Nam Joo Hyuk, out.
[If Kwang Soo's guess it also wrong...]
- This is your erasure chance.
- So this is not the answer?
[The incorrect answer
that they got to see...]
I really thought this was it.
[But the answer that
Ha Ha got eliminated for...]
[Asking me for dating advice
while confessing feelings for someone else.]
[The answer that Gary was sacrificed for...]
[When your crush is all you can think about.]
Completely ignoring me when
being fully aware of my crush on them.
Nam Joo Hyuk, out.
[The likeliest answer of the three
answers that are still left remaining...]
[Could it be the ball that Jong Hyun
is holding in his hands?]
[The answer the 15 year old gave as being
the toughest part of crushing on someone.]
She says it's when
you're left waiting around.
[The ball that Jong Hyun just found...]
We have to get Jong Hyun.
He's headed up to the second floor.
Come on, let's not do this.
- Get him!
- Come on, let's not do this.
I need my teammates to get Jong Hyun!
[Will Jong Hyun score the ball first,
or will he be caught first?]
[Everything is riding on this one ball.]
[Jong Hyun successfully gets
the ball in the net.]
[Could that have been the answer?]
[Flower Boy Crush Report-
Team Juniors wins!]
[Jong Hyun correctly guesses
the feelings of teenaged girls!]
[Number one- Unable to call first,
and left waiting around for his call.]
[Flower Boy Crush Report-
Mission complete!]
All those seven things are tough.
- Crushing on someone is hard.
- Everything about a crush is tough.
- What's their winning prize?
- Haven't seen these rings in a while.
- Wow, these are nice.
- They look like class graduation rings.
Captain, say something for us.
- How about we say, fighting, five times?
- Fighting, fighting, fighting...
- Let's do it, too.
- On the count of three.
- One, two, three.
- Fighting, fighting, fighting...
[Two opposites ends of the extreme.]
- Ugh, this is so aggravating.
- Why are they always trying to copy us?
[Good luck to our flower boys in 2015!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[In April 10, 2011-
Yoo-ames Bond was born.]
[In April 22, 2011-
Yoo-ames Bond makes his return.]
[And on January 25, 2015...]
[Yoo-ames Bond makes his return
after three long years.]
[An important announcement.]
[Yoo-ames Bond's successor joins the elite.]
[Who will be the successor
that'll join the elite status?]
This is your final test.
History will be made today.
[Yoo-ames Bond of Running Man- Three.
The battle of the successor.]