[Running Graduation Album]
Episode 232
[On a winter day in 2015, at a cafe]
[People who are waiting to be reunited.]
[A very special reunion.]
Today, your friends came
to pay a visit.
Are they really our friends?
They must be our real friends.
[I wonder who they are.]
- The first guest is my friend?
[Jong Kook's friend will come out first]
- I have many friends.
- Is it Jung Nam (A Turbo member)?
Come out, Friend!
Who is it?
[ I missed you, Jong Kook.]
- Come out, Friend!
- It's Kyung Min!
[The Korean Ricky Martin,
Hong Kyung Min!]
[Is that Kyung Min?]
- It's real!
- He's Jong Kook's real friend.
[The two tough guys' passionate reunion]
- You should have dressed up!
He dresses well after he got married.
[Kyung Min, a newlywed groom.]
It's been a while.
Congratulations!
- I went to your wedding, you know.
- Thank you.
[Everybody's saying
that they attended his wedding.]
Jae Suk didn't go.
I was hosting a TV Show.
But I paid more for you than Suk Jin.
You did?
[He did, Suk Jin.]
- I did.
- I know how much you gave him.
- Don't give too much, it makes me look bad.
Kyung Min is really close
to Jong Kook.
[They are both the year of the Dragon, along
with Jang Hyuk, Jo Sung Mo,and Hong Kyung In.]
Many people already know
that he and I are good friends.
It's not a big surprise to see me
as Jong Kook's friend.
- But I have seen the other guests.
- You've seen them?
And I had to ask them...
'Who are you friends with?'
- I have no friends.
- Who did they invite?
I didn't expect to see them.
[It's unpredictable.]
I think that's why I came out first.
[Who is this unexpected guest?]
It's going to be Ji Hyo's friend.
My friend!
- Who is it?
Ji Soo!
[The pure and innocent.
Kim Ji Soo.]
- She's not her friend.
- Are they close?
[Everyone's puzzled to see Ji Soo.]
- Ji Soo is not Ji Hyo's friend.
- She's my Sister.
- Hello?
[9 years older sister, Ji Soo.]
It would be nice if I were her age.
I used to carry a laminated photo
of you when I was younger.
- Are you really close to Ji Hyo?
- We were in the same agency before.
We've known each other for
10 years now.
We never worked together
but we were beer buddies.
[They got close by drinking together.]
Now you're talking about
your true colors.
She was MC'ing when I debuted.
She was the MC for the show
'Best 50 of MBC'.
[She has an unexpected connection
with Kkuk.]
[That was 20 years ago, in 1995.]
[She was there when Turbo debuted.]
We are revealing Turbo's debut
performance. 'My Childhood dream'.
[90's style excessive fog]
[First start of the turbo engine]
[He started to act like a tiger.]
Friend!
I wonder if it's Song Eun Yi .
Maybe Eun Yi will come out.
[Who is this man?]
Friend!
Who is it?
[Original Flower Boy,
Kim Won Joon.]
It's Won Joon.
- He's your friend?
- Yes, he's my friend.
- Won Joon!
- He's an ancient celebrity!
[He's acting like an old man.]
- You're so old!
[Jae Suk's best friend]
- He was the icon of x-generation.
[Icon of x-generation, Kim Won Joon]
[He achieved stardom as soon as he debuted
with his song 'After All Goes to Sleep'.]
Yoo Jae Suk and Choi Seung Kyung
from Seoul Institute of The Arts.
[Shoulder pads]
My mommy is...
[Dragonfly eye glasses+ obscure jokes]
- good at singing
[The combination?]
- and makes good food for me.
[What kind of relationship do they have?]
- He and I were singers.
We debuted at the same time.
We made a team named 'OHD' back then.
- He's my friend, so stay back.
- He's my friend as well.
[They are suddenly competing with
each other for Won Joon.]
Won Joon is my friend
we are the same age
- and we went to the same school.
- Class of 1991.
The class of 1991 is still very active.
Hwi Jae, Jae Suk, and Do Yeon.
- Who is Do Hyun?
- Jeon Do Yeon.
Oh, I was thinking of Yoon Do Hyun.
So, what happened to 'OHD'?
[Arrogant walking]
- At that time, I debuted as a singer.
You're supposed to stay here.
Why are you walking forward?
Kun Mo, You, I and Ha Soo Bin
were in the group.
[Original fairy Ha Soo Bin]
- She's was a junior in my class.
Are you serious?
[Jae Suk is an alumnus of Soo Bin?]
Everyone went crazy for Soo Bin.
We sang 'Oh Happy Day' together.
Your story is too long.
Please go back.
[Please come back when it's your turn.]
- I am the big nose!
I wonder who Suk Jin's friend is.
Most of my friends stay home.
You'll be surprised, too.
- I will? I'm well dressed today.
- It doesn't even make sense.
Why did he dress so well?
Friend!
You're not going to believe
who it is.
[An old friend of Suk Jin...]
[The Empress of Rare Beauty,
Oh Hyun Kyung.]
How can they be friends?
[Their eyes are about to pop out.]
[Is Hyun Kyung really
Big-nosed brother's friend?]
She's so beautiful!
Are you close to Suk Jin?
She came to see Suk Jin.
We met 20 years ago.
I just started MC'ing and
she was really popular back then.
We were MC'ing together.
We were MC'ing together for a
show for about 6 months.
[There's another surprising relationship.]
Ji Soo and Hyun Kyung went to
same high school.
- Oh, really?
- I was a freshman
- when she was in her last year.
[Hyun Kyung is two years older.]
She was really famous in Kye Won High,
as a goddess of beauty.
You went to Kye Won High?
No wonder!
What about our school?
We tried to hook up with Kye Won High,
but we always failed.
[We were different than the others
since high school.]
She's here as my friend, but she has
more acquaintances with the others.
I keep in contact with her.
[Even Kwang Soo knows her from filming
a sitcom together in the past.]
[It seems like most of them
know her better than Suk Jin.]
- Why do you keep covering my face?
- I don't have enough space.
- Welcome.
- It's nice to see you again.
Me? I don't have any friends
in the entertainment business.
He's well dressed, too.
- Friend!
- Who is it?
Who is Gary's friend?
[Who...]
Miryo!
Miryo?
Jo Miryo?
[No.1 female rapper,
Brown Eyed Girls' Miryo.]
[Reunion of the nation's
female and male rapper]
- Is Miryo a friend of Gary's?
- No, she is younger.
We were in the group
'Honey Family' together.
I cast Miryo for the group.
I've known Miryo
since she was in high school.
She started rapping
when she was in high school.
She was the best rapper
amongst college students, too.
She belonged to the same agency
as me for a bit.
[Three people are acquainted
with Miryo.]
Who's Kwang Soo's friend?
Friend!
Shin Da Eun is here!
[Cute and cheerful actress Shin Da Eun.]
- Everyone is so pretty today.
[He seems more embarrassed
than pleased?]
[Da Eun is giving off her fresh charm
in dramas and movies.]
She is pretty, too.
[Kwang Soo seems to be restless.]
- Is she younger than you?
- No, she's my friend.
- You guys are the same age?
- I can't believe it.
Did you guys have crush on
each other or something?
I wasn't interested in him,
but he said he was.
[She's dangerous.]
You confessed to me last time!
- Be quiet!
[You confessed to me last time!]
[Such a huge disclosure]
When did I confess to you?
[The Pandora of Da Eun]
- What a playboy!
- He's a wild animal!
Defendant Lee Kwang Soo.
Do you admit that you
have confessed to Shin Da Eun?
Please answer it quickly and go
back to your spot. One, two, three!
You do?
He never disappoints us.
[I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.]
It wasn't that kind of confession.
[The more he tries to explain,
the smaller he gets.]
- Who's your friend?
- I don't know, either.
I wonder who Ha Ha's friend is?
I think it could be Lee Deok Hwa.
Call out your friend.
Friend!
Be careful, this is getting weird.
Don't panic and stay calm.
[Who is it?]
[The queen of talk shows,
Park Ji Yoon.]
She is indeed my friend.
She is a dear friend of mine.
Hello, dear friend of mine.
Why are you calling her like that
if she's your friend?
[Welcome, dear friend of mine.]
Dear friend of yours?
She gives me advice on parenting
and many other things.
We still talk formally.
- She's like a female warrior.
- Her nickname was General Shoulder.
- Why would you say that here?
- You look slimmer.
I have narrower shoulders
than before!
I could say things like this
because we are close.
You were MC'ing together
before, right?
- It was 'Star Golden Bell'.
- Isn't she more of your friend than Ha Ha's?
To be honest,
Ji Yoon and I are closer.
You should have called me,
Kwang Soo!
[Their relationships are all tangled.]
You will be starting the
Best Friends Race.
Did he say gold?
You will get seven suitcases.
One of the suitcases has a golden key
which is worth 1.5 million Won.
The last team that gets the suitcase
wins the race!
You will have to find the
suitcase yourself.
[Special bonus for the team who gets first.]
- Do they really give us the money?
Ji Soo just asked if she
can use all the money now?
Her eyes sparkled
when she heard the word 'gold'.
[Pure and innocent Ji Soo
dropped her jaw in front of money.]
[The heart of Seoul - Yeouido]
[There are five mission sites in Yeouido.]
[Find clues about the
location of the suitcases!]
[Get the answer by clearing
the missions!]
[Which team will get the suitcase
with a golden key?]
The mission sites are...
They are all located in Yeouido.
The southern part of Seogang Bridge?
- It's going to be outside.
- It's going to be cold.
- It's a bridge and bridge is cold.
- Let's go to a warm place first.
- Coffee shop?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Let's have some morning coffee there.
- And a bagel.
- Black coffee and a bagel?
- As usual.
- Since when? We like traditional breakfast.
- You mean blood sausage soup?
- Yes.
['Ji Sisters' are tomboyish
when it comes to eating.]
- How's your married life?
- It's nice. You should get married too.
I should.
You need to meet someone now.
I need to work.
You've been working for 20 years already.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to get married
because of my age.
- I'm telling you, you should hurry.
- I know I should.
I'll introduce you to a nice person.
That'll be nice.
- Where should we go? The snack bar?
- That's a good idea.
I hoped that you'd pick the
snack bar.
We always went to snack bars
when we were in school.
More than half of my allowance was
spent at snack bars.
It was more than half of what we had.
And we didn't have much money.
Friend, I haven't been to the
Hongdae Area for a long time.
I don't go out that much.
- I heard you went back to school.
- That's right.
I just finished grad school, at this age.
- You graduated already?
- Yes. I wrote a thesis.
This reminds me of my college years.
- Did you know that I entered the contest?
- To be a comedian?
- You entered the college gag contest, too?
- Yes, but I failed.
Everyone in my class entered.
We wanted to get at least one job.
You shouldn't enter for gag contests.
We need to make living, too.
- It wouldn't haven been fair.
- I remember seeing your name on the list.
I thought I was going to get
a silver medal at least.
I couldn't believe when they called my
name for the participation award.
[20 years ago, he was full of confidence.]
- I was arrogant.
That experience made you
the person you are today.
The class of 1991 are all proud of you.
- We can't help it.
- Enough! That's too much.
[90's style Won Joon's
excessive complimenting.]
- You're the big star among the class 1991.
[The source of pride, Yoo Big Star]
[Each team is bonding while they're
heading to the mission site.]
- We're here.
- I think we came first.
[Suk Jin and Hyun Kyung arrived first]
- We came first!
Hello, can I have some
Kimbop please?
Can you cut it quickly for me?
Are you hungry?
- We're here for a mission.
- But I'm hungry, too.
Sharing.
Enjoy lunch with your friend.
The keyword is sharing.
- What do you want to eat?
- Order anything you like.
- What do you like?
- I like rice cakes.
- Then let's order some rice cakes.
- She's very thoughtful.
That's all you want?
Order something else.
Thank you.
- Can we just eat it?
- Just eat it?
The mission is to share it.
[Hungry Hyun Kyung, takes a bite.]
Can we just eat it?
[No other rules were given.]
[Yoo Big Star and Won Joon arrive now.]
- Jae Suk!
- Hyun Kyung, you're here, too.
- Hello!
- I can feel it as soon as I step in.
- Feel what?
- This is awkward for both of you.
When I opened the door,
I could feel the awkwardness in the air.
- Did you feel that?
- Why are you sitting awkwardly, Hyun Kyung?
We're just busy eating.
Are they doing the mission now?
Enjoy lunch with your friend.
The keyword is sharing?
Kimbop, rice cakes,
Pork cutlet, dumplings, fish cakes
- How about fish cakes?
- Fish cakes, okay!
We want some fish cakes, please.
- Were you born in 1971?
- No, in 1970.
1970 is the year of the dog.
- Is yours the horse?
- Yes.
We're a good pair. Horses,
dogs, and tigers get along very well.
Why am I so happy to talk
about this?
They're so old.
Old people like to talk about
Chinese zodiac and compatibility.
Horses and dogs get along really well.
Were you born in the year of the rat?
- That's so cute.
- He looks like a rat.
We're the 70's people and
you're the 60's.
We remember the new village movement.
What about you?
Was it barley hump?
- We had new village movement.
- I was born in 1970.
[Jae Suk and Won Joon's menu]
- We shared the rice cakes.
- Don't share it with them.
- It doesn't have oden.
We call it fish cake these days.
It was called an oden back then?
I know retro style is trendy now
- but this is further back.
[It feels like ancient history.]
You know my last name is Oh.
I just love the word 'o'.
I think you've taken the Gwageo
Civil (in the Joseon era) exam.
[They have finished eating.]
The mission is to eat with your friend.
We'll give you a clue
when we see the correct action.
What is he talking about?
Correct action?
Then we need to act in a certain manner.
[I see!]
- So, the correct action means
we should do something
when we share the food.
Maybe it's like the pocky game?
She's enthusiastic.
She's watched Running Man!
- It's sharing, isn't it?
- That's right!
- Let's do this and leave this place.
- We need to act something out.
Let's leave.
What are you two doing?
[It's not a big deal for the mission.]
You're not even hesitating.
[Feeding each other doesn't work.]
Are you finished with the dishes?
Please clean the empty dishes.
Please give us some Kimbop.
[What's the answer?]
I don't really know
what we're supposed to do.
We're supposed to share the food.
I think this might be...
Won Joon, I'll give you one.
- It's for you, Big Star.
[Feeding each other]
Is this going to work?
Why are you copying us?
Look at the way we eat.
[Eating in a love-shot pose]
Since it's sharing...
Eat it.
[Hyun Kyung, seriously?]
[This is not it?]
It's divided.
- She's too active.
- What are you doing?
- I divided and shared it.
- She's very enthusiastic.
- That's not it?
[What would be the correct answer?]
[While they were talking in the snack bar...]
[Kwang Soo and Da Eun, under the Han River
bridge in the middle of winter day.]
What is that?
- Eat with your friends.
- Keyword is Dalgona (flat toffee).
We need to cut out the shape well.
[Nostalgic snack Dalgona]
- Are you good at this?
- Have you tried it before?
- We're not really the Dalgona generation.
- Please give us one.
- It feels like Myeong dong.
You know lovers do this kind of stuff.
You get another one if you cut out the shape.
We just need to cut out one shape?
- It's so cold.
- My hands are freezing.
We can feed each other.
- That's what we're supposed to do.
[Kwang Soo is falling for her again.]
- You broke it.
- Of course, winning is important but...
- Do we get a new one?
- Yes.
[This Dalgona mission is difficult.]
[They are doing it together this time.]
Don't we need to get shy
when our hands touch?
This is how comfortable you are.
I thought you were my mother.
It's so cold. Hurry up.
[Ji Hyo and Ji Soo went to the cafe]
It's right here.
It's marked with an 'R' sticker.
I think we are the first team.
We're the first!
Drink with your friend in a
friendly manner.
It's 'drinking'.
We are good at drinking.
- We can drink anything.
- Should we order here?
We were going to order
hot coffee and bagel, right?
- Hot coffee...
- I'm a bit worried.
I think hot coffee can be dangerous.
There's got to be something else.
- Fresh fruit juice!
- Let's order that.
- Fresh fruit juice is good for the skin.
[She's an actress who cares about her skin.]
- I will have kiwi juice.
- Strawberry and banana juice for me.
Do we pay with the money
you gave us?
This is the mission.
Do you think it'll be a lot?
- I don't know. You should know better.
- It's a friendship test.
- Maybe they will give us too much.
- Loyalty test?
Your beverages are ready.
Mister.
We paid for the fruit juice.
Why are you giving us this?
What is it?
Is it water?
- It's soda.
- Maybe they put something in it.
Nothing special. Look at
the camera when you talk.
[She's not used to variety shows.]
- Don't turn your back when you talk.
We need to drink it in a friendly manner.
Let's link our arms together
and drink.
No, it can't be. It's got to
be something more than that.
Drink... in a friendly manner?
- I hate thinking.
- Someone's here.
Jong Kook is here.
[Jong Kook and Kyung Min join.]
- I don't know what it is.
- What is it?
We have a mission?
Drink beverages with your friend
in a friendly manner.
We ordered juices
but they gave us soda.
- They gave you soda instead of juice?
- Let's order first.
- Hi. What can we order?
- Here is the beverage menu.
The important thing is
that they gave us soda.
[No matter what,
they only give you soda.]
See?
- See?
- That's weird.
By the way, why so little?
- Isn't that too little?
[There's got to be a reason.]
- See you later.
[Jong Kook and Kyung Min go upstairs.]
- Do we really need to just drink?
- I'll tell you once you drink it.
Morning soda.
[Drinking soda in the morning.]
- Did you drink it all?
- Yes.
Order your drinks again.
Another glass of soda?
Then we'll get a clue?
I think there's got to be something.
What could it be?
It's to test our friendship.
I think the answer is the love-shot.
How do you know that?
- The keyword is 'to drink'.
- This is friendship test, though.
Do you think it's a love-shot?
That's usually for alcoholic drinks.
Maybe one person should drink both.
Still think it's the love-shot?
Should we try that?
Bottom's up?
Bottoms up!
It pops in my throat!
[They drank it, boldly.]
Is it the correct answer?
I think they look surprised.
'How did they figure it out?'
That's what they're thinking.
[The new groom is very confident.]
- They must have been surprised.
- We never thought that you would get it.
- Are you serious?
This is not a joke, right?
Do we really need to
drink it together?
Why are they laughing?
Let's go upstairs and see
what happened.
I thought you were joking.
You have passed the friendship test.
[The friends with the dragon zodiac
succeed in one blow.]
[Unbelievable]
I think I'm a genius.
No, I think you drink too much alcohol.
[The friendship test: Drink with
your friend in a friendly manner.]
[The answer: Love-shot]
[The clue: UI]
- Could it be 'UIRI' (loyalty)?
-'UIRI'?
-Don't show it to anyone. Hide it.
- Did you get the hint card?
- Did you?
- Us?
- They did.
- Did you get it or not?
- We did it.
-You did get it.
- Are you drinking again?
Yes, we are.
- I guess they have free refills.
- Think about friendship.
This is awesome!
I think this show is for me.
[He is emerging as a dark horse.]
[Jong Kook and Kyung Min succeed
their mission and go to next site.]
I think I'm optimized for
Running Man games.
[Jong Kook and Kyung Min are
the ones to receive the first clue.]
[One couple heads to a photo studio]
['S' studio in Yeouido]
[There are so many celebrity pictures.]
[Today's guest, Kim Ji Soo]
Oh, it's Ji Soo!
[Jae Suk, dressed as a woman]
[Lee Sun Jae, always looks the same.]
[A very rare picture, young Sin Goo.]
[Young Lee Deok Hwa]
This is Choi Bul Am.
Here is Lee Gye In's picture, too!
He looks so young!
Hyun Kyung is here.
I guess a picture stays forever.
[Take a picture with your friend.
Keyword: Pose]
Ha Ha, Park Ji Yoon!
Cross! Forever!
Could it be a human tower?
Let's try making it.
Aw, Ji Yoon... I won't say anything.
- Please take it quickly!
- Ahh, my knees!
I think you should be at the bottom.
Is it a piggyback?
I think it is.
[That's what friends do sometimes.]
Let me give you a piggyback.
No, I can't let you.
- I'm General Shoulder.
- Let's give it a try.
- Is this it?
[Piggyback of friendship]
Isn't this it?
I think it's the answer.
[The answer: Piggyback]
[Fantastic couple-
General Shoulder and Haroro]
[Clue for the suitcase]
- 'GONG'
- Just one letter for a clue?
- Let's try one more.
- Gong?
- We'll get one more letter
and guess the location.
It's difficult to solve it with one letter.
[Two teams have earned a letter each.]
[Who will find the suitcase first?]
No one is here yet, right?
We need to hurry up.
That's how it is.
I think it's here.
[Gary and Miryo's mission site-
the stationery store.]
Here's the mission.
Friendship test for finding the suitcase.
Pick it with your friend.
The keyword is 'To pick'.
I think we need to pick
the same thing, at the same time.
- Can we pick together?
- Take a look.
It says 'Pick it with your friend'?
What do you think it is?
[The store is a difficult spot.]
I don't know!
Do we need to pick something random?
- Since it's a friendship test...
- Could it be this?
- What is it?
- This coin machine.
- It's a coin machine.
- Maybe we'll get the same thing.
- It's been 30 years.
- How do we insert the coin?
One, two, three!
It came out.
- I've got marbles.
- What's this?
- Play again!
[Gary lost the draw.]
I'm just letting you know that the
producers don't really tell you anything.
- So, don't get upset.
- I see. We can't spend all the money.
- We shouldn't waste it.
- One, two, three!
[Turning and turning
and shaking]
[More turning]
Nothing comes out.
Is this how your life turns out?
What if we use up all the money here?
What is it?
What do we need to pick?
They never tell you what it is.
Have some candy.
Let's check the mission again.
- Pick it with your friend.
- Friendship test.
The keyword is 'to pick'.
What would it be?
Let's look for something with
the R stickers.
[Searching and more searching]
What would it be?
- Miryo, do you sense anything?
- Gary!
This is my first time on Running Man.
It feels like the first time for me, too.
Do you know anything about it?
The keyword is 'to pick'.
- It's underlined with a highlighter!
- That's it!
- That's right!
[Find the yellow highlighter!]
- Is this it?
- No, this isn't a yellow highlighter.
- Is there an R sticker?
- Should we pick it and check?
[Winner!]
Gary!
You're smart!
- Do I look trustworthy?
- Yes, you are.
[The answer:
Pick the correct highlighter.]
- Congratulations!
- Thank you!
- 'DO'?
- Is this the hint for the location?
'Do'?
We're in Yeoui-do, right?
- Thank you.
[UI] [GONG] [DO]
- I'm getting full.
- Then I'll eat it.
See? We have five pieces.
It's five.
So, let's eat one of each.
Let's feed each other.
Here, friend have some.
I'll eat it, too.
- We can have one more.
[Full concentration]
I'll eat this.
[Three pieces left]
[Again, eating one of each]
You can have the last one.
Thank you.
[It's the last piece.]
[Hyun Kyung eats it.]
- Aren't you eating?
- We want to watch them first.
- Please come forward.
- I think they did it. - Thank you.
This is the clue
for the location of the suitcase.
[They earned a letter.]
- We did it!
- You have the list of the mission site?
- There are other places, too.
[Jae Suk and Won Joon saw the whole thing.]
Here, friend.
- You can have these, too.
[Generous Hyun Kyung]
- Good bye.
[Suk Jin and Hyun Kyung leave.]
[The last piece.]
- You can have it.
Can I?
Thank you, Friend.
[The answer: give the last piece
to your friend.]
- One letter from the hint.
[YEO]
You can pay and leave. Ji Suk Jin
left without paying for his food.
- Can you pay for them?
- We need to catch them.
[Money and friendship
are two separate matters.]
Suk Jin! You left something!
You left something very important.
[They are collecting clues one by one.]
[Dragon friends
linking their arms together.]
[Putting arms around each
other's shoulders]
[The 'V']
Should I carry you on my shoulders?
- Give me...
- a piggyback?
[20 years of friendship]
Success!
[Great sense, Kyung Min!]
We're doing so great today!
This time, you're the thinker
and I'm the driver.
[This is the fantastic combination
of 20 years of friendship.]
[They earn another letter: 'GONG']
'Gong Gong Ui Jeok'
(Public enemy)
[Kwang Soo and Da Eun
came to the stationary store.]
[Da Eun looked at the mission
in a glance.]
[She starts picking yellow highlighters.]
I found it.
[She brings it to the cashier.]
- Congratulations!
[The mission is complete in an instant.]
- Was is the highlighter?
[They earn 'WON' and 'DO']
Have some faith in me.
I came here to exercise
but what is this?
Do we have to eat it?
[Jae Suk and Won Joon arrive]
- Ji Soo, are you getting used to this?
Where were you before you got here?
- The snack bar.
Hello! This is flat toffee.
- Hello!
[The two exhausted teams meet.]
Is today some kind of a retro special?
This reminds me of the old days.
You have to lick it first, Ji Hyo.
- Have you tried this before?
- She's on a roll.
The tactic is to lick it first.
When you do this...
You broke it.
You've failed!
- It was only a little piece.
- No, you failed!
Again? We have to do
it until we succeed.
[Broke in half again]
Is that where it got its name?
[Ji Hyo and Ji Soo try again.]
Ji Soo!
What are you doing!
She's the worst.
What? What did he say about me?
What did he say?
[Shattered in pieces]
- Where are you going, Ji Soo?
- I can't play this game with her!
She didn't even open it yet,
and she broke it.
- What are you doing, Ji Soo?
- This one is defected!
[Lick it first then pick it with a needle.]
- You guys, it looks dirty.
- It's better than staying in the cold.
It's better to be dirty and
leave sooner.
Do you think you can do it
in a cleaner way?
- She's licking it too.
[She lost to the coldness.]
- You're close, Won Joon.
- It's impossible to cut that one out.
What if I do it?
You can't do it!
If I do it, will you hook me up
with somebody?
- He wants to hook up at this age.
- Would you like to meet each other?
You can go to a cafe later.
- No, the snack bar.
- We've been there already.
[A shy boy]
[An enthusiastic woman]
Ji Soo, is Kim Won Joon not your type?
No, why wouldn't I?
- She's very bold.
- I know right?
- She's not shy at all.
- She's not.
- We did it!
- Success!
This is my heart.
[Jae Suk and Won Joon
complete the Dalgona mission.]
Give it to Ji Soo.
Give it! Give it to her!
- I want to, but I licked it.
- It's fine, just give it.
- Give it to Ji Soo.
- Give it to me.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
[90's style confession.]
- Yes, give it to her.
It's stuck!
You accepted it, right?
What are you doing?
Put it back together when
you meet later.
Put it back together later, okay?
You guys look cute together.
- I did it! I cut out a heart, too!
[Ji Soo succeeds right after.]
[Won Joon's enthusiastic applause.]
- She did it!
[Ji Hyo and Ji Soo complete the mission.]
Do you want it?
Please take it out from your heart.
[Won Joon and Ji Soo - In my heart]
[Location hint of the money bag.]
- Still, isn't this fun, Ji Soo?
- Yeah.
Honestly though, what do
you think of Kim Won Joon?
He's not your type?
Won Joon is so handsome and pretty.
I like everything about him.
I think he might be interested in you.
Ji Soo, how old are you?
I think we're the same age.
But Won Joon doesn't look his age.
Right?
I can't always live with regret
I will give you everything
Must you always ignore me?
I can't do that...
[Ta-da.]
I can't always live with regret
- The movements are so artistic.
- I know.
Won Joon, the movement are so artistic.
[Meanwhile, Suk Jin and Hyun Kyung
are having a blast taking pictures.]
- One, two, three.
[Ah,this pose?]
You're kind of heavy.
[Embarrassed.]
[Photo studio mission is
successfully completed.]
I knew it!
There has to be physical contact!
[Suk Jin and Hyun Kyung
also got a location hint.]
We're good together. I guess being
four years apart is a good match.
- I know.
- We're a good match for games, too.
- What zodiac sign is your wife?
- She's a tiger.
See? Dog, horse, and tiger.
Yeah, but the tiger... I don't think
the tiger and horse are a good match.
No one's perfect.
Women and men are just different.
- That's the right answer.
- Women and men are just different.
Ah, I think I know what it is.
When friends eat together, they all check each
other out when there's only one piece left.
Or they fight over it.
I'll let you have the last piece since
you're older than me. Eat, Gary.
'Ah.' Eat it.
Gary, please come this way.
[Fast Food Joint Mission Success!]
[It was that?]
[After all the twists and turns, Ha Ha
and Ji Yoon discover the highlighter.]
Hey, what do you think this is?
Gong. Do. Eui.
Something, something, Gong.
Hey! It's Yeoido!
Yeoido... park!
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
Wow, this is just...
This is awesome, right?
Yeoido. Yeoido Park.
I'm 98% sure that's what it is.
It's Yeoido Park.
Do you think it would be Yeoido factory?
It's Yeoido, but...
- Yeoido park.
- Park!
- Yeoido park. Yeoido Park!
- You're right.
Yeoido park.
- I think Yeoido park is right.
- Really?
- 'Yeo.' What's next?
- There's 'Won'.
- 'Gong' from the photo studio.
- That's right.
It's Yeoido park.
The park is really big,
so there's a lot of places to hide.
They said it's hidden
somewhere in there, right?
[Everyone is heading over to
Yeoido park around the same time.]
[Just who will be the first to arrive?]
[Yeoido Park.]
[In front of the octagon
pavilion at Yeoido park.]
[There are 7 bags in front of the pavilion!]
Ji Hyo and Ji soo might be there first!
Outrun them! Outrun them!
Where do we go?
- What's going on?
- Hurry up!
[All the teams have arrived at Yeoido Park.]
They're coming!
How can we be this slow?
Hello. Hello, hello.
- What did you eat today?
- We ate pork cutlets!
- You ate pork cutlets?
- I take it for you.
Let's take it together.
[Fan service in this urgent moment.]
- One...
One, two, three. One more time.
[With the fans at Yeoido Park.]
- Someone just gave me their cell phone.
[While Jae Suk and Won Joon are having
a fun time with their fans...]
- I see a pavilion.
- There's the bags!
- Where, where? Where?
- The bags are over there!
See? I told you it's here.
[Jong Kook and Kyung Min
are in 1st place!]
Congratulations.
- Well, it was pretty easy.
- This was the perfect mission for us.
You guys came in first place.
We made it clear early on that we would give
a special benefit to the team that places first.
Among the seven bags there, we will tell
you which bag has the real gold key inside.
- You're going to tell us? Really?
- Yes, for now.
The gold bag is...
Ah, the real one... this is the real one.
You can take the real bag and
protect it to the very end.
Or you can leave it here on purpose
and take a different bag.
We have to take advantage of this.
The team that picks this bag is
going to think they were lucky.
We're the only ones that know that bag
is the real deal. Including that team.
- Right?
- Let's take number four.
- Since the numbers aren't good.
- Right, right.
If anything, they might think
that this is the bag of gold.
- We'll take number four.
- Okay.
- Work hard, everyone.
We just have to play hard
to get it back now.
[Time to reveal the
location of the real bag.]
- Number six.
- You guys picked number six.
You do it. I'm unlucky.
- Don't be like that.
- Seriously, you pick it.
I'll give you some of my energy.
You pick it, Gary.
- I think it's this one.
- I think it's this one, too.
- We'll take this one.
- Number two.
Take a look and if there's real gold
inside, then you have the gold key.
[Checking out the contents of the bag.]
Is it real or fake? Is it real?
Hey, I think it's real.
I think it's real too, but we
don't know if it's fake or not.
Anyone can see this is real.
- This is real.
- Seriously?
Keep a straight face.
Don't make it obvious, okay?
[It's really obvious...]
Miryo, you have to keep
a straight face, okay?
- Okay.
- You have to keep a straight face.
People are going to come at us
with questions and suspicions.
- I'm about to smile right now.
- No, no, no.
Even if you deny it,
you're going to get caught.
But, aren't we all taking
the same bus together?
- I think so.
- We'll have to maintain our poker-face.
[They're all taking the same bus to
the final location of the mission.]
I'm not sure if you all know this, but there's a
lot of chemistry going on here. It's no joke.
- Between who?
- What chemistry?
I'm trying to get Won Joon
and Ji Soo to hook up.
Really?
Ji Soo told me this morning
that a woman needs a man.
- Switch seats with her.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- Sure.
- Change seats with her.
When did I ever say that
a woman needs a man?
You guys look good together.
Kyung Min, how long have
you been married?
- Two and a half months.
- It's been two and half months
and he looks so happy.
Can we have a party after this is over?
[He's already dreaming of returning home?]
Because he's happy.
Because it's been a while since
I've met my awesome colleagues.
Don't worry, there is no party.
- He has to go home.
[Trying to maintain their poker-face.]
I didn't know variety shows were
so considerate. When did that start?
You should go home early if you're married.
It's the honeymoon stage.
Suk Jin, you said your wife still doesn't know
the exact time of when the recording ends.
Be quiet, it's a secret.
It's a secret. I'm recording
'Running Man' four days a week.
Four days.
[He cracks me up.]
[Gary is holding their
bag of gold tightly.]
Someone among here knows
where the gold key is.
- Exactly.
- Right?
There's usually a couple
that doesn't talk too much.
Miryo couple!
- We're purposely...
- No. No.
Is it Jong Kook then?
[And so it goes back and
forth, very dangerously.]
[To the final location of the mission.]
- I think it's here.
[Arrived at the next mission location.]
[Entering as couples in a friendly manner.]
[What kind of mission will unfold here?]
What should we do? I think we pretty
much know which team has the key.
The people who are handling their
bag with care is the real one.
So much so, that they gave
the bag to me.
Seriously, I was carrying
it around for a while.
- Everyone has their bags, right?
- Yes.
Starting now, I will explain
the traveling bag of gold race.
- Traveling?
- Oh, it's traveling.
Among the seven teams, only one team
has the bag with the real gold key.
Starting now, you can move the location
of the bag of gold through the mission.
For every mission that's
completed at this location
the winning team can move all
seven bags in one direction.
And you can check the contents of your bag
after all the bags have stopped moving.
Okay.
- Look at their faces.
[Spaced out.]
I just hope it goes well for Ji Soo.
[Shy.]
They just happened to stand
next to each other.
[Me, too... chemistry...]
Starting now, you have a time
limit of exactly three hours.
- Three hours?
- No way.
After three hours, no matter what the
situation, even in the middle of a mission.
Each team must open the bag at that
time and the team that has the key, wins.
So, you only win when
the time limit expires.
- Only when that time expires.
- Those are the rules.
- You're calculating, so you must have it.
- Do you have the gold?
- I swear, it's not us.
- Do you know where it is?
- Really?
- Then why did you give it?
But your intention... I'm so
confused because of your behavior.
- We'll go ahead and start the first mission.
- Shall we?
- You have to go find something first?
- Oh really?
It's the part where I'm really bad.
- Is that so?
- I think I might have to pass on this one.
- You're not good at finding things.
- I'm really bad at finding things.
Everyone will go up to the
second floor and get a towel.
Find a towel and come back here.
Now, ready! Start!
Let's go!
[The clock is finally ticking.]
- Move, move, move!
- Go, go!
[Win the game and bring the bag of gold.]
[Until the game is over, the team that
has the gold key is the final winner.]
[The mission starts as soon as
they bring back the towel.]
- What do we need to find?
- Towel, towel!
[Goal: Two towels.]
This place is too big.
[Have you been watching 'Running Man'?]
[Meticulously checking every drawer.]
What is it? Did you find one?
[Kwang Soo found one towel.]
We just need to fine one more.
Just one more.
Hey!
[Two consecutive towels in a row!]
- Let's go, let's go!
[Now, they quickly head off
to the mission location.]
Run.
I found it! Hey, Won Joon!
- Won Joon! I found it! Come quickly!
- Jae Suk!
- Hurry up.
- As usual... Yoo-ames.
[Ji Yoon also finds two
in a matter of moments.]
Let's go, Dung Fly! I did it!
Awesome!
Where did you find it?
[Kwang Soo and Da Eun
arrive in first place.]
We found two towels.
[Quickly complete the mission
and make the gold bag yours!]
Starting now, the mission
is an underwater relay.
While one person is underwater, the other
person will run up that escalator.
- Do you see the balloons over there?
- Yes.
There's masking tape on those balloons.
Just take off three.
Take it off without popping it.
Then run down and as soon as you touch your
partner's back, the mission is complete.
Now, decide who is going to run and who
is going to go underwater. Quickly.
You're good at finding things.
[Jae Suk and Won Joon arrives in 2nd place.]
- I'm usually bad at it.
- Oh, it started.
- Is there already a team down there?
- Yeah.
I'll go underwater.
Let me catch my breath first.
Da Eun, you're aggressive.
- Ready... start!
- Run fast.
Start!
He is really slow.
- Don't run like that, okay?
- You're not supposed to run like that.
- Seriously, what is that?
- I thought he'd be fast with those long legs.
- Are you okay?
- Da Eun, come up.
- Yeah, you guys lost.
- Don't bother.
[Take off three tapes on the balloons.]
- You guys lost.
- It's over.
He's falling.
[Already giving up before Kwang
Soo even takes all the tape off.]
[Kwang Soo and Da Eun fail.]
- It's over!
It's over!
Ah...
You should've held your
breath a little bit longer.
Won Joon!
See you soon.
This team could win.
My lung capacity isn't all
that great right now.
Won Joon is at an advantage
since he's a singer.
Not really.
- Ready...
- I might be useless.
- Fighting, Friend!
- Fighting!
Hold on, my nose is runny.
That's okay. It's water, anyway.
- Because I'm going to drink it, right?
- Yeah, it's okay.
[Start.]
[Jae Suk runs up to the
2nd floor like an arrow.]
Jae Suk fell.
- Won Joon.
[Eyes wide open.]
[Jae Suk has reached the second floor.]
- Won Joon.
- It's over.
[The spectators are doing their best
to distract him with their words.]
- Poor Jae Suk.
- What is he doing?
He's still going up.
- Jae Suk! Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk!
Jae Suk.
What the...
He's still going up.
[A singer of 24 years and
insufficient lung capacity.]
[This is enough.]
- That was too short.
Jae Suk!
- What the...
[Happy.]
What were you doing?
[It's already over?]
- Hey!
[It just happened that way, my friend...]
- Jae Suk.
What is up with him?
- Jae Suk, I'm sorry!
- That was the shortest time ever.
[Ji Hyo and Ji Soo.]
Are we the last ones?
Do me a favor and don't
talk to me at all.
- Okay.
- We understand.
Fighting.
- Fighting.
Fighting, Mother.
[Start.]
[A slight falter from Jae Suk's interference.]
[But he furiously runs up to the 2nd floor.]
- It's over, it's over.
[An explosive speed that goes
beyond the length of your legs.]
- He's still fast.
- He's gotten better.
She's holding it in really well.
It's a difficult mission to complete.
- Good job.
- There goes another one.
He keeps popping them.
[Someone might think that it was
a balloon popping mission...]
I think you should come
down for Ji Yoon's sake.
Ji Yoon is holding it in really well.
I guess having a sturdy upper body
really helps in holding your breath.
[Successfully takes off one tape.]
[Takes off another piece
of tape successfully.]
No, just one more!
Just one more! Hold on!
- My upper body feels stronger after talking.
- He's popping all the balloons.
- Just one more, just one more! Hold on!
- Hey!
Wow, you were in there
for a really long time!
- I can't believe what I was hearing!
- You held it in for a really long time.
[Ha Ha and Ji Yoon fail.]
You held it in for a really long time.
I can't believe what I was hearing!
He was popping all of them!
You were underwater for
a really long time.
[Embarrassed.]
- This was nothing!
She's a dolphin.
Ji Yoon's practically a sea creature.
Ji Yoon, I got it now. Seriously.
[Why are you realizing that now?]
- Anyone can win this.
- Let's finish this in a minute.
- You better hurry up.
- I'll get it done in one minute.
- This team has the best chance.
- Still.
Ready...
[Start.]
[Blast off, Kyung Min.]
It's fine as long as there's
no touching, right?
Wow, he has a huge chin.
- Ah, his eyes are closed.
- His eyes are closed. They're closed.
There's a hole on his pants.
[Distract me all you want because
it's not going to faze me.]
He's doing it, he's doing it!
[Kyung Min has reached the
2nd floor at that time.]
[Careful, careful.]
[Successfully taken off one tape.]
[Calmly takes off another one.]
[Just one more tape to
complete the mission...]
[Kyung Min succeeds in one try.]
- Three!
[A state of emergency.]
You have to come down.
Hey, what should we do?
It's over. Block him, block him.
- Block him, block him.
- We can't let him touch his back.
[Sound attack.]
- Don't let him touch his back.
- I know. We can't let him touch his back.
[Kyung Min has made his
way to the 1st floor.]
- Don't let him touch his back.
[A human fortress.]
- He has to three off.
- He did. He got three.
[I'm here, Friend.]
[Touch.]
[Jong Kook and Kyung Min success.]
- It's over.
Hey, you're pretty good!
This is not fun. It really isn't.
- You're pretty good at this.
- This is supposed to be a fun game?
- What is this?
- You're a natural.
Shouldn't the actresses
get their face wet, too?
Hyung Kyung and Ji Soo should get
a chance to dunk their faces in.
I tried to pop some of them, but they just
came off. What am I supposed to do?
- Is it game over?
- I came out because of this.
I could've shown you my bare face.
I even brought a scrunchie with me,
so I could put my hair up.
[Feeling sorry all of a sudden...]
You guys can really hold your breath.
It's not over yet. We're not
playing any games right now.
The clock keeps ticking.
Please hurry.
We're running out of time.
Come on, they're helping us out.
Please hurry.
[Everything is a variable.]
[Who has the bag with the gold key?]
One, two, three, four.
This one is number five.
As promised, Jong Kook and
Kyung Min may rotate the bags.
At least one space and in
a clock-wise direction.
And up to six spaces at most.
The bags just have to
move no matter what.
- At least one space, right?
- Yes.
It has to be at least one space.
- One space.
- Just one space?
[They already know where the
real bag of gold is at.]
Hurry up, we don't have time.
Because there's still a lot of time left,
we'll move it just one space over.
Sounds good.
There's still a lot of time left, so having
the actual bag isn't all that great.
[The bag is no longer in their possession, but
they know where the real bag of gold is at.]
[The Gold Key.]
I can't keep a straight face.
[The relaxed look of the people who
know where the real bag of gold is.]
- There's not a single person you can trust.
- Did it come?
- Did it come here?
- I don't know.
- Really?
- Is it Gary?
- It's not me.
This is getting really complicated.
[Will Ji Hyo and Ji Soo be able to protect
the bag of gold to the very end?]
[There's still a lot of time left.]
What are you doing?
[Moving to the next location.]
It's the karaoke room again.
How can we get 90 points
on this trampoline?
- Isn't this easy for you guys?
- No, not at all.
- It's not?
- I have a sweet voice.
- It won't make an impact.
- You have muscular vocal cords.
- No, no.
- You're all muscle.
[Putting his hopes on rocker, Kyung Min.]
- What songs are there?
- Something simple.
What songs are really simple to sing?
- Something like 'The South-Bound Train.'
- You have to scream it.
Sounds good.
Good, good, good.
We'll go ahead and sing
'The South-Bound Train.'
- We're going to sing that.
- That's our song!
[First come, first serve.]
- We were practicing the choreography!
We were practicing the choreography!
[There's no such thing when
it comes the bag of gold!]
You guys stole our song!
'The South-Bound Train.'
Okay.
[The South-Bound Train.]
[A song that can give you a high score.
What will their score be?]
[Screaming and cheering!]
[Totally in tune with one another.]
- Fighting!
- Starting now!
Okay! Fighting!
It's raining at the Honam station
On the south-bound train
[Taking turns singing a verse.]
The rain is falling down
And my tears are falling down
[The spectators automatically
sing along with them.]
[Fun explosion.]
[A party atmosphere in a
matter of moments.]
[Hyung Kyung, come over here!]
[So excited.]
[Singing loudly for 25 years of friendship.]
Let's go!
What is he doing?
What the heck?
[I just can't hold it in any longer.]
[24 years since his debut and
he's ending it with a screech.]
Good job.
[Unbelievable! They succeeded in one try!]
We did it!
[The party atmosphere goes cold
after Jae Suk and Won Joon's win.]
- What is this?
- It doesn't matter if you win.
- We did it.
- You stole our song.
- We were going to sing that song.
[Ceremony of happiness.]
[I was wrong.]
I was wrong!
Bear it, my friend! Jae Suk!
Seriously, that makes me mad.
[Anyway, Jae Suk and Won Joon
won the second mission.]
- Thank you.
- Ah, what is this?
We did it.
[As the clock keeps ticking...]
[The team that has the bag of
gold is going to drag time.]
[And the team that wants
it is going to rush it.]
Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Won Joon
won this second mission.
The bags must be moved at least one
space or up to six spaces if you want.
[The people who already know which is
the real gold bag are more nervous.]
[Let's see here...]
It's Kwang Soo. We have to check Kwang Soo
or it might be Ji Yoon and Ha Ha.
- Jae Suk, it's Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk, there's no need for that.
- It might be Suk Jin.
- Kwang Soo doesn't have it.
Really?
[Currently, Ji Hyo and Ji Soo have
possession of the real bag of gold.]
Ji Hyo.
- Do you have it?
- Ji Soo suddenly stopped talking.
- Ji Soo, look at my eyes.
- I really don't have it.
- Truly?
- We really don't have it.
Then let's move it four spaces...
one, two, three, four, five.
We'll move it along five spaces.
I want to check Ji Hyo's bag.
- You check it, Mister.
- Mister?
You check it, Mister.
[The real bag of gold is now being
transferred to Jae Suk and Won Joon.]
You can give that to me.
Number three should be here.
[The teams that know the location
of the real bag of gold:]
[Ji Hyo and Ji Soo, Jong Kook
and Kyung Min, Gary and Miryo.]
[Gold Key has been confirmed.]
[Trying hard to maintain a straight face.]
[We know that feeling.]
[The gazes of the wolves
aiming for the bag of gold.]
[Fine. If that's the case...]
[Third Mission: Lung capacity battle.]
[In 30 seconds, the team that has the least
amount of balls in front of them wins.]
[Won Joon easily makes it
to the preliminaries.]
[The semifinals.]
Jae Suk has none right now!
[Jae Suk and Won Joon will
compete in the finals.]
[Final battle against Gary and Miryo.]
[A perfect match.
They dominate Gary and Miryo.]
[The reason they wanted to
be in first place is...]
[Time to move the bags.]
We'll switch with number six.
What number are they?
- You want to move it three spaces.
- Yes, three spaces.
Three spaces.
- Then this bag is going to Jong Kook.
- That's right.
- That's coming to me?
- Yes.
- Three spaces?
That must be the bag of gold.
- This is the gold.
- Really?
Why are you giving it away then?
It's a part of our plan.
[Their biggest enemy is Kim Jong Kook.]
[If Jong Kook and Kyung Min have the gold, then
whoever places first is going to take it away.]
[And if by chance Jong Kook and Kyung Min
wins, they still have to move the bag along.]
[This is the removal plan of the winners.]
Jae Suk, I see what your
intentions are...
I see what you're doing,
but it's a bad move.
Well, that's just my style.
- I'll tell you happy news later.
[Ji Yoon must leave due to her schedule.]
- Can you do it on your own?
- What choice do I have?
- Fighting!
- Fighting, fighting.
- Show them what you got.
- Okay! I'm going!
- Here, I'm going to give you my Iron Man ring.
- Okay, okay.
- Fighting!
[24 minutes left. Starting now,
it's a battle against time.]
[Arrived at the next mission location.]
- We're here.
[The first team to stick their hat on the
ceiling while jumping on an acupuncture pad wins.]
You have the edge since you're tall.
[The floor is completely covered
with acupuncture pads.]
- Did you see it?
- Huh?
You have to jump and stick
your hat on the ceiling.
How is that even possible?
What?
[It's possible since it's a knitted hat.]
- Ah, I see.
Da Eun, let's go right away.
- Hurry, hurry!
- You have to wear this...
[Trying to receive a hat
is just as difficult.]
Can we do a running leap
if jumping doesn't work?
[A running leap?]
Do it from where you stand!
Don't run and jump!
[That looks painful.]
- Ah, it hurts!
Hey, be careful.
What about me?
What should I do?
- You're on your own.
- By myself?
Sticking it on the ceiling is one
thing, it's the landing that hurts.
That's why they covered the
whole floor with this.
It's not supposed to be
comfortable and easy.
One, two, three.
- Awesome.
- She got it!
I did it.
[If Suk Jin is successful,
they win right away.]
[The clogged blood vessels go 'boom!']
[Hop.]
- You did it, you did it!
- Hurry up, Gary!
[They place first if Gary succeeds.]
[Too short.]
[At that time, Won Joon
goes on top of the desk.]
Please!
[Success?]
This hurts!
This is the only solution.
[A strong and healthy cry is
heard throughout the room.]
I have to do one more!
Give me another one.
- I'm scared!
- Fighting!
[A head butt to the ceiling.]
[A bad side effect of being overzealous.]
- Did it stick?
- No, it didn't.
[Lost his mind. Lost his hat.]
[Jae Suk is successful!]
Oh, Mother! Oh my gosh!
- I'm next.
- There's no such thing!
There is no order.
[Complete chaos.]
[15 minutes left. At this rate,
the whole game will be over.]
[In that case, Jong Kook and Kyung
Min are the final winners.]
[Kwang Soo succeeds!]
[Whoever sticks their hat
to the ceiling first wins.]
- I got it!
- You did it! Good job!
Good job, good job! We won!
- We did it.
- We did it, we did it.
- Let's move to the next game.
- Let's do the next game. Hurry!
[The people aiming for the bag of gold
need to play the next game quickly.]
Jae Suk, you have number six.
Do I have number four?
- Ha Ha, you're number four.
- What number did we have?
- Let's hurry it up.
- Let's do the next game.
[With the real bag in their possession,
Jong Gook and Kyung Min are very calm.]
Let's move the bags.
Just move it one space over.
- Let's move it.
- Just once space?
Everybody already knows.
Go ahead and take number two.
- One space over.
- Okay.
Move it one space.
From here on out, number two is
the same as carrying a knife.
Just win the next mission then.
It can end in the middle of the game, too.
[Heading straight to the
next mission location.]
[The countdown to zero is approaching.]
- Look at the time!
- One person will go upstairs.
- And that person will drop the hula hoop.
- Okay.
You win if your partner catches 10
hoops with their neck in 30 seconds.
- Okay!
- You have 30 seconds!
- One person go upstairs.
- Go!
[Besides Suk Jin and Hyung Kyung,
everyone needs to hurry.]
The way you throw it is really important.
Da Eun, just drop from it there.
Da Eun!
[Only 10 minutes left.]
Da Eun! Drop it!
[Now is the perfect time to win the mission
and get the bag in our possession!]
Hurry!
[They got one!]
[Trying to stay calm in an urgent situation.]
Three!
Is it over?
[The next team has to
hurry up and get ready.]
[Throwing it steadily and
accepting it calmly.]
There's only 8 minutes left.
We just have to drag it out.
They could win here.
[But...]
[It looks pretty serious.]
- He's really calm and focused.
How many do you have to catch?
He looks like a seal right now.
[If they get one more from here...]
[No...]
- How many is it?
- Nine!
It would've been over if
you got the last one.
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay!
[It's Jae Suk's and Won Joon's turn.]
I can't see! Hey!
How am I supposed to catch this?
What are you doing?
You two really suck.
- Catch it, friend!
- Hey!
You can do it!
Don't throw it upright!
Okay, Hyun Kyung!
Take your time. Don't rush it.
Whoa.
[Their goal is to waste time, anyway.]
Quickly, quickly.
What are you doing right now?
What is this?
- Nice. Keep it going.
- What's with that look on your face?
What is this?
What's with that look on your face?
[Is he trying to catch it... or avoid it...]
What... What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Just what was that?
[In any case, 30 seconds
were successfully expended.]
- Hyun Kyung!
- Yes?
We're going to be winners
in three more minutes!
Three minutes!
Look at the clock!
- Yoo Jae Suk, fighting!
- Throw it!
Five.
Six.
- Yes!
- Suk Jin might win if we're not careful.
We're about to win here.
Two minutes and twenty-two seconds!
Here I go.
You have to do it quickly.
You have to look while
you're doing it!
- Okay, okay, okay.
- One!
[Nervous.]
One minute and fifty-one seconds.
Okay, okay, okay!
Why don't you just call it quits?
Honestly, that might be better.
Why are you quitting?
Keep going. Why are you stopping?
There's one minute left! One minute!
Hyun Kyung, one minute!
Hurry, hurry! Hurry up!
Throw it quickly!
Throw it well!
- Hey!
- We won! Hyun Kyung, come down!
Come down!
We're not going to do it.
We won, anyway.
Hey, hey, hey! Ah, this...
[However...]
- Jong Kook, get ready!
There's 35 seconds left!
Jong Kook, get ready!
- 31 seconds.
- Okay!
Kwang Soo.
This is it. This is your last chance.
[They miraculously catch every hoop.]
Come out!
- Throw it, throw it!
- Do all of it.
Hey, 15 seconds! 14 seconds!
Hyun Kyung!
Ji Soo, come quickly. Where is Hyun Kyung?
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Seven seconds!
Kyung Min, we did it!
Just get this last one and we win!
We got all of it! We got all ten!
We're done! We got all of it!
- How many? How many?
- We got all ten of them!
You went over three seconds.
[Will it be the time limit or the
completed mission that comes first?]
- Ten seconds left!
- This is the last one!
[Jong Kook and Jong Min caught
nine with three seconds to go.]
[But before the tenth hoop came down...]
[Time was already over.]
Yeah!
[Suk Jin and Hyun Kyun are the victors!]
The winners are...
Ji Suk Jin and Oh Hyun Kyung.
[They fought to the very
end to gain victory.]
Since you won today,
please say a word or two.
I had so much fun today and this
was such a stress reliever.
My daughter got a chance to see me have
fun and work hard with other people.
It was so much fun!
You guys worked really hard today.
The winner's today are Ji Suk Jin
and Oh Hyun Kyung!
- Thank you.
[We hope everyone's
friendship never changes...]
If it's Super Junior, then
there's Siwon, Leeteuk...
- Is he too fat?
- Ryeo Wook.
[Idols that rarely go on variety
shows, come storming in.]
Hello, I'm Eric Nam!
[I've been waiting for this day. You
will remember my name before I leave.]
[But, can you do this?]
[However, they do their
best and get it done.]
[A fierce battle is about
to unfold on Running Man.]
- You guys.
- Please help us.
- I don't know when I'll see you guys again.
- I know.
- I had a great time.
- Sure.
Subtitles by DramaFever