Running Man
[Happy New Year Running Man]
Happy New Year!
Have a great new year!
[Down flat]
[Have a great new year]
Today is the first episode of the year.
However, the actual day we're
filming is in December.
It doesn't yet feel like new year's but,
today we will
try our best since it is the first
episode of the new year.
Let's give it our best.
[Mental Revolution]
Who do you think the first
guest of 2015 will be?
Since they are the first guests
they are probably great people.
Look at what they made in the back.
They are probably really great guests.
Who are you?
Come out!
What is this?
It must be cold.
It must be very cold.
[Emerging from the snowstorm.]
[The much anticipated first guests of 2015.]
[Here they come!]
[Lee Seung Gi and Moon Chae Won!]
[The comeback of the
National Handsome Boy, Seung Gi.]
[The definition of elegance,
Moon Chae Won.]
[Shining from the start of the new year.]
[They look like a lovely couple
straight from a storybook.]
- It's Moon Chae Won.
- Look at how skinny she is.
[Chae Won escorted by gentleman Seung Gi.]
- Where are you going?
[Giraffe, get out of the way!]
Seung Gi can do that!
[National Charming Couple, Seung Gi
and Chae Won's Running Man visit.]
She's pretty.
She's really pretty.
Why are you coming over here?
What are you two doing?
I'm helping her take this off.
Seung Gi.
- Don't do that.
- Get out of here!
Get the lint off your own coat!
This isn't lint!
Get the lint off your clothes!
The first guests of the year are
Moon Chae Won and Lee Seung Gi.
[The greatest visual couple
starts off the new year.]
Running Man viewers,
I visit almost once every year.
This is the first time the both of us
filmed a movie.
Isn't this your first movie?
Let's hear Moon Chae Won's voice.
It's been a long time since I've
been on television.
It's been a year and a half
since I finished 'Good Doctor.'
I'm sorry but...
Don't do that!
What are you doing?
Just leave it!
I was just taking that off.
It looks fine on her.
Why are you touching that?
What are you doing?
Get out!
I haven't seen you for a while.
But you've become really hot-blooded.
He's like this everyday.
[Dizzy]
He's always like this these days.
He's the variety show gangster.
Variety Show Gangster.
That is because
Suk Jin is older but he's my junior.
What?
- He's my junior comedian.
- He is my senior of two years.
That is why he acts like my senior.
[Giraffe keeps looking at Chae Won]
Go in.
Why are you coming forward?
- Stop coming out.
- I am also friends with Chae Won.
- You did a drama with her, right?
- She did a drama with him.
You guys did a drama together.
I filmed 'Nice Guy' with her.
We text each other.
He sends you the text first, right?
Yes.
Chae Won really...
Chae Won is my... Chae Won...
He's really messy!
It's not being messy.
Who is the younger co-star
Wang Ji Hye spoke about?
That's not true.
I... I also...
I texted him first in the beginning
but later he...
You found out he wasn't all that
great later on, right?
It's not because of that.
She only sent him the text as a friend
but he became too aggressive
so she stopped because she
felt uncomfortable.
If you're even a little nice to Kwang Soo
he thinks that you like him so...
Oh...
What do you mean 'oh'?
It's not true!
This is a nice way to start the year.
This is very nice.
I will tell you the rules for today.
I'll announce the teams first.
You know what to do, right?
- In order to make good teams...
- I'm really close to her.
Please make good teams.
Don't worry about it being Monday.
It is the new year so please
give us a gift.
Lee Seung Gi who is an important guest
that visits us once every year...
Seung Gi is our family.
Lee Seung Gi...
Yoo Jae Suk...
[Happy vs. Disappointed]
[Jae Suk is not on the same
team as Chae Won.]
I like Seung Gi.
Isn't this too much?
- I know you want Chae Won but...
- Seung Gi, it's not that...
I'm sorry.
It's not that.
[Disappointed.]
And the person that made a good partner in
solving the mystery behind the numbers...
Lee Kwang Soo!
You guys are one team.
Congratulations.
[Can't hide the disappointment.]
I'm not that happy with this either.
Seung Gi, it's not that.
I'm not that happy either.
[People that want to be on
Chae Won's team are hopeful.]
I can't believe this.
[Now there is Chae Won's team
and Running Man's team left.]
Ji Hyo! Where's Ji Hyo?
I'm right here!
We need to take care of Ji Hyo too.
[They almost forgot Blank Ji.]
Is it like this?
Is it the four of us?
No, it's not like that.
It is the three of you.
Come over here.
What?
[Frozen]
Chae Won wants to be on this team.
Let's be the four of us with Seung Gi.
Chae Won really doesn't want
to go over there.
She really doesn't want to.
It's okay. We won't hurt you.
Can everyone move away
to the sides?
[Firm as a rock]
Move!
Come here.
I moved one step away.
His clothes are rough too.
[Crumpled]
There is a lot of competition today.
Please!
Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I pushed away
your arm.
I don't expect anything from you either.
I'm sorry.
[There is no Monday couple today.]
Please!
It is the two people that are crazy
about beautiful women.
I'm really crazy about them.
I'm totally crazy about them.
[Everyone admits it.]
Is it me?
I'm really crazy about beautiful women.
It is the two people that will stand out
with Moon Chae Won between them.
I must be on the same team with her.
The person on Moon Chae Won's team is...
It is me, the squid.
Gary and Ha Ha.
They really do stand out.
[They clearly stand out.]
The two of you will assist Song Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook can't get married again.
[Lonely Bachelor I]
[Bashful Bachelor II]
I will explain today's rules.
We need to listen to this carefully.
It is today's weather.
[Weather Weather]
Because of the world's diversity, all kinds
of weather are occurring at the same time.]
- Again?
- I can picture it already.
I can picture it.
It means there's also summer.
Why is it always like this
when I come?
The last mission is this...
An enormous disaster will occur
because of the unusual weather.
There is only one place that has
normal weather.
Everyone's mission will be to
find the safest place
through the hints you will gain
throughout the day.
Jong Kook keeps sighing really loudly.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to rest today.
I'm going to be relaxed today.
This team stepped on poop in the
first episode of the year.
This is the first day.
What are they going to do?
It could've been worse.
They don't like being with each other.
[Break through the unusual weather
and find the safest location. Start!]
[As soon as they come outside,
the cold greets them.]
It was always cold when
you came out.
It was always cold and there
was always water.
It can't be...
We won't go inside water in
this weather, right?
Red.
[They move to the next mission
place in teams.]
[Kiddo Ha Ha with manners.]
The heater...
[Still a little amazed]
Chae Won was worried about
filming Running Man.
Why?
Since filming a variety show makes
her feel awkward.
It's been a while.
We need to be nice to her.
They'll be good to her, right?
- Of course.
- The red car seemed to be in high spirits.
Gary and Ha Ha are experts at
assisting actresses.
Really?
They are experts at tending to
the needs of actresses.
They are really good at that.
I'm being very truthful.
Jeon Ji Hyun and Moon Chae Won
are the best.
Looks are important.
They are very beautiful.
They are.
Can you send me a heart?
Send it through the camera.
Squid!
[Happy Chae Won and the two squids.]
[The landscape continues to become
more suspicious.]
In noir movies they get dragged
to these places.
That's exactly what it is.
This isn't a place we would go to voluntarily.
We get dragged to these kinds of places.
Even the air is cold.
[Arrived at the first mission site.]
Whenever Seung Gi comes
he always has a hard time.
What did we do last time he was here?
We did some flying thing.
I remember.
[Early winter water gun attack]
[Flying chair mission]
[He did the flying chair mission twice.]
[The icon guest of hardships, Lee Seung Gi.]
- What's worse is that I am afraid of heights.
- This is what I like.
Having a fear of heights.
This is what I really like.
This is the best situation for
variety shows.
There needs to be things like this.
If they aren't scared when they
go up to high places then...
Ha Ha!
Do I also have a name tag on my back?
Yes, you do.
Chae Won, what's wrong?
Did something happen?
Chae Won is really funny.
She has a very cute charm.
Kwang Soo keeps on wondering whether
or not he was close to you?
I personally thought we
were like family.
- Can you stop bothering her?
- Bothering?
Actresses don't want to come out
because of you.
[No...]
When Kwang Soo sends you a text,
is it long or short?
It's short. He sends 'kekekeke' a lot.
He sends me long texts.
What are we going to do about him?
You are hopeless.
Should we call Wang Ji Hye
one more time?
- Should we call her?
- I told you that it wasn't true.
Who is it?
Is it Chae Won?
There was a reason for everything.
Why are we walking so far?
How did they find this place?
What is this?
The place is too noir.
[An empty piece of land]
[with an unidentifiable container
and puddle.]
[What is this?]
Why does this only happen
when I come?
What is this?
[Also what is this thing supposed to be?]
Why does this only happen
when I come?
[More than panic. Cries.]
[What is the first mission of 2015?]
Look at Chae Won's expression.
Look at Seung Gi.
Seung Gi, this only happens
when you come!
Chae Won can't believe
this is happening.
[Putting on their variety war shoes.]
[Chae Won puts on the variety show
war shoes for the first time.]
No, wait.
They're both for the left foot.
This is size 280. Do you want it?
[No thank you.]
[Blank Ji puts it on with ease.]
Nobody is taking care of Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo can take care of herself.
It's fine!
Why can't you let me do this for you?
[Boards the unidentifiable container.]
[Her legs give out because of
the new atmosphere.]
Chae Won is still in her own bubble.
She needs a lot of help.
Your mission is
'Running Bedrock Protrusion.'
The earth was suddenly becoming dried up
so the bedrock suddenly changed form.
That is why the people took shelter
in the container.
[So that's what happened.]
We will now...
Are we starting?
[Mommy...]
Why are you doing this to us?
[They instinctively moved to the
inside of the container.]
Why are you moving to the back?
Why do you keep moving back?
What is with Moon Chae Won?
[The container suddenly tilts.]
[What is wrong with this?]
[The slope suddenly changes due to
the unusual weather.]
What are you doing?
We didn't start yet.
What do you mean 'we didn't start'?
[It is hard to control their body movements
because of the sudden steepness.]
It started.
The last person remaining
gets one point.
The first team to get three points, wins.
[Push down the opponents.]
[Do whatever it takes to be
the last person remaining.]
We will now get it to the game angle.
[As the slope gets steeper]
[the bigger the fear becomes.]
Ready...
[Start Round One]
If only one person has to live,
it will be me.
We can all live!
[There is even a surprise blizzard.]
[The slope keeps getting higher.]
[It is difficult to hang on.]
Seung Gi, come up!
[Kkuk grabs the wall]
[Chae Won blocks Kkuk]
[Because of Kkuk,
Gary and Seung Gi are out.]
[They fall into the puddle in the
middle of the winter.]
[Jae Suk and Big-nosed Brother are out.]
[Kkuk and Ha Ha are also out.]
[The only ones left are Chae Won,
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.]
[The last one remaining gets one point.]
[Chae Won knocked out six people
with one blow.]
[Each team has one person left.]
Kwang Soo!
How did we all fall?
Chae Won!
There is only one person left
on each team.
- Kwang Soo is still alive?
- Kwang Soo is alive.
[They can't attack each other because
holding on is difficult enough.]
Ji Hyo, kick Kwang Soo's head!
[Chae Won listen to Kook and
kicks Kwang Soo right away.]
[She turns aggressive.
Her kicks are tough.]
[Kwang Soo is out because of
Chae Won's kicks.]
I told you to hang on!
[This is the moment!]
[Ji Hyo's sudden attack!]
[The last person remaining wins!]
Chae Won, you need to hang on!
Just fall together!
If they fall together, then later...
[First slapstick comedy of 2015]
Where did Suk Jin go?
[While the bystanders are laughing...
the survivors are fiercely fighting.]
[The container gets steeper.]
[Chae Won fights back!]
[Her hidden fighter's instinct!]
Nice!
[Her fighting spirit
surprises the Ace!]
Pull her!
[Chae Won pulls out the Ace!]
[Blank Ji and Chae Won fall together.]
[Whoever's foot reaches
the puddle first loses.]
[Whose foot will reach the puddle first?]
[Splash]
[Her fighting mode turns off and
she's back to peace mode.]
She finally let it go.
[I did my best...]
Are you okay?
Song Ji Hyo and Moon Chae Won
are both in first place.
Let's do this properly!
Chae Won, you got first place.
We got first place!
[She showed amazing fighting spirit.]
Hang in there!
[Wink]
[Nod]
I can hear you rolling your eyes.
I can hear it very clearly.
It's not that.
[Everyone makes a silent alliance
against Mr. Capable.]
Hang in there!
Let's wait for the right moment.
Right moment?
You know what their plan is, right?
[They're waiting for the right moment
to get rid of me, right?]
[Start Round Two]
[Big-Nosed Brother gets attacked right away]
[It wasn't me but Big-Nosed Brother?]
[Mr. Capable Explodes!]
[No!]
[His super power pushes
six people at once!]
[They all helplessly fall down.]
Hold on to it!
[They got rid of Big Nose first for being
on the same team as Mr. Capable.]
[Big-Nosed Brother and five
other people are out!]
[Ha Ha is also out!]
[Yellow Team: 2 Brown Team: 1 Blue Team: 0]
We are doomed now!
We are now done for!
It was because Suk Jin was sliding down.
They pulled me down.
It's good.
We just need to leave Suk Jin.
[Can Big-Nosed Brother remain the last
person standing by himself?]
Since we got rid of the boring person
we will get a funny scene.
It's because of Suk Jin.
Our strategy is a success.
The Blue Team has the highest chance of
winning because they have three people.
You know that, right?
We need to take out a person
from the blue team.
Ha Ha, let's do it together.
[Yellow team is leading with two points.]
[Yellow team numerically has the
highest chance of winning.]
This is the best because we have
all three people remaining.
What is going on right now?
If I remain inside then we win.
Yellow team is leading.
Try to stay on.
Stay at the top.
I will live up to your expectations in 2015.
[I believe you, Big-Nosed Brother.]
[Jae Suk won in Round 3.]
- Sit down.
- Why?
[They all focus on Big-Nosed Brother.]
I won't go down by myself.
[Start Round Four]
Suk Jin, the top!
[All five of them start to come down
in one piece.]
[First target: Big-Nosed Brother]
Suk Jin can't win!
[Ha Ha and Seung Gi fell at the same time
but Ha Ha reached the puddle first.]
[At the last moment, Ha Ha jumped.]
I fell down first.
[They're trying to make Seung Gi win,
in order to get him out of the next game.]
I jumped down first.
No!
I jumped down first!
I told you to jump down first!
I really came down first!
[The last person remaining was
Lee Seung Gi.]
[Yellow Team: 2 Brown Team: 1 Blue Team: 2]
What is this?
I really tried my best to jump off.
My head is all wet.
Seung Gi couldn't stay on.
We need to send Kwang Soo.
I didn't know he would be able to
jump down that quickly.
[Round Four's strategy is a success.
There are two people left on the Brown team.]
[Trickle]
What is this?
[He tried his best.
There is muddy water in his hat.]
Do you want coffee?
[Seung Gi can still joke about things.]
[Gary won Round Five.]
There is no nervous tension.
Only the Traitors Club left.
This game with only traitors left
has a different kind of fun.
[Traitors Club meets:
Ha Ha vs. Kwang Soo vs. Suk Jin]
The person that falls down first
can't get a hint.
You know who it is, right?
You know who it has to be, right?
You know, right?
[No. One Target Kwang Soo is in the middle.
They're scheming up something.]
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo's toes are arched.
Can't you change his shoes?
His shoes are 260.
His feet are popping out.
- Step on his feet!
[Start Round Six]
Isn't that too dangerous?
- Kwang Soo!
- Suk Jin!
Push him down!
You have to get a good spot!
Push them down!
You can't give him your spot!
[It continues to get steeper.]
[The Traitor war is firing up.]
You can't give up your spot!
[The winner of this round decides
which team gets the final win.]
That's how you do it!
[Big-Nosed Brother and Kwang Soo
get entangled.]
Suk Jin! No!
Push them!
[Ha Ha attacks both of them.]
Push!
Suk Jin!
[Ha Ha pushes!]
[Both people fall down helplessly.]
Nice!
No!
[Kwang Soo uses his long legs as
emergency brakes.]
[Big-Nosed Brother and Kwang Soo
are in danger!]
[Will Ha Ha win just like this?]
[Big-Nosed Brother and Kwang Soo are out!]
[Brown Team wins.]
Big-Nosed Brother is buried in the puddle.
[Ha Ha is the strongest out of the weakest
members of each team.]
[Big-Nosed Brother and Kwang Soo prove their
weakness at the beginning of the year.]
Isn't there a hint for second place too?
There is.
[Ha Ha is in first place.]
[Brown Team wins the first mission.]
[The first place hint for the last place
with normal weather.]
We won first place.
We got first place because of Chae Won.
[A place that makes energy in order to prevent
global warming always has clear skies.]
A place that makes energy in order to prevent
global warming always has clear skies.
We need to find each letter.
That's not what we are
supposed to do with this.
Move to the next mission place.
This is the second place hint.
[Big-Nosed Brother won the
second-third place game.]
See it here?
[Peek]
Don't look at it.
[Because of the high atmospheric pressure, there
are clearer skies and therefore, more tourists.]
Let's take it and think about it.
[Whisper]
[Seung Gi succeeded in stealing a
glance at the hint?]
[Moving to the next mission place.]
Today's weather:
A place that makes oxygen in order to prevent
global warming always has clear skies.
Clear skies...
- That part is confusing.
- Right?
I think it's a tree.
It's a tree!
Let's take a look at the hint.
The main point is that it is a
tourist hot-spot.
It is a tourist hot-spot.
We're the only ones without a hint.
We only have what Seung Gi was
able to steal a glance at.
Tourist hot-spot.
High atmospheric pressure.
Why high atmospheric pressure?
It said, something because of
'high atmospheric pressure'...
High atmospheric pressure comes out
because it has something to do with weather.
If we think of it real simply,
it could just mean a high place.
If we don't get first place this time
I don't think we can win.
- We have to do it this time.
- We must get first place.
We need to get first place in this round.
- If we get last place then...
- It's over.
We need to return our car keys...
[What do these hints mean?]
[Ice Age]
What is this?
[Above white ice...
there is a table.]
It's like a restaurant.
What is this?
I welcome everyone.
[What age is this?]
What age do you think this is?
Ice Age!
Stone Age!
Correct.
It is the Ice Age, Lee Seung Gi.
Kwang Soo doesn't know things like that.
I welcome you to the Ice Age restaurant.
It is now the Ice Age so
everything has been frozen over.
You will do a mission that
has to do with food.
The first team to finish the mission
will come in first place.
The next teams will be in second and
third place respectively.
There are currently two teams
that have won hints.
It is the first and second place.
If it's something to eat,
it is probably ice cream.
We will eat it even if our teeth fall out.
Stop talking on the side.
Since you don't have a hint
the hint about the last place
Seung Gi saw something.
Seung Gi saw something secretly.
- He didn't see everything but...
- Are you looking down on me right now?
High atmospheric pressure!
And tourist hot-spot.
- When did you see the hint?
- Don't say anything.
I feel like she's going to say something.
If you know something say it.
Can they steal glances at the hint?
What is he talking about?
I didn't hear anything about the
high atmospheric pressure.
- It's the second place hint.
- It's not this way.
You need to put your hand
on the other side.
High atmospheric pressure and what?
If you know the hint you usually share it.
Tourist hot-spot.
You need to tell us something too.
[Tourist hot-spot is our hint.]
You can't tell them.
Don't let them get to you.
She's not coming over.
Can they steal the hint from us?
- You are the worst.
- Can they steal it from us?
We'll steal the hint too.
[Should I not have done that?]
I'm going to grab it, rip it,
and see it later.
- I'm going to rip their clothes.
- Why would you rip our clothes?
It's war today!
Go home in shorts later!
[Yellow vs. Blue: Ice War]
Let's stay out of this.
Stay still.
Since Lee Seung Gi's team got here
first, please have a seat.
You're talking about
Handsome A group, right?
Shall we start?
Ice Age Restaurant.
We thought you'd be hungry so we will
start with the main course right away.
That will be great.
Please bring the main course in.
What is it?
The concept is nice but...
give him a jacket to put on.
He's shivering because it's cold.
[What is inside?]
- Tell me what you want to eat.
- I want ramyun.
- I want soo jae bi.
- Warm soo jae bi.
- Steak.
- Steak?
Please open it after you
count to three.
One, two, three!
[Main course is revealed...]
[The result?]
[Disappointed]
[Ice Steak]
It's steak.
They made it really well.
[You want us to eat this?]
It was a steak but it froze
because of the Ice Age.
So this is an ice steak.
I'm really angry.
Are you picking a fight with us?
We're in big trouble...
I like it very well done so cook
it more for me.
What do you want us to do with this?
I think you need to slice it and eat it.
You need to slice the steak
into three pieces.
You need to slice it in three pieces and
eat it within the time limit.
- You want us to eat that?
- We need to cut it in three pieces.
Slice it against the grain.
What is the time limit?
- It is 60 seconds.
- 60 seconds?
Start!
- How do we..?
- Be careful.
We can't help this.
It's working.
One piece.
[Snatch]
[Mouthful]
That's the smallest one.
This is too big. Jae Suk...
[The biggest piece: Seung Gi]
[Second piece: Jae Suk]
- Why did you give Seung Gi such a big piece?
- You must really like Seung Gi.
This is too big.
[Because of fast Kwang Soo,
Seung Gi has a difficult time.]
Seung Gi is doing it.
[I will eat it all.]
[There is no progress in
eating the ice steak.]
[Total focus]
Chew it.
Just chew it.
That won't work.
It's delicious, right?
Does the steak taste good?
Is the steak well done?
[Kwang Soo is melting the steak
in his mouth.]
Isn't this too big?
Did he spit it out?
That's my tooth.
It's my tooth.
It's so big though.
[They're trying their best but
the ice steak is still the same.]
[Eating Ice Steak - Fail]
How are we supposed to do this?
- Why do you keep drooling?
- 'Why do you keep drooling?'
Why don't you try it?
You try it.
We have insurance, right?
For our teeth.
Are your teeth all right?
And you...
We're a team. How could you snatch
the small one like that?
I didn't know that you were
that fast.
That's how you do it.
You're sneaky.
Can you give us the kid's set?
It's too big.
It really is too big.
It's too much.
How are we supposed to eat this?
Chae Won needs to eat a good
amount for us.
Chae Won can eat this piece.
Can you eat this much?
That much in one minute?
We're going to start.
Start!
- That's good.
- Eat it.
Nice.
Mine is the biggest!
It's as big as Ha Ha's face.
You have to eat it like Gary.
Ha Ha's really fast.
You need to bite it.
Chae Won, you're good at this.
Because Chae Won's eating it,
it looks really delicious.
It fell.
[Quick Mouth Gary is faster than light.]
Chae Won is really good at this.
Gary, were you hungry?
Chae Won already ate half of it.
[At this rate]
[they might succeed in 60 seconds.]
Chae Won, what are you doing?
Chae Won...
makes it look like Snow White is
eating a poisoned apple.
They look like Snow White and
the dwarves.
This is Ha Ha's.
Do you want it?
Gary, it looks like you're
eating something hot.
[Force feeding]
I can't feel anything.
[Snow White wants to play pranks.]
[Tired Gary, melts the ice]
[They try their best but...]
We can't even do this in two minutes.
[Eating ice steak - Fail]
Chae Won, you ate a lot though.
They did eat a lot.
Gary's good at this.
[What a shame.]
[I should've eaten a little more.]
You can't eat the main menu again
since you already ate the steak.
Is there anything Korean?
The second menu is
- I like Spaghetti.
- Chicken breast?
Isn't there anything like superfine
fibre noodles?
Bean?
If I feel like they will succeed,
I'm going to swallow it.
Please open it.
[Second dish: Ice Pepero]
We need to succeed for this one!
Time limit.
Two people from each team
needs to come out.
They're going to play the pepero game.
The person with the shortest ice
fragment will come in first place.
The important point in this game is that
if you drop the stick while
breaking it with your teeth
then it is a failure.
You will be disqualified.
- Can we grab it with our hand?
- You cannot grab it with your hand.
My front teeth are weak.
- If it falls you're out.
- I'll do it with Kwang Soo.
Since my front teeth are weak.
I really want to help you but...
He wants to help but his front teeth
are weak.
[Healthy Smile is Seung Gi's Achilles heel]
Only my front teeth are weak.
He is the youngest one on our team
but his front teeth are weak.
We need to work on it like a board.
At the end we need to melt it.
You do know that if you tilt it while you do it
then your spit will slide down, right?
That's too much detail.
You need to make sure you're
on the same level.
Or else the spit will slide down
to one side.
Look up front.
If the ice cracks and falls,
then it's a fail.
[Make sure the center doesn't break]
[Ice pepero game: Start!]
[They carefully chew towards each other.]
[Eyes fixed]
Nice.
[They're almost there.]
[We won't drop it.]
What are they doing with their neck?
[Why are they tilting their heads?]
That's it.
[Please stop.]
[Shock]
[Irritation]
[The ice kiss calls for a fist.]
What are you two doing?
They ate everything.
Who's going to beat that?
[They dropped it!]
Fail!
It's right here.
They should be disqualified.
It disappeared.
[Thankfully they found it.]
You probably know this but
we will measure the longest length.
In my whole life, I have never done it
so intensely, even with a girl.
If it's like that, shouldn't they
be disqualified?
Don't melt it with your hands.
Please put it down.
I understand.
[Let us measure it.]
This is the width.
[Alien words]
Don't touch it.
1.4... 1.3 cm
It is 1.4 cm long.
Chae Won came today.
Chae Won and Gary should do it.
You two can do it.
It's no fun then.
Okay. Chae Won!
This is a game.
We just have to do it thinner
than the other team, right?
Thinner than the first team.
Do you really want to do this?
Tell me for sure.
I want to do this.
Please tell me for sure.
[Sad]
How did we do it before?
One bite, one bite?
- Tilt your head like this and...
- You both have to chew.
We need to bite it and at the end
our teeth have to touch.
The last time I did this was
in high school.
Did you do this before?
In college?
In college it was harder.
It wasn't ice like this.
We had to move the square ice.
Can we change?
Why did you say that all of a sudden?
Awesome!
[Amazed]
In college we used the small square ice cubes.
We had to use our lips to move it.
Is that how you played back then?
[Let's remember the small ice cubes.]
One bite each, right?
[Chae Won: 'A game is just a game.']
[But Gary: 'Pit a pat']
[Extremely Nervous]
Ready!
Calm down.
[Eating ice pepero: Start!]
- Slowly. A little more.
- They're almost there.
Calm down.
[Stare]
[They're getting rid of the
ice pepero really quickly.]
Slowly.
Look at them.
[Will...]
[Chae Won and Gary's ice
be shorter than 1.4cm?]
[The ice slipped!]
[What a waste!]
Let's start again from here.
Let's do it one more time.
[Let's save Ha Ha's challenge
for another time.]
Let's measure... where is it?
What's the point of measuring
the length?
It is 4.5 cm.
Suk Jin refused to do it with me
and Jong Kook.
Just do it together.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
- You two do it.
Why us?
He says that he really hates
this game.
I hate this game.
- You have a reason to play this game.
- I don't care about the reason.
- Just do rock, paper, scissors.
- Just do it.
Should I do it for you?
Black Knight?
[If it's with Blank Ji,
I can do it 100 times.]
I can do this 100 times.
Rock, paper, scissors.
There you go.
Oh my god!
[Embarrassed]
Did you guys promise to do paper?
They wanted to do it together.
[Trying to smile]
Don't hold the center.
I think this is the first time I've seen
these two together like this.
It's the first time.
[Serious]
- You have to win. It's just a game.
- Of course.
- Wait.
- It's a game.
It can't be just one person doing it.
- It doesn't fit in one person's mouth so...
- I got it.
It's a game.
Ready!
Gary, can you stand back a little?
It's just so funny so...
[A lot of preparation.
She's even putting her hat back.]
Ready?
You scared me.
Why are you closing your eyes?
This is heartwarming.
This is their first pepero game.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's first
pepero game...]
[But Ji Hyo...]
[succeeded in 0.4 cm in the past
with Park Seo Jun.]
[And Jong Kook...]
[is Mr. Capable that succeeded in
0.3 cm with Ha Yeon Soo.]
[Mr. Capable and Ace]
[Their first pepero came will result in..?]
Start!
They might discover some feelings
that they didn't know about before.
[One bite]
[As they keep going...]
Do you two like...
[It ends in vain!]
Let's do it again!
[Blank]
What is this?
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyo get the worst result.]
You two don't work together.
They just don't work together.
What doesn't work, doesn't work.
Gary likes it the most.
I though this would lead to
something new.
Monday Couple's power is blocking us.
[Monday Couple forever!]
First place is Lee Seung Gi's team.
[They finally got a hint!]
We don't have any hints yet.
We should've done this.
Who got second place?
[Yellow team won in the ice cup
juice drinking game]
- It's me.
- What do you mean 'me?' It's 'us.'
It's ours.
Why is that important?
- It is important.
- Not yet.
The other team saw it before
because of you.
[Should I see it or not?]
I'm sorry.
We won't see it.
[Yoo Hyuk is eavesdropping.]
Today, this place...
Be quiet.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you reading it?
[It's now!]
It's okay.
Why are you doing this?
I can't see it.
Can't we change our team?
Do we have to see it now?
Yes. You need to see it here.
[What's Yellow team's hint?]
Finished?
They don't know what it is
even if they do see it.
- First place.
- It's us!
Seung Gi.
The three of you need to see it together.
[Under tight security]
Be careful.
[Surrounded by enemies]
Gary, over here.
[Ha Ha's plan: look through the camera]
[They hide it deeply.]
[Ha Ha and Gary see everything.]
[Please show it to us...]
Did you read it already?
- You couldn't see it.
- I couldn't see it.
You have to see it too.
[He shows it to Seung Gi again.]
Did you see anything?
Wait! Gary, what are you doing?
I saw the letter.
I was so close to seeing it.
What are you doing?
[Everyone's staring at you.]
- I saw it.
- They're smart.
[Hide your hint or we'll be able to see it.]
[You can't let your guard down,
even at the last moment.]
You can take it.
If we can take it, why'd you
make us read it here!
If we were gonna take it...
What are you doing?
[What hint did the blue team get?]
[Blue Team's hint]
What is this?
Today, at the place where I show myself twice
a day, the sun is planning to shine brightly.
'At the place where I show myself twice?'
Isn't it like a riddle?
'At the place where I show myself
twice a day', what?
'The sun is planning to shine brightly.'
Clock?
Twice a day?
The clock goes twelve and then twelve
again in one day.
The clock that is a tourist hot-spot?
The clock at the city hall?
Show myself twice a day?
It is a tourist hot-spot.
Today, the sun will shine as bright as the
temperature of the water at this place increases.
That means there is nice weather.
The water at this place?
The 'water' is the important point.
'The water at this place'...
Where heaven and earth meet
at Mt. Baekdu?
The answer is this place.
It is a tourist hot-spot that
has water.
River? Sea?
[What is the next mission that awaits
the members that came from the Ice Age?]
I will tell you first.
You do know that currently there has
been unusual weather changes?
[Stop with the 'unusual weather']
So there have been some people that have
become weird along with the weather changes.
And so, those people...
You must find it ridiculous too.
There is a vaccine hidden in the
vicinity in order to prevent these changes.
Do we have to find it?
- Yes. It is in this building.
- I got it.
We don't have any hints to
find it, right?
Do we just look for it?
Seung Gi, I have a favor
to ask of you.
Can you stop acting like you know
something when you actually don't?
Can you not do stuff like this?
I understand.
I'll ask you very calmly.
Jae Suk! Here...
Where is the bathroom?
He keeps on talking as if he
knows something.
We're trying to prevent mutations
from occurring, right?
You're looking for the vaccine.
The team of the person that finds
the vaccine wins.
One person out of the three of us
needs to find it.
You know that I'm bad at finding
things like this, right?
You two need to find it.
It will be advantageous for us to
find the vaccine first.
That way we can go first.
Let's go!
Do I just find it in places like this?
Yes. Look for it.
[The mysterious R- vaccine is
hidden in this place.]
[And there are hidden dangers lying ahead.]
There is nowhere here in which they
can deeply hide things.
Kwang Soo, they couldn't have
hid it there.
Why?
Jae Suk!
Already?
Awesome!
[Kwang Soo found a mysterious R box.]
Kwang Soo, hide it.
Let's see what it is.
They are doing something else.
[But...]
[It's empty.]
There is nothing in there.
What is this?
It's empty.
Don't scream thoughtlessly.
Scream only if you found
something for real.
Let's promise each other.
Let's not scream thoughtlessly.
Seung Gi, but...
I'm good at finding things today.
What is this?
Why is there a jail?
[They need to find the vaccine,
but there is a jail?]
Really?
Why is there a jail when we were
just told to look for a vaccine?
What is this?
We need to find it quickly.
[At this moment]
Kim Jong Kook Out!
What?
Why is Kim Jong Kook out?
[Out of nowhere, they hear that
Mr. Capable is out.]
What is this? Hurry up!
What is this?
[They just started but Mr. Capable is out!]
Are we supposed to rip off
each other's name tags?
[Confusion]
Why is he out?
Kim Jong Kook is out?
What is going on?
[One minute ago]
[Kkuk and Blank Ji were calmly looking
for the R-vaccine...]
Let's try going in there.
[But]
What is this?
[A black being suddenly appeared.]
This person is...
[Monster]
[Because of the unusual weather?]
[This human became mutated.]
[A life form full of anger.]
[His name is 'Monster'.]
[Symptoms of the Mutation:
Attacks all life forms other than itself]
Why?
[Lifts him up]
[Mr. Capable levitates in the air.]
[Super strength Monster suppresses
Mr. Capable at once.]
He's fighter, Kim Ji Hoon.
[It's a rare sight.
Mr. Capable is on the floor.]
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you taking off my shoes?
What are you doing?
[Taking off the name tag has no
effect on the monster.]
Why are you doing this?
Why?
What are you doing?
[Monster completely captures Mr. Capable.]
You have to tell me...
[Stamp]
[He stamps his foot?]
What?
What is this?
I'm out?
[Kim Jong Kook out!]
[The greatest super strength Monster
has appeared!]
Kim Jong Kook out!
What?
[He even drools because he's so shocked.]
What is going on?
What is this?
Did he just say that Kim Jong Kook is out?
What is going on?
Why is Jong Kook out?
[How can Mr. Capable be out?]
It must not be related to
strength then...
I know.
It must have something to do
with using your head.
[Seung Gi...]
[You're very keen...]
I think there is something else today.
[I will greet you one by one.]
Wait!
Why do I feel so good?
Why do I feel so good about
Kim Jong Kook being out?
[He calms down and quickly looks for the vaccine.]
This...
[Ha Ha finds a R box.]
There's nothing in here.
If it's not in here then it's not this?
[There is only one box that has
the real R-vaccine.]
[He pushes back his fear and opens
every door that he can.]
[Monster's second attack]
Why are you doing this?
[He lifts him up again]
[and throws him down.]
What?
[Giraffe rushes to the scene as soon
as hears the scream.]
Why are you doing this to me?
[He runs after witnessing the
tragic hunting scene.]
What do I do?
[Monster has no mercy.]
What are you doing?
[If you get a stamp from the Monster
on your foot, you're out!]
Ha Ha out!
We're in big trouble.
Who is that?
Who is that person?
[Fear increases by 10,000 times.]
What?
What is this?
[The clueless members keep on
repeating 'what is this?']
Someone is here.
- Someone is here.
- Who's here?
- Someone's here.
- Where?
Someone who's in a black suit.
He also has a name tag.
What are you talking about?
[Blank Ji saw Mr. Capable get taken
out with her own eyes.]
You scared me!
[M...Monster?]
[Ji Hyo, it's me.]
What's wrong with you?
- Lee Seung Gi, you scared me!
- What?
Go away!
Don't come!
Why are you running away?
What's wrong?
I don't know what's going on either.
Someone's here.
He's here.
You scared me.
[After seeing Monster you get
scared of everything you see.]
Chae Won.
There is someone here.
Why were they taken out?
What happened to Jong Kook?
- Right now...
- There is a mutant here.
There is someone with the virus.
Let's go to the first floor.
Aren't there anymore floors up there?
There aren't any.
There are only two floors?
There are three floors.
[Courageous Gary takes the lead.]
[But...]
[that was his last.]
[The Monster is everywhere.]
Why are you doing this?
[Frightened]
What is that?
Then I'm the only one left.
I saw it.
In front of me!
Wait!
That hurts!
[Monster's signature move: Thunder
take down then take off the shoes.]
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
Wait!
[Once you're caught, it's over!]
Gary out!
[Absurd]
What is this 'Monster?'
[Should I speed up the process now?]
[At the battlefield after the tsunami. ]
- What's going on?
- Did you see his face?
I couldn't see his face.
He has a mask on.
- He has on a mask.
- He was this big.
He has a mask on and he looks as
if he weighs over 100 kg.
He lifted up Ha Ha and
stuck him into the ground.
Really?
What happened to Jong Kook?
If he took out Jong Kook then...
He is a mixed martial arts fighter.
He really is.
He threw Jong Kook on the floor.
- What did it say on his back?
- Monster.
- Monster?
Ripping off his name tag has
no effect on him.
Really?
We need to find the R-vaccine if we
want to capture him.
But that person...
He is a mutant.
I need to take off my jacket.
He's taking off his jacket.
I need to use my strength today.
There is no other way.
Kwang Soo...
- You, really?
- Let's find the vaccine.
I should take off my jacket too.
I can't take this anymore.
All the members on my team are out.
What do I do? I'm alone.
I need to find the vaccine.
Where is it?
Mommy!
[Because of the tension,
the VJ freaked her out.]
[Shock]
Is she on the first floor?
Let's look for it on the
second floor then.
We're going to look for it
on the second floor.
Let's look for it.
It's Chae Won or Ji Hyo.
If we get caught, it's over.
[Let me live first]
[The owner of the scream is...]
[She thought the VJ was the Monster again.]
[This is the first time Chae Won
has felt this kind of fear.]
I keep thinking that the
camera guy is the mutant.
There is a real one and a fake one.
[One's heart leaps into one's mouth]
[Hurriedly runs]
[This time]
[he's real.]
[Let me get rid of all of you]
[Shock]
[A mess]
[Hair stands up]
[Monster brings with him the thrill
of a disaster movie.]
[The place he ran to in
order to live is...]
[where Blank Ji was hiding.]
[Their souls have gone out]
Don't come here!
Did you see Suk Jin?
I lived.
I turned really nicely, right?
[Where are they?]
Let's take Monster out.
How are you going to take him out?
Should we punch him in the stomach?
Do you think you'll be able to do it?
You can...
you can...
get out!
You try going out.
The moment you punch his stomach, you'll
probably be laying down somewhere else.
Be careful.
[At this moment! A scream is heard
all throughout the building.]
Don't go out!
It's best not to join this kind of fight.
Come inside.
[Big-Nosed Brother was celebrating
how he escaped.]
[What's up?]
[Few moments later he meets
Monster at a dead end.]
How can we meet here?
[He runs with his thin two legs but...]
[it's too late.]
How can we meet right there?
I'm so unlucky.
[Ji Suk Jin out!]
Ji Suk Jin, out!
What are you doing?
What is that?
You're out if you get stamped
on your feet.
So?
I'm not leaving any space for
him to put a stamp.
Why are you erasing it?
Why?
What do you think you're doing?
[It's useless because spit can
even erase it.]
There's not that many of us left now.
How many of us are left?
Chae Won.
Ji Hyo.
Jae Suk, Me, and Seung Gi.
There's only five people left.
Chae Won!
Where have you been?
[Drop]
Why?
I'm so tired.
[Chae Won's legs are shaking from running
away and getting scared by her VJ.]
What's going on?
We have to find the R-vaccine first.
Am I thinking too hard about this?
Let's think of this in a simpler way.
Someone...
We just need to find it first.
You don't need to use your
head for this game.
- Who uses their brain in Running Man?
- It's not?
You just need to look for it.
[That's right!]
[They need to find the vaccine first.]
[That way they will find out how
to take out the Monster.]
[What's wrong with him?]
You scared me!
It's on the third floor.
[He scouted the Monster is through the
window in order to safely search for the vaccine.]
What is the vaccine?
What does the vaccine look like?
I don't know.
[The identity of the vaccine is a mystery.]
[Sudden U-turn]
[How are you?]
[I'm not fine]
[The Monster has come]
[While the Yoo-Lee Brothers are being chased]
[Seung Gi and Blank Ji run away.]
Third floor.
[Chae Won also heard the noise.]
[Flustered]
[She quickly hides in the corner]
I lived..!
[On the other hand]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo vs. Monster]
[Eventually captured in the
corner of the staircase.]
[Traitor Giraffe tries to grab Jae Suk
who's trying to get away.]
[Jae Suk escapes]
No!
Don't!
[It's not the foot he colored.]
[Lee Kwang Soo out!]
Who are you?
[Monster seems to be out of breath.]
What is this?
He must really be into character.
[I'm also a little tired.]
[Collapsed]
Lee Kwang Soo...
Lee Kwang Soo held onto me.
Lee Kwang Soo first...
This intense tension...
[Seung Gi has seen Monster
for the first time.]
[He hurriedly looks for the vaccine.]
Where is it?
[Blank Ji is also alert.]
It's crazy out there right now.
I have to find it quickly.
[Peek]
[Found Blank Ji.]
[He blocks the exit.]
Can you let me off just once?
Just once.
Can you let me go one last time?
When I get caught next time then...
[I'm too tired now.]
You could've let me off one last time.
[Girls get stamped on their hand.]
Song Ji Hyo, out!
We need to find the vaccine first.
Where is it?
[The person that finds the vaccine
and takes out Monster wins!]
[Therefore, the last person to remain
and look for the vaccine is important!]
[Please]
[Seung Gi looks everywhere without rest.]
[He finally found the R box.]
[There is something inside.]
[He finally found...]
[the vaccine bracelet.]
[Deeply moved]
[Thrilled]
Where is he?
[He just needs to put the bracelet
on the Monster!]
Jae Suk!
Where is it?
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Since he doesn't know when the Monster
will appear, he is very uneasy!]
Why is he so fast?
Jae Suk!
Come here!
Where are you going?
What about me?
[However, he runs away from
all loud noises.]
Jae Suk!
This is 'Catch Yoo Jae Suk' right now!
Did you find it?
Seung Gi, did you find it?
I found it.
- Who found it?
- Me.
Where did you find it?
It's over once we put the
bracelet on him?
- Can you lure him in?
- I also have chocolate to lure him in.
- What is that?
- Chocolate.
Did you get this from someone?
- No.
- Is it yours?
Why are you taking that?
No!
I'll put it on him, so can you lure him?
Can you please lure him in?
Hey!
Give it to me.
Hey! Give it to me.
[Chae Won's weapon: Irresistible Smile]
What are you going to do with this?
Give it to me.
Give me a chocolate then.
[She first takes the bracelet.]
[Then puts the chocolate in his mouth.]
You need to walk around with me
from now on.
Jae Suk.
Why? I'm not on your team.
I'm not on your team.
Let's stick together.
I was the one who found it.
I gave you the chocolate.
Spit it out then!
I'll buy one for you.
Then you can put it on but
after you put it on,
share the hint with me.
Let me know what the hint is.
I put this on that person.
Then I'm in first place.
Then I get the hint.
But you want me to give my hint to you?
There is now your hint and my hint.
Give me the bracelet then! Forget it!
Give me the bracelet!
Spit out the chocolate!
I'll give you the chocolate later.
Share the hint.
Promise me that.
It doesn't matter who puts it on.
That's not how it works. I gave you
the chocolate so this is mine.
Call the mart and ask them to
deliver it to here.
I'll give it to you as soon as
we get out of here.
As soon as we leave this place.
Jae Suk, come here.
He's funny.
Why?
I found the vaccine.
- So?
- I found it.
- He's really funny.
- What is this?
This is the vaccine.
- He found it but...
- Then you have to put it on him.
I asked him to give this to me
and gave him a chocolate.
But he keeps asking for a hint.
What are you talking about?
What are are you two talking
about right now?
Seung Gi found this.
- I found this.
- Seung Gi found this.
I had a chocolate and
Seung Gi found this.
He was going to put this on him.
Then he's first place.
You guys are on the same team.
- Yes.
- What is she talking about?
What are you talking about right now?
If Seung Gi found it,
then he has to put it on.
No.
I gave him chocolate.
Did you eat the chocolate?
Wait here for a moment.
I'll go throw it back up.
Just wait here for a moment.
Why did you eat the chocolate?
Chae Won, if Seung Gi found it then
he's supposed to put it on him.
Then he has to give me back
the chocolate.
What did it look like?
I'll find it. Wait right here.
We don't need to find the vaccine right
now. Let's find the chocolate first.
Why did you give it to her?
There are two people on our team.
Then put it on him by yourself.
- You put it on him yourself.
- I'm not going to help you at all.
I'm going to just go and die.
No. Help me.
Should I help you or not?
You’re good at this, Seung Gi.
I didn't even think of that.
- I'm good at pushing and pulling.
- Yes you are.
I'll put it on him. The person that
puts it on him is first place.
You're first place so you just need
to share the hint with me.
Understand? Promise.
You have to put it on his wrist. You
can't slap him with it or something, okay?
You can't put this on us, okay?
You can't do that.
You have to put it on him.
Jae Suk, let's be the bait.
Hide this.
[Let's go catch the monster]
[Welcome]
[Surprised]
He's over there.
- Is it him?
- It is him.
Can you give me some water?
[Now]
[we face him]
No.
What should we do?
[Danger]
It's not that.
Wait.
We need to save the human race.
Can I get some water?
Can you give her some water?
[She was going to put it on his wrist
when he handed her the water.]
He must be weak when it
comes to women.
Be careful.
- Wait.
- Catch him!
We can catch him?
Is it okay for us to chase him?
- Wait.
- Hurry!
- Catch him!
- Can we catch him?
[Is the bracelet going to be first
or the stamp?]
He needs to stamp us.
If he stamps us we're out.
Wait. We need to move to
a larger space.
Why aren't you catching him?
[At this moment...]
[He focuses on Yoo Hyuk]
Wait!
Put it on him!
He dropped it.
[Thankfully, Monster dropped the stamp.]
What is this?
We would've been in big trouble.
It's the feet.
He's really giving it his best!
- It's not that!
- He smiled.
He smiled.
He needs to give it his best.
He should just do enough
and go home.
Chae Won, give that to me.
The contract still holds, right?
Of course!
Chae Won, you can't put it
on him yourself.
Chae Won give it to me.
We'll keep our promise.
- We'll show you the hint.
- Promise?
- Of course.
- You promised.
Everyone saw this, right?
[At this moment]
[Monster attacks Seung Gi!]
[Monster is aiming for Seung Gi's feet.]
[Chae Won is defending with her whole body.]
Hold on a little longer!
It doesn't go on his arm.
Not the arm then.
[Chae Won throws her whole body.]
[His wrist is open.]
[Jae Suk!]
[Hurry..!]
[Click]
We put it on him!
[Putting the bracelet on
Monster's wrist is a success!]
We put it on him!
Nice work today.
Aren't you a mixed martial arts fighter?
How did you come all the way here?
[Road FC Kim Ji Hoon]
Please give him a round of applause.
You did a really nice job!
By himself he...
[Thank you for your appearance.]
Then now all that's left is the
Blue team's hint.
Chae Won made a deal
with us before.
We will tell you the hint
that we received.
It is the place
that Running Man likes the best.
- The place that Running Man likes the most.
- That's the hint?
- I think I know where it is.
- That is the key point.
We just have to put all the
hints together now.
Okay.
I feel like this was a losing business.
It is a tourist hot-spot with water.
- Tourist hot-spot.
- Sokcho!
Sokcho!
There is a lot of water there. Creeks!
What do you think it is?
We just need one more hint.
- It is the place that RM likes the most...
- it shows itself twice a day.
- I don't know.
- I really don't know.
[Where is the place?]
[The earth is full of unusual weather.]
[There is only one safe place!]
What is this?
[In the studio]
[there is a step with the picture
of each topography.]
[What is the meaning behind the nine
topographical photos?]
Today's weather.
It is the final mission.
Currently there is a rainstorm
alert all over the world.
There is only one topographical area
in which the sun will rise.
It's too difficult.
Put your hints together
and figure out which one
topographical area
will have a sunrise out of the nine.
[It is a tourist hot-spot with a lot of water.]
[It is a place that Running Man likes that makes
oxygen in order to prevent global warming.]
[It's a place that Running Man likes
that shows itself twice a day.]
With our hint, it's this place.
Let's just go with this.
This is the only place we can go with.
Now each team can step on their
choice and wait for the results.
For the team that gets it right,
there will be bright sunlight.
For the team that doesn't get it right...
Clouds, there are a lot of clouds.
If they get it wrong, they
will be rained on.
Take off the microphone.
We should take off our jackets.
In case we get rained on, we should.
[Everyone removes their
microphone and jacket.]
[Yoo Hyuk surpasses Park Seri's
bare foot fighting spirit.]
[Which region out of these is the safe region?]
Move at the count of three, please.
One!
Two!
Three!
[Choose]
[Each team makes their decision]
What is this?
[All three teams head to the same spot.]
Everyone chooses this place?
[All three teams choose the mud flat!]
Everyone thought of the same place?
[It makes oxygen in order to
prevent global warming.]
[It is the place that Running Man likes most.]
I think I know what it is.
Running Man loves mud flats the most.
Did you guys go the the mud flats a lot?
We went there a lot.
We're 230% sure that it is
the mud flats.
[Brown team's guess: Mud Flat]
[It show itself twice a day and
is full of sunshine.]
[It is the place that Running Man
likes the most.]
What are they talking about?
- I know.
- What is it?
This is the mud flats of the west coast.
I am 100% sure of this.
Twice a day.
The tide comes in and out.
And doesn't Running Man like
the sea the most?
The mud flat shows itself
twice a day.
[Seung Gi put the two hints together.]
[Blue team's guess: mud flat]
[It is a tourist hot-spot with a lot of water.]
This place has water and nice weather.
[After looking over the topographical
regions at the studio...]
[they put it together with their hints.]
We have decided.
[Yellow team's guess: mud flat]
[All three teams headed for the mud flat.]
[Will]
[their choice]
[be the right choice?]
Are you sure it's this?
Our hint tells us it's this region.
The one at the back is an island
and a volcano.
Let us check to see if it is
one of those regions.
We can tell by listening to the sound.
[Rainstorm]
[It comes out like this.]
You said that it was rain.
What is this?
[It sounded like Niagara Falls.]
[Check river, creek, ocean and mountain
in the middle row.]
[There was no safe place in
the middle row either!]
[The fear is creeping up.]
There is only one safe place
in the front row.
It will either be jungle, desert, or mud flat.
If your answer is wrong then
it will rain.
If it is right then
there will be a congratulatory salute.
Jungle, desert, mud flat!
One!
[All three teams are on the same boat]
Two!
[Everyone's right or everyone's wrong.]
Three!
[The place Running Man likes the most]
[Where there is water]
[A place that prevents global warming]
[A place that shows itself twice a day]
[The one place that the
hints point to..?]
[Mud Flat]
[Instead of rain there is warm sunlight!]
Isn't this the first time in
Running Man history?
[Pause]
[Dramatic fuss]
Is this rain?
This is not rain.
This is the first time that everyone
has gotten the right answer.
We're in big trouble.
We're too good at this now.
[The new year is off to a good start.]
[Everyone's a winner of the first mission.]
[There's no way 2015 is going to
be an easy year!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
I don't like this program!
Lee Seo Jin!
I told you not to do things like this!
I don't want to!
Give me a piggy back ride!
Stop it!
Lee Seo Jin is getting me angry!
Seo Jin!
You're really into Running Man, aren't you?
I'm going to do this for real now.
[Seung Gi and Chae Won couple's
remarkable activities.]
- Did you get it taken away from you?
- Stop it!
Seo Jin, what are you doing?
Seung Gi, how can you do this to me?
You really like Running man, don't you?
You're cute!
[Running Man with Prickly Seo Jin]