[The five hottest men in Korea]
[have arrived.]
[A charm battle for survival!]
[A fiery race between the hottest men]
[begins now!]
[A chilly day in April]
[6 AM]
[Yoo Hyuk arrives neatly dressed.]
Hello!
Good morning!
[Huh? There's nothing...]
Hello!
Get in the car.
Right away?
Do I just get in?
[Getting on board without explanation.]
- Gary!
- What are we doing today?
[The rest of the members join!]
- Hi, Gary!
- Gary, why are you there by yourself?
They just told me to get in.
[Why kind of race
will they have today?]
- Everyone's here?
- Yes!
I will explain the rules
of the race today.
Today's race will be
with the hottest male icons.
[The hottest icon race.]
- Are there any hottest female icons?
Five top stars who qualify
as the hottest icons
are waiting nearby.
The way you make the teams are...
The guests will be waiting
on the street.
You need to discuss whether or not
you want that guest in your car.
- There's nowhere to sit!
- Maybe we get off!
One member has to get off.
If you don't want the guest,
continue driving.
Kim Jong Kook, get out!
What are you saying?
We just started!
We will collect the people
who have been thrown away.
What do you mean collect?
[The strong candidates
raise their voices.]
- That's too much!
- Can we physically kick them out?
It's over if you're out!
If we don't like any of the guests,
we can just leave.
Yeah, we can do that.
People who are kicked out are one team.
Keep seven people in this car.
Depart now.
If you kick me out, I'm going to
sharpen my sword for revenge.
This isn't the first time.
You always sharpen your sword.
[Let's go meet the hottest icons!]
[The five hottest men of 2015.]
[They're coming!]
I think some of them are handsome
and some are funny.
Loosen your belt a little.
Oh wait, do it when we stop.
Why should I?
You don't think you need to take if off?
Jae Suk!
Make quick decisions.
If you don't want the guest,
just go.
That's a given.
- Someone's here!
- Who is it?
- He's covering his face.
- His head is really big.
Who are you?
[His hands are full of shopping bags.]
- He's really cute.
- How can he be that cute?
[A very cute hot icon.]
- He's so cute!
- How can he be that cute?
[He is the definition of cynical.]
[I wonder who he is.]
Who are you?
- Please show us your face, Mr. Guest.
- Your face!
He's tall.
Show us your face!
- Who is it?
- He bought gifts.
[Reveal!]
[Who is hot guy No. 1?]
It's Kyun Sung!
- Hello!
[Kang Kyun Sung of Noel.]
[He became a hot icon for variety shows
13 years after his debut!]
[Everyone wants Kyun Sung
on their show.]
- It's Kyun Sung.
- Hello!
Kyun Sung,
what are you doing up so early?
Please let me in your car.
What's that?
Let's see it first.
You look really similar to that doll.
Please let me in your car and run!
[He acts randomly
with his straight face.]
With that face?
Wow, you can do that this early.
Kyun Sung is really hot these days.
Yes, please let me in.
The other team needs a leader, too.
Jong Kook, get out.
[Yoo Hyuk's only target is Kkuk.]
They need a team leader.
Doesn't it make sense?
How about this?
Let the guest pick who they want.
- That's good.
- That's okay, right?
Kyun Sung, someone has to get out.
Pick one person.
Kyung Sung, have a look.
Do I even need to look?
[Big Nose, get out!]
- Get out.
[Why is the bad feeling never wrong...]
Why did I suggest this idea?
[Collection No. 1, Big Nose.]
- Wait and see.
- I'm sorry.
- Hurry and get out.
- His face got red.
Well, this was his idea.
- Kyun Sung, put your belt on.
- Kyun Sung, you...
[Bye, Big-nosed brother!]
- Your ride is coming soon!
- Hello.
- It's Kyun Sung!
[Heading towards hot guy No. 2.]
- Kyun Sung, how long did you wait?
- Not that long.
- Really?
- He was the first one.
Have a good life!
- You must be really busy nowadays.
- Kyun Sung is really busy.
- I'm not that busy.
- You're on TV every time I turn it on.
You're always on TV.
Your face is always emotionless.
Isn't there a second one over there?
[Hot guy No. 2 is reading a magazine
early in the morning.]
- But who is that?
- He's reading.
[He's holding a magazine...]
- He's wearing white pants.
- I think he's nearsighted.
- Who is it?
[He's unusual...]
- Please show us your face, Mr. Guest.
- He's reading in English!
- Show us your face.
[What is he doing?]
Show us your face.
- Show us your face.
[This intelligent hot guy No. 2 is...]
[The initiator of robot-acting,
Jang Soo Won.]
Why do you drive like...
Are you hurt?
Are. You. Okay?
Were. You. Surprised?
I. Am. Sorry.
Do. Not. Make. Me. A fool!
[He's entering his renaissance
with his robot-like acting.]
[His presence is big
within the hottest men.]
- Are. You. Okay?
- Were. You. Surprised?
I. am. okay.
Jae Suk, let. me. in.
It. is. so. cold.
Soo Won, I can't just let you in.
Show me 'The way this guy lives'.
- At this time?
[At 6 AM... in the streets?]
[I need to get in the car...]
[Voice accompaniment.]
['The way this guy lives' at 6 AM,
let's play!]
[I am going to get in that car!]
[The climax.]
I live for the look,
I die for the look
[He's about to break through
the exosphere.]
[On the way that robot-Soo Won
comes and goes.]
[I only have passion,
I'll only live and die for the look.]
- Wow, it's really been a long time.
- Was my dance okay?
There's no space.
Let's do this.
One person at a time...
do a vote, and whisper it in my ear.
Alright?
He got off.
Jae Suk is out!
I knew this would happen.
[He's thrown away as soon as
he empties his seat.]
Soo Won, pick one person.
Have a look inside the car.
- You're going to get off yourself?
- No, no.
Who?
[Kwang Soo.]
[Collection No. 2, Kwang Soo.]
Why me?
[Hot guy No. 2, Soo Won.]
Why are you doing this to me?
Soo Won, put your belt on.
- Are you really leaving?
- Of course.
Bye!
This is really scary.
[Annoyed.]
It's upsetting.
[Anger meter rising.]
Thinking about it now,
they don't have a team leader.
[Everyone's enemy Mr. Capable.]
- That's what I'm saying.
- They need a team leader.
- There can't be two kings.
There's another one over there.
[Hot guy No. 3.]
It's so cold.
[Hot guy No. 3, with the big eyes...]
[is feeling very cold.]
I'll see who this person is...
We can't take all the guests in.
Who is that?
[A rendezvous with hot guy No. 3.]
- He looks like an idol?
- He's fashionable.
Show us your face.
[Reveal.]
[Today's visual ace.]
- Who is that?
- Ho Jun.
[Son Ho Jun, the hot icon
from 'Answer Me 1994'.]
[He holds the stage of dramas
and variety shows!]
[Little tribal chief, Son Ho Jun.]
Hello.
It's so cold.
Ho Jun!
What do we do with him?
He's too popular.
[He brings the sandwiches
for extra points.]
If we take all the popular people
that team only has weak people.
[We can't just take all the aces.]
You stay here.
[No hesitation.]
[Collection No. 3, Son Ho Jun.]
Poor Ho Jun.
We need some hot guys
on that team too.
[The car leaves...]
[They didn't take him
because he was too hot.]
I need to be more active...
[The weather's cold too...]
- It's Ho Jun!
- Oh, it's Ho Jun.
- Hello.
- They left you?
They took all the guests up 'til now.
- Have you eaten?
- Sandwiches!
- We don't want to just take anyone.
[Active Ho Jun.]
- He's giving us sandwiches.
- My wife is your fan.
Wow, sandwiches.
Why did they leave you?
- I wasn't active enough?
- Really?
He even has tears in his eyes.
I'll try my best, please let me in.
It's so cold.
- Ho Jun is an ace.
- Get in.
- Why didn't they take Ho Jun?
- Why didn't they take you?
What are they doing?
- Ho Jun.
- Yes?
I think you're really handsome.
The sandwiches are frozen as ice.
The coffee's cold.
Ho Jun, we can't just take
anyone from now on.
- I'm so angry.
- Let's take revenge.
Turn the light on so
Ho Jun's face can be seen.
[He's like a manager?]
[Pet-friendly guy with Brownie.]
Only two left.
[There are two hot guys left.]
Who is that?
He's in good shape.
Show us your face, please!
[Who is hot guy No. 4?]
Who are you?
[Dangerously attractive guy,
Hong Jong Hyun.]
[He started as a model]
[now he's in dramas, movies,
and even an MC.]
[His first movie will be released soon.]
My dear puppy, did you embezzle
the money well?
[Look at his smile.]
- Isn't it Jong Hyun?
His face doesn't even swell
even though it's early.
Can I get in?
I'll ride in the trunk.
[Jong Hyun...
pick Jong Kook...]
Not me.
I drive really well.
[He unexpectedly picks Yoo Hyuk.]
- I have class 1, regular license.
- Just open the door.
[His target is the driver, Yoo Hyuk.]
What are you doing, Jong Hyun?
Stop him.
[Jang Robot loosens his belt.]
- I can drive really well.
- What are you guys doing...
- Get out!
- You don't know anything!
[Bye bye, sneaky Yoo Hyuk.]
- Push him, push.
[Collection No. 4, Jae Suk.]
Please take care of my dog.
You think you will stay
in there forever?
Hey! You think you'll be
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk!
[Perfect timing,
the collection car arrives.]
Ho Jun!
Ho Jun, I'm sorry.
We don't just take anyone.
I'm sorry for before.
Ho Jun, I...
let's talk inside.
- What do you mean inside?
- Suk Jin, I'll drive.
What do you mean drive?
Look at this guy!
- I'll drive.
- No, this isn't working.
- Okay, okay.
[They bickered for a while...]
[We only have hot guy No. 5 left.]
- Hello.
This person is the last one, right?
Yes, there he is.
Is he homeless?
[He's scratching underneath the papers.]
[The blonde bench-guy.]
[Who are you?]
Is he a foreigner?
Foreigner?
No, his hands look Korean.
- Show us your face!
- He's pretty short.
[Something special about hot guy No. 5?]
[Extremely appealing guy,
Yoo Byung Jae.]
Byung Jae!
[A variety show screenwriter
who can act and do gags.]
- He's good.
- Why are your eyes so shaky?
I'll confess.
Your girlfriend is ugly.
[The blue-chip icon,
Yoo Byung Jae.]
I like this guy!
Hello!
Byung Jae!
Make some faces!
He's the expert of making faces.
[Dissatisfaction]
[Sad]
- He's really good.
He's a master of comic skits.
[Thousand faces, Yoo Byung Jae.]
- What do we do?
- You choose one person.
Decide who you want to pick.
I choose Kang Kyun Sung.
[Kang Kyun Sung]
I kicked out Suk Jin before,
and I have to see him again?
[Collection No. 5, Kyun Sung.]
[The survivors are relaxed.]
- You got picked?
- Byung Jae!
Lock the door.
Lock it!
Ho Jun, hurry and close the door!
- Close it.
- Help me out.
Why are you letting him in?
- How did a guest get kicked out?
- Kim Kook Jong should have been out.
Are we the leftovers?
- What do you mean leftover?
[Getting worked up.]
Ho Jun, this is the ace team.
This is a gathering for people
who get jealous.
[Self-comfort for being thrown away.]
Welcome, Byung Jae!
You can leave the mask outside.
[From 'K' Exhibition center
to 'H' Village.]
[This village has special places?]
Where is it?
This is the entrance of the village.
It's so beautiful.
Come here, Byung Jae.
Where are you going, Byung Jae?
Why do you look so timid, Byung Jae?
We'll have two teams with
six members each.
The team with seven members
need to send one member over.
- Is that so?
- We have to match the numbers.
See? One person has to come.
Our character-theme is complete
if Byung Jae comes here.
It's only complete with Byung Jae here.
I can't send him.
Give us the youngest member.
What are you doing?
Wait.
Byung Jae wants to come!
I'm pouring so much affection!
Byung Jae, come here.
Why won't you let him come?
[He's scary.]
Byung Jae's lips are dry!
Look at your members!
He's sensitive to cold.
You need to hold him tight.
I'll give you my jacket.
You'll regret it.
- It's cold.
[Kwang Soo gives his jacket.]
You look like Chow Yun-Fat
from 'A Better Tomorrow.'
It's the long coat from
'A Better Tomorrow'!
[Hot guys team vs. Cool guys team.]
You've made a big decision.
We have other good members, too.
Now you're smiling, Byung Jae!
[A bright smile he didn't have before.]
Leaving this team doesn't mean
we're not seeing each other.
[I feel more comfortable here.]
I asked you a question before.
Where is the hot place in your life?
There were various answers.
We set up in this village
with the answers you've given us.
For today's Hottest Icon Race
you will be traveling around the
hot places and doing missions there.
The only thing different will be
the all-kill name tag mission.
- What this is...
Byung Jae, you should leave.
You should have told us before!
[Some are happy, some are sad.]
What are you talking about?
Jong Kook!
Give us Jong Hyun or Gary.
- You don't like name tag elimination?
- No, I don't.
Choose one.
Name tag elimination or a fist fight?
What do you mean fist fight?
Just bring the leader.
- This guy!
- I'll face you.
- I want to go to that team.
- What?
He spilled his true feelings.
- What are you saying, Ho Jun?
[You never know.]
Here are the rules for the all-kill
name tag elimination.
You can only eliminate name tags
of the other team
in between games.
- How?
- In between games?
If you take all the name tags off,
you will win.
The team who wins a mission
will get a 10 second head start.
That's too much time.
We have 10 seconds to run away.
We need to win all the missions.
One team doesn't run away
while the other chases.
You face each other.
No, we will chase them
and they will run.
You will receive a 10 second head
start and a golden coin.
It's an advantage to win the mission.
We have to win.
The first place...
is Anyang billiard hall.
[The first mission: Anyang billiard hall]
[What mission is waiting
for them at the hall?]
[Anyang billiard hall]
[The hottest place mission, start.]
[Anyang billiard hall.]
This must be Kim Jong Kook's
hot place.
It's Anyang.
Jong Kook lives in Anyang.
- It's Anyang!
- Anyang billiard hall!
[The materials are laid out.]
[Both teams enter with confidence.]
What is this?
It's a real billiard hall.
Why are the balls so big?
[Extreme size.]
It's like a bowling ball.
They are bowling balls.
We didn't play eight balls
back in my day.
It was introduced in the 90's.
People who studied abroad
started playing it.
- In the early 90's...
- In Apgujung-dong...
the orange tribe played it.
If you're under the 300 level,
do not perform Masse shots.
Call it a curved shot.
It doesn't feel like it
if I say curved shot.
Please, tell us the story
behind this place.
This is the place I picked.
Jong Kook is living in Anyang now,
but I used to live near Anyang.
At this Anyang billiard hall...
- I was in elementary...
- Did you get beat up?
I got my lunch money stolen.
At the Anyang billiard hall.
Why did you go to there when
you were in elementary school?
I was curious back then.
They didn't let elementary students in.
- You could go in.
- You could enter.
It was very popular back then.
You lived in good times.
We got in trouble for playing billiards.
I never got my money stolen.
But my jacket and shoes were
robbed many times.
There are a lot of victims here.
I've been robbed many times, too.
Byung Jae, have you ever
been robbed?
A half-eaten piece of a bun.
Did you prepare that comment?
Do you prepare comments
for every situation?
How did you say that right away?
The Pokemon bun used to
be popular.
They took it because
I didn't have money.
That's disgusting!
Well, this isn't related to eight ball.
- But let's reveal each others' level.
- I'm level 150.
Don't lie.
Gary's 250.
- How about you, Suk Jin?
- I'm around 80.
His level used to be 120 when
he played with me 10 years ago.
It decreased.
- What's your average score?
- About 150.
How about Byung Jae?
I'm level 30.
I've never played billiards.
He's no help.
You look like you would've spent
all your time playing billiards!
Have you been living under a rock?
- What's your score?
- I'm 30.
- You've never played?
- Really.
You've never played?
When my friends went to
play billiards, I went on dates.
[Surprised.]
Why do I feel like I lost at games?
Mister, please wipe the table for us.
[Automatically becomes a worker.]
You have to wipe the rail.
[Winner gets 10 golden coins
and a head start.]
Those were good times.
I play, even now.
If we win and get a head start...
We need to win no matter what,
and run away quickly.
- Is it better?
- Yes. That's better.
Our name tags will be ripped off
if we attack them.
You can put it down and roll it.
[Get the balls inside the pocket
by throwing the cue ball.]
What's happening?
[After the first crash,
it hits no. 2.]
[Will it go in at once?]
What's happening?
The next one is right here, Ji Hyo.
Just push it.
Isn't this her first time?
Why is she so good?
Just push this one.
- She's probably done it before.
- Probably.
You can do it!
A little hard.
Like that!
[This time as well?]
[That was close.]
[Cool guys team - 4 and 6.
Hot guys team - 1, 3, and 5.]
How do you hit this?
Kyun Sung, it's your turn.
- Me?
- Your level is 40, right?
[40? Had he played billiards before?]
- Where did Kyun Sung go?
- Kyun Sung, you can push...
What are you doing, Kyun Sung?
- We need to run away later.
- What's wrong with my team members?
They're too tight!
[How will he play the name tag
elimination with those weak legs?]
- We'll need to run later.
- All they think about is running away.
Why did you tie them so tight?
- With the white ball...
- Oh, this one?
If you hit it wrong, the cue ball
might go in as well.
You need it to hit it toward
this side, about 90%.
Like this, right?
Like this?
- That's right.
- No, no.
[In the midst of all this chaos.]
[Finally, hits.]
[It went in.]
[Kyun Sung's surprising result, 1 in.]
It's right here!
- Ball no.3 is possible.
- Wait, Kyun Sung!
- Slightly to the right.
- Like this?
[Kyun Sung's confident second shot.]
- That's right.
[Hits the the rail, and fails.]
- It's our turn.
Let's hope for the cue ball goes in.
That's never going to happen.
- Don't do that.
- What are you doing?
It'll never go in, Gary.
- It won't, right?
- It might.
[Ball no. 6 goes in.]
- It goes in!
[Followed by the cue ball.]
- It went in!
[You said it would never happen.]
It's okay.
- We have to take it out, right?
- Yeah.
You're supposed to take it out
if the cue ball goes in.
That's different
between neighborhoods.
- They didn't take it out in Jamsil!
- This is my billiard hall!
Take it out, now.
[And it goes in the center.]
- Jong Hyun knows the rule.
Don't come on the pool table.
Jae Suk, put some chalk.
That's too much!
What do you mean, too much?
Next time, put some here.
We need to run away as soon
as we get a head start, okay?
If you make us unhappy,
I'll eliminate you first.
Failure, failure!
[It's in the right direction.]
[Failed by an inch.]
- Next!
- That was close!
- Is it short?
- It's short.
I thought you don't play billiards.
- This is too hard.
- Just look here and take a shot.
Make it spin.
Do you want to hit this one?
- This one?
[He changes the target.]
- No, it's too hard.
- Hard?
Just try it.
It might be easier.
[He tries to shoot a bank shot.]
I don't know how much
the ball will curve.
Don't make the angle too wide.
- Show us an artistic shot.
- We should try a variety of shots.
- It goes in!
[Hits the the rail first.]
[It's heading towards
the right direction.]
It goes in!
[It went in!]
[What's with this guy?]
[Ha Ha, succeeds with ball no. 4.]
Pay close attention!
If we lose, our name tags are gone!
[Swallow.]
I need to look at that spot.
Good!
[Rolls away perfectly...]
[and hits no. 6.]
It got caught!
[It hits the the rail, and fails.]
Good, good!
Go up, Ho Jun.
- Ho Jun!
- Our plan...
Good job.
- Here first.
- Think of it as pushing it to the rail.
Don't think about running away.
Don't tighten your laces.
Ho Jun, just take a light shot.
- You mean cutting it, right?
- Yeah, cut it!
Just slightly!
[The cue ball is heading
towards the pocket.]
- Good.
- That's good!
[No!]
[Go in, go in.]
It's going in. It's going to fall.
[The cue ball is hidden
between the rail.]
That's amazing.
Ho Jun, you're amazing.
This is hard.
Don't worry Jae Suk.
- It's really hard.
- We're ruined.
Just think of it as pressing
it against the rail.
- That's it?
- Don't tie your laces.
Why are you all tying your laces?
[Getting ready to flee.]
Soo Won, go this way.
[If they get this last one,
Cool Guys team wins.]
[All eyes on the ball.]
It goes in, it goes in!
[Failed.]
We're alive!
Untie your laces!
[Just like their shoe laces,
their hearts tighten and loosen.]
- We need a curved ball.
- It's Byung Jae's turn.
Don't try avoiding it!
Why did you tie them so tight?
You have zippers on the side!
[There was a zipper.]
These aren't my shoes.
He's never received
a sponsorship before.
He came with a close friend
because he doesn't have a manager.
But his friend was so funny.
'I'm going to be bored
when you're shooting.'
Because he'll be alone.
- He's not a manager.
- It's first time for him waiting.
He didn't even have breakfast.
He felt awkward eating with our staff.
He's very shy.
It's his first time seeing
other managers.
- Byung Jae, over there.
- Okay.
- Can you point it out for me?
- Point it out.
[He has no experience
and he's easily influenced]
- Yeah, the other way.
- No, this way.
- Counter clock wise!
- Tell me when you're decided.
Why are you so sensitive, Byung Jae?
You did it right the first time.
To the right.
[His very first shot in his life.]
Good!
[Hits the rail]
[and hits it perfectly.]
- Byung Jae!
[It went in!]
[Revival.]
[Everyone's surprised
with his miraculous first shot.]
Loosen your laces!
[Cool guys team - no. 6,
and Hot Guys team - no. 5.]
Byung Jae...
[He's giving out tips on the table.]
- You need to hit it like this.
- I have to hit the right side, right?
You became one with the table.
To the right, at an acute angle.
[If they get this in,
the Hot Guys team wins.]
Imagine the cue ball hits the rail.
- Do I hit it hard or lightly?
- Hard.
- Not too hard, though.
- But a little hard.
Think about it.
It can't be too hard nor too weak.
- Play it by ear.
- Do what you want.
You need to put it in a pocket.
That's what we want!
I thought you were swearing.
[Surprised.]
- Me, too.
It's because his name is Byung Jae.
- Byung Jae!
[Will this beginner's luck continue?]
[Please, get in!]
- Great!
- It's going in!
[Oh my god!]
- Byung Jae!
- Yoo Byung Jae!
[A player that's level 30 leads
them to a miraculous win!]
[Untie your shoe laces!]
[Hot guys team vs. Cool Guys team]
[1: 0]
[Kwang Soo will execute
the first break shot.]
- Pocket two balls.
- We can win this.
Let's finish this quick and run away.
I think you should hit in the middle.
They will split no. 4 and no. 6.
Break the center.
Good, good!
- Nice!
- Good Job, Kwang Soo!
It's going in.
Number four!
[Hot Guys team succeeds
at pocketing no. 4.]
- That's it, Kwang Soo!
- Try number two!
We need to run away!
Move aside!
Control your power.
You're my number one target.
I'll only chase you!
Move aside, please!
Roll it along the rail.
- Hit it hard.
- No, not too hard.
[Kwang Soo succeeds with
two balls at his reminiscing place.]
Finish it, Kwang Soo.
Hurry up!
Why are you hiding
the ball from our sight?
I think you tried to hide the cue ball.
[The eldest brother is honest,
but he's not helping.]
- You're very honest.
- Of course, I am.
[They'll win if he pockets the ball.]
[There's only one ball left.]
- I'll strike it now.
That looks good!
[Will it go in?]
[It stops.]
Please!
[But it stays at a very good spot.]
It's even better.
We just need to hit
one fifth degrees to the right.
He always says one fifth degrees.
What should I hit?
[Cool Guys team - no. 1, 3, 5.]
[Hot Guys team - no. 6.]
Really strong?
That's nice!
Ji Hyo, I told you to throw it hard.
[Failed]
- It worked for us!
[Hot Guys team is one step
away from winning.]
[He's the one to finish the game.]
- Kyun Sung!
Just hit it from here.
It's going to go in.
- If you succeed...
- You know how it is, right?
Hit the right side slightly.
- What if the cue ball goes in?
- Just hit the right side.
- Hit the right side slightly.
- Just do it however you like.
[What just happened?]
[Failed]
[We're ruined!]
[His face explains it all.]
[I'm sorry.]
- How can you fail at it?
[Cool guys team, Gary's attack.]
- Number one!
- This one makes it scatter.
- I'll strike it now.
Good, good!
That's a clean shot!
[Gary's clean strike.]
[He succeeds at no. 5 on the bounce.]
[The Gamble Master,
Gary makes the match tied.]
Do you know what you did to us?
Tie your shoe laces.
[The atmosphere turned around.]
- Tie your shoe laces!
[Both the teams have
only one ball left.]
- That's a little too weak.
- It'll stop here.
- It stopped!
- It's over.
Suk Jin, finish it.
If we can't finish it,
we'll be finished!
This is the only chance!
- Who's next?
- It's Ha Ha.
[Will Ha Ha finish this game?]
[Is he performing a fireball?]
[What a narrow escape!]
[Jong Hyun plays this time.]
- Try hit this part.
Okay!
[Completely ruined.]
- You try, Byung Jae.
[They put the hero of the first round.]
Byung Jae, you're the best player.
This isn't that easy.
[It's a little far.]
- You can do it, Byung Jae.
90% to the right, you know...
Be careful.
Focus!
- It's the same as the last round.
- I see.
It's the same situation.
Good, good!
[The result of the first game
hangs on this ball.]
[Gary grabs the ball but...]
- What are you doing?
[they still succeed at it!]
[Super hero, Byung Jae]
- Yoo Byung Jae!
[It feel even worse
to lose against Byung Jae.]
- Yoo Byung Jae!
- We can run away now.
[Wait and See!]
- Pay for the game for us.
Here are ten coins for
the winner, Hot Guys team.
Here are five coins for
the losers, Cool Guys team.
Having ten coins are good
only if you can survive.
If you can't survive, what good
is having ten coins?
From now on,
you have five minutes...
to get to the next mission site
which is Changkyung palace.
That's my hot place.
Meantime, you can oust
the other team's members.
If you eliminate everyone's name tag,
that'll be the end of the race.
Go to the next site before
your name tag gets eliminated.
You'll see a taped area
and that's the safe zone.
You can participate the next mission,
if you enter the safe zone.
[Anyang Billiard Hall]
[Changkyung Palace]
There's a sign outside.
Move!
- Where is it?
- To your right!
[They don't even think
about ousting the other team.]
- Hurry!
- Where is it?
- Where it is?
- Go over there!
[The rule is to eliminate each other.
You know that, right?]
Three, two, one, move!
Five minutes from now on!
[The Cool Guys team starts.]
They're not here.
Are they chasing us?
Where are they now?
- Where is the palace?
- Run fast!
[Changkyung Palace]
Run at full speed!
They're coming!
- Where is the palace?
- Is it that building?
I'll hide and eliminate their
name tags.
- It's so tiring.
- Gary is coming!
- Suk Jin is here!
- Wait!
Jong Hyun!
Catch Suk Jin!
[Big-nose has left his group
and he's alone.]
Throw away your water bottle!
[He might be the first one
to be eliminated.]
[Jong Hyun catches Suk Jin.]
[Big-nose is ousted.]
Help me!
- Suk Jin is ousted.
- His name tag is eliminated?
[Those cold-hearted guys...]
[Changkyung Palace]
Should I go over there?
- Go that way.
- Okay.
Go to the other side.
[Ha Ha crosses the empty lot.]
Ha Ha ran to the other side.
[The quick-witted Giraffe
reveals Ha Ha's plan.]
It's right here!
Hurry up!
It's Changkyung Palace!
They're just two people.
Should we eliminate their name tags?
This is really tiring!
Why did I hide there?
[I shouldn't have left the group.]
Everyone is here, right?
I see one of your members is missing.
[Big-nosed brother fails to survive.]
- Huh, Suk Jin?
- Yes.
Don't pretend you didn't know.
You knew that he was ousted.
I mean, he's wearing...
I yelled for help.
I'm telling you again.
Running Man is like the Serengeti.
If you leave your group,
you'll be sacrificed.
Did you realize that you'll be ousted
even if you win.
I'm sorry, Mister. We're not
on the same team any more.
I think I'm on your team.
Is he on our team?
The one who gets ousted...
Let's say three members are ousted.
It will be five verses four.
The eliminated one can play
for the team with four members.
If the team with a spare player wins
that player will also earn a golden coin
but can't win the race.
- He'll get something?
- Gold coins.
- I'm my own team now.
- But you can't win the race.
For this game...
he'll join the Hot Guys team.
- Please, join us.
- Treat me well.
- I could ruin your game.
- He's like a mercenary.
This is Yoo Jae Suk's hot place.
Yes, it is.
Changkyung Palace is my place.
This is where I had a group blind date.
At Changkyung Palace...
[High school student Grasshopper's
first blind date spot.]
[What's the story behind this place?]
- At Changkyung Palace...
- You had a blind date here, too?
I feel sorry for the girls
who came for the date.
The person who arranged the blind date
must have taken the blame.
I'll tell you what...
15 boys from my class went there
- and I was within top five.
- Stop that nonsense!
Who did you go with?
I saw his picture.
He was ugly.
[Do you remember?
The top five at Changkyung Palace.]
- Did you pair up with someone?
- No.
It ended at the palace.
He must have played
the mood maker for others.
- You mean, the funny guy?
- Yes, he's the funny mood maker.
Have you ever tried it, Jong Kook?
I tried it only once.
With a girl from
Anyang High School of Arts.
[At a high school famous for pretty girls!]
Kim Hee Sun is from that school!
In a great combination, there were five
or six handsome boys from my school..
Then why the heck were you there?
That was the original plan,
but we hijacked the occasion.
[You hijack some weird things...]
The girls were so startled.
They were surprised that the boys
did not look like the pictures.
You hijacked that?
I can't believe you did that.
How about you, Gary?
I did it once in high school.
So what happened?
- Nothing happened,
- Why?
I wasn't a popular boy...
- Why would you ask that?
- I'm sorry...
I admit I can be very cruel.
I wasn't a popular boy back then!
I think I can be very cruel!
- How about Jong Hyun?
- Look how relaxed he is!
I never went on a date like that.
It wasn't a thing amongst my friends.
For people like him,
girls just come to them like magnets!
You don't need to go on
these meetings.
Did girls give you letters and gifts
all the time?
- No, they didn't.
- Then how did they show their affection?
Too many questions!
[I don't know how
handsome men live...]
I did receive letters here and there.
I never received any letter
other than those chain letters.
[All the letters I got when I was young
were bills and the conscription notice...]
Walking down memory lane!
So what are we doing here?
A representative from each team
will hold a bomb.
The other team members will line up
and have a mechanical pencil relay.
Every member will try to take out
one mechanical pencil lead...
The first team that finishes wins!
Best out of three.
The losing team's bomb will blow up.
I haven't played this game in forever!
[A mechanical pencil relay, best of three!]
[The losing team's bomb will
blow up on the spot!]
Please bring in the bombs.
Suk Jin will hold our bomb.
You're the extra in the team.
Come here.
You guys... Just wait until
we extras get more power!
But until then, I must comply...
When we have the power, you're all done!
- Ready?
- Yes.
- One at a time, right?
- The person before you must finish first.
So the losing team's bomb goes off?
You must win, guys.
- Let's try our best!
- Okay!
Fighting!
[If they lose, their departure
will be delayed by 10 seconds.]
[Speed is everything,
the mechanical pencil relay!]
- I think we got this!
[Kwang Soo vs. Ha Ha]
[The difference is as big as
that of their heights.]
What are you doing?
[Why is that Giraffe so fast?]
- Hey, Dong Hoon!
[Kwang Soo is successful!]
[Kyun Sung vs. Ha Ha]
[This lead is no ordinary lead.]
I think Jong Kook is going to
beat him up!
Done!
We're ahead!
[Kyun Sung vs. Jong Hyun]
- We won!
[Kyun Sung makes it!]
But should I be happy or not
about your pending victory?
[The extra gets some gold coins too
if his team wins!]
- Okay!
- They're catching up!
[Jong Hyun finishes]
[Ho Joon vs. Ji Hyo]
- Fighting, boys!
[Ho Joon finishes]
No matter how powerful Jong Kook is,
that's not going to help with this.
Just a bit more!
[Byung Jae vs. Ji Hyo]
- We got this!
[Ji Hyo finishes]
[Biting his lips!]
- Come on, Byung Jae!
[Byung Jae vs Jong Kook]
He's good at this too...
[I'm Mr. Capable!]
Go, Byung Jae!
[Jae Suk, the last one, starts!]
[Just you wait, grasshopper...]
- He's good at this too!
[Jae Suk vs. Jong Kook]
- I don't know who will win anymore!
[Soo Won will finish off]
- This is so close!
[Jae Suk vs. Soo Won]
Oh no!
[The game is dead close thanks to
Jong Kook and Soo Won!]
- Almost there!
- Come on!
[Head to head]
[Who will be the winner?]
- You must win, Jae Suk!
[Jae Suk vs. Soo Won]
[Jang Soo Won wins!]
[Hot Guys 0:1 Cool Guys]
The key is pressing it with your palm.
Jong Kook is no joke.
He's even good at this too!
[Kook and Soo Won contributed
to the flipping of the game!]
Do it with your palm.
We're going to lose at this rate.
We must win.
If we lose here, we're done!
Total annihilation!
[They might have to leave
10 seconds late...]
[The Cool Guys are reorganizing
their line-up.]
The fastest guy has to go first.
You're the fastest, right?
Kyun Sung is fast too.
You should go last, then.
[Speedy Kyun Sung will go last.]
Look!
I can be pretty fast!
[The big-nosed extra
is showing off his skills]
I'll take over the spot
of the slowest one.
- Take my spot.
- I'm on fire!
I'm really on fire!
We must win!
[Will the Big-nosed Brother lead
his team to victory?]
[Second Round of the
Mechanical Pencil Relay.]
Please take your spots.
Help your neighbors!
- Fighting, everyone!
[Enthusiastic Big-nose goes first.]
Fighting!
Faster!
[Big-nosed Brother...
You're slow!]
Why is he so slow?
Ji Hyo is super fast!
- Let's go, Ji Hyo!
[A breakneck speed!]
- Faster!
[Suk Jin vs. Ji Hyo]
[Ji Hyo finishes]
What is he doing right now?
[Kwang Soo vs. Jong Kook]
- That's great, Kwang Soo!
[The unstoppable Giraffe catches up!]
[Jong Kook finishes]
[And Kwang Soo finishes right after]
[Dead close]
- Focus...
[Ho Joon vs. Ha Ha]
Just a bit more!
[Fast and furious,
just like a car race!]
[Jong Hyun is at it]
[Byung Jae is next]
[The rocket technique!]
[Byung Jae vs. Jong Hyun]
[At a critical moment when the
smallest mistake can lead to defeat!]
That's great!
[Four runners have finished
almost at the same time!]
- Kyun Sung, please!
[Kyun Sung vs. Soo Won]
[The whole game depends on these two!]
[Will it be Kang Kyun Sung
the Speedy...]
[Or the machine man,
Soo Wonator?]
[The result is...]
[Kyun Sung vs. Soo Won]
[Dropped!]
[Right after that...]
[Jang Soo Won wins by a split second.]
- We won!
[Hot Guys 0:2 Cool Guys]
[The public enemy of his team.]
[The winning team gets 10 gold coins.]
[The losing team gets 5 gold coins.]
So, you have five minutes to reach
the next destination
which is an apartment building
in Shinwol 3-dong.
[Whose memory would be there?]
[Yoo Byung Jae's
Shinwon 3-dong Apartment!]
The Cool Guys get a head start of
10 seconds. Go ahead.
I'm counting to ten.
[Their name tags can be taken out
while moving to the next place]
[If they lose their name tag or don't
get there on time, they'll be out!]
[Cool Guys 15:15 Hot Guys]
[Shinwol 3-dong Apartment]
We must find some other route.
Let's go that way.
[Going around to
avoid a possible ambush.]
We must be invisible.
They can't realize our plan.
The earth is round,
so we'll get there eventually...]
We have five minutes to get there.
We have to climb this mountain?
[A mountain of problems.]
So if we win, we must run fast,
and if we lose, we must run far.
Do you think this is the right way?
We might be ousted all together
in this mountain!
If we don't make it in five minutes!
They're up there right now!
On the mountain!
[What kind of team is this?]
- What are they doing up there?
[The Cool Guys are strolling.]
- They're right there.
[The Cool Guys trying to find their way.]
They saw us here.
Then why did we come all the
way up here?
- Don't get scattered.
[Going down before it's too late]
That's the building right there!
[The Cool Guys have located
the apartment building.]
- I think they'll attack us near the building.
- Yes, I think so too.
You're running out of time!
Everyone will die!
We'll die either way!
There's no tomorrow for us!
They're coming.
Let's go and wait.
- To your right!
[Three minutes remaining]
Where is it?
[After an arduous journey...]
[Arrived at the apartment building!]
- Come here, Ho Joon.
[Hitching a ride]
Sir, may we get a ride to there?
- Thank you!
[Approved]
It's fine.
- You can go ahead.
[At this rate, they'll all make it!]
[Will their plan work?]
You can just go straight.
[A routine search, gentlemen.]
Get out of there!
We're busy!
We need at least one name tag.
You're safe, Kyun Sung.
Let's negotiate.
Give us Kwang Soo.
Gentlemen!
Open the window at least.
[With two minutes remaining,
some sort of decision is needed]
- What will you do?
- Kyun Sung can pass.
- Hold on...
[The door of negotiation is open]
We'll let everyone through
except Kwang Soo.
Why me?
- Let us think about this.
- No time for that!
He's sitting on the end!
How convenient!
- You have less than a minute left!
[Lying about the time]
This is crazy!
- Go, Kyun Sung.
- We won't take your tag.
[It seems like they're willing to
sacrifice Kwang Soo.]
We really won't take your name tag.
Move the car, please!
[Big-nosed Brother is looking
for new recruits.]
Go inside.
Do you want to go in or not?
[Fighting against Kook is hopeless.]
[The best option is sacrificing Kwang Soo!]
[20 seconds remaining]
- Go inside.
[Byung Jae surrenders too]
You can go, Jae Suk.
Just abandon Kwang Soo and go!
- Do you want to die together then?
[Grasshopper is resisting]
- Come on, let's go.
[10 seconds remaining]
[You've fallen for our plan,
Kim Jong Kook!]
[Giraffe and Grasshopper
turned into glue!]
[Time over]
- You should've listened to me!
[Thanks to their sacrifices, Kkuk is out.]
We've ousted Jong Kook!
[Jong Kook, Jae Suk, and Kwang Soo
are now extras.]
[Cool Guys vs. Hot Guys]
[15:15]
- How did this happen?
- I got a lot of friends now!
[The Extra Brothers]
This is my team now.
Don't think of us as weak.
Usually it takes more than three men
to get Jong Kook.
We did pretty well.
But even in my opinion, I think
it'll be a good match from now on.
We should've gotten one more.
The extras can't win.
There will be other perks,
but you won't be able to win.
The Cool Guys have five people
and the Hot Guys three.
So the two of the extras will join
the Hot Guys.
I'll join them.
If the Hot Guys win, only the extras
who participated in the game get the coins.
That's not fair!
I'll do it!
- This game is my all-time favorite!
[I can do well!]
- The reason why I can do well is..
[The rules haven't been explained yet]
You just ruined our game before, Mr. Ji.
I'm the most experienced extra here.
[The extras must consider seniority now?]
- Can the team choose?
[Kkuk and Big-nosed Brother join by force]
This is a public service announcement...
We're recruiting for the next class of extras...
[Anyone can join as long as
your name tag is gone!]
But let's first talk about
why we're here, Byung Jae.
- There's a videotape!
- Why is it x-rated?
What did you do in Shinwol-dong?
[An apartment building in
Shinwol 3-dong...]
[And an x-rated video...]
[What could be his story?]
I've been living with the guy who came
to visit just before for eight years.
We used to be very poor, so we
could only afford to live in basements.
Then he got a girlfriend,
and this is her place.
This apartment?
To me, it was the best place
I've ever lived in.
So all three of us lived together...
[Little too intimate!]
Let's just say
you were there all the time.
I lived in the apartment too.
I had a separate room.
[So you lived with your roommate's girlfriend?]
The girlfriend was quite generous.
And then?
Then she ended up cheating on him.
[The landlady ended up getting
another boyfriend...]
My roommate and I knew that
she was cheating.
But we just pretended as if
we didn't know.
[In fear of eviction, they
pretended as if they had no idea.]
Otherwise they would've been kicked out!
The moment she knows that they know!
I assume your roommate was in
an awkward position.
So we lived like that for two months.
My roommate kept ignoring his girlfriend
every time she tried to talk to him.
[Love, hatred...]
[But survival triumphs them all!]
This is a survival story!
So in the end, he met up with
his girlfriend and her new boyfriend.
I've been told that he got beaten up.
Then we got evicted.
So he got beaten up
then kicked out?
There were four streams of blood
coming out of his nose.
Is that even possible?
Then what is this tape?
So it was about how
the story could be x-rated.
The instructions are on the back.
The rules are as follows.
Each team will sit in a row
facing each other.
The defending team will move
the videotape behind their backs...
Without giving any hint to
the opposition.
The attacking team will try to locate
the videotape by asking questions.
The defending team gets
30 seconds to move the videotape.
The attacking team gets five minutes
for questioning.
- So we must decide who will attack first.
- That's right.
How should we decide that?
- You can attack first.
- You can.
- Okay!
[Toward the Hot Guys]
We'll attack first.
- 30 seconds to move the tape.
- Yes.
We have to do it in the back.
We must get closer.
Ready, set, go!
Where is my youth?
[The singing defense to
muffle the sound.]
[Speedy delivery!]
[The tape is with Gary]
[Hunting hawks]
[Still blank, regardless]
It's really hard to read Ji Hyo.
The tape isn't with her.
Why?
I saw it through that gap.
- Why did you see it?
[Disappointed]
[Because it was showing...]
- You should've been more careful!
[Byung Jae was just trying to win.]
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six...
You have it, don't you, Gary?
Five, four, three, two, one.
[The videotape moving is done]
You have five minutes to question.
So it went from here
to that side.
I think it didn't go all the way.
It's probably somewhere in the middle.
I think it's Gary...
Why Gary?
I'm pretty good at guessing in general.
- Is that so?
[Son Ho Joon the Guessing King?]
What did you guess in the past
that you got right?
On my college admission exam
the hardest math problem was the
last open-ended question.
The one with the biggest weight.
I guessed that right.
All the way to the decimals.
Quite precise!
The answer was 7.95.
How is that even possible?
So you just wrote 7.95?
So I measured the figure
with my ruler...
It seemed like it'd be more than seven,
but slightly less than eight.
- So 7.95.
[Quite analytical in his own way]
So that was your best guess.
There's no way one can guess
that number.
- Let's go with Gary.
- He's smiling.
I don't think it's with him.
[Does Gary really have the videotape?]
Soo Won.
Is it to your left or right?
I. have. it.
- It's really hard to read him.
- We shouldn't ask him.
He really is a robot.
We can't tell.
I. have. it.
[Everyone is acting like robots]
That's how you can tell they're old.
That used to be the classic way
of mimicking a robot.
Beep, beep, beep...
I have it, I have it...
The robots these days are very natural!
But why is Ha Ha so close to Gary?
Everyone else has some gap.
Closer, closer!
[Where is this videotape?]
I really have no idea.
Should we choose Soo Won?
Then let's just choose Gary.
I support Ho Joon.
Please say out the name
on the count of three.
You got it, don't you Gary?
I really don't have it.
He was very natural.
Too natural.
Do you have it, Jong Hyun?
No...
[Awkward]
Three, two...
[What is this awkward feeling?]
- Let's go with Jong Hyun.
- One!
- One, two, three!
Jong Hyun!
Please show your hands one by one.
He isn't it...
[Empty-handed Blank Ji]
Ha Ha?
[Empty-handed Ha Ha]
Gary?
[Does he have the video as
Ho Joon guessed?]
[Gary is empty-handed too!]
[Only Jong Hyun and Soo Won left!]
Please raise your hands simultaneously.
One, two, three!
[So...
Who...]
[Has the videotape?]
[Jang Soo Won is the culprit!]
[Are you okay?
Have I surprised you?]
[Everyone got tricked by
his robotic acting.]
I managed to pass it down that way
at the last moment.
The Cool Guys win!
[Cool Guys 20:15 Hot Guys]
[Boramae Park]
I have an extra map.
Do I have to give it?
- He stole a map!
[He picked up a map of the Hot Guys!]
I didn't steal it.
I picked it up.
Don't we have to hurry up?
What will happen if they attack us
all of a sudden?
Shall we split?
Gary and I will go to the right side.
You can go left.
One, two, three!
[Scattering]
[What...]
[What was that?]
They're here!
Pretend like you're running away!
[Luring them in]
They're running away.
I think that was Ji Hyo.
Don't go here.
From the back!
Run!
Go inside!
Come!
Quickly!
Hurry!
We got sandwiched!
What should we do?
[A critical moment for the Hot Guys]
[At 5 vs 3, they're heavily disadvantaged.]
Get him!
Just let him go!
[Escaped by himself]
[Good luck, everyone!]
[Focusing on Ho Joon and Byung Jae
after abandoning Kyun Sung.]
[Grabbed!]
- No!
[Is Ho Joon ripping Gary's name tag?]
[Byung Jae's tag is caught too!]
[Gary was fast...]
[But his own name tag is
in Ho Joon's hand!]
[At this moment!]
[Jong Hyun?]
- We got it first!
[Simultaneous tag ripping ensues]
So what happens now?
[Byung Jae is out]
[Ho Joon and Gary are both out.]
[Boramae Park]
[Meanwhile, Kyun Sung arrives at
the Boramae Park Safe Zone.]
Hey, Kyun Sung!
You should've helped the other guys!
Why did you run away?
There's at least one person remaining
because he ran away.
At this rate, we'll be able to
wrap up today's filming before lunch!
[Overcrowding of the extras]
He's making me angry.
What should we do with that punk?
That little guy...
[Jang Robot is also happy about
the team's performance]
Now we have the third class
of the extras.
- Is everyone here?
- Yes.
But they are not very excited.
Everyone, we must participate
in order to get coins.
- We know.
- Do you?
We do know, but we also have
preferences when it comes to games.
[The extras at this job fair
only want to do the ones they like!]
[Dissent level is high]
I'm sorry, but if you're looking for a job,
you must be more enthusiastic about this!
I don't want to work today.
What's your memory here, Ho Joon?
It's nothing funny.
When I first moved to Seoul,
I used to live around Shinlim-dong.
I was told that Boramae Park is a
good place to exercise, so I came here.
- And it was huge!
- It indeed is.
[When he was just a newcomer to Seoul,
he exercised in this park.]
What was the first thing you saw
in Seoul, Byung Jae?
Yongsan Station.
- So you got off the train at Yongsan Station?
- Yes, I did.
Where are you from?
I'm from Hongseong,
in Chungnam Province.
Anything other than Yongsan Station?
Anything that impressed you?
Anything that made you realize
that you were in Seoul!
The electronics market in Yongsan.
Please try to leave Yongsan!
[The enduring impression of Yongsan]
So what's our mission here?
It's a pet relay.
Here are the rules.
The first runner will dress up as a bear
and run with four feet.
[Releasing two bears]
[They're rather fast!]
[Amazing four-feet running speed!]
Soo Won's beat is off.
[Awkward]
[Kyun Sung touches the next runner first!]
Give him the baton!
The next runners will dress up as snakes
and crawl with a sleeping bag on.
- You need to roll!
[Why don't you give it a try...]
[Two snake are rolling like sushi...]
[And still haven't made much progress...]
- Just go on top of him!
[Caught up!]
[Keep up the good work, brothers...]
- Quickly!
[Twisting his whole body]
- The third runner will be a kangaroo.
[Kwangaroo runs!]
They'll dress up as kangaroos
and have a ball in between their thighs.
Then they'll jump to the goal.
If the ball drops, they'll start again.
[Jong Hyun-garoo is a lot slower]
[Kwangaroo makes it!]
[The last runner, Son-rabbit begins.]
The fourth runner will dress up as a rabbit
and squat-jump until the end.
[The blank-rabbit tried her best
but Son-rabbit was a lot faster!]
[The extras did their best to give
Kyun Sung the victory!]
The snake is the hardest part.
I don't want to be a snake anymore!
I can't show my face,
and it hurts!
[Best of Three]
[The second round of the pet relay]
Just win and be done with it!
Fighting, Kyun Sung!
Fighting!
[Two bears charging!]
[Kyun Sung Bear is used to this now.]
[Ha Bear is side-running?]
That's pretty funny.
Kyun Sung is fast.
[Kyun Sung's speed has gone up.]
He really is fast!
[He touches first again!]
Hurry!
[Became a cobra.]
[Creepily similar]
- Hey, you actually look like a snake!
[But it's not very effective]
- You must roll!
[Jong Hyun Snake decides to roll!]
- Roll!
[Jong Hyun flips the game]
- Side!
[I'll roll too!]
Go over him!
Just like that!
[Flipping the game again
after hitting Jong Hyun?]
[Grabbed!]
[Snake hands appear!]
Snakes can't grab!
- You can't grab!
[Good luck...]
- You can't grab...
[The snake guys are getting tangled up.]
- You're just like cobras!
[Attacking with teeth!]
Nice work, Kwang Soo!
You're almost here, Jong Hyun!
You're doing great, Jong Hyun!
[Kwang Snake moves on
after beating Jong Hyun.]
You're rolling with your body,
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Snake makes a great
sacrifice and molts!
[Jong Hyun Snake passes the baton too.]
[Yoo Hyuk Kangaroo is doing well...]
[Then he loses the ball!]
[Meanwhile, the robot kangaroo
is at full speed!]
- Quickly!
- This is hard to tell!
[Their race will decide the result!]
Ji Hyo is fast!
Hey, Ho Joon!
Keep it up!
That was definitely a robot acting.
[Two rabbits are close to each other.]
[Their team's victory depends on their leap!]
[What will be the result?]
We won!
[The Hot Guys win!]
We won by a split second.
I lost by one step!
You can run, Kyun Sung!
[Kyun Sung's chance of survival
has gone up.]
Well done, extras!
We did some good work.
So we're going to get paid!
We must get paid!
We're going to get some coins!
Kyun Sung takes ten coins.
What's the total?
The Cool Guys get five coins.
You must pay us too.
Only to the ones who participated.
[Five coins to Jae Suk, Kwang Soo,
and Ho Joon.]
Let's divide it equally.
Don't be ridiculous.
Let's just divide it!
- We're on the same team!
[Trying to freeride...]
What are you doing?
What's going on?
[This is the Extras Job Fair,
where robbery is common.]
You can't do this!
Assuming that Kyun Sung will make it
to the next mission place...
I'll let you know the rules of
the next mission.
A karaoke place in Anyang.
- It must be this guy.
- Jong Kook!
I remember it very well.
You have five minutes to get to
the karaoke place in Anyang.
Kyun Sung may leave 10 seconds earlier.
Where is it?
- Go find it!
[The sole survivor is lost]
I'm going!
We passed it before.
- I think you can go straight.
[I don't feel good about that guy...]
A karaoke in Anyang...
[It's 4 vs 1- The priority here is making
it to the destination alive.]
He's right there.
[I'll survive until the end!]
The karaoke in Anyang is this way.
- Can we go faster?
[The extras are taking a tour]
Hello!
- Hello!
[Gong Yoo is at the Heylee Cafe!]
[Actors Ma Dong Seok and
Jung Yoo Mi are there too!]
Everyone is here!
Do you want a ride, Gong Yoo?
What brings you here?
Dong Seok! Why don't you
join us for an episode soon?
Yoo Mi is here too!
Hello!
Is this some sort of a gathering?
We're doing a movie together.
[They're shooting for
a film called "To Busan."]
Mr. Ma!
Would you please come on Running Man
and take this guy to the ground?
He's too arrogant!
I'm too old for that.
Good luck!
- Goodbye!
[Please appear on Running Man soon!]
Everyone should come with Yoo Mi!
Goodbye!
Yoo Mi is pretty...
Would you please give us a heart?
[A heart for the extras]
Thank you!
Goodbye!
[We hope the movie is successful!]
Mister!
Please sit down!
Gong Yoo is like my brother.
Wait, hold on!
- Hey, Gong Yoo!
[Confirming right away]
- Wait a minute...
- Just go! Hurry!
He claims that he's like a brother
to you. Is that true?
We are brothers!
Right, Gong Yoo?
[Just continue going your way]
How embarrassing!
I should have said it when
we were further down the road.
[Thank you for your quick confirmation, Gong Yoo!]
[Meanwhile, the Cool Guys are
looking for Kyun Sung.]
Is he hiding somewhere?
[Kyun Sung is hiding.]
I think he's hiding somewhere.
[Jong Hyun's eyes catch him!]
Below the truck on the right side...
[Pretending to be ignoring him...]
[Then charge!]
[His clumsy hiding results in
a even bigger problem]
[The race is over if he gets ousted here!]
[Karaoke in Anyang]
[He makes it to the safe zone
by a split second!]
[Cool Guys 30:30 Hot Guys]
[Karaoke in Anyang]
[Where a man's memories are still alive...]
Kim Jong Kook...
I have a lot of memories here.
Many of my friends used to work
at karaoke spots.
- For part-time jobs?
- Yes.
They really helped me
to become a singer.
- They gave you free practice time?
- Yes, of course.
They were all my friends,
so I went during lunchtime.
My friends worked right in
front of the school.
Shouldn't you have eaten
then paid attention in class?
- When I was on a break..
[He's actually scared]
What kind of high school student
can enjoy so much freedom?
You know how we all got
lunch period?
We were allowed to leave the campus
during that hour.
- No, my school didn't allow that.
- My school did.
But because he worked so hard
using his small breaks...
that helped him to become
a successful singer!
You're scared of him, aren't you?
Just a thought.
[Was it that obvious?]
That's when I realized
I had talent in singing.
The karaoke place opened
when I was in the 11th grade.
What was your favorite song?
I sang "She's Gone" a lot.
And...
- "My Sight of You" by B612.
- That's right.
"The Serenade of Late Night"
by Black Hole.
All these songs are high-pitched.
I used to be into rock.
Since we're at a karaoke now,
and because we sing all the time...
- Let's have Ho Joon sing something for us!
- Let's hear it!
- He's a singer too!
[He used to be in idol group "Takion"]
- I can do a slow song...
- Like what?
He and I have a similar taste in music.
- Something like "Emerald Castle?"
- Love songs?
I guess I got it right!
You want to sing "The Steps?"
Someone came and sang it already.
"Emergency Room" by izi.
He really likes love songs!
- I'm so excited!
- How fitting!
He likes slow and romantic songs like this!
Ho Joon likes love songs!
["Emergency Room" by izi]
How handsome!
- My wife is a huge fan of his.
- He can sing!
- He used to be a singer!
- Yes, he used to be!
[Would you mind?]
Stop singing along!
You're ruining the song!
- It's my favorite.
- Just be quiet.
[A bad rap feature.]
[Laughter]
[His voice is still wonderful
despite the bad environment.]
[I don't think this is for you, Suk Jin...]
[This has become Ho Joon's
solo concert!]
[Everybody is impressed by
Ho Joon's singing]
Who were you just thinking about
when you were singing?
Your ex-girlfriend?
It fits today's weather.
How about Kyun Sung sings
some cover songs?
Cover songs?
- Then Since Gary is here...
- Jung In!
- I'll cover Jung In's part.
- Great!
How can you possibly do her part?
- Really? Jung In?
- How about "Rush?"
How can a guy cover a girl's part?
["Rush" by Leessang]
[Grandmother?]
This can't be Jung In!
I'm sorry.
The actual singer was helping you!
[This shouldn't be happening...]
We need to hear from Byung Jae!
Sing a song!
How about "Swallowtail Butterfly?"
[Only because he has a mustache
like the original singer...]
What would you like to sing?
I do sing "Rush" quite often.
Perhaps he can be Gil's part!
I can do all three parts.
He says he can sing all three parts.
Give us "Rush!"
You're not trying to play
a joke on me too, are you?
I won't cooperate!
[It'll be hard to hear Gary's rap
from now on...]
It'd be so awesome
if he could actually do all three.
How is that possible?
[Gil's part is first]
[His husky voice is quite similar
to that of Gil.]
[Then how about Gary's part?]
[Gary explodes]
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
What are you doing?
- What did you just do?
[Quite brave in front of the original singer.]
He claimed that he could sing
all three parts...
[I'm sorry...]
Is today the fraud special or something?
What's going on?
We need something good now.
For a great impact, I'll try Kim Jang Hoon.
Jang Hoon!
- Please raise it higher.
[And he's raising the interval!]
Is he really raising the key?
["If You're Like Me" by Kim Jang Hoon]
[Doesn't sound like it'll be a success.]
- Similar!
[Huh? The feeling is quite similar.]
- Are you sick?
- This is Jang Hoon when he's sick.
- What kind of voice is this?
- Let him continue.
I think he's actually ill.
- The climax is coming.
[They'll judge by the chorus.]
[Coming up soon!]
- It's here!
[And now..]
[Cancel]
- What are you doing?
[Oddly similar, yet very weird.]
- This can't be Jang Hoon.
[Apologetic mode]
We know how he sounds!
[At least it was refreshing...]
This will be your last chance!
Kim Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook!
- He sounded just like him on TV.
- Which song of his?
- "The One Man!'
- "The One Man?'
- Which one?
"Lovely."
This is hard to cover.
This is rather difficult.
But he's daring to do it while
the original artist is right here.
I guess he's that confident.
- You want to raise my song by four keys?
- That's how I can sound similar.
Seriously?
Is that even possible?
- We'll trust you this time!
- So high!
["Lovely" by Kim Jong Kook]
[Is there a mosquito flying around?]
[This must be how you felt, Gary...]
I think it's similar!
No he's not!
He sounds like Ji Sang Yeol!
[Even he's laughing]
Definitely Ji Sang Yeol...
[I shall be patient for now...]
[Checking the mood]
Don't worry about him!
Keep going!
[Then I'll be a mosquito!]
Jong Kook's face is getting rigid.
[Along with Kyun Sung's
embarrassing singing...]
[He is concerned by the
old fashion style portrayed on the TV.]
- Look at the bobbed-hair!
[I'm not really laughing...]
[Mosquito voice explosion!]
[Hmph...]
I'm sorry...
- Are you kidding me?
[Apologizing after singing...]
I do think he's making fun of us.
I think he started with Jung In.
[Then I'm going to join too!]
Don't do it.
He's good, but not similar.
- Now we can start our mission.
[This was just the warm-up!]
Well done, everyone!
- We had fun thanks to you!
[The real mission begins now!]
Kyun Sung is the sole survivor
among the Hot Guys.
He'll compete against Jong Hyun
for a single round.
The rule is too simple.
They'll press a random song number and
whoever gets the longer song title wins!
So this is just about luck.
There used to be this song titled "I'd Vaguely
Remember About Old Times Beyond the Window."
"The Woman Who Can't Break Up,
the Guy Who Can't Leave."
- This is just completely about luck!
[Any song with the longer title will do!]
- This is the end!
[If Kyun Sung loses, he won't have time to run!]
[Kyun Sung enters a number]
3575?
3579.
[Didn't know]
[Despondent]
Now, Jong Hyun!
Challenge accepted!
13274...
[Today's result depends on this number!]
[Please be short...]
[What is 13274?]
[A Pretty Woman]
[The Cool Guys win!]
Do you know this song?
[Yoo Hyuk the Extra's
impromptu celebration.]
- Do you know this song?
["A Pretty Woman" by Seol Woon Do]
[Huh?]
[Something's off...]
Are you sure that's the right song?
[You don't know it!]
[Quit it!]
You've caught me.
You didn't have any confidence
in your singing.
Ten coins for the Cool Guys!
Quite a lot!
- It's hard to get coins as extras!
[Kyun Sung gets five.]
He should have won.
The next destination is...
There's no point to it now.
The game is over.
- Try to survive.
- Okay.
We're going to camp out right here.
You guys can leave ten seconds early.
The next destination is
Ji Hyo's toilet at Gimpo Airport.
What the heck is that?
Start!
He's done.
[Nervous]
- Don't loiter around!
- Let's take a walk.
[The Cool Guys are camping out]
- I guess there's no way out, Kyun Sung.
- You've done enough.
Why aren't you leaving?
Scary.
[If Kyun Sung makes to the next destination,
the mission resumes.]
We'll give you three seconds.
Three...
Two...
One!
Wait...
Get him!
[Breaking out at full speed!]
They won't be able to catch him.
They really can't catch him.
Get him!
He's getting away!
[What will come out of this chase?]
[Toilet at Gimpo Airport]
[The Extras have already arrived.]
[Huh?]
We're here.
[How about Kyun Sung?]
Did you get it ripped?
[He did his best to run...]
[But!]
[Jong Hyun easily catches up.]
So fast!
[He was at a dead end...]
[Grabbed]
[He tried his best against
four people...]
[But Ha Ha ousted him.]
[And this is how today's race ended.]
Why are you so fast?
As Ha Ha ripped the last name tag,
the final victory is to the Cool Guys!
I'm envious!
I didn't like our name to begin with.
- It was rather old-fashioned.
- What is "Hot Guys" anyway?
We'll exchange your coins for gifts.
Five coins can be exchanged
to coffee gift card.
How many do you have?
I have four...
If you don't drink coffee, donate!
- Please give me!
- I played an important role!
[The serial robberies have made
the real ownership vague.]
- You have three?
- I don't want to give it to you.
- I have four!
- Just give me one!
[You can just go out for
coffee together!]
The victors, please come forward.
You have 40 coins, correct?
We'll give you gift certificates
for a department store.
- Good job!
- I'm envious!
Well done, cool guys!
[Many thanks to our five guests
for their wonderful performance!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
We'll start the wedding now.
[Jesse, Kim Yoo Ri, Seo Yeh Ji,
Cho Ah, Jang Do Yeon...]
I don't want to get married to this guy.
- The name tag...
[Someone objects to this wedding!]
makes a man.
[A horrendous event
that happened at a sacred place...]
Just a moment, please...
We don't have it?
[Provocation of dangerous brides!]
[The dream wedding must be accomplished!]
What is she doing?
This is a competition.
You shouldn't have come on this show!
Just mind your own emcee business.
[Dangerous Brides]