Hi, Running Man.
I'm Selma.
I'm Frehley.
We are big fans of
Running Man from Algeria.
We're sending you our
idea for a game proposition.
And we hope you win.
Thank you.
Hi. My name is Dulce
and I'm from Mexico.
Hi, Running Man.
My name is Charlotte.
And I'm from Melbourne, Australia.
Hi, I'm Dita.
I'm a fan of Running Man
from Indonesia.
Hi, Running Man.
I'm Audrey from Canada.
Hello.
We come from Taiwan.
I'm Huang Yun Ting
and I'm Ke Yu Gen.
[With games from all over the world...]
[The Running Man Global Mission Tour]
[Mok-dong SBS
in Seoul, South Korea]
What's with the red carpet?
Who is it?
- Hello!
- Who is it?
- It's Jung Il Woo!
- Wow!
[The Hallyu Prince, Jung Il Woo.]
He's handsome.
[A new face on Running Man.]
- He has good lines in his face.
[A star who leads the k-pop frenzy.]
- Isn't it Yong Hwa?
- It's Yong Hwa.
[Hallyu's tidal wave, Jung Yong Hwa.]
Your outfit doesn't fit
with the red carpet.
I didn't know I would
walk on the red carpet.
It's Hong Ki!
[Their new album made a hot issue.]
[A major Hallyu band,
F.T. Island's Lee Hong Ki.]
They're more popular overseas.
I often see Hong Ki at the gym.
I'm wondering what kind of games
we'll play with these three stars.
Today, we have guests who are
very popular overseas.
They are Hallyu stars.
(Celebrities in the Korean wave.)
They're indeed Hallyu stars.
Let's take a photo with them.
So you can upload on
your social networking sites?
He posts so much.
- He's addicted.
- You post more than me.
Why did you upload the photo
of you using a facial mask?
[Annoying]
[Big-nose's facial mask]
[A celebrity paparazzi,
Big-nosed brother.]
A lot of your pictures
look like you're in anguish.
Anyway, let's take a picture together.
Today's 'Hallyu Race' is different
from the previous races.
Your missions are
suggested by the fans.
We've invited public participation
for the games on Youtube
and on social networking sites
all over the world.
From Monday to Wednesday
we've received more than
2,000 emails in about 50 hours.
I got some, too.
[The countries of the fans
who sent their ideas.]
- South Africa.
- Even European countries?
Morocco, Algeria, Australia, UK...
France, Thailand, Mexico...
Brunei, Arab Emirates, and Ecuador.
- El Salvarod.
- It's El Salvador not El Salvarod.
Hi, Running Man.
This is Lou.
I'm from the United States.
Hello.
My name is Ying Yi Lau.
This is Elisa.
I'm from the Philippines.
- That's amazing.
- Thank you so much.
Again, thank you for
sending us your ideas.
I can't believe this.
We've decided how
you'll play the games.
There will be a team of three
and a team of seven.
- This is unusual.
- Three versus seven?
You'll play three games.
One member from the team of three
will play against the
seven people per game.
[Who's the leader?]
The leader of the team
of three will be...
Kim Jong Kook.
What do you mean
by three versus seven?
[Suddenly seven looks
like a small number.]
The other team's leader
will be Yoo Jae Suk.
We've decided the teams
by request.
Which team should I be on?
Why did you move away from me?
These seven people can be my team.
Hey, you fools!
- You're calling me a fool?
[Kim Jong Kook and the fools.]
We have pretty good records.
[It's already heating up.]
Well...
Let me see from a distance.
Step back, if you're not confident.
Why don't you step back?
The first member I'll pick is...
[The second member
of Jong Kook's team.]
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Yes!
Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
Did you pick someone
you can boss around?
[I still want to be picked.]
Don't use your strength!
[Even though there are three members,
it's possible to win with Jong Kook.]
I'll pick the last member.
- It'll be a Hallyu star.
- They want to get picked.
I don't know why I want
to get picked.
One, two, three!
Jung Il Woo!
He doesn't look happy.
- Me?
- How come?
[Il Woo is new to variety shows
and slow to react.]
I just thought...
he said 'Jung Yong Hwa.'
My feet just moved forward.
[It was close.]
He's good in shape.
By the way,
Il Woo looks uncomfortable.
[He suddenly wraps his arm around.]
- Why?
I'm very shy.
I was surprised.
- I'll do my best today.
- Okay, let's do it together!
Let's do it!
Let's show our sneaky actions!
[Nothing can be better than this!]
[The extraordinary missions from all
around the world will be revealed.]
[Pick the card of the country
of the game maker.]
[How will the card be
used at the final mission?]
We can't play together but
one of us will play for each game.
The first game will be
'What time is it, Mr. Wolf?'
If it's a wolf, this game
will be a strength-related game.
- You should play the first game.
- Okay, I'll play the first game.
I see.
Il Woo is very fast.
I just try hard.
He has an athlete's body.
He gets his hopes up, but then he'll
scold you when he's disappointed.
Just act like a fool from the
beginning or do well until the end.
I think he'll be good.
I chose the path of a fool.
I've always wanted to
be on Running Man.
But my schedule didn't let me.
You should win since you're here.
I've waited so long.
I can't lose.
Bring your face in more.
[SNS addicted Big-nose
is taking a photo]
Jae Suk, smile!
I'm driving now.
- Who drives like this?
- It's for the fans all over the world.
He's driving.
- Make a pretty face!
- Cheese!
[Yoo Hyuk wears an awkward smile.]
[Big-nose with Hallyu stars.]
It's a lot of work to manage
three social networking sites.
[He's always busy
managing the three sites.]
I heard days pass by
in the blink of an eye.
You don't have time to eat.
[Will they be able to
defeat Mr. Capable?]
[Somewhere in Gyeonggi Province]
I see it's filled with water.
What is the tree for?
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- It looks horrible.
Is this the outdoor studio for us?
What is this?
This is your first mission
of the Hallyu race.
This game is suggested by
Nila Andina from Singapore.
- I love Nila Andina.
- Hi, Nila Andina!
We couldn't see the mission paper.
- Pardon?
- Jae Suk lost it.
- It's my fault.
- You left it in the waiting room.
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
Please tell us what it is.
- What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
- What's that?
- That's the title.
[Kwang Soo translates it in Korean.]
The children in Singapore
play this game a lot.
One person from the team of three
becomes a wolf and stands
in front of the tree.
All the members of the team
of seven will be lambs.
You will ask the wolf,
'What time is it, Mr. Wolf?'
Then the wolf will choose between
one o'clock to eight o'clock
and answers the time.
You will go forward the number
of steps the wolf says.
You will win when you rip off
the wolf's name tag.
When the the lambs are close,
the wolf says 'meal time!'...
turns around and runs.
The wolf has to oust the lambs
before they get out of the water.
After the wolf says 'meal time,'
he will run toward us.
- Can we rip off the wolf's name tag?
- Not at that time.
You think you can rip off Jong Kook's
name tag when he's running toward you?
- Refrigerated patient!
I'm hungry today.
You look very relaxed, Kwang Soo.
This game is not a problem for us.
Please choose who will be the wolf.
You should know that the
person who plays this game
won't be able to play
the next game.
Is there another game that
needs physical strength?
We've already given you the information,
but Yoo Jae Suk lost it...
- Damn!
- It's his fault!
Why didn't you bring it for me?
What did you say?
You should have brought it yourself.
You're the leader.
Actually, we don't know
what the other games are.
Come out, Kim Jong Kook!
Bring it on!
- Are you scared?
- Why don't you do it?
- What are you going to do?
- I don't mind doing it.
Kim Jong Kook is scared.
[Scared...]
[The team of seven starts provoking him.]
- Don't listen to them.
Kim Jong Kook is scared.
[Big-nose sings an impromptu
song to provoke him.]
I'll play the wolf.
I'll do it.
It's important to have good roots.
We need to win this game.
I'm not afraid to get wet!
Be quiet!
I'll be the wolf.
Kim Jong Kook will be the wolf.
- Please wear the lamb head bands.
- I see.
- I made another title for this game.
- What is it?
It's 'The Silence of The Lambs.'
'The Silence of The Lambs,' you know.
You never know what will happen.
Jong Kook is already calculating
how many steps we're away.
He's meticulous.
[He's a spine-chilling wolf.]
- He looks like a wolf.
Go, Jong Kook, go!
[Come on, my prey!]
- He looks like a real wolf.
- I'm scared!
[The wolf's team members are happy.]
[In Kkuk's head,
the lambs are all dead.]
- I hate him.
- Me, too.
I hate myself more for being
scared of him.
Don't we need to make a plan?
Regardless of a plan, we'll
have to sacrifice some of us.
Look, all of us won't
be able to survive.
But the team has to win.
Do we have to walk forward?
Don't even think of running away
or kicking your team members.
Kicking the team members?
Let's finish this in one round!
We'll start the game that
Nila Andina sent us.
We'll win, Nila!
Don't worry, Nila!
We'll finish it in one round!
Ready, set, go!
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
[The wolf can say any time between
one o'clock and eight o'clock.]
Eight o'clock!
- Eight o'clock.
[The lambs have to move eight steps.]
Five, six, seven...
[The lambs have to move discreetly.]
[The wolf has to figure out
where the lambs are.]
They came further than I thought.
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
- Five o'clock.
- Pardon?
- Say it louder.
Five o'clock.
[The lambs move five steps.]
- Some of you shortened your strides.
- Be careful.
It'll be his meal time soon.
Be careful.
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
Two o'clock.
- Why?
- Why is it two o'clock?
[I can hear you.]
They're not very close yet.
Be careful, he's going to eat soon.
Aren't you little too far, Gary?
[I'm scared.]
[Let me see...
they're pretty close.]
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
Meal time!
[Eliminate the lambs' name tags
before they get out of the water.]
[Run for your life!]
[Meal time!]
[Wolf Kkuk's maximum power.]
[Incredible speed.]
[He closes the gap in a flash...]
[I got you!]
[He eliminates Big-nose's name tag.]
[Big-nose is ousted.]
[Shocked]
- He did it!
[Horrifying]
Am I ousted?
When did it happen?
[His hunt was successful!]
[With incredible speed...]
[he hunted the lamb right before
he got out of the water.]
[This is how wolf Kkuk hunts.]
[They are in a state of panic.]
They were in the middle last time.
- You can eliminate two name tags.
- Let them go further.
We can't play like this.
Let's work together.
[Wolf Kkuk is ready
for the next round.]
Let's say it's three o'clock.
I can walk three steps and
eliminate the wolf's name tag?
- He can't eliminate me, can he?
- No, I can't.
- Is that so?
[Gary understands the rules now.]
- You were at the back!
- I didn't know that.
[I was wondering why
everybody was in a hurry.]
Let me tell you one thing.
Yong Hwa and Hong Ki,
you've shortened your strides.
We're a team.
You shouldn't do that!
- We'll work together.
- Help us!
- Let's eliminate the wolf together!
- Let's go!
- Let's do it.
- We can do it!
Let's do it this time!
I'll do it this time!
[Which lamb should I get?]
- Ready, set, go!
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
- Eight o'clock!
- Okay!
[Their aggressive steps.]
[They've already reached
the mid-point.]
Go, team, go!
Wait, wait!
Oh my!
I think two o'clock is a good time.
Please don't let the wolf know.
It's eight o'clock, but
they're already...
[In a suppressed tone...]
- What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
One o'clock!
- One o'clock?
- Don't move.
Just pretend we're moving.
[I can hear you, Ji Hyo.]
[What good is it to whisper now?]
- Don't go!
[Jae Suk and Yong Hwa take a big step.]
- What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
[What time is it, Mr. Wolf?]
One o'clock!
- One o'clock!
- Don't go!
The water makes noise!
They put us in the water!
And they tell us to walk quietly.
[I hear the water.]
People at the back should ask the wolf.
- Jae Suk!
[Only two of us will ask the wolf.]
Oh, I see. Yong Hwa will
stay at the back and ask...
Are you going to let this happen?
We can't help it.
Because we can hear it.
I said one o'clock a while ago.
Didn't you move yet?
[He made a lot of progress....]
[It's too close...]
[Am I too close?]
[Tactless Gary joins Jae Suk.]
[Jae Suk and Gary attack the wolf.]
[If I can eliminate that name tag...]
[we, lambs can live in peace.]
[He just needs to rip it off.]
[Were you there?]
I can do it!
What time is it?
- What time is it...
- Don't ask!
[Wait for me.
I'll do it this time!]
[I've reached my limit...]
[I'm hungry.]
- No!
- Give up on them!
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
[Jae Suk and Gary's crisis.]
Now?
You mean now?
Now, now, now?
It's meal time!
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Jae Suk the lamb is
ousted in a moment!]
[Gary the lamb made to the land.]
I was on the land!
Yoo Jae Suk is ousted.
I told you not to ask!
Is that garbage looking thing
Jae Suk's name tag?
I'm upset!
We'll lose if we keep this pace.
You need to be more aggressive!
- Just take care of Kwang Soo!
- Don't worry!
[Kwang Soo made a big contribution.]
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
- Eight o'clock!
- Again?
Do your best!
[Their plan is to go
as much as possible.]
- That's good!
- You're sill too far!
Wow, I can tell you're close.
[Hong Ki does a run-up...]
What time is it, Mr. Wolf?
Meal time!
[Meal time came too fast!]
[Ha Ha the lamb turns around.]
He truly looks like a lamb.
I feel sorry for him!
He looks like an impala in a meadow.
[Kkuk stalks his prey again]
[just like a lion who
rules the grassland.]
[His target is poor Ha Ha today.]
Run away!
[You might be able to
survive by running.]
Come over here.
[Ha Ha is cornered.]
[Kkuk slowly corners Ha Ha...]
[and pounces at him.]
[The is the law of nature.]
The lamb who left his group
becomes the prey of the lion.
He shouldn't have left the group.
He ended up...
[Ha Ha is ousted.]
I feel so bad for him.
The lamb who left his group
becomes the prey of the wolf.
[Lesson learned.]
The wolf is satisfied now.
But the wolf seeks another lamb.
- How many rounds do we have?
- If you win this round, you're done.
Is that so?
What do I do?
Show him off!
Should I let them live once?
He's so cute!
- He's cute!
- He's annoying!
Let's be positive.
We don't have to play
against him after this game.
- That's right.
- Just think about that.
It's a good thing.
Let's send him away.
[I'll do my best, then.]
Meal time!
[Kkuk versus Yong Hwa]
[Kkuk makes a spurt
at the last minute.]
[But he missed Yong Hwa
by the split of a hair.]
[The lambs win the game
for the first time.]
[Yong Hwa manages to lose Kkuk
with incredible speed.]
Mr. Wolf, you'll be done
after this round.
All you have to do for the
rest of the day is move your snout.
- Snout?
- Because you're a wolf.
- It's a mouth.
- Snout is a mouth.
- He has to do it.
- One more step left.
You should fly.
[Operation human slingshot]
[What will happen this time?]
Let's count to three.
One, two...
[He needs to eliminate
the wolf's name tag.]
- three!
[Fire!]
- He's too far.
- He can't make it.
Is it going to be me again?
This is your last chance, Yong Hwa!
It's like a penalty kick.
It's either of the two.
Yong Hwa,
at least punch him in the side.
How about a piggy back?
- How?
- No, it's impossible.
- He can jump.
- It's easy to say it.
It's not possible.
I'll die an honorable death.
Get your breath back, Yong Hwa.
Just think of it as a piggy back ride!
You're dead meat!
[What a big accident!]
- Jong Kook is upset!
- I'm not.
It's fine, Yong Hwa.
[Goodbye, Yong Hwa!]
He won't eliminate you gently!
Run fast!
You might be able to survive.
This is the last round, Yong Hwa.
[Hong Ki is ready for a dead run.]
- Do your best!
Just give up, Yong Hwa.
Are you ready?
What time is... it, Mr. Wolf?
I'm getting nervous!
- It's is thrilling.
- You never know.
[This meal time will decide
the outcome of the game.]
I think Jong Kook is nervous, too.
I'll run really fast this time.
[Wait and see.]
[You don't have to do that...]
Yong Hwa's dead.
Meal time!
[Run for your life!]
[Kkuk runs at full speed.]
[Kkuk's target is Yong Hwa.]
[Will Kkuk eliminate
Yong Hwa's name tag?]
[Or will Yong Hwa escape first?]
[Yong Hwa succeeds at escaping.]
- You did it!
[It was concluded in four seconds.]
[The lambs win by a nose.]
We've defeated the wolf!
[Kkuk and Yong Hwa's chase will go
down in Running Man's history.]
I should have caught
them in the beginning.
[Yong Hwa saved the lambs.]
- We won!
You're amazing, Yong Hwa.
We did it!
This is for the winner
of the first game.
'What time is it, Mr. Wolf?'
We've got the Singapore card.
Jong Kook won't be able to play.
No, he can't.
He's useless.
What?
Didn't you see what I did?
- You should have won the first game.
- You saw it.
But Jong Kook was the
right person for this game.
[The Global Mission Tour]
What will be the next game?
- It's 'the World Tour'.
- The World Tour?
It fits us.
We've done world tours before.
We need to win this time.
A world tour is a must
for Hallyu stars.
We need to win the game
in the beginning.
We shouldn't let them win.
If you think you'll
be good at this game
don't hesitate.
- Okay.
- We need to win.
[The Global Mission Tour]
['C' cafe in Kimpo]
The second mission of the
Hallyu race is 'the World Tour' game.
We've bundled the games
the fans sent us.
[It's time to see different
games of the world.]
Why don't we just play
the name tag elimination?
We can play it all day long.
The name tag elimination
for all the rounds.
You're something else.
This is why Suk Jin wants to
be a cryopreserved patient.
- Why?
- He wants to revive when you're 80.
I'm looking into the procedure.
So, he can physically overpower you.
By the way, people worry
the lab technician might
accidentally turn the
knob to 'refrigerate'.
Suk Jin will end up getting old
and revive in 30 years.
- And he caught a cold.
- A refrigerated patient.
Jiao Hanggai from Inner Mongolia
suggested this game of trust.
Ni Hao.
The key point is trust.
One member falls from 3 or 4 meters
high and the other members catch him.
- What?
- From 3 meters high?
Are you sure it's a game of trust?
Where do we fall from?
3 or 4 meters down?
I wonder if this person
watched Running Man...
It's not a mixed martial arts.
On the ground?
We're not going to play this.
It's what they've suggested.
We're not going to play it.
[They're at about 3 meters
above the ground floor.]
You're not going to fall from here.
Mae Katrina from the
Philippines suggested this.
Climb up a slippery bamboo tree
and catch the flag that is 10 meters
high with your bare hands.
They're joking, aren't they?
- Calm down!
[They're games made for Spider-Man.]
We're not superheros.
Katrina, you have a incredible idea.
But please don't think
we have super powers.
Did you really think
I went against time?
- I think it might be fun.
[Are you sane?]
All kinds of games
from all over the world.
We really appreciate
that you love us so much.
One member from the team of three...
It's either Il Woo or the pond skater.
[The pond skater
with long arms and legs.]
Their ace unexpectedly lost the game.
- It hit them hard.
- I didn't think we'd lose.
Il Woo will play this time.
[Il Woo's been doing Pilates.]
There are seven games here.
Please pick one.
Pick a good one.
- What is it?
- Are you usually lucky?
[What will be the first game
for their second mission?]
What is this?
- Bottle fishing?
- I know what it is.
This game is suggested by
Try Desyant Oppieta
from Indonesia and other...
I love Try Desyant Oppieta.
people from Asian countries.
Place a rope with a pencil
around your waist.
The pencil stays
at the back like a tail.
Place an empty bottle on the floor
and try putting the pencil in.
You win when you
lift the bottle first.
Who's going to play this?
Do you want to go first, Hong Ki?
- You'll go first?
- It's difficult.
You have to make it lower.
For the team of three to win
you'll have to beat four people
from the team of seven.
The bottle has to be
lifted for three seconds.
- It is possible, right?
- Of course.
- Show it off, Hong Ki.
- Yes.
Show it to Try Desyant Oppieta.
Let's win.
I know Il Woo is not
good at games like this.
- Don't listen to him.
- I'll show him.
Show it off.
[Hong Ki vs. Il Woo]
Do it slowly.
[Hallyu idol, Hong Ki vs.
Hallyu actor Il Woo.]
- Hong Ki!
- Move forward.
That's good.
[That was close.]
You said you have problems
with your bidet, Hong Ki.
- Lift it now!
- He almost did it.
[Almost in?]
[Will Il Woo possibly...]
[win this game now?]
- Just a little bit.
- Lower, lower.
[It landed on the neck.]
You did it, Il Woo!
Lift it now!
[He lifted it.]
[He lost it.]
[A brief moment of
cockiness ruined it.]
Move forward, Hong Ki.
[It's thrilling for the watchers.]
It drives me crazy!
Now!
[He did it again.]
Who thought of a game like this?
One, two, three!
[Il Woo succeeds at bottle fishing.]
I'm sorry.
[Depressed Hong]
How did you do it, Il Woo?
The next runner.
- Let me do it.
- Okay.
[Jae Suk vs. Il Woo]
[5 years of Running Man experience vs.
A Pilates Boy's flexibility.]
It's one to zero.
Ready, set...
I think you can do it.
Put it in!
He's good at it.
- Did he put it in?
- Not yet.
- Lower.
- Don't shake it.
Now!
- It's in!
[He lifted...]
[He loses it again.]
[Jae Suk's fishing line goes in.]
[Power lifting]
- One, two...
One, two, three!
[Jae Suk succeeds
at bottle fishing.]
[Jae Suk celebrates it
with his hip dance.]
[Fired up!]
- That's nice!
Look at this!
This is how you play it.
Il Woo, you're in trouble.
Just like this.
It's okay, Il Woo.
This is good!
- Go away!
- What did you say?
What did you say?
Cheer up, friend!
We're on the upturn!
Let's decide who'll go next.
Why is he playing now?
[Just trust me.]
I think I can do it quickly.
Suk Jin is pretty good at it.
- Ready!
- Let's go!
Set, go!
Don't worry about him.
Suk Jin's pencil seems like it's weak.
- It reached.
- My aim is good.
- It went in.
- Now!
Go little further.
You did it!
One, two, three!
Okay!
[Il Woo does it easily.]
What is he doing?
You broke the upturn.
No, he was very fast this time.
- He was fast.
- Bring it on.
[Holding his head high.]
Bring it on!
He's smiling again.
He is 'il-hee il-bee.'
(Now glad, now sad)
[Introducing Jung Il Hee.]
(Now glad)
[Introducing Jung Il Bee.]
(Now sad)
Show him, Yong Hwa.
I was born for Running Man.
How many times was Yong Hwa
on here, 16 times?
It's his 12th time.
It's my 12th mission.
Is he a regular member?
He has won more than Suk Jin.
[An inconvenient truth for Suk Jin.]
Look at Hong Ki.
He looks sad that he lost.
[Depressed Hong.]
He didn't play an active role today.
- He feels bitter.
[I wanted to do it well.]
Ready!
Set!
[Two adventurers have
met at the bottle fishing!]
Set, go!
Il Woo is very good.
- He's getting used to it.
- Lower, lower!
[Il Woo puts it in.]
[Yong Hwa puts it in, too.]
[It's neck and neck!]
[Who will win this round?]
[Il Woo lifts up first.]
[Jung Il Woo wins by a hair.]
One, two, three!
Okay!
[We're proud of you,
Jung Il Woo!]
It was really close.
I missed it by a second!
- He did it really well, though.
- You did well.
Bring it on!
Because of Suk Jin,
the upturn is ruined.
Bring it on!
We need to take it back.
The pencil reaches to the neck
when you bend your knees.
[Blessed by his height.]
- Wow, it's close.
Wait, that's too low.
Your belt is too low.
- Your pelvis can't be that low.
- This is my pelvis.
I take after my mom's family.
The belt is touching his bottom.
Wear it on your pelvis.
He says it's his pelvis.
Why are you saying it's not?
It's my mom's family.
Il Woo, you will win the first game
if you win this round.
- Will it really happen?
- This is the last round, Il Woo.
He's Il-hee Il-bee guy.
Don't worry.
Don't be too serious.
[The ridiculous competitive
spirit of his.]
I'm very competitive.
He's well balanced
because of the Pilates.
- That's the effect of Pilates.
- We should have practiced it, too.
Ha Ha's pencil is already
touching the bottle.
Great!
You need to win, Ha Ha.
[Goal in.]
[He lost it.]
[Il Woo's pencil went in properly.]
[It's going to take off.]
[Il Woo wins the bottle fishing.]
- He's too good.
- It makes me so mad!
[The team of three wins
the bottle fishing game.]
I'm not the only who lost it.
- Hong Ki.
- He's too good!
[He dances out of joy.]
Suk Jin played the game
without discussing with us.
He totally broke the upturn.
As a leader of the team, I order you
to take a break for the next game.
It doesn't even make sense!
You'll need me.
You can't do that.
He has to play for us.
This is my team's matter.
- He needs to play.
- Mind your own business!
You know how popular I am?
He must play!
- What's next?
- Please pick another one.
- I'm upset.
- Let's beat Il Woo.
Let's say 'woo.'
(boo)
Jung Il Woo. (Boo)
I have a good feeling.
Yellow is nice.
Your face will turn yellow soon.
This time, it's from the United States.
- The zombie game.
- Zombie?
The zombie game is suggested
by Julie Chung from the United States.
Il Woo will be a zombie.
He will wear an eye patch and bite all
seven people's arms and oust them
within two minutes.
You will have to stay on
the blue mat.
Is it okay if he bites off some flesh?
Of course, he's the zombie.
He'll wear lipstick,
and it will leave a mark.
[Il Woo the zombie
with Red lips appears.]
I'll throw away the
one who's bitten.
Please count the blood as lipstick
when someone's bitten.
Are the stork and the muscle man here
doing something for this game?
The stork and the muscle man?
- Move away.
- I will.
- Get ready!
[Second Mission: The Zombie Game]
Get set...
Go!
Put your arms out!
[Waving his arms in the air
even though the space is very small]
He's really bad!
He stepped outside of the mat!
[The producers were originally concerned
that this game might be over in 30 seconds...]
- You must oust those who step out!
[But no one is out still!]
- Turn around!
[What kind of zombie is so relaxed?]
What the heck are you doing, Il Woo?
Do you know how much time
has passed?
What are you doing?
- Hey, Il Woo!
[Waving]
Go away, it's me!
[He looks more like a sad
neighborhood boy than a zombie]
Push them into one corner!
- Are you playing hide-and-seek?
[Trying to rely on his ears]
[To no avail]
He got one!
Bite him!
[Ha Ha becomes the first victim of
the slow zombie]
[I'm still hungry!]
He got one!
[This is a big one!]
[He catches Yong Ha the Ace]
[Hurling to the ground]
[Yong Hwa is out!]
[Five people remaining]
Go that way!
They're getting angry!
One minute remaining.
[Only one minute remaining after
ousting only two...]
You can't give up already!
Get up!
Get up and run!
It's me, Il Woo.
Go the other way.
[Caught one!]
[Big Nosed Brother is out!]
[Four people remaining]
[Survivors: Jae Suk, Gary,
Ji Hyo, Hong Ki]
I think we won this.
- Hit the corners, Il Woo!
- We won!
- This way, Il Woo!
[Kwang Soo guides Il Woo by clapping]
[As he focuses everything on his ears...]
[He gets very tired]
Get up, Il Woo!
Come here!
[A special treat for a terrible zombie]
[Serving Jae Suk live]
Bite!
[All the stress accumulated
from this round...]
[I will release it at once!]
Ouch!
[The zombie bites Giraffe
instead of the grasshopper!]
[Time over]
- We won!
[With four survivors, Team of Seven wins!]
That was not easy.
This one was difficult.
Anyway, thanks Julie!
[Thank you for your great idea, Julie!]
[Are you watching this, Julie?]
The score is one to one right now.
Are you crying, Il Woo?
[Angry Il Woo appears!]
So you're not even gonna talk?
He's not even responding to you.
He's very angry!
- Are you angry?
- You're the one who just bit people.
- Look at my team members!
- Are you annoyed?
- He's tired!
[Let's play the next round right now.]
- I said he's tired!
[Protecting his player]
- Why is he angry?
[They're too scared to play the next round.]
We'll just beat them again!
[Team of Three won the third round of
untying tangled earphones.]
Make it our last game!
[Team of Seven: 1, Team of Three: 2]
From Hong Kong...
Water Gun All Kill!
This is submitted by
Mr. Ho Chun Leung from Hong Kong.
This will be one-on-one type game.
Each person will run to the table to grab
the water gun and hit the other person.
There'll be one water gun
and one pot lid as a shield.
One point for the shooter
if he gets the other person.
One point for the blocker
if he defends himself.
- Il Woo only needs to get four people.
[The team that gets four points wins!]
- No problem, right?
[This won't be easy]
Gary is fast, so he should go first.
Then Hong Ki...
Then Yong Ha...
Let's win this.
I don't feel too confident
about this one.
Just beat them.
- Just put it like this.
- Wait.
[The leaders are fighting over
the position of the water gun.]
If you put it like this,
it's easier to grab from this side!
So then give it to me.
- Do it like this!
[Then make it stand!]
- We must be fair!
- This is fair!
Fighting!
- Ready!
- Leaders, please stand in the middle.
[First Round]
[Gary vs. Il Woo]
[Burning]
Go!
[Splash]
- I got him!
- I blocked it!
- He got hit first.
[Gary loses by a split second]
Great!
[Team of Seven 0:1 Team of Three]
Great strategy!
Il Woo was pretending to
grab the lid first!
- Hong Ki!
[Hong Ki vs. Il Woo]
[I'll show something this time]
We've conceded a lot this time.
[Come on...]
Go!
[Hong Ki grabs the water gun!]
- Got it!
[But Il Woo blocks it perfectly!]
[Depressed Hong again...]
It's okay.
It's not that you're bad.
Are you okay? What have
you done to my dear Hong Ki?
[Blocking Hong Ki's future while
blocking his attack...]
Hong Ki is very enthusiastic when he
begins, but after his games...
He tries hard!
[His beginnings are always grand...]
[But his ends are always inglorious.]
I'm sorry!
[At least in this game...]
[I wanted to do well...]
[Today's very long for Depressed Hong!]
Next!
- Yong Hwa!
- Let's go, Yong Hwa!
[Payback time!]
[Come on!]
Relax a bit!
He's so intense!
- Ready...
- Look at his glare...
Go!
We got him!
[Yong Hwa didn't pull the trigger]
- Shoot now!
- He has to shoot!
Go again!
Replay!
- We won this round!
- No, this is undetermined.
- No, we won!
- This is vague.
[You're the one that didn't shoot!]
Do it again!
This is nonsense!
Hey, don't do it again!
Are you going to hit me?
Then hit me!
Then come with me.
I need a camera!
Follow me!
- I need a camera!
[Save me, camera!]
You have to do it right!
You were supposed to
follow me!
So, 3:0?
- What are you doing?
- We have to do it again.
- We won!
- It's not certain.
It was certain.
It was very certain.
Let's do it again.
Il Woo lifted this,
and he lifted that!
- That's a round!
- But Yong Hwa didn't shoot!
Come with me!
- Jae Suk!
[Save the Big-nosed Brother!]
Cameramen!
Follow them!
[They'd live in fear
if cameras were not around...]
He didn't pull the trigger!
[He objects with his back turned]
- Fine, then...
- Don't touch it, mister!
- At least we can do this.
[The game should be fair...]
- This is not in the middle...
- Hey...
Do you want to come?
[At a loss for words]
[Where is he trying to bring
these men to?]
- You should just go with him and see.
- My pride is hurt.
Why don't you just go?
Let's see what happens.
My teammates need me,
so I can't leave right now.
[No rematch]
[Team of Seven 0:3 Team of Three]
They arrived almost at the same time.
[Team of Three only needs
one more win]
- This should come this way...
- This has to be aligned here!
- Do you see this cross?
- But it's near here.
[Big Nosed Brother is moving
the starting line]
- What's the score right now?
- 3:0!
- We only need one more win!
[Absolutely clueless]
[The construction work is done
after moving the line about a foot ahead]
[An obvious difference]
[Ours is an alleyway
while theirs is a highway!]
Let's go!
[Ji Hyo vs. Il Woo]
You're on this round?
Just wrap it up!
If you win, you'll take this round.
Just go cry, Ji Hyo.
- Fighting!
[Startled]
Wait!
- It already started!
- There's no waiting!
It's your fault for not catching his
foot crossing the starting line!
Will you really not focus on
the game like this?
I'm focused!
Go!
[Strolling away after
flipping the water gun]
Are you grilling a fish or something?
It was about time to flip it.
Fighting, Ji Hyo!
You'll be fine.
Get ready...
Go!
[What just happened?]
What are you doing, punk?
[Sister Ji Hyo just watered
Il Woo flower in full bloom.]
Have we won or lost?
I'm sorry, Il Woo!
She just cleaned Il Woo's teeth!
[Why are we filming a romance
variety show all of a sudden?]
She really cleaned his teeth.
Things like that are not cool these days.
It worked maybe ten years ago...
You have to shoot at
people to be cool these days!
I think he did that because
he could afford it...
Don't say sorry!
[Ha Ha vs. Il Woo]
- Get ready!
- We can just win the rest of this!
Great!
[Team of Seven's newfound confidence.]
[Kook saw it!]
[I knew this would happen...]
[I didn't know we'd be caught so fast...]
[Kook came all the way to tell him
not to step on the start line.]
[What kind of dumb luck is this?]
Why?
What is it?
- Let's go!
- No stepping on the line!
Don't step on the line!
Go!
[They can't lose when
they're already a foot ahead...]
[Team of Seven 2:3 Team of Three]
[At this pace, Team of Seven
might be able to flip the game!]
Oddly, I feel like even
I'll be able to win.
What is that?
Why is it so close?
- Why is it so close?
[Finally discovered]
- What's going on here?
[Busy bees]
- I don't know what you're talking about.
[Lies galore]
Then we can do it again.
What do you want us to do?
[Come with me...]
It's still 3:2.
What is going on here?
- What do you want us to do?
- Bring me a tape measure.
- I need a tape measure!
- That's not necessary!
Fine, measure it again!
- Measure it!
[Using Giraffe's hand for now]
Five and a half hands!
Check it!
Do it here!
It's not that much.
[Squish]
- I didn't see you.
[What kind of mishap is this?]
We can just measure it again.
[The starting line for Team of Seven looks
closer, but they're letting it slide this time.]
We can switch sides if you want.
Okay!
Let's do it.
Why the heck would you say that?
- That was a great idea!
[Let's move before they change their minds!]
Suk Jin is the player this time too.
Why is this place so far?
It's amazing that you've won
this many rounds from here!
- Get ready!
[Forget him]
Hold on...
What?
It's just my heel.
Hold on...
What?
It's just my heel.
[There are so many weird
tricks in this world...]
Professional sprinters
lift their feet like this too!
This is how he runs!
It's his style!
- Fine, don't step on it though.
[They agreed to respect his style]
This is my style.
I walk like this.
You people...
[Il Woo vs. Big-nosed Brother]
Ready...
Go!
[Il Woo easily wins, as expected.]
[What's wrong with this guy?]
Foul!
[Hit his knee!]
[I'm dying now!]
- He's injured!
[Team of Seven 2:4 Team of Three]
[Team of Three wins the game!]
Does this double as an X-ray machine?
[World Tour Game Mission is over!]
- We lost.
- It was a difficult victory.
We won thanks to Il Woo!
[Team of Three gets a very useful
'Country Hint' for the final mission.]
How did you know, Kwang Soo?
What?
What is it?
Is it not a country?
Share it.
It says "World."
We gave you that because you played the
games that came from all around the world.
[How will this hint be used?]
Don't forget your card.
Please move onto the next mission.
Well done!
[Korea]
[Tanhyeon SBS]
We have to find it quickly, Hong Ki!
Please move quickly.
[Team of Seven look rushed.]
[They're looking for something
in a hurry.]
We must find it quickly.
Go here.
- Did you look here before?
[What are they trying to find?]
[Ring, ring]
[All of a sudden, the sound of a bell?]
[Someone's chasing them
with a bell!]
We're in danger!
Run faster!
[The chaser is...]
[Jung Il Woo!]
Run fast!
This is the final mission of the Hallyu Race.
There were a lot of fans who
submitted this idea...
3 vs 7 Bell Hide-and-seek!
[Suddenly happy]
We're going to have bells on us?
[Shaking of joy]
Is this going to be okay for them?
Run faster!
You should live at least!
Your opposing players will put
bells on them and hunt you down.
[Oh, my God!]
Why are there bells involved
every time I come on this show?
- Not the bells...
- Mr. Producer...
Your mission is to find English letters
hidden in this building...
And spell out "Running Man."
Running Man...
There are ten letters.
R, U, N, N, I, N, G, M, A, N.
Once you have all the letters, you must
put them together on the platform outside.
That'll constitute your victory.
So our name tags don't matter?
[Team of Three can't be ousted even
if they lose their name tag.]
- You're truly blessed.
[They have to oust the other seven.]
Not having such pressure on you
will get you an extra year of life!
Seriously.
You get two years if you're on the
same team as Jong Kook.
- You came to the right team.
[Welcome to the bell attackers!]
So far, you've gained
the Singapore card...
You get the letter 'G' from it.
Then, the other one is...
USA...
[Ah... U.S.A...]
I'm so scared!
[The third mission that was based on
the idea of Mr. Aaron Whithing of USA.]
[The Musical Square, where
the unlucky one falls.]
[Kwang Soo did his best, but...]
[He couldn't beat the Goddess of Luck!]
The second letter is "A" from U.S.A.
So you have two letters so far.
[Team of Three has an "R"
from "World."]
- Right here...
[Team of Three is hiding their letter]
Under the water tray?
We can put it in like this...
[They chose a spot under
the water tray of a water purifier.]
This is a good idea.
They're probably hiding the letter
at a very difficult spot.
The key right now is finding their letter.
We don't have to renovate
the whole place to find it, right?
Let's not do that.
The rest is up to fate.
[The victory...]
We can win!
Fighting!
[Depends on fate!]
- Can we really win?
- Of course.
[Will the Running Man Alphabet
be completed?]
[3 vs 7 Bell Hide-and-seek]
[Start!]
Let's hurry and find them.
We must find them early on.
[They must move quickly before
Team of Three starts]
These bells sound scary.
[The clear sound of bells that
will instill fear in the opposition]
Please say something if
anyone has found anything.
[No!]
[Already nearby?]
Turn off the light!
[Heart beating]
[Screaming internally]
[Hiding under someone else's blanket.]
[Just patrolling the hallways
is scaring them.]
Quickly and accurately.
- Did you see everywhere?
- I don't think it's here.
- Did you go this way?
[Yong Hwa is looking with Gary.]
- Yes, I did.
- Then we should go down.
[Then!]
[Great!]
[The sound of the bell!]
[The hunt begins!]
We're in danger!
Run faster!
[He already caught up!]
At least you have to live!
They're here!
- They're coming!
[Kook is on the other end of the hallway.]
We're surrounded.
[Surrounded by Kkuk and Il Woo.]
[The nightmare scenario ensues.]
- At least you should live!
- Grab anyone!
[Grabbed]
[They try their best...]
[But they're both caught]
- I'm sorry...
- At least one of us should live!
I'm sorry.
[This is for real?]
[Enthusiastic Il Woo's
early hunt is greatly successful!]
[Team of Seven just lost their
two important members.]
I should've just sacrificed myself.
Jung Yong Hwa, Gary, out!
- What should we do now?
[Mass panic]
[This place is no joke...]
The bells...
They're everywhere.
[Startled]
- Hey...
[It's Hong Ki]
Why are there bells everywhere?
It's a chaos over there.
We've lost two people already.
Hello.
[Big-nosed Brother walks into
the costume room.]
I don't think they'll come to this side.
[He found an alphabet box!]
- I found one!
[He got an "N."]
I've found an "N."
Awesome!
Where did you find it?
On the first floor.
Wow...
Why are there...
- Bells everywhere?
[On repeat over and over again]
How can we find so many letters?
[Huh?]
- I found it.
[A box was hidden in a teddy bear!]
I found an "M."
Well done.
M...
That means we have four now.
Six more to go.
They gave us two, and we've found two.
At least four so far.
[Il Woo is back to hunting]
[Getting some water first]
I'm exhausted.
[Huh?]
[No!]
[He didn't see me, did he?]
[Creaking]
[A sound came from that side...]
[He's coming...]
[He's coming!]
[Mother!]
- Run, Ji Hyo, run!
[Blank Ji is his target]
[I'm sorry, Ji Hyo...]
[Blank Ji tries her best to run...]
[But she couldn't go far.]
[I'll be quick, Ji Hyo.]
Let's not do this!
I can't!
[No mercy from this guy!]
[Song Ji Hyo, out!]
He's so competitive...
[My team is in jeopardy...]
Song Ji Hyo, out!
Ji Hyo is out?
Did you oust her, Il Woo?
- Yes.
- Really?
You're unstoppable!
[His laugh is even scarier.]
- I'm just walking around.
- Why?
I can't see anyone.
How can I just be walking around
alone like an invisible man?
[Big-nosed Brother is going
to another building.]
This is driving me crazy!
[The cameraman hit something.]
You startled me!
[No!]
[It's really startling this time!]
[Caught Big-nosed Brother
at the speed of light!]
- I'll give you some information.
- Like what?
If I help you to catch Jae Suk,
will you let me go?
Where are you, Jae Suk?
[I'm sorry Jae Suk,
but you'll have to sacrifice...]
Where are you, Jae Suk?
[Every single cell in his body is
telling him not to answer this call...]
- Who do you want?
- You're abandoned by the team.
That's not true.
I love you, Suk Jin.
Ji Suk Jin, out.
- He's really trying hard.
[Il Woo's stellar ousting surprises Kkuk.]
Where could it be?
- I must do something too.
[Giraffe has contributed 0% to his team.]
How did I get caught here?
- Hey...
- I'm already out.
You're the first blue team member
I've seen so far.
I'm just aimlessly walking around.
- You saw no one?
- No one.
- Il Woo got you?
- He got everyone.
- All four of them so far...
- Where is Jong Kook?
- Jong Kook is walking around too.
- In the main building?
- I guess I haven't seen him either.
[Kkuk is staying in the main building]
Jong Kook in the main building!
Kwang Soo is in between
the main building and the annex.
[It took some time for
Giraffe to catch on]
Il Woo is in the annex.
- Let go of my radio!
[Give me your radio!]
I'm already out!
- Why are you taking this away?
[Fighting someone who's already out]
Hey, hey!
[I'm going to hunt too!]
Oh, my God!
[He almost fainted because
he was startled by the same team.]
You're okay.
You're on my team.
- Stand up.
[This must be how the other team feels.]
[Meanwhile, Team of Seven is...]
[Peeking]
Not here.
This might be a good place to hide it.
But they didn't.
This is really scary.
I can just keep hearing those bells.
- Am I hearing things now?
[The side effect of this game: Auditory illusion]
I keep hearing the bells.
[That one is real!]
[That way!]
[Jae Suk runs opposite of
the bell sound.]
[Running to the costume room.]
[Barely got away...]
[Could it be...]
Mr. Yoo Jae Suk?
[Were you hiding there?]
[His thick arm comes in]
I knew because I heard the door.
- But really...
- There's no way out...
Are you trying to push
this door right now?
I don't have any other way.
- But are you really trying right now?
- I can't go anywhere else now!
Excuse me, sir...
- Are you really trying your best?
[Really sad]
I'm sorry, but...
You do realize how obnoxious
you were today, right?
Are you going to hit me?
Hit me, then!
I need a camera!
Follow me!
[He didn't know it would all
come down to this...]
My team must win!
- You can't!
- We must win!
No!
I feel lucky.
See you later!
Gwon Yeol...
Why did you shut the door so hard?
Why are you even more
scared than me?
I'm scared too...
Yoo Jae Suk, out!
[The only hopes left are
Haroro and Hong Ki.]
[They must quickly find the other letters
to complete "Running Man!"]
[I've missed you, alphabet!]
I found it at a nonsensical place.
[Five letters remaining]
[Riding on this wave to the next letter...]
Oh, my God!
[Finds Kkuk right after finding a letter.]
This shouldn't be the way.
[I think I'm next, Hong Ki...]
I felt like you'd be here.
- Open the door.
[Kwang Soo joins]
[His first time seeing a surviving
member of the opposition.]
You don't have to be here.
Go.
[Feeling small]
- They're avoiding me.
[Still zero contribution today.]
No, you can't!
[Devastating]
There's no need for this.
[With a sad scream,
Ha Ha is out.]
Ha Ha, out.
I'm the only one left?
Where are these letters?
[I'm the only one I can trust!]
[I have to find five letters by myself]
[Huh?]
[He needs four more to win!]
Wait!
G.NA, the singer!
[Talking about G.NA
in this urgent situation...]
[Meanwhile, Il Woo the Hunter is...]
[Going back to check on
the letter he hid.]
They'll never find that one.
[Will Hong Ki be able to find it?]
[And the arena is full of beasts.]
[Not just one...]
[But two beasts!]
Could it be in here?
[Where is he hiding?]
- It was you?
[Giraffe is still useless]
[Where are you, Hong Ki?]
[Somewhere near here!]
[Peeking]
[Someone there?]
[I felt like someone on the other team.]
[Bells on the other side?]
[I finally got you!]
[Catch me if you can!]
[Is he successfully getting away?]
[Kwang Soo, who was on the
other side, catches Hong Ki!]
[For someone who didn't do
anything all day...]
- What is going on?
[This can make up for the whole thing!]
Hold on...
- He's there?
[Kkuk joins late.]
I almost got away...
- It's finally over!
[Proud of catching Hong Ki]
- I heard you guys.
[Proud of his teammates]
We've been looking for you, Hong Ki.
Like how the newlyweds cut
their cake together at a wedding...
Let's do it all together!
One, two, three!
[Team of Three wins the
Global Mission Tour!]
[The victory ceremony]
[Completion of Running Man]
It really is Running Man of the world.
That looks great!
[The ideas of our fans,
both from Korea and abroad...]
It lights up!
[Have come to fruition!]
This is great!
Most importantly, we thank everyone who
sent the game ideas to us for today...
Our fans in Korea and around the world...
Thank you from the bottom
of our hearts!
We had a lot of fun today
thanks to them.
Again, thank you everyone!
Thank you!
Subtitles by DramaFever
- This is my kind of place.
[Old places with memories...]
I had dates here.
He used to work at a Karaoke joint.
I used to go there.
So today's over if
everyone's out?
[All kill!]
[All out!]
- Where are we going?
[They'll lose their tag if they get lost]
We're surrounded!
Where is Boramae?
- I need a bridge stick!
- I can help.
This is not a real pool game.
[Playing old games
while reminiscing about old times!]
Letters, sometimes...
That's X-rated.
I have it.
It'll make your nose bleed.
- Just like the old times!
[Old places of popular stars]