[The time capsule that contains
our dreams and friendship.]
[But...]
[Someone stole those dreams?]
[The identity of a black hand
that destroys their friendship.]
[Don't trust anyone!]
[The Secret Alumni]
Today, you're here
to bury a time capsule
with new students
who are as pretty as flowers.
- They're pretty!
- There are four girls!
It seems like a group blind date!
They're wearing uniforms!
It's exciting!
- They're almost here.
- By the way there are four girls.
- Park Ye Jin!
- My heart is fluttering.
[The four flower girls, F4.]
[F1, Park Ye Jin.]
[F2, Yoon Jin Seo.]
[F3, Shin Se Kyung.]
[F4, Song Ji Hyo.]
[Welcome to Running High!]
[Everyone's excited to see them.]
Nice to meet you Jin Seo.
We've met Se Kyung and Ye Jin before.
- This is the first time seeing you.
- This is the first time being here.
He hasn't changed at all!
- That's not it!
[Just the same as 'Family Outing.']
It's in the song lyrics, too.
A woman you don't know is beautiful.
A woman you met for the first time.
It's been a long time, Se Kyung.
She's still pretty.
- What's your beauty secret?
- She's captivating.
- Thank you.
- You're prettier now.
The woman you met for the
second time.
How did you know that?
A woman we met for the first time,
the woman we haven't met for a while
the woman we used to see every week,
the woman we see very often.
Very distinctive.
I'll announce the partners you'll be
with for your high school journey.
- But there are four girls.
- We have more boys.
Which means we'll have a boys couple.
Why do you do that?
They are standing next to each other.
What are you talking about?
The Easy Brothers haven't been
together for a while.
You never know what will happen.
Yoon Jin Seo, who you met
for the first time will be...
- Jong Kook!
- Are you going to help Jong Kook?
the partner of Kim Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, find your lifetime partner
through Running Man.
- Get married!
- She's Jong Kook's type.
- He's acting differently today.
- Help Jong Kook.
Jin Seo, please
think of him as a man.
- You're his type.
- It's true.
Jong Kook seems nervous.
You look good together.
I always say this,
but he's an easy man.
Just tell him that you like him.
Don't make her feel uncomfortable.
Shin Se Kyung's partner will be...
I think it's me.
Who said that?
I have a good feeling.
- Is it Jae Suk?
- Gary thinks it's him.
That's right.
It's Gary.
- See? I was right.
- It really is Gary.
They can't be a couple anyway.
I'm getting worried.
This is not good.
Park Ye Jin's partner will be...
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Lee Kwang Soo and Park Ye Jin.]
What is this?
[How could it be?]
- I'm disappointed.
- What are you doing?
He's my prince.
- How can Ye Jin...
- Ji Hyo!
- I'll be nice to you.
I'm really close to her.
- We teamed up so many times.
- She's my best friend!
Get off of me!
Come here, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo is very beautiful today.
- Mister!
Why in English?
You are so beautiful to me.
It should be me.
Stop this already!
What do you mean stop?
I've been Suk Jin's partner
so many times.
I don't like you, either.
This is annoying!
Song Ji Hyo's partner is...
Who is it?
Ha Ha!
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo.]
[Jae Suk and Big-nose.]
Are we the expelled students?
Are we suspended from school?
We're gathered to bury
the time capsule today.
[Today is the day
to bury our the time capsule?]
We might bury you instead.
Be careful!
We're not very happy today.
We'll bury a time capsule
and open it in 10 years.
There happened to be
ten white stones here.
One stone for each of us?
Each of us will take a stone.
These will be our friendship stones.
Okay, let's do that.
Let's make a wish,
and put the stone in this box.
You first, Jae Suk.
I hope Jong Kook gets married soon.
What are you doing?
Suk Jin.
I want to invest in stocks...
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with you?
I can share the information with you.
What kind of a high school
student are you?
- You're corrupted already.
- Just do well yourself!
I wish Suk Jin will still be alive
to open these.
Why would you say that?
He'll be in his 20's.
I wish Jong Kook finds his
companion and settles down.
Why are you saying that?
- I wish this continues...
- He's shy.
Tell Jin Seo your heart.
All of a sudden, he looks serious.
Jin Seo...
I hope we stay the same
and see each other...
It's like he's proposing to her.
- even after ten years.
- I've never seen him like this before.
Hope you'll meet a good person.
[Oh no.]
- I just said he'll meet a good person!
- Wow, Jin Seo...
I wish everyone will be
happy and healthy.
This is how a high school
student should be.
- She has a heart of a girl.
- I mean it.
I agree with Se Kyung,
be happy and healthy.
Do high school students
talk like that?
- I agree with Se Kyung...
- It's Kwang Soo's turn.
- I wish everyone's dreams will come true.
- Ok!
Pop!
[The ten friendship stones.]
[See you in twenty years...]
- It's pretty soft.
- It's good!
[They buried it together...]
- Cover it.
- Let's pray for our dreams.
I hope they don't redevelop this area.
[The Running High's Warren Buffett,
Big-nose.]
Congratulations on your graduation!
- See you in ten years!
- Let's meet in ten years!
[The commemoration of our graduation.]
[Time passed by.]
[20 years later...]
[A reunion after 20 years.]
How have you been?
Let's dig up the time capsule!
- Is our friendship tree there?
- It's the same.
There were ten white stones.
Why does this sign look new?
[He dug it up so fast!]
- Be careful!
- I think it moved up near the surface.
I wonder if it's the same?
[How will the time capsule be?]
- It looks old.
[They opened it.]
It hasn't changed.
- One is missing!
- Are you sure?
[One is missing?]
[There are nine stones only?]
- Did someone dig it out first?
- Who took it?
- Who is it?
- One is missing?
- Someone must have dug it up.
[Someone broke their promise.]
- Who took it?
- We promised not to dig it up.
- No wonder.
Is one of us dead?
[Is this 'The Sixth Sense Race'?]
- Is there a ghost amongst us?
A ghost is among us!
You're the most suspicious one.
- Do you see what we don't see?
- No, no.
Just wait for me.
[The hand that seized the stone...]
[Whose hand will it be?]
I'm going to tell you the rules now.
Today's race is 'The Secret Alumni'
'The Culprit is Among Us!' race.
One of the stones that was
in the time capsule is missing.
That stone is a meteorite
and it's worth a fortune.
No wonder!
The culprit who knew where it was
buried is amongst you.
From now on,
you need to find the culprit.
You'll win if you reveal
who the culprit is
before the race is over.
You'll be awarded with the money
according to the meteorite's value.
A meteorite is expensive.
It's like winning the lottery.
You can spot someone as the culprit
at the end of each mission.
The first and the second
team will spot them.
If one of the two suspects
is the culprit
you will win the race.
We can end the race in one mission.
This means someone
touched the meteorite?
- Lee Kwang Soo is suspicious.
- I'm not the culprit!
The culprit will try
and win the missions.
- Is that you?
- I always try to win!
Someone who tries really
hard is the culprit.
- Being too quiet is suspicious, too.
- Se Kyung!
I think Se Kyung is the culprit.
[Who stole the meteorite?]
- We don't have mercy.
- We'll do our best.
We don't care who the culprit is.
We'll check during the break, too.
- Don't do anything suspicious!
- Se Kyung is suspicious.
She doesn't speak at all.
One of the guests might be the culprit.
- You're the most suspicious one.
- Why me?
We might find out right away.
See you soon.
- Yoon Jin Seo, you're suspicious!
- I'm watching you!
[Alone time with Jong Kook,
Jin Seo...]
- I feel relieved to be on your team.
- Really?
- Why? Are you the culprit?
- No, it's because you're good at games.
Are you nervous or something?
You don't want to get caught, right?
- I think you're a distrustful person.
- No, I'm not.
You're not the one, are you?
I don't even understand
what the rules are.
The rules weren't that complicated.
It's because you're used to
the games.
If it's you, I'll be shocked.
No, I'll be shocked if it's you.
- I'm serious.
- We're not the culprits, then.
- I'm not the culprit, seriously!
- Me, neither!
It could be one of the guests.
You think so?
I'm not the one.
- Really?
- I'm not.
Tell me ahead of time,
if I have to win a mission for you.
Do you think I'm the culprit?
If you're the culprit,
you have to win the missions.
- Am I wrong?
- I don't have to win.
[I'm not sure about Se Kyung.]
Trust me, Gary.
I kept trusting Kwang Soo
for three years...
and he tricked me all the time.
Now, I can't trust him in real life.
I'm too used to his lies.
[They're suspecting the female guests.]
[Is one of them the culprit?]
[While the members were
changing into their uniforms.]
[The meteorite was in
an unidentifiable hand.]
[Shin Se Kyung is
carrying the meteorite.]
- Can I just hide it in my clothes?
[Why would she?]
I'm really bad at this.
[Whose voice is that?]
I hate the mafia game the most.
[Park Ye Jin joined her?]
Me, too.
It just shows on my face.
Maybe the guys will
suspect each other.
[Even Yoon Jin Seo is here.]
Are we spies today?
[Song Ji Hyo, too?]
We're a team, right?
[They're the partners in crime.]
- Let's not betray each other.
[The female students have
teamed up to steal the meteor.]
Your mission is not to
get caught from the boys
and keep the stone until the end.
Then, you'll win this race.
When you win
you'll win millions of Wons,
the money worth it's value.
It's not millions of Wons
per person, isn't it?
We'll have to share it, right?
Se Kyung, since when
were you like this?
[Was she really a hidden card shark?]
Before all the missions are over
each of you have to have
a turn keeping the stone.
In short, let's say they doubt me
but we'll be fine if I give it to
someone else before I go up.
Who wants to keep it first?
[No one wants to be the first keeper.]
Rock, paper, scissors?
It feels like it's a bad thing to keep.
Let's give it to the winner first.
[It makes sense.]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Shin Se Kyung wins!]
Se Kyung!
I usually lose when I play this.
This is so funny!
Here it is.
[The first keeper is
Shin Se Kyung.]
[Will she be able to
defeat the pressure?]
Go, girls, go!
We're on the same team.
One, two, three!
Let's go!
[Boys vs. Girls.]
[Who will win the meteorite?]
[Currently, the meteorite is
in Shin Se Kyung's hand.]
[Will girls' meteorite relay
be successful?]
[Jin Seo with Mr. Capable is...]
- I want to survive with you.
I think you... are the culprit.
Pardon?
We're on the same team.
We shouldn't suspect each other.
That's right.
It's not that I'm suspecting you,
but you have to suspect everyone.
- I've been tricked by actresses.
- Oh, really?
Actresses are good at acting.
[Here's another one.]
- I think it's Se Kyung.
- Se Kyung?
She wasn't talking before
the meteorite was stolen.
All of a sudden...
But she's not very used
to variety shows.
It's possible that she started talking
just not to be suspected.
That's possible.
[Se Kyung is in danger!]
I don't think it's one person.
They told us to pick two suspects.
It might even be three people.
But it could be one person, too.
One person can easily get caught.
[He's sharp.]
- I was looking at Jin Seo.
I'm sure it's either
Se Kyung or Jin Seo.
They look suspicious to me.
Or even Ye Jin...
[How can I help Se Kyung?]
[The marked girl, Se Kyung is...]
- You're at a good age to date.
- Isn't it?
- That's right.
At your age, you say
'Good night, dream of me.'
I'd rather not date anyone.
You don't do that?
You're not the cutesy type?
I don't have child-like charms.
I think you do.
You just did it.
That's called acting cute.
You never said,
'Good night, dream of me'?
No, but isn't that too corny?
I said stuff like
'See you in my dreams.'
You've never did that?
Never?
You like to touch people
in a friendly way, right?
- Do I?
- I think you do.
I'm that type of person.
Men are simple.
They delude easily.
- Why is she doing this to me?
[Look who's talking.]
Especially, Kwang Soo does.
Try him.
- Does he like that kind of stuff?
- He'll text you when he gets home.
'Wasn't the shooting
too tiring for you?'
He might even feel responsible.
[How will she attack the simple men?]
[Suwon Worldcup
Artificial Grass Stadium]
Yoon Jin Seo is suspicious.
- It's not me.
- I'll pick you if I win.
- She's not.
- Park Ye Jin, are you not?
I don't think she's
likely to be the culprit.
She's not very competitive.
Wait until the battle begins.
[The meteorite keeper,
Se Kyung arrives.]
[She hid the meteorite in her pocket.]
[Will she be able to keep the secret?]
What is the mission?
The first game of 'The Secret Alumni'
is 'The retro sunflower.'
You will stand on each of
the petals of the sunflower
facing your partners.
One of the team members
has to get the mask in the middle
run to your partner,
and stand on the petal together.
You'll win when you wear the mask.
It's absolutely advantageous
for Jong Kook.
- Why do you think I'll win?
- We need to join forces!
[For this game, there will be
a lot of physical contact.]
Your mission is not to
get caught from the boys
and keep the stone until the end.
Then, you'll win this race.
[I didn't expect this...]
Do I have to fight again?
Should I play not too hard?
[Is it a time-out?]
- It's still suspicious either way.
You're already suspected.
I knew it.
They're really quick.
[Jae Suk is looking at us.]
- Just do what you can.
[They pretend that they chatted lightly.]
- I don't know.
[Thanks to Ye Jin, he doesn't doubt.]
- I don't think it matters where we stand.
[We need to be careful.]
It's about getting a rebound,
or going straight to the center.
Bad players will go to the center!
The men's round!
Go, Gary, go!
[The cutest cheer.]
[It's very effective!]
- Catch this, Se Kyung!
Catch what?
She said she doesn't do cute stuff.
But she does!
Ye Jin, try being cute!
She hates it the most.
- Try Ye Jin.
- Go, prince, go!
Where is the prince?
[Ye Jin's nasally voice melts down
the Prince of Asia's heart.]
Kwang Soo!
Ji Seo is next.
Come quickly!
I'll do my best.
He's going to go quickly.
Jin Seo has a quivering voice.
Go, Jae Suk, go!
Come here, honey!
This is clearly a business relationship.
- Come here, honey!
[Oh, my eyes!]
The men's round starts!
Gary seems like he will do his best.
[Giraffe catches the mask first.]
[The Giraffe tower.]
[Everyone is jumping
for the Giraffe tower.]
Make Kwang Soo sit!
The four of you can do it.
That's right.
No!
Kwang Soo, no!
[Ha Ha is fishing in troubled waters.]
[He runs straight to Ji Hyo.]
[Ha Ha wins the first round easily.]
- It's awesome!
- What happened?
- We did it!
- It's amazing.
- It's weird.
We need to watch for spies carefully.
- There's a reason that Ha Ha's desperate.
- I think they let me take it.
That's right.
We need to doubt the one
that plays too hard.
- Ha Ha is suspicious.
- We can't be lazy!
[She looks more calm and composed.]
[It's getting easier than I thought.]
- Go, Se Kyung, go!
[Gary's cute cheer!]
- Park Ye Jin! Park Ye Jin!
[The guys cheer for their partners.]
Go, team, go!
Yoon Seo Jin, don't get hurt!
Go, Se Kyung!
Even if you get hurt!
[By the way...]
[I don't have to worry
about the girls...]
[except this girl.]
[Will she be able to
guard the meteorite?]
Go!
[The women's round starts.]
[This round won't be tough
because they're accomplices...]
[What's happening?]
[She can't get too close.]
Se Kyung, try getting inside.
[I can't take the risk.]
[She kept staying away,
and she sits down.]
[Ye Jin grabs the chance.]
[Her desire for winning boosted up.]
[Help me!]
Park Ye Jin reveals her true self.
Look at Ye Jin!
You're so close, Ye Jin!
Now she looks like herself.
[She only thinks about winning.]
[Jin Seo is squeezed out.]
What are you doing, Jin Seo?
- What is she doing?
[She attacks with sand.]
[What is this?]
[What's wrong with her?]
[She sits gracefully and
keeps throwing sand.]
- What is she doing?
- She's unbelievable.
[The Big-nose power!]
It doesn't look cool at all.
Ji Suk Jin!
Get off!
- Kick him!
- He's not going to look cool.
- Grab his leg.
- Get off!
Wow, women...
Don't let go!
She stepped on it.
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin win.]
- Ye Jin is scary.
- It's scary.
[Ye Jin completely changes
her attitude when playing games.]
Are you okay?
Yoon Jin Seo!
[The human fork-lift.]
It was great!
Good job!
You haven't been on
many variety shows?
- It's my first time.
- Is it her first time?
Throwing out sand is
what the culprit would do.
[A growing doubt.]
- It's a dirty action.
When people are cornered...
[Ji Seo turns their doubt toward her.]
[Don't worry, Se Kyung.
I'll take the suspicion.]
Good! Jae Suk grabbed it.
[I'll do it for her!]
No, no!
- Here, here.
- Se Kyung!
[Come on!]
[They scream loudly,
but they stay the same.]
[The sunflower mask is ripped.]
- It's ripped!
What should we do?
I did it!
[It's not how you do it.]
[Kwang Soo holds Jong Kook's pants.]
[Again?]
[Ha Ha fishing in
troubled waters again!]
[Ha Ha was very quick to win.]
See?
We're a good team!
Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are the winners!
[They can point out the suspect.]
[I'm counting on you!]
[Ok! Don't worry.]
I think Jin Seo is hiding something.
It's not how you wear it.
Don't wear it like that!
You looked like a small octopus.
- This is not?
- She's strange.
- She's suspicious.
- But your head goes in from there?
- It's not big enough.
[It's as I planned.]
[Jong Kook and Jin Seo, Kwang Soo
and Ye Jin each scored one point.]
[The Tiger's rush!]
It's a foul!
He punched him!
He bit him.
[Everybody screams.]
- It's not even funny!
[Great number of zombies appear.]
They are zombies.
They're putting so much effort.
[Jae Suk puts his foot in the mask.]
[Even the viewers can feel the pain.]
[The mask is in the crotch
and he runs to Suk Jin.]
[But he gets dragged.]
[They fight for the mask.]
[At the moment all men
share the pain...]
You heartless bastards!
Kwang Soo, you're almost here.
[Just one more step...]
[He falls on the petal
and moves his legs quickly.
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin win.]
[They can point out the suspect.]
- It's over.
- You heartless bastards!
['The retro sunflower' is over.]
[The current meteorite
keeper, Se Kyung.]
It's time to point out the suspects.
Please check if there are
ten envelopes in your bags.
Two, four, six, eight...
It's correct.
Yes, I have.
I'll tell you how much
each envelope is worth later.
You wouldn't want to lose them.
The first and second winners
don't have to bet their envelopes
and you can point out the suspects.
You can all make deductions.
Even if you're not the real culprit
you'll lose five envelopes
when you're pointed out.
[Deduction time?]
[If she gets pointed at,
the game is over.]
I think Se Kyung is suspicious.
Se Kyung is suspicious...
[Se Kyung is in danger!]
[You got caught, Se Kyung!]
- Se Kyung didn't talk at all.
[She kept staying away
during the game play.]
[She's acting differently today.]
- Is there just one culprit?
- She's suspicious.
[Shin Se Kyung is in a crisis!]
Who do you think the culprit is?
I think it's Kwang Soo...
Let's pick Jin Seo.
I don't think she knows
what's going on.
Whoever we pick has to
give up five envelopes.
- I think Ye Jin is suspicious too.
- She's even more suspicious now.
You're really weird.
- Me?
- She's just being honest.
[Thank you, Jin Seo.]
Who wants to spot the culprit first?
We'll go first.
When I count to three,
say 'the person's name, get out!'
One, two, three!
Yoon Jin Seo, get out!
[He chooses Jin Seo.]
Jin Seo.
[I'm safe.]
Go to that side and stay.
The woman who threw the sand.
[She's celebrating with sand.]
What's with you?
She does it habitually!
She acts like a child.
I used to have friends like that
when I was young.
Open your bag
and give us back five envelopes.
- What a loss.
- But you were too suspicious.
It's fine, Jin Seo.
We can get it back at the end.
I'll spot the second person.
The second person?
Say the name after
I count to three.
[Ha Ha is sure it's Jae Suk.]
- Are you ready, Ha Ha?
- Yes.
One, two, three!
Yoo Jae Suk, get out!
[The first round's
secret mission is successful.]
Hey, you!
You're supposed to find the culprit!
Nobody put that much effort.
[Jae Suk staked his all on the game.]
[He passionately played for the game
but Ha Ha suspects him.]
This is frustrating.
It's not Jae Suk.
- It's so frustrating, Jin Seo.
- I know, right?
I must win the next round.
Five of them, right?
[Jae Suk returns five envelopes.]
[The final reveal.]
The two couples who didn't win
need to return two envelopes.
- It's fine, Jin Seo.
[Two envelopes are nothing to me.]
Jong Kook, she might be the culprit.
Wait for the next round.
It won't be easy for you.
- I lost five envelopes.
- You're irritated and that's suspicious.
We've decided.
Do one of you...
have the meteorite?
[Do one of you have the meteorite?]
[If one of them has it,
the red light will be on.]
- They're not?
- I told you we're not!
You don't have it?
[She's acting like she's shocked.]
- I told you I don't have it!
I think the culprit is
amongst the winning teams.
- It wasn't you, Jin Seo?
- I said I don't have it.
Can we only judge once per game?
The culprit is among those four.
I said I'm not the culprit.
It's clear now.
We won't doubt you any longer.
- Aren't you thankful to us?
- What about my envelopes!
Do I have to get confirmed
by losing my envelopes?
Say thank you because
you could prove your innocence.
Your dividends will be confiscated.
I'll pick you again, if I win.
- I see how it is.
- Let's pick a couple next time.
[It'll be the safest to hand over
the meteorite to Jin Seo.]
[Se Kyung bravely gets
close to Jin Seo.]
[It's successfully handed over.]
[The meteorite is in Jin Seo's pocket.]
[Will she be able to hide it?]
[The current meteor keeper,
Yoon Jin Seo.]
Who do you think it is?
- I thought Jin Seo was the culprit.
- Me, too.
- She was really strange.
- But she's not.
Let's pick one person each.
For now, I'll pick Kwang Soo.
Me, too.
Is there another person?
Are you really not the culprit?
I'm not the culprit.
I'm serious.
- Can you trust me now?
- Of course.
- I trusted you.
- No, you didn't trust me.
- You tried to interrogate me.
- No, I didn't.
I kept asking Se Kyung.
- She said she's not.
- She might not be the one.
It's too obvious if one of
the guests is the culprit.
[But you can't figure out the obvious.]
It wasn't Jin Seo...
I think it's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo had the shovel
and everything.
I'll point him out
if I win again.
Kwang Soo has to win the games.
Even if we could catch Kwang Soo,
I think there's another person.
- Two people?
- Yes, I'm sure.
But we only have one meteorite.
[We've got to be careful with Ha Ha.]
- Only one meteorite.
[They arrive at the next mission site
while they're guessing the culprits.]
[Will they be able to catch
the culprit this time?]
We talked about who could it be.
We think it's you.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- What are you talking about?
It's you, Lee Kwang Soo.
I'm absolutely not!
We think it's you, too.
Why is everyone suspecting you?
I don't know why.
Then who do you think it is?
- I think it's either Gary or...
- What? It's you!
Do I look that easy to you?
Out of all people, you picked Gary?
Either Gary or who?
Honestly, I think it's
either Ji Hyo or Se Kyung.
[Look at this Giraffe!
He only points out girls.]
What about Gary then?
Are you losing your mind?
Is it possible to point out
the same person again?
[What's with Kwang Soo today?
He even points out Jin Seo again.]
- He's not thinking straight.
- Go ahead and play the game.
- Should I go first?
- You better do your best.
We'll start it now.
The second game of
'The Secret Alumni' is
'Girls over flowers.'
We'll show you a word, and the girls
have to explain with gestures.
The guys have to be on
the bar behind the wall.
You have to do chin-ups
and guess the word.
The girls will be standing here
and explain it.
Each couple can only
pass the question twice.
You have one minute
for five questions.
It's the same as before.
The first and the second team
will get to choose the suspects
and keep their envelopes.
Please decide who will go first.
- Lee Kwang Soo will go first.
- What? That's so unfair!
Don't we need to play rock,
paper, scissors?
[Will Giraffe be able
to tell their secrets?]
It's going to be easy for Jong Kook.
No, it's not.
This can't be easy to anymore.
It doesn't matter.
You know it's hard for everyone.
The category will be movies.
This category is of
great advantage to her.
[Whispering Corridors]
It's too easy!
What is it?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing, Jin Seo?
- Isn't it really easy?
- Pass!
- Why would you pass this?
- Me! Me!
- This one's easy one!
[Jurassic Park]
What are you doing?
- Is it an elephant?
[Do elephants live in that park?]
What did you do?
Godzilla, Godzilla?
King Kong?
- That's not even close!
- What is it?
[She's never acted as a dinosaur.]
- It's more romantic.
- Beauty and the Beast?
[What is she doing now?]
There's nothing like
that in this movie.
- Just pass!
- Isn't that Black Swan?
[Titanic]
- She can do this.
- Titanic?
[Finally, he's got one question.]
[The Thieves]
[She's kicking with
her 'forefeet' again!]
She's really bad at explaining.
What are you doing?
[This looks a little like stealing.]
- Ocean's Eleven?
[Time's up.]
[They fail at getting five questions.]
[She could win the Academy Award
with the dinosaur performance.]
I guess you can tell
we're not the culprits.
Your team is absolutely not.
That's right.
This is such a nice couple.
She was getting better though.
[It's getting easier to
move around the meteorite.]
The next category is...
male celebrities.
Male celebrities!
I only know a few...
Ready, set...
[Jackie Chan]
- Bruce Lee!
[Drunken Master!]
- Jackie Chan!
- Okay!
[Jo In Sung]
- Jo In Sung!
- Okay!
- Hurry up!
[Kim Soo Hyun]
Who are you?
[He'll never be able to get the clue...]
- Ji Suk Jin!
[His weird imitative sound.]
- What is that?
Shoot!
Swoosh!
From a star... swoosh!
What?
What is that?
- From another star... swoosh!
- What?
I don't know!
Pass!
- Wait!
[Jung Woo Sung]
[He can pass one more time.]
What is that?
- Deliveries!
[He thinks he's like Jung Woo Sung.]
What is that?
Arnold Schwarzenegger!
He's very tall!
[That's so funny!]
- What is that?
Come back!
You've got ten seconds!
Blob jump Running Man!
Blob jump!
- That's too much!
- I can't think of anything else!
- I know this one!
[They fail at getting five questions.]
How would you describe
Kim Soo Hyun?
- Why can't you?
- How?
From a star... swoosh!
[What kind of a imitative
sound is that?]
From a star... swoosh?
- I tried my best.
- This is terrible.
How could he not get it?
- That was a hard one.
- I think they're not the culprits, either.
- Se Kyung, use the sound.
- Okay, let's go!
[She puts down her bag.]
- I'll put this away, Se Kyung.
[Ji Hyo puts her bag away,
and stands next to Jin Seo.]
[Does it mean....]
Before all the missions are over
each of you have to have
a turn keeping the stone.
[Rule - All the female members must
carry the meteorite at least once.]
[She passes the meteorite on!]
[She passes it on
at the speed of 4G LTE.]
Do I pass it on quickly like this?
Yes.
Or put it in the pocket of the person.
[Before the mission ends...]
[we must pass along the meteorite.]
[Through a bold move, the meteorite
is with Ji Hyo]
Se Kyung is good at games like this.
[Good job, sisters!]
- Ready, Gary?
- Yes!
Your category is "Girlfriend."
This is too easy!
Ready, set...
[Being cute]
Whining!
Being cute!
[One down with the power of cuteness!]
[Playing coy]
Refusal!
Being shy!
[Seems like Gary never met a girl
who played coy with him...]
What is that?
Hold on...
Pass!
[One pass left!]
This should be easy.
[Back hug]
Hugging!
Back hug!
[Two down!]
Wink!
[Smiling with the eyes]
[Look at my eyes...]
Crooked smile!
What does he mean,
crooked smile?
Half-moon smile!
[Frustrated]
Wrinkles!
- He doesn't know this?
[Gary is lost with an easy question]
Pass!
Hold on!
My arm is stuck!
[Great job, Gary!
You're a true entertainer!]
[Time is up!
Mission failed]
[Next up, Ha Ha and Ji Hyo]
Listen to the category first.
- Can you give me movies?
- The category is...
Children's literature.
- That's good!
- That's an easy one.
- Children's stories...
[Doesn't seem like it'll be easy...]
- Ready?
[Ji Hyo needs a clutch performance]
[I must win so I can avoid being called on...]
- You got it?
- Yes!
[Man with a Lump]
Man with a Lump!
- Pass!
[Two Love Stars]
[Only one pass left!]
[Jack and the Beanstalk]
This is really easy!
[Describing the growth of the beanstalk]
Jack and the Bean Sprouts!
Didn't he just say "bean sprouts?"
Bean sprouts!
See?
He says bean sprouts!
[Jack and the Bean Sprouts
doesn't pass]
[A Dog of Flanders]
A Dog of Flanders!
- Pass!
[The Wizard of Oz]
You're allowed to make sounds.
- You want to pass?
- You don't have any left!
[Is this for a Children's story?]
[What is she doing?]
She's scaring me!
Crazy Woman!
E.T.!
[Mission failed]
[Alice in Wonderland]
That was bad.
"Jack and the Bean Sprouts."
I said beanstalk!
It's supposed to be a beanstalk.
That's what I said!
You said bean sprouts!
What kind of idiot would say
bean sprouts?
You!
You said bean sprouts!
I was trying to be funny!
Even if you got that one,
you only got three right.
So I passed.
You have to get five right.
I see...
[Why was I paired up with Ha Ha...]
From now on, you can decide
who will be hanging on the bar.
- I'll go on the bar.
- You should try the bar, Suk Jin.
Yoon Jin Seo is going first again!
I'm already excited!
The category is...
Female characters.
Female characters?
Like what?
- Ready?
- Yes.
Set...
[Nine-tailed Fox]
[She always uses front paws]
Nine-tailed Fox!
- Sleeping Beauty!
[Sleeping Beauty]
[Pippi Longstocking]
Who is that?
- Who is that?
[Quite difficult]
Medusa!
Cinderella?
Pi...
- Pi...
[Whatever...]
What did you say?
What is this sound?
[This is the Pi-turing hint]
Make some sound?
Pi?
Pippi!
[Elsa]
[Three down with ten seconds left]
El...
Don't do that!
She can't do that!
That's too much!
That's too obvious!
Ice Kingdom!
No...
[Mission failed]
What is it?
[Kook turned Frozen into Ice Kingdom]
He married Elsa to Le Petit Prince!
So, Suk Jin is...
I'm going to the bar.
The category is...
We're getting this, Suk Jin!
Let's go!
Action and status!
- What is that?
- That sounds difficult.
Ready, set...
[Half-sitting posture]
[He evaporates with the whistle]
Come up!
You have to come up
for me to give you hints!
What are you doing?
Look at me!
[I'm sorry, but I'm not ready
to see you...]
What the heck are you doing?
Look at me!
Look at me now!
- Pass!
[He's a very difficult person to meet...]
Look at me!
- What's going on...
- Hey, mister!
- Look at me!
[A big nose appears]
Look at me!
He's not there.
Damn it!
[The Big-nosed Brother disappears
after short appearances]
Look at me now!
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin]
[Failed with zero]
[Should've had a better breakfast...]
- What was that?
[In last place as the only male-male pair]
I'm sorry.
[I'll catch the culprit who
has the meteorite...]
- It's our turn.
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin]
I'm going up.
Do you think you can be quick?
Quickly?
They are difficult...
You can make sounds too.
[Kwang Soo is very enthusiastic today...]
[Kwang Soo's fondness of Ye Jin
is only making others more suspicious]
Your category is...
Movies.
- Got it?
- Yes!
Ready, set...
[A Moment to Remember]
A Moment to Remember!
[One down right off the bat!]
[Tazza: The High Rollers]
Tazza!
[Terminator]
- Kwang Soo...
[What could it be?]
[The famous thumbs-up ending scene]
- You have to do it going down.
- Going down?
Terminator!
[Three down!
Almost there!]
[This is almost performing art!]
The Six Siblings!
Crazy Woman...
- She's very cold...
[Look at me...]
What will be the answer?
200 Pound Beauty!
[One question to go!]
[Edward Scissorhands]
- Scissors!
Scissors!
[Five seconds remaining,
with one question left!]
[Will they seize this opportunity?]
Edward Scissorhands!
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin
pass the mission!]
Is that it?
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin in first place
at 57 seconds.]
[Unfortunately, Kwang Soo
is first place...]
Kwang Soo survives.
[Everyone thought he was being
enthusiastic to avoid getting picked.]
He had to win.
We already know the answer!
That narrows it down.
- I'm really not it.
- Why did you take the meteorite?
I did my best because everyone is
suspicious, but I'm not it.
[At this rate...]
[Our task will be very easy]
[Gary and Se Kyung are the last couple
of the second round.]
[They'll win if they beat Kwang Soo's record]
The category is Girl Groups.
Too easy!
- All Gary has to do is dance!
[Easy if he knows all the girl group dances]
[It'll be easy if he knows all the
girl group dances]
SES!
[Fast!]
[One down]
- This!
[Kara]
- Kara!
- That's right!
- This is easy!
[Brown Eyed Girls]
[Despite his weird dancing...]
- Brown Eyed Girls!
[Three down!]
- This!
[Girls' Generation]
Girls' Generation!
[Unbelievable speed!]
[Four down in 20 seconds!]
[Lee Jung Hyun]
Uhm Jung Hwa?
No, Lee Jung Hyun!
[Gary and Se Kyung pass!]
[Gary and Se Kyung take first place
at 25 seconds!]
Damn...
[All I can trust are Se Kyung
and Ye Jin...]
[Ji Hyo has the meteorite right now!]
[Time of judgment, again]
I hope we catch the culprit this time.
[Only Gary, Se Kyung, Kwang Soo, and
Ye Jin are allowed to call on people.]
- We've narrowed it down.
- Among the four who are left.
There's a 50% chance.
The couple who won this round
will get a hint about the culprit.
The winning couple, come forward.
What if it's one of those two?
- That's possible.
[Frozen]
[The Culprit is Here]
[It was not done by a single person]
[Acting as if she's surprised]
Pretend like you didn't see that.
[The hint is forcing them to be more
careful when passing the meteorite.]
So we'll get some clues by seeing
whom they pick!
I'm not it.
Really.
We should pick someone
based on the hint.
A member from these teams
were called on.
So I think we should pick someone
from your team, to be fair.
[What is this unexpected scenario?]
[The meteorite was passed from Jin Seo
to Ji Hyo during the second mission]
[They thought it would be 100% safe
with Blank Ji!]
[A critical moment for Song Ji Hyo?]
Kwang Soo and Ye Jin can call on
one person.
Then Gary and Se Kyung
can call on another person.
We're suspicious of you, Ji Hyo.
Any last defense?
[Giraffe has already decided on Ji Hyo?]
[Ye Jin was not aware of this]
What would you do if it's not me?
[Is he Sherlock Giraffe right now?]
[Blank Ji might end up on the scanner]
Call on someone.
Go, Song Ji Hyo!
[Is this the end?]
[Per the rules, Blank Ji is required
to return five envelopes]
We know she's not it,
but there's no other way.
Go in there too.
We'll say it out together.
One, two, three!
Go, Lee Kwang Soo!
Can I go home if I'm right?
[Running Men are suspicious of Kwang Soo]
[Kwang Soo alone is suspicious of Ji Hyo]
- Is he not it?
- Really?
The rest of the crew, please return
two envelopes per person.
We'll get nothing at this rate.
[If they catch the culprit, they can
split the money inside of the money bag!]
I feel like I'm giving money
at a wedding.
[Bitter]
[The moment of judgment]
Song Ji Hyo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
Do you have the meteorite?
Is it really Ji Hyo
who has the meteorite?
- Do you have it?
- Please...
Kwang Soo is it...
No meteorite!
Neither Ji Hyo nor Kwang Soo
has the meteorite.
[How is this possible?]
I'm suspicious of Se Kyung now.
[Where did Ji Hyo's meteorite go?]
[Ji Hyo and Ye Jin were standing closely
during the previous mission]
[As everyone was paying attention to the
game, she approached from the back...]
[And passed the meteorite!]
[Ye Jin had the meteorite all this time]
They're not it.
This is shocking.
I don't like how I'm mistrusted!
Then why did you behave like
the culprit?
What did I do?
[Haroro is consulting Ji Hyo,
who has been acquitted.]
I'm not it, Ji Hyo.
- Se Kyung is it!
- No...
[She's diverting the suspicion
with her comment.]
How about Ye Jin?
[Too late now!]
[Will Ye Jin manage to keep the meteorite
throughout the next mission?]
[Park Ye Jin has the meteorite now!]
This stadium got nicer!
[Suwon Baseball Stadium]
- It feels like broad daylight!
- This is a great stadium.
[The ultra-modern, dream stage]
[What will be the final mission here?]
What is that?
[The scoreboard is decorated by
hearts and flowers]
- The third mission of Secret Alumni...
[Balloons on the ground?]
Kiss Time at the Ballpark!
When there's a break between innings, the
scoreboard often shows couples and kissing.
We got the idea from that.
You'll see those balloons on the ground.
One of these balloons will appear
inside of that heart.
Then we'll take the picture.
The shutter will go automatically
in 30 seconds.
The couple who shows their cheek-kiss inside
of that heart when the picture is taken will win.
[Smiles]
What about us?
Who wants to play the girl?
Is that important?
[He will be Big-nosed Sister this time]
[Trying to play cool]
[Are we really doing this?]
[I can't drop the meteorite while running...]
The tricky part is that
there are three balloons per color.
You must use your judgment
to find the right one.
We should approach this strategically.
[Peeking]
- We must stop the culprit.
- Stop whom?
- We must know first in order to stop.
- I think it's Se Kyung...
- We must be suspicious of Ye Jin too.
- That's right.
[Hear, hear, Kwang Soo]
[Nervous]
Now that he got scanned once,
he wants me to do it!
[Nothing better than blaming Kwang Soo
to deflect suspicion!]
He keeps acting like it's him.
[Thank you for being here, Kwang Soo.]
Shall we?
[Moving to the start line]
Do you have it?
Yes.
This investigation will not be easy...
[This is the last mission...]
[She's worried about the meteorite]
[Slipped!]
[A huge accident!]
[Huh?]
[The scene of exposed meteorite...]
[Did Haroro see it?]
[After she picked it up...]
[He didn't notice it.]
[Thank heavens.]
[I can't trust myself, Ji Hyo...]
Get ready...
- The speed is not that important.
- Red, yellow, blue...
[Only one balloon will appear
on the scoreboard.]
So we must run to the balloon
that appears on the board?
Just grab me.
[They start running as soon as
a balloon appears on the board]
[A red balloon!]
[Just start running!]
Quickly!
- The center one!
[Only one of these is on the board]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are running
to the left one.]
This is not it!
- This is it.
- Not the center one?
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin
are going to the one on the right]
[But the scoreboard looks the same
even though they're close.]
They're coming!
This is it!
Is it not?
It's wavering.
Is this it?
Is this not it?
- This is it!
[I'm on the big screen, mom!]
That's Jong Kook!
- This is it! Quickly!
[Hyenas are running to the balloon]
[Huh?]
[There's a lot of time left.
But one kiss and that's it?]
[Hyenas attack in the meantime.]
- We were in there!
[Chaos]
- We must do it quickly!
[Kisses everywhere]
[Enjoying the moment as much
as they could.]
[Kiss time is over.]
What happened?
- We did it!
[Who amongst them made it?]
Here's the picture.
[Revealing the picture]
No one made it.
[The couple's eyes, noses, and
mouths must be in the heart]
Kwang Soo almost made it.
I'm doing it right here!
I can't see it!
[Ye Jin is blocking Suk Jin's kiss]
[And Kwang Soo is blocking
Ji Hyo's kiss]
I did that?
[Anger of a man who
got his love interfered with.]
I did it though!
[First Round: The Kiss Breakers]
- I can't see that.
[Sad]
- Is it on my cheek?
- Do you want me to wipe it?
How many years has it been since
there was lipstick on your cheek?
[Today is the day when
Kook's cheek got stamped.]
K-I-S-S-I-N-G!
[I like the mood of this mission.]
Then there are people who keep sticking their
cheeks out to those who aren't their partners.
- Who was that?
- I've warned you.
I saw someone who got their kiss
then went to someone else!
This is my only chance!
Ready!
- I think it'll be blue.
- I think yellow.
[A blue balloon!]
- There are several!
[Running to get their kisses!]
- That one.
- That one?
[There's only one blue balloon
that's on the scoreboard!]
I think this is it!
If it is, it's us!
- This is not it!
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin run to the right again]
[Only to be wrong again]
Is this it?
No...
[Jong Kook and Jin Seo are
observing other teams.]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are running
to the left.]
We must run with all our might.
I think it's that one.
This isn't it?
[We're on the scoreboard!]
- This is it!
[They came to the right one]
[Everyone is rushing toward Ha Ha]
[Regardless of the detractors,
Blank Ji assaults Ha Ha with her kiss.]
[Se Kyung's shy kiss.]
[Still getting his kiss
after the whistle.]
[Kiss time is over.]
How many times do we have to do this?
[Why did we have to be a couple today?]
You guys were so intense.
[Blank Ji made sure her
aggressive kissing was seen.]
We should just run while we're kissing.
It'll be us.
[Again!]
I'm in there!
I did it!
We did it!
[Ye Jin is the kiss break once again.]
I think I'm good at blocking.
Look at that village idiot.
[Lost half of his mind by Ji Hyo's lips.]
Now I know why she's so popular.
[Bittersweet...]
What's wrong with your face?
[Second Round: Losing Face
But Feeling that Kiss on the Cheek!]
Ready!
[Trying the Kiss Time Mission again]
[A yellow balloon this time!]
Let's just go this way!
[Did they pick the right one
this time?]
This isn't it, is it?
Damn it!
[The male couple is always wrong!]
Jae Suk is...
Wrong!
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are
running to the left]
That's not it!
This!
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin choose
the middle balloon.]
[Haroro is on the screen again!]
There it is!
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo found it in
one try again.]
[We won't just leave you
to be the only kissing couple!]
[The Kissing Army is rushing
toward Ha Ha!]
[It seems like they're running
out of time!]
[At this rate,
it'll be their perfect victory.]
- Come to the front!
[The male couple is late to the party.]
[Will the shutter be faster?
Or the detractors?]
[Kiss time is over.]
We did it!
No, we blocked you.
That was no joke!
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are
certain of their victory.]
Here it is!
- We did it!
[A perfect success!]
[Jong Kook would've blocked him a second later.]
[First place for the
Kiss Time at the Ballpark Mission]
Why are they so happy?
What is Gary doing?
[Waiting patiently for his kiss.]
[He seems to be ready to receive it.]
[Hilarious]
I forced her once or twice.
[Monday Couple, and their crossed fate.]
So, Song Ji Hyo and Ha Ha
are the winners!
[They can call on someone now.]
That team is okay.
Please come this way.
[I must work hard too.]
We must do something so Gary
doesn't make it.
I think either Gary or Se Kyung
must be scanned this time.
I want to put those two on there.
Ye Jin...
[Suspicion points to Ye Jin again]
[Ye Jin...]
All I ever did was
have too many envelopes.
Is that so?
Let's go!
[I think you're in danger]
[I must do something]
[A red balloon this time!]
- Red...
[Which team will get it right this time?]
- If this isn't it, we're going left.
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin run right again.]
This isn't it, is it?
[They're right this time!]
This is it!
- That's it!
[Swarming toward Jae Suk.]
Block them!
[Blocking the enemy first...]
[Then kiss!]
[Literally, a kissing war.]
[Giraffe is acting weird]
[Retaliating with another kiss!]
[While the others are busy,
Gary and Se Kyung kiss too!]
[Whose kiss was caught on camera?]
I was so rushed, I did it
while facing backward.
[This kissing war is grueling.]
Here it is!
- I did it backward!
[The back of his head]
- You almost made it.
- I was in a rush.
Did he do this on purpose?
- I think he did.
[Uneasy]
Isn't it suspicious that
he got his directions confused?
Anyway, let's do it again!
- I think Se Kyung tried her best.
[Fourth Round: I'll See You Later!]
I envy you, Gary.
[Fifth Round: To the blue balloon...
Go, go, go!]
This is right.
Come here.
[Get out!]
Now is it!
[Chaos ensues again]
[Quite desperate male-to-male kiss.]
We did it!
I think we did it!
I think we did it.
They did it!
[The spectators are certain
of their success too.]
Kwang Soo pushed me.
I didn't push you, Se Kyung.
I was going to kiss, but you pushed me!
For him, our own kissing comes second
to pushing everyone around first.
Yon can at least let us kiss first.
He doesn't come near me because
he's so busy pushing people.
Again, you can push people
once they kiss first.
Our spot was the good one.
[Time to check the picture]
Everyone looks like they
had a good time.
- Us, too?
- Have you seen me?
I think Suk Jin is a bit thrilled.
Here's the picture!
[Kwang Soo and Ye Jin made it!]
We were in that corner...
Your face is that of an
australopithecus.
Why am I always the only one
who's craving?
[The man who is craving for kisses.]
[Not enough yet]
- Her chin line is pretty!
[Venus Who Descended Upon the Ballpark]
Park Ye Jin and Lee Kwang Soo
take second place.
Now that the third game is over,
we'll do the judgment.
[If I can keep this until the end...]
[Park Ye Jin has the meteorite
right now!]
This is the last judgment.
Take a look at the hint
and think hard.
[Find the person who has the stone
"right now."]
Can we search them?
[No...]
You?
[If they do a body search,
her cover will be blown!]
I'm sorry, but would you
please take your hat off?
Try touching my hat.
There's no point of searching us now.
- Let's discuss.
- Gary!
- Share the hint!
- I think it's a she.
- There are co-conspirators?
- I knew it wasn't done by a single person.
The hint said it's not done
by a single person.
So it's not just one person.
It's harder to guess two.
- So we have to guess both of them?
- What was the second hint?
[Giraffe starts the search]
- You must tell us now.
- It's the person who has the stone right now.
[Discreetly]
[Ye Jin approaches Se Kyung]
[Ye Jin?]
[Perhaps...]
[Was there a secret deal
between those two?]
I presume the person does
have the stone.
[Ye Jin's face is hard to read]
[Kwang Soo's search is getting closer.]
Even if the person might have the stone,
it might not be here.
[He began to search Ye Jin!]
[An emergency!]
The stone!
[Ji Hyo suddenly changes the subject!]
Suk means stone.
Yoo Jae Suk!
Ji Suk Jin!
Yoo Jae Suk and Ji Suk Jin!
But Jae Suk wasn't it.
He didn't have the stone at the
moment, because Suk Jin had it!
- They might have hidden the stone.
[Phew...]
- You two are the stones!
- I'm not it!
- This is weird...
- The hint said someone has the stone right now.
Ji Suk Jin.
Yoo Jae Suk.
This is it.
We've got them.
[Time to put the suspects on
the scanner.]
- What will you do?
[Teams in first and second place choose.]
I'll choose Suk Jin.
Okay, do that.
Hold on.
Come here.
[Ha Ha seems to be suspicious of Se Kyung.]
One, two, three!
Go, Ji Suk Jin!
He must be the culprit.
[For the girls, this is a great choice.]
When you go to prison,
do repent for your crime!
- My Lord...
- I think he's it.
[Time to designate one more person]
I think Se Kyung should go.
[She is startled by the idea.]
[Ye Jin's face is also serious.]
[Right before the body search...]
[Perhaps...]
[Did Se Kyung receive the meteorite
from Ye Jin?]
I think it's Se Kyung.
The only thing she's been saying
the whole day is "Ahh."
- You've been pretty quiet, Se Kyung.
- In the car, too...
Let's do this.
Go, Shin Se Kyung!
- Se Kyung is it!
- It must be one of the two!
[Ye Jin's face is getting harder to read]
- Ji Suk Jin is it!
- No, he's faking it.
I must turn in my money, right?
[Collecting 500,000 won first]
If it's not one of those two,
we can't take the money.
If you look above,
there are flour buckets.
- Where?
- Not there, Gary.
- Why, are you worried?
- He was staring at the sky.
[Looking for flour in the sky.]
See? I can't be it!
[If Se Kyung does have the meteorite...]
[a bucket of flour will be]
dumped on her...]
[and the girls will lose!]
Ji Suk Jin, Shin Se Kyung.
Do one of you have the stone?
[The fateful moment...]
[Were the boys right to pick Se Kyung?]
[Did Ye Jin give the stone
at the very last moment?]
[What could be...]
[the truth?]
[Failed to catch the culprits!]
[Victory of the four girls!]
We've won!
[Se Kyung did not have the stone!]
[The meteorite is...]
[Right here!]
So you had the stone, Ye Jin?
- I didn't have it the whole time.
- Where did you hide it?
In my back pocket.
I even dropped it once!
- I was trying to put it in a safer place...
[She almost got caught!]
I should search
all female guests from now on.
Thank you for your hard work!
[The victorious girls get the envelopes
with money inside!]
[Amazed]
- You're pretty amazing.
[Blank Ji is the lucky lady.]
Did you remember just now?
We were all smiles when
those girls kissed us.
We were seduced.
Today's victors are
the four female classmates!
- Well done!
[Congratulations!]
The Hallyu Stars!
Jung Yong Hwa, Jung Il Woo,
Lee Hong Ki...
[All different kinds of games
created by our fans worldwide!]
There are so many different games!
How do they think of such games?
- Who's next?
- I'll show you who the boss is.
[Hallyu stars become
the boys next door.]
[Mission Worldwide!]
Subtitles by DramaFever