Running Man
Episode 234
[2015 New Year's Cooking Battle]
Rival? It's myself.
I think my team can win easily.
[His goal is to win twice in a row.]
I have a good feeling.
[He believes in his good luck.]
I think I can win this battle.
I have the best partner!
My goal is to win.
You should look forward to my victory.
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle
It's gotten harder and tougher.]
[Get the best ingredients
by land, sea and air.]
[The cooking battle
is spreading throughout the world.]
[A symphony of taste
beyond imagination.]
[Add a divine trick to your dish!]
[And judged by the four
best chefs in the country.]
[Harsh words that go
between heaven and hell.]
[For an ideal taste
that hasn't been discovered!]
[What will be the best dish of the
2015 New Year Cooking Battle?]
[2015 New Year Cooking Battle]
[7AM Feb. 2nd Taean Country
South Chungchong Province]
Hello!
It's so early!
What time is it?
[Chunsooman's sky is tinged with crimson.]
-This is one of the island in West sea.
- Hwangdo is the name?
It's an island?
This is an island indeed.
It's an island!
What do you want me to do?
[At the same time,
Jeju island, Korea]
Jeju island!
Everyone, I'm in Jeju island.
What am I doing here?
I have no idea.
By the way, where are the other members?
[Why does Ha Ha come to Jeju island?]
[At the same time,
at an orange farm in Jeju island.]
Let's leave.
Just the two of us.
Let go of everything.
Welcome to Jeju island.
I'm at an orange farm in Jeju island.
And this looks like... a tangerine.
Isn't that pretty?
Let's leave. Just the two of us.
By the way, why am I in Jeju island?
[At the same time,
Jungsun, Kangwon Province.]
Hello!
Thank you for coming all the way
to Kangwon Province.
[ At the same time,
Bulkyo, South Jeolla Province.]
[Kkuk is stylish even
early in the morning.]
- What's the theme for today?
- It's so far, right?
[The members are are all scattered.]
[Korea]
[But two members are missing.]
[Thailand, Hong Kong]
[At the same time,
Bangkok, Thailand.]
[The world famous tourist attraction,
City of angels, Bangkok.]
[There are lots to see
and eat here...]
Sawadikap! (Hello!)
[Gary is alone in Bangkok!]
Come into my heart, Thailand!
[City full of exotic taste, Bangkok.]
I remember getting on that boat before!
Sawadikap! (Hello!)
Why are you holding the 'Peaceful Gary'?
That's very old!
I love Tom Yum Goong.
- Suai! (Beautiful!)
- You're handsome, too!
- How do you say 'handsome'?
- Laaw.
So I can say that I'm 'laaw', right?
You are 'suai'.
I think I'm well adjusted to the
East Asian countries.
[Thailand.]
[At the same time,
Hong Kong.]
[This city is everyone's dream.]
[The number one travel destination
all throughout the world.]
[Hong Kong.
the city of fashion, city of taste.]
['H' hotel,
Hong Kong.]
[Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Giraffe sleeps like a dog.]
[What's the reason that the members
are all scattered?]
[Tired Giraffe who needs sleep
more than a mission.]
[A mysterious woman approaches
the sleeping Giraffe.]
[Who is she?]
[She enters to the room
while Kwang Soo is still asleep.]
Ni hao, Mister Lee Kwang Soo.
[Blank.]
[Half asleep, half awake.]
[Blurry...]
[Who is she...?]
Get up.
[Kwang Soo's partner,
Fei.]
[He's still in a daze.]
[Where am I...]
[Right...
I came to Hong Kong last night.]
- I'm in Hong Kong.
- That's right. Ni hao?
- Let's keep it up!
- Please treat me well.
- Way to go!
- Go!
Why didn't you tell me
that my partner is here?
I was looking at the wrong places.
[His partner is a guy?]
Who is it?
Oh, the guest is a man.
[Disappointed.]
- Yeon Jung Hoon?
- Long time no see.
[Jae Suk's partner,
Yeon Jung Hoon.
[A man from city, Yeon Jung Hoon coughs.]
You should have come
with your wife, Ga In.
Why did you come by yourself?
- When did you leave home?
- At 4 am.
- You came so early.
- They wouldn't tell me anything.
- You went to the salon at 4 am?
- I came with my stylist.
That person standing there?
It's hard to find my partner.
I see someone over there.
[There's a lady looking at the ocean.]
[Who is the Big-nose's partner?]
- Hello!
Wow! I'm your big fan!
[Suk Jin's partner,
Yoo Sun.]
[Thrilled.]
- You look better in person.
- You're more beautiful in person.
- You got married 4 years ago.
- That's right.
I know that exact information.
- I really like you as a fan.
- Should I believe it or not?
I'm not lying.
I don't usually smile this much.
[While the Big-nose meets his partner...]
[Ha Ha looks for his partner
in a canola flower field.]
Why are you hiding so obviously?
Why are you putting
that much effort to hide?
Is she one of the producers?
- Shoo?
- Who are you?
[Ha Ha's partner, Shoo.]
I hope you believe in me.
[The dance of greeting partners.]
Dreams come true.
[Shoo takes a break from
the childcare and dances!]
I thought you might have
skipped breakfast.
- You ate two pieces though.
- I'm sorry.
[Reporter Blank Ji is
in love with tangerines.]
Don't they look so good?
Look at how big it is!
They look so delicious.
Oh my!
I was surprised!
Is that my partner?
- Hello!
- Taecyeon!
[Ji Hyo's partner,
Taecyeon.]
We have matching outfits.
I have a good feeling.
- What are we going to do?
- I have no idea.
- I was told to come to Jeju island.
- Me, too.
I took a nap and I was in Jeju island.
Then my manager brought me to this farm.
[What is today's mission?]
I think I can find my partner soon.
[Where in Bulkyo is Kkuk's partner in?]
[Could it be here?]
What?
[In between the doors.]
Wait, there's a woman.
[Fancy fur
and high heels.]
She looks cold.
[Who is she?]
Excuse me.
Hello.
Are you here for...
Running Man?
No?
But your outfit is too fancy.
Jong Kook!
Jong Kook's partner,
Seo Woo.]
- So, it was you?
- You came all the way here?
Aren't you cold?
you look very cold.
I can't give up my high heels.
[A woman's pride.]
I received many casting calls
after I appeared on Running Man.
It's been a while, Seo Woo.
What is it? It's for me?
Aren't we dressed too well
for this kind of occasion?
I didn't know I would be coming so far.
[Bulkyo Runway.]
[With her shiny eyes.]
You've got to show the flower.
What makes my style complete
is the flower.
[Lastly, who's the partner of Gary,
the man in Bangkok?]
I see someone wearing
the same shirt as mine.
[She's on the boat to cross the river...]
[in the same outfit as Gary.]
Sung Ryung!
[Gary's partner,
Kim Sung Ryung.]
Sung Ryung!
[Gary...]
[Gary and Sung Ryung
meet in Bangkok.]
Sung Ryung!
You oust me as soon as we meet?
I really wanted to eliminate a name tag.
- Please put it back.
- This is fun.
Sung Ryung, are you ready for this?
I'm always ready.
- You don't mind to work with me?
- I don't.
- Did you put lots of sun block?
- Why? Is my makeup cakey?
No, you're beautiful as always.
[Finally, everyone
found their partners.]
[It's time to receive the mission.]
- Hello! Good morning!
- Hello!
You don't let me wash up
even in Hong Kong?
- This is the new year's special.
- Is it?
I will give you the mission.
Hello, Running Man.
I'm the winner of the 2014 New Year's
Cooking Battle, Song Kyung Ah.
Hello, everyone!
[The winner of 2014 Cooking Battle,
Song Kyung Ah.]
[She made a good team with Jong Kook.]
[Healthy chicken stew and fresh Kimchi.]
[They won
with their well-being dish.]
I haven't seen her for a long time.
We had a cooking battle last year.
Song Kyung Ah and I were the winners.
Song Kyung Ah and Jong Kook were the winners.
Song Kyung Ah won
last year's cooking battle.
You can guess
why I'm giving you the mission.
It's because the New Year's
Cooking Battle has come back.
Today's mission is cooking, then.
- Are you good at cooking?
Not really, just a little.
I'm not really good at it.
- You're a mother of three children!
- That's exactly why!
I'm going to tell you the rules.
You have to get the ingredients
with your partner
learn a secret recipe, and
make the most delicious dish.
It looks like it's Kimchi, but not.
The dish seems like it's Kimchi.
Pardon?
It looks like it's Kimchi, but not.
The dish seems like it's Kimchi.
- What? I don't know how!
- Kimchi?
- Isn't it Kimchi?
- I've never made Kimchi before.
- Do you usually buy Kimchi?
- Yes. And people give me.
We have prepared five kinds of Kimchi.
Old fermented Kimchi, whole cabbage Kimchi
cut radish Kimchi, young radish Kimchi
and white cabbage and radish Kimchi.
You can choose one of these
and make a dish
along with other ingredients
that you will get.
Wait, do you remember
that I won the golden horse trophy?
Thanks to me, Jong Kook got it, too.
Do you take a good care of it,
Jong Kook?
I won the gold.
Of course, I remember.
Last year was the year of the horse.
Jong Kook and Kyung Ah won
the golden horse trophies.
Is it the golden goat trophy this time?
- I was born in the year of the goat.
- Were you?
Do your best, just like I did last time.
I hope you win the great prize!
Then, 2015's New Year
Cooking Battle now begins!
Let's go!
Last year
I did most of the work.
- People don't know...
- What are you talking about?
They said our presentation was great.
You talk too much!
- We need to think of an idea first so...
- What a nagger!
let's do our best to win.
- I understand.
Cooking isn't my area.
I wont' be able to win.
Aren't you good at cooking?
- I try to do it well.
- That's great!
I like the fact that
the main theme is Kimchi.
What do we need to get for the ingredients?
- First, you can go here.
- Where is it?
Find Madame Choi Geum Ja?
Madame Choi Geum Ja?
- Then, she will be teaching us...
- That's right.
the secret recipe?
Is she your mother?
- No, she's not my mother.
- Isn't this your hometown?
No, you know my father...
Oh, I forgot!
I thought about your wife
and forgot about your father.
You must be embarrassed.
That's right. Your mom is in Seoul.
I forgot about that.
Can we just go here?
Let's go.
[At the moment, no one knew]
[what would happen
on the day of the battle.]
[The judges with harsh criticism.]
[A cry burst out in the
middle of the cooking battle?]
[Find the ingredients and the secret recipe
throughout Korea and Asia.
Sawadikap! (Hello!)
Kokunkap! (Thank you!)
I greeted in Thai, because I just got
back from Thailand.
[First impression of Sung Ryung?]
There were a lot of guests.
But she's one of the guests that
made my heart flutter.
There were three guests so far.
Oh Hyun Kyung
Oh Yeon Soo
and Sung Ryung.
Why do I like ladies
that are older than me?
Anyway, my heart was singing of joy.
[What's their first mission?]
- Let's begin.
Tada! Our first mission!
Go find this person by three pm
and get the invitation for the battle.
First, take a Tuk Tuk and go to Khaosan Road.
Have you ever been to Khaosan Road?
- No, I haven't.
I guess we need to meet
this person for the mission.
Sawadikap! (Hello!)
I think it'll be nice if we can get
some street food on the way.
[Arriving at Khaosan Road.]
[Khaosan Road] a short street
in central Bangkok.
[It's a world famous backpackers' street
and famous for street food. ]
Are you okay?
You seem tired
but this is only the beginning.
Isn't this an R flag?
What kind of a crude indication is this?
[What kind of mission is waiting
for them at Khaosan Road?]
Eat the top three street foods of Bangkok
and get R stickers.
Find Ma Muang, Kwetiau Kai, Itim Kati
out of these numerous street foods.
Let's go. Ma Muang?
- Do we need to find these?
- Yes.
All of a sudden, I feel hungry.
He's handsome.
Sung Ryung!
She's weird!
She keeps saying that he's handsome.
Let's go ask.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Where are you from?
- Denmark.
- Denmark? I'm from Korea.
We're from Korea.
She is... Miss...
Miss Korea
long time ago.
She told me you're handsome.
You're handsome, too.
- How is she?
- Beautiful.
Beautiful?
- Do you know Ma Muang?
- No.
Thailand food, Ma Muang?
No, I'm so sad.
Thank you.
- Nice to meet you. I love Denmark.
- Hope you enjoy being here. Bye!
- Sung Ryung.
- There are many handsome people here.
[This is the hottest traveler's spot
Khaosan Road.]
[This is paradise.]
You gave us a mission
that's not even in Korean
to give us a hard time.
I guess that's the fun of
being on Running Man.
I only watched Running Man on TV.
but running around
actually made me want to win
just like Gary said.
It made me active and not shy.
It was very fun.
That looks romantic.
Wait, Ma Muang...
Look! They have food there.
[They find a food cart]
[with delicious looking fruits.]
- Ma Muang?
Ma Muang?
Do you know Ma Muang?
- Ma Muang!
[He points at a fruit .]
Mango?
Is this right?
- Okay, okay. Let's pay first.
[Ma Muang means mango in Thai.]
I will put it on a stick for you.
[Sung Ryung tastes it first.]
- How is it?
- It's good.
[Thai Mangoes are big and sweet.]
It's really good.
Kwetiau Kai?
[He understood right away?]
[He points at another food cart.]
Kwetiau Kai? Right?
Eat one more, Sung Ryung.
- I need to eat the next snack.
[Look at you!]
You've succeeded.
[They succeed in eating Ma Muang.]
We did it.
Kwetiau Kai.
[Let's go get some Kwetiau Kai.]
[Hot broth and delicious looking chicken.]
- Kwetiau Kai?
- Yes, it is.
[They come to the right place.]
We can choose the sauce.
- It looks like rice noodles.
[Put some chicken on the rice noodles.]
We can eat a lot of this.
We love this.
- How much is it?
[Add the toppings.]
[Pour the hot broth.]
[Thai rice noodle, Kwetiau Kai.]
- Try it.
- It's good.
- Is it? It looks good.
I'm surprised.
What do they call coriander here?
It's good, right?
- It will be good with white Kimchi?
- Yes. It will.
We can replace these vegetables
with white Kimchi.
It's really good.
The bean sprout is good, too.
[They succeeded in eating
the second street food.]
Excuse me, do you know
'Gangnam Style' dance?
No, do you know 'Up and Down'?
'Up and Down'?
I'll teach you.
- Come here.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Spain.
- Spain?
She's Miss Korea.
Okay, I'll show you 'Up and Down.'
Everybody!
One, two, three, four!
Up, down, up, up, and down.
- His pronunciation is good.
- Up and down is ''Wi A-re".
- Up and down is ''Wi A-re", okay.
- Okay, have fun!
[It's time to find the last street food.]
My song should have been playing.
[Bulkyo, Korea.]
So, we'll have to cook.
We have to use Kimchi but
we should find something famous
around here first
Then we can make some kind of
fusion food using Kimchi.
You know cooking is an interpretation.
You need to show the judges
how much effort you've put in.
I'm close to Kang Leo,
he's my friend.
- You know who Kang Leo is?
- I know.
There's gonna be a judge
that will be very serious for sure.
[Why am I getting tired already?]
Wait, can you stop talking
for a moment?
You talk too much while you drive.
We should keep talking about the idea.
- You're not a rapper, are you?
- No, I've been singing the melody.
You almost sound like you're rapping.
[It would have been a waste,
if he just sang.]
I was on the Running man
'Thanks Giving Special' last year.
I've gotten close to Min Seo who was
on the show with me.
She told me a lot about Jong Kook.
That he nags a lot.
As soon as I saw Jong Gook today,
I thought it might be tiring.
As you already saw...
(he made me feel tired.)
[For another 30 minutes,
Teacher Kkuk's sermon continued...]
[Finally arriving at the mission site.]
[Is this the mission site?]
This mudflat... is not... an ordinary one.
[Mudflats... how far does it stretch out?]
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo's mission
is to dig out 1,000 red shells.]
- Can we start?
- Yes.
[Let's go to the mudflat.]
This is the
'Let's go to the mudflat' dance.
That is the
'Let's go to the mudflat' dance?
You're missing out.
You need to twist your legs like this.
- I can't move like that but...
- You need to move your legs.
[They make us feel uneasy
from the beginning.]
I'm not scared! I'm not!
I'm scared of you!
Can we get off now?
You can get off now.
Be careful.
Hello!
They're getting ready to dig out
the red shells, too.
You know we can't really count
1,000 red shells.
They say it's about ten Kilograms.
[Have you even been to any mudflats?]
- It was first time to be in a mudflat.
I had no idea how
I can dig out the red shells.
I thought, 1,000 shells for a show?
No way...
I didn't think they would actually
make us to dig out 1,000 shells.
[Kkuk is getting a mud sled.]
Are we really going to start?
[Even the Running Man members
haven't been in this kind of mudflat.]
Give it to me.
I can tell our sled is a good one.
[His legs fall into the mud.]
[The mudflat welcomes him.]
[Mommy, the ground is pulling me.]
This sled is in good condition.
[The other ladies already arrived.]
Then, let's go!
[They push with all the strength.]
[Seo Woo moves forward with her scream.]
Can you move?
I'll pull it for you.
What should I do?
Let's go!
The sled moves well.
[Mr. Capable learns how to control
the mud sled right away.]
This is tiring.
Do you think you can handle this?
- Father, I'll be there in a minute!
- What are you doing?
- Hurry up and come.
- I'm almost there.
Seo Woo, it's going to be
difficult to pass here.
She didn't listen to Kkuk.
Please save me.
[Seo Woo is fighting with the mudflat.]
[What kind of partner is Seo Woo?]
She's a handful.
She can't do a lot by herself.
You need to stay by her side and
take care of her all the time.
[She moves forward little by little.]
Father!
You're doing well!
- Keep it going!
- Father!
[Just let me go, mudflat!]
- Wait!
Wait there!
Father is on the way!
You can't imagine how hard it is.
You keep falling into the mud
if you can't control the sled.
I'm more than a handful.
I feel so sorry.
I have nothing to say.
It's harder to go backward.
Did you get out?
I got out!
I'm already tired.
[They both arrive to the working field.]
[Will they be able to
dig out 1,000 red shells?]
[Bulkyo]
[Jungsun]
I heard that you're good at cooking.
Don't you cook at home?
My wife cooks well.
Really?
What food is she good at making?
She's good at everything.
- She makes good Rich Soybean Paste Stew.
- Really?
She's pretty, is kind to your parents,
kind to you, a good cook, and a good actress.
[She is my wife.]
- I feel embarrassed.
- But that's what you just said.
I think we're here.
I think this is the house
of Madame Choi Geum Ja. Let's get off.
Hello!
This is Yeon Jung Hoon here.
Madame Choi Geum Ja,
is she the great Jang Geum of Jungsun?
Yes, she is.
I think I saw you on TV.
Yes, I'm on TV.
Come help me here.
Are you by chance, Madame Choi Geum Ja?
- Yes, I am.
- The jewel in Jungsun!
- She's making tofu now.
- She's making tofu?
Making tofu?
[Master of traditional food,
the great Jang Geum of Jungsun.]
Can we help you?
I came with Yeon Jung Hoon.
- Where is he?
- He's here.
- Hello!
- His father is Yeon Kyu Jin.
I see.
His wife is Han Ga In.
- I'm 'Hanga' (not busy) today.
- I mean...
[She only thinks about tofu now.]
I thought you just took out
a beating stick.
- Can we help you with that?
- Yes, please.
Put this boiled soy milk
through the cheese cloth.
- I ground the soy beans.
- This is going to be so good!
This silken tofu tastes
totally different from factory-made ones.
[The genuine taste of homemade tofu.]
We also use the soy beans that we grow.
Where are you?
I can't see anything.
It smells nutty.
Suddenly, it feels like the show
'Korean Cuisine and Dining'.
You know the program, right?
Choi Bul Am is the host.
He visited my house, too.
- Did he visit here?
- He came for his second episode.
- You were on the show?
- Yes.
She is indeed
the great Jang Geum of Jungsun.
Korean Cuisine and Dining
came to look for you.
It means you're the great chef.
I'm not good at cooking.
I'm a country bumpkin.
But you were on
Korean Cuisine and Dining.
I just move my fingers to mix the food.
You moved your fingers for
Korean Cuisine and Dining?
- We know it's not that easy.
- But we never use MSG.
We don't use unnecessary seasonings.
- Is this the silken tofu?
- It's going to be.
[Add the bittern in the filtered soy milk
and the tofu hardens.]
[She gives the pot full of tofu
to Jung Hoon and Jae Suk.]
This is how the tofu is made.
[Wrap the silken tofu with cloth.]
[Press it with something heavy
for about 20 minutes]
[to get rid of excessive liquid.]
[All you have to do is wait.]
Can you bring
some Dongjimi(dialect) for me?
Do you mean Dongchimi?
(Water based radish Kimchi.)
It's going to be very cold.
Let me give you some gloves.
[She thinks the coldness
of Kangwon Province is harsh for them.]
[And she gives them
a pair of vinyl gloves.]
- My hands might still be cold.
- I know they will be.
I think it'll be better than nothing.
[Mother's love.]
I think we can have
snow ball fights with these.
[A trying time for
the young master from Seoul.]
He'll get some Dongchimi for you.
Is it where I get Dongchimi?
Wow, it's under the ground?
[Traditional way of storing Kimchi.]
Is it frozen?
Madame gave me these gloves.
I will get it.
[Even the smell is different.]
- I brought Dongchimi.
- Add some water.
- Can you peel this for me?
- That's a potato.
- Peels (dialect).
- Pardon me?
You can put the peels over here.
Peels.
- Potato peels, Jung Hoon.
- Aha!
- Don't I need to wash it?
- You don't need to wash it.
- My hands are frozen.
- Your hands are frozen?
Yes.
My hands are frozen.
You're a typical...
man from a city.
I can tell you've never done this before.
You're even worse than me.
- You try then.
- Move over.
I can tell you never help at home.
Han Ga In does all the work.
Look how I do it.
Just like this.
- That's too thick!
- How can you not help at home?
- You're wasting it.
- Just like this!
How long do you need to peel it?
A day?
Aren't you doing it
for the first time?
Ga In, you're doing a lot of work.
I can tell.
[Grasshopper never stops talking.]
He's too much.
See? How fast I'm doing it?
Kyeung Eun (Jae Suk's wife),
I feel bad for you.
I was the MC for Jung Hoon
and Ga In's wedding.
I have a connection with the couple.
Ga In is a close friend of mine.
Although we don't call each other.
Why? There are people who's close
but don't call each other.
She's still a close friend.
Jung Hoon's father is also a senior
in the entertainment business.
You know when the connections
meet together
positive things can amplify the synergy.
I think we'll have a good luck.
By the way
we have a cooking battle tomorrow.
Can you suggest what we can make?
You can make traditional food.
Traditional food?
What is it?
You can make buckwheat porridge soup.
- With buckwheat?
- Yes.
- Put one spoon.
- One spoon?
We should watch her carefully.
[Pour in the soaked buckwheat
once soybean soup starts to boil.]
[When buckwheat is near finished cooking,
add in the mushrooms and the plum extract.]
- How much? Would one spoonful be enough?
- Yes, one spoonful should be plenty.
- What else do I put in here?
- Then you add in the secret ingredient.
[The secret ingredient, aged soybean paste,
is added into the soup mixture.]
[Young master from Seoul tries a taste.]
- How does it taste?
- It tastes the same.
- Does it not taste very good?
- I don't taste the aged soybean paste.
If it doesn't taste very good,
then I add in a little bit of MSG.
[The master's cool solution to the problem.]
MSG?
- What else am I to do then?
- I thought you said you never use MSG.
What else can I do? I have to add some
if it doesn't taste very good.
She just told us that we can add in a
little bit of MSG if we need to.
No, I don't think we're going to need any.
I think it'll be good on its own.
[She pulls out her secret stash of MSG
that she'd prepared just in case.]
[MSG Grasshopper launches into action.
Dumps in the MSG without any hesitation.]
- Did you let it come to a boil?
- Yes.
- We still have to add in the tofu.
- Can we add that in now?
You sound so much more relaxed now.
[Young master Seoul tries another taste.]
[Yes, this is the good stuff!]
There it is.
I can taste the goodness now.
Ma'am, we're all set now.
[Tofu finishes cooking while they learn
the art of making buckwheat porridge soup.]
Wow, that looks so delicious.
[Being generously liberal with her
fresh and delicious tofu.]
[Buckwheat porridge is finally ready.]
[Buckwheat porridge is a traditional dish
made with tofu, soybean sprouts and potatoes.]
- Please sit, and we'll bring the rice.
- Have some silken tofu, too.
Yes, thank you.
It's good.
[Sweet words of compliment to
the two hard working young men.]
Sir, this really is delicious.
We'll enjoy eating it, too.
- Thank you for the meal.
- This is really good.
[Enjoying a delicious meal together
like one happy family.]
[Even the silken tofu tastes like honey.]
This really isn't bad.
- What are you thinking about?
- Thinking about what we learned.
I completely trust you, Jung Hoon.
- Ma'am, this was such a delicious meal.
- I should be the one to thank you guys.
- No, there's no need to thank us.
- That really was a delicious meal.
Buckwheat soybean porridge.
That with the tofu really was
a fantastic meal together.
[Thus, secrets of the legendary dish
gets passed down to another.]
[Jungsun, Korea.]
[Hong Kong]
[In the midst of all the sunshine
shining brightly atop the tall buildings...]
[A beautiful morning in Hong Kong.]
- Hello.
[Fei starts to speak in
her native Chinese tongue.]
Is everything all set now?
- Did he get what you just told him?
- Yes.
Wow, you're no joke.
[Thanks to Fei's help,
they immediately get on their way!]
[Fei continues to give directions to
the cabdriver in Chinese.]
[Korean speaking Giraffe starts
to feel more and more alienated.]
- Stop talking just amongst yourselves.
- I just asked him how long it would take.
He said at the speed we're going,
it's going to take about 20 minutes.
- I'm hungry.
- I'm really hungry, too.
Yes, I'm very...
I had a really great time.
I just acted as a translator in Hong Kong.
I felt really lost and confused.
[Arrives at the site with hungry stomachs.]
- I'm so hungry!
This market is an infamous
breakfast hotspot in Hong Kong.
This is a market.
I've been here before.
You have to beat the employee in a game of
rock-paper-scissors for both of you to eat.
Can't you just let us eat breakfast?
- We're hungry!
- You may get started.
- Fei, what do you want to eat?
- Just anything.
We need to have breakfast.
- Do you know any good spots around here?
- No, I don't know of any.
- I really want some dim sum.
- Dim Sum... Oh, that looks good!
[They discover an eating hot spot.]
- That place looks good.
- Morning.
[The inside of the restaurant is
already full of diners and customers.]
Wow, this place looks really good.
Look, that's a picture of Chow Yun Fat.
[A place enjoyed by Chow Yun Fat, himself.]
Hello.
What does this place specialize in?
What's really good here?
[Main menu of this restaurant-
Hong Kong's typical breakfast dishes.]
I'm going to get that soup dish.
[The sight of it makes their mouths water.]
- Wow, I really want some of that right now.
- Should we get two of those?
- Yes, let's get the same dish.
Can we please have what she's having?
Is it good?
[Someone who knows how to speak
in Korean in Hong Kong!]
- Do you know how to speak Korean?
- I'm not Korean.
- But you're very good at speaking Korean.
- Wow, that looks so good. Can I smell it?
[Offers her roll out of pity for the Giraffe.]
[The smell is starting to
make his mouth water.]
- But I'm not allowed to eat this right now.
- I'm hungry.
That looks so good.
Yes, this is exactly what I wanted.
[The macaroni soup that they ordered
is brought out to their table.]
- What is this called?
- It's a sort of macaroni soup.
[A common breakfast soup in Hong Kong
that is full of protein and flavor.]
- I love foods like this.
[Everyone's favorite, sausage and eggs.]
[Hong Kong's traditional breakfast menu.]
I'm very hungry.
- Can I just take a bite?
- No, you can't.
Kwang Soo, you have to set your spoon down.
- How about just a bean?
- No, you can't.
Let's just win the mission and eat.
Let's not be so pitiful about it.
[They both need to win at a game of rock-
paper-scissors in order to be able to eat.]
I'm really good at this game.
[The owner of the restaurant comes up
to the table to play the game.]
We have to play a game of
rock-paper-scissors.
Are you going to throw out a rock?
I'll throw out a scissors
so that the two of you can eat.
[A secret deal that's made in a language
that the PD's aren't able to understand.]
[Are you ready?]
[I'm going to throw out a scissors.]
[Fei loses from having thrown out
a paper out of her confusion.]
[An extreme sense of regret
from her hungry state.]
- Please let me try it again!
- No, I'll be eating your breakfast.
[I told you that I was going to
throw out a scissors.]
- I was too nervous. Let me do it again.
- I'll be eating your breakfast.
What about me?
Let me eat some of it, at least.
[Goodbye macaroni soup,
and goodbye sausage and eggs.]
[And the milk and tea.]
[Hungry Giraffe can't let go
of his disappointment.]
[His delicious looking dishes are
being enjoyed by the staff members.]
[One more sniff for the road.]
[Off to find the next restaurant.]
Fei, you should've discussed
your plan of action with me first.
- Okay.
- Wow, what's this?
[Street butcher stand with fresh meat.]
- Look at all the baby back ribs.
I think this is where all the customers
comes to get their meat.
- I think it's a local butcher stand.
- It's a butcher stand?
It's like we're newlyweds right now.
- That's so delicious!
- What is it?
- It's my favorite vegetable.
- It's usually stir-fried, isn't it?
- It's usually stir-fried.
- I heard you eat it like kimchi?
Wow, look at all the fruit!
[Stomachs growling at the sight of fruit.]
- I'm so hungry... what is all this?
You know what this is, don't you?
It's Yutao.
[Yutao- Fried fermented flour dough.
A popular Chinese snack.]
The batter is fried,
and it's usually eaten as breakfast pastry.
Then let's try this place.
[Decides on the restaurant
without any further hesitation.]
[Main menu items at this restaurant are
beef congee and yutao.]
- It's basically beef porridge.
- Beef porridge?
- Beef porridge is really good.
- It looks really good.
- They have stir-fried noodles, too.
- I want the beef porridge.
In that case...
[An order of beef congee and yutao.]
I'm really hungry.
Let's eat. I can't hold off any longer.
[Giraffe looks gaunt with hunger.
Will he be able to succeed this time around?]
[Their ordered food
is brought out to their table.]
- Kwang Soo, you go first.
[Do I have to do something?]
We have to win a game of rock-paper-scissors
against you before we can start eating.
- Okay, I got it.
- Are these chunks of beef?
- Beef.
- Do we dip the yutao in the congee?
- You have to play the game first.
- Okay.
[Are we supposed to play it now?]
Can you please throw out a scissors?
[Making another deal this time around.]
[Don't worry, Fei.]
[Just what in the world
are they talking about?]
[Trying to signal the Giraffe.]
[Did he catch onto Fei's signal?]
[Giraffe misinterprets Fei's signal.]
[This guy is driving me nuts!]
I thought you had it all set up.
[I did have it all set up,
but you didn't understand my signal.]
- Ugh, I really love dishes like this.
- We have to go, there's not much time.
[Off to the next restaurant.]
Look at that in the picture!
That's the Chinese version of kimchi.
- That is?
- Yes, this is what I told you about earlier.
It's stir-fried white kimchi.
- Want to try this place out?
- I'm going to win this round no matter what.
Yes, I agree.
[Main menu items-
A variety of various noodle dishes.]
Is that a rice dish?
[What is he doing over there?]
It's a rice dish.
Rice dishes are so satisfying.
[His extreme state of hunger has him
fixating on other people's food.]
[If he gets any hungrier, then he'll
start stealing other people's food.]
Fei, we need to win this time around.
I've decided that we can't let this go on.
I want the rice dish
that he's eating right now.
- Really?
- But I want it with noodles.
- With noodles?
- I want this one.
This dish is made with pig intestines.
- Kind of like blood sausage?
- Yes, just like that.
- Then let's order that dish.
- Okay.
Noodles with pig intestines.
What is that dish over there?
[The tall giant is pulled towards the new dish
as if hypnotized by its scent.]
[A steamy bowl of soup...
and a brain that's starting to get soggy...]
He really must be very hungry.
Wow, that's really my cup of tea.
Wow, that does look very good.
[Danger!
A creepy lurker within the restaurant!]
He's making the man feel uncomfortable.
Is it good?
[Who is this creature?]
Our dish is coming!
[Their ordered dish is finally ready!]
[I vow to eat this dish!]
We can only eat this noodle soup if we
beat you in a game of rock-paper-scissors.
[Hang on, Kwang Soo!]
Let me explain the rules of the games first,
then we can actually play it.
So we're going to throw out a paper.
You're going to throw out a paper?
[Kwang Soo wins by accident!]
[A work of miracle in the midst of confusion
between Kwang Soo and the server.]
[If Fei wins her turn, then they
finally wins their breakfast mission.]
[Fei understands the server's confusion,
and throws out a rock like Kwang Soo did.]
[Kwang Soo and Fei
finally wins their mission.]
I was really starting to struggle.
Can you please tell her that for me?
Tell her that I was starting to get so sad,
and really starting to struggle.
Thank you so much.
- Fei, enjoy your breakfast.
- Okay, you too.
[Finally gets to enjoy their breakfast.]
- You like to drink, don't you, Fei?
- No, I don't like to drink.
I'm just so excited
that we finally get to eat.
Wow, this is really good.
I've never had anything like this before.
Really?
Isn't it an addicting taste?
Can't stop eating it, right?
[Kwang Soo and Fei's mission comes to an end
with an unending sigh of contentment.]
[Jeju Island]
- Let's go.
[Ji Hyo and Taecyeon are in Jeju Island.]
Isn't that Seongsan Ilchulbong Tuff Cone?
[National historical landmark.]
[An unpredictable mission that awaits them
in this beautiful and historical site.]
Jeju Island dialect
that we studied earlier...
[Been studying Jeju Island dialect...
will they be able to succeed their mission?]
- There they are.
- Ma'am!
- Hello.
- Welcome, welcome!
[Even the initial greetings from these
female divers are hard to decipher.]
Is that halibut?
[An impressive array of
various different sea creatures.]
- That's sea cucumber.
- This is sea cucumber?
Look at this sea cucumber.
Aren't they supposed to be longer?
- I've never seen it like this.
- They shrink when they're out of the water.
[Even gets a lesson on sea creatures
before starting their mission.]
- Can I try it?
- Sure, you can try it.
This sea cucumber was caught by
these ladies just moments ago.
- We just caught this ourselves.
- Wow, this is just so fresh.
- I've never seen one so big.
- I think this is the biggest I've seen, too.
It's the red sea cucumber.
- Try a piece now.
- Go on and eat.
This is so delicious.
This is such a rare treat.
- Ma'am...
[What about their mission?]
What is our mission?
'Men-do-rong Tto-Tto-hol Ttae,
Hwak Deul-li-jap-Suk, mehrong.'
Excuse me?
I didn't understand you.
'Men-do-rong Tto-Tto-hol Ttae,
Hwak Deul-li-jap-Suk, mehrong.'
[Blank...]
[Are you okay?
Caught off guard, aren't you?]
'Men-do-rong Tto-Tto-hol Ttae,
Hwak Deul-li-jap-Suk'?
- Did I get that right?
- Yes.
[They can't even follow the dialect,
let alone figure out how to decipher it!]
- I seriously have no idea what she's saying.
- I told you that this was going to be hard.
[This is like deciphering a secret code.]
I think what she said was...
Can you say it for us one more time?
'Men-do-rong Tto-Tto-hol Ttae,
Hwak Deul-li-jap-Suk, mehrong.'
What do you think she's saying?
What is she saying?
- She's saying...
- This is a mission, right? You know what?
I think she's saying that we should eat
the seafood as soon as she cuts it.
- No, I'm not.
- No? She says no.
[Taecyeon, don't even fool yourself...]
[It looks like dark roads are ahead
for this young man from Seoul.]
- What do you think she's saying?
- Do you understand anything I'm saying?
Gam Soo Kwang.
[Ah... I miss my mommy.]
- Coffee?
- She wants us to drink the coffee?
[Could this be what she's saying?]
Don't you think that she's telling us
to drink the coffee while eating the seafood?
While eating this?
The sea cucumber?
You're telling us to eat the sea cucumber
and drink the hot coffee along with it?
- I think that's what she's saying.
- Ma'am, is that it?
[Will Taecyeon's guess be correct in
deciphering Jeju Island dialect?]
Dip the sliced sea cucumber in the sauce,
and take a slurp of the hot coffee with it.
[Taecyeon's guess-
Dip the sea cucumber in the hot sauce.]
- Yum, that's so delicious.
[Then take a slurp of the hot coffee.]
- You got half of it correct.
- We got the half of it correct.
We got half the mission correct?
What was it?
[What did we get right, and what was wrong?]
- What was it that she said at the end?
- 'Mehrong'?
[Could that be the correct
portion of the mission?]
- Say the word after eating it?
- Eat the sea cucumber first.
- And the coffee...
- Drink the coffee.
- Drink the coffee before it gets cold.
- Drink it.
- Then say the word.
- Mehrong.
[Mission fail]
- Did you not stick out your tongue?
- No, I did stick out my tongue.
- You have to act it out precisely.
- We have to act it out precisely?
- Please say it for us one more time.
'Men-do-rong Tto-Tto-hol Ttae,
Hwak Deul-li-jap-Suk, mehrong.'
You have to act out only the portion
that she's telling you right now.
[We have to act out only the portion
that she's telling us to?]
[Now that they think about it,
the sentence she spoke was very short.]
[Then could it mean...]
- I figured it out. I think I know what it is.
She just wants us to drink the coffee.
Just drink the coffee.
[Just drink the coffee...]
- And say, mehrong.
[Could the answer be this simple?]
- That's correct.
- Yes!
- See? Yes, we got it!
[Jeju Island dialect mission- Success..]
We just needed to drink the coffee.
It was only about the coffee.
- Ma'am, Jeju dialect is way too hard.
- But we understand Seoul talk very easily.
So why do you have such a hard time
with our Jeju dialect?
Ma'am, what is 'Gam Soo Kwang'?
- It means, 'Where are you going?'
- Really?
- So that's what it means?
- Do you know this song?
[A joyous celebration of
'Gam Soo Kwang' song.]
- See? I told you that the song exists!
- We succeeded our mission.
- Yes, we did! Good job, Taecyeon.
- What's our ingredient?
- Drink the hot coffee and say, mehrong.
[Where do we go now to start cooking?]
It's another mission?
[Wait, there's another mission?]
[Get your ingredients by fishing for
five silvery cutlass fish from the ocean.]
Get your ingredients by fishing for
five silvery cutlass fish from the ocean...
[On my goodness...]
[Are they kidding us right now?]
[No wonder why they fed us
the cutlass fish lunch earlier today...]
[There were five pieces of fish
in the braised fish dish earlier...]
[And five pieces of the grilled fish...]
[Now they're telling us to go out
and catch five fishes of our own...]
[I thought we were going with
Jeju Island honeymoon theme...]
[But this is the real reality of life.]
[Have a great time!]
We're off to catch the cutlass fish.
We'll be back with our cutlass fish!
We're going to go and catch a lot of fish!
[Will these two be able to safely come back
with their five cutlass fish?]
[Tai'an, China.]
Let's go fishing for small octopus!
- Go, go!
[Suk Jin and Yoo Sun- Catch 6kg of octopus.]
- This is nice, isn't it?
- It's not bad with the nice weather.
This is nice.
This is much better than I had expected.
[Let's go out on the boat
and fish for small octopus!]
- The boat's very fast. I feel freed.
- I feel like I can really breathe.
[Throwing away all their worries and
anxieties off to the wind.]
- And I'm here with one of my favorite actors.
[Big-nose with one of his favorite actresses.]
I'm being serious.
[Both are in the best of spirits.]
- Don't worry about a thing!
- Then catch all the octopus for us.
I'll take care of the fishing,
so you can take care of the cooking.
I wonder if they have any
hot sauce on the boat.
Nothing tastes better than being able to
eat your freshly caught seafood.
[Off into the depths of the ocean...]
Okay, I think we're here.
[Finally arrives at their fishing location.]
- Just tell us what you want us to do.
- We're going to be starting off right here.
We're going to cast out the net from here,
and you're going to have to pull it back in.
- Are the octopus under us right now?
- We'll just have to pull the net back in.
So all the octopus are already
caught in the net right now?
- They're inside the seashells.
- Really? They crawl inside the seashells?
- They're already inside there?
[He's been saying they're already inside!]
We just have to pull them out after
they've already crawled into the shells.
- Then do we have to pull them all out?
- Do we pull them out?
Seriously?
[Pulling the octopus out of the shells
requires 100% manual labor.]
- Are there really small octopus here?
- This spot is crawling with them.
- Really?
- Isn't it past the season for it?
- No, this is actually the breeding season.
- So there are lots of the small octopus?
- Is it going to be impressive?
- Yes, you'll see for yourself.
I'm so excited!
I'm excited!
[We'll see you soon, small octopus.]
[Pulling up the net of seashells
that they had cast into the ocean.]
Here it comes, I see it!
[Will they really find a small
octopus inside the shell?]
[Must pull the octopus out in first try
as soon as they see it inside the shell.]
We have to check each and every one.
This one is empty.
[Time to start checking all the seashells.]
Nothing.
[All the seashells are coming up empty...]
- Check the one that just came up.
- Which one?
- Yes, I see it.
- I see it!
- Get the hook in there and pull it out.
[There's something inside the shell!]
- Get out of there!
- You're really good!
Let me see.
It's a small octopus!
[Catches the first
small octopus of their lives.]
[Still can't believe what they're seeing.]
- Wow, I can't believe they're really here!
[A huge adrenaline rush!]
You're really cruel.
Wow... hey!
[Pulls out her second small octopus.]
- You're such a brutish woman!
- Don't you even feel bad for them?
- Here's another one!
- Pull it out.
- Get out of there!
[Yoo Sun is onto her third catch already!]
Why are you so cruel?
I was told that this was her first
fishing boat expedition.
But she was like a fisherman's daughter.
Fisherman's eldest daughter.
The daughter that goes out to catch the fish
in place of her father when he's ill or sick.
That's the kind of power
that I saw within her.
I thought that Yoo Sun was a machine.
You know what I mean, don't you?
I see another one!
[While octopus hunter, Yoo Sun,
is busy hunting for her prey...]
[Her 'ill father', Big-nose,
just watches from behind her.]
I see another one!
[Pulls... and pulls some more out.]
[The precise movements of a new expert.]
I'm just cheering for her from behind her.
She's doing such a great job.
[It's as if she's done this all her life.]
[Did you enjoy fishing for octopus?]
- Maybe it's because I hyped it up too much?
But it was much better than I had expected.
It was actually fun.
Were you an octopus fisherman
in your previous life?
I sure lucked out with my partner!
[Will they be able to catch 6kg
of small octopus before the sunset?]
[Big-nose tries his hand at it.]
I'm sorry!
[Big-nose gets his very first small octopus!]
I think this is small enough
for me to eat right now.
[Dips the still live small octopus
into the hot sauce...]
[And puts it right into his mouth.]
[The attack of the tentacles.]
Ouch, that hurts.
- You have to cut it up first.
[Some extra sauce on his big nose.]
[Another attempt at getting
the octopus into his mouth.]
[A mouth full of the freshest
octopus the sea has to offer.]
It's really good.
[Time for Yoo Sun to give it a taste.]
Just slurp it all into your mouth.
- Isn't it good?
[Slurps down the last bit of the leg.]
Isn't it so delicious?
- Let's make an amazing dish with this.
- Yes, I agree.
- The ingredient is so fresh.
- It's the freshest ingredient.
It's going to be good no matter what.
Here's another one.
[Fisherman's daughter pulls out
the octopus that Big-nose has lost.]
I got it.
- Did you get it?
- Every last one is very precious.
[And another precious one is
slurped into Big-nose's mouth.]
You can't eat every single one that we catch!
[This one can't seem to grasp
the mood his partner is in.]
Yes, pull it out.
Wow, this one is huge!
[Big-nose isn't doing any of the work?]
- Wait a minute.
- Wow, this is awesome.
[The octopus squirts ink
all over Yoo Sun's face.]
Your face.... looks so pretty right now.
- You look so pretty.
- Keep it going.
[The sun starts to dip
lower into the horizon...]
This is so great...
I'm in such a great mood!
You're not going to beat me!
[Octopus cry and cheer that can be heard
throughout the western sea.]
We're going to win first place!
[Were Suk Jin and Yoo Sun able to
catch their 6kg of octopus?]
[Jeju Island]
[Clear blue skies of Jeju Island.]
I don't remember the last time
I went away like this on my own.
- Look at the scenery next to you.
- It's so beautiful.
Just enjoy yourself today.
[A moment of freedom
for this mother of three.]
Wow, the ocean looks so beautiful.
[Your first impression of your partner, Shoo?]
- Shoo was my favorite member of S.E.S.
And she's now the mother of three
and I saw how she just lit up
the moment we arrived on Jeju Island.
Seeing that almost brought a tear to my eye.
I really want to bring home
the victory for my partner, Shoo.
What is all this?
- I don't see anything here.
- What are we supposed to do here?
This is a field of winter carrots.
- Get a total of 300 carrots...
- What?
Clear the mission by harvesting
a total of 300 carrots.
[Time to start harvesting
the winter carrots.]
Wow, it's really huge.
[Did he get something?]
- Wow, look at this. It's huge!
- Wow!
It's like the size of a radish.
[Immediately pulls out his second carrots.]
It's really big!
[A size that can only
be seen on Jeju Island.]
I can tell that you're a mother because you
give out complements in a high octave.
You know how people compliment babies?
[High octave compliments.]
- Look at this one!
- We've struck gold!
[A family of carrots.]
- We've already got ten.
- You're so positive.
Wow, they look so delicious.
- Ha Ha!
- Wow, how many are there?
[A cluster of carrot triplets!]
[Did the mother of twins pass off
her karma to the carrots?]
That was awesome!
We're like working machines.
[Immerses themselves into carrot harvesting
without even noticing the flow of time.]
I think I'm going to sleep very well tonight.
[Compared to raising three kids,
harvesting 300 carrots is a piece of cake.]
[The victorious carrot ceremony.]
You have succeeded your
300 carrot harvest mission.
[300 carrot harvest- Success.]
Look at my filthy nails.
[A glass of carrot juice for their efforts!]
Here's to a pair of twin boys
for you in the new year!
No thank you!
[I already have my hands full with three.]
[Ha Ha and Shoo's second mission-
Feed the black pigs.]
[A shower of dried plums for the pigs.]
[Black pigs of Jeju Island are fed plums
to grow big and lean.]
- What good eaters they are.
- The sound of their eating is almost musical.
[Since they've come to Jeju Island,
it's time to grill up some black pork.]
- Hello?
- Yes, hello?
- Hey, Soo Young.
- Hi, Tony.
We have a competition coming up
where our pride is on the line.
[Shoo's friend, Chef Tony Oh, is called
for some input on finalizing their menu.]
The ingredients that we have to use
are black pork and kimchi.
- Those are winning ingredients.
- We're going to win?
You have to use the meat
from the front leg portion of the pork.
We were told that's the yummy part.
You're going to make kimchi stew with it.
But you're going to put a twist on it,
and make curry kimchi stew.
- Curry kimchi stew?
- What? Curry kimchi stew?
- Hard to fathom, isn't it?
- Yes, I can't imagine that at all.
Ha Ha, I guarantee that
it's going to bring home the win.
- Curry kimchi stew.
- I think that's a nice idea.
Okay, we're all set.
[Their menu is set on curry kimchi stew.]
- Thank you!
- Call me and let me know how it goes.
[Let's push off thinking about the recipe
until we're done with the grilled pork.]
I'm going to validate myself with this win.
- I'll impress everyone with the taste.
- I'm not going to be afraid of the judges.
- Things are really going our way.
- It's either win it or lose it.
- Something very creative.
- We'll work hard and bring home the win.
- We're going to make the ultimate dish.
- I feel very confident about it.
- We're very strategic about our plans.
- We're going to keep our hidden card hidden.
[Gary and Sung Ryung's attempts to find
the means to an end to the street cuisine.]
Is it a juice or something?
[Sung Ryung starts speaking
to the man in her Korean tongue.]
[Continues to repeat, 'Ai-Ddim-Kkag-Ddi'.
But what does that even mean?]
[They must find what they're looking for
in order to succeed the mission.]
[Meanwhile, Jae Suk and Jung Hoon
are still in the rural outskirts of Gangwon.]
You have to gather 1kg of wild mushrooms.
You have to complete the mission in order
to obtain the participation ticket.
- Without it, you can't participate.
- Watch your steps.
[Thus starts their dangerous search
for the wild mushrooms in the mountains.]
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo are knee deep
out in the mud flats.]
I think I feel something.
I see something!
I got some!
[It must be cockle season.]
[Mr. Capable proves his capabilities
even out in the mud flats.]
[Has Seo Woo also acclimated herself
to the conditions of the mud flats?]
- Am I now fit to marry someone around here?
- You can be my daughter-in-law.
[Jong Kook and Seo Woo are
the new cockle shell team.]
- This is the dim sum of all dim sums.
- It must be very popular?
Yes, it's the most popular kind.
Look out for the gold flake.
[The deep flavors of dim sum that
he's getting to taste in its native land.]
The shrimp itself in here is different.
This is so delicious.
Like you said,
if we put some kimchi in here
the flavors of it would
suit the judges' taste buds
and I think we'll be able to create
a special sort of dish.
[Fei writes the directions down in Chinese.]
How am I supposed to read it
when you write it down in Chinese?
[Is this the start of
Kwang Soo and Fei's strife?]
- Wow, there are tons of them.
- They weigh a good amount on its own.
Wow, this is amazing.
[A steaming pot of small octopus
ramen out on the open waters!]
[What dish will they make
with kimchi and small octopus?]
[And Jae Suk and Jung Hoon are still
hiking after two whole hours of it.]
[A troublesome expedition
for the wild mushrooms.]
[But they finally find the mother load
of Phellinus linteus mushrooms.]
Here it is!
- There they are up there.
[A discovery of wild Phellinus linteus.]
We've struck gold!
[A gift down from the heavens.
What dish will they make with the mushrooms?]
- How is it this sweet?
- Wow, this is really good!
[Ha Ha and Shoo are given their
magical elixir of fresh carrot juice.]
- Thank you.
- The color looks so pretty.
[How will they use the elixir
in their winning dish?]
Okay, we're going to start fishing.
Can you please teach us how to catch them?
[Desperately waiting
for the cuttlefish to bite.]
[The pole is bent!]
[The cuttlefish...
starts to make its appearance.]
[All the preparations are now complete
for the 2015 Cooking Battle.]
[Time to put taste against taste.]
- Today's winner is...
[The ultimate dish that'll capture the
taste buds of the four hottest chefs are here.]
I think it's good.
[The moment is finally here.]
[Take the kimchi given,
and within the allotted time limit...]
[The ultimate cooking battle
with the world's best ingredients.]
[Aspiring King of the Kitchen-
Place everything you have on the line.]
[You'll taste something even better
than your wildest imagination.]
[2015 Cooking Battle-
Who will be the ultimate victor?]
Wow, that's phenomenal.
[2015 Cooking Battle- Part Two.]