[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Kwang Soo's everything.]
[Desirable Kwang Soo.]
[Of Kwang Soo, by Kwang Soo
and for Kwang Soo!]
[But... is that all today...?]
[Six chairs for seven members?]
- There are only six seats.
- Where is the last chair?
- Gary's a celebrity today.
- Gary...
I like your clothes.
[Ji Hyo, Ha Ha and Jong Kook arrive.]
I had some business
to take care of.
- There are no chairs?
- There are six chairs only.
Where's Kwang Soo?
Isn't this Kwang Soo's neighborhood?
Today, Lee Kwang Soo
is the main character.
Is Kwang Soo the main today?
Kwang Soo will
get to know that shortly.
Really?
Suk Jin and I came here last week.
Oh, you mean Kwang Soo's house?
Kwang Soo told me he'd give
me a room when he moves.
I've been there, but
he has no rooms to give.
Before we start the race
Kwang Soo thinks
that we're filming at 1 p.m.
Because he's the main today,
we're going to his house.
What?
[Visiting Giraffe's house?]
It was two years ago...
didn't we go to Namyangjoo?
I know this place really well!
We will be visiting his house,
as a surprise opening.
As a warm-up, we have prepared
an expedition mission.
[We will search Kwang Soo's house?]
[Everything about Giraffe...]
[will be revealed.]
- Congratulations on the house warming!
- Nice to see you!
[We will soon see this face.]
He doesn't know that it's
a housewarming party.
The house is too small for
the Prince of Asia.
He still lives at a rental,
he used to rent a celebrity's house.
But the landlord sold the house.
He used to pay the monthly rent
at Hyung Jun's house.
- You cruel people.
[They prepared housewarming gifts.]
- Let's go.
- Should we go?
[Going to Kwang Soo's
house in a good mood.]
- Is he awake?
- He should be awake.
Kwang Soo's probably feeling good
about the delayed filming schedule.
- Kwang Soo?
- This neighborhood is really nice.
- Kwang Soo's car.
- Seo Jun lives nearby too.
This is your first time here, right?
- Yeah, it's their first.
- Except Jae Suk and I.
- Did you get everything?
- Yeah.
Was it five days ago?
- He lives in a nice apartment.
- Yes, he does.
He lives in a nice place.
He must have made a lot of money.
Kwang Soo doesn't tell us,
but he seems to have made a lot.
It turns out that he's rich.
My agency should have
made a contract with Kwang Soo.
The elevator is a little slow.
- Yes, it's slow.
- There's a con.
Now, let's be quiet.
[Arrival at Kwang Soo's floor.]
[The infiltration operation begins.]
- He lives really high up.
- You don't know his password?
- I forgot.
[Hesitate.]
- Should I call his manager and ask?
- Jae Suk, just open the door.
Do you have cutting pliers?
[It looks like as if they're
going to arrest a criminal.]
- What if he is with his girlfriend?
- Then that's a jackpot!
Then we'll put mosaic effects on her.
We can just introduce
her as his wife, casually.
If it's a celebrity, that's
even more of a jackpot!
Film his shoe rack first.
Her shoes will be at the entrance, right?
We can cut it out later.
Just press the door bell.
- Is he sleeping?
- Still?
Is he not at home?
[Anxious.]
- Is he not home?
-It's possible.
- He's coming!
- Kwang Soo, its me.
- The camera is visible.
- Kwang Soo!
[Hello.]
[The surprise attack
at Giraffe's house, start!]
[A broadcast like
a bolt out of the blue.]
[Shocked.]
[At 11:26 a.m., the big
reveal of Kwang Soo's house.]
[The VJ's will enter too.]
Congratulations!
Wow, it's so clean!
[The invasion of the cameras.]
[Giraffe's house has been
invaded by foreign powers.]
[I'm a little confused...]
Kwang Soo turned the shower on.
- Kwang Soo!
[Is this going on broadcast?]
Why are there so many
toothbrushes?
Wow, it's so nice!
- The view is great!
[A luxurious view of Han River.]
- Yeah! Over here!
[Gary enters the bedroom first.]
Is this your bed?
Kwang Soo!
Do you sleep here?
His house is so nice.
[This is Giraffe's house.]
[Giraffe's day begins and ends here.]
- Kwang Soo, do you sleep here?
- Kwang Soo.
What the heck is going on?
- Kwang Soo, what's your address?
- Kwang Soo.
- Hello, address?
- Tell him the address so we can order.
- What?
- The address.
One sweet and sour pork,
three black bean noodle...
We can eat out!
- two fried rice, and
two seafood noodles.
And dumplings on the house!
Kwang Soo, you must be confused.
You should finish brushing your teeth.
[Big Nose's report on the smaller room.]
- He collects a lot of figures.
Wow.
- Wow, it's nice.
- What?
If you look closely,
you can find Jae Suk.
- Get out!
- Wait a second.
- I need to find something!
- What are you looking for?
What are you looking for?
- What?
- What are you looking for?
- Are you looking for porn?
- What do you mean, porn?
- What are you doing then?
- Why would I be looking for porn?
- The house is so nice, it's cute.
- Kwang Soo, hurry and get ready.
What is this?
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
I'm going to call the police!
[Blank Ji is crawling
around to find a jackpot.]
Where do you hang your laundry?
[Why?]
- That's not the leopard boxers.
- What are you doing?
- Kwang Soo, do you have arm warmers?
- Kwang Soo, where's your leopard print?
You have it, right?
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- He wears the leopard boxers a lot.
Everyone get out!
Why are you doing this?
You said filming was at one!
- Why are you doing this?
- You need to be calm.
- The house is so nice.
- No!
Kwang Soo, finish getting ready.
Where does your girlfriend
mostly stay when she's over?
Wait, let me brush my teeth!
Sit down!
Where are your leopard print boxers?
Where are your leopard boxers?
[Why are you looking for my leopard
print boxers at a housewarming?]
- Today's main is Lee Kwang Soo.
- Really?
So to warm up, we've prepared
an expedition mission.
Find six items in Kwang Soo's
house.
You will succeed if you find
four out of six items.
[1. A hair strand of 20 cm, 2.
Leopard print boxers]
[3. Food over the expiration date,
4. A computer folder with a bird name]
[5. A letter from a fan,
6. A non-family member female photograph.]
Finding a hair strand of 20 cm.
Finding a folder with
a bird name on the computer?
It's someone's personal preference.
If you don't name a new folder
it automatically names
it as a bird name. (with Alzip)
How do you know that?
[I can't tell you that.]
You must have a pheasant
on your computer.
[His love for birds.]
Is that a strand of hair?
[Did she catch a big fish?]
Is it Kwang Soo's?
I think I've seen his
leopard-printed ones.
Me too...
- I think I've seen them.
- I definitely saw them.
I swear he has them.
[Kkuk checks the fridge first.]
[His fridge is messy.]
This dressing has a
long expiration date.
- I can't find a hair...
[He's checking the expiration dates.]
that's long enough.
- Which one are you talking about?
- Here's a girl's dress!
- Where?
That's what Kwang Soo
wears all the time.
- It's locked with a password.
[Big-nose is on the computer.]
I've unlocked it!
You have a time limit though.
As soon as you get inside
order some food for delivery and
do the mission before the food comes.
[Ha Ha ordered food
delivery for the mission.]
[That's how they started
the exploration.]
[Kwang Soo, finally
finishes brushing teeth.]
- What is this?
- I can't find a girl's picture, either.
[What is this for?]
It's hard to find anything
in a new house.
What are you doing?
It's difficult to find
anything in a new house.
Why are you doing this to me?
Get out, you too!
What are you doing?
- What are you filming?
[He's ordering the VJ to get out, too.]
Where are his letters from fans?
Kwang Soo!
You scared me!
What's wrong with you?
Where is the boxer?
- What boxer?
- The one with the leopard print.
[He's checking the one he's wearing.]
You're taking herbal tonics?
You have a lot of soju in the fridge.
What's the combination with
alcohol and healthy tonics?
You have more soju than me!
Wow, he's just saying it
because it's not his.
Is there a letter from a fan?
- I'm still searching for them.
- He's should many letters.
Long hairs should be in the kitchen.
By the end of 2012. June. 28.
[Big-nose is sitting on the computer.]
[Looking for a folder
with a bird's name.]
[Recent]
[Privacy protection]
There's a folder named 'Chicken.'
[He found a bird's name!]
Can you find me a hair
that's 20 cm long?
Why would I have a hair that long?
- Don't take it personally, I just need one.
- My hair's not that long.
So... you don't have any?
Should I search the bathroom?
Here it is.
[The writer is humiliated
in front of everyone.]
What's everyone doing?
[My house has turned
into a game site...]
I came here last week and
had chicken and noodles.
Should we eat that?
This is the letter from a fan.
It's a storybook that
a fan of Kwang Soo made for him.
- This book is for Kwang Soo.
- Yes, it is a kind of a fan letter.
- That's right.
- Look at the photo.
Was your mouth caught
by a fishing hook?
[His lip on the left side
seems like it.]
[They're trying to find a long
hair in the walk-in closet.]
[What is Blank Ji doing?]
[They're going to use
Ji Hyo's hair for the mission.]
Give me a hair that's 20 cm long.
Excuse me, what is this?
This is long!
[The hair strands that
Ji Hyo scattered around.]
- I found one, too!
- That's Ji Hyo's hair!
These two are different colors.
[Check the length first.]
[They look long enough.]
How many girls visit this place?
One is black and the other is brown.
You've succeeded your mission.
[They've finished the exploration.]
[Buzzer beater! The food came
at the moment of success!]
Let me pay, where is my wallet?
Why don't you pay for the food?
It's your housewarming party!
- Who said it's today?
- It's hot, can you turn on the AC?
Who turns on the AC for this weather?
I've turned off the heater.
- You turned on the heater?
- Just to use hot water!
[Anger meter is going up.]
- Why are you mad?
Kwang Soo is upset.
[I could really hit them now.]
- I understand you, Kwang Soo.
What are you trying to do?
Wait, Kwang Soo.
I'm on your side.
You're on my side?
[He's upset.]
Kwang Soo...
if you want to delete a file, you
need to empty the recycling bin.
I found a few files.
What are you talking about?
Kwang Soo was a man!
He was a man, too!
I didn't know that.
[The exploration of Kwang Soo's
house was successful.]
[The meal arrived.]
He's here.
I'll show you magic.
[It transforms from a coffee
table to a dining table.]
Kwang Soo, let me treat you a meal.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
[Are you pacifying me
after what you did?]
We're here to take care of you
and feed you.
[Do you know how much we
care for you?]
[Kwang Soo wears
his microphone now.]
It's good.
Look, what I just did.
I tried to grab this onion
without unwrapping it.
I guess you're enjoying it so much.
I tried to pick up a slice of onion
without unwrapping.
Please come when I want you to.
[He won't be able to open his
door to anyone easily.]
Suk Jin and I came to visit you because
we were worried you'd be lonely.
We've waited for about
two hours here.
Why would you wait for two hours
inside when I'm not here?
Don't come out,
if you have nowhere to go!
No, we had a schedule
but it was canceled.
[He looks pitiful.]
I know you're eating, but
please listen.
We've started with an unusual mission.
Were you surprised, Kwang Soo?
[What kind of a question is that?]
The reason that we came to
Kwang Soo's house is...
because Kwang Soo is the main
character for this race.
[Today's main character, Kwang Soo.]
- That's why we're here!
[He looks a bit happy.]
- Let me listen to what is it.
Today's race is
'Desirable Lee Kwang Soo.'
Lee Kwang Soo has the critical
role in winning this race.
- You must be happy.
- That's why we came here.
Can we win when
Kwang Soo plays it well?
Kwang Soo is the King Maker
for winning the race.
In the end, someone who wins
Kwang Soo will win the race.
- Kwang Soo is going to be popular today.
- He looks happy.
[I feel much better now.]
Kwang Soo, you're our...
You can win a hint by
winning the interim mission.
The rest of the members
need to earn Kwang Soo's heart.
In the end, only the one who stays
with Kwang Soo will win this race.
It'll be hectic to earn
Kwang Soo's heart.
I remember what you did at my house.
- I didn't really do anything.
- Who found the long hair?
- It was Gary.
- No, It wasn't.
- It's Jae Suk.
- No, It's Ha Ha.
You'll see when it's on TV,
I disapproved the idea.
- Didn't you ring the doorbell?
- That's right.
He asked your manager
to get the pin number.
He cursed when he knew
the pin changed.
[I'm watching you...]
He was the happiest
to hear about this game.
[That's how Kwang Soo
acquired absolute power...]
[30 minutes have passed
for Kwang Soo's makeup.]
You've arrived, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
Get out of your car.
The main character is here.
You're still inside your car?
I cooled the air for you.
- I did it on purpose.
- You have to get out and greet him first.
He's not going to go with you!
- Pick one person who'll go with you.
- Just one person?
You know I drive safe!
- I had no accident for 20 years.
- I don't drive over 80 Km/h.
You know I'm a good driver.
I'm at your beck and call today.
- You dropped honorifics in your speech?
- Please.
I think Gary is disqualified.
You're disqualified, Gary.
That's fine by me!
I've been frustrated by you!
You won when you played
the game with me.
- That's right.
- She has a lack of sleep.
It'll be really boring
if you go with her.
Song Ji Hyo fails!
- Ji Suk Jin fails!
- Why?
Just because!
You're lucky that I didn't hit you!
[Big-nose revealed
Kwang Soo's masculinity.]
I cleaned the table
when we were done eating.
- Don't forget that.
- I'll chose one of you.
What's on your neck?
Are you tired?
Do you have a stiff neck?
Try rotating your neck.
Fail!
That's dangerous!
How dare you trying to guard
Kwang Soo in that condition!
You still can't fight against him.
I'll raise the hand of
the person who I'll go with.
- You know I'll listen to you.
- The one I will go with...
He'll bother you if you
choose him.
Ha Dong Hoon!
- Get out of here!
- See?
- I was just kidding.
- You know this is just the beginning!
I'll see you later, Sir!
- Look how imprudent he is!
- Kwang Soo, stop being arrogant!
Ha Ha is a flatterer
in Infinity Challenge, too.
Seriously, this is not
Girl's Generation.
It's Lee Kwang Soo's generation!
- This is Kwang Soo's generation!
- Don't say that!
Soo, Soo, Soo, Soo,
Kwang Soo's generation.
Lee Kwang Soo,
I'll serve you well today!
- Let's go!
- Please drive safe.
That's a must.
And look at the weather!
We've never won a game
when we were paired for five years.
Who made Running Man?
It's us, the victims!
Actually, that's right.
- Until Running Man became popular.
- Whose name tags were ripped?
Who took the role of the weak party?
With the sacrifice of Lee Kwang Soo,
Running Man rose!
At the very person next to you,
I was there, too!
- Ha Ha is very bright today.
- Not at all.
You're very talented!
[A fantastic combination of
the complaisant and the flatterer.]
Listen Producer,
make sure you use a CG for it!
- It's so bright!
[I'll follow your order...]
[Today is happy Kwang Soo day.
We'll do whatever he wants.]
[The rest of the members who
were abandoned by Kwang Soo...]
The weather is really nice.
A palm reader told me he's never
read anyone like me before.
- Is it that bad?
- No.
- It's good?
- He said it's really good.
- Do you have a straight line?
- That's right.
Is the 'straight' from
you're in dire 'straits'?
At least with Running Man.
Can any of you sum up the
race for me?
- Just forget what happened.
- In short...
make Kwang Soo the winner.
[What did you just say?]
Make him the winner.
He will be with one person at the end.
We should make Kwang Soo
betray the person.
I think it's easy for him
to betray Jae Suk.
Lee Kwang Soo is
the main character for today.
Is he the main character again?
Today's race is
'Hidden camera for Lee Kwang Soo'
['Hidden camera for Lee Kwang Soo'?]
[This real mission is to
deceive Kwang Soo.]
Why do you like me so much?
I don't know where to choose from.
You're just you!
[Are you enjoying this, Kwang Soo?]
Until the filming is over
and he goes home...
This hidden camera
shouldn't be discovered.
Make Lee Kwang Soo believe
that he wins alone.
If you fail at the interim mission,
he'll get a hint about the hidden camera.
Make sure that you succeed
at the interim missions.
You're the main character.
(For the hidden camera)
Main role!
[Hope we can trick you well.]
You're holding the key to winning.
(Hidden camera)
We can win when Kwang Soo
plays the game well?
[We'll survive only if you're deceived.]
When the filming is done,
and Kwang Soo gets home
you'll share the prize money,
and that's the end of this race.
Kwang Soo will figure it out
by watching TV?
Six million Won will be
given to Kwang Soo
if he becomes aware of
the hidden camera.
Six million Won?
If you successfully finish this race,
each of you will get one million Won.
Do you understand the rules?
Kwang Soo has the key
to winning?
But only Kwang Soo doesn't know
that this is the hidden camera.
[What will be the result of this race?]
[The first mission site,
SBS in Mokdong.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Did you serve him well?
- Yes.
- Let's go, Kwang Soo!
[Kwang Soo doesn't open
the door by himself.]
[Ha Ha is doing his best
at serving Kwang Soo.]
Ha Ha is the best flatterer.
He's really good at that.
I wonder what we'll do here.
The first mission of
'Desirable Kwang Soo' is
'Find the guest.'
We have a guest?
[They have a guest?]
There will be lots of
celebrities in this building.
On the screen behind Ji Hyo,
you see '30.'
Between three minutes to zero
bring the guest and
stand on the 'R' mark.
The person who makes
a heart with the guest wins.
From now on, find the guest.
- Where is the guest?
- You're not giving us any hints?
- Is it a male or female?
- You're not telling us?
- How are we supposed to tell?
- How can I find the guest in 30 minutes?
[Who will be the guest?]
- What floor do we have to search?
- You're not giving us a hint?
- That's what I'm saying.
- What to do?
[As soon as the mission starts,
Kwang Soo is heading to a corner.]
- Hello.
The main character, Kwang Soo
from the 'Desirable Kwang Soo'
Am I the main character
for the whole race?
I mean for this episode?
If you succeed at the first mission,
we'll give you a surprising hint.
Do not tell the others about it.
For the first mission,
someone is waiting to see you.
He's already here.
- Hello.
[This familiar voice is...]
The guest who's waiting for you is...
your father.
[My father?]
[My dad is in this building?]
Hello.
[He's Kwang Soo's father.]
[Fall, 2013 in Namyangjoo]
- Are you Kwang Soo's father?
[When the Running Man members
attacked him all of a sudden...]
[he stayed calm and
he showed his talent in acting.]
[Lee Jong Ho, Kwang Soo's father.]
[The variety father and son
have met again!]
Hello.
- Hello.
- Where are you?
I'm at the coffee shop.
Coffee shop?
The coffee shop on the first floor?
On the first floor?
On the first floor, there's
a coffee shop by the entrance
Why did you choose such
an easy spot?
I'll be there.
I can only see my back,
so it won't be that easy.
Oh, okay.
You'll participate in the mission.
By the way, if you succeed
the mission in solo
you'll get a surprising hint.
[Father and I will make
a heart on that mark.]
[No one knows the guest is my dad.]
[Ok!
No problem!]
[On the other hand...]
- We need to find him before Kwang Soo.
- That's right.
But I feel Kwang Soo will find him first.
Because he can call his dad.
[He can call his dad?]
[Huh? His dad?]
Last time, he was wearing a suit.
He did wear a suit last time.
I'll look for a person wearing a suit.
Where will he be?
I need to watch what I say.
If Kwang Soo hear me
mentioning his dad...
[All the members know about him?]
I'll tell you about
the interim missions.
The first mission is
'Find the guest.'
Your mission is to
pretend to find the secret guest.
But you actually need to act
in a certain way for the guest.
Each of you should act differently.
You have to win this to prevent
Kwang Soo from getting the hint.
Yoo Jae Suk needs to give the guest
a hug for three seconds.
Ji Suk Jin needs to take
a selfie with the guest.
He likes to post his pictures.
Jong Kook needs to give
the guest a shoulder massage.
He always does it anyway.
Gary needs to buy a drink
and give it to him with a straw.
Ha Ha needs to exchange winks.
They're the things we normally do.
Ji Hyo needs to dust off
the guest's shoulders.
That's easy.
I'll announce the surprise guest.
The guest is
Lee Kwang Soo's father.
I should make him
drink out of a straw?
With his father...
There are precautions.
It's a hidden camera.
Kwang Soo knows
the guest is his father.
He even knows he will get a hint
when he wins the mission.
[They have to be extra-careful
not to get caught.]
I should start the camera now.
We can do the mission while
we're bickering with Kwang Soo.
Gary has the most difficult mission.
We can pretend to steal his father...
and act it out.
You can give him a hug like that.
- Mine is the easiest.
- Gary's mission is the problem.
I should buy a drink first.
[The battle of wits between 2 vs. 6]
[Who will win this battle?]
[Kwang Soo goes to the coffee shop.]
[There are many people
walking in the lobby.]
[Where is my father?]
Hello.
[Kwang Soo successfully
contacts his father.]
What am I supposed to do?
Just stay here, I'll be back.
- It's started already.
- Already?
Should I keep wearing the wristband?
- Yes, yes.
- I shouldn't show it to anyone?
This is perfect.
I didn't know it was you.
You look really casual.
[What a brilliant plan
of Kwang Soo's father!]
[15 minutes left!]
In 15 minutes, we can walk
to the middle of the lobby.
To the middle of the lobby?
- With me.
- With you?
I see.
- We were filming earlier at my house.
- At your house?
They found a girl's hair...
And?
It was mother's hair.
I don't know how they'll
show it on TV...
Tell them your mom and
sister visit you.
At your age, what
misunderstanding will it draw?
That's not a problem.
Why am I explaining it to my dad?
[Hopefully, time flies.]
[At that moment...]
[Ji Hyo has found Kwang Soo.]
[Why is he sitting there quietly?]
[Big-nose is searching the lobby.]
[It's Big-nosed brother!]
- Did you find the guest?
- No, I have no idea who would it be.
Excuse me, can I have a
glass of water?
- Thank you.
- Here's water.
We have 14 minutes left.
We'll fail at it.
- How can we find the guest?
- I've seen someone.
Who did you see?
Did you find the guest?
I'm not sure.
Did you perhaps find
the guest and hide them near here?
[He has a good hunch today.]
Do you want to go check with me?
- I've seen someone.
- Let's go check.
Let's go.
Kwang Soo was here.
That means he's around here.
He was circling around
the coffee shop.
Let's go from the opposite direction.
Yes, that's good.
- He will be near the coffee shop.
- Of course.
[Kwang Soo leads Big-nose
to the second floor.]
[But he keeps checking the coffee shop.]
- What?
- Why is Gary there?
What?
Kwang Soo!
Your mission is easier than mine.
[Kwang Soo saw them.]
[Why are they at the coffee shop?]
Where are you going?
What's wrong with you?
[Gary and Ha Ha
enter the coffee shop.]
Don't make it obvious.
Pretend we're searching.
Gary!
[They fail at finding his father.]
- I think he's around here.
- Hurry up, Gary.
- Why?
Where do you want me to go?
Third floor.
Where did Gary go?
I don't think we should go
one by one.
[What am I saying?]
It's suspicious.
There should be something.
Wait!
Gather together!
[Emergency!]
- I see someone.
- I'm in a bad mood.
- Kwang Soo is not in a good mood.
Gather together.
[In an emergency,
he quickly wears his glasses.]
Jong Kook!
Earlier, I was checking...
[They're right behind him.]
Ugh!
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
It's probably nothing, right?
[Kwang Soo, it's too obvious.]
[On the contrary, his dad
is still very casual.]
He looks like him...
[They're not sure.]
- Where are you hurt?
- Can you stop the timer for Kwang Soo?
- What's wrong, Kwang Soo.
[All the members go back to his dad.]
[Oh, no!]
Kwang Soo is hurt.
- Wait a minute, what's going on?
- He's hurt... huh?
[Oh my god...]
[It's ruined.]
- I thought it was you.
I saw some cameras,
so I looked at him.
- He looks like Kwang Soo's dad.
[He's still acting casually.]
Aren't you Kwang Soo's father?
[They have found Kwang Soo's dad!]
- Aren't you Kwang Soo's father?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Kwang Soo's father!
- I need to take care of my puppy.
- He's Kwang Soo's father!
- What?
[I'm sorry, Son.
I can't ignore them any longer.]
- How have you been?
- I'm good.
You're Kwang Soo's father, right?
[I need to stop them.]
[Kwang Soo,
I must have been discovered.]
How are you?
- Your father is here.
[Kwang Soo pretends he didn't know.]
He must be the guest.
We even went to Kwang Soo's house.
[They have met the guest.]
Your mission is to act
in a certain way for the guest.
Ji Suk Jin needs to take
a selfie with the guest.
Ha Ha needs to exchange winks.
Ji Hyo needs to dust off
the guest's shoulders.
Jong Kook needs to give
the guest a shoulder massage.
Gary needs to buy a drink
and give it to him with a straw.
Jae Suk needs to
give the guest a hug.
Maybe he's the guest.
[Jong Kook succeeds at his mission.]
- I'm here to support a drama.
We're donating some furniture
for a drama.
- So you're not here for Kwang Soo?
- I can see him at home.
He doesn't have any drinks.
Why don't you give him one?
[Kkuk's nice assistance!]
[Gary succeeds at his mission.]
- Would you like some coffee instead?
We don't have much time
left for the mission.
- That's right.
[Wait on an opportunity.]
There's something on your shoulder.
[Ji Hyo succeeds at her mission.]
[Jae Suk succeeds.]
How have you been?
[They can't discover he's the guest.]
- We'll come back later.
- Don't worry about me.
We've met your father.
- See you in a moment.
- Take care.
- Father!
[Wink]
[He winks back.]
- What are you doing?
- Take this drink.
Jong Kook helped me.
- It was nice!
- It was very casual.
[Bravo!]
We shouldn't be happy now.
[Kwang Soo is tired after the crisis.]
I don't understand this mission.
Kwang Soo is puzzled.
We shouldn't push him.
He might discover the real race.
Kwang Soo, why is your dad here?
He's providing some
furniture for a drama.
Furniture?
I'm not really sure.
What's wrong with your hair?
I didn't have time to
go to a hair salon.
They should give us more time since
we had to greet Kwang Soo's dad.
[Please, don't act!]
Please!
I can't handle myself.
Suk Jin, you can ruin everything.
Go do your mission quickly.
I need to take a selfie.
I'm the only one
who didn't finish the mission.
Did you do it?
Me, too.
I winked at him,
and he winked back at me.
Everyone succeeded their missions.
Anyway, Kwang Soo has
to make a heart with his father.
And we need to let it happen.
Kwang Soo has no idea
about our missions.
[Only five minutes left.]
Father, please take a picture
with me.
- I want to post it on SNS.
- You said you'll visit me.
I'm sorry, I'll visit you next time.
This is for my SNS.
- Is it okay if I upload this?
- What will be the title?
Let's take one first.
[Suk Jin succeeds.]
I took it in a way that flatters you.
[Two minutes!]
He shouldn't see us.
Time's up.
Did you find the guest?
Suk Jin!
I couldn't find the guest.
[No one knows that
my father is the guest.]
We only have one minute left!
Dad, let's do it.
Dad, pretend you're leaving.
Walk casually, then make a heart shape
with me near the clock.
We need to go now.
Walk casually toward the clock.
Kwang Soo started his action.
He's doing it.
I don't know what's going on.
Where is the clock?
[The father and the son attempt
to accomplish the mission.]
I'm going to wait here.
20 seconds!
They shouldn't stay together
like that.
Kwang Soo's dad is coming toward here.
Why is he coming here?
- Suk Jin, did you do it?
- Goodbye, Kwang Soo's dad!
- Goodbye!
- Take care!
Let Kwang Soo finish the mission.
Ten, nine...
Stand on the 'R' mark.
- Could it be his dad?
- And make a heart.
Dad, make a heart with me!
We made a heart!
It's a heart!
Kwang Soo's dad!
It was him!
Only Lee Kwang Soo wins!
[Kwang Soo wins the first mission.]
- It's not fair!
- What was that?
[Their hidden camera is successful.]
He was wearing it on his wrist.
I should have checked his wrist.
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you.
It was really weird.
[We feel bad deceiving him.]
So you don't really know them?
I feel a bit weird.
You were really nice to me.
I feel like you tried
and gave him a chance.
Because you said you're
not the guest.
- They were being polite.
- It's none other than you.
If it wasn't you, Jong Kook would
have dragged the guest by force.
Thank you very much.
Because Kwang Soo won this mission
alone, only he will get a hint.
- Kwang Soo gets a hint by himself?
- You were too nice to me.
- You looked serious.
- You said you're not the guest.
[Hint - You can win
today's race by yourself.]
Thank you very much
for being here, Mr. Lee Jong Ho.
Yesterday was my dad's
60th birthday.
I'll treat you with
fish stew in Namyangjoo.
As appreciation, we
prepared something for you.
Open and check before giving him.
Let him open it, Suk Jin.
It's a golden key.
Here, you like gold.
This is embarrassing!
- You've watched Running Man.
- I'm so embarrassed.
Thank you for the gift.
[We're sorry to surprise you,
but thank you again.]
We've succeeded at it again.
Kwang Soo's father is very...
- He reacted quickly.
- It was difficult to spot him.
I think he's better
than Kwang Soo at acting.
I can tell Kwang Soo
by looking at his eyes.
- It seems Kwang Soo didn't sense anything.
- He has no idea.
[The second mission
of 'Desirable Kwang Soo Race.']
This is a really deep pool!
[A huge stage is set out
on an outdoor pool.]
[Six chairs are hanging
on top of the pool.]
[Kwang Soo's private
high quality chair.]
[King Kwang Soo's greets like
a winner at a beauty pageant.]
Is that my chair?
Please get a massage chair
for me next time.
[The rest of the members are wearing
a swim suit underneath their clothing.]
Hurry up and run!
It'll be by order of arrival!
I'll see who arrives last!
First place!
You're the fastest.
- It's only right for you to be the man of power.
- You're right!
You're a good talker today.
Come this way.
How come you're not wearing it?
How come?
[How dare you!]
- I'm sorry.
Please stand in line.
The name of this game is
'As Kwang Soo Says.'
Doesn't it sound fun?
The name of this game is
'As Kwang Soo Says!'
That's right.
Let me explain the rules.
You will sit on the chair.
Then I will give you one of
the two numbers you have.
As you can see each
chair has two numbers.
You will have to...
cut the number I call out.
One of the two numbers
will make you fall.
And the other one won't
make you fall even if you cut it.
You're very good at
explaining the rules.
The second mission will be
at a pool.
There will be six chairs hanging
above water that you'll be sitting on.
The important thing
is five members need to fall.
Oh, no!
You need to make a
choice with your hunch.
- I believe in you!
- Please believe in our hunch, too.
You know I'm pretty quick.
You know Ji Hyo is quick-witted.
I start analyzing
as soon as games start.
[Why is that?]
There are two ropes in
front of you.
I'll let you know which one
will make you stay even if it's cut.
But Kwang Soo doesn't know that.
We need to lead him.
The numbers that
will make you fall are...
one, four, five, eight, nine,
and eleven.
1,4,5,8,9, and 11.
Upon the January Fourth Retreat,
she made a promise to meet
her Oppa (sounds similar to 58)
on September 11th.
[Will they be able to succeed?]
- Our fates depend on your commands.
- Trust me.
I won't let you fall!
[Trust us, we'll trick Kwang Soo.]
- Good luck!
Lee Kwang Soo!
I can't do this any longer.
[What?]
- I didn't mean it.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[We'll do whatever you want,
for the hidden camera.]
Let's cheer by doing the waves!
The other direction!
It's been a long time since
I've seen you this happy.
[Be patient for the hidden camera.]
- Should we go in?
- Yes, please!
[While they go to sit on the chair.]
[See me for a second,
Big-nosed brother!]
1,4,5,8,9, and 11.
Were they the numbers for falling?
Or for hanging?
- They're for hanging.
- I think they're for falling.
- No, they're not.
I think they're for falling.
What is right?
For number two and four...
Number two and four, go sit.
[Big-nosed brother takes Ji Hyo.]
[Red alert!]
[Emergency!
Kwang Soo is approaching!]
- Suk Jin!
[Please stop talking!]
- Are number nine and eleven for falling?
- Yes, they're for falling.
- What did you talk about with her?
- I wanted to switch spots.
[He's suspicious.]
[Just be fooled by the trick....]
- I'm an easy target to you, right?
- No, I was just...
[Thanks to Ji Hyo,
they escape from the crisis.]
Be careful, the water is cold!
[We tricked you!]
[Will they be able to succeed
at this mission?]
For your safety, divers
are ready in water.
We're ready for it!
Please raise the chairs!
[The chairs are going up.]
This is good enough!
[Stop!]
- It's good, stop here.
Please raise them up to the max.
You should play this too, Kwang Soo!
[They keep going up...]
Is that all you can do?
Let's show the power of the film set!
It's the maximum.
It feels very far from up here.
Are you ready?
I'm so nervous!
I'll make sure that
you'll go home safely.
[Absentmindedly]
- Yeah!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- That's very good.
- I'll give you an additional points!
- Thank you!
We'll start the game.
I'll give you the number.
I believe in you!
Please choose a number
with your loving heart.
Number one!
- Number one!
- You made the right choice!
- How about number two?
- No, I don't want it.
- Are you sure it's one?
- Yes!
I recommend number one, too!
- I'm scared!
- Isn't it a good thing to fall?
- I see!
[Gary, you need to fall for the camera.]
Kwang Soo has a good hunch.
I'll cut it now!
Why isn't this cutting?
[Fall!]
[Oh, my!]
- I'm scared!
[It's scary even though they know.]
I've never guessed wrong!
- Everyone!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
Lee Kwang Soo!
- LKS!
- Thank you so much!
- I don't regret this!
- That's right!
- How did it feel?
- Wasn't it scary?
I really hate falling.
I want to know if I fall or not.
[Gary is enjoying swimming now.]
Please pick four from
the 'death' for me.
The number on the right side
made Gary fall.
It might be the left number
for the second time.
- I think four is a good number!
- I believe in Kim Jong Kook's hunch!
Can you give me a hint
about which numbers are which?
I guess you want to make me fall.
Is there any way I can get a hint?
Just pick four!
It'll be very funny to see him fall
after he calls out four himself.
- So, you want to cut four?
- Yes!
[Pick four, please.]
I see, then cut four!
One, two, three!
- Yeah!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[Two out of five successfully
fell into the water.]
[King Kwang Soo is the
king of misfortune.]
- Kwang Soo, I'll give you some hints.
- I see, just come out.
- How are you feeling?
- It's rather cool!
[I might be staying.]
God Kwang Soo, I feel a bit relieved.
I want to pick the number for him.
What?
Why me?
Why did you touch my computer?
Cut it when I tell you to!
I recommend this number.
Lucky seven!
[Lucky seven?]
[The number for a fall is number eight.]
[And he suggests number seven.]
[What a selfish suggestion!]
Lucky seven.
Lucky eight!
Cut the number eight!
- Just listen to me.
- This game is called 'As Kwang Soo says.'
Let me cut seven.
- Just do as Kwang Soo says.
- Cut number eight!
Kwang Soo is the one to pick.
Cut it quickly and fall!
This is not a cheering wave!
You need a break!
- Cut it quickly!
- Seven is for falling.
- No, just cut eight!
- Pick seven!
No, I said eight!
This one is not going to make me fall.
Cut your own life line!
[Big-nosed brother
gives up on surviving.]
Bye, Suk Jin.
[I'm leaving...]
You're amazing, Kwang Soo!
[He picked the right numbers
three times in a row.]
- You lost your glasses..
- Your glasses!
I don't care!
[Even with Big-nose's selfishness]
[three of them fell
thanks to King Kwang Soo.]
Now, you have a chance of surviving!
- Between five and six...
- That's difficult.
I want to choose an even number.
Even number?
Number six?
Mine was even number
so pick an odd number.
Odd number!
Odd, odd, odd number!
SBS is...
channel six!
At my house, it's channel five!
Mine is five!
- You have a feeling when you sit on it.
- You do?
- Oh, his body is inclined to left side.
- I told you.
His body is tilted to the
side of number five.
- I'll pick number five!
- Number five?
I don't want to make you fall.
Then... five.
You're not going to change your mind?
[That's lame...]
[A vertical drop!]
[Now four in a row fell into the water.]
[Why am I playing so well?]
Wow, he's incredible.
How can he make all four of us fall?
How about this?
It happened to be a pattern of
odd number and even number.
Pick the odd number and even number.
Then they may survive.
I don't think they kept the pattern.
[Big-nosed brother, am I the target?]
Don't do it.
[Big-nose and Kkuk control Kwang Soo.]
Let us pick our own number!
I will follow your decision.
Listen, Kwang Soo.
Please let me pick my own number!
Please give me that right.
What number do you want to cut then?
What number?
He's thinking.
[What do I do?]
- We don't have much time.
Five, four, three, two...
[Haroro's choice is...]
- one!
Number nine!
[Good job.]
What about you Ji Hyo?
I recommend you number eleven!
Just pick the odd number
and the even number.
I'll follow Kwang Soo's opinion.
Odd number and even number.
- Number twelve?
- Yes.
- Number nine and number twelve!
- No one is on my side?
Today is Kwang Soo's day!
Cut it now!
One, two, three!
[Ha Ha's give.]
- Ji Hyo's turn.
Ji Hyo!
[The fifth diver, Ha Ha.]
- Ji Hyo's turn.
[If Ji Hyo stays,
this mission will succeed.]
[King Kwang Soo waits for
the result without any doubts.]
- Ji Hyo survived!
[They succeed at the mission!]
Ji Hyo survived!
I survived!
She is the goddess of fortune.
Isn't it supposed to happen
as Kwang Soo says?
It doesn't make sense otherwise.
It just happened as Kwang Soo said.
- Didn't you already know the numbers?
- No, I didn't know that.
Then we've succeeded at
this mission!
Everyone, we've succeeded
at the mission!
[They're doing a good job carrying out
the hidden camera missions.]
['A' aquarium in Ilsan.]
This is the last mission.
You'll be separated first.
And we will give you the final mission.
You have to be separated.
You can't separate us!
[We cannot be separated
from God Kwang Soo!]
- What are you doing?
- I'll stay here!
Let's part for a moment.
- See you soon!
- I love you, Kwang Soo!
Don't forget me, Kwang Soo!
[The race draws to an end.]
Now, I'll tell you the rules
for the final mission.
The title is...
'Be with the King Maker,
Lee Kwang Soo.'
I like the titles for the missions
very much today.
The members have to
oust each other.
The last one to go to the final stage
with the King Maker, Lee Kwang Soo
and put both hands on the station
with the King Maker will win.
The last one to put the hands
on the station with me?
One person?
So, if I win with the person,
I'll have to split the reward.
- If I win by myself, I'll have it all?
- Of course.
If you say so...
[That's how it works?]
That's what we told Kwang Soo
for the final mission.
That's the fake rule
that Kwang Soo received.
But our rule is different.
Survive until the end and
make Kwang Soo betray you.
If Kwang Soo betrays you...
and wins by himself, we win.
Make Kwang Soo betray you
and win by himself.
The last one to go to
the final station with Kwang Soo...
Wait a moment!
Kwang Soo!
The last survivor will receive
double the prizes.
You should have told me earlier.
[Which means...]
[the members will be
competing against each other?]
[Who will be the last survivor?]
[Project 'Let Lee Kwang Soo
win alone', starts!]
[It's not a name tag elimination!]
This time, you won't eliminate the
members by ripping the name tags
instead, you need to find the special
liquid that erases the name tag.
This crazy liquid is called...
'Kwang Soo', 'Kwang' from crazy,
and 'Soo' from water.
Wait, my name doesn't
mean 'crazy water.'
My name is not Crazy Water!
Find the crazy water and
erase other members name.
I can erase the name from the back?
- Is there a way for them to win solo?
- No.
They can only win
with the King Maker.
Wait, are you serious?
Wait for a second.
Ji Hyo!
Isn't that too...
- Did you erase my name?
[This is the power of double prizes.]
Let's bulldoze out everyone!
- Let's not run away today.
- I won't, this is our last chance.
Let's show them our will.
[Gary and Kwang Soo have met.]
[Big-nose's sudden attack!]
- That's how you play?
- Yes, that's how I play.
- What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo!
My head, wait!
My head!
[A serious battle between
the men with the crazy water.]
Stay out of it, Kwang Soo!
Help me, Suk Jin!
- Am I ousted?
- Gary is ousted.
- Do I have my name?
- Ha Ha is ousted, too.
- How about me?
- You survived.
You're still alive.
- Good work, Gary!
- Ha Ha was too...
[Gary acts like he's sulking.]
Why are you making a sad face?
What did I do?
That's okay.
I thought you would have helped me.
[Good luck with the hidden camera!]
[The rest are still fighting.]
[The name tag erasure is going pretty much
the same as the name tag elimination.]
Wait!
Give me a break!
[Let me send you off in peace.]
[Kwang Soo looks like he's painting.]
[I know it's for the hidden camera,
but I don't want to end miserably.]
It's very clean now.
Wow, this liquid is very powerful.
[At the jail...]
You're here.
I think this is unfair.
- But we'll win in the end.
- It's really easy to erase Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin should erase Ji Hyo.
- And Suk Jin should stay alive.
It's easier for Kwang Soo
to betray Suk Jin.
I...
whoever wins the race out of
you two
I will congratulate.
- But I want to see the sincerity.
[He's still alive.]
- I'm serious.
- What do you want me to do?
Turn around.
- Me, too?
- I don't mind at all.
- You don't want to turn around?
- I do.
Never look back!
Don't turn around!
Never, ever!
Do not look back!
I know how much you want
to turn around.
- But at the moment you turn...
[He's erasing 'Jong.']
- At the moment you turn!
- How many are you erasing?
- Wait a minute!
- The moment you turn...
- I will be going with the other person.
- You're erasing too much!
- I see.
- The moment you turn!
- Wait, I won't turn but...
- I can even erase my own name.
- I can erase my own name.
- But you're erasing too much!
[I think you're the target.]
- I don't know what I'll do.
Wait, wait!
[This is how it ends for me.]
[Clean]
- Don't ever look back!
You need to go to jail now.
Why?
You're ousted, but listen!
I tested you, and you passed the test!
You're not supposed to oust me!
I erased it all before I knew...
He's unbelievable!
- I'm moved by you!
[Kkuk enters the jail.]
- Kwang Soo...
- Jong Kook was sincere to me!
He's not the one to betray me!
It was difficult.
You've worked hard!
I've acted well and was ousted nicely.
I know it was all acting but
you shouldn't have hurt my feelings.
We're a team.
We all did it for the bigger picture.
I understand it, but
didn't you try surviving?
It was tempting
but it's easier for him to oust me
than betray me in the end.
But Suk Jin survived.
The last survivor receives
double the prizes, right?
That makes people greedy.
I was a little greedy for a moment.
You know Suk Jin is greedy.
You and I are the only ones left.
Your name is almost gone.
I, honestly...
You should think carefully.
You won with me last time.
I'll be honest.
I can't handle her by myself.
You should help me
if you want me to win.
I see.
[The last battle of crazy water.]
- You have two water guns?
[Kwang Soo starts an action.]
[He's rubbing on his palm?]
[He charges toward Big-nose!]
- It's me he's after!
[Kwang Soo's next target is Big-nose?]
[He pretended attacking Big-nose
and wiped Blank Ji's name tag!]
She's ousted.
How did you do it?
[Song Ji Hyo is ousted.]
Kwang Soo, that was an
awesome tactic!
- It's a plot twist.
- High five!
[Kwang Soo makes
Big-nose the final survivor.]
So, If I win with the person,
I'll have to split the reward.
If I win by myself,
I'll have it all.
[If Kwang Soo doesn't betray Suk Jin,
the hidden camera will fail.]
[Then Kwang Soo will obtain
the full amount of prize.]
If you make Kwang Soo believe
that he wins alone, you win.
[What will be Kwang Soo's choice?]
- This is the final stand!
- Awesome, it's the main stage!
This is how it ends, Suk Jin.
I didn't really plan to pick someone.
I was worried but I never knew
you would be the one.
This is a meaningful gift of 2015 to me.
Yes, can we proceed now?
Put your hands on it.
You've worked so hard.
Can I just put my hands, too?
[That's it, Kwang Soo.]
[He's pretending he didn't see it.]
[As I expected, you are...]
[He rubs his hand with the crazy water.]
[And casually puts it
on Suk Jin's back.]
Thank you so much.
[Wiping]
[He never disappoints me.]
- Wow, this is amazing!
Awesome!
Ji Suk Jin is ousted.
Go to jail now!
Leave at this moment!
What do you mean?
Wait!
Why am I ousted?
I haven't won solo in years!
You're the loser! This is what you get
for looking at other people's computer!
Seriously, you... in 2015...
- I'm serious!
- Yes!
I haven't won solo for a long time!
Lee Kwang Soo!
I think we completely deceived him.
It worked out well, right?
Double prizes for me, right?
[Thank you so much, Kwang Soo!]
['The hidden camera -Let Kwang Soo win'
was successful, but it wasn't over yet.]
Welcome back!
- Aren't you supposed to keep one member?
- Lee Kwang Soo!
There was supposed to be two, to
succeed the mission. Right?
Lee Kwang Soo, you petty...
You said two people should
stand on the final stage.
I will never trust you!
After you came to my house,
the first mission with my dad...
the hint I won was...
'Winning solo is possible.'
They gave me the hint
at the time.
Why letting only Kwang Soo know?
Suk Jin wanted to win.
I'm sorry, but I never
thought I'd win with you.
Unbelievable!
He doesn't watch TV unless
he wins these days.
- He's going to watch this episode for sure.
- What are you talking about?
[Soon, we'll show you how
he feels about it live.]
Anyway, the winner for this race...
is Lee Kwang Soo!
This isn't right!
We'll transfer the money on wire now.
[He won't receive the prize.]
- Thank you!
Thank you everyone!
Cut!
Thank you.
[If Kwang Soo goes home like this,
the hidden camera will succeed!]
- I'm going to eat you up someday!
- Thank you for your hard work!
- Kwang Soo!
- So we could have won solo.
- Only he knew about that.
- That hint was for everyone?
I received the hint.
Kwang Soo, can I talk
to you for a minute?
[After Kwang Soo left...]
Congratulations on winning!
[Kwang Soo might hear us.]
Here's the envelopes for you.
You're giving us a million Won each?
Ji Suk Jin was the last survivor
so we're giving him double.
I'll treat everyone.
At first, we felt really sorry for Kwang Soo
for visiting him without any prior notice.
This time, Kwang Soo kept betraying us.
If he didn't eliminate me
and finished the final stage...
then theses envelopes would be his.
If you stayed with us, these
prizes would all belong to you.
In fact, he's the betrayer.
Anyway, we'll leave the site.
- Kwang Soo, this could've been yours.
- Let's leave here.
[Lee Kwang Soo didn't have any ideas about
the hidden camera before it broadcasted.]
Don't let him know until he watches TV.
[How are you feeling, Kwang Soo?]
- Hello, everyone!
- This is a live broadcast.
Is everyone enjoying the weekend?
It was a Happy Hidden Camera
for Kwang Soo.
We're here at Lee Kwang Soo's house.
And this is a live broadcast.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Did you know it was a hidden camera?
I had no idea.
I have goosebumps now!
How do you feel after
watching Running Man?
I'm happy for making the
audiences laugh, but...
- it's frustrating!
- He's been tricked for two weeks.
For two weeks, Kwang Soo
had no idea about this.
- We arrived here a moment ago.
- I feel dizzy.
- Do you have anything you want to say?
- I will take revenge no matter what!
I will take revenge in person,
if you don't let me on Running Man.
The viewers are watching.
We are broadcasting live now.
- 10 seconds left!
- It's time to say goodbye.
We'll come back with another
exciting race next week!
- Have a good rest of the weekend!
- Have a good weekend!
At Lee Kwang Soo's house...
- I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
- I'm Ji Suk Jin.
- I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
- See you next week!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The biggest pot luck
in Running Man history!]
[Celebrities born overseas head over
to Running Man's penalty fearlessly.]
[There is no gray zone!]
[Extreme experiences! Heated reactions!]
- There's only one way!
[The same sky view, different
customer satisfaction degrees.]
[Submit to your fate!]
- You can't say it!
[You'll experience the heaven or hell...]
- Running Man is gone crazy!
[The polar opposites
- the Penalty Race.]