- I don't like this show.
- Tell him to get out here!
Why are you making me do that?
I don't like this, I don't want to do it.
- What is this? Just hurry it up.
- Lee Seo Jin is making me mad!
[It all starts now.]
[A snowy white winter day.]
['N' Hotel in Incheon]
[A lone man in a hotel room.]
[Lee Seung Gi]
- I've asked you to meet me in secrecy.
- Yes, I've noticed that.
Yes, it was so that I could
give you your special mission.
Can I take a look at it?
Wait.
Oust all eight members by
secretly eliminating their name tags.
[Oust all eight members by
secretly eliminating their name tags.]
I smell the scent of betrayal.
There are a total of eight members including
RM cast members and Moon Chae Won.
You must oust all the members by secretly
eliminating their name tags in order to win.
I have to do that?
But as you already know, they're pros
when it comes to name tag elimination.
- Yes, they are.
- So...
- The help that you have requested...
- Ah... he is finally here.
[A special guest that Seung Gi
himself has requested!]
He is a very special guest, and it took
some effort to bring him on the show.
Yes, and he is finally here.
Please show him in.
[He is none other than...]
Why are there so many cameras?
[Nation's best grumbler, Lee Seo Jin.]
Seo Jin, you came.
[You came...]
Why are you so dressed up?
You're just going to have to
take it all off.
Come and have a seat.
I really didn't want to come.
[Starts to grumble from the moment
he steps onto the scene.]
I told them how much effort it took
for me to get you to come on the show.
[Mr. Grump's first-time
appearance on Running Man.]
- Did you sleep well?
- I drank too much last night.
You're going to run your hangover off.
- I have to run? You can run by yourself.
- Just a little.
I can't run.
This is the mission that we received.
We have to oust all eight members by
secretly eliminating their name tags.
You can rip off all the name tags.
[Mr. Grumpy doesn't want to
be bothered to do anything.]
Yes, I will rip off the name tags.
But I think we need to work
together as a team
to come up with a plan to
eliminate all their name tags.
I don't know. You take care of it.
We can't eliminate Jong Kook.
That's why we have to deceive Jong Kook
and eliminate him while you distract him.
- Just eliminate me first.
- No, we can't do that.
This is going to be hard enough as is,
so how am I to eliminate you?
There are seven Running Man members,
and Moon Chae Won, as well.
I'm going to give them an opening mission of
having to go around searching for a card.
That's when you'll have to covertly
go around and rip off all their name tags.
When you do, a special advantage
will be given to only the two of you.
But the name tags can only be eliminated
when the two of you are together.
Then I think you're going to have to
rip off some name tags yourself.
I'm about to start puking right now.
I can't rip them off.
I'm not going to do any of that.
If someone catches on to your plans
and asks if there's something going on
or if any of the other eight asks if
you're secretly trying to oust them...
then at that point, you fail your mission.
Just any question of suspicion
would signal the failing of our mission?
- Yes.
- Then we're going to fail right away.
[Seriously, Seo Jin...]
[Grumbling and complaining when we
already know how hard you'll be working.]
I think we're going to have to individually
lure them away from the rest of the group.
I'll stay away on my own and you can
go around eliminating their name tags.
I'll bring them to where
you'll be waiting for us.
- Then I'll just stay away somewhere.
- Yes, that sounds good.
- Okay.
- Why do you look so smug about it?
- You look way too happy about it.
- You just said that we can't get caught.
- You can plan it however you'd like.
- We're going to need a plan.
[Struggling fumbling little brother,
and a lazy and grumpy older brother.]
[Will they be able to succeed their mission?]
[30 minutes later.]
The whole river is frozen over.
[Everyone gathers together for the opening
while Seo Jin remains in hiding.]
I went home and practically passed out.
- I don't remember a thing.
- Really?
That's the first time I lost my memories
when I haven't even had anything to drink.
- You blacked out?
- You don't remember anything?
- Did you get home okay last night?
- Yes.
- Wow, that sounded nice.
Did you hear how Chae Won sounded
when she answered that question?
[A breathless sounding answer.]
[While everyone's laughing and
chatting amongst themselves...]
[Even while saying he didn't want to bother,
Seo Jin's observing the scene from the lobby.]
[Working hard even while acting
like he doesn't care about his mission.]
In order to earn a special advantage,
you will be given your opening mission.
- Right away?
- Yes, right away.
You have to find all 15 pieces of the card
within the time limit that you're given
and complete the puzzle on the board.
[Find the pieces and complete
the puzzle board on time.]
There are a total of ten numbers, and
five other numerical symbols in the puzzle.
Therefore, there are a total
of 15 puzzle pieces.
- Then this is an individual mission?
- No, it's not.
- We have a time limit to adhere to.
- You have to find all the puzzle pieces.
What are you doing?
[Collateral damage.]
- Are you okay? Get out of the way!
- Chae Won, are you okay?
[They're only worried about Chae Won.]
- What are you doing?
- What were you thinking?
- You have to watch out for others.
- Chae Won, are you okay?
- But I heard Seo Jin was going to be a guest.
- I saw that on the news, too.
- I heard something about that, too.
- When will he be coming?
- Well... I did hear something about that.
- But I'm not sure when he'll be joining us.
- Me neither.
- He'll be joining you later on.
- Why?
- Why later?
- He's flying back from overseas right now.
- He's heading back from overseas?
- Today? He's flying back today?
- He's flying back today?
- Yes, from the airport.
- I heard he's flying into Incheon.
- So that's why we're here?
That must be the reason why
we're here in Incheon.
- He's coming later?
- Yes, later.
- Then it's just us for now?
- Can we get started?
- Yes, you can get started.
- Let's go!
[Off to start their mission with
the understanding Seo Jin will come later.]
The opening must already be over.
[Seo Jin is already hiding in the room
that he and Seung Gi have agreed upon.]
Why did I go down to the lobby
instead of watching them from up here?
[Carefully shuts all the curtains
while grumbling the whole time.]
- Is this a team mission?
- Yes, this is a team mission.
- We have to work together.
- I think it's us against the producers.
I'm really bad at finding
things like this.
[Seung Gi hangs back
to send Seo Jin a quick text.]
[Seo Jin, I'll start bringing the members
one by one up to the room.]
[Okay, let's just finish this up
and go get something to eat.]
[Is he nervous?]
- I found one! Here it is!
- Already? There it is.
[Blank Ji finds a number card
as soon as they start the mission.]
[Already?]
- That's what we're searching for?
- It's nine.
- That's what we're looking for.
- How did you find it so quickly?
[Seriously?
We haven't even gotten started yet.]
Wait for me.
[Stick the puzzle piece onto the board.]
- Where could they be?
- They're really easy to find, I think.
[All the members must be ousted
before all the puzzle pieces are found.]
- There's one.
- Another one?
That's awesome.
[Another one?]
We're finding them very quickly.
[This is not good...]
I'm sure it'll get tougher
towards the end.
Ugh, why are they finding them so quickly?
This is driving me crazy.
- Here's one!
- You found one?
Where?
You found another one?
- Here it is. It's under the bed.
- You found one?
- It's not as hard as I thought it would be.
- I found one pretty quickly.
[Seo Jin, what are we going to do?]
[Whatever, I don't care...]
- Seung Gi, have you found anything?
- No, I haven't found anything.
I've already checked these rooms.
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are searching through
the fourth floor where Seo Jin is hiding.]
- Kwang Soo, search over there.
- Okay.
[Jong Kook turns around to
go and search another floor.]
[Oh? If Jong Kook leaves...
then only Kwang Soo is left on this floor.]
[Just then, Seung Gi enters the room
where Seo Jin is waiting.]
- Oh, Seo Jin!
- Huh?
Seo Jin's in here.
[Awkwardly lures Kwang Soo
into the room.]
- Seo Jin's in here.
- Hello, Seo Jin.
[Kwang Soo and Seo Jin meet.]
- Come in.
- Come in, Kwang Soo.
Come in, Kwang Soo.
This is awesome.
Why...
Have a seat.
[Remains so cool
after just having ousted him.]
- Have a seat.
- Sit down, Kwang Soo.
- What just happened?
- You haven't met him before, have you?
[Eliminate first, and greet later.]
They said we'll win something
if we rip off your name tag.
- Just sit down.
- Don't think about what just happened.
- Sit down and chat with him.
- Have a seat.
[Huh?]
[Seung Gi heads back out
to go and find his next target.]
- Just sit down.
- Weren't you at the airport?
- When did you get here?
- A little while ago.
I got here a little while ago and
was told to rip off your name tags.
Help me rip off the others' name tags
when they walk in here.
- The two of you are spies?
- I think so, but I'm not really sure myself.
They're going to come in here one by one
as you sit there in that chair.
- Yes.
- And I just want you to help me oust them.
Then our puzzle completing mission
really doesn't mean anything?
I don't really have any interest in that,
so don't even ask me about it.
Don't ask me any questions
because I really don't even care.
[What an odd spy this man is...]
[Yes!
We've eliminated one person!]
[In the meantime, the puzzle board is
already halfway complete.]
[Seung Gi's newest target, Chae Won,
is lured onto the fourth floor.]
Chae Won, I'll check this side,
and you can check the other side.
Seung Gi, you have to find something.
You did well with your searching yesterday.
I'll check over on this side.
This door's locked.
[Oh?]
[That room is...]
[That's the room where
Grumpy Spy is hiding!]
What are you doing in here, Kwang Soo?
[Seung Gi follows in her footsteps.]
What are you doing?
Why are you ripping that off?
- I just had to do that.
- Wait, what was that all about?
[Kwang Soo suddenly breaks out
in fits of laughter.]
No, this is a name tag elimination game.
What? I'm just doing what we're told.
I don't know anything about what's going on.
I'm just sitting around here.
You're really dense, aren't you?
I just saw what happened to you.
It took you about two full seconds to
finally register what Seung Gi did to you.
[It took Chae Won two full seconds to
realize what Seung Gi had done to her?]
What is your deal?
What's that supposed to mean?
- Seo Jin, I think you have to come with me.
- Why are you hiding in here?
[Luring in the members is too dangerous, and
it's time for Seo Jin to spring into action.]
- You won't get much airtime from here.
- I don't want any airtime on the show.
I have no desire to be on this show.
- We have to promote our movie.
- I'm just a special guest star.
Why would I need to promote
the movie?
- Ugh, seriously.
- You just make a special appearance?
Why would I need to promote your movie?
Seo Jin, please do this for me.
[Grumpy Spy is finally talked into
stepping outside of his comfy hotel room.]
[Chae Won checks to make sure
that Seo Jin and Seung Gi leave the room.]
- Seo Jin doesn't even know.
- That was so weird.
That was so weird.
[Huh?
What are these two talking about?]
Hey, did you see Seung Gi falling for it?
[Big-nose and Jae Suk are also
talking about Seung Gi...]
- Seung Gi's not good at this, either.
- He's really gullible.
- He is...
- Jae Suk!
Where are you?
[The plan succeeded and we're both ousted.]
[The members are exchanging
secret signs with each other.]
[It's time for us to get to work.]
[Just what is going on here?]
[Two hours prior.]
- Lee Seo Jin!
- I saw the news for it.
- We heard that Seo Jin will be coming.
- We saw the news.
Why is Chae Won here, and
not Seung Gi?
There's a reason why there are only
the eight of you here right now.
- We're getting someone?
- It's a 'Fool the guest' mission.
[Mission- Two against eight.
Fool the guests.]
Lee Seo Jin and Lee Seung Gi have been given
the mission to oust all eight of you.
- They'll be eliminating your name tags.
- How embarrassing for them.
I'm really good at acting surprised.
You have to act natural and
let them eliminate your name tags
and if they succeed in ousting all of you,
then you succeed your own secret mission.
Then what would result in us failing?
If they suspect of something odd
going on before you're all eliminated
or if either Lee Seo Jin or Lee Seung Gi
suspects there being a candid camera
- then you fail the mission.
- That's not going to happen.
Then we have to let them think that
they won by a real close call.
Chae Won, can you act really natural
if you get your name tag ripped off?
- Are you going to scream out or what?
- Let's practice doing it.
- Okay, I just ripped off your name tag.
- Okay, what are you going to do?
- You have to do something.
- Your name tag was ripped off a while ago.
Are you lacking any feeling in the back?
[Chae Won, the woman with the
senseless back.]
[Even during the actual event,
her reaction is one step behind.]
[This is the reason why Kwang Soo
burst out laughing.]
[Seriously, Chae Won!]
[But the oblivious Spy Brothers are just
happy about having eliminated her name tag.]
Where should I let them oust me
for them to feel like they actually got me?
[The members are pondering about how to
let themselves be ousted during the mission.]
Look at him acting weird.
[The members are having too much fun
watching Seung Gi getting flustered.]
[Our Seung Gi is so adorable.]
[And the Grumpy Brother finally takes
a step outside of his comfy room.]
[His gaze continues to dart around
even while pretending not to care.]
Okay.
Let's get this done.
Jae Suk just went up there
to get ousted.
I think we're going to get ousted
one at a time.
[Considerate enough to go in one at a time
to help out the awkward spies.]
Jae Suk just went up there.
We'll go one at a time.
[But Seung Gi still remains oblivious
and is ready for the face-off.]
I think this is the sauna.
- You've already checked out the sauna?
- Oh? It's Seo Jin.
- When did you get here?
- I got here this morning.
I heard you weren't coming
until the afternoon.
No, I'm not doing anything.
[A sudden acting performance.]
[Grumpy Brother rips off his
first ever name tag.]
I don't know why either,
but I was just told to do that.
- I thought we were looking for numbers.
- Numbers and this, too.
- I was just told to do what I did.
- Shouldn't you be cooking somewhere instead?
[This man has been quite busy
cooking for others lately.]
Yes, he and I are quite close.
[Be careful of how you say things!]
Why are you just hiding out in here
if you're the spy?
- You should be out and walking around.
- I don't like walking around.
I'm not very motivated.
I don't really want to do that.
[Seung Gi is still left struggling
because of his lack of motivation.]
- Am I ousted?
- Yes, you can just take a little rest.
Seriously, Seung Gi.
- I'll see you later.
- Yes, I'll see you later.
Seung Gi is so sloppy.
[The eight members are left to getting
themselves ousted by these Sloppy Brothers.]
What just happened?
[Nominated for Best Actor Award-
Ha Ha's act of shock.]
I've actually never met him before.
Hello.
[Nominated for Best Actor Award-
Big-nose's act of nonchalance.]
[Next up is Seo Jin's once
former co-star, Blank Ji.]
Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Why do you look so shocked?
- Seo Jin!
Sorry, Ji Hyo.
[Definitely a true actor.
What great act of shocked bewilderment.]
Ask him what's going on
because I don't know anything.
His character is like that
of a rich household's spoiled son.
He really hates to sweat,
and he really hates to be cold.
You know how most people feel guilty
if they're the only one warm and comfortable?
But he actually goes around
bragging about how warmly he's dressed.
That's what he goes around saying.
He acts like a brat.
If Seo Jin and Seung Gi
come around the corner
- we have to act like something's off.
- Jong Kook.
Yeah?
- Seo Jin's here.
- Seo Jin!
[Will the Sloppy Spy Brothers catch onto
the candid camera mission?]
- Seo Jin!
- Hello.
[Another awkward greeting time.]
I thought you weren't
going to come until later?
This is kind of sudden.
Jong Kook, I'm going to search upstairs.
Something about this feels off to me.
[Gary is being so obvious
about leaving the scene.]
[But Seung Gi doesn't even
catch on to Gary's awkwardness.]
Seo Jin's acting a little funny.
Don't you think so, Seung Gi?
[Kkuk pretends to be suspicious
of Seo Jin.]
- What are you saying is weird?
- The rest of the members are...
Hey!
[A thriller to Seo Jin and Seung Gi only,
and it's a comedy to everyone else.]
It's not like I can stick my name tag
out for them to rip off.
[Gary is the only one left to eliminate!]
[Let's get him!]
[Seung Gi's suddenly getting excited,
and Gary goes along with the act.]
[And the Young Master who will not
break a sweat by running.]
[Will he be eliminated first,
or will they catch on first?]
- Why don't you say 'hi' to Seo Jin first?
- Wait, he's scaring me.
Why would you be scared of me?
- How about we shake hands?
- This is what Choi Min Soo was like, too.
- No, I'm not like that.
- Okay, we'll just shake hands.
[While they're shaking hands,
Seung Gi goes in for the kill.]
[Gary's realistic acting.]
Let's just go eat, okay?
Come on, it's all over now.
[Two against eight mission-
Successfully eliminates all the members.]
Seo Jin, did you just oust me
because you want to go and eat?
I just wanted to finish it
so that we can go and eat.
- No one caught onto what we were doing.
- I was just searching for the pieces.
- You really didn't suspect anything?
- No, I didn't suspect a thing.
[This sloppy spy is so happy at being
complimented for his mission accomplished.]
[But, too bad...]
[Time to reveal the real truth
to the Spy Brothers.]
Seo Jin.
What was it that Seo Jin and
Seung Gi were doing?
I didn't feel comfortable
about what we were doing.
Here are the results
for your opening mission.
The opening mission results are...
'Two against eight- Fool the Guest Mission',
The eight members, wins!
[The eight members win the
opening mission!]
[Huh?]
[A celebratory atmosphere except
for the two Spy Brothers.]
[Unable to comprehend what's going on.]
- What's going on here?
- We just won.
Why? We eliminated everyone.
It was all candid camera?
[Amazing how they actually thought they had
fooled everyone with their awkward spy act.]
We had to let you eliminate us.
We had to let you think that you got us.
I was thinking that it was
all too easy.
What do you mean, it was easy?
You were getting beet red in the face.
[Had they been real spies, they would've
been caught within 5 seconds.]
- Seriously, I was so flustered.
- I didn't know what to do.
Do you see Seo Jin's expression?
It's like he doesn't even care.
[Seo Jin- 'What about it?']
[Who cares?]
He didn't really care about the mission,
and I was the only one feeling anxious.
I was feeling so anxious about
getting the mission accomplished.
- I know.
- We'll first announce the teams.
Seo Jin's really looking forward to lunch,
so we need to get the ball rolling.
[Announcement of lunch has
his two dimples showing.]
- Lee Seo Jin and Yoo Jae Suk.
- Us two?
Seo Jin and I are really close,
so I'm glad that we're a team.
- Look at that expression on his face.
- Seo Jin doesn't seem to agree with you.
[In reality, they haven't met
more than a few times in real life.]
[Seo Jin's pushing him away.]
[Grumpy Seo Jin is pushing
clingy Jae Suk away.]
- This is how you're supposed to do the show.
- No, don't do it.
Look at how he's sweating right now.
[Breaking out in a sheen of sweat
with Jae Suk's closeness.]
Maybe it's because he's happy about it.
Seo Jin's so awesome.
And Lee Seung Gi
and Moon Chae Won will be a team.
- Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo.
- Yes!
Kwang Soo.
Get away from me!
[Not happy with what he's seeing.]
That kind of overreaction is
what Seo Jin hates the most.
I told you not to do things like that.
- Right? He drives me nuts with that.
- Why do you keep doing things like that?
I really can't stand that.
[Grumpiness, venomous words, grumbling=
An unprecedented character.]
- Ji Suk Jin and Ha Ha.
- What? Why would you do that to me?
What kind of a reaction is that?
And Gary and Song Ji Hyo
will make up the final team.
[Lastly, Gary and Ji Hyo.]
Okay, here are the rules of
today's mission.
It's a Couple Making Race.
Seo Jin, you really have to listen.
[Doing everything that Seo Jin
hates the most.]
- Then shall we all do it together?
- One, two, three.
[Everyone leans in to listen together.]
Stop doing things like that.
Okay, this is good.
I'm going to have fun with Seo Jin.
[Wait for their new bromance to come.]
- What's that?
- We have one for each couple.
[An adorable character bag
for each of the couples.]
- Will Seo Jin have to wear one, too?
- Wear it around your neck.
Come here, and put this around
your neck.
That looks even weirder.
Just wear it across your chest.
- I'll put it on later.
- It's a cross bag.
- Wear it messenger style.
- Just put it on now.
Just put it on around you.
Or let me put my arm around
your shoulders.
[A huge laughter for the audience.]
[Ugh, seriously!]
[Maintains his pride and
tucks it underneath his arm.]
- Do you remember the cards that you found?
- Yes.
A total of 15 cards consisting of ten numbers
and five numerical symbols.
There are two sets of the 15 cards
that you have found
totaling 30 cards, and they've been
divided out to three cards per person
which comes to six cards per team, and
they're randomly divided out to everyone.
- They're all mixed up.
- I can feel them in there.
The team that gets rid of those cards first
at the final mission site wins the race.
[First team to get rid of the cards
wins the entire race.]
Here's how you can get rid of the cards.
There are two of each card.
In order to get rid of your cards, you
have to swap them out with other teams
to get a matching pair
in order to get rid of them.
Only the teams that come in the
first three places during the missions
will get the chance to swap out
their cards with another team.
The more missions you win,
more chances you'll have to swap
to make a pair of a certain number
or a symbol to get rid of them.
[The first team to make the pairs to
get rid of all the cards wins the race.]
[Under the bright winter sunlight,
they're off to their first mission site.]
You totally fooled me.
[Seung Gi was completely fooled
by Chae Won's great acting skills.]
- I was good, wasn't I?
- You were no joke.
Here they come.
Wave at them.
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin flag down
Jae Suk and Seo Jin's car.]
- What?
- I came up with a poem for Seo Jin.
- Just keep going.
- Let me hear it.
- Lee.
- Look here.
- Seo.
- Seo Jin.
- Jin.
- I really love you.
I really love you.
Go!
Just go!
[Feeling embarrassed.]
- He really hates it.
- Why does he hate it so much?
Seo Jin, do you want to do
one for Ha Ha?
- No, don't do things like that!
- We have to reciprocate their efforts.
[A rule of variety shows-
Return what you're given.]
Then just laugh out loud for me, okay?
Just do that for me, okay?
Just do that.
Okay, here we go.
We got them at the red light.
- Wait.
- What is it?
- Seo Jin and I've prepared something.
- What?
- A poem for you. Say your name.
- Ha.
Ha.
I said, stop it!
[An unexpected completion of a poem.]
[Intentional, or perhaps,
unintentional grumpy gag humor.]
- I can't believe that actually worked out.
- See?
[The bright winter sunlight
shines brightly off the winter ocean.]
There it is.
I have a good feeling about this.
Hurry, we have to run over there.
[What kind of a mission awaits
them by the ocean?]
- He's like a diamond in the rough.
- Why?
He complained nonstop the
whole way here.
[A grumpy variety show treasure.]
When I pointed out the beautiful ocean,
he complained about it being too bright.
[His grumpiness brings out
laughter from others.]
[First mission-
Piggyback ride for my love.]
- This is good.
- I've given you a piggyback ride before.
- It's okay.
- Sorry, Gary.
It's okay, you'll be giving Gary a ride.
One member from each team will
crawl under the net
and snatch the sack off the bar,
then over to their partner
and pull out a rubber shoe from the sack
to put it on their partner's foot.
Then you'll run over to the white line
and stand in front of the basket.
Then the person riding the piggyback will
throw the rubber shoe into the basket to win.
First place winner will be excused
from playing in the next round.
[First place winner will be
excused from the next round.]
- You can be excused from the next round.
- Then let's finish this at once.
- I think you'll be playing again.
- You can do the running.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Why do I have to?
We should play for it.
- What are you two talking about?
- What are you two mumbling about?
[Grumbler and the Grasshopper-
A lippy duo.]
[It seems as though Mr. Grumpy
will be sweating a bit himself.]
- He'll have to do it, too.
- Chae Won, let's start with you.
- You want me to give you a piggyback ride?
- No, I'm kidding.
[Piggyback ride for my love- Round One.]
[Piggy backers are getting ready
to give their partners a ride.]
[Everyone's looking relaxed and at ease.]
- Seung Gi, I've already got my shoes off.
- Okay, I'll be right there.
- Can someone cheer us on?
- Fighting!
- Kang Gary, fighting!
- Wait, and I'll come running to you, Seo Jin.
- What was that all about?
- Okay, fine.
- Lee!
- Look here.
- Seo!
- Seo Jin!
- Jin!
- I really love you!
[Turns around with a smile on his face.]
[Grasshopper's passionate declaration
of love for Mr. Grumpy.]
As mentioned before, the first place winner
will be excused from having to play again.
[First place winner will be excused from
having to play anymore rounds.]
- Ready!
- Sorry, sorry.
Set, go!
[Running full speed ahead.]
[Everyone arrives at the net
at the same time.]
[Their sense of urgency has them
crawling both under and over the net.]
[Getting their acts together to
go about it the right way.]
[Ha Ha moves full speed ahead.]
[Ha Ha's in the lead.]
[Jae Suk moves at a 90 degree angle.]
Where is he going?
[Ha Ha is first to get across the net.]
[Runs full speed ahead toward the sacks.]
[That's Jae Suk and Seo Jin's sack.]
That's not the one!
[The schemer we all know and love!
Throws it far off the course.]
[After eliminating Jae Suk and
Seo Jin's sack far off from the course...]
[Aims for his own team's sack.]
[But fails to grab his own sack.]
[Meanwhile, Jae Suk finishes
getting through the net.]
- Where did mine go?
- Seung Gi!
He threw it over there.
Over there.
Run, Seung Gi!
[Seung Gi gets through in third place.]
[Nice jump!
Gets the sack on his first try.]
[Seung Gi is suddenly in the lead.]
[Kwang Soo and Gary pass through
almost simultaneously.]
[Giraffe's natural instincts come out,
and throws Ha Ha and Suk Jin's sack away.]
You did great!
That was a good move!
[Seung Gi and Chae Won are in the lead
for the rubber shoe throw off course.]
[The partner on the back must make the goal
with the shoe in order to win the round.]
[Is the rubber shoe too heavy
for her slight foot?]
[The other four couples are
about to follow hot on their trail.]
Why is he so heavy?
[Mr. Grumpy looks to be having fun.]
[The area is suddenly busy with all
five couples making their attempts.]
[Let's just throw it and see what happens.]
[Seemingly uninterested, but
showing a fierce level of concentration.]
This is exhausting!
This is way too hard.
[The culprit in question, Lee Seo Jin.]
[Resorts to cheating when
his team isn't winning.]
[A fierce streak of competitiveness
behind the grumpiness.]
You're working really hard at this.
It looked like it was going to
make it in.
[Makes another attempt after
kicking away the other team's shoe.]
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are
also ready to take their aim.]
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
win the first round.]
[Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are excused
from playing in any further rounds.]
[Grumpy and the Grasshopper-
Arguing about who will give whom a ride.]
- You can't make the goal.
- I'm too exhausted.
Seo Jin, if we don't win it this time,
then you have to do it in the next round.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Ugh, Lee Seo Jin.
- Yours was going to make it in.
- I was going to make it in.
- Yes, it looked like it was going to.
It was going to make it in.
It looked like you were going
to make it in.
[When words aren't enough,
add in some footwork.]
Ugh, seriously!
- Lets rest after this one, Gary!
- Win this, and I'll buy you dinner!
- Wait, and I'll come for you.
- Win this, and I'll buy you a house.
- Okay, deal!
- Seo Jin!
You should say something, too!
- Seriously...
- Just say something!
Do a good job.
[A cheer from Mr. Grumpy.]
- He even said it twice!
- Yes, he said it twice!
- He said it twice, right?
- Get ready!
[Slides under the net.]
[Moving faster under the net.]
[Ha Ha's shocking spurt of speed again.]
[Ha Ha gets through at an alarming speed,
and the Grasshopper isn't far behind.]
Jae Suk was really fast, too.
Move!
[They all fail in succession.]
None of them can reach the sacks.
- They can't even reach it.
- You have to help each other.
[Ha Ha throws his shoe to knock it down.]
[Ha Ha's unbeatable scheming brain.]
Do a good job and I'll buy you
an apartment.
[Ha Ha's shoe comes speeding
through the air.]
[Just then, Gary jumps into the air
to snatch down his sack.]
[Jae Suk also gets his
with the help of his shoe.]
[Ha Ha also gets his
with the help of his own shoe.]
[Seung Gi finally takes off his own shoe
to attempt grabbing at his sack.]
[The shoe flies off into the stratosphere.]
[A true klutz in the works.]
[Makes a second attempt with
his other shoe.]
[Knocks the sack up even higher.]
Ugh, I'm going to lose it.
Hang on, Chae Won.
[Jumps into the air with
both the shoes in his hands.]
[The never-ending battle with the sack.]
[Ji Hyo and Gary arrive first
to throw off the rubber shoe.]
[Carefully takes aim...]
[Bounces off the basket and misses!]
You have to kick it off with some force.
Let me do that again.
[Gary and Ji Hyo's second attempt.]
[Second round- Gary and Ji Hyo win.]
They made it in.
[The remaining couples
are depleted of their energy.]
[Ji Hyo and Gary are also exempt
from participating in the next round.]
[Clumsy Seung Gi runs out of battery.]
- Seung Gi, you didn't even get started.
- What are you doing?
Sorry, Chae Won.
I don't even know what to say.
I can't believe that even
Ha Ha beat me.
Seo Jin.
You saw how I did it, right?
You just need to do it like that.
Do it just this once.
I promise that I'll make it in.
- We'll get it for sure this time.
- No.
- Just do it.
- We have to do it again?
- Come on, just do it.
- Let's just go!
- Where are you going?
- Seo Jin, where are you going?
Come on, just do it.
What are you doing?
I told you not to do stuff like that!
[The more tired he becomes,
the grumpier he gets.]
Hurry up, Seo Jin.
Just go.
What's he doing?
- Why are you walking around like a drunk?
- Lee Seo Jin is pissing me off!
[Grasshopper finally explodes from
all of Seo Jin's grumbling.]
Tell Lee Seo Jin to come out here!
[It seems as though he's quite stressed
from all of Lee Seo Jin's antics.]
[His fire isn't very easily flamed out.]
- Ugh, Lee Seo Jin!
- Just keep drinking!
Ugh, Lee Seo Jin! Who asked
Lee Seo Jin to come on the show?
[Piggyback ride for my love- Round Three.]
This is just ridiculous!
I just can't lose to these two!
- Seung Gi's really bad at these games.
- He's really bad.
- Want me to show you for real this time?
- Yeah, show it to me for real this time.
- I'm doing it for real this time.
[Please do it for real this time...]
Seung Jin... I mean, what am I saying?
[Seung Gi and Seo Jin= Seung Jin?]
All I'm even thinking about
in my head is Lee Seo Jin!
[A hand behind his back and a lazy stance-
His own way of being ready.]
- Can you please get ready?
- This is me getting ready!
[Grumpy is ready to go.]
- Who's ready to go like that?
- You're making us look weird.
[Please get ready like a normal person.]
- This is how you get ready.
- Can't you stand like this?
[Can't win against all the argument,
so steps one foot slightly forward.]
Satisfied?
- Ready!
- I don't think I've seen Seo Jin run before.
Set...
What are you doing!
- What are you doing!
- No, do it over!
[One man's sexy catwalk.]
[First ever net crawling
in Lee Seo Jin's variety career.]
- What is that?
- What is he doing?
- Look at Lee Seung Gi.
Look at what Seung Gi's doing.
[Young Seung Gi in his twenties
is first to get through the net.]
[A 27 year old's spurt of speed.]
[Pulls down the sack with just a single try.]
[The 40 year olds are still
struggling to get through.]
[Working hard even with all his grumbling.]
- What is he doing?
- What is Seo Jin doing?
[Meanwhile, Seung Gi and Chae Won
are ready for the rubber shoe course.]
[Grumpy finally manages
to get through the net.]
[Even in the midst of all his activities,
he still manages to obstruct Suk Jin.]
[Forcefully spikes down the sack.]
- He's the only one jogging.
- This isn't the beach in Miami!
[What a sad human being...]
[The Grasshopper finally hops
onto Grump's back.]
Okay, I'm going to make this in.
Step forward a bit.
He almost just swore at me.
Seo Jin was about to swear at me.
Seo Jin almost just swore at me.
[The couple in their twenties
takes their aim.]
Seo Jin almost swore at me.
[Seung Gi and Chae Won win
the third round.]
Seo Jin was about to swear at me.
What the heck?
What was that?
Wait... how did you get that
done already?
- Seo Jin, what is your deal?
- Let's just go now.
[Sorry to tell you this,
but this is only just the beginning.]
[Time for the card swap.]
Everyone has three cards each,
which is six cards per team.
Second and third place winners can choose
one couple to swap out their card with.
[Second and third place winners can swap out
their card with any one of the couples.]
[The first place winner can swap out two
of their cards with any couple they choose.]
Take a look at the six cards
that you have amongst your team.
Choose and decide which card you'd like
to swap out with which team.
The first place winner has
the best advantage.
Why would you take one of ours?
Why not take someone else's card?
Do you guys know which
cards we have?
- No, I don't know what you have.
- Let's just make it quick and go home.
[Grumpy starts his grumbling since
he doesn't have a chance to make a swap.]
- This is the fun of it!
- It was a close call for you, too.
[There are more games to be played.]
I'm just saying that we should go.
No, he's right.
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo makes
a swap with Seung Gi and Chae Won.]
- We choose just one card?
- I'm going to take this one.
You have to give us one in exchange.
Give it to us with the card facing down.
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
already have a match.]
- They already have a pair.
- Let's take one of theirs.
- They have a matching pair.
- We're going to swap with them.
[Ji Hyo and Gary also choose to
swap with Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.]
[Unhappy with their excitement,
first place winners are being targeted.]
We don't like how happy you are.
Ji Hyo's good at choosing things like this.
- Why are there only four cards?
- What are you doing?
[Giraffe is caught
trying to pull a fast one.]
Kwang Soo, let's make it quick, okay?
I'm sorry, I'll make it quick.
Seo Jin has to go and cook.
He doesn't have much time.
He's pressing down really hard
with his right thumb.
I think he's doing that on purpose.
[Their matching pair is still left intact.]
[Embraces each other whenever
they look at their cards.]
[First place winner has two chances
to swap out their cards.]
- We're going to choose one from Seo Jin.
- Good.
Seo Jin, you have to pull out your cards.
Yes, you can take it.
- We're going to look.
- We're going to look at it.
[Gets a matching pair.]
[What luck is this!]
[Okay... I got it, so get away from me.]
He seems happy about something.
Look at how big he's smiling.
- Yes, he's happy.
- Did we give them a pair?
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo choose to
swap again with Seo Jin and Jae Suk.]
What are you going to do?
Just hurry up and do it.
- Make sure not to take ours back.
- Just hurry up and do it.
[The start of real mental battle.]
[Who will be the ultimate winner
of this mental battle?]
We have a matching pair right now.
We lost a matching pair,
but we gained another one in its place.
We're going to have to be careful about not
looking too excited when we get a pair.
It doesn't really matter to me
even when we do get a matching pair.
- Yes, I've noticed that.
- I don't really care to win that much.
I think that's what confuses
the other teams.
Because just like you said, you don't
really get all that excited about it.
You just wait and see.
We're going to end up winning this thing.
Just pick whichever card.
What's all the fuss about?
That's because of Kim Jong Kook.
And Jae Suk's team has the seven.
Because Jae Suk and Seo Jin got
really excited when we gave them our seven.
- But we took back our seven.
- Yes, then they have the seven.
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin's excitement over
the seven shows they have the other one.]
Why isn't Suk Jin in the car?
Suk Jin wasn't in the car with Ha Ha.
I wonder if he's sleeping in the back.
No, there's no way he
could be asleep.
[Yes, that's a very likely possibility.]
This is the place.
Seo Jin and I make a really good pair.
We're like real brothers.
There's something enigmatic about him.
There's an unknown charm about him.
Hey, Song Ji Hyo.
Seo Jin told me that you threatened to
poke his dimples through his face?
- When did I ever say that?
- He told me that's what you said to him.
- Do you really want me to spill your secret?
- What?
- Go on and tell us.
- You're the one with secrets, not me.
That's why you're not spilling, isn't it?
Seo Jin is...
[Only one sitting down while
everyone else is standing.]
[Seo Jin looks more like someone
who's just here to watch the filming of RM.]
Seo Jin, I saw that
your niece is here outside.
- You have to look towards the camera.
- You won't get much airtime like that.
- No, it's better that I don't.
- Wait, I'll go and get her.
[Yoo Hyuk leaves the room
to get Seo Jin's niece.]
Ellie.
Why don't you come with me?
- You can watch from the inside.
- Really?
[Seo Jin's niece and his sister.]
- Ellie, tell your uncle to work hard, okay?
- She's so pretty.
[Ellie is an avid fan of Kwang Soo's, and
it's been her wish to visit the set of RM.]
Ellie, can you say something
to your uncle?
Tell him to work hard.
[An obvious fool over his niece.]
[On the set of Running Man
with Uncle Seo Jin.]
Ellie, keep watching and see how
hard your uncle's working here on set.
- She's so cute.
- I'm not working very hard.
[Will he work harder now
that his niece is watching?]
Your next mission is,
'Lovey-Dovey Back hug.'
You will randomly choose one of
the fifteen items that are set behind you.
All the items are numbered and
while one hugs his partner from the back
the couple will then proceed to move
the items with a pair of long chopsticks.
You can succeed by moving all five items
within the time limit that you're given.
- Yes, you'll be given one minute.
- Not just one, but five items?
- You can succeed in one try.
- Really?
Please bring out the chopsticks.
[Time to bring out the chopsticks.]
[The giant chopsticks are longer
than an average person's height.]
- Why don't we have Seo Jin try it out?
- Seo Jin, give it a try.
- Stop just sitting around.
- It's time to spit out blood.
We have to pick the items?
Pick something.
[The items that they randomly choose
will play a key role in their success.]
[What did Seo Jin choose?]
A shower stool?
Okay, that's not bad.
[A light and easy to grab shower stool.]
- You're going to have to help me with this.
- Should I take my jacket off?
What got into you?
I can't believe you're taking off your jacket.
[For the first time ever,
Seo Jin shows some initiative.]
- I guess you're trying to work harder?
- You want to do a good job, don't you?
It's done in the method as described,
and if by a chance...
[The picture they draw
elicits some laughter.]
- You guys look like a couple.
- It's as if you are one.
We look pretty good, don't we?
Seo Jin and I are close enough
to be brothers by now.
Seo Jin has a pretty big stomach.
- Maybe I'm seeing things wrong.
- Seo Jin works out.
- You have to move one every ten seconds.
- This is a shoo-in.
[If they win this,
then they'll win first place.]
- That's too easy.
- How are you going to grab this?
Are you going to grab it like this
or grab it from the side?
[From top to bottom, or from the side?]
[Plan is to grab it from the side.]
Ready, set, go!
[Lovey-Dovey Back hug.
Round one.]
[They got it!]
[Fails again.]
[Totally focused.]
- Look at his dimples.
- He's gritting down on his teeth.
He's having fun.
He's liking this game.
[Mr. Grumpy is into this game.]
[Good luck, Uncle!]
[Finally gets a firm grasp!]
- What are you doing, Seo Jin?
- Grab it from front to back!
[This time... throws it off to the side.]
- Seriously.
- He's like a little kid playing.
Seo Jin, what are you doing?
[The clock keeps on ticking...]
Come on, seriously!
Okay, we've got this one.
[Barely manages to get their first one.]
[New plan- drag it over to the table.]
[Now they just need to
lift it onto the table.]
This is a really aggravating game.
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin fail the mission.]
This is impossible.
[Ugh, that's too bad.]
They were too rough with the stools.
[Second couple- Ha Ha and Suk Jin.]
Suk Jin, we really can't lose this one, too.
- Please, Suk Jin.
- Okay!
[Suk Jin's random draw- Lipstick.]
- Ping pong ball!
- No, it's lipstick.
[Mr. Grumpy looks very enthused.]
[And Seung Gi seems just as enthused.]
- They got lipstick as their item.
- I guess we'll get our chance next week.
I guess this week isn't it.
- Our win will come next week.
- Big nose is flustered.
I think Seo Jin's having fun now.
He keeps smiling nonstop.
I can hear him laughing
nonstop next to me.
He really likes the lipstick option
that you pulled.
[Finally seems to be getting into the game.]
Suk Jin, we just need to
grab it from the bottom.
- Grab it from the bottom.
- Ready!
Big-nose can't do this.
Big-nose won't be able to do this.
No, I can't do this.
- Big-nose can't do this.
- I thought I could, but I can't.
[Oh, they got it!]
I failed it as I thought I would.
[Forcing back down his laughter.]
- You have to really bend down.
- I think I got this one.
Okay, take it slow.
[Oh, no... so close!]
- It's all over now.
- Big nose is annoyed.
Big-nose is annoyed,
but continuing to try is Big-nose's style.
[My name is Big-nose,
and giving up is not in my vocabulary.]
[Persistent Big-nose finally succeeds
in getting one on the table.]
- That was awesome!
- Big nose!
I'm the figure of hope
for all men in their forties!
[Forties figure of hope, Big-nose.
Two lipsticks on the table!]
Never giving up is the most important thing.
[He grabs another one!]
[Big-nose's miracle!]
This is Big-nose's time!
[With one falling on the ground,
only two are left on the table.]
[And successfully gets the third one
up on the table.]
One fell off the table.
[Succeeds in getting four,
but one fell off the table earlier.]
- You have to pick the other one back one.
- Big nose is going to succeed.
I like Big-nose's persistence.
[Persistent Big-nose successfully
gets all five on the table.]
- You succeeded.
- But you failed at minute and 50 seconds.
[Fails the mission by going
over the time.]
[Mr. Big-nose is the best!]
Big-nose, my butt.
He just said, 'Big-nose, my butt.'
[Can't contain his words any longer,
and lets them slip out past his tongue.]
I can't believe he just said that.
[But kudos to Big-nose's persistence.]
[Seung Gi and Chae Won's turn to draw.]
[Yogurt]
- Did you get the shoelace?
- No, it's the yogurt.
Yogurt?
[Will they be able to pick up and
move the small yogurt bottles?]
- Ready...
- Do you want to do this?
- No, you can do it.
- No, you do it.
- You can do it.
- I think Seung Gi will be awful at it.
[Self-proclaimed klutz.]
- I think we're going to be about the same.
- Why don't you try it?
You're not going to ruin
this opportunity, are you?
[Seung Gi and Chae Won- Start.]
Seung Gi's doing it.
[Carefully picks up and moves the bottle.]
- There's a little nook for him to grab.
- What just happened?
[Chae Won's slapstick comedy attempt.]
- You knocked Chae Won down!
- No, keep going.
No, you can keep going.
I did that on purpose.
- I did that on purpose.
- You have to hold on.
Time out.
What's wrong, Chae Won?
[Chae Won's repeated slapstick comedy.]
You can do it.
[After only two weeks on Running Man,
Chae Won shows promise in the variety world.]
She's like the drunk master.
[Starts over with Chae Won now in front.]
We have to stand this one back up.
[Chae Won easily succeeds
with the first bottle.]
[But flips the next one,
and knocks the next one over.]
Think about Big-nosed Brother
and don't give up.
Remember Big-nose's mentality.
Seung Gi, Seo Jin says
you can't be doing that.
[Drops it right in front of the table.]
[Seung Gi and Chae Won fail.]
[Ugh, this isn't easy.]
[Jong Kook, Kwang Soo and Gary, Ji Hyo
also fail at their first attempt.]
Please let it be the stuffed animal.
The metal pot!
- That's going to be easy.
- The pots have handles.
- You can go up front.
- Okay, I'll go up front.
[Pots are easier to move due to
their lightness and easy to grab handles.]
Ready.
[Is Mr. Grumpy nervous
with his niece watching?]
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin's second attempt.]
[A steady grasp under the handles.]
See?
They got it under the handles.
[Easily succeeds in moving their first pot.]
Seo Jin, isn't this fun?
Seo Jin's having fun.
Look at how Seo Jin's
shoulders have narrowed.
Seo Jin's shoulders have narrowed
because he's actually trying.
[Transforms his stance for the win.]
[Stares at the pot
as if he's ready to gobble it up.]
[Succeeds with their second
pot with Seo Jin's efforts.]
[40 seconds left on the clock.
At this speed, they just might succeed!]
Look at how focused he is!
He's not even blinking his eyes.
He's taking one tiny step at a time.
[Moves the third one successfully.]
[Cheating Kwang Soo steps behind Seo Jin.]
They've got less than 20 seconds left.
[Works around Kwang Soo's interference
to successfully move the pot.]
This isn't good.
[Five seconds left on the clock
with only one left to go.]
[If they succeed, then they win the chance
to swap out two of their cards.]
[Lovey-Dovey Back hug.
Succeeds the mission.]
[They did it!]
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin win first place.]
[Even with all his grumbling,
Seo Jin still manages to get the job done.]
- You did it, Seo Jin.
- Okay, fine.
You did it!
[The annoyed vs The emotional]
Isn't this so nice?
[Uncomfortable with Jae Suk's back hug.]
Can you give me a piggyback ride?
[Get away from me!]
This is so great!
Seo Jin and I did it!
Let's all give him a group hug.
[The ever so popular, Seo Jin.]
Wow, that was so great.
[Only one more winner's spot left with
Seung Gi and Chae Won having won 2nd place.]
[Lipstick]
- What was it?
- Lipstick!
- Lipstick, please!
- We'll accomplish the impossible.
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
attempt mission impossible.]
Just stay in the back!
- We're supposed to do this together.
- Just stay in the back!
I told you to stay in the back!
- Stop doing things like that!
- I need to grab the chopsticks, too.
- Can you tell him to stop doing it?
- Grab the back end.
[Poor Kwang Soo...]
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo- Start.]
- Suk Jin really had done great.
- How did he do that?
- You have to grab it low.
- That's good.
Move slow.
- Hold still.
- Okay.
[Succeeds the first one.]
Think like Big-nose.
[Succeeds the second.]
You can't let yourself feel anxious.
[Succeeds the third.]
Jong Kook, we have to get this done.
[Succeeds the fourth.]
[Please...]
[Will they succeed?]
[A dramatic finish!]
[Jong Kook and Kwang Soo go against
all odds to come in at third place.]
Today must not be my day either.
But there's still next week.
[Big-nose will still rise up
to the challenge next week.]
Give me a high-five.
[Gives him one as if he has no
other choice.]
Big-nose will try again next week.
[Cheers to Big-nose's unfailing spirit.]
Please stand on top of the hearts.
The third place winner has the chance
to swap out one of their cards.
Please choose which team
you'd like to swap your card with
and the chosen team will then
step forward.
[Who will they choose?]
- Who do you want to go with?
- Chae Won and Seung Gi.
- Let's see your cards.
- We don't really have anything.
- They already have a pair.
- We're going to make our selection.
- You have to keep them well hidden.
- I wish I could trade, too.
[Choose number three
to make another matching pair.]
[Seung Gi makes the decision for him.]
The choice is ours to make,
so how can he do that?
I was just touching it
and he pulled his hand down.
- What were you thinking?
- I was just touching it.
- But you were still holding it.
You have to give them one of your cards.
[The card Seung Gi and Chae Won
will be receiving is...]
- Okay, it's your turn to make your swap.
- We've got a lot that you'd want.
- The choice is yours to make.
- You want us?
[Seung Gi and Chae Won choose
Ha Ha and Suk Jin.]
- I can't believe they chose us.
- Big-nose is very happy.
Go on and choose whichever
one you'd like.
[Successfully gets a matching pair
after drawing number two.]
- They don't look happy.
- No, I think Seung Gi got something.
- You have to give us one.
- Give us a card.
[Zero is given out.]
It's time for Yoo Jae Suk
and Lee Seo Jin to step forward.
You can swap out two of your cards.
Let's take one from Jong Kook.
Just trust us and take one of ours.
- We're serious.
- No, you have to think about this carefully.
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin are once again selected.]
- But you know that we have something.
- No, you don't have a pair for us.
[They already have one matching pair.]
I feel really bad for this team.
[Draw the equal symbol to get
a second matching pair.]
No, he's peeking!
He's leaning over to take a peek!
- I can't even see anything.
- What are you doing!
[Bravo.]
You're totally into our show now, aren't you?
You're so cute.
Your dimples are so adorable.
[A dimpled angel?]
Dimpled brother.
[Successfully matches up another pair.]
- Give us a good one.
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin fail
to make a matching pair.]
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
Seo Jin, you really are a good listener
when it comes to doing what I say.
- You're a good listener.
- Just do it.
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin's bromance.]
[Chooses Gary and Ji Hyo
to swap their second card with.]
- I think he's peeking through the camera.
- I can't see anything.
- He's looking at the glare off the camera.
- He's not that type of a person.
All the exchanges have now been made,
and I will reveal the current card status.
[Current matching card status.]
- We're ruined.
- A matching pair...
- A matching has been made.
- Someone must have two matching pairs.
- There are two couples with a matching pair.
- There must be a team with two.
There must be a team with
two matching pairs.
There is one couple...
with two matching pairs.
- Wow, see that?
- It must be Jong Kook.
- It really isn't us.
- You're overreacting.
No, Jae Suk's acting weird.
- No, it's not Jae Suk.
- Yes, it's us.
[What fate will come to our currents lead,
Jae Suk and Seo Jin?]
So we're currently tied
for second place, right?
- Yes, we are.
- We could've had two matching pairs.
- Where did that card go?
- I know they had it earlier on.
[Seung Gi and Chae Won also
have a matching pair.]
Three out of the five teams
currently have a matching pair, right?
But we don't have any.
How can we be this unlucky?
But which one of the three teams
do you think has the two matching pairs?
- Aren't you even curious about that?
- The team that had the most chances to swap.
I think it could be Jae Suk.
I think it's Jae Suk's team.
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin are currently
in the lead with two matching pairs.]
Wow, I haven't heard this
song in forever.
I used to love hearing this at nightclubs.
I have a lot of old nightclub songs on here.
Really?
You put them all on there?
[Mr. Grumpy is a lover of 90's music.]
- I love music.
- Yes, I really love music, too.
I thought you'd like calm music,
but you like upbeat music like this?
Rock music is what I grew up with,
and that's pretty much what I listen to.
Wait, this song?
You have this?
- Wow, I can't believe this!
- This is the best nightclub song, isn't it?
This song is the best!
I've been searching for this type of music,
but I just haven't been able to find any.
[DJ Jin's throwback to 90's nightclub music.]
- Who sings this song?
- Genie.
- I don't go to clubs.
- Me neither.
- We come from the days of real nightclubs.
- Yes, you're right.
- Clubs are no fun.
- Have you ever been to a club though?
Once or twice?
- And you didn't think it was fun?
- No, not at all.
I didn't even want to go,
but I was basically dragged along.
[Loves the old nightclubs better than
the current trendy clubs.]
We're not used to this type
of music, are we?
- We like the shorter three minute music.
- Yes, you're right.
Songs with actual lyrics.
Then there are songs like this one.
[Time for a little romance
on the nightclub dance floor.]
Wow, Seo Jin.
You really are full of surprises.
We're definitely going to win today.
Do you know that you're smiling and
laughing a lot more than you did earlier?
You're really into it now.
It's really great.
[Reminiscing about
the old days with Jae Suk.]
- Remember how much fun it used to be?
- It used to be so much fun.
But it's no fun at all these days.
[While these two are busy taking
trips down the memory lane...]
['M' Museum in Bucheon.]
[The final mission site.]
I'm suddenly feeling nervous.
Where are you going?
I'll see you later.
Before we start the final mission,
we will get the final tally of the cards.
If you currently have a matching pair
in the stack of cards that you have
set down the matching pair on the tray
as you shout out the word, 'clear'
to eliminate those cards from your stack.
- Must we really shout that out?
- Are they serious?
Can you please edit that part?
What's going to happen now?
Is something going to explode?
So I can prepare
an appropriate reaction for it.
[After five years of being on RM,
Giraffe now even requests for CG effects.]
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin currently have
two matching pairs.]
Throw the pairs on the tray
as you shout out the word, 'Clear'.
[I have to shout that out?]
Okay, multiplication symbol, clear!
[Jae Suk shouts out the first clear remark.]
- What do I shout out?
- I have to shout out, 'Clear'?
Equal, clear.
Can't you be more
cool about it as you say it?
- Why are they making us do this?
- Can you put more emphasis on it?
- They'll going to add in a CG effect.
- What's that?
- Why would they add in a CG effect for this?
- Okay, equal symbol, clear.
The card bounced off the tray.
[Here's an example of how it should be done.]
Clear!
Wait, where did it go?
[Masters of CG effect reaction acting.]
[Kkuk's overreaction to the effects.]
Okay, clear.
[Seung Gi and Chae Won sweetly
clear the matching pair of two's.]
If you have a matching pair of cards...
- We don't.
- Okay, sorry about that.
- Do you have any matching pairs?
- No, we don't.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha don't have
any matching pairs either.]
[The remaining cards are attached under
their name tags as little number tags.]
[This is... how the final
mission will be carried out.]
Here's your final mission.
Your final mission is...
'Card elimination.'
- Card elimination.
- Why is he being so dramatic over nothing?
If you rip off the number or symbol card
from the back of another player
then the player missing the card
will be frozen on the card.
At which point, you can give one of the cards
from your back to the frozen player.
[Give an unwanted card to the frozen player.]
[Pull off the card you want,
and hand off the card that you don't want.]
Once you find a match to your own card,
lay down the pair on the 'R' marked tray
and you must shout out the number
and the word, 'clear', for it to be valid.
The first couple to get rid of all the cards
will be the ultimate winners of the race.
- We just have to get the cards.
- This is very simple.
Then I just get the number we need
and get rid of the other to win the race.
We have the biggest advantage right now
because we already had two matching pairs.
We will now start the final mission.
Go!
We should stick together.
- Hey, Seung Gi!
- Oh my, you startled me.
[Both teams each have the number, six.]
[Checking to see if they have any cards
that their own team needs.]
We need to see if you have
anything that we need.
[Running around in circles
to see what they have.]
- You can't try cornering us like this.
- Gary... Gary... he has something.
[Chae Won mistakes the nine
Gary has on his back for a six.]
No, you saw it wrong.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo has the seven.
- Really?
- Come here.
Come here, Chae Won.
[Splits up.]
[Seo Jin keeps his bottom
firmly planted on his seat.]
Jong Kook!
Just end it now!
Gary!
[Everyone's ganging up on Gary and Ji Hyo.]
- Ji Hyo.
- Why are you doing this?
- Do I have something that you need?
- I don't know, I didn't get to see.
- What's wrong with you?
- I didn't get to see.
- Get away from me! Go away!
- Look at the numbers on my back.
- You don't have anything we need.
- Let me take a look at what you have.
I don't have anything.
[Seung Gi sneaks up behind Ji Hyo
to snatch her six.]
[Attacks while Ji Hyo's
distracted by Chae Won.]
[Kkuk gets the three he needs
from Seung Gi.]
[And dumps one that
he doesn't needs on Seung Gi.]
Clear!
You need to work out more so that
you don't get knocked down like that.
- I was just so startled.
- I know.
Yoo Jae Suk.
There he is.
He's in the bathroom.
There he is!
[They both need the Five.]
[Yoo Hyuk is left to defend himself
while Mr. Grumpy takes a break.]
We have to get the Five.
We have to get the Five away from him.
[He got the Five in his hand!]
[But Yoo Hyuk maintains
his defensive position.]
[Ha Ha resorts to a Tyson move.]
[Ha Ha rips off the Five with his teeth!]
- I'll give you this one.
- Okay, give it to me.
[Swaps out the two numbers.]
[Ha Ha gives Jae Suk his Division symbol.]
- Okay, on the count of three.
- Five, clear.
[Ha Ha and Suk Jin clears Five.]
Seo Jin, what floor are you on?
I now have a Division sign,
which I know Gary has.
Chae Won has the Four that you need.
You need to come down for us to do this,
so come down to the second floor.
Seriously.
[Ugh, this is so bothersome.]
Hey, just get up here!
Hey!
- You're going to be had!
- I'm sure Jong Kook will win anyway.
We lost the game.
How are we to beat Jong Kook?
[Guys, it's easier to just give up.]
[Meanwhile, the rest of the players
haven't given up and are still battling.]
Why are you laying down?
You can't lay down here.
[Is something going on over there?]
There's still Suk Jin.
Let's go after Suk Jin.
[Mr. Grumpy sits himself back down.]
I can't believe how hard
everyone's working at this.
[With their two current cards,
they only need one more match to win.]
[Just then!
Jae Suk spots the Four!]
[Ambushes Chae Won... and fails.]
[Lays back down on the ground.]
- Chae Won, I need that number!
- No, don't do it!
We can't let Jae Suk win!
[Seung Gi chases Jae Suk away
with Kwang Soo's help.]
You can get up, Chae Won.
Get up, Chae Won.
- What are you doing?
- Why is she on the floor?
- Come on, get up.
- You can't sleep down there.
What was Jae Suk going for?
Jae Suk needs Chae Won's number to win.
- Chae Won needs to be careful of Jae Suk.
- We can't let Jae Suk win!
- Seung Gi, you have to protect Chae Won.
- Seung Gi, you have to stick with me.
- You have to stick with me.
- There's nothing you can do about this.
[Jae Suk is now targeted
as their number one enemy.]
If not me, then someone else will win.
Let's go find Seo Jin.
[Seung Gi and Chae Won leave
to go search for Seo Jin and his Four.]
[Ha Ha and Seung Gi immediately
corner Seo Jin for his number.]
No, you're not coming after me.
[Mr. Grumpy runs away with
his bangs flying in the breeze.]
[Seung Gi can clear Four if
he can take Seo Jin's away.]
No, you can't.
[We've never seen Mr. Grumpy
quite like this before.]
Seung Gi, you can't do this to me.
[Seo Jin, this is what Running Man is like.]
- You have to rip it off.
- No, you can't.
- It's already practically off your back.
- Why are you doing this?
[Mr. Grumpy is desperate
to hold onto his Four?]
[But Ha Ha takes the number instead?]
[Seo Jin's Four is swapped out
for Ha Ha's Six.]
- Seo Jin, you have to grab Ha Ha.
- What is this?
[Ha Ha now has the Four
that Seung Gi needs.]
[What is he talking about?]
Seo Jin, grab Ha Ha for me.
[Seung Gi requests for Seo Jin's help.]
You guys take care of it yourselves.
[The person who took the number is more
desperate than the one who got ripped off.]
- Seo Jin, did you get it?
- No, I had it taken away.
- Who did?
- What do you have?
- Who took your Four?
- Dong Hoon.
What do you have now then?
Okay, Ji Hyo has the Six.
Come with me.
We have to stick together now.
[The card battle is reaching its climax.]
We have to target Ji Hyo now.
[Gary and Ji Hyo are close to
winning the race themselves.]
[The end is near.]
- We have it, too.
- What did you say?
We have it right here.
What are you doing?
We have the Division symbol.
[Immediately launches into attack.]
[Trying to break it up as if breaking up
a fight between his nephews.]
- Tell him not to do it!
- Get the card, Seo Jin!
[Either Jae Suk's Division symbol, or
Kwang Soo's Division symbol will be taken.]
[That'll mark the end of the race.]
[Something definitely doesn't sound right...]
[Seung Gi eyes his chance,
and springs an attack on Big-nose.]
[Did his ambush succeed?]
[Fails the attempt.]
[To make up for clumsy Seung Gi,
Chae Won launches her own attack.]
[Chae Won succeeds!]
[The symbol on Kwang Soo's back...
Jae Suk grabs!]
[And he gets it!]
[Jae Suk and Seo Jin get the Division!]
[Seo Jin's unwanted Six is handed off.]
Division, clear!
[Pair matching race- Game over!]
Today's victory goes to
Yoo Jae Suk and Lee Seo Jin.
Okay, I admit that you won, but Jae Suk's
the only one who shouted it out.
I'm totally serious.
They're supposed to shout it out together,
so let them shout it out together now.
If they won't do that,
then we can't accept their win.
[Must I really do that?]
[They demonstrate how it needs
to be done.]
Shout it out like that.
I'm just going to leave.
Hey, listen.
He won't do the first portion of it.
[Refuses to take the win
if he must go through all the shouting.]
These are just the rules,
so you have to shout it out.
- We were told to shout it out together.
- No, he's right about that.
Okay.
Mission...
Okay, fine.
I think he's about to do it.
[Second attempt.]
Seo Jin, Ellie is watching this right now.
- Are you ready?
- Do it for Ellie.
Mission...
[A little more enthused than earlier.]
We have to shout it out together.
Clear!
[What is Seo Jin doing!]
Okay, let's start over.
We'll take the 'clear.'
You just have to give the
ending emphasis.
[Must I really do that, too?]
See?
I did it.
[Finally manages to squeak
something out.]
- That was his best.
- He gave it his best efforts.
[Now that he 'cleared' the mission,
time to hand out the gold ring prize.]
I bet Ellie would like that.
[Hand that over, too.]
[Puts the ring for his niece
deep in his pocket.]
[And hands the other ring to Chae Won.]
[Seung Gi can come back another time
to claim his prize then.]
Give me the gold that you already owe me.
I still haven't received mine yet.
It's over at his house.
I had so much fun being back together
with my Running Man family again.
I really hope that everyone
loves our movie.
Chae Won, anything you'd like to say?
I've never ran so hard in all my life.
You'll come back again, won't you?
You should come back again.
[A cute E.T. promise instead for an answer.]
[And a closing word from
our dimpled angel.]
I've never really liked
Running Man to begin with...
and I like it even less now.
[Dimpled angel's closing remarks.]
That's a lie.
He's such a liar.
Did you all see how he reacted when
Seung Gi tried to take his number?
[Even though he may grumble a certain way,
Mr. Grumpy had a lot of fun on the show.]
[Thank you to Lee Seo Jin, Lee Seung Gi,
and Moon Chae Won for your participation.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Hong Jong Hyun]
[Seo Kang Joon.]
[Choi Tae Joon.]
[Nam Joo Hyuk.]
[Seo Ha Joon.]
I just got beat by a bunch of kids.
[Attack of the new flower boys.]
[Is this the variety world's new wave?]
Have you ever had a crush
on any one of them?
[And a round of questions with their fans.]
- I let him know that I liked him...
- I crushed on her for three years.
[Win their hearts for the win!]
[Crush report from the flower boys.]
[And a new secret gets revealed.]
Have you ever had a crush?
[Next week on Running Man-
Flower Boys' Crush Report.]