[A new challenge for Running Man.]
[Sometimes the things that look
the easiest are the hardest.]
[Tense]
[Anxious]
[Restless]
[And nervous?]
[What's making everyone this anxious?]
[An unfamiliar mission, location,
and a limited amount of time.]
[A performance in three
and a half hours?]
[Their opponent,
"People Looking for a Laugh" crew.]
[The war of laughter starts!]
[Their first ever time
taking on live comedy!]
[Awkward]
[Am I doing well?]
[I need to throw myself
away to be funny!]
[The performance time is nearing]
[and the audience is filing in.]
[Their fear grows]
[and the suffocating tension.]
[They need to overcome
everything to succeed.]
[Team Running Man has]
[an iron will and undying passion.]
[And...]
[the best live comedy
performances around, the PLL crew.]
[For someone, it's a new challenge.]
[For another, it's a battle of pride.]
[Running Man vs. PLL]
[The war of laughter starts now.]
[The Running Man members are]
[headed somewhere,
without knowing this.]
We could have won
with a better strategy.
[They're still in shock from
the 100 vs. 100 battle.]
I had a drink with Geun Sik yesterday.
He was so upset.
- Geun Sik grabbed him first.
- He didn't know.
The Hongdae people all
had a drink together.
We put all our strongest people
in the first and second round.
There were only people like me
left for the third round.
There were only weaklings
during the third round.
It was like a war between
ants and humans.
I looked around, and all of a sudden
there were like four people
surrounding me.
When people see it on TV,
they think it's easy.
But when they actually try it...
But you saw everyone
yesterday, right?
As soon as a game started,
everyone went crazy.
Jinu was in the back.
But as soon as he went up,
he fought with everything he had.
[That's natural for
the name tag game.]
Seriously...
We would have never
seen Chang Jung Koo.
- That was an honor!
- He's a hero.
I'd never imagined I'd throw
toilet paper rolls with him...
And I didn't think he would cheat.
It was an honor, and we're thankful.
I bet he enjoyed it though, when else
would he get to do these things?
I got a text from Sung Mi saying
that she had a great time.
I don't know what we're doing today
but it's not easy to beat us
when we're a team.
Where's our opponent?
[Who will be their next opponent?]
[After the 100 heroes?]
We're in Gangseo-gu.
This is SBS in Deungchon-dong.
[SBS in Deungchon-dong?]
- SBS!
- It's really SBS.
- Thank you.
We used to come a lot before the
Mok-dong building was built.
[Why did they drop them off here?]
It's been a while.
It has been a long time.
["Three Great Emperors"
is being filmed.]
They're filming "Three Great Emperors."
(cooking show)
It smells so good.
I'm so hungry, and it smells so good.
[We will introduce you to
Running Man's opponents.]
[SBS comedy department]
[People Looking for a Laugh]
A slice of cake should
be enough for your birthday, right?
Here's your slice of cake.
[They represent the comedy show
that keeps live comedy alive.]
[Over the course of ten years]
[they've had so many
stars and catchphrases.]
[So many comedians
work day and night.]
[The comedy department is
always busy for all 365 days.]
[Creativity grows and blooms here.]
Jung Soo is planning
something new all of a sudden.
[For the five minutes that
they stand on stage]
[They never stop planning and
discussing, day and night.]
[This is where laughter is born.]
[Running Man came
to see the PLL crew.]
[Really? Where?]
Oh, this is the "Between Men" team.
You guys are married, right?
[They're a real couple,
but not married.]
- Hello.
I've never been in a place
like this before.
[It's Hip-kwondo
and Namolla family!]
Chan Woo's here too?
[The entire PLL crew is here!]
[The icon of PLL,
Cultwo is here too.]
[The two big brothers from Cultwo
are here to cheer them.]
Hello.
[Rip]
[As soon as Tiger enters their territory,
the enemy catches him.]
I just really wanted to rip it, wow!
[I want to try, once...]
We used to do this a long time ago.
- I know, right?
- Do you guys still get tested?
[They're in Suk Jin and
Jae Suk's spots from 20 years ago.]
They're a couple.
- Are you guys still together?
- Yes, we are.
- And you guys, too.
- For seven years.
[Eun Hyung and Jae Joon
have dated for seven years.]
There isn't any drama?
[We're happy!]
Jae Hoon, Jae Hoon.
Jae Suk, Jae Suk!
Eun Hyung, Eun Hyung!
[With the greetings aside]
[why did they come to the
comedy department?]
We just got off the bus...
- We had no idea.
- Why are you here?
We don't know either.
We've explained on the way,
but the Running Man will be one team.
And the PLL crew is one team.
[Team Running Man vs. team PLL.]
Since there are a
lot of PLL members
two groups can be sent to
the Running Man team.
Team Running Man
can pick two groups.
[The competition will
be a game of Ddakji.]
You can get two groups if you win.
[Team Running Man can
only scout when they win.]
[Pick me, pick me.]
[Makdoongie (The youngest)
is already working on it.]
[A character who is the
youngest of a gangster group.]
[Is she still in character?]
I'm so curious what her
real personality's like.
- Please say your catchphrase.
- I don't have a mic.
I am Makdoongie.
[She's so cute.]
[Close your eyes and ears,
I am Makdoongie.]
[And a Hip and a Kwon and a Do.]
Ambar!
(Amber lookalike)
I auditioned for your
music video once, and failed.
[He auditioned for
Namolla family's music video?]
Who did that to you?
- Really?
- Yes.
- He might have a grudge.
- No, no.
We were very ambitious.
So we prepared a skit for you.
Oh, thank you.
And a in, and a few, and a moments.
[In a few moments.]
[Ha ha]
They're catchphrase is "and a".
And a la, and a ter.
Later.
And Run and a ning, and a man.
Running Man.
[Running Man vs. PLL
War of laughter.]
[Cultwo gets to choose
the participants.]
["Cobong", Jang Jae Young.]
Cobong, Cobong!
[Nose vs. nose]
He has seniority here.
- Do your signature move?
- Okay.
[Nose, nose, nose.]
It makes a noise!
[Big Nose, too?]
He put the same finger
in his nose.
[That's gross...]
He couldn't say anything because
everyone was watching.
[What are his Ddakji skills like?]
[Slap!]
[He caught everyone's attention
with an intense sound.]
[He failed because it
turned around twice.]
[Wow]
[Big Nose succeeded in one try.]
[Big Nose is showing off
his Ddakji skills.]
[Slip]
[He's taken aback by
his powerful opponent.]
[Moran-bong Home Shopping
is on their priority list.]
[Water bottle?]
[Homemaker Baek's TV,
Jung Soo's sketch.]
I will try drinking water without
using my hands.
Really, how?
Low blood sugar!
[Without using his hands,
but his feet.]
[Splash]
[He needs to wash
his entire face, though.]
[Good job!]
Kwang Soo, drink some!
You need to kick it!
Low blood sugar!
[Splash]
[Gulp, gulp]
[Good job!]
- You did it.
- I did it.
That was great.
You look exactly like Big Mama.
[She resembles Chef Lee Hye Jung.]
She looks like Big Mama,
Chef Lee Hye Jung.
Yoon Hwa, you go up.
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Ha Ha gets to go first.]
[It turned around twice.]
Go, Yoon Hwa!
[Monstrous strength]
[Her super slap-down attack.]
- There's such a skill?
- Yoon Hwa's pretty strong.
[Ha Ha succeeded!]
[Disappointed]
I can't just fail...
They're good at Ddakji.
[The next group is "Between Men."]
He's funny.
I will pick Song Ji Hyo who looks exactly
the same as my girlfriend, Eun Hyung.
[She looks the same as Ji Hyo?]
[They look alike.]
I'm the Song Ji Hyo in the comedy world.
You look alike.
[Do we look alike?]
I can mimic Song Ji Hyo's face.
She can be a little
blank sometimes.
When she's sleeping in the car.
It's the same!
It's Ji Hyo!
[A match between the
two Song Ji Hyo's.]
Let's go!
[It flipped over!]
[A ceremony between men.]
Between Men!
Next is...
Lee Dong Yup.
"This Day in History."
[He's performing in
"This Day in History."]
He's my friend.
Is your hometown Hapcheon?
Mine is, too.
[They're from the same hometown.]
I'm from the home of ducks, Yaro-myun.
[Yaro in Hapcheon,
Gyeongsangnam-do?]
- Yaro?
- There's a place called Yaro?
Just play already!
[We're from Hapcheon!]
Let me just talk!
I haven't been on TV!
[What is he doing?]
I love Hapcheon!
[He's using this time to
promote his catchphrase.]
Is that your catchphrase?
It is.
He's from your hometown, go easy.
[Jong Kook failed.]
- I love Hapcheon, so much!
[I love it so much!]
[Success!]
[There's no hometown
in front of victory!]
[Team PLL is back on track.]
Dong Yup knows how to play!
[Who's the next opponent
on Team PLL?]
I'm the newest member of the
comedy department, Lim Ji Hyeon.
[Wow, she's pretty!]
I'm Nurse Lim in "Awkward Boknam."
She majored in
physical education!
She went to Ewha Womans University.
[What will the passionate and
youngest member show us?]
I will show you a surprised
African American woman.
She approaches.
What?
[Burst of laughter]
She studied kinesiology,
so she must be quick.
[She missed.]
[Boo!]
You're not very fit...
[Plot twist]
[Big Nose succeeded.]
[Team Running Man
is good at Ddakji.]
[This is a coldblooded battle.]
[They flip]
[and flip again.]
[Team Running is in the lead.]
And a con and a gratu and a lations.
[Kim Seung Ho from
"C'est si bon Returns."]
Seung Ho is a hard worker.
I will also work hard.
Do you like him?
I like someone else.
Her voice got deep.
She's so honest.
[Shy, shy]
Does he know?
I got rejected today.
[Oh no...]
To be honest, everyone here
spends day and night together.
And people get along fast.
But if you're going to date,
erase your makeup.
[Oh...]
[The Laughter War]
[Number one, Casting War]
[Team Running Man won by
a significant amount.]
Two, four, six, eight.
Thank you.
Our team won a lot.
[Our?]
Makdoongie doesn't
have a Ddakji, right?
No.
We completed our
performance a month ago.
I was wondering,
because I watch the show...
I was like,
"why is she still wearing makeup?"
She even made her own name tag.
I really loved that group.
- You guys are done?
- Yes, they are.
Please take her,
she put in so much effort.
We'll bring Hyun Jung to our team.
As an additional member.
- Is that okay?
- That's okay.
[With everyone in agreement,
Makdoongie is on Team Running Man.]
It doesn't matter which
group joins us.
We like everyone.
We have to compete in games, right?
Then we have to pick groups
that can play well.
It's a win-win for everyone.
I'm hesitating because of Anna.
And a win, and a win.
We know because we're comedians.
He might make us a little tired.
- "Between Men."
- I personally want them.
Because they have the signature move.
We'll pick "Between Men."
We haven't picked Hip-kwondo yet!
- It's a little hard...
- What about Ji Hyeon?
[Please pick me!]
That was big!
- At the last minute...
- Boknam seems so awkward!
[He's always awkward.]
I was so surprised.
We'll pick "Awkward Boknam"!
Nice, nice!
Hip-kwondo
was next on the list.
[He transformed.]
Hip-kwondo was next on the list.
But because of Anna...
I thought it was going to be
a long day, listening to him.
Then I'll speak less.
And a get, and a lost.
[They picked their teams.]
[No more warming up!
The war of laughter starts!]
[The slapstick battle that
they don't budge an inch!]
[We will win with
our final weapon, our faces!]
[Who will be the winner of
the Laughter War?]
[After both teams
have been decided.]
We're on the same team, now.
[It's each team's lunch time.]
This reminds of a long time ago.
It's nice.
[Thumbs up]
She keeps telling me
to come visit her house.
[Makdoongie's cute confession.]
When I break up with my boyfriend
- are you going to date me?
- No.
[Sad...]
Jong Kook will accept you
if you keep trying.
[Really?]
Jae Joon and Eun Hyung have
been dating a long time.
It's been seven years.
- The award acceptance speech.
- Many people remember it.
Congratulations, Kang Jae Joon.
My girlfriend is Lee Eun Hyung.
I'm going to marry her!
Eun Hyung, I love you!
We are going to get married soon.
[Wow!]
January or February of next year...
You didn't know?
Really?
This is how it kept
getting delayed.
You wanted to, but you couldn't?
- We had a slump.
- PLL wasn't doing really good.
I was curious, but wasn't PLL
stopped for some time?
After PLL disappeared,
we were helpless.
We were hoping that it
would return again.
We just kept making new sketches
in a little theater in Daehang-ro.
That really gave us strength.
That's what made us today.
We can just perform now.
What about Gun Young?
He was a staffer for
"Infinity Challenge."
[Have I ever seen him?]
I worked as an assistant cameraman, too.
- I worked hard.
- And then you became a comedian?
We're living together.
To be honest, unless you're
a fixed member on PLL
it's hard to pay for rent...
What do you do?
When PLL disappeared in 2010
I worked part-time as security
at the mart across the street.
[He didn't have any other choice]
[but to survive.]
I worked for two months
and no one recognized me.
And then one day,
as I was greeting customers.
One of the comedians recognized me.
- It was Comedian Son Byung Eun.
- I know her.
She gave me lots of advice
and she helped me come back.
- And parents...
- can be against it.
I prepared to be a comedian
discretely for two years.
They were against it,
but when I appear on TV
they love it.
[That's how parents are.]
How many years has it
been for you, Hyun Jung?
- It should be like ten years.
- Yes, it's been ten years.
Her colleague is Jung Joo Ri.
Joo Ri appeared in different programs,
but I wasn't able...
Can't you invite me on
"Happy Together"?
[Let's be happy together.]
[Flustered]
Why are you talking about a KBS
program on Running Man?
Or just ask for
"Infinity Challenge."
Can I be on "Infinite Challenge"?
Are you asking me?
He doesn't have a solid ground, either.
What are you saying?
[Makdoongie, isn't
Running Man enough?]
Let's not get swayed
by Running Man.
You need to do well!
Let's not get swayed by them.
Serious, let's win this!
[They get motivated!]
[The Laughter War]
[Number two. The laugh triathlon]
["P" University Stadium, Seoul]
The weather is really nice.
They're coming!
They're here!
Hello!
[We're here, brothers!]
How many are there?
[Fighting spirit is charged!]
[On alert]
Let's go Running Man and PLL!
Jung Hwan is here.
He always brightens up the mood in
"Same Bed Different Dreams."
Jung Hwan is on
"Same Bed Different Dreams"
every morning as a warmup MC.
He comes every morning
for that short amount of time.
For the audience,
when they arrive.
Can you show us a little bit?
[We want to see!]
Thank you for coming today!
Please give a round of applause!
[The atmosphere is good!]
- Two, two!
- Three, four!
- Bird goes?
- Chirp, chirp.
That's so surprising.
[Use a quick wit test to
bring up the atmosphere.]
[Their teamwork improved,
already.]
[This time, it's time to test
Team Running Man!]
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- Two, two!
- Bird goes?
- Chirp, chirp!
- Cat goes?
- Meow, meow!
Turtle?
- Stretch, stretch!
- What do you mean stretch?
[For some reason,
they really want to win at this...]
[Make a battle between
the two teams to raise]
[to raise their participation.]
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- Two, two!
- Bird goes?
- Chirp, chirp!
- Running!
- Man!
- National!
- Singing Contest!
- AB!
- CD!
[Team PLL is this good.]
[Let's do well, too!]
[We can do it!]
Turtle goes crawl, crawl!
[Wake up!]
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- Two, two!
- Bird goes?
- Chirp, chirp!
- Infinite!
- Challenge!
- Running!
- Man!
- National!
- Singing Contest!
- AB!
- CD!
LM!
MG!
[We've been tricked again!]
Please give a big round of
applause to Jung Hwan!
[His devilish MC skills.]
It gets me to focus quickly!
He sweats for 30 minutes
and leaves.
[A hidden supporter
that gives all his energy.]
There's such a difference when
Jung Hwan MC's and when he doesn't.
It got me pumped!
- I learned it from Dong Yup...
- He learned it from someone, too.
It's a cycle,
there's always someone.
Can we see Dong Yup's version?
- Let's see Dong Yup's version!
- Jung Hwan already did everything...
[The expert warm-up MC is up!]
A round of applause from PLL!
[Wait]
When they become an expert,
it's not just "applause."
It's more slurred!
It's free and casual.
The tone is different.
It's a little different.
[Lee Dong Yup's version
is about to start!]
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- Two, two!
- Choo, choo!
- Chug, chug!
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
- The best comedian?
- Lee Dong Yup!
- A comedian that you like?
- A successful comedian?
- Lee Dong Yup!
- Choo, choo!
- Chug, chug!
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
Choo, choo, choo, choo,
choo, choo, choo.
Chug, chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug, chug.
Wow!
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
[That's the best!]
[Team Running Man, we can do it too!]
It's not hard.
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
Choo, choo, choo, choo,
choo, choo, choo.
Chug, chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug, chug.
I will do it on my own!
Sorry, we were practicing!
We're just practicing.
[Okay, let's try it again!]
- One, two!
- Three, four!
- Two, two!
- Turtle goes?
- Crawl, crawl.
- National!
- Singing Contest!
- Choo, choo!
- Chug, chug!
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
- The best comedian?
- Lee Dong Yup!
- A comedian that you like?
- A successful comedian?
- Lee Dong Yup!
- A comedian that you hate?
[Oh...]
A comedian that you don't like!
You aren't thinking!
[We've been tricked again!]
[Team Running Man's last chance.]
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
Choo, choo, choo, choo,
choo, choo, choo.
Chug, chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug, chug.
- Choo, choo, choo!
- Chug, chug, chug!
Choo, chug, choo!
[What?]
[A qualified rehearsing MC.]
This is so much fun!
I want to have a day
of just recreation.
[Now that we've warmed up,
its time for the real battle!]
We will start the triathlon.
The first game is
face battle.
You must wear stockings
that are tied to the pole
and stack five yogurt drink
bottles quickly, to win.
I love stuff like this.
This is made for comedians.
Who will go first on Team PLL?
We'll have Kang Hyun go first.
His face is overwhelming.
[The aura of a comedian.]
- So we have Kang Hyun...
- And what about Gary?
We'll have Gary!
[He's slightly alerted.]
They look alike!
- They look alike!
- There's a similarity...
Kang from Jinju clan?
Which generation?
Who cares?
His face is very overwhelming.
[Both participants are]
[heading to the battlefield.]
[His back is already humorous.]
I can't see!
Gary!
[His hip-hop charisma is gone.]
If I do this and lose,
I'd be really upset.
[I've met a strong opponent...]
[Extreme visual]
I've lost my pride.
[They managed to raise their motivation,
will they be able to win?]
Ready... start!
[Round one: Gary vs. Kang Hyun.]
[They're already speeding up.]
[Oh my!]
[He had to break due to
the stretchy stockings.]
[The visual brothers can't
hide their struggle.]
[With one mistake,
the tower flopped down.]
[Just a little more...]
[This is a first...]
How do you even make this face?
Ow!
Gary, you look second to none.
[That's a compliment, right?]
You look like salted pollack roe!
[Salted pollack roe]
[Gary managed to
stack four bottles.]
He sort of looks like Je Dong.
[Kang Hyun needs to stack two more!]
[Gary's on his last.
Kang Hyun needs two more.]
[I can't...]
[Gary completed the tower!]
[Team Running Man won the
first round of face battle!]
Gary won!
[Good job, my brother!]
Gary looked just as
bad as Kang Hyun.
[Team Running Man one vs. PLL zero.]
Jae Joon will go up this time!
Lee Soo Hwan!
[Let's play fair.]
They're a little similar.
[Slide]
How do you win that?
[Visual big match!]
Ready, set...
[Round two of face battle, start!]
[Speed up!]
[Relaxed]
[Squeeze]
[Wow]
[The face revolution!]
[Full of surprises]
[Let me take a picture with you.]
What are you doing?
[I need to record this rare event!]
[Collapsed]
Jae Jun, Jae Jun!
[This is a chance!]
[Okay, it's a good chance!]
He can't see anything.
[His eyes are completely closed.]
[How come I can't see anything?]
[Where is the table?]
[Oh, it's right here.]
[As soon as he gets to the table,
his eyes are closed.]
He can't see it at all.
[Pawing the air]
My stomach hurts!
[Meanwhile, Jae Jun
makes a final burst.]
[He put four in a row.]
[Pawing the air again.]
[He keeps putting it around the tower.]
[This is my last yogurt!]
[Just a little more to go!]
[Kang Jae Jun completes
the yogurt tower!]
Wait a minute!
[I did it!]
[Team Running Man wins
the second round of "Face Battle."]
[I want to open my eyes!]
Soo Han couldn't do it because
he was able to see up to this point.
But, it got tight and
made his eyes close.
He calculated over there, but...
You can't really see anything?
Give them a round of applause!
[For Jae Jun and Soo Han
who made us laugh!]
I've never laughed so hard
in the past five years.
Do you have anything
that you can show us, Soo Han?
- Anything better than this...
- I think I've shown everything.
Team Running Man wins the first game.
[The first game, face battle]
Good job!
[Laugh Triathlon]
[Running Man vs. PLL]
The second game is to
test your expression.
And the title is
"Speak While You Jump."
A rep will play jump rope
and explain the quiz by gestures.
The rest of the team
will solve the problem.
You have 100 seconds to do the game.
We need someone who's really expressive.
That person will be...
how about Jae Young?
[Cobong falls into the
category of slapstick.]
Jang Jae Young!
Wait a moment!
In my opinion, you're
clapping for nothing.
For us, being on Running Man
is a big event!
[Being on a variety show for the
first time makes them very excited.]
No, no!
The new members are at the very back.
You need to listen to
everyone's opinion.
I only noticed three people speaking.
Just you three were talking,
and the rest were just clapping.
[Yoo Jae Suk never lets us down!]
We have other games, too.
This time, Choi Baek Seon can do it!
[The rep for "Speak While You Jump"
is Choi Baek Seon.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes, Jae Suk!
- Kwang Soo's good at it.
- Solvers should be good, too.
- Kwang Soo, can you do it well?
- Yes, I can do it!
The category is proverbs.
- Proverbs?
- You're good at it!
Try and explain only the key words.
- Start!
- Good luck!
[Knock stone bridges before you cross.]
(Look before you leap.)
- No smoke without fire?
- Knock stone bridges before you cross!
Tread on a worm and it will turn.
[Tread]
Tread on a worm and it will turn!
[Nice!]
[Cutting water with a knife.]
Many hands make light work.
Cutting water with a knife!
[It hurts!]
[But, we got the problem!]
[Stabbed by a reliable ax.]
(In trust is treason.)
Stabbed by a reliable ax!
[They already got the answer,
but he keeps acting.]
[Did they solve it?]
[Oh, no!]
Rotate a little slow!
[A frog doesn't remember
that it was once a tadpole.]
[That must be frog!]
[His gesture for a tadpole!]
A frog doesn't remember
that it was once a tadpole!
[Lee Kwang Soo successfully
explained five questions so far.]
[He that will steal a
pin will steal an ox.]
Once bitten, twice shy!
[His energy is running on empty.]
The eye of a needle...
[After making a gesture of a needle...]
He that will steal a pin
will steal an ox!
[Nice words for nice words.]
[He's speaking ill words.]
Old habits die hard!
He that will steal a
pin will steal an ox!
Nice words for nice words!
[Lie down and spit.]
(Cut off your nose to spite your face.)
Lie down and spit!
[He works hard and keeps spitting.]
Okay!
[Many drops make a shower.]
- Now stop!
- Good job!
[Good job, Lee Kwang Soo!]
[Team Running Man scored eight.]
[Team PLL's rep is Choi Baek Seon.]
[You can do it!]
Get ready, and start jumping.
[Love and Soul]
(Ghost)
Love?
You Are My Destiny!
- Love Actually?
- Marriage Is a Crazy Thing!
[Frustrated]
I Love You!
You need to do this!
[The most famous scene!]
- Love and Soul! (Ghost)
- Okay!
[Drunken Master]
[Stagger, stagger]
Drunken Master!
[The Monster]
(The Host)
[Roar]
The Monster!
[With just one glance!]
[Titanic]
Titanic!
[The Matrix]
The Matrix!
[So far, Team PLL solved five problems.]
[The Beauty is Distressed?]
(200 Pounds Beauty)
The Beauty is Distressed?
[Moving up and down]
Are they cheering for the World Cup?
[Scissorhands]
(Edward Scissorhands)
Scissorhands!
[Scissorhands]
Stop, how many did they get?
[Exhausted]
They looked like they were
cheering for the World Cup!
Seven questions!
[Team Running Man vs. Team PLL]
[8:7]
[Laugh Triathlon]
[Team Running Man wins.]
[And finally...]
[The final match for
"The Laughter War Race!"]
[The live war of laughter will
take place at a theater in Daehak-ro.]
[Team PLL vs. Team Running Man]
[Who will win the race?]
[The Laughter War]
[The final mission, show time!]
["K" Theater, Jongro-gu, Seoul]
You're here for the second match
of "The Laughter War."
- We won last time.
- We won the first match.
Those games were the ones that
were favorable for Running Man.
So, you've won the first match.
The second match will be favorable
for Team PLL which is live comedy.
The rule for the second match is...
A total of eight groups
will be performing today.
It's the match between the
three groups that will include you
and the other five groups.
It's a sketch battle!
The audience will vote
when the show is over.
So, we'll compare the vote for the
three groups and the five groups.
These three groups have someone
on mind for their sketches.
I recommend Kwang Soo.
It should be Kwang Soo.
[They're recommending each other.]
Gary!
- My group...
- "Between Men"
Our catchphrase is
"Haha, it's so funny!"
So we picked Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha has been chosen.]
[Embarrassed]
[Haha, it must be funny!]
And if we're allowed...
we also want Song Ji Hyo
who looks like Eun Hyung.
Haha, it's so funny!
[Ha Ha is happy to share
the embarrassment with Ji Hyo.]
Haha, it's so funny!
[It's the first time for RM members
to be onstage for a live comedy.]
I really love their sketch,
I don't want to ruin it.
That's what I'm saying.
Siu is a member of
"Makdoongie (The Youngest)."
- Makdoongie.
- Hyun Jung is putting on makeup.
You should pick Jong Kook.
It's not a heavy role,
it's going to be very short.
Kim Jong Kook!
[Kkuk is chosen!]
[Whatever the reason is,
Hyun Jung picks Kkuk.]
It fits you!
[Oh, my stomach!]
[Abruptly hugs]
- You didn't draw your beard yet.
- I didn't have time.
Hyung Jung, Jong Kook
in picked for your sketch.
[At every opportunity]
I put a kissing scene.
[Helpless]
[So far, Ha Ha, Ji Hyo,
and Kkuk are chosen.]
[Who will be chosen for
"Awkward Boknam?"]
- We really wanted to pick Kwang Soo...
- Awkward Kwang Soo!
We choose Gary.
[What am I going to do?]
[So much pressure]
I feel so relieved.
[Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Kwang Soo
can sit and watch the show.]
[The joyful ceremony!]
Why did you pick me
instead of comedians?
Gary was feeling uneasy about this.
Gary feels awkward with
this kind of stuff.
Unlike the other groups,
they don't look so happy about it.
[The happiest face]
That's their personas.
[Makgoongie],
[Awkward Boknam], [Between Men]
vs. [Burdensome Deal], [Homemaker Baek]
[Hey, Hochan!], [Hip-kwondo],
[This Day in History]
[Time until the show]
[It's time to practice!]
Gary, I never knew the day you practiced
for a sketch would come!
I can't believe it!
- I'm so awkward, go away!
- The best casting ever!
[The really awkward Gary]
What's his role?
I think he should be
the one who's awkward, as well.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
If I memorize the line...
I'm sure I'll say it awkwardly like,
"I'm sick."
It'd be better if I just follow
the situation and act.
Gary has acted for movies, too.
Started his career with "Dachimawa Lee."
[Gary's retro hair style suits him.]
As a member of a Korean independence
army who disguised as a Japanese spy.
And he acted as a drunk man
in "Wonderful Radio."
I've acted as a drunk man twice.
In "Emergency Couple", too.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are practicing
with the "Between Men" team.]
- Steak, steak!
- We ate that yesterday, too.
[Ji Hyo is an immature girlfriend.]
We didn't today, I want it!
If I buy it again today,
my wallet will be empty.
Then, the seat right next to you
will be surely empty, too!
[Actor Song's
facial expression and panting.]
[Good job, Song Ji Hyo!]
[They're here to watch them.]
Look at Ji Hyo.
[She's nervous for her first comic role.]
It's funny to see them
practicing for a sketch.
- Don't interrupt us, please.
- I'm sorry.
[Regardless of what they say,
Actor Song is focused on her acting.]
Jae Hun, Jae Hun!
[Scream]
[Awkward]
[She's demonstrating.]
If you don't buy me a steak,
I'll become a snake.
[This is the original actor's acting!]
If you don't buy me a steak,
I'll become a snake.
What if I can't do this?
You need to make
a fool out of yourself.
Seriously!
[Make a fool out of myself,
and become a snake.]
[I'm a snake!]
Haha, it's so funny!
Do I have to act all of this?
- Ha Ha and I will do that part.
- You just need to show a reaction.
[Anxious]
This drives me crazy.
Ha Ha, Ha Ha!
[Ha Ha's role is a boyfriend who's sick
and tired of his immature girlfriend.]
Buy me a steak, hurry up!
Where are we?
Thank god, I didn't take that role.
I couldn't possibly act like that.
When I'm timid, I become a coward.
But you did a good job taking
the comic role in "My Boss, My Teacher."
No, not at all.
You'll probably standing
up on that side.
After saying "yes,"
it's my turn, right?
[Serious]
What is it?
Is Gary acting?
Keep quiet, do you know
what the detailed acting is?
[Actor Kang Gary is
absorbed into acting.]
I've read the script.
This is a sketch,
but I don't have any funny lines...
I only have kissing scenes...
We had a meeting together
but Hyun Jung wrote the script.
At least, when you guys
have action scenes
I could protect her or something.
- There's a scene.
- Is there?
I usually do an ad-lib
around that time.
Didn't we say we'll have
a new member today?
Yes, I recruited a really good man.
Nice to meet you, I'm Makdoongie.
By any chance, are you Hyun Jung?
No, it's "my first love Hyun Jung."
I love you, but I hate when
someone says the line wrong.
I draw a distinct line between
public and private matters.
By any chance, are you
my first love Hyun Jung?
- Jong Kook...
- Didn't you say I'm your first love?
Who are you?
[Grabbing by the collar]
[While he was acting,
he accidentally punched his chin.]
Did you just punch my brother?
[What is Makdoongie doing?]
- How dare you?
- Whose side are you on?
Just grab me tough, then I'll say.
"Please, let go."
[Polite]
When you let go of me,
then you can talk with her.
[Gary and the Awkward Boknam team
are practicing on stage.]
I think it's good that you said
Ji Hyo twice.
[Giraffe praised Gary's acting.]
Don't explain to me.
Are you trying to teach me?
- Did you record that?
- Was he giving you a lesson?
- Did he give you a lesson?
- Yes, he did.
I know what I'm doing!
- My pride has been hurt.
- He started acting way before than you!
He was in "Dachimawa Lee."
I started acting in
"My Dad Is a Bodyguard."
[An hour before the show]
[Team Running Man
is working hard to practice.]
[The show time is near, and the script
seems even more confusing.]
[No matter what, I need to
memorize the lines.]
Jae Hun, I want to eat a steak!
[Ji Hyo has to get used to the tone.]
We had that yesterday,
let's eat something else.
Don't swear!
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
[I'm afraid...]
[Gary is nervous, too.]
[The more I look at the script,
the more confusing it seems.]
I'm sorry.
[He's so serious.]
I confused the order of the lines.
- You should put yourself in my shoes.
- You have a lot lines.
You have to act at the right time.
I have to quickly act
right after they say.
[If he gets the timing wrong,
the sketch will be ruined.]
[Worried]
Boknam gives the stethoscope to Gary.
Gary examines Boknam.
[Gary looks like as if he's going
to memorize the whole script.]
This will be removed.
Let's do it again, I need to
memorize it anyway.
[Practice makes perfect.]
[Kkuk's team is at the
peak of practice, too.]
At this moment, you need to block
and move to that side.
No, we're used to do it from here.
Because, I have to punch
and move like this at the end.
But, Jong Kook will be standing here
and he has to push me.
- But pushing...
- Then from where and how?
Do we have enough space for that?
How about doing this?
- That's pointless.
- What should we do?
[30 minutes before the show,
the audience gathers slowly.]
[She keeps staring at the script.]
[Read and memorize,
that's the only way to go!]
Then, the seat right next to you
will be empty, too!
- It's "surely empty."
- Will be surely empty, too!
This is so embarrassing,
it's driving me nuts!
[As the showtime is near,
their head blanks out.]
[Kkuk is rehearsing on stage.]
I'm so nervous.
[The movement at the
right timing is really important!]
[Will they be able to do
as they practiced?]
[While they're busy practicing,
the audience has started to enter.]
[They couldn't possibly imagine that
Running Man members are here.]
[The theater is almost full.]
[Backstage, everyone seems busy.]
[Gary is the first one to perform out
of all the Running Man members.]
- Good luck!
- Gary!
It's good to do it first.
If the person before you does it well,
you feel more pressure.
Also, it means he'll finish early.
[Envy]
Could you put the microphone
on my right cheek?
I have a thing.
[He even avoid his jinx, to act better.]
If you don't buy me a steak,
I'll become a snake.
[Ji Hyo acts like Actor Song today.]
That's too bad!
[Team Running Man checks with
the action meticulously.]
[Team PLL is getting
ready for the show.]
[After a few strokes]
[she transforms into Big Mama.]
(Chef Lee Hye Jung)
[They're used to their roles]
[but they keep practicing.]
Good luck, PLL!
[We'll win the Laughter War!]
[It's showtime!]
[The audience can't imagine they'll
be able to see Running Man here.]
[Finally, the stage lights turn on]
[and Running Man members
appear on stage.]
[the audience starts screaming.]
[Scream]
[What in the world is happening?]
[That's Giraffe!], [Big-nosed Brother!]
[And there's You Hyuk!]
[The audience welcome
Running Man ardently.]
- Nice to meet you!
I'll tell you why we're here.
We're filming the Laughter War today.
We've filmed the first part last week
and we're filming the
second part with you today.
[Cheer]
- Are you excited?
- Yes!
The final mission that'll
take place here is...
the battle of live comedy
between PLL and Running Man.
[It's a battle of live comedy.]
Please enjoy the show
and cheer for them.
When the show is over,
you can vote at the exit.
Please vote for the funniest group.
With a big round of applause
we'll start the show today.
Thank you!
[The second round of
the Laughter War begins now!]
We'll watch here with you!
[What's going on here?]
[The theater is full of cheers already.]
[But there's full of
tension at the backstage.]
- You'll standby now.
- Bye!
Bye, Gary!
[Gary is the first one to perform out
of all the Running Man members.]
[Good luck, Mr. Gary!]
[Will he be able to do it as he
practiced and not make mistakes?]
[The first group to perform today is]
[Homemaker Baek's TV.]
[They start performing
to a big applause.]
The first group is
"Homemaker Baek's TV."
They started it already, right?
- Yes.
[Nervous]
[Awkward Boknam is the next to perform.]
- Do you want me to give you a present?
- Yes!
Here's sugar for you!
(Chef Baek's nickname is the Sugar Boy.)
[His lips became parched
out of nervousness.]
And you set a fire!
This is how I burn vegetables
and eat only meat!
[Oh, my god!]
[Hong Yoon Hwa provoked a good laugh.]
[Right before they go on to the stage]
["Awkward Boknam with Gary"
team encourages each other.]
["Homemaker Baek's TV" team
brightens up the mood.]
[Finally, Mr. Gary's turn
to be on stage.]
[Team Running Man:
the Awkward Boknam with Gary]
Garam, why do you want
to break up with me?
Do you love another woman?
It's nothing like that.
Watch your mouth, we're in the clinic.
Please come in, Mr. Oh Bok Nam.
Then what's the reason?
I said what's the reason?
I think I've got a cold.
[Good luck, Gary!]
You left your stethoscope
at the x-ray room.
- The x-ray room, I'll be right back.
- Mr. Oh, wait!
[Boknam goes to the back,
it's Gary's turn.]
[Oh, no!]
[Finally...]
[to the stage!]
[Awkward Boknam's choice is Kang Gary.]
That's so awkward!
Gary was feeling uneasy about this.
Gary feels awkward with
this kind of stuff.
[Practice, practice, practice!]
[Practice makes perfect!]
I need to practice this part.
I can't make it smooth yet.
[He summoned his secret acting skill
with 20 years of experience.]
I didn't even make any mistakes!
This is confusing!
[Will Actor Gae be able to
act without any mistakes?]
[Gary appears.]
[That's Gary!]
What the heck is the reason?
- I've got a cold.
- Won't you shut up?
[Sad]
[Awkward]
Let me ask you one thing,
who's the woman you see every Monday?
Song Ji Hyo...
Song Ji Hyo.
Do you know Ji Hyo?
Why do you like her so much?
Why don't you two work together?
[You two... us?]
[Awkward]
He's normal.
Just stop it!
Can't you do it properly?
[Properly?]
[Can you hear my heartbeat?]
You should shift your position!
[What?
That wasn't in the script...]
[He said to shift.]
Please show us!
[Thanks to the ardent
support of the audience]
I have hairs on my stomach...
[Laughing]
Hey, Kid, can you close
your eyes for a moment?
I have nothing to show you.
[Embarrassed]
He sounds normal, too.
You dirty bastard!
[Shocked]
Why would you behave indecently?
[You told us to...]
We're sorry.
No, I didn't say that to you.
I'll examine Mr. Oh Bok Nam first,
and call you after.
- See you later.
- I'm sorry, Kid.
[Kang Gary leaves the stage
after his splendid cameo.]
[Actor Gae, wow!]
Gary did a good job.
[Kang Gary, thumbs up!]
[Gary is waiting for
the next appearance.]
Are you saying the patient
is more important than me?
- Lim Ji Hyeon!
- Why are you doing this to me?
[He's really shocked.]
Where are you going, Doctor?
- Does he think I would stay?
- Miss Lim, nurse, Ji Hyeon!
[Gary appears again!]
Doctor, I think I'll come back later...
[For some reason...]
[I feel shy...]
I feel strange...
Let's go get some air together.
[The Awkward Boknam and Gary
happily ended.]
[Desirable Kang Gary!]
[Lighthearted]
Thank you so much!
You did a fantastic job!
You guys worked in perfect harmony.
I liked your ad lib.
"Hey, Kid, close your eyes."
My legs are shaking.
People laughed a lot.
[The Awkward Boknam with Gary,
successfully performed.]
[The next group is Team PLL's
Hip-kwondo.]
My name is cheek-bone!
[The audience is under
these three men's control.]
There are so many people.
- Really?
- Did you see the audience?
- Go take a look.
- Are there a lot?
- No, it'll make him nervous.
- I think it's better if you stand-by.
- Sure, no problem.
[After the Hip-kwondo, it's Makdoongie.]
Cheer for me, too!
Good luck!
Why are we out of sync all the time?
[Makdoongie with Jong Kook
team is on standby.]
- Who the heck are you?
- We are Hip-kwondo!
[Hip-kwondo team leaves the
stage in cheers, too.]
[Right before they go on stage,
Mr. Capable gets nervous, too.]
[Running Man team-Makdoongie
with Jong Kook]
So, the new member Makdoongie
is supposed to come here?
[Runs]
Hello!
I'm Makdoongie!
[Makdoongie is cute.]
[Nervous]
[Acting silly]
Aren't you, by any chance,
my first love Hyun Jung?
- You said you became a police officer.
- I'm an undercover officer.
- Is that why you're disguised as a man?
- Don't look!
Please, close your eyes
and ears.
[Shaking]
Aren't we supposed to
get a new member today?
That's right.
I've recruited a very good man.
[Is it my turn to go on stage?]
You'll be able to tell how good he is.
Come out, Jong Kook!
[Mr. Capable Kin Jong Kook,
he's heading to the stage.]
It's not a heavy role,
it's going to be very short.
[He was already
picked from the beginning.]
[Laugh]
[The script was written for Kkuk.]
I don't have any funny lines,
but I only have kissing scenes...
[Kkuk's group even practiced
for an action scene.]
[Mr. Capable has been
on stage countless times]
[but it's his first time
performing live comedy.
[Will he be able to do it
without any mistakes?]
He's coming.
[Greetings, I'm the newest
member of Group Ax!]
[I need to start acting now.]
[Good luck, Kkuk!]
You!
By any chance, are you
my first love Hyun Jung?
Jong Kook...
You said I'm your first love!
I'm sorry, I lied to every men
that I met they're my first love.
Hey, who are you?
[Push]
[This scene is...]
[that Jong Kook hit
his chin by mistake.]
[He made a mistake
during the rehearsal.]
[What? Did I just get hit?]
[The timing has to be precise
to be successful.]
[Will Kkuk be able to do it this time?]
Who are you?
[He was able to do it smoothly!]
- Don't do that, Jong Kook!
- Be quiet!
- Please, Jong Kook!
- You be quiet!
Please talk to me!
[If you don't shut your mouth,
I have no choice...]
[Cringe]
[She uses her makeup.]
[Please stop!]
My beard... my beard smudged on you.
- They really did it.
- They did it?
She was going to draw my beard
but I guess she didn't bring
the pen on purpose.
[While Kkuk is performing,
Ha Ha is getting super nervous.]
I hope it quickly passes.
No fun!
No fun at all!
[Blank Ji Hyo doesn't put
her script down until the end.]
You picked the youngest members but...
Do you need to get beat up
to come to your senses?
- Young Goo.
- Yes?
What are you doing?
- You're being unreasonable...
- Are you joking?
[It's time for Kkuk to get beat up.]
[Are you going to beat up?]
Big Brother!
[Complicated]
I'm the Big Brother!
[Takes off]
[Confident]
Do you exercise?
[Big Brother vs. Big Muscle]
Beat him up, Big Brother.
Stop, don't push me.
[Rebellious]
[He hit him!]
Hey, Jong Kook!
[Makdoongie, be patient...]
It's Big Brother!
- Are you kidding?
- I'm sorry, I don't want to get beat up!
[At the moment, he blocked him!]
[As a result of countless practice,
the timing was perfect!]]
[There's a man...
who loves you so much...]
[Please, stop it!]
[Mommy, I want to go home.]
Who are you?
We're the cute and youngest,
Makdoongie!
[Hee-hee, Hee-hee!]
[It started funny and
ended as a romance.]
[Without a mistake, it was perfect!]
You're the best!
- I forgot to bring the pen.
- But, it was funnier.
Was it?
[Return with glory]
[Kkuk's performance got
abreast of other comedians.]
- Unbelievable.
- You supported me so much!
- Did I miss anything?
- Not at all, it was perfect!
You should think about
being a comedian.
Invite me sometimes!
[Nervous, anxious]
Hurry, hurry...
I'm sorry, let's order something.
What do you want to eat?
Jae Hun, Jae Hun,
I want a snake... snake?
[She's too nervous,
she said it wrong.]
[Team PLL:
Hey, Hochan!]
[What?]
Sexy!
[He's dancing
Yoo Jae Suk's sexy dance.]
[Oh, my god...]
- Get down!
- A little kid told you to get down!
[He's smiling, but shaking.]
Please, come forward, Jae Suk!
[The original sexy dance.]
- He'll show you what it is!
- "I'm So Sexy."
[Sexy]
[Provoke]
See?
That's how you do it.
That's awesome.
Where did you do that dance?
- Infinity Challenge.
- Get down.
[Yoo Hyuk made everyone laugh.]
[Hey, Hochan's team leaves the stage.]
What am I going to do, Mommy?
[It's finally Ha Ha and Ji Hyo's team,
"Between Men" 's turn.]
[I'm going crazy!]
Why did they plan this race?
[Will Ha Ha and Ji Hyo get over
their nervousness?]
[Team Running Man:
Between Men with Ha Ha and Ji Hyo]
[Ji Hyo and Jae Hun
are getting ready first.]
[I'm so nervous!]
[Ji Hyo enters.]
Jae Hun, Jae Hun!
[Oh, my god!]
Steak, steak,
buy me a steak!
If you don't buy me a steak,
I'll become a snake.
[It's the first crisis...]
[From the moment she saw the script]
What if I can't do this?
[Mental breakdown]
[She kept practicing since that moment]
[until she made a slip of the tongue.]
Steak, steak...
[I'll show you what
I've been practicing!]
I'll become a snake!
[Sticking her tongue out]
Haha, it's so funny!
[Oh, my eyes!]
[She actually did it!]
Steak? We ate it yesterday.
Let's eat something else.
We didn't eat it today!
I want to eat it!
[Ji Hyo is in her element.]
Then, my wallet will be empty.
[Ji Hyo is the best.]
[Her method acting]
You're so beautiful.
- Can I recommend you a dish?
- What is it?
[They're laughing so hard.]
It's a dish that King of UK
and France frequently eat.
- Then, we'll have that.
- Yes.
A big pork cutlet!
Oh, my friend!
[The whole theater is
moving up and down.]
What was that?
What's wrong with him?
Let's take a seat.
[Ji Hyo did a very good job]
[and it's time that
Ha Ha and Eun Hyung will enter.]
Ha Ha, Ha Ha!
[Ha Ha appears!]
[His perfect acting for
the boyfriend who's sick and tired.]
Haha, it's so funny!
Ha Ha, Ha Ha!
Buy me some wine!
Hurry up!
Eun Hyung, wine is expensive.
Do you think it's waste of money
to buy something for me?
Haha, it's such a waste!
What's wrong with you?
Ha Ha, hurry up and buy me!
Hurry up!
I see...
Order it, then.
Can I have the wine from 1930?
That's too old,
so it's rotten.
Oh, friend!
[A passionate head banging!]
[Dizzy, dizzy]
[He moved too passionate,
his glasses flew away.]
Are you okay?
[Ha Ha's good!]
Let's eat.
It looks delicious.
Why are you nibbling?
Enjoy the food.
I see.
Drink some water, too.
Your stomach will be upset.
Why did you spill it?
It's so filthy.
[I'm really upset!]
What?
Eun Hyung, you...
[Stand up]
Why is your mouth sticking out so much?
You look just like Yoo Jae Suk!
[Gasp]
[Hopefully they don't
appear in our dream.]
Hurry up and wear your glasses.
Haha, he looks so funny.
[Jae Suk's surprise appearance
heats up the atmosphere.]
[Thank you, Jae Suk.]
Why are you nagging so much?
What kind of man acts like
a nagging mother-in-law?
Hello, darling?
You want one of my new born puppies?
How dare you to covet my son?
[The nagging mother-in-law
from "The Hole" revived.]
This isn't edible.
How can you serve something like this?
[Another scary
nagging mother-in-law appears.]
Get this money and
break up with my son!
Oh, friend!
[Dancing with joy]
[Team Running Man,
Between Men is over.]
[It's finally over...]
I did my best at dancing.
Thank you for the hard work.
I feel so much better now.
[It's over anyway!]
You were the best!
I paused for a bit.
[They regret after the show is over.]
- I'm so blank now.
- Me, too.
[Team PLL's last group,
This Day in History]
I have a wish before I die.
- What is it?
- Can you push up my eye glasses?
It keeps slipping down.
[The show is over!]
Thank you for your hard work!
[Team Running Man gathers
after the show.]
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo!
- I made a mistake.
- I couldn't tell.
Jae Suk helped me.
I couldn't think of anything
when I was on stage.
It was harder because I
had to stay awkward.
I couldn't do anything else
because I didn't want to ruin it.
The audience opened their mind,
so they cheered for us.
[The voting begins!]
[Vote for the group
who was the funniest today.]
[The result will be the winner of the
second round of the Laughter War.]
[Who will be the winner
of the second round?]
[In a moment!]
[wait and see something that
no one expected happens at the end!]
[Stay tuned for the secret surprise!]
[The second round of the
Laughter War is over.]
Thank you so much for your
hard work, members of PLL!
[Fellow soldiers of
the Laughter War!]
It's time to declare
the result of the poll.
Last week, Team Running Man
won the first part of the race.
We'll sum up the scores of
the first and second round.
The winners will get a golden mouth.
[A golden mouth
for winning team members!]
Before that
we'll play a special slide show.
[While they wait for the result,
they'll watch a special slide show.]
What is it?
[Curious]
Tae Hwan, it's me.
[Kim Tae Hwan's Mother]
[My Mom?]
You're doing a good job,
so keep up the good work
at being a good comedian,
good son and brother.
Get along well with your colleagues
and be nice to the senior members
and the new members.
You always tell me to stop working
but I'll work as long as I can.
So, you be a good comedian
to make people laugh
and also enjoy yourself.
Cheer up and good luck!
It's Tae Hwan's Mother.
[There's another one!]
Since you were young...
[Hong Yoon Hwa's Mother]
[Oh, dear!]
- You look just like your mother.
- She's beautiful.
you always make me laugh.
Now that you grew up
and become a comedian.
It's a somewhat tough
and capacious path.
I see you can handle all sort of things.
And you can make so many
people happy as well.
Also, you're on TV, and
I can see you everyday.
I'm so thankful to you, my daughter.
I hope you stay healthy all the time.
Some people worry that you're big
and you might not be very healthy.
Some of my friends say that to me
but I know you have to eat well, too.
And you exercise, too.
So, I'm not too worried, Sweetheart.
I'm so proud that she lives her life
with a thankful heart.
[There's another one!]
Ji Hyeon, it's me.
[Lim Ji Hyeon's Mother]
I always call you
my princess Ji Hyeon.
I thought you would stay like a
princess even when you grow up.
But, we became a comedian and
appeared with frown face.
On one hand, I felt upset and hurt.
But, you said you want
to follow your dream
and I want to cheer for you
by your side
and give you a hug
when you have troubles.
I know it'll be hard, but I hope
you do your best with your life.
Thank you, and I love you, Ji Hyeon!
[For some people, they're
just a nameless comedian]
[or an assistant never.]
[For other, they're
just a funny person.]
[But we all are...]
[someone's source of price]
[someone's treasure]
[and someone's precious
son and daughter.]
Ji Hyeon!
[Huh?
This voice sounds like...]
[Ji Hyeon's Mother appears!]
[Yoon Hwa's Mother and Tae
Hwa's Mother appear!]
[What's going on?]
[But that's not all!]
[The family members of PLL
keep entering the theater.]
[Am I dreaming or what?]
Family members!
I got goose bumps!
Everyone's parents came!
[It's the gladness that no one expected,
they laugh and cry at the same time.]
[I'm right here!]
- My dad came, too!
- Amazing!
Look, my mom's there!
[Hug]
[Don't cry, my daughter.]
It's unbelievable!
This is amazing!
[The family member of PLL crews
are gathered at this place.]
Everyone came.
You didn't know they're here, right?
They've watched what
you performed today.
- They were sitting in the audience?
- Yes, they were.
They were watching the show.
How come I didn't know that?
Let's greet them now.
Hong Yoon Hwa's mother
[Hong Seon Hwa, Kim Mi Hyun]
and her sister is here,
but why were you so surprised?
My sister works overseas
and she came home during her break.
But I couldn't see her
because I was busy.
I was going to see her
after work today
but she was going to leave today.
- I felt so sorry.
- What happened?
I was going to leave today
but I delayed my ticket.
They had a seat available for tomorrow.
So, I'll leave in the morning.
You watched her performance today,
how was it?
- She's adorable.
- How about you, Mother?
Every time I see my daughter,
she looks like a general.
Who calls their own
daughter a general?
- Who's father are you?
- I'm Lee Eun Hyung's Father.
[Lee Young Jun]
[Like father, like daughter]
Where are Jae Jun's family?
[Kang Chi Won, Hong Young Ja]
[Kang Jae Jun's parents]
Did you greet each other?
[They met at the dinner today.]
Yes, I greeted him politely.
[Running Man invited all the families.]
[It became a family meeting
for the future bride and groom.]
What do you think?
They've been dating for seven years.
If they love each other,
I'm happy for them.
- Do you think so?
- It's their life.
How about you, Jae Jun's Father?
I agree with him.
Gun Young performed today,
how was it?
[Jung Gook Ja]
Sometimes, I don't see him on TV.
When I call him and asks
if he eats his meals
he says he manages
to stay on pearl barley tea.
[Pearl barley tea?]
What do you mean by that?
[Shake, shake]
Why pearl barley tea?
I'm not a young kid any more,
when I don't have any money...
and Mom asks if I'm doing okay.
I feel bad to say that I have no money.
So, I say I drink pearl barley tea.
- She sends money?
- It's like a code.
She asks if I have
pearl barley tea left.
If I say, I ran out of it...
It's a secret code
between you and Mother.
I'm Jae Hun, Jae Hun, Lee Jae Hun's Dad.
[Lee Eung Yeol]
Do you know his vogue word, too?
- Of course, I do.
- Could you show us?
Haha, it's so funny!
[Haha, he's so good!]
[My dad is the best.]
I'm Oh Bok Nam's Mother.
[Cho Mi Ja]
[Shy]
Bok Nam, Bok Nam!
He looks awkward.
He's "Awkward Bok Nam,"
but he's really nice.
When I first saw the sketch
I thought it could have been better
if it was "Happy Bok Nam."
[My Dad is here, too.]
[Kim Sung Gook, Kim Young Koo's Father]
I hope he stays happy.
Don't just make others laugh
but also make yourself laugh.
[Kim Soon Deok]
I'm Kim Won Koo's Mother.
[He bows deep with so much emotion.]
Good luck, Kim Won Koo!
[Lee Hwa Yeon]
Hello, I'm Ho Chan's Mom.
- Nice to meet you.
- She has a really nice voice.
It was hard to stay seated
and watched the show.
I thought about that it must be tiring
and nervous while they
wait for their turn.
I'll be nice to him.
[Choi Hee Sook]
I'm Kang Hyun's Mom.
His mother is really beautiful.
What happened to you?
It doesn't make sense!
Don't you feel bad to see his role?
No, I'm proud that he can
compete with Yoo Jae Suk.
[My son is the number one to me!]
[Lee Hun Young, Lee Hye Ji's Father]
Did you enjoy the show?
There's a place in Nonsan.
Every Sunday, at 8:40 pm.
I go there with 40 friends of mine.
And we raise the viewer ratings for PLL.
[Just trust me on that one!]
[Every single words he says is witted.]
[Choi Kyung Hee, Kim Jung Hwan's Mom]
Hello.
Jung Hwan's Mom.
[Everyone pushes him forward.]
He's wearing skinny jeans today.
Before Jung Hwan became a comedian,
I never watched comedy.
Did you enjoy the show?
I feel proud that he seems
he's talented in many different fields.
In the future, I hope he'll be a beloved
and acknowledged comedian and emcee.
- Thank you.
- Say something, Jung Hwan.
My mom is being nice to me...
but I became a comedian
later than everyone else.
There are many young comedians
so their parents are young, too.
It's because I picked my job so late...
she looks older than everyone else.
I'm so sorry.
[Freshen up the atmosphere]
Why didn't you put some more makeup?
This is the best I could do.
Thank you so much!
[Thank you for accepting
our invitation!]
We didn't expect it, but we're glad
that you came all the way here
and I'm sure this gives
them really good energy.
Let's give a big round
of applause to cheer!
[The sons and daughters
cheer for their parents]
[and the parents cheer
for the children.]
Is the result in?
The way I see is that the poll
will decide the winner.
[The result of the poll will
decide the final winner!]
Out of 255 votes
the result is...
Team Running Man vs. Team PLL!
[The final winner
of the Laughter War!]
I hope PLL won.
136 vs. 119,
Team Running Man won!
[Team Running Man is the final winner.]
[We won!]
[Congratulations, my son, my daughter!]
They're called as Team Running Man,
but they're actually PLL crews.
We divided team for the game
but it's actually what PLL members did.
Please give another round of
applause for PLL members!
[Thank you for participating,
"People Looking for a Laughter."]
[Team Running Man gets
the winning prize.]
[Gold Mouth]
It's for Ji Hyeon.
Members of "People Looking for a Laugh"
worked with us for two weeks.
Thank you for working so hard!
Please keep watching "People Looking
for a Laugh" and "Running Man."
- Thank you!
[Running Man will do our best
to make you laugh!]
[My colleague's family is my family.
We're all family!]
I always pick someone good,
and your daughter is really good.
Father, please take one.
Thank you!
[We'll cheer for your happiness!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
We're at Gary's place.
[Ha-parrazi on the move!]
[To Gary's house!]
It's me, it's me, it's me!
We will now show
Gary's house to the public!
What is this?
[An unexpected part of Gary's charm?
He knows how to keep a clean house?]
- Wow, this is incredible.
- There's nothing to eat!
Get off, get off, will you?
You should at least
do the dishes for him.
[Kim Kwang Gyu, Jo Jung Chi,
Min Kyung Hoon, Niel, Park Soo Hong]
[Everything about his life
will be exposed!]
Look, there's a green one
and a red one!
[It even gets locked with
an actual lock!]
[What in the world is going on?]
- Want to wash up with me?
- What is this?
[Next week: That Man's House]