[Suspicious taxi drivers are coming!]
[Leave without delay!]
[Attack!
Cab drivers' favorite restaurant!]
[A fatal temptation of taste!]
[The eating show you can't
handle if you're hungry!]
[A secret mission
arrives in real time.]
[Who will be the final
winner of the race?]
[2015, at the end of summer]
[Yeouido, Korea's business
and investment banking district.]
[What will their race be today?]
Hello, everyone!
Hello!
What do I have to do?
[The 'Running Man' members are
scattered all over Yeouido.]
[Abrupt mission card delivery.]
Huh?
Running Man, call taxi.
We take our customers quick and
safely to their destination.
We have to call?
We call the taxi?
Su Ro Su Ro Masuro,
the Gas station Attacker, Mr. Gun
Big Eye Taxi, Navy Violet.
[What's with these nicknames?]
In a few moments, there will be
a call from Running Man
members who are
waiting to ride your taxi.
You will each receive a phone call
while you drive around Yeouido.
You can pick whoever you want
to ride in your taxi with you.
Your team must have three members,
including yourself.
You can take up to two people.
[Make a team of three.
Running Call Taxi, go!]
I know who all these people are!
Euro ours Masuro, is Kim Su Ro.
[Is Euro ours Masuro really Kim Su Ro?]
Hello... yeah, where are you?
[Kkuk called him first.]
I'm at... um...
Yeouinaru Station,
in front of the second exit.
- Please hurry.
- Yes.
I called... and it's just Kim Su Ro.
It's just Su Ro.
Are you on your way to Kim Jong Kook?
Yes.
He called me first, so yes.
[Kim Su Ro]
[One of the best actors with
real acting credentials in Korea]
[He takes over variety shows
after concurring movies.]
[The immortal King of Games.]
[The original King of Games,
super competitive.]
I really hope Big Nose
doesn't call me.
It won't be easy getting to him...
Because I'm here to win.
[Beware! The return of the King of Games!]
Navy Violet seems like... a female?
I don't who Navy Violet is,
but it's a woman for sure.
I'm going to call Navy Violet.
Yes, hello?
- You're Navy Violet, right?
- Yes.
Yes, I'll be on my way!
[Even her voice is
refreshing to hear.]
[Nam Bo Ra]
[With a cute appearance
and lively acting]
[she takes over dramas,
movies, and advertisements!]
[The eldest of 13 siblings,
but the youngest, today.]
- Please come to the 63 building.
- Yes, I'll be on my way.
- Alright.
- Okay.
But... but... but...
where is this 63 building?
There's no need to go elsewhere.
- Oh, okay.
- If you want victory, come this way.
Okay, I'll be right on my way.
Yes, just wait a moment.
- I'm not calling anyone else!
- Yes, of course.
I'll be waiting.
I'm not calling anyone else!
He's not going to call anyone else?
I know that's a lie!
[The identity of the
Gas Station Attacker is]
[Kang Sung Jin]
[A famous scene stealer]
[Every character he has played
stood out.]
[The pillar of Korean movie industry]
[The pronoun of tough,
The real man of the hour]
I'm so lonely because
I don't have any passengers.
[He's somewhat scary...]
Who are you, Big Eyes Taxi?
[The identity of
Big Eyes Taxi driver?]
[Kim Min Gyo]
[The best comic actor]
[You don't know when and how,
but he will make you laugh.]
[He has beautiful deer-like eyes.]
I've been getting a lot of calls
and then suddenly
I've been found out that I'm a guy...
They stopped calling...
[And the last driver.]
Yes, this is call taxi.
I see.
[Who is the mysterious Mr. Gun?]
[Park Gun Hyung]
[From being an
attractive movie actor]
[to a musical super star.]
[Characteristics:
Handsome taxi driver.]
[A war of making up
teams, has started!]
[Su Ro headed straight
towards where Kkuk was.]
[He scouted Mr. Capable first.]
[He spotted Kkuk!]
[Is it really Su Ro?]
[Welcome!]
Brother!
I got Jong Kook!
(He's talking to Ha Ha.)
Hang up!
You're not on our team
so I'm hanging up!
I hung up.
Who should we get?
- Who called you?
- Ha Ha and...
- Ha Ha or Kwang Soo's okay, too.
- Yeah, Kwang Soo's alright.
But Kwang Soo hung up!
Kwang Soo's probably
looking for a female driver.
[So that's how it is...]
Yes, please hurry.
[Beep, beep]
[Is it the taxi I called?]
Get in, get in, hurry!
Hurry and get in!
- Get in?
- We don't have time!
- Get in, hurry!
- Do I have to get in?
In the back, get in the back!
[He even comes out to greet him.]
[I'm glad to see you but...
do I have to get in?]
- I give out free water.
- Wait, hold on.
- Just get in.
- Wait a minute!
But it's okay if we
pick up one more, right?
Okay, okay.
- Wait a minute!
- Let's go, let's go.
[Let's just go!]
We meet again, like this.
You're the Gas Station Attacker!
Don't look any further.
I'm the best guest, today.
Who are the other people?
If I tell you that,
you're going to get off, right?
[It pricked his conscience.]
- The voices were not that...
- Did you call them all?
[He's calling Navy Violet.]
- Yes, yes.
- Hello?
- Oh!
Oh!
Sir, I'll get off here.
Wait a minute!
- Navy Violet!
- Are you getting off?
- I'm... no... getting off!
- Pardon?
- Navy Violet, where are you?
- I'm in front of Yeouido Middle School.
- Yeouido Middle School?
Sorry, but could you drop me
off at Yeouido Middle School?
[I can't hear you.]
Sir!
He's pretending not to hear me!
Please call the police,
I've been kidnapped!
- I will... go...
- That's a rival company!
My driver's mad right now.
They're taking away my customers!
It was my decision!
In front of the 63 building?
- Oh, Ha Ha!
- What's this?
- Valued customer!
- Oh, hello!
Just push him aside, and get in!
Hold on, hold on!
The driver's grabbing
onto my pants!
Navy Violet, why don't you
pick up the phone?
[Who cares what
Navy Violet is, just get in!]
Navy Violet's at the 63 building!
- Navy Violet!
- Sir!
Valued customer!
It's a really busy time,
don't be choosy!
- Wait, but...
- We're busy!
Navy Violet's at the 63 building.
- Well, hello.
- Yes, hi.
[Sung Jin got two people, first.]
[Jae Suk is waiting
for Big Eyes taxi.]
What happened to Big Eyes taxi?
[He's been waiting for 20 minutes.]
Where are you calling?
Hi, Big Eyes!
[Big Eyes'
'find your own customer' service.]
Were you calling someone else?
I was only calling
because you didn't come!
Big Eyes!
Shall we go, then?
[Jae Suk is in!]
[Everyone's slowly
finding their partners.]
I waited a long time.
I can't make a U-turn, here!
[Mr. Gun is lost and is wandering.]
[Looks around]
I usually wander for about
two hours when I come to Yeouido.
[At this rate, he'll be driving
around alone all day.]
[Meanwhile, Su Ro and Kkuk are]
[still discussing about their
teammate recruitment.]
- Ha Ha?
- Yeah.
Ha Ha's not that bad, to be honest.
It's easy to order him around.
But, you won't like his game skills.
That's hard...
I didn't pick up Gary's call.
[He rejects his close
friend just for victory.]
If were talking teamwork,
Ha Ha or Kwang Soo are better.
- We need to find Kwang Soo.
- I bet he's calling a female driver...
[Kwang Soo, we're coming for you.]
I think the Yeouido Middle School
driver will be lonely...
Since there was a call from the 63
building driver first, we'll go there.
[He's calling Navy Violet.]
This driver is friendly.
- Ha Ha!
- Oh, my!
- Where are you?
- Navy Violet!
- We're on our way!
- The driver won't let us out!
We have a female driver!
[Chaos]
- Navy Violet, are you at the 63 building?
- We're on our way!
- Yes, I'm there
- Stay there!
- Ha Ha, get off at 63 building!
- She called my name!
- Navy Violet!
- Just you wait!
[What are you guys doing?]
Please get on my taxi!
[I will get on that taxi
even if it goes to hell!]
Just wait a little!
Please go to 63 building.
I'm coming!
Ha Ha!
[Scream]
63, 63!
[Cute, cute]
[Please come this way!]
Sir... could you hurry...
Should I go there?
[Now's the time!]
Wait!
I am currently... wait!
[Runs away]
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo
both escaped.]
[Sorry, Sung Jin!]
[We need to go to Navy Violet's taxi!]
[Darn it.]
How did I lose both my customers?
[Upset]
What if I end up all alone?
[I won't lose the next customer!]
Who's Navy Violet?
I'm curious.
Oh, it's a taxi!
[Sung Jin's taxi arrived.]
- I'll get on!
- Hold on, don't get in yet!
It was Kang Sung Jin!
- I'm slightly upset.
- Don't be!
I thought you were
at the LBS Annex!
[Main building, Annex,
I don't anything...]
This is my only show, so I'm not...
- Do I get in the back?
- Yes, get in.
- Get in the back.
- Oh, okay.
[He has a child-lock so
Gary can't run away.]
Wait, what are you doing?
There are some who got off.
[It actually doesn't open!]
[Escape if you can!]
Let's go!
Hello?
- Where are you?
- Where are you!
Navy Violet, where are you?
Ha Ha, you pushed me?
Wait, calm down.
Hold on, it's a red light.
- It's Bo Ra!
- Bo Ra, hi!
- Just wait, we're coming!
- Bo Ra, wait!
Kwang Soo, get in too!
- I'm coming!
- Both of you get in!
And then I'm going to throw
one away and get Ji Hyo.
I'm going to get them... and then...
[We're coming!]
Then I'll get Ji Hyo...
Hurry and get in!
We're good to go!
Both of you get in...
Both of you get in.
Don't fight!
Nice to meet you.
[She locks the door right away.]
We waited so long!
How have you been doing?
She's so pretty!
Thank you for riding in my taxi!
Thank you so much!
- She's already so grown...
- She drives now...
I've been accident-free for
two months, don't worry.
- Two months?
- Look at her talk...
She's so adorable.
[A mysterious plan
behind that smile.]
[Will she be able to execute it?]
[Big Nose is waiting
for Big Eyes taxi.]
Where are they...
Who is it?
It's Min Gyo.
You can't let him in so easily!
- Excuse me, sir!
- You can't let him in!
He had a glass of water!
- No one came to you?
- I sent away four people.
- It doesn't open there, it seems.
- It doesn't.
Grasshopper!
Sir!
Min Gyo, it's been a while.
You've gotten handsomer!
Sir, did you just lie?
- You just lied, right?
- No.
- It's the truth.
- You lied.
Grasshopper, you're handsome too.
[He laughs as he says it.]
You're so charming.
Min Gyo!
Get in the other way.
[They accepted him with sympathy.]
We shouldn't have let him in.
[Min Gyo's taxi has
three passengers.]
Yes, let's go.
More than anything,
Jong Kook's with Su Ro.
That's one of the flaws about Su Ro.
He always wants to win!
How's your competitiveness?
I let you in my taxi.
Can't you tell?
I'm pretty much like Buddha.
Is your group complete?
Yes, yes.
Why? Is our team no good, in your opinion?
We're too weak, right?
But it could be a game
using our brains.
Are you confident
using your brain?
Well, that's true...
We have Big Nose and Big Eyes here.
And my mouth protrudes...
Big Eyes, Big Nose,
and a protruding mouth.
If we photoshop it, wow...
If there's hell,
I bet that would be it.
If there's hell
it's got to be Big Eyes, Big Nose
and my mouth protrudes.
It's hell!
[And here]
So, the three of us...
Kwang Soo, what's with your face?
No, no.
I thought you were a ghost!
Why are you making that face?
[Why is Kwang Soo here?]
[Kwang Soo went to say hi to Su Ro.]
- What are you doing?
- Get in!
Just get in for a sec!
Yeah, get in.
Hello!
- Get in!
- Kwang Soo changed.
I didn't know it was you!
But I had a lot of difficulty
getting in Bo Ra's taxi...
[I shouldn't have come...]
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- We'll be a team together.
- Of course.
Let's shout, 'we're one team!'
One, two, three!
We are one team!
[He's about to cry...]
- What's with the camera?
- Ji Hyo!
Kwang Soo
- who's taxi are you in?
- I'm in...
a taxi that I can
never get off of...
I was in here before
I even knew it.
I'm currently
with Front Su Ro, Right Jong Kook.
And the left door doesn't open.
The left door of the
taxi doesn't open...
[Bye, Ji Hyo.]
[At this moment,
two teams are complete.]
[This man is struggling
with the streets of Yeouido.]
Why is the 63 building so far?
[He's having a tour in a call taxi.]
The navigation just randomly
told me to turn right...
Where, where?
Let's go!
[She lost the guys and found the ace!]
Let's go, let's go!
[Gun Hyung, who was lost]
[got Ha Ha who was
thrown away by Bo Ra.]
Wow, this is war!
[An intense chase of anger.]
[Ha Ha, Gun Hyung.
Ji Hyo, Bo Ra]
[Gary, Sung Jin]
[The guys met up to
determine victory.]
Oh, it's Ha Ha!
Hello!
Please open the door!
Get out, get out!
- Get out!
- Wait, wait!
I wasn't going to betray you!
[Pandemonium]
Ji Hyo, I haven't seen
you in 10 years!
[With this, Bo Ra and Ha Ha got in.]
- Gary!
- What?
[Gary also goes in Bo Ra's taxi.]
Hurry, let's go!
[Another team is
complete in a flash.]
[What is this?]
I'm sorry!
I kind of like this team!
[I've been driving until now,
and I finally met you...]
[Eventually, the ones who didn't
get to choose or get chosen.]
[are on one team, automatically.]
It worked out kind of well.
Our team is pretty good.
Do you guys know each other?
- Yeah, of course.
- Good, it works out.
- Our team is actually good!
- So we're good to go?
Yeah, this is our team.
- Ji Hyo...
- You have to do well, today!
I missed you so much.
Ji Hyo, I missed you so much.
We should have met in a movie.
We need to go now.
[How will this team turn out?]
Turn on the navigator.
I turned it on already.
I'm all ready..
[A soccer field
in 'P' University in Seoul.]
We're the Eyes, Nose, and Mouth team.
When our features meet, it's hell.
When his eyes, my nose
and his mouth combines
it's monstrous.
[And here comes the team
that will kill all, today.]
- They're going to win.
- How did they end up together?
Look at their strut.
I don't care about the other teams,
but we have to win them.
- We have to.
- How did they end up together?
Look at their expression,
and their strut.
They're coming down as
if they already won.
Your team is so gloomy!
[They're dissing them
as soon as they see them.]
This is cheating!
You and Jong Kook on
one team is cheating!
How do we judge all
the power in this world?
Your team is useless.
What's with that team?
- Oh, she's so cute!
- She's so cute!
She's cute!
We're the youngest team!
Violet, you're too much!
That team was the un-chosen team.
The ones that got thrown away.
- Oh, really?
- They got thrown away?
You guys were thrown away!
[What are you talking about?]
- We were destined.
- It's fate.
Ji Hyo is so nice.
She accepted all
the poorly people.
Although it seems so, we've been
friends for for 10 years.
When did you last contact each other?
Ten years ago!
- It's been 10 years, that's why.
- They're friends for 10 years.
Has it really been 10 years?
We were both in Ji Hyo's
debut movie together.
And it's been 10 years since then.
Their team combination is great!
And Sung Min...
Why is only your
lower body so white?
- He's more white than Ji Hyo!
- Why is that?
Don't look at the color!
[Exclusive calf muscles]
It's similar to Lee Man Gi's muscles!
(A famous Korean wrestler)
That looks like a cow's tongue!
[This is nothing...]
Are you all happy with your teams?
I am very satisfied.
Min Gyo knows nothing
about cheating...
He's too nice.
He picked the first
two people as his team.
You should have
thrown this one out.
What did you say?
[Just kidding]
- You'll get beat up today!
- You know when you curve?
You should have made a
quick curve and thrown him out!
Did you see Suk Jin just now?
He attacked but blocked
at the same time.
[Multi-tasking with
an attack and block.]
[I need to live, too...]
So you've all arrived in a taxi.
So we have a race involving taxis.
Ally a taxi ride
and your hunger.
A place that you might have
wanted to visit once.
A hearty meal with an affordable price,
it's at taxi driver's restaurant.
[Taxi driver's restaurant race.]
[When the drivers are exhausted
with long hours of driving]
[they recharge their energy
with these delicious meals!]
[An affordable price
and a hearty meal.]
[A place anyone can go, easily!]
[Let's go to a taxi
driver's restaurant!]
There are lots of
delicious places!
Stir-fried spicy pork!
- Bulgogi with rice!
- Pork cutlet!
Those kinds of places
have many taxi drivers
so they can't last if
they don't taste good.
It has to be inexpensive
and tastes good.
That's right!
During every interim mission of
the taxi driver's restaurant race
you will pick one
out of the top 20 dishes
that the taxi drivers
have picked.
Before you head
to the final mission
by the way, there will be a
get-together at the final mission.
[What's up with the
Running Man production crew?]
Before you head
to the final mission
you will catch your own taxi
and get a recommendation
from the driver.
Taxi!
[Please recommend us a dish
from a drivers' restaurant!]
One, two, three!
You must eat the first dish
that the driver picked.
It depends on their taste...
[All their recommendations
are different to their taste.]
The problem is,
after you complete the mission
the dish that you think is the best
and the driver's recommendation
must be the same
in order for you to move on
and go to the final mission.
We might get stuffed today.
If you pick pork cutlet, but the
driver says stir-fried spicy pork
then you have to eat it.
And then you take another cab.
You have to go around until
you eat what you picked.
It's either that, or pork cutlet.
[Short rib soup,
pork back-bone soup]
[Kimchi stew]
[boiled chicken soup,
braised spicy chicken]
[pork cutlet]
[pork and bulgogi with rice]
[bean paste stew,
grilled short rib patties]
[wraps]
[sausage stew]
[bibimbap]
[grilled fish]
[ox blood hangover soup,
ox bone soup]
[Korean sausage and rice soup]
[soft tofu stew]
[spicy meet stew]
[stir-fried pork with rice]
[bean sprout soup with rice.]
I'm already full!
There's nothing bad!
The patties aren't in the top ten!
There's no chance of winning.
And?
- The wraps aren't in top 20.
- I love it...
It doesn't matter if we do!
Kimchi stew is
in the top five for sure!
Pork cutlet as well!
Isn't pork cutlet a little hard?
It's very possible because
it comes with soup on the side.
You have to think
about the nutrients.
[A very elaboated analysis.]
He's one of the people who
pronounces soup the old way.
Soup!
What do you think, Low White?
Who's Low White?
Kang Sung Jin.
[Low White: Lower body is white.]
I would like to give points
to the grilled fish, actually.
You can't give it points!
What points?
I will give it 100 points!
[He gives out 100 points.]
('White' and 'Hundred' sound the same)
I personally think the
wraps are number one...
No, it's risky.
What's wrong with you?
It's not about what you want!
Have some common sense!
[So that's what happens
if you're with them...]
- Wraps?
- It started already.
Why on earth did you think that?
At this rate, you'll be dead meat.
If you say something wrong...
Let's go eat
delicious meals today.
Let's have a tour today.
[Will I be able to
get through, today?]
This game is called bumball.
- It is being played as a sport.
- It actually exists?
You have to have the ball
without holding it
with your hands.
You can only attach it
on your chest and bottom.
In each goal zone,
there are Velcros.
You need to attach the ball
on the Velcro to get a point.
[The young blood
vs. the old friends team.]
[There's so much tension
on the battlefield.]
[The first round is to get the
priority for picking a dish.]
[How the female players do
are the biggest variable.]
[Who will get to choose first?]
Ready, set!
[Game start!]
[As soon as the game starts,
Gun Hyung gets the ball.]
[I want to steal it!]
Give it to me!
Ji Hyo, run!
[You can only attach the ball
with your chest or bum.]
[Blank Ji attaches it on her chest.]
I can't grab it...
How can we take it away?
Take it!
Go near their goal!
[They plan to pass it right
in front of the goal.]
Catch it!
[But Gary steals it quickly.]
[Hug]
[Na-na-na boo boo!]
[What are you doing, Ji Hyo?]
[Love follows the bumball.]
What are you doing?
[The audience stirred as
they hold a romantic pose.]
You can take the ball with your hand.
[Monday Couple ignore the rule
and communicating physically.]
Throw it!
[Are you leaving already?]
[It was a short moment,
but I was happy.]
[Gun Hyung quickly attacks.]
[No mercy!]
Gun Hyung, you shouldn't do that!
Gun Hyung is incredible.
He doesn't care about his image.
[Bo Ra doesn't let it go.]
Do I still have it?
Run, Bo Ra!
[She's heading to her team's goal.]
Steal it and lie down!
[If she lies down,
she'll score an own goal...]
Can I just lie down?
[Team Old Friends goes to finals.]
They won.
Isn't that her own goal?
The ball didn't touch the Velcro!
- Bo Ra was supposed to go over there.
- But they didn't put the ball on it.
[I'm burned out.]
[Team Eyes, Nose, and Mouth
vs. Team Strongest]
We need to do it fast.
Kim Jong Kook, please don't
grab the opponents' clothes.
You're not allowed to do that.
It'll be too painful, because
I need to grab their skin.
What did you say?
I might grab your ribs.
Or the collarbone!
- This is frustrating.
- Wait for me, Jong Kook!
He can actually do it.
It's upsetting but
what can you say?
Ready!
[Which team will go to the finals?]
Start!
[The game starts.]
[It's intense from the beginning.]
[Min Gyo tries stealing the ball.]
[How dare you!]
[Su Ro is blocking two people.]
[What is Kwang Soo doing?]
[He attaches the ball
on his bum slowly.]
What a nice strategy!
Run!
You need to run!
[It's hot.
I don't want to run.]
[While the weak
opponents are struggling]
[Giraffe casually walks to their goal.]
[Team Strongest goes to the finals.]
What was that?
It's is upsetting!
I hurt my pride.
[They're enjoying the victory.]
Sometimes, you need to
enjoy victory, Kwang Soo.
Who made this game?
[I won't forget this humiliation.]
It's not possible to win over them.
[Team Strongest vs. Team Old Ffriends]
It's obvious that team
has an advantage.
[The strongest team's
competitiveness is at its peak.]
What are we going to do?
Ji Hyo, walk casually and grab it.
[The vanguard attack, Blank Ji!]
I think Ji Hyo will
spring out at the ball.
Block Gun Hyung and Min Gyo.
[Mr. Capable sees
through their tactics.]
First grab their arms...
[The dish selection is
riding on this game!]
[Who will be able to
pick the first dish?]
It's a single round match!
[Bumball finals start!]
[Both teams rush as
soon as whistle blows!]
[He carries Blank Ji
and runs to their goal.]
[What kind of strategy is it?]
[Ji Hyo, you will also
score your own goal.]
[Hurry up, Su Ro!]
[A sweet and scary run]
[The strongest acquires the
priority to pick a dish.]
[Total wreck]
[Victory is sweet!]
What's this?
- It's frustrating!
- It is!
[Look!
This is the scream of winners!]
[We're the real strongest.]
[Acquired the priority
to pick the dish]
Send this team for an
international competition.
We can only pick one dish, right?
- Just one.
- And we need to eat until they say it.
Until they say what we pick.
We can end it at once if we pick bulgogi
with rice and the driver says it.
Stir-pork?
That might not be it.
Think carefully,
it could be something else.
I think it's some kind of soup.
Something ordinary like kimchi stew
or soy bean paste soup.
Seriously...
When are you going to pick your dish?
If you're not going to pick one,
the next team will pick it first.
You can eat the stew
if you think that's it.
I don't think it's kimchi stew or
bean paste soup.
Five, four, three!
- Two!
- Wait a moment!
[It's time to decide!]
- Bulgogi with rice?
- Wait a moment!
Bulgogi with rice?
[The dish taxi drivers would recommend]
[What will be the
strongest team's choice?]
Ox bone soup!
[What?]
[Ox bone soup?]
[What have you done?]
[He said it without
discussing it with his team.]
- No, the ox bone soup is...
- It's over.
We need to say it all together!
Did you film the moment
my jaw dislocated?
My jaw is dislocated.
- Look at my jaw!
- I mean...
You should have picked something else!
[A taxi driver has to
recommend ox bone soup.]
People eat ox bone soup
at specialized restaurants!
They will pick it for sure!
Trust me!
[He's driving me crazy.]
It was between Bulgogi
or Stir-fried pork.
All of a sudden, he said ox bone soup!
Bulgogi with rice!
It wasn't ranked number one?
But bulgogi with rice
wasn't ranked number one.
Sausage stew...
One, two, three!
Stir-fried pork!
What did you pick?
[Team Young Bloods gets to choose.]
You know, taxi drivers'
restaurant serve
pork cutlet with a big green pepper.
- You dip the pepper in the sauce.
- That's right!
- How about curried rice?
- Kimchi stew is okay, too.
- Curry.
- Vongole spaghetti!
[Absurd]
You know, drivers love
vongole spaghetti.
No, they like curry with naan.
How about tom yum soup?
Don't do it to us.
- You should have asked our opinions.
- 'Buddha Jumps Over the Wall!'
Kimchi stew or pork cutlet...
Di you want to pick kimchi stew?
I recommend soy bean.
[What should I pick?]
Stop, everyone.
- You have to decide now.
- Let's just pick pork cutlet.
One, two, three!
- Pork cutlet!
- Pork cutlet?
It's a popular dish.
It's better than ox bone soup.
What's wrong with ox bone soup?
[Taxi drivers love ox bone soup.]
Who would eat ox bone soup
in the middle of summer?
Tons of restaurants
only make ox bone soup.
[What result will
Kwang Soo's choice bring?]
[The strongest: Ox bone soup]
[Old friends: Bulgogi with rice]
[The eyes, nose, and mouth:
Stir-fried pork]
[Young blood: Pork cutlet]
[We don't know
what the result is yet!]
Please, recommend us a dish
from a drivers' restaurant!
[They have to get a taxi in the street]
[And the dish has to be
the same as they picked.]
[You can taste it right now!]
[Special dishes of taxi driver's
favorite restaurant are coming!]
[And...]
[What's the secret of
the final mission site?]
[They have to get a recommendation
for the dish they've picked]
[and go to the final site!]
I think older people like ox bone soup.
Nowadays, all the older drivers
eat bulgogi with rice.
Let's just get on a taxi and see!
It's a perfect weather
for ox bone soup.
Just pretend we're exhausted.
Our team color is same
as radish kimchi.
Radish kimchi is a perfect
side dish for ox bone soup!
No, that's the color of the
blood you'll spill later.
I hope they like stir-fried pork.
It doesn't matter if it's spicy or not.
If we can make it less
than three or four times...
We're actually curious about
other food in the restaurant, too.
We are!
And the food there are really good!
I'm curious what they like.
Honestly, I think Pork bulgogi
is their favorite.
- You think so, too?
- Yes.
Wow, how can you be so lucky?
Maybe it is a fate
that you formed a team.
[You picked bulgogi
when you won second place!]
How is it possible
it becomes your dish
It's the favorite dish at taxi drivers'
restaurant near my house, too.
It's pork cutlet in my neighbor.
Come to think of it, I think
pork cutlet is also popular.
That's not important at all.
There's a team that
picked ox bone soup.
It's like all-you-can-eat for them!
I'm sure they will throw up in the end.
I think only one member would throw up.
[Frightening]
Taxi!
I'm getting nervous!
We need to sit at the backseat.
- Let me get in first.
- Okay.
It's a good spot to get beat up.
- Hello.
[Confused]
Excuse us, we're filming for a show.
We'll ask you a question.
Please, recommend us...
Sir...
Please recommend us a dish
from a drivers' restaurant!
[If the driver says ox bone soup,
they'll complete the mission.]
Spicy stir-fried pork.
[Spicy stir-fried pork]
It's the best.
Yes, please drive us there.
See? It's either
stir-fried pork or bulgogi.
[Team Strongest fails
their first attempt.]
Please go to the restaurant you like.
You need to go Shinjung-dong.
Sure, let's go.
There's a good restaurant there.
You're going to eat it anyway.
Do you eat stir-fried pork often?
I used to eat a lot.
What do you usually eat now?
I like ox bone soup near here.
[He's the ox bone soup lover!]
Oh, no!
[Why did you tell us the other dish?]
[Team Eyes, Nose, Mouth gets a taxi.]
- Can we get in?
- Yes, you can.
Hurry up!
- Let's go!
- Thank you for waiting.
I'm nervous!
What if we succeed now?
Please tell us after
we count to three!
Please recommend us a dish
from a drivers' restaurant!
One, two, three!
[A well-known dish
of drivers' restaurant]
Pork bulgogi with rice!
I think Ji Hyo's team will win.
Please, go to a restaurant near here.
- Is it okay if I drive to Hwagok-dong?
- Yes.
Sir, pork bulgogi...
They're in the taxi.
I wonder what the driver said.
- What are you going to eat?
- Pork bulgogi!
[That's our dish!]
If you took this taxi,
you've already won!
We should have gotten the taxi.
There's a taxi.
It's coming!
Ask him, Ji Hyo.
Hello, Sir.
We're going to go to eat now.
Can you please recommend us a dish
from a drivers' restaurant?
The dish you usually eat.
One, two, three!
[The flower of drivers' restaurant,
bulgogi with rice!]
[Please, tell us that's what you like.]
Grilled pork belly!
[It's pork belly party!]
Wow, it's unexpected.
I couldn't imagine.
Let's go.
[Laugh]
Wow, that's amazing.
We need to eat three servings
of pork belly this early.
Hello, Sir.
[Team Young Bloods follows the next!]
Did you have lunch?
I have a question.
Can you recommend us a dish
from a drivers' restaurant?
One, two, three!
[A new dark horse
of drivers' restaurant!]
[Please, give us the name!]
Kimchi stew.
[We gave up on kimchi stew
but picked pork cutlet...]
Where is a good restaurant for that?
Please, take us to
your favorite restaurant.
Let's go to the restaurant
in Yeonnam-dong.
Thank you, Sir.
How about pork cutlet
on a day like this?
Pork cutlet is for children.
[Did we pick a children's dish?]
Wow, it's pretty close.
It looks like it's a good restaurant.
- Pork bulgogi is written on the window.
- That's like a main dish.
Stir-fried pork.
Hello!
[We're here to try stir-fried pork.]
We heard stir-fried pork
is good here.
Can I get three
stir-fried pork, please?
- Just three stir-fried pork?
- Yes.
I don't see ox bone soup on the menu.
We don't have it here.
Not many people eat ox bone soup
at drivers' restaurant, right?
No, they don't ask for it.
[They knew it, but
it's harsh to hear it.]
Aren't there drivers' restaurants
with good ox bone soup?
Why did you pick ox bone soup?
I just wanted to eat it so much.
[Here comes stir-fried pork]
If I we go out to eat,
I'll buy you ox bone soup from now on.
Me, too.
I'll buy you ox bone soup.
I love ox bone soup though.
It looks good!
It does look good!
[What a delicious looking dish!]
This much rice...
We serve rice in a stone pot.
[They have to finish the meal
without leaving.]
This much rice?
I didn't know they give us
rice in a stone pot.
I've never seen this much rice
in a stone pot.
[They don't know how many times
they need to eat...]
I've always thought, there are
too little rice in stone pot.
We give you a lot of rice.
We're at the right place!
I scooped a lot, but
it's still the same.
You gave me too much.
It looks so good
and smells great!
Thank you for the food!
[Kkuk takes a bite, too.]
It's really good!
You're eating with lettuce?
[But it's good...]
[The savory flavor!]
[They've forgot about ox bone soup...]
[Team Eyes, Nose, Mouth
arrives in Hwagok-dong.]
- Thank you!
- Let's go!
We're here.
Bulgogi with rice.
It was hard to find this restaurant.
Pork bulgogi with rice.
Can I have three pork bulgogi
with rice, please?
[They're expecting to taste it.]
Pork bulgogi, please.
Dishes at drivers'
restaurants are good.
They're really good.
Look at the menu.
They have stir-fried pork, too.
They do have it.
What's the most popular dish
among taxi cab drivers?
It's bulgogi with rice.
- What about stir-fried pork?
- No, bulgogi with rice is more popular.
They like it the best.
I think stir-fried
pork are popular, too.
No, bulgogi with rice is more popular.
She said it's the most popular
Why can't it be stir-fried pork?
No, bulgogi with rice is more popular.
- I see.
- Is she all she talks about?
I like her voice.
Look at this.
Let's eat with lettuce.
This is perfect!
[Bulgogi with rice is love!]
It's marinated very well.
It's really good!
It's a little sweet and...
I think you prepare a lot of this.
But, the rice...
is too much!
Do you want us to give you two?
No, it's fine.
[At drivers' restaurants, rice means
stone pot cooked rice.]
Didn't we decide to eat a little?
[What will be the result of
the binge eating?]
[Team Young Bloods arrives
in Yeonnam-dong for kimchi stew.]
[Ta-da!]
It looks so good!
Let's eat this as an appetizer.
Then we'll go eat pork cutlet.
I can't wait to taste it.
I was going to go on
a diet from today.
- It's okay to eat it for lunch.
- It's good!
That's not how you eat stew.
To enjoy the stew like drivers
you need to learn how.
[Eat it like an old man!]
This is it!
No, this is it.
Put the meat on top of rice.
Wow, that looks good!
You can usually see this
on TV on Sundays.
[The reaction of Sunday morning]
You need to close your eyes, too.
I never imagined someone would
recommend pork belly for lunch!
- I almost fainted.
- Our first dish is pork belly.
I think he wanted to
let us enjoy something delicious.
I don't think we can finish it soon.
[Piles of pork belly slices]
Let's eat it quickly.
- Wow, it's good!
- Is it good?
It is good.
[The unlucky team that picked
bulgogi rice but eat pork belly.]
[Will they be able to
succeed next time?]
It's delicious!
It is really delicious!
They've finished everything.
I think I can have another meal.
For lunch, stir-fried meat is the best!
- Did you get a message?
- Yes.
What is it?
The team in last place of
'The Taxi Drivers' Restaurant Race'
will have to pay the social dinner
for all the staffs.
You have to pay out of your pocket.
['S' restaurant in Hannam-dong]
[Where there's social dinner,
there are people...]
[This place becomes a holy spot
with more and more staffs.]
[The last team will have to pay
for the 200 staffs' dinner!]
Wow, it's unbelievable!
The last team have to
pay for social dinner!
The social dinner with
all the Running Man staffers
I might have to sell off my house!
We don't have time to drink water!
[The unexpected always happens.]
- Why don't you eat some now?
- We're saving up.
Can we get a tax receipt for that?
Anyway, we need to hurry up.
[The social dinner won't be cheap...]
[They've received the message, too.]
- Let's hurry up.
- The last team?
Hurry up and eat!
We're not going to be the last.
There's ox bone soup!
Kwang Soo will pay for
everyone in a long while.
[Don't give up yet!]
[They give them
two bottles of soda for free.]
[Why are they so friendly
at a time like this?]
[He opens them in case
they don't drink them.]
Just one...
He opened both.
[He's adding salt to the wound.]
I'll give you some watermelon.
No, we're really fine!
We need to hurry up and go.
[Is that so?]
[She won't listen.]
No, it's really fine.
We're fine.
Please tell her not to do it.
We really don't need it.
[What can we do?]
Let's just eat it.
Thank you so much.
[Show your heart with watermelon.]
Wow, it's cool!
[Let's go to get a taxi!]
Thank you so much!
It was really good!
[Team Young Bloods filled their
bellies with Kimchi stew]
[Will they eat pork cutlet next?]
Hello!
You're working hard.
Sir!
Would you please hold my hand?
[I hope you can feel
the pork cutlet spirit...]
Sir, if you were to pick
a taxi driver's dish
what would you recommend?
- For young people like us...
- The dish is?
One, two, three!
[A dish that young people
like us would enjoy.]
[The crispy and crunchy dish...]
Stir-fried pork!
[Youngsters enjoy
stir-friend pork!]
Sir, did you mean the
pork bulgogi with rice?
- Yes!
- Kimchi stew...
Pork bulgogi with rice...
I could eat up to this.
It'll be good.
- We could eat...
- But!
I don't think anyone would
recommend pork cutlet!
How are we going to pay
for the social dinner?
If we picked Kimchi stew,
it would have been better...
I thought I could eat
least two meals...
But after the watermelon, I'm done!
I could have ate two meals!
I'm done eating for the day...
And we'll conclude it with
a bowl of ox bone soup...
If we succeed,
I'd gratefully eat that...
It's here!
I have a feeling it's ox bone soup!
[Their second try for ox bone soup]
[and the results?]
I really enjoyed
that stir-fried pork!
Sir, we will be giving you a question
so all you have to do is answer us.
One, two, three!
Please recommend us
a taxi driver's dish!
[After eating stir-friend pork, there's
only one thing that comes to mind!]
[An excellent dish known
for its white color.]
Squid bulgogi!
Squid bulgogi, it is!
- Would you know where it is?
- Okay, please take us there!
Okay, thank you!
Yes, we will head there.
Sir, do you think anyone
would say ox bone soup?
It's a little hard...
[Flustered, flustered]
It's usually stir-fried pork
or bulgogi with rice, right?
Yes!
[The top two are bulgogi with
rice and stir-fried pork.]
If you get 10 taxi drivers and
ask them what they had today
no one will say ox bone soup.
You are so right!
Don't say that...
We'll see...
If you want to find a driver
who eats ox bone soup
- go to Shingil-dong.
- Shingil-dong?
Is Shingil-dong better?
There's famous ox bone
soup restaurant there.
Many taxi drivers go there.
If anything...
we'll get a call taxi...
And we'll ask them for a
driver who likes ox bone soup.
- A call taxi?
- That's a good idea.
- If nothing works out.
- Yeah, yeah.
It's here.
Oh, it's here?
Across the street?
They have spicy pork
with rice here, as well!
[They arrived at the
squid bulgogi restaurant.]
Spicy pork with rice...
- Hello!
Could we get three
squid bulgogi?
[Spicy pork with rice]
Sir!
Have you, by any chance
had ox bone soup at
a taxi driver's restaurant?
- Yes!
- You've had it before?
- Ox bone soup?
- Yes.
Where?
- Which area?
- Shingil-dong!
That's the place our
driver recommended!
If we tell the driver Shingil-dong,
there's a possibility.
[Forget about ox bone soup for now]
[and enjoy your squid bulgogi!]
- What singer?
- It is a singer!
He's not a singer!
[What's this?]
Kim Jong Kook,
you're not a singer right?
Ma'am!
I am a singer!
[I've been a singer for 20 years.]
You know, 'One man', or 'Lovely'?
Wow, everything of you
from head to toe is lovable!
You don't know it?
[I'm so embarrassed...]
- You know it, right?
- She had a huge argument over there.
'No, he's a singer.'
'No, he's an athlete.'
I know him, though.
I know Kim Suro, well.
I seem him on TV all the time.
Well Giraffe is on TV a lot, too!
[He's not an actor,
nor a model but a giraffe.]
Thank you.
I found out today
that you're a singer!
This is year is my
20th anniversary!
As a singer!
[Embarrassed]
Long time ago, Kim Bo Sung came...
but he was really handsome,
like a celebrity!
['Kim Bo Sung looked
like a celebrity.']
[Then what about us...]
What about us?
It's because we
were running around!
Your faces are so tanned!
It's because my
makeup's been erased!
Kim Bo Sung wore a trench coat!
- He was super cool!
- I have a trench coat, too!
Although we have name tags on, now...
If we wore sunglasses,
we would look cool!
I wear a trench coat
when I go to bed!
Thank you, thank you!
[They finished eating
grilled pork belly.]
Taxi, taxi, taxi!
Please recommend us a dish!
[Will they be able to
hear 'bulgogi with rice'?]
Out of all the dishes
could you recommend
something you eat often?
One, two, three!
[You know,
the dish taxi drivers love...]
Pork bulgogi with rice.
[We finally got it!]
[They succeeded in two tries!]
Oh my god, thank you so much!
You're the best!
- You're the best!
- In which area?
- Banghwa-dong.
- Banghwa-dong?
[The driver suggested
Banghwa-dong.]
So, the other teams...
what did they...
Some teams went
to eat pork cutlet
- another went for ox bone soup.
- That's pretty rare.
They have the wrong idea.
You know Lee Kwang Soo?
He went to eat that.
Yeah, he would pick it...
- That was good.
- A taxi!
Isn't there one over there?
The front one or the back?
The back!
There's someone in there.
- Is it empty?
- Could we get a ride?
Sir!
Are you leaving now?
[Will they be able to
hear stir-fried pork?]
Sir!
We will give you a question,
so you just have to answer.
Please give us an answer on three.
Please recommend us
a taxi driver's dish!
One, two, three!
[Please say stir-fried pork]
[instead of bulgogi with rice.]
Stir-fried pork!
[They got stir-fried pork!]
[The succeeded in two tries!]
[Thrilled]
I love you!
[They're on their way
to eat stir-fried pork.]
Thank you, thank you.
I can eat up to stir-fried pork.
We're a great team!
Today is our day!
- Should we ride that?
- Which one?
It's not an empty taxi.
I have a good feeling
about this one!
- This car?
- I have a good feeling!
I have a good feeling!
- Hello.
- Sir, hello!
Hello!
[We need a plan...]
Sir, please listen to us carefully.
We're headed to ride
the Namsan cable car.
- Where?
- Namsan.
What is a dish that you
would recommend to us
- in Namsan?
- One, two, three!
[The crispy dish famous in Namsan...]
One, two, three!
Pork cutlet!
[They got pork cutlet!]
Please depart!
Yeah!
You're the best!
[They succeeded in three tries!]
[They finished
their bulgogi and rice.]
Wow, thank you for the coffee!
[Touched, touched]
You saw just now, right?
Taxi driver restaurants are awesome.
I want to come here with my family.
It came, it came!
[The location of the social dinner!]
'S' Garden
Hannam-dong.
If it's a garden,
there's going to be meat.
I'm so full already!
I'm stuffed!
Let's just go anyway.
- It's rush hour!
- Yeah, so we have to go.
It's going to take an hour, right?
[They've finished their dish.]
I can't eat any more.
[But they've finished all of it.]
You have a message.
What is it?
Read it for me.
The restaurant for the social
dinner is 'S' restaurant
in Hannam-dong, Yongsan-go...
That's the address.
- Hannam-dong?
- We can just go now.
We're too full, so we won't
be able to eat with them.
I want to eat since
the last team will pay.
[Big-nosed brother wants to
eat everything that's free.]
[The strongest team
finished pork bulgogi.]
Let's get the taxi.
[Their fourth taxi]
Can you tell us a dish?
When you come to Shingil-dong
there are many restaurants
in other places
but in Shingil-dong, what's the dish
you want to recommend?
Because we're already in Shingil-dong.
You can tell us.
- Can you think of anything?
- Maybe with some soup.
[The famous dish in Shingil-dong]
[Will he say ox bone soup?]
[Please...]
Chicken soup with ginseng...
[Chicken soup with ginseng?]
[Did I say something wrong?]
[Disappointed]
- Where's the ox bone soup restaurant?
- It's over that side.
He answered instantly.
[They've gone to everywhere
except the right one.]
Thank you.
[They arrived at the restaurant
for chicken soup.]
[They're not even upset any longer.]
But this was the most
similar dish of all.
Yes, it's soup.
It might taste the same
if you eat it with your eyes closed.
Let's go to the main restaurant.
They have two building.
This is a really mean game.
If this was our first dish...
They have three restaurants.
This must be very famous.
And they don't have any seats.
Can we take out?
- Yes, you can.
- Then we'll take it.
We can't even eat it
in the restaurant.
Let's just eat it on the street.
This is a good spot.
Let's just sit here and eat.
Wow, the smell of pork cutlet!
[How does the pork cutlet taste?]
Wow, it's crunchy!
It's good!
[The taste is like a miracle.]
I actually like it very much.
I wonder if they're
eating ox bone soup.
I worry about them.
[Team Young Bloods is relaxed.]
[The strongest team looks pathetic.]
- Let's eat.
- Open it.
The broth...
it's different from other restaurant.
Should we just taste the broth?
[The broth looks very rich.]
Wow!
It's really good!
Do you want to eat
some chicken breast?
Just the chicken breast.
Do you want to shut up
or get beat up?
I would shut up.
Hurry up and eat, Kwang Soo.
Ha Ha!
Are pork-cutlet good?
How about your dish?
You haven't eaten it?
No, we're about to go.
Take it easy.
- We're in Gapyung.
- What?
Ga..pyung?
It's where Bae Yeon Jung's
restaurant is.
Yes, it's right next door.
There's traffic, take your time.
I see, Su Ro.
We're about to leave from Gapyung.
Okay, I see.
I see, bye!
That's really funny!
Gapyung is too far.
I need to make them relieved.
But the game isn't over yet!
[Giraffe finished it all by himself.]
- You're done?
- Let's go.
He finished it.
We're getting a message.
Yes, we got it.
Hannam-dong in Yongsan-go!
It's really close from here.
Isn't it right next to this place?
We could walk there, right?
Wow, how could it be Hannam-dong?
Wow, this team is very lucky!
[Will they be able to
laugh until the end?]
This is unbelievable!
[At the restaurant for the social dinner]
[There are more than 150 staffers]
[and they're eating pork belly.]
[The meat is cooking and
the atmosphere is good.]
[Someone arrived?]
Enjoy your meal!
[The eyes, nose, and
mouth team arrive.]
Help yourselves!
[What's that?]
[The applause from 150 people...]
[It feels weird...]
Eat a lot.
We're not the last, aren't we?
You are... not the last.
Oh, no, Su Ro!
[They start worrying about others.]
[Huh? What's the matter?]
[Team Old Friends arrived
first and they waited.]
What was your dish?
It was pork bulgogi with rice.
That's really popular!
You can either go home or eat here.
I understand.
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
Enjoy your meal!
[Only the last two teams are left!]
There's a taxi.
[Giraffe wants to run to the taxi.]
Wait, let's think of a plan.
What are you going to ask?
[Su Ro stopped out of surprise!]
[Why?]
[What did he see?]
[Oh, my god!]
[It's an ox bone soup restaurant!]
[It's in front of us!]
[He bravely chose ox bone soup,
but the reality was...]
[favorable for stir-fried pork,
fried squid, pork bulgogi with rice]
[and chicken soup with ginseng.]
[Eat, eat and eat...]
[They have tasted food and humiliation.]
[It was such a long day.]
Point the restaurant.
If the cab driver recommend
the ox bone soup...
Just point at the restaurant.
Sir!
Excuse us!
Please recommend us a dish.
[Will it be ox bone soup or not?]
Their ox bone soup is good.
[Ox bone soup!]
He said it's good.
We didn't even point it.
We did nothing to make him say it.
He actually said it right away.
It's real!
[Okay, we'll let it pass.]
What did I say?
What did I tell you?
Ox bone soup is the
drivers' favorite dish!
Let's sit at the corner.
[Black pepper spread
like stars on the milky way.]
I really wanted to eat it.
Our mission for the game was
to get a recommendation
from a taxi cab driver.
What do you think the
most popular dish is?
It's ox bone soup.
[Giraffe meets his soulmate.]
They keep saying they
don't have ox bone soup.
I'm a fan of yours.
[Displeased]
We should have met him earlier.
It's really good!
It was a nice meal.
- What place do you think you will win?
- The first place.
I don't think we're the second even.
[Team Young Bloods
is still relaxed.]
I'm done.
Let's go.
[Their mission that looked impossible
to complete was accomplished!]
I've got a message.
It's the address of the restaurant.
It's in Hannam-dong!
Let's go.
Hurry up!
[Team Strongest leaves in a hurry.]
Now I see.
Ox bone soup wasn't that popular...
Say it correctly.
It's not that.
It's hard to find it
at drivers' restaurant.
I admit it.
It was my bad.
[The young blood vs. the strongest]
[Who will end up in last place?]
[The last mission site]
['S' restaurant in Hannam-dong]
Are we the last?
[Anxious]
Let's go.
We don't know the result yet.
Maybe there's another team
[Another taxi arrives.]
- It's on the third floor.
- Right here?
We might be the last.
Are we the last?
No way!
[Team Young Bloods
was relaxed for the whole time.]
What's going on?
[The strongest team
who was pressed for time]
Are we the last?
[A round of applause
for the young blood team...]
[No way...]
[What's the meaning of the applause?]
We place the last?
Are we the last?
You are, out of four teams,
[No way...]
[we're the last team?]
Our of four teams
you're not last place.
[Not last place]
You can go home now.
Enjoy your meal!
[Then it means...]
Are we the last?
- Where is everyone?
- They've finished eating.
[Absurd]
The people who finished
eating went home
They ate and left?
Since it was social dinner,
they ate and left.
We've had a social dinner all together.
Thank you.
Thank Kwang Soo.
- We're really the last team?
- Yes, you arrived here the last.
Congratulations, Kwang Soo!
As the rule, one of you
will pay for the dinner.
Take your name tag on your back
- and put it on the rullet.
- It's not decided yet!
I'm going to pay with
your credit card anyway.
You're not supposed to decide that!
Wow, you've worked so hard!
[They've waited to see
the funny scene.]
When did you arrive?
The ox bone soup was...
- it was a bad mistake.
- Did you eat a lot of dish?
Yes, we did eat a lot.
We'll film until the moment
the person pays.
Please, check the name
on the card, too.
Do you see on the other side?
There are people eating still.
Stop eating so much!
We'll rotate the rullet, then.
Please, rotate it, Bo Ra.
Rotate it, Bora!
[Worried]
When it's decided, we'll leave.
One, two, three!
Rotate!
[Please, don't stop at my name...]
[They're nervous, too.]
[The rullet gets slow.]
[Kkuk?]
[Kwang Soo?]
[Or Su Ro?]
[Who will pay for the dinner?]
It's Jong Kook!
[Giraffe runs out of joy!]
[A gloomy foreboding
always come true.]
[It's not me!]
Jong Kook looks really upset.
[He pretends it's okay,
but he's heated up.]
[As they promised,
they leave the site.]
You are the main player for this race!
[Don't be sad, we love you! (meats)]
- Bye!
- See you tomorrow!
Okay, see you.
Ah... this drives me nuts.
Let's go to pay.
[It's time to pay.]
What are you doing here?
Why don't you sign on the invoice?
Sign on the receipt!
[Thank you, Kwang Soo!]
How much it is?
[Even Mr. Capable
is scared of the receipt.]
[She's calculating.]
Don't they give a discount like 1,000 won?
That much, I can handle it.
[Minus 1,000 won]
[The total amount is... jaw-dropping!]
She gave me 1,000 won discount.
That's like 0.1 percent discount.
Thank you, Jong Kook.
You can go home.
You'll be able to make
a lot more than this.
Subtitles by DramaFever
We'll have 'Beautiful Youth Race.'
We need to play youth games
with young people.
Attention!
Attacking university campuses!
[The youth responded to
the shout of Running Man!]
[The message that cheer the youth!]
[Next week, Running Man]
[Beautiful Youth Race]