[You've invited the main PD.]
[What's up?]
[I have something to tell you...]
[Yes?]
[I'm telling you this without
letting my parents know.]
[Wait, then are you...]
[Yes, you're right.]
[I have a wish.]
[Could you come over to my place?]
[Come over to my place.]
[One day...]
[a little boy sent a message
to the production crew.]
[The house that boy lives in]
[shows that he's a fan of 'Running Man.']
[Come Over To My Place.]
[A desperate struggle to
find the fan's house.]
[A cold-blooded fight for the fan!]
[Team Running Man]
[Team 2PM]
[Baek Jin Hee]
Who is it?
[A touching race]
Maybe it's a little girl!
[For the one person.]
Which floor do they live on?
[The fan's identity that
surprised everyone!]
[Come Over To My Place.]
[A red carpet runway gives us a hint
about the celebs coming today.]
Flying is so much fun, as usual.
It's a nice place.
Flying from my house to the
filming set is always nice.
Oh welcome, guys.
Why are there so many of
you piled into one helicopter?
Just buy your own.
[Just then!]
[Another star just landed!]
[They have arrived!]
It's Chansung!
[Number one beast idol, Chansung.]
[Asia's dancing machine, Woo Young.]
[Reborn into a
singer-songwriter, Jun K.]
[Deadly smile, Junho.]
Jun K!
[Sweet Thailand Prince, Nichkhun.]
[The all-round cooking idol, Taecyeon.]
[All of 2PM came!]
[Hallyu stars who came after
their concert overseas.]
[They have become quite acquainted
with the 'Running Man' members.]
Our 2PM!
[The runway seems full and complete.]
Jong Kook, you might have to
use some strength today.
[Full level workout presence.]
We need to use our strength today.
Did you come for Jong Kook?
[We'll show you today.]
It's going to be
six times harder today.
It's Ji Hyo!
Oh, Song Ji Hyo!
[Welcome, Ji Hyo!]
[She's dashing on the
runway in a dress.]
[She runs towards 2PM.]
Hi Nichkhun!
Hi, hi, hi!
[Today, Blank Ji is teaming up with 2PM.]
Why did you put on so much perfume!
[Slightly self-conscious]
Is it the guest's perfume?
[Their hearts are pounding.]
She's over there!
[Faraway... another female passenger!]
- Be careful!
- Kwang Soo's already fallen for her.
Wow, Baek Jin Hee!
Baek Jin Hee!
[Really?]
[Pure and innocent, Baek Jin Hee.]
[Attacks a man's heart with her
lovely charm and innocent looks.]
[A lovely girl that attracts
the maternal instinct.]
[She's ready to show off
her charms on 'Running Man.']
[Jin Hee is on the team with
the 'Running Man' regulars today.]
- What's wrong with you guys?
- What, what?
Why are you looking over there?
- No, not at all.
- Do you know anyone here?
Kwang Soo.
- We filmed an ad a while back.
- Yeah, we did.
- When was it?
- Three years ago.
Three years ago?
You might as well be strangers.
Three years ago is a long time!
- Do you contact him, personally?
- No, I don't.
- No, no.
- Why are you denying so much?
Don't send him any texts either,
he'll misunderstand.
[Don't worry, I won't.]
Today, we will explain
the rules differently.
We're connected onto an SNS chat with
the fan that requested a fan meeting.
It was real.
Do I press 'Running Man' fan?
From now on, the fan will send you
the rules, through the messenger.
Today's concept is finding the fan.
You can't ask about the
name, age, gender, or
personal details because
they can become hints.
Oh, they said 'hi Running Man.'
Oh, it's actually live!
- Oh is it?
- Maybe they're young.
They're using slang.
Where's the emoticon?
[Somewhat stiff]
I need to send an emoticon!
- You're so slow!
- Give it to me!
I can't see.
Who is it?
Ask them if they have a boyfriend.
Today's race is
'Come Over To My Place.'
Oh, we have to find their house?
[What kind of a person is our fan?]
[He always watched over 'Running Man.']
[You can find my house, right?]
I'll give you a hint
if you win the game.
Just tell them to send the
address on the navigation!
Ask them what game we have to play.
If you win the game,
I'll give you a hint.
Mister PD will tell
you the exact rules.
Mister?
They're probably young!
Ask them who they like the most?
I accidentally typed 'Girls Generation'
instead of 'are you a girl?'
I can't really see...
- Who do you like the most?
- Girls Generation!
He likes Mr. Yoo Jae Suk
and Mr. Big Nose!
He's probably old.
He's for sure an old man!
[See you later.]
[Fan left the chat.]
They left!
It's because you said he wasn't a kid!
Are they here?
They might be hiding!
I re-invited them.
[Why did you leave?]
He's older than me!
Junho invited him as soon as they left!
Junho's a little obsessive.
I'm so curious, but they won't tell me!
He's obsessive.
Today is the 'come over to my
place' race, like the fan said.
It's the 'come over to my place' race.
We will give you a hint
about the fan's house
every time you finish
the interim mission.
We will give a detailed
hint to the winning team
and a less detailed hint
to the losing team.
You will have to find the fan,
and give them a hug
to win the final mission.
[If it's for the fan]
[we must run, run, and run some more!]
[The identity that shocked everyone!]
[Team Ji Hyo is driving
through Il San.]
If we go a little more, it's my school.
Where's your house?
Il San, near Jungbal Mountain.
We're going to meet a fan...
Is it your mother?
My mom?
- Is it Junho's mom?
- I hope not.
Let's go to Junho's house.
Are we going to win right away?
Would it be a celebrity?
I don't think it will be.
It could be a celebrity.
Really?
Jin Hee, what kind of men do you like?
Stop it!
[Giraffe's more curious about Jin Hee.]
Kwang Soo's hoping it would be him!
I like funny people.
[The entertainers are
greatly satisfied.]
You like funny people.
Who do you like from 2PM?
Like in order.
- Based on their looks.
- They're all good looking.
If I was a girl, I'd pick Woo Young.
I'd pick Taecyeon.
- I'd pick Junho.
- Me, too.
- Hold on, if I were a girl...
- You don't have to pick.
[They're talking about imaginary
2PM boyfriends on the way.]
[They've arrived at the mission site.]
[What will the first mission be...]
[to find the fan's house?]
[Ta-da]
[What is this machine?]
- Is it a see-saw?
- It's a see-saw.
[It looks like a machine
NASA would use.]
Ride it!
[They try the four-way
see-saw right away.]
[A see-saw's nothing...]
This is scary!
[Tremble, tremble]
You haven't had fun as a kid!
Isn't this having fun?
[The problem is that
you're having too much fun.]
Stop, stop!
[This is so much fun,
I'm going to die!]
[Shiver]
It kind of feels like riding a viking.
[Team Jin Hee also enters
the see-saw zone.]
This is no joke!
[The 2PM kids who are figuring out
how to play with their new toy.]
Wow, what is this?
- They made this just for the game?
- Isn't it obvious?
[Why would the city hall make this...]
Who else would build this?
Don't mock me!
You'll get in big trouble!
Welcome to the first mission.
This is your first mission.
[The first start to finding their fan.]
[It's the see-saw
name tag elimination.]
- Pardon?
- Name tag elimination?
How would you rip a name tag on that?
[The game everyone has
once dreamed of!]
Behind you, is a four-wheel see-saw.
Four members from each team will sit.
The females on each team will
rip off four name tags in
the shortest amount of time.
[The name tag reps are
Jin Hee and Ji Hyo.]
The team to rip off all the name tags in
the shortest amount of time will win.
The men have to properly
adjust when to lift their feet off.
The reps have to take the least amount
of time, using whatever method...
You said 'whatever method', right?
[What are you planning on doing...]
Don't give her a cause.
Don't let her grab our hair.
[The will to fight is
charged to the max.]
- We won!
- Look at her...
What do I do...
[Nobody knew up to this point.]
[How brutal these two females were...]
- Do rock-paper-scissors.
- Oh, to choose who goes first?
- To choose the four members.
- Oh, the four members.
You can win with scissors.
[Very startled]
[Big Nose, what did you just do...]
She was really startled just now!
I thought you were going
to kiss her cheek!
I gave her a hint on what to play.
Jin Hee isn't familiar with you yet!
I almost took you down!
[He almost got a take down
for trying to whisper.]
You almost got elbowed!
- I'll give you a signal next time.
- Do you know what he said?
'You can win if you play scissors.'
[He always talks about scissors.]
- Do we go first if we win?
- No, you choose who goes first.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[She lost with scissors!]
[She lost with Big Nose's scissors.]
- You can do it!
- Nice, nice!
[See-saw name tag elimination,
first round.]
Jin Hee, don't let them win!
- Throw away your smile!
- Don't show your teeth!
What do I do...
- We're starting.
- Good luck, Jin Hee!
Good luck!
[Round one, start!]
Lower him!
Jin Hee!
[No matter how hard she tries...]
[how are you going to rip anything
off with those delicate hands...]
[Open back]
[What are you doing?]
[She aims for your back
with her delicate hands...]
[Oops]
[We thought her hands were delicate,
but they're like hooks.]
[Admire, admire]
[The next target is Ok's back.]
[Her non-stop hunt.]
[She rips off Woo Young's right after.]
[Woo Young's name tag, clear.]
[The only name tag left is Chansung's!]
That's it!
[It won't budge!]
[The Ok stake.]
[I can live only if you stay there...]
[Ok-ay.]
[Struggle]
Jin Hee!
[I never clung onto anything before...]
No!
[She finally got rid of the Ok stake.]
Hold on just a minute!
Hold, on!
You can't do this, it's dangerous!
It's actually very dangerous!
[Surprise attack]
[That was close...]
Jin Hee!
Like now, like now!
I think we won!
[Jin Hee is squeezing
the last bit of energy.]
[How dare you!]
Chansung, you've done enough.
[Awkward]
[Ha Ha crushed his mentality.]
[Finally Chansung's
name tag is eliminated.]
But why did you do this?
What are you going to do about this?
[Back split]
It's like the awards ceremony.
If he does it, it's fashion.
Wow, that was amazing.
Ji Hyo, good luck!
[See-saw elimination round one,
Ji Hyo's turn.]
[If those hands are hooks,
these hands are a bulldozer.]
- Don't sit too close.
- You and I need to balance properly.
Oh my god!
Wait, don't move so fast!
- Don't move!
- This is no joke.
It looks easy.
If he goes there, I'll sit.
[Really?]
Let's do well!
[Ace Blank Ji vs. Running boys]
Are you ready?
[See-saw elimination, round one.]
Good luck!
Hold on, hold on.
Is anyone filming Jae Suk?
Did you just see?
Chan Hee just said
'Is anyone filming Jae Suk?'
Chan Hee loves me so much.
I'm disappointed!
[Why are you disappointed...]
[I only look at Jae Suk.]
I'm so jealous...
Ready, start!
[Team Ji Hyo, start.]
[Sorry, but I have in front of me...]
[The Kkuk lump!]
[So... what?]
[Ultra-speed drop]
[Oh my]
[Giraffe's name tag is destroyed
as soon as round one started.]
[Now it's time for
grasshopper hunting.]
Wait, wait!
You can't!
[Rip]
Ji Hyo!
[Deeply moved]
[Now it's time to play with Kkuk.]
Jong Kook!
[If you slightly push Kkuk down...]
[It's hell here.]
Jong Kook!
[This is how she deals
with his resistance.]
[The tiger escaped!]
[Smashing the watermelon]
[A slam dunk on his butt crack...]
You can't do that!
[Rip]
[She got rid of Kkuk's name tag!]
[The last one is Gary's!]
[Tremble]
[Good job Ji Hyo!]
She's a monster...
[I knew she was scary,
but I didn't know it was this much...]
There's no reason for the see-saw!
What's the point of a see-saw?
[Blank Ji's success using
whatever method she wanted.]
Baek Jin Hee got
two minutes and four seconds.
Song Ji Hyo got
one minute and four seconds.
This time, a male rep
is going to eliminate.
You can't grab the see-saw
but you can grab other opponents.
- You can't touch the...
- Jong Kook's our rep.
Jong Kook can actually grab people.
[He's skilled at grabbing?]
Is it okay to come down
because you're scared?
[I'll save you...]
They might ask to come down.
I'll rip all of them.
Jin Hee, just think of Kwang Soo
like a rock.
Jin Hee, I need to go up for defense...
Kwang Soo, just sacrifice yourself!
Just think of Kwang Soo
as a property.
[Defense role, stake role.]
Think about the time!
We just need to stall!
[See-saw round two, start!]
- You're doing well!
- That's it!
That's good!
He's stuck!
[Giraffe's name tag is cleared.]
[Next is Big Nose's turn.]
[He cleared Big Nose's in a flash.]
Oh right, I can't touch the see-saw!
[Pull]
Jin Hee!
[She's a Jin Hee-us.]
Wow, you're good!
[He changed his target to Ha Ha.]
[Raising the spine]
[Ha Ha, you're cool!]
[He's completely prohibited
from ousting...]
[Pull]
[He's allowed to grab the opponent...]
[Extremely embarrassed]
[The only one left is the Jin Hee-us.]
This is...
[Catch me if you can!]
[He approaches the see-saw
without touching it.]
[I'm coming!]
With your foot, avoid him!
[Crush]
[The taste of hell.]
[Shake, shake]
[The pain only men know.]
[Giraffe has his head down low.]
Jin Hee!
[His sliding show his fighting spirit.]
[Will he rip it off this time?]
[Next time!]
[Good job, leader!]
[He watches for a chance!]
[He succeeds at the surprise attack.]
[She got robbed right after
hearing compliments.]
[Taecyeon finishes the
mission with difficulty.]
Why did you high five?
You lost!
Taecyeon is upset!
[Taecyeon is mad!]
Can I least wear a diaper or something?
Prepare an adult diaper!
[Will Kkuk be able to break
Taecyeon's record?]
I can't grab the see-saw, right?
It's okay
for a little bit of blood, right?
- Just slightly is okay, right?
- They all have to clothes on, right?
- Good luck, my team!
- Yeah!
- Kim Jong Kook, good luck!
- Good luck!
[I will show you what hunting is.]
[I miss my Mommy...]
You guys are dead.
[See-saw round two, start!]
[Rip]
[Roar]
[The tiger stalks his prey on the tree.]
Don't do this, Jong Kook!
[Why are you in such a hurry?]
[The tiger heads towards
his last prey.]
[He ripped all four name tags.]
[This is all part of nature.]
What is this!
There's no point!
Why did you make the see-saw?
It's as if the tiger stalks his prey...
We acted too rashly.
We shouldn't have planned a strategy...
Taecyeon's record is 01:49.
Jong Kook's record is
29 seconds.
[You're incredible...]
It was 29 seconds?
It took longer than we expected.
Try harder!
- You need to try harder!
- Sorry.
We actually had a strategy...
There's no use.
It's now tied.
We're going to play the last round.
You can't touch the see-saw or climb it
but only eliminate the name tags.
Anyone can be the rep
except the members who
have already been the rep.
[Team Jin Hee votes
Kwang Soo unanimously.]
- It's your time, now.
- It's time for the giant.
Instead, can we do this
if we're up there?
- You must be sitting.
- Sitting?
What were you doing before?
Were you sitting or standing?
[His humiliating
confidence over his hips.]
There's only a point in sacrificing
if you do it like Jin Hee!
[I don't think we'll be able to
see Ha Ha in the last round...]
[Time for strategy]
[The last defense is Blank Ji, Jun K]
[Taecyeon, and Junho.]
Kwang Soo can jump really well...
- Stay close to the handle.
- You have to avoid him.
- Stay close to that.
[Strategy planner Junho,
and commander Jun K.]
The ones on the bottom
will die for sure...
With Kwang Soo's height,
he can reach without jumping.
He'll reach if he jumps.
Chansung's really strong.
I can't touch it, anyway.
Jin Hee, did you wear
something underneath?
Did you wear something underneath?
[What did you say?]
[Shy, shy]
What are you saying!
- Why are you checking?
- Just in case it rips by accident...
You guys are really something else!
- So what if she is or isn't?
- You're really harsh.
[Falsely accused]
Are you ready?
[Round three, Chansung start!]
[He's attacking grasshopper first.]
Go forward!
[Rip]
[Grasshopper's name tag, cleared!]
[He goes up just in time.]
[Your sense of rhythm is perfect.]
[He avoided quickly... what?]
What is this?
[A free delivery service?]
[Grasshopper's off-beat.]
What are you doing?
Wasn't it three quarter time?
[The capable tiger vs.
Young champion wrestler Chansung.]
[Strength vs. strength]
[Risky, yet exciting]
Wow, that's amazing.
[Now the only one left
is the Jin Hee-us.]
I can't see clearly...
What do I do...
[Good job, you're stuck!]
You're doing well!
[Avoid, avoid]
That's good!
- Taecyeon's eyes!
- Why?
Those lustful eyes!
I'm just observing, that's all!
That's it, slap his hand away!
[Invincible defense]
[Even brushing past a
person is one's destiny...]
They're going to fall
in love at this rate.
You're right, you're right.
[Oh my god!
Her clothes!]
[Big accident]
[What happened?]
[Catch him!]
[The justice society is punishing him.]
[Slip off]
[A temporary solution
with Giraffe's clothes.]
[The sinner]
[The prophecy, Ok-stradamus.]
He predicted it, and it happened!
[Did you take revenge for Nichkhun?]
Go over there.
Over there!
Taecyeon, are you happy?
- You go over there!
- Jin Hee, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
We've timed it up to here.
Kwang Soo, why did you
take your clothes off?
[Awkward]
[You didn't have to do that...]
- Do we look that filthy?
- I was just trying to cover...
Why did you automatically strip!
He just wanted to
protect Jin Hee, but...
You've been really conscious
about it nowadays!
- You've done enough!
- I wasn't conscious!
He always does this
in front of the camera!
This is the last round.
Kwang Soo will be our rep.
Chansung's record is
isn't very good, to be honest.
Chansung's record isn't good.
What's worse than Chansung's record
was the situation.
[He was confronted by catastrophe.]
Isn't he the first idol?
[You need to reflect on your actions.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes!
Ready, set!
[Round three, Kwang Soo start!]
Good, good!
Wow!
Giraffe's next target is Taecyeon.
[We said no touching, but...]
Grab him, grab him!
[He does some wrestling skills
he always wanted to try.]
What are you doing?
[Stop sticking your butt out!]
[He's completely hiding his
name tag in this situation.]
[Fumble, fumble]
[Let's flip him!]
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, you're doing well!
[Will he flip, or will he not?]
[Give up.]
[Jun K wasn't paying attention.]
[He attacks Blank Ji
as soon as he rips Jun K's.]
[Catch me if you can!]
[Collecting hair]
Sorry, sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I was trying to grab your clothes!
[Have you been hit
with a see-saw before?]
You can't touch!
[He pulls on Blank Ji's clothes.]
You can't!
Ji Hyo, bend over!
- Bend over!
- You can't grab her!
[Struggle]
[What?]
[Why did this...]
[We told you to rip name tags,
not clothes!]
- Why did you rip that off?
- He's weird!
[That's like the ace!
She's still calm after]
[her clothes ripped.]
He's impure!
- Good job!
- What are you doing?
- Kwang Soo!
- I'm getting so frustrated!
- Good, good!
- When did he eliminated them?
Didn't he eliminate
Tae Yeon's name tag?
[I have to attack
since there's no time!]
[He's not going to...]
Wait, wait!
This is a torture!
[Win or lose?
It depends on Taecyeon.]
- No!
- Good job!
- Hold it out!
- Kwang Soo!
[Roll]
[Team Jin Hee eliminates
all four name tags.]
[Dizzy, dizzy]
This is risky...
I'll announce the result.
I think we won, but...
Lee Kwang Soo's record
is two minutes...
It was more than two minutes.
And 24 seconds.
- One minute and 24 seconds?
- Two minutes.
Chansung's record is
two minutes...
and 15 seconds.
Wow, we won!
[They were nine seconds faster.}
We won!
[Team Ji Hyo vs. Team Jin Hee]
[Their flippant ceremony!]
[Bitter]
[While they're celebrating
their victory...]
Jin Hee is planning to sue you.
She's very much hurt.
[Always watch out for your back!]
Like I said before, the fan is
going to give you on the phone.
Write 'Team Ji Hyo won,'
then the fan will give you a hint.
Team Ji Hyo won.
You should at least show it to Jin Hee.
Congratulations!
The hint is about the pin number.
The pin code at my door is '?00?,'
and the two '?' are same numbers.
But we don't know where it is.
We'll get to know soon.
Did you get the hint?
Then, go to your car.
[Team Ji Hyo can go
to the next mission site.]
- We've sent the message.
- Let's wait.
Wait for the answer.
I thought Team Jin Hee was going to win.
Aw-shucks!
But I'll still give you a hint.
The pin code at my door is '?00?.'
[He doesn't let the two '?'
are same numbers.]
- Something, 0, 0, and something?
- 1004?
- '*00#'?
By the way, did you see
'Aw-shucks'?
- That's what we used to use.
- 'Aw-shucks'?
That's right!
We use it when we play pool.
When we almost hit the ball off
the table we used to say 'Aw-shucks!'
I'm pretty sure the person
was born before 1960.
- Let's go.
- 'Aw-shucks' is the 90's expression.
Guess the hint quickly
and meet me soon.
[Who is the fan who says 'Aw-shucks'?]
[Finding the mysterious fan]
[The identity of the mysterious fan
is slowly revealed.]
[The closer they get to the fan
the more shocking it gets!]
It's unbelievable!
[Is it a pool?]
What a nice weather.
It's perfect for water games.
Isn't it amazing?
[There's something
that doesn't fit in the pool.]
What is it again?
It's dreadful...
It's a basketball hoop.
What are we going to play here?
What's that?
It's for dunk shot.
We're really bad at ball games.
We're hopeless.
That's why we're called beast idols.
Our hands and feet are like beast.
The second mission is
diving basket ball.
Diving basketball?
Do a run-up on the springboard
and throw a jump shot.
[Huh?]
It's moving further.
[The hoop is moving away.]
[Can't we leave it in here?]
[I knew it.]
How far will it move?
- That's too far!
- How far will they move it?
[About 12 meters (40 feet.)]
They want us to dive.
We have no choice
but to get in the water.
The hoop goes up!
[About 6 meters (20 feet.)]
That's too harsh!
We need to shoot a bank-shot.
Jong Kook sucks at basketball.
He's bad at ball games.
[Should I show you all today?]
[Diving basketball]
[Team Jin Hee vs. Team Ji Hyo]
Good luck, Jae Suk!
[When it comes to basketball,
we automatically play this song.]
[The players are picked
by rock-paper-scissors.]
[Serious]
[Grasshopper shooter]
[Pros: Always calm.]
[Cons: Not a good basketball player.]
Don't think about jumping.
Only focus on the rim.
[The problem is
the rim is far and high.]
[Team Jin Hee's first shooter...]
[Grasshopper]
[He tries to loosen up by dribbling.]
[How long are you going to do that?]
- You're going to be tired.
- I can't move my legs.
[Totally agree.]
Jae Suk, be brave!
- I feel you!
- In my mind, I'm already running.
[Grasshopper gathers up his courage.]
Fight, Jae Suk!
[Now...]
He's going at it!
[The only thing I see it the rim.]
Go, Jae Suk!
Fly, Yoo Jae Suk!
[Grasshopper runs!]
[Run]
He's doing it!
[Will he be able to score
at his first attempt?]
[After the run-up,
he throws a jump shot!]
[He threw it!]
[He puts up with the diving
and shoots the ball.]
[The trajectory looks good...]
[Not really!]
[It wasn't even close!]
The wind makes the ball curve.
I didn't score?
[No, you didn't score.]
It's farther than I thought.
Jae Suk fell into water,
but no one cares about him.
He didn't score.
No one asks if he's okay.
It's fine.
Come back.
[He flew like a grasshopper]
[and fell meaninglessly.]
[Basketball is not my strong suit.]
[Team Ji Hyo's first shooter, Chansung]
Whoever scores will lead the team.
[Beast shooter, Hwang Chansung]
[Pros: He's strong.]
[Cons: He's only strong.]
[He starts off with
spinning the basketball.]
What?
He can...
- You're good with balls!
- Challenge!
Run slowly.
Don't be in a hurry!
Good luck!
[He runs with a serious face.]
[Startled]
[Slap]
[What is he doing there?]
Mister, we're trying to
play basketball here.
This is too tight.
[Chansung pulls himself together.]
Challenge!
[I won't be bothered
by any interference.]
Chansung!
[He ignores Giraffe and shoots!]
[Will he...]
[The ball flies in an arc.]
[Straight to the rim!]
[No goal!]
[It was at the right angle.]
[But a little short.]
[After throwing the jump shot,
everyone dives.]
Diving makes everyone nervous.
[Also, no one cares about
who fell into the water.]
Can we start over?
[He throws it like a NBA player]
[but he shootis like a girl.]
[Diving basketball]
[Both fail at the round one.]
[Team Jin Hee's leader's attack.]
[The little woman, Baek Jin Hee]
[Pros: Small but strong.]
[Cons: Not that strong.]
We'll make it closer
for female players.
Aren't you good at basketball?
Can you show me this?
Dribbling.
[Slow and weak]
I'm so sorry.
[Why did you ask me to do it?]
[Team Jin Hee's second shooter,
Jin Hee.]
Run, Jin Hee!
[She runs briskly.]
- You can do it!
- Go, Jin Hee!
[She throws the ball and disappears.]
[This isn't a shot.]
[She whipped the ball down.]
[I'm sorry I asked if
she was good at basketball.]
[Like the hoop is at the bottom.]
[She squeezed her eyes
and jumped into water.]
[I miss my mommy...]
[It's kind of fun
to mimic Jin Hee.]
[Everyone is mimicking her.]
It was a battle against herself.
[She comes out of water.]
- Was the ball close to the hoop?
- Yes, it seemed like it.
[It's the first time diving
and throwing a ball.]
[Diving basketball]
[Jin Hee fails at round two.]
[Team Ji Hyo's second shooter,
Taecyeon.]
[The beast shooter, Ok Taecyeon]
[Pros: Very athletic.]
[Cons: He has beast hands.]
- Taecyeon, you should do it.
- I'd like to.
For your persona, you shouldn't...
[He runs as if he's playing football.]
I think he will make it!
[A shot of a beast]
[Bounce]
[It bounced back
by the rim.]
[It was close.]
It was very close.
He said he's bad at it,
but he's still good.
[The closest shot of them all.]
- Do you want to go first?
- Okay.
[Team Ji Hyo's third shooter,
Jun K.]
[2PM's number one shooter,
Jun K]
[Pros: The strongest out of 2PM.]
[Cons: 2PM is bad at ball games.]
[He catches his breath
and runs briskly]
[and shoot!]
[It's at the right angle!]
[Did he score?]
[Scream]
No, he didn't make it.
[Huh? No goal?]
It was a little short.
[It seems the ball went into the rim]
[but the ball just hit the net.]
[No goal!]
- Didn't it go through?
- No, it didn't.
[Only if it was
just a little higher...]
If the ball went 5 centimeters farther,
it could have gone through.
That was so close.
[Aw-shucks!]
You're the basketball man.
You should score a goal.
[At that moment,
a man picks up the ball quietly.]
[Who's the man?]
[The basket man Ha Ha!]
Dong Hoon will score a goal!
[Say my name, who am I?]
[Hichael Jordan, Ha Ha]
[Pros: Good basketball player.]
[Cons: Short stature]
[I'm not going to lose at basketball!]
[Because I'm the basket man!]
[He was born to play basketball.]
- Wasborn Basketball!
- Hichael Jordan!
The pantsless basketball man!
[Huh?]
[Oh, we get it.]
He scores by taking off his pants!
- He's confident about his skills.
- I think he will score for sure.
[Ha Ha's never this serious.]
Let's go!
[The basket man's attack.]
[Haroro's shot!]
[The shot flew in the highest
and the prettiest arc.]
[Wow, it's awesome!]
[The goal was a little off
from the hoop.]
It was the closest
out of the whole team.
[Yes, I'm Haroro.]
I think I can make it in my second try.
[Team Ji Hyo's last shooter.]
[All-around athlete, Nichkhun]
[Pros: He's good at everything.]
[Cons: ...]
Nichkhun, you're not going to
be good at this, are you?
You already have everything.
You don't need to be good at this.
He looks like he's playing volley ball.
[He's really fast!]
[He has the ability to react instantly.]
Nichkhun crossed the river already.
[He even has endurance.]
[All-around entertainer, Nichkhun!]
[Will he conquer
the diving basketball as well?]
[Runs without hesitation and shoots!]
[Look,
how the all-round entertainer plays!]
[Home run!]
[The ball headed to the sky.]
He made a poor shot.
It was our worst shot.
Oh, my Khun...
You ruined your carefully crafted imaged.
He's usually very athletic.
He's really bad.
He looks like
a prince of basketball.
The prince of Thailand
is not good at this!
This won't do.
Let me finish this game.
It's the last player.
You can finish the game!
- Go, go!
- Fight, Jong Kook!
[Team Jin Hee's last shooter,
Kkuk]
[The muscle shooter,
Kim Jong Kook]
[Pros: Limitless capabilities.]
[Cons: There should be...]
Let's go back a little.
[He's Mister Capable,
but bad at ball games.]
[He's shaky.]
- Don't you need to throw like this?
- His throwing motions is weird.
[These people...]
[should I really show them?]
I'll score a goal.
[I still believe in you.]
- I will score a goal.
- Please.
[Babe Kkuk is making a prediction?]
[The Tiger leaps.]
[His left hand...]
[is not just there,
but helps with the shot.]
[Kkuk's frog shot!]
[No way...]
[Please, go in!]
[It went through the net!]
- He scored!
- That's amazing!
[His motion was a little clumsy
but the ball went through the hoop.]
[Kkuk made it!]
[Team Jin Hee wins
the diving basketball.]
[With this, Mr. Capable
conquers ball games.]
I think I would hate him
if I was his enemy.
But it's nice to have him on my team.
[He keeps his face calm.]
[Absent-minded]
Let's play the name tag elimination!
[He jumped like a frog]
[and shoot to the hoop!]
[Of course, I'm a genius.]
This time, you'll get
hints on the phone.
You'll be able to talk to
the mother of the fan.
Mother?
We can guess from her voice.
You can't ask the address.
She'll only answer yes or no.
Ask as many questions
during the given time.
[Team Jin Hee has 30 seconds.
And Team Ji Hyo has 15 seconds.]
Hello, ma'am.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hello.
[She is the mother...]
[of the mysterious fan.]
[She looks very young
for a mother.]
[But, she looks familiar...]
By any chance, is your son in his 40s?
No.
- In his 30s?
- Jin Hee!
[It's like letting the other team
know the answer.]
- Is he an entertainer?
- No.
- Do you live in Seoul?
- Time is up.
- Is he married?
[This will be the last question.]
No.
[Team Jin Hee's time's up.]
[Did they get all the information
they wanted?]
You have 15 seconds.
Hello.
Is your child a son or a daughter?
She can only say yes or no.
Is your child a son?
- Yes.
- Five, four, three...
- Is he a singer?
- No.
Goodbye.
[Team Ji Hyo's time is up.]
[Finding the mysterious fan]
[The pin code of his door is '*00*.']
[The fan is a child,
and not a entertainer!]
What did Jin Hee ask?
He's a boy.
He's not an entertainer.
He's not in his 40s.
Maybe his mother is an entertainer.
It's possible.
Is she No Sa Yeon?
No, it wasn't her voice.
How was her voice?
- She sounded young.
- Young?
- Does she sound like in her 30s?
- Yes, between 30 to 40.
- She sounded...
- The the fan might be a student.
- Didn't she say he's in his 30s?
- She said he's not in his 40s.
So, we don't know how old he is.
Wake up, we're here!
What's that?
What is it?
[Huh? What is that?]
[All kinds of makeup]
[and a snugly teddy bear.]
[This is Hallyu actress
Blank Ji's house.]
[On the other side]
[a rising actress, Jin Hee's house.]
[In front of the two rooms]
[filled with luxurious items are...]
[a super-sized rice paddy.]
[The last mission of
'Come Over To My Place'!]
I left 'Three Meals a Day'.
But I still came to the country.
[It's a good place to build a house.]
What is this?
[What will be the last mission
that they will play?]
This is your house.
It surrounded by the rice paddy.
You're amazing!
This looks like a set
for the music show.
[They start looking
around the house.]
I've never seen so many
spring onions before!
[Just for one day,
I'd like to be the bed in your room.]
These are all spring onions.
[Farming instinct.]
Let's go.
[Team Jin Hee arrives at that moment.]
Is this a house?
- It's Jin Hee's house.
- Ji Hyo's house.
[Have your own house
by the spring onion field.]
- The last mission is...
- What is it?
'Why did you come to my house?'
Why did you come to my house?
Who to attack first will be
decided by rock-paper-scissors.
Offense team will decide
whose name you'll call.
When the game starts, you'll hold
your hands with your teammates.
Start singing the tune
'Why did you come to my house?'
and move while facing each other.
After you sing the part,
'What flower are you looking for?'
Then, offense team will call out
the name you decided.
From that moment, the offense team
needs to oust the person by
taking off one of the person's shoes.
Defense team needs to protect the
person whose name is called out.
If you protect the person,
you'll win the round.
Winning at rock-paper-scissors
is important.
Please play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Jin Hee wins.]
[Team Jin Hee is on offense.]
- Very good!
- Did you win by throwing scissors?
[Good job!]
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
[Team Ji Hyo is on defense.]
We'll block them.
- Who should we call out?
- They're all strong.
How about Nichkhun?
Let's pick the strongest one first.
Between Taecyeon or Chansung.
- Chansung will be hard to attack.
- I'll attack.
Once your name is called out,
that person goes to the back.
And the rest can fight them.
But, we need two people
to block Jong Kook.
No, we need three people.
[That's right...
Jong Kook is on that team.]
[We still remember
the Idol Athletic Competition.]
[Nichkhun was ousted in a flash.]
[He also overpowered Jun K.]
[And ousted Woo Young
mercilessly.]
[Monster Kkuk made
the beast idols look like pets.]
[It still chills down my spine.]
[Why did you come to my house?]
[The first round]
[The players enter the field.]
Go to that side, okay?
Did offense team decide on
who you'll attack?
Yes.
[Wobble]
[She feels weak
after the diving basketball.]
Are they wearing shoulder pads or what?
[Six men with big shoulders.]
- Focus, focus!
- Get ready!
I'm very nervous!
[Who will receive the last hint?]
- They'll be even more nervous.
- Start!
Why did you come to my house,
to my house, to my house?
[Little by little]
To look for a flower,
a flower, a flower.
[Startled]
Don't we need to move back and forth?
[They can't move forward.]
Let's do it again.
[We know the rule...]
We're scared, that's why!
Think about it,
wouldn't you be scared?
You need to meet someone like you!
You know it hurts
to lock my fingers with him.
- I have to endure it.
- We'll start again.
Why did you come to my house,
to my house, to my house?
To look for a flower,
a flower, a flower.
[Can't you look for it slowly?]
What flower are you looking for?
One, two, three!
Taecyeon!
[Gosh!]
[Taecyeon is cornered.]
[Junho and Nichkhun
are blocking Jong Kook.]
[The rest are one on one,
as they planned.]
[Give me your shoe, Taecyeon!]
[At that moment...]
[Kwang Soo attacks Taecyeon's shoe.]
[Let me see your sole.]
[Big Nose attacks the other foot.]
[Here's Taecyeon's shoe!]
[Team Ji Hyo's member,
Taecyeon is ousted.]
[Rip]
What's wrong with this shirt?
[The trace of the battle.]
What's wrong with this?
[Suddenly, so sexy.]
[The strongest member,
Taecyeon is ousted.]
- Then, we only have six members.
- There's nothing you can do.
[He made his own uniform
with a yellow plastic bag.]
They don't have any extra uniforms.
- They don't have anymore yellow shirts.
- This looks bad.
[The yellow plastic bag
is what completes his fashion.]
They don't have any!
I think it'll be ripped
as soon as we touch it.
If you win, attack him first.
This makes our team look very weak.
You looks like a mischievous boy.
[Why did you come to my house?]
[The second round]
[Chansung vs. Jin Hee]
Jin Hee!
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Chansung wins.]
[Team Ji Hyo's offense..]
You should have thrown scissors.
[Ode to scissors]
[Ji Scissors-win.]
- Team Ji Hyo, did you decide a name?
- Yes.
We'll start the round two!
[Why did you come to my house?]
[The second round starts.]
Why did you come to my house,
to my house, to my house?
To look for a flower,
a flower, a flower.
What flower are you looking for?
One, two, three?
[Who is their first target?]
Kang Gary!
[He runs away with all his might.]
[Junho throws Mr. Capable.]
[Stop there, Gary!]
[He's been running away
for five years.]
[Let me protect you, Gary!]
[Grab]
[Team Ji Hyo captures Gary.]
[Chaos]
Endure it, Gary!
- I took it off!
- No!
We got it!
[Woo Young got Gary's shoe!]
[Team Jin Hee's member,
Gary is ousted.]
Don't take off my shirt!
[It's 2PM's turn to
take off their shirts.]
What is this?
What kind of a game is this?
This show is testing our patients!
[It was a sudden exposure,
but their six-packs are firm.]
- It feels weird.
- Give us four blue plastic bags, please.
[Just look at me
and style like me.]
- Look at Chansung.
Chansung, are you a warrior?
[He recreates '300' poster.]
[Even the top looks like a cape.]
What's wrong with this?
Why don't you use this style
for your next album cover?
[Isn't it nice?]
[I support the album cover idea.]
The score is 1:1.
You'll play rock-paper-scissors.
- Reps!
- Suk Jin, you go!
The god of rock-paper-scissors!
[Chansung vs. Big Nose]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Chansung wins.]
[Team Ji Hyo is offense team again.]
- I lost by throwing scissors.
- Why do you always throw scissors?
[Whisper, whisper]
[Team Ji Hyo decided quickly.]
The third round, ready!
Why did you come to my house,
to my house, to my house?
To look for a flower,
a flower, a flower.
What flower are you looking for?
One, two, three!
[Who's their target?]
Ji Suk Jin!
[It's unexpected!]
[They picked the weakest.]
[Big Nose gets caught by Junho.]
[Scream]
[Big Nose's crisis!]
Run, Suk Jin!
Suk Jin!
[Do you think it's possible to run?]
- Hold my shoes!
- I'll hold them.
Hold it just for a moment!
[Suk Jin, endure it!]
Just for 30 seconds!
[Team Jin Hee can win if they
keep his shoes for 30 seconds.]
Keep your toes wide open!
[My toes... hang in there....]
I'm getting the cramps!
My toes!
My big toe!
Ten seconds left!
I have the shoes!
- It's almost done!
- Stay strong!
I have the shoe!
Don't let him hold it up!
[Team Ji Hyo will win
if Chansung hold up the shoe.]
Two, one...
[Big Nose's toes endured hardship.]
- I had the shoe.
- You didn't hold it up.
[Team Jin Hee wins.]
Wow, unbelievable!
[Bravo! Enthusiastic Big Nose!]
Suk Jin, you did well!
Jong Kook was on top of me.
How can I possibly hold it up?
- Who can defeat him?
- Did you see it?
Look at my shirt.
[The see through plastic bag
is fashionable and strong.]
Did you see it?
[Team Ji Hyo vs. Team Jin Hee]
[1:1]
Mr. Ono-no-Tofu is walking around!
(A man with an umbrella on Hanafuda)
[Mr. Ok-no-Tofu]
Ono-no-Tofu,
why are you walking around?
I want to protect my members
from the sun.
Jin Hee, come to your senses!
[They won again!]
[They lost again!]
You should have thrown
scissors in the beginning.
You're really lucky today.
Two out of three, please!
Let's do best out of three!
- Let's start deciding.
- Jin Hee is asking you.
Look at Jin Hee.
[Please...]
Just look at her.
[Best out of three?]
[Yes, best out of three!]
Okay, let's just do it.
[Her cute appeal worked!]
- So, it's two out of three.
- Okay, good!
He won once already.
[1:1]
Okay, okay!
[Slap]
[He won five times and lost once.]
I won all the other games!
It just once!
I'm hurt!
[I apologize.]
Jin Hee, just win one more time.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Let us attack once!]
[Chansung wins.]
[Team Ji Hyo is on offense again.]
[Thanks to Chansung, Team Ji Hyo is
on offense four times in a row.]
I'll tell you who the target it.
I can see it from here.
- How do you know?
- I can see it.
It'll be over, if we lose this time.
It's true. [They whisper
from where Gary can't see.]
[Huh?
Who is it this time?]
Ready, set, go!
Why did you come to my house,
to my house, to my house?
To look for a flower,
a flower, a flower.
What flower are you looking for?
One, two, three!
[I'm sorry, I don't know this time.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Oh, it was Kwang Soo?]
[Grabs]
[Woo Young attacks his shoe right away.]
Wait, wait!
[Chansung vs. Jong Kook]
[Nichkhun vs. Jae Suk]
[Don't worry, Kwang Soo!]
[Let me protect you.]
[Thud]
[Jong Kook, you don't have
to use your technique!]
[I'm sorry, Chansung!]
What happened to Kwang Soo?
[Chaos]
[We don't care who wins.
Just finish this game quickly!]
[No way!]
[Team Jin Hee's member,
Kwang Soo is ousted.]
[Team Ji Hyo wins the last mission.]
It's over.
We lost because of
the rock-paper-scissors.
[They were on offense once,
then the rest was on defense.]
We won!
- You've worked so hard, Jin Hee.
- How many rounds did we fight?
The winner is Team Ji Hyo.
The loser is Team Jin Hee.
We'll give you the last hint
after you take shower.
This time, the hint is the fan's address.
It's the address.
The mud stain is hard to get rid of.
Here, I'll give you the last hint.
This is the most important hint.
We've received the message already.
['J' Apartment Building 218]
[4th City street,
Goyang City in Gyeonggi]
[Come quickly.
I'll be waiting for you.]
I think it's pretty close.
Did we get it?
- Did we get it?
- Yes, we did.
[City street, Ilsan-dong,
Goyang City in Gyeonggi]
This is my address!
[That's the area I live!]
[Did he say he lives there?]
[Team Ji Hyo gets in the car quickly.]
I've got a very important information.
It's possible the fan is Suk Jin's son.
What?
[The fan might be Big Nose's son?]
That's why he said he likes
Jae Suk and Big Nose?
Is that really your address?
- I think it is, don't you think so?
- Where is it?
Didn't I say it's hard to find
a fan of Suk Jin?
[It's suspicious.]
That's right!
He said he likes me and Jae Suk.
We should have asked him who he dislikes.
Hyun Woo dislikes me.
- Even you don't know about this.
- Of course, I don't know.
- Could it be?
- I was talking to my wife a moment ago.
Why don't you call her back
so Jin Hee can hear her voice.
Call her and let her listen.
- That's amazing.
- You can tell, right?
- She's busy.
- Maybe she's on the phone with the PD.
Could it be really your house?
Could it be?
No way, it doesn't make sense.
[Both teams are heading to
the area in a hurry.]
[It's a battle of speed!]
[The team that gives the fan
a hug first will win this race.]
[What's the identity of the fan?]
[They are near the area.]
I can't believe it's my house.
A lot of celebrities
live in this area, right?
Right, there are many celebrities.
- But he's not a celebrity.
- Perhaps...
[Perhaps?]
It could be Jun Soo.
[Lee Jong Hyuk's son.]
Jong Hyuk's family
lives one floor above us.
- But she said he's not a celebrity.
- His son is not a celebrity.
Right, the fan must be a child.
But think about 'Aw-shucks.'
[They arrive at the building.]
Suk Jin's son would write, 'Aw-shucks'?
That doesn't make sense.
No way...
Could it be really my house?
[They arrived at Suk Jin's apartment.]
This doesn't make sense!
This is unbelievable!
[He hurriedly returns home.]
- Why doesn't this work?
- Suk Jin, are you flustered?
[He seems very flustered.]
[They reached Big Nose's elevator.]
Is it really our house?
This is unbelievable.
[There are cameras in
the elevator as well.]
[It can't be...
Let's go to my house first.]
[They got off on Big Nose's floor.]
[They arrive in front
of Big Nose's house.]
[As usual]
[he tries pressing]
[the password to his house.]
Huh?
It changed!
[But it's my house...]
[Mental breakdown]
You're the house owner,
just tell your wife to open up.
[They changed the password!]
[Suk Jin's house is mostly
likely the fan's house.]
Please press the password.
She said press the password.
Are you going to be like this?
[Suk Jin's house is the fan's house?]
Honey... Soo Jung.
[Honey, please open the door.]
[We must have failed...]
They changed the password.
Only you can solve it.
It must have a meaning to you.
Ask your wife for a hint.
It's a really easy number.
- Is it Hyun Woo?
- Yes.
Would you give me a hint?
- It's really easy.
- He says it's easy.
[If it's easy, is it 0000?]
Does that have a meaning to you?
[Will that really be the answer?]
[Press, press]
[It opened]
[They finally entered
Big Nose's house.]
Is it really my house?
[Then the fan waiting here is...]
- He likes Big Nose and Jae Suk!
- He's older than me!
[It was a difficult mystery at first.]
[The fan's password is?00?
The?'s are the same number.]
[The closer and closer they got every
time they finished a round.]
[The fan is a child!]
[Not a celebrity!]
- They're not in their 40s.
- They're in their 30s.
[They realized it was a
child near the end.]
[The fan's house is in
an apartment in Il San.]
[The mystery fan was
Suk Jin's son, Hyun Woo.]
[Dad, I'm always your number one fan.]
- It's really your house!
- Hello!
[Ji Hyun Woo and Ryu Soo Jung.]
Hello!
Go hug him!
Wow, that's amazing.
It was really my house?
[Dumbfounded]
I really didn't know...
You were fooled!
Then did you text them saying
you were a 'Running Man' fan?
Yes.
[You must be surprised.]
[From the greeting at the
opening to the missions.]
[Hyun Woo guided them
through the whole thing.]
[The hints in the middle were
given by Hyun Woo as well!]
It's something, zero zero, something.
[In Suk Jin's home]
[Hyun Woo had bits and pieces
of Running Man memories.]
[And the unforgettable moments
he had with the members.]
[Welcome, I was waiting for you.]
Soo Jung!
Aren't your clothes a bit excessive?
[I wanted to look nice.]
- I know this family really well...
- Hyun Woo, let me give you a hug.
We have to hug.
[Come here, my number one fan.]
[I thought you didn't like me]
[because I couldn't
be with you enough.]
[But I never knew
the mystery fan was my son.]
Me, too.
You made him breakfast this morning?
It was weird.
She usually sleeps past 9.
She woke up to my alarm.
[They've found the right place
thanks to Hyun Woo's text.]
You left a message...
[Oh!]
Oh, they were already here!
[Team Ji Hyo was already here,
but were hiding.]
[15 minutes ago]
[They knew the exact address, so they]
[were able to come earlier!]
- Are you wearing sunglasses inside?
- It's a child.
It's child.
By any chance, do you know if Suk Jin's
son lives somewhere upstairs?
- The ninth floor?
- Which house?
[He knew the exact house number!]
[A kind boy who helped Team Ji Hyo.]
What floor do you live on?
- The 14th floor.
- Are you close?
- Uncle Suk Jin knows my dad.
- Is it this boy?
Oh, this is Lee Jong Hyuk's son,
Tak Soo.
Oh, I'm sorry.
How is your dad doing?
[They thankfully got to the
right floor thanks to him.]
[Surprised]
Try '0000', first.
Wow, that was amazing!
For real?
Excuse us!
[Is it my dad?]
Please, excuse us.
Hello, Soo Jung!
[Peek]
- Hello.
- Hello Soo Jung.
Hyun Woo, it's you right?
We have to hug him!
[Team Ji Hyo won the final mission.]
Hyun Woo!
- Hyun Woo, did they hug you?
- Yes.
[Really?]
We hugged him as soon as we saw him!
- Who hugged you?
- Everyone.
Hyun Woo said he didn't
like celebrities a lot
- but he loves them!
- You liked them a lot?
[Hyun Woo is a fan of 2PM.]
He's supposed to finish at 3 a.m.
because it's 'filming day.'
But he came home a little earlier.
We have additional filming, right?
[See you later, honey.]
Do you have anything to say to
Suk Jin, or about the show?
Next time, please win.
[Embarrassed]
Hyun Woo, do you have something to say?
I also want to say... please win.
[Big Nose's family
wishes for his victory.]
[The winners are also slightly
in an awkward position.]
[Photo time]
[Big Nose's family, please be happy!]
[Let's summon the legendary heroes!]
[The soccer Crown Prince,
Song Jong Gook.]
[The strongest spiker, Kim Yeon Kyung.]
[The immortal dunker, Hyun Joo Yup.]
[The rhythmic gymnast, Shin Soo Ji.]
[Genius wits expert, Hong Jin Ho.]
[The experts of different fields.]
[The Go master, Cho Hoon Hyun.]
[The Mystery solver, Pyo Chang Won.]
[The Korean folk singer, Song So Hee.]
[The webtoon artist, Cho Suk.]
[The sound analyst, Bae Myung Jin.]
[The Chef, Michael.]
Summon my hero!
[The heroes' unbelievable
supernatural powers are on the move!]
[Who will be the first
to bring peace to the world?]
[The Battle of Heroes.]
Subtitles by DramaFever