(An ordinary-looking building
in Sangam-dong)
(A secret hideout
of martial art masters)
Hello.
- Hello, Jong Kook.
- Hey, you're here.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hey.
(Shouting)
This is "The Matrix."
(So Min is dressed
like the movie, "The Matrix.")
- Gosh, my back.
- Hey, I meant this.
- Why did you do that?
- My back hurts a lot.
Sir, please tell me about my future.
- I'll read your future.
- Yes, please.
- All right.
- What will happen to me?
So...
- What time were you born?
- This is ambiguous, right?
You look Japanese.
- I'm not Japanese.
- It's Japanese-style.
This is hanbok.
- Is it hanbok?
- It's hanbok.
You're wearing
something colorful today.
- It's red.
- Yes. This is all I had.
I wanted to wear something black.
- This is Bruce Lee.
- That's what I intended.
It seems like Haha will...
- try drunken boxing.
- Haha is...
- Look at him.
- Sir.
Are you a fortune-teller?
No, that's drunken boxing.
Do you work at the royal kitchen?
The royal kitchen?
- I bet he's from the royal kitchen.
- I'm scared.
(Moving abruptly)
- What?
- My gosh.
(Ji Seok Sam, a master
who has never hit anyone before)
Hello.
You look so neat and tidy.
- I'm...
- You look weak.
No. People like me are real masters.
- Master?
- That's right. You're a master.
Masters are dressed in black.
- Did you go to a hot spring?
- Shut it.
A hot spring?
What are you talking about?
You look like an informant
with the glasses on.
- I'm not an informant.
- I know.
What are you talking about?
- It's not like that.
- This is not working.
This is the traditional clothing
of Korea.
- Don't get me wrong.
- Why do you look like an informant?
- This is the traditional clothes.
- Okay.
Why are you dressed like a spy?
What did you tell them to wear?
- She's the same.
- Isn't this "The Matrix?"
- I'm a martial artist.
- This isn't a martial artist.
- I'm Chun Li.
- What?
- You look nothing like Chun Li.
Chun Li isn't dressed like this.
I'm Chun Li today.
- You're not Chun Li.
- But...
- That's Michael Jackson.
- Ji Hyo.
You know this is how Ji Hyo talks.
But when the shoot ends,
she calls me on her way home.
"Hi, Ji Hyo. What's the matter?"
"Jae Suk, do you think
my costume was inappropriate today?"
(Jae Suk, do you think
my costume was inappropriate today?)
"So I was thinking..."
"No, I was just joking."
- I'm glad she calls you.
- "No, Jae Suk."
"I'll wear something
appropriate next week."
"Seriously, I'll make sure
I'll do things right next time."
Isn't Se Chan coming today?
- Se Chan is not here?
- The thing is...
Today, Se Chan has...
- He's not coming?
- He's shooting another show.
- Really?
- He couldn't make it today.
He does another show on Tuesday.
Se Chan would've dressed up
perfectly on a day like today.
I know.
Se Chan would've been excited.
We had to reschedule this shoot...
- at the last minute.
- That's right.
Since Se Chan can't make it today,
we prepared his life-size cut-out.
- Come on.
- His life-size cut-out?
- That's not necessary.
- There's no need.
- It's not a big deal.
- He's just not here.
He would've dressed up perfectly.
- That's not enough.
- His life-size cutout...
- This isn't just right.
- No way.
- Hey, you brat.
- You should've dressed up.
We don't have to make
his life-size cut-out.
So Se Chan is a cut-out.
- So Min, you sound serious.
- He's a cut-out.
Anyway, we have a special guest...
for today.
- I know that.
- I saw that on social media.
All right. Please come on out.
- He's coming already?
- So...
Who's that?
(Is he coming already?)
- Is he coming from there?
- He's Jong Kook's friend.
- Hey.
- My goodness.
He's the master of Wing Chun Kuen.
- Welcome, Hyuk.
- The master of Wing Chun Kuen.
- Hello.
- Hyuk.
(Korea's famous action star)
(Martial artist and actor,
Jang Hyuk)
- The master of Wing Chun Kuen.
- Hyuk.
- He's a member of Running Man.
- Hello.
- The master of Wing Chun Kuen.
- Hyuk, you're here.
You're here.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Stand in the middle.
- You're still good-looking.
- Hyuk.
- All right.
- He's handsome.
- He's here for Donnie Yen.
- That's right.
- He's the master of Wing Chun Kuen.
- Exactly.
- Hyuk is here with us.
We know nothing about martial arts,
so we need him here.
Actually,
Jong Kook is a good fighter...
- But he's not a martial artist.
- He's new to martial art.
- He's...
- So Hyuk came here for us.
It was about 20 years ago.
We went to a funeral.
And he kept trying
to show us his Jit Kune Do.
- Okay.
- He kept saying...
- this was painful.
- You mean this.
But it didn't hurt at all.
He kept insisting
that it really hurt.
- When you hit like this?
- Yes. So...
So this is Jit Kune Do.
It's called the one-inch punch.
It doesn't have
unnecessary movements.
It's a martial art
for an actual fight.
- That's right.
- It involves a mental fight.
Does it have to do with mentality?
- It involves a mental fight?
- Yes.
What did you just do?
- I did an impression of him.
- An impression of him.
You're good at it.
- Did you just do that?
- After I hear Hyuk's voice,
I can do that better.
- I thought Hyuk was speaking.
- I did it.
What did you say?
- It involves a mental fight.
He sounds similar.
You're good at this.
He's actually not good
at stuff like this.
So this is what I sound like.
Hyuk is the best in the country
when it comes to Jit Kune Do.
- This is what you do.
- He's the best actor.
- But the thing is...
- That's true.
Well... It was 2007.
At the Chinese
Martial Arts Festival,
you won the Best Rookie
Martial Artist Award.
You won the Best Rookie
(The Best Rookie
Martial Artist Award?)
- Back then...
- Is that true?
- I don't know why I won it.
- Really?
He won the Best Rookie
Martial Artist Award?
- Is that true?
- He's serious about this.
- Seriously?
- The thing is...
- I did some action films.
- Action films?
They were submitted.
So they watched your films
and evaluated them.
A martial art director said
he's Donnie Yen of Korea.
That's what he's called.
Honestly... I'm not saying this
because he's my friend.
When it comes to martial arts,
- I think he's the best actor.
- That's true.
Actors like Ma Dong Seok
show a powerful blow,
but he's different.
- He has splendid skills.
- He has skills.
Hyuk is the one
with the best skills.
Hyuk is good enough...
to replace Se Chan...
who couldn't make it today.
- Of course.
- He's better than enough.
- I know.
- Se Chan is not here.
- No, he's not.
- You didn't know, did you?
- I had no idea.
- He couldn't make it.
If he were here,
he would've done
an impression of you.
"Hello. I'm Jang Hyuk."
Hyuk, you look like
you are about to cry.
- I'm not crying.
- Your eyes are moist.
- That's not true.
- No?
No way. He's a real man.
What are you talking about?
You should give him rice.
He cries while eating rice.
Why?
You know the drama.
- He cried while eating.
- He's your friend.
Was it a rice ball?
- It was rice and soup, right?
- Yes, it was.
- By the way, Hyuk...
- No, it was an egg.
I know Jong Kook is your friend,
but why don't you get upset at him?
- We're friends.
- Is that why?
I parked my car at his place.
I see. He parked his car at your place,
so he can't be mad.
- That's right.
- That's why.
Hyuk has done Jit Kune Do
for a long time.
So we prepared the Wing Chun Dummy.
- Show us.
- That's the Wing Chun Dummy.
- Is it called the WingChun Dummy?
- Yes.
I saw it
in "The Little Dragon Maiden."
You saw it in the movie, right?
(The training from the movie
you'd want to try yourself)
We saw that in a movie,
but we don't know how to use it.
- Do you want me to hold this?
- Have you tried this lately?
- I haven't done this in a while.
- It's been a while, right?
Go ahead and practice it.
Show us how to use it.
- Go ahead and touch it.
- Right.
Hang on. I need to take this off.
All right.
I need to take this off.
He looks sturdy.
Look at his muscles.
- No, it's not like that.
- You look good in a turtleneck.
I know, right?
He says a turtleneck.
- You look good in a turtleneck.
- You look fit.
Jong Kook is a little too big.
But you look perfect.
Okay.
I should touch it like this.
- I see. Like water flows.
- You should stroke it.
- It goes like this.
- I see.
- Like this.
- So you hit it like that.
It looks like waves.
It's like a dance move.
- It's flexible.
- Right.
- So this is it.
- I watched it before.
- I watched it.
- That's it.
- I know this move.
- He's really good at this.
- And you speed up.
- You're good.
Make it harder.
Speed up.
This is how I start.
- My gosh.
- That's good.
(He speeds up
as the audience requests.)
(Flashy)
- Oh, dear.
- My goodness.
That's amazing.
(Jang Hyuk is so cool.)
- That's awesome.
- Hey.
(Groaning)
- That's awesome.
- Hey.
That was really cool.
This is my first time thinking
you looked really cool.
- So this is how it works.
- That was amazing.
Haha, are you all right?
I couldn't hold out.
So this is how you do it.
So Min, you should try.
At first...
(Wriggling)
- She just does as she's told.
- Look at her face.
- Her face...
- The look on her face...
When she's told to do something,
she just tries.
She gives it a try anyway.
She's good.
- But...
- All right.
- This is...
- It's not bad.
She's pretty good.
She's good.
(She just punches it.)
- So Min.
- She just punches it.
Do you even know what you're doing?
This was harder than I thought.
- It's hard to hit it.
- Ji Hyo, you try it.
- Ji Hyo.
- That was pretty good.
I bet Ji Hyo is good.
- She'll do it for real.
- Ji Hyo is...
My goodness.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- My goodness.
- What's with her?
- My gosh.
What are you doing?
(She suddenly starts dancing.)
- You're not at a club.
- What's with you?
Ji Hyo, this isn't a club.
You're not at a club, Ji Hyo.
The reason you hit it is...
- Hang on.
- You should block it.
It's like...
Let's say he's trying to punch me.
- I block it, then attack.
- I see.
- This is what we do.
- That's so cool.
He kept doing this at the funeral.
- Really?
- That was amazing.
It goes like this.
- So that's how you block an attack.
- That's what you do.
- So this is...
- Jae Suk.
Ji Hyo told me to try it.
So Min wants me to attack her.
I want to try.
Suk Jin, try punching me once.
Slowly.
So Min wants me to attack her.
- Slowly.
- I'll do it.
- Hang on.
- I think you'll be too fast.
I'll make it slow.
- I'll block it and hit you back.
- Okay.
(What?)
(This isn't what they promised.)
But So Min is...
- I feel bad for her.
- So Min is...
Are you all right?
- So Min.
- So Min, come here.
- You told me to attack you.
- I'll do it.
You know what?
So Min calls me
after she does things like this.
So Min calls me and says,
"Jae Suk."
"What's with Kim Jong Kook?"
(So Min after the shoot)
- "When I try to do something..."
- She can't do anything.
"When I try to do something..."
"What on earth is with Jong Kook?"
(Encore performance)
Gosh, they are...
The two sisters are really funny.
- They're funny.
- They are so funny.
Today, you are meeting...
with Donnie Yen,
the world's famous action star.
Donnie Yen is coming to Korea today.
So he's on his way here now.
He says he's bringing
his prized possessions for you.
- Really?
- Are you serious?
So you'll be doing the race
for Donnie Yen's prized possessions.
It's called The Colorful Master
of Martial Arts.
After each mission,
you'll get swords
of the color you chose...
for the Pirate Roulette Game.
Donnie Yen will play
the Pirate Roulette Game...
with the swords you gather
during the race.
If the Pirate pops out
with the sword of your color,
- you win the prize.
- I see.
- I'll be sure to win this prize.
- Me too.
I'll give it to my dad.
We will start
the first mission, then.
- What is it?
- I'll explain the first mission.
All right, Donnie Yen.
- It's about balancing.
- It must be difficult.
I'll explain the rules.
The first mission is called
The Unknown Master of Martial Arts.
You'll get on the circular platform
as the masters of martial arts.
You will attack
one of the two people...
standing next to you
with the edge of the hand.
If you touch the person's arm
between the hand and the elbow,
you succeed.
The ones standing
next to the attacker...
can change their posture...
to avoid the attack.
You will be ranked
according to the result of the game.
Okay.
(The players step up.)
- I'm scared.
- My gosh.
Let's decide who will go first.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- The first one to go?
- Yes. We should decide.
Seok Sam, you go first.
All right. You go first.
- It goes counterclockwise.
- Okay.
If you fall off, you're eliminated.
Is Jong Kook the next one to go?
You shouldn't fall off.
You're eliminated if you fall.
- My gosh.
- This is no joke.
What do I do?
You're eliminated if you fall.
(The fake martial artists
brace themselves.)
I'll get rid of you.
This is...
(Shaking)
Gosh, this is no joke.
(The game starts.)
- Who goes first?
- Who's first?
- Seok Sam.
- Me?
(Shouting)
(The attack fails.)
He has never tried martial arts.
(So Min is up next.)
- Is it your turn?
- Sure.
No. It's his turn.
- No, it's her.
- It's me.
You should've said it was your turn.
It's clockwise.
- Why... So Min...
- Excuse me.
- You should've said that.
- It's So Min's turn.
I could dodge it.
- I thought it was his turn.
- Fold your arm.
- My gosh.
- You guys...
never give each other a break.
I didn't try to defend at all.
- You hit me here.
- Okay.
- It's from here to here.
- You can't fold your arms.
Around the forearm muscles.
(It's Jae Suk's turn.)
Who's his target?
(Jang Hyuk?)
(Or Haha?)
Go ahead and do it. This is hard.
(A surprise attack)
(They just take it out
on each other.)
Hey.
- This is fun.
- He's so annoying.
Okay.
He's so annoying.
(Jae Suk lost his right arm
when he was off his guard.)
He was off his guard.
- Gosh, this is...
- He's quiet, but he's strong.
- It's Jong Kook's turn, right?
- Yes.
(It's the most dangerous man,
Excited Kim Jong Kook.)
I have a bad feeling.
He got hit.
- He got it.
- Get off.
- But you're...
- You're eliminated.
- You're out.
- Get off.
- Give me three arms.
- You're out.
I want three arms.
- Give me three arms.
- Just get off.
- Why are you being like this?
- My gosh.
I'm so upset.
(The next attacker is So Min.)
- All right.
- You got hit.
No, he hit my watch.
- Your watch...
- It was the watch.
- Your arm is cut.
- That's ambiguous.
- The watch.
- It was the watch.
- It's ambiguous.
- He hit the watch.
- You're safe.
- It's thick.
- Okay. You're safe.
- This is a foul.
- You hit the watch.
- The watch.
- You weren't here.
It didn't start yet.
- I hit you.
- You got hit.
(Upset)
(Little Ha breaks forth with anger.)
You got hit.
(The strange action scene
only hurts your ears.)
You're out. Get off.
Why would I get off?
- Hey, switch with me.
- You got hit.
- What are you talking about?
- No.
Just get off.
- Give me three arms.
- I...
- I hit him first.
- All right. Let's do it again.
You two will do it again.
- Haha goes first.
- Haha, you first.
- This is so upsetting.
- He hit me over here.
I'm strong enough to cut the watch.
They are being childish.
- He's safe. And I'll go next.
- You two are safe. Haha goes next.
- I'm next to go.
- Are you sweating?
- Yes. I'm sweating.
- Look at Jong Kook.
This is so fun. Can I join you?
- I go first.
- Why?
- Hyung In told me to go first.
- All right.
- We should move like this.
- Do you have both hands?
Gosh...
Gosh. He's so cheap.
(Dirty)
- He's so crafty.
- Hey, So Bal.
Just come here.
Who's turn is it?
Is your right arm out?
My right arm is out. Hyuk hit it.
Hyuk is next.
Nice.
(Jae Suk is eliminated.)
- Okay.
- That wasn't even close.
So Min is still up there.
So Min still has one arm.
(So Min is still alive,
but Jong Kook is up next.)
- You're making me sweat.
- Do you think you can dodge it?
Do you think you can dodge it?
- You think?
- Make it quick.
It was the wrist.
- You got hit.
- So Min, come here.
Hurry and come.
It's already over.
Close the distance.
Let's shake it.
- Seriously.
- All right.
- Okay.
- This is disappointing.
All right. Good.
It was really scary.
(Haha's attack is successful.)
He's good.
(Shouting)
He hit me.
(Roaring)
(With the martial art masters'
flashy movements,)
(3 arms got eliminated
only in 5 seconds.)
Gosh, this is really fun.
- My gosh.
- He's in trouble.
(Right at the moment...)
He's in trouble.
(Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
You shouldn't move.
You can't move like that.
(He's so terrified that his eyes,
nose, and mouth become petty.)
(Groaning)
(Will Haha be able to survive?)
- Haha... Is he doing it? No?
- He'll go right away.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
- Is it Jong Kook?
(Haha is eliminated.)
- It's the two friends.
- All right.
They each have one arm left.
Only one arm?
It's Hyuk's turn, right?
- But Hyuk was...
- Show us your Jit Kune Do.
His posture looks cool.
- He's different.
- He looks stable.
(It's Jang Hyuk's turn to attack.)
His posture looks cool.
- He's different.
- He looks stable.
(It touched!)
(Laughing)
- That was really fun.
- Okay.
- He hit him.
I've never seen Jong Kook
sweat like that before.
- It was a lot of fun.
- He's sweating a lot.
It was fun.
That was a workout.
- That was fun.
- You will be rewarded by rank.
The winner will get seven swords.
- I should've won this.
- Second place will get six,
third will get five, and so on.
I should've done better.
- First of all...
- That's a huge gap.
The winner will go first
and choose the sword they want.
- Then...
- The game was very important.
The game was important.
Exactly. You should've told us that.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- If we had known...
We wouldn't have
fooled around like that.
- Every game is important.
- Red.
- The red one?
- Yes.
(Jang Hyuk gets 7 red swords.)
Wait. Am I next?
I choose black.
(Jong Kook gets 6 black swords.)
- Next.
- These look cool.
- Haha.
- Can I choose whatever I want?
- I choose the gold one.
- Gold?
- Ji Hyo.
- I'll take the blue one.
- White.
- Yellow-green.
Do I take what's left?
You will change clothes before
moving on to the next mission.
- Okay.
- Got it.
But what I'm wearing is comfortable.
- Anyway, Donnie Yen will be here.
- Donnie Yen.
We watched a lot of Donnie's movies.
- Of course.
- Exactly.
"Ip Man" and...
I even watched
"Seven Swords" yesterday.
- Really?
- I watched "Seven Swords."
- Ji Hyo's father...
- He's a huge fan.
He's a big fan of Donnie's.
He's a fan?
Mr. Young Chang is a huge fan.
(The world star has fans
all over the world.)
Who's Young Chang?
That's my father.
- Anyway, when he gets here...
- Yes?
You should know
that he has a busy schedule.
- Of course.
- Of course, he's busy.
We've been abroad as well, remember?
- We know how it is.
- Exactly.
Even though Donnie
wants to stay longer,
- he can't.
- Exactly.
It's why we'll be
squeezing the games in.
Hyuk. Isn't it your first time...
- seeing Donnie Yen?
- That's right.
- Haven't you been a fan?
- I have no doubt about it.
Well, of course.
- From movies like "Ip Man"...
- Exactly.
"Blade 2."
- He looked cool in "Blade 2."
- He was in that movie.
- Was he in "Blade 2?"
- He was.
- This time around...
- You have no idea.
You should know that he'll be in
"John Wick: Chapter 4."
- He's in that movie.
- Yes, in "John Wick: Chapter 4."
- Is he in that movie?
- Yes, "John Wick: Chapter 4."
- It'll hit the theaters in March.
- You should know...
- that he's a Hollywood celebrity.
- Exactly.
- He has international fame.
- Of course.
For some reason, Donnie Yen...
- He reminds me of Nam Chang Hee.
- Yes, Chang Hee.
- Why isn't he here today?
- As you know,
- he mimics Donnie a lot.
- From this.
They're practically the same.
- It'll be our first encounter.
- Exactly.
But he'll seem oddly familiar.
- They look exactly the same.
- Exactly.
(Fake Donnie Yen)
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- He...
- They look exactly the same.
He mimics the facial expressions
of Donnie Yen doing martial arts.
It's him in action scenes.
We talked about...
- having Chang Hee over.
- You should know...
that his facial expressions...
resemble that of Donnie Yen.
- I agree.
- He has gotten better looking.
That's right.
- What...
- Hold on.
What's going on?
I can't believe it.
- He must be here.
- He's here.
- Behind us.
- Where is he?
(With the soundtrack
from his legendary movie "Ip Man")
(He got off the plane and came
straight over to Running Man.)
- It's Donnie Yen.
- Where?
(Donnie Yen)
- It's Donnie Yen.
- Master!
(The man who is welcomed
with cheers)
Master!
(Along with Bruce Lee,
Jackie Chan, and Jet Li,)
(he is a legendary action star
of the Great China Region.)
(The leading man in "Ip Man"
who captivated the world.)
Donnie Yen!
(Even at 61 years of age,
he is still in his prime.)
He looks so young.
No way.
- He looks so young.
- He looks young for his age.
(Eyes light up
for the fans of Donnie Yen.)
Can we say hello?
Since Donnie Yen is here,
- we should ask him...
- Right.
- to greet the viewers.
- Yes.
Hello, everybody in Korea.
I'm Donnie Yen.
It's really nice to be here.
I'm very happy...
- The Year of the Rabbit.
- That's right.
I wish everybody
health and happiness.
- Yes!
- All right!
Happy New Year.
You have a good voice.
Why don't we talk more after we sit?
Let's have a seat.
(Talking with
an international celebrity)
He's so cool.
You should know that...
he's older than Suk Jin.
- That's right.
- I'm amazed.
- Doesn't he look young for his age?
- He does.
Since a young age,
he learned tai chi.
- He trained...
- Yes.
by getting up at 6 a.m.
- They do it a lot in the park.
- This... Right.
My mother ran a dojo
when I was a young boy.
She woke me up at 5 a.m...
and had me train in martial arts.
Is that so?
We have a video of him
honing his techniques...
and building a muscular body.
- Right? We have one prepared.
- Great.
He must really be flexible.
I had no idea he'd be that flexible.
He's really flexible.
- No way.
- Look at his splits.
Check out his fists.
His punches are fast.
- Gosh.
- Check out his body.
Should you be looking
at the camera like that?
Donnie, you're glaring
at the camera.
Should you be doing that?
I try to train as much as I can
when I have the time.
I've been doing martial arts
since I was a kid...
and have been filming movies
for 40 years since I was 19.
- For 40 years.
- Yes, for 40 years.
It must get old though.
- I respect him a lot.
- Yes.
Hyuk gets up early...
- to train as well.
- Really?
He has been working out every day
for over 20 years.
- For 27 years.
- He has never skipped a day.
For 27 years?
- I worked out every day.
- Bodybuilding?
Bodybuilding, boxing,
- and everything else.
- Boxing too?
Anyway,
- the Wing Chun Dummy...
- Right.
Can we ask Donnie
to give us a demonstration?
Good idea.
- I'd like to demonstrate.
- Can you do it?
Can I do it?
There you go.
But...
- But I'm old.
- Can...
I know, but it's fine.
Just slightly.
Then, Donnie Yen...
- A brief demonstration.
- Yes, a brief one.
(What will the action star
of 40 years show us?)
I can't believe
I'm getting to see this in person.
I can't wait.
Donnie will demonstrate
how one trains with this.
- I'm getting to see this in person.
- Exactly.
(He begins.)
(The expert shows his power moves.)
(Gosh)
No way.
(No one can afford to even blink.)
- My gosh.
- No way.
(The end)
(You couldn't look away
from the action star's movements.)
Donnie, no way.
- He said he'd go gentle.
- I can't believe it.
It's why I wasn't expecting much.
- Go ahead.
- I can't.
Hyuk, go ahead.
Show us.
- Take this off.
- Hyuk, come on.
Drop the bag and show us.
- That's right.
- Show us.
- I'm excited.
- I do it...
- in a different style though.
- I see.
(Take that!)
It's not like what you did earlier.
(Donnie Yen is watching.)
- This isn't like before.
- This isn't what you did earlier.
- He's serious.
- You're taking this seriously.
Hey.
Look at him taking this seriously.
This isn't like before.
You devoted yourself just now.
- You did your best.
- Very good.
- You tried really hard.
- What do you think?
What did you think?
It was really nice.
- It was really nice.
- Really?
Wing Chun Kuen and Jit Kune Do.
He executed them both well.
What you did
was Jit Kune Do, right?
Yes, I can tell.
The side steps
were from Jit Kune Do.
It's a little different.
He has a good understanding
of martial arts.
The demonstration he gave us...
I mean...
- It was different.
- Yes, it seemed different.
It seemed different to me.
The level of energy was different.
Could we perhaps learn...
- something simple?
- Could he teach us a few moves?
- Something we can learn.
- Just one.
How about a simple move?
This is Wing Chun Kuen.
(He starts off
with the Wing Chun Kuen.)
- His moves.
- They're different.
(There's energy coming
from even his fingertips.)
- His moves.
- He's extending his hand...
so that he can pull it back.
- I see.
- He then pulls it back.
- No way.
- Rotate the wrist.
(Take that!)
What a powerful move.
(Donnie suddenly teaches them
a few more moves.)
Did you see that?
I could feel his energy.
Wing Chun Kuen is
a form of martial arts...
from the Southern Chinese region.
Did you see this move?
It's like a tiger.
(The moves embody those of a tiger.)
It's like a dragon, right?
- A dragon.
- Like this?
You know Jackie Chan.
Jackie Chan.
- Drunken boxing.
(He suddenly performs
drunken boxing.)
(He's just a drunkard.)
That was so cool.
Did you see his drunken boxing?
- His drunken boxing?
- Tell me about it.
Yes, like Jackie Chan.
(When mimicked by him,
he looks like a drunkard.)
I can't believe it.
Anyway, Donnie Yen
is joining us today.
I doubt we'll spend all day
just talking to him.
- Just as you were informed earlier,
- Yes.
you will play a game
where you will win swords.
- What's the game?
- The game is...
Martial Arts Foot Volleyball.
- Martial Arts Foot Volleyball?
- Yes.
Along with Donnie Yen,
you will play foot volleyball
in two teams of four.
Foot volleyball?
I wonder if he's played it before.
- Foot volleyball.
- Does he know the rules?
Have you ever played
foot volleyball?
- Can you play foot volleyball?
- I don't know.
- Oh, you don't know?
- He doesn't seem to know.
- It's similar to volleyball.
- He'll learn fast.
The basic rules are the same
as regular foot volleyball,
but whenever you touch the ball,
you should make the sound...
that reminds you of martial arts
that your opponent team chooses.
- Like yelling, "Abyo?"
- Yes, just like that.
- "Abyo!"
- Oh, I see.
If you don't make the sound,
your opponent team gets one point.
- Okay. Got it.
- The first team...
- to get 31 points wins.
- Okay.
The members of the winning team...
- will receive seven knives.
- Seven knives?
- Oh, the winning team?
- The losing team gets five knives.
- Got it.
- Okay. I understand.
- We divided you into two teams.
- Yes.
- I'll start with the four-member team.
- Okay.
- Hyuk,
- Oh, my.
Jae Suk, Haha, and So Min
are on the same team.
- So Min is on my team?
- So Min is on the other team.
- The ones on Donnie's team...
- So the rest of us...
- We're on Donnie's team.
- are Suk Jin,
- Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.
- Oh, yes.
- Okay.
- We're on the same team.
- I'm on your team.
- Yes.
- Great.
- We'll move to the back...
- We're on Donnie's team.
- to begin the game.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Then Hyuk and I...
Hyuk, have you played it before?
- While serving in the military.
- That's good enough.
- I'll receive the ball at the back.
- Okay. You do that.
Can we pass the ball
as many times as we want?
- We can only pass it three times.
- Before...
- Okay. I understand.
- Yes.
- Okay. We'll begin.
- That's one.
- One and...
- And two.
- Two.
- You go.
- And three.
- Okay.
- Nice.
(Donnie kicks the ball
over the net easily.)
- Is this your 1st time?
- Yes, this is my 1st time.
Oh, my. Why are you so good?
- Indeed. Donnie is so good at this.
- No.
Two.
That's good.
He's amazing as expected.
You can also kick it over the net
without passing it.
- Oh, okay.
- Yes.
- Okay?
(Screaming)
It went out.
- He got too excited.
- Why would he do that?
- He's trying to impress Donnie.
- Exactly.
- Why did you kick it so hard?
- Gosh, seriously.
Oh, yes.
And do we have to make the sound?
- Yes, we have to make the sound.
- What sound?
- A kung fu sound.
- "Woo."
- Yes, whatever you want.
- "Ada!"
- Yes.
- Exactly. Okay.
- What do you want?
- You choose.
- You pick one.
- What do you want? Wing Chun Kuen?
- How about this?
- Yes?
- Instead of a high-pitched shout,
- how about a low-pitched shout?
- A high-pitched shout?
- Ha!
- Like this.
- Hey, you.
- We should shout, "Ha?" Okay.
- Try it.
- Ha!
- So Min, try it.
(Shouting weirdly)
- That's not it.
- Lower your pitch more.
- Ha.
- How do I do that?
- My gosh.
- You can do as you just did.
- Ha.
- Lower your pitch. Good.
We want a very high-pitched shout.
- A high-pitched shout.
- How? Show us.
- Abyo!
- Right.
- Abyo! Okay.
- That's good.
- Abyo!
- That's right.
- Abyo! Okay.
- Okay.
- Okay. That's great.
- Abyo!
- Good. Donnie's ready.
- Okay.
If you don't make the sound,
your opponent team gets one point.
Got it. If we don't make the sound.
My throat hurts already.
- Abyo!
- Right.
I'm sorry, but this is Donnie's
first time playing this game.
- So please go easy on him.
- All right.
Will Donnie play in the back row?
- He should play in the front row.
- It's up to him.
Your position is there.
- He should be in the front row.
- Oh, okay.
- He should play in the front row.
- The main position.
- Okay. That's good.
- Oh, I'm covering him.
- I'm covering Donnie.
- It's an attack position.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
Which team should serve first?
- How about rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
- You serve first.
- We'll begin without practicing.
- Okay.
I'll receive the ball by heading it.
- Let's do this!
- We've got this!
- Abyo!
- Ha!
Hey, what was that?
(She headed the ball
toward the floor.)
Let it go to us
when the ball comes like that.
- So Min, I told you several times.
- Also...
- So Min, you should make the sound.
- Right. Why didn't you shout?
She didn't shout either.
(Donnie is thoroughly
checking the play.)
The score is 2 to 0.
He's quite strict.
- Why didn't you say "abyo?"
- Oh, I forgot.
(He didn't make the sound.)
(The game continues for now.)
Suk Jin, head the ball.
- Good.
- What are you doing?
- You should've shouted, "Abyo!"
- Why did you kick it here?
- What did I do?
- "Abyo!"
It was hard to receive.
No, it wasn't. You should've stepped
back and received it.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
- You didn't shout when serving.
- You should shout when serving too.
- Go ahead. I'll receive it.
- Okay.
- I'll start.
- Our team is doing well.
Go easy on us since Donnie is here.
- We're invincible.
- Ha!
- I said, take it easy. Okay!
- Gosh.
(The boy monk from Shaolin Temple
made a ridiculous mistake.)
What's wrong with you?
- Hey, Donnie...
- Donnie hasn't touched the ball.
It's 2 to 2.
- Oh, it's 3 to 2.
- Do you want to try it?
- Sure.
- Just one time.
- Can I bounce it...
- Say, "Abyo!"
- Yes. Whatever you want.
- Can I bounce it?
- I'm sure he'll do well.
- Yes.
He seemed good at kicking a ball.
- Okay. Ready?
- Okay.
(Everyone is excited to see
the martial arts master serve.)
- Okay. Yes?
- Donnie. Abyo!
- Abyo!
- Oh, my. That's great.
- Nice.
- He's good at kicking a ball.
- You should kick like that.
- Right.
- You should shout.
- He didn't make the sound.
- Jae Suk, you didn't shout.
- Oh, right. Oh, man.
- He didn't make the sound.
- Gosh, I forgot to shout.
- He's good at kicking a ball.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Suk Jin,
and Donnie didn't shout.)
- Right. We didn't shout.
- Why didn't you make the sound?
- Right.
- Why didn't you shout?
- Come here.
- Sorry.
- Abyo!
(They focused on the game so much
that they forget to shout.)
- Sorry. Okay.
- Abyo!
Can't we play the game
without shouting?
- Right.
- Abyo!
- So we don't have to shout?
- We'll play it without that rule.
- I can shout if I want, right?
- Okay.
- To make it simpler for Donnie.
- I see. Okay.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
- I just want to do it.
- You don't have to.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Haha, what's with you today?
- It's okay.
Haha, what's with you today?
- What's with Haha?
- Head it. Okay!
- Okay!
- Ji Hyo, head it!
- That's good.
- Okay!
- Good.
- Here.
- That's great.
- Hyuk, here you go. Hurry.
- Oh, my. He did well.
(K-Donnie Yen kicks the ball!)
- Great! Oh, no!
- Okay.
(But the original Donnie Yen
made a mistake.)
- Okay.
- I wanted to do this.
- That's allowed, right?
- I can do that, right? Can't I?
- Oh, like this?
- I can't? Okay.
- Yes, you can.
- Thank you, Hyuk.
- Don't mention it.
- Nice.
- He's so fast as always.
I'm really bad at this.
Oh, no. We're losing.
- What are you going to do?
- You go ahead.
- You can do it.
- That's good.
- Nice!
- Oh, my.
(Right then, K-Donnie Yen smashed
the ball unexpectedly!)
(He scored a point neatly.)
- Great job, Hyuk.
- That was good.
- That was really good.
- My gosh.
That was a Jit Kune Do kick.
- That was a Jit Kune Do kick.
- It was the taekgyeon style.
- A Jit Kune Do kick.
- That was great.
- He did a Jit Kune Do kick.
- Right.
Big bro, you can do the same thing,
okay?
- Like this? Okay.
- Yes. Okay.
- I'll serve.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Nice.
- Receive it.
- Good.
(The ball hit the net.)
Okay... Oh, no. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- By the way, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- You're so generous toward Donnie.
- He's generous, indeed.
- If it was me, he would've yelled.
- You don't treat us like that.
- It's his first time playing this.
- He's so strict toward us.
- Okay. Big bro.
- Me?
- Should I try again?
- Yes. You try it.
I'll try it.
- Okay!
- Let's do this.
- Good.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Mine.
- Okay.
(The martial arts master
served neatly again.)
- Oh, good.
- Okay.
- That's good. Okay. Big bro!
- Receive it.
- Okay.
- Head it. Big bro!
- Big bro!
- Donnie.
(He kicked in the air.)
Why?
- Big bro!
- Donnie.
(Shrieking with disappointment)
(He makes a mistake
when he's out of the serving zone.)
- What a shame.
- Don't worry. It's okay.
- Okay!
- Okay.
- Nice.
- It's good.
Let's let them win one point.
- Let's give them one point.
- You're very strong.
We should be more modest
and considerate of the other team.
- Let's be considerate of them.
- He's being considerate of us.
We're losing.
- Our team is doing well.
- Kick it lightly.
- I'll serve. Let's do this!
- Okay.
Give So Min a chance to kick it.
This is so much fun.
- Okay. Mine.
- Go.
- Big bro!
- How he calls Donnie is funny.
- Okay!
- Good.
- Suk Jin. Head it.
- Okay.
- Okay. This is good.
- Pass it. Big bro!
- Wait. Big bro!
(Stepping backward)
- Okay!
- That's good.
(Donnie kicks the ball when he hears
"big bro" like Pavlov's dog.)
- Okay.
- Mine! Big bro!
(Jong Kook passes it
to Donnie again.)
(The purgatory
of being called nonstop)
- My gosh. Hey.
- Okay.
- Oh, I made a mistake.
- Okay!
(Home run)
- Okay.
- Great.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Okay. He's good at this, right?
- You keep passing the ball...
- He's good at this, right?
You pass the ball to him every time.
- He's our hitter.
- You want to see him kick the ball.
- I'm under a lot of pressure now.
- Okay.
(He didn't feel this much pressure
even in Hollywood.)
But it's really good
that you pass the ball to him.
- No pressure.
- No pressure? Okay.
- Donnie is very good at this.
- Indeed.
- Let's applaud him!
- He's really good at this.
(Seok Sam serves this time
since Donnie feels pressured.)
- Good.
- Haha.
Okay.
- Okay.
- You should kick it over the net.
(He barely managed to save
the ball!)
- Good job.
- Nice!
- Big bro!
- "Big bro."
(Again?)
- Oh, boy.
- Oh, no.
(Big bro failed to overcome
the pressure in the end.)
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
- You should've saved it.
- You...
- put too much pressure on him.
- I thought he'd kick it over.
If he failed to kick it over,
you should've saved it.
- Hey.
- I thought he'd kick it over.
- Even so, you should've saved it.
- I'm sorry. I thought...
(Are they fighting because of me?)
You're putting too much pressure
on Donnie.
- No, I'm not.
- Donnie must be feeling...
- It's my fault. I made a mistake.
- I mean...
- I was just saying...
- You're putting pressure on him.
- He can make a mistake sometimes.
- Don't put pressure on him.
You should've saved it
since he made a mistake.
I thought he'd kick it over the net.
I'm really sorry.
- This is his first time.
- All right. I just thought...
- he would kick it over.
- Stop putting pressure on him.
All right. Let's go.
- All right. Let's go. That's good.
- Okay.
- You'll receive it, right?
- That was really good.
Suk Jin.
- That's good. Head it.
- Good.
Ji Hyo, head it. Hey, you brat!
(She missed the ball.)
- Hello.
- Was that drunken boxing?
- Hi. You're very polite.
- You should wait until it comes up.
- Why didn't you just pass it?
You should've hit it
when it bounced back up.
- Didn't I do that?
- No, you didn't.
- You hit it when it was going over.
- Let's go.
(Donnie serves again.)
- Good. Nice.
- He serves really well.
- Donnie...
- That's good. Okay!
- Hey.
- Kick it over.
- Okay!
- Okay.
- Save it. Gosh.
- He cheated.
(He hit the ball with his hand.)
- Why would he use his hand?
- That's not allowed.
- I'm sorry.
- You shouldn't use your hand.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Why would he...
He hit the ball with his hand.
He told Donnie not to use his hand
earlier.
- I'm sorry, everyone.
- He felt rushed.
The rallies end too quickly.
I'll do it. Okay. I'll serve.
- He's good at it.
- He's good.
- Donnie is good at kicking.
- Nice.
- I'll do my best.
- Okay.
Hit it.
Oh, my.
That worked.
(Bowing)
- Hyuk, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Hey, Hyuk.
- Nice!
- Are you okay? Hyuk...
- Are you okay? Your face...
That was good.
(Proud)
- Hyuk...
- That was good.
- Give us the ball.
- Hyuk is bad at this too.
(He laughed while saying,
"Hyuk is bad at this too.")
I'm not that bad at this.
It's just that it rarely shows
because of So Min.
- But he makes small mistakes.
- Okay.
- Let's begin.
- Okay. Let's go.
- I should receive it.
- That was hilarious.
We must win.
- Go.
- Big bro.
- Oh, my.
- That's sharp.
(The low, straight serve)
Right. That was sharp.
- He got the hang of it.
- I see that he's a fast learner.
Right. That was sharp.
(Donnie got the hang of it.)
I see that he's a fast learner.
It seems that Donnie...
Do you want to serve again?
- No.
- Serve again, please.
- I can only...
- Donnie got the hang of it.
Right. We won't go easy on you.
Do you hear me?
- Mine.
So Min, come here.
- You know...
- Why...
Why do you keep kicking the ball
toward us?
- So Min.
- Come over here for a second.
- Why would you do that?
It's a little dark around here.
- Where should I stand?
- So can you hold the light?
(He suggests she should touch
the light instead of the ball.)
- Okay?
- Okay. Good.
Then I'll stand here for now.
Stand right in front of the net...
and kick the ball over the net.
It'll be easy.
Let me cover the area behind you.
I guess Hyuk realized
how bad I'm at this.
- He told me not to move back.
- Right. Just stay...
- in front of the net.
- He told me to stay here.
It's our turn.
I'll serve like Ip Man.
Abyo!
I'll serve like Ip Man. Abyo!
- Oh, man.
- Hyuk.
(Did he try to hit it
with his shoulder?)
- Hyuk, what's the matter?
- What was that?
- Why did you do that?
- I tried to use my shoulder.
- Why did you move your head...
- like this? What was that?
- I'm sorry.
Gosh, seriously.
- Hey, what will you do?
- So Min. Okay!
- Okay!
- So Min, come here.
Good. Okay!
(As So Min keeps doing a bad job...)
Why did you use your hand?
- Ji Hyo!
- Okay!
- Okay.
- Good.
Come on, Suk Jin.
- You hit it with your forehead.
- Okay.
It was very difficult.
- You need only one point to win.
This is it.
We shouldn't let them win.
Let's score another point.
- Okay.
- Yes. Good. It's okay.
Move to your right.
They only need one more point.
- Suk Jin, move to your right. Yes.
- Okay.
- Let's end the game.
- All right.
- Okay.
(Haha serves
while there's tension in the air.)
- Okay.
- It floated high.
- Big bro.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin, move. Oh, it's good.
- Good. Great job.
- Okay.
- Good. Great job. He's moving.
- Okay!
- Good.
- Great.
- Let's end it now. Let's win.
- Okay. Let's go.
The score is 30 to 30.
Both teams need only one point.
- Is it a deuce?
- Only one point.
- Or just 1 point...
- The 1st team to get 1 point wins.
- Got it.
- We can't let them win.
When any of the teams gets a point,
the game will end.
Yes, it ends
when any of us gets a point.
Let's win. Let's not let them win.
(The last 1 point will determine
the result of the game.)
- We need only one point.
- Good.
That's easy, right?
- Be careful. Move.
- It's coming.
Okay! Mine!
- Big bro!
- Go!
- Okay!
- Mine!
- Good job.
- You did well.
- Mine!
- Big bro!
- Okay.
Go!
- Okay!
- Great job!
- Good. That was great.
- Mine.
Big bro!
- Go!
- That's great.
Okay.
- Big bro!
- Okay.
(Flinching)
Big bro.
(Oh, no.)
- It's okay.
- Okay.
(Donnie couldn't overcome
the pressure in the end.)
- We did it.
- Gosh. I'm so upset.
(Team Jae Suk wins.)
- Okay.
- Very good.
It was the foot volleyball game
that I won for the first time...
and where I touched the ball...
- more times than ever before.
- Come here.
Now, I'll tell you
how many swords you obtained...
- through the preliminary mission...
- Yes.
and the foot volleyball game
you played with Donnie.
The person in the first place...
who obtained 14 swords...
- Who is it?
- is Hyuk.
(Hyuk placed 1st.)
(K-Donnie who won both games
placed 1st.)
- Hyuk, you must be happy.
- Right. He came in first earlier.
He placed first earlier.
Hyuk got 14 swords.
Haha got 12 swords.
- Jong Kook got 11 swords.
- Yes.
- And So Min got ten swords.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo and Jae Suk got nine.
- Suk Jin got 6 swords.
- I got 6?
- Yes.
- Okay. Got it.
Now, Donnie will play
the Pirate Roulette Game.
- He can choose any color he wants.
- Oh, I see.
Oh, I choose it? I see.
- All right.
- The member who chose the color...
of the sword he uses
when it pops out...
- will get the prize.
- Okay. I understand.
(Donnie doesn't know
which member chose which color.)
Shall I start? Okay.
(What color will Donnie choose 1st?)
- What color will he choose?
- I think I'm going to choose...
Shall I start? Okay.
I think I'm going to choose red...
- because I like red color.
- Oh, I see. Okay.
(He chose Hyuk's sword.)
- Yes. Okay.
- Okay.
- Any color you want.
- Hold it.
- You can hold it. All right.
- Oh, I see.
- What?
- All right.
(The Pirate popped out
in his 1st attempt.)
- No way. That's impossible.
- Really?
(Hyuk beat the impossible odds...)
(and was chosen at once.)
- No way.
- What was that?
- That's it.
- No. We should do it over again.
- He got so lucky.
- He got lucky.
This is like making a hole-in-one.
- Congratulations. The winner...
- It rarely happens.
- to receive Donnie's items...
- It's almost impossible. Amazing.
is Hyuk who chose red.
- It's really amazing.
- Oh, my.
Hyuk, this is amazing.
(Signed DVDs of the "Ip Man" series
and his book on martial arts)
This is a great gift.
(Signed DVDs of the "Ip Man" series
and his book on martial arts)
This is the biography of Ip Man
that I wrote.
The other one is my book on kung fu.
That's awesome.
- His gift found the right owner.
- Hyuk must be happy.
- It found the right owner.
- Exactly.
We prepared a small gift
for Donnie...
- to thank him for coming here.
- Yes.
What is that?
What does it say?
- It's your name.
- Oh, I see. Okay.
- I wish you a happy new year.
I wish you all a happy new year.
(We thank Hyuk and Donnie for making
us laugh and fascinating us.)
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
Gosh, it's cold.
I heard we don't have to wear a mask
starting today.
There's still a Christmas tree here.
(The place is still filled with
winter vibes.)
Okay. One... So Min, come here.
- Come here.
- So Min, can you move aside?
- Oh, okay. Hello.
- I mean...
Seriously...
(A frog interrupted Jae Suk
when he was going to slate.)
One, two, three.
(He made the frog move
and managed to slate.)
I've never seen Mr. Kang Chan Hee
being so cold to me.
You sounded so cold-hearted.
You never talked to me like that.
- It was understandable.
- You sounded so cold-hearted.
Jong Kook, hurry up and come.
- Okay.
- Hello.
I must say, it's nice...
to be here
since the air is so fresh here.
- Hey.
- You're lying.
- There's a Christmas tree here.
- It's so nice.
- They haven't taken it down.
- Jong Kook.
Why do you look smaller
in tight clothes?
- This jacket is too small for me.
- Why is it too small for you?
- It makes his body look smaller.
- That's not good.
The T-shirt I'm wearing under it
is too small for me too.
- Look. It's so short.
- Right. I can see that.
- It's too small for me.
- Did you lose weight?
- No, I gained so much weight.
- It looks nice though.
- Pull it down like this.
- It looks okay, right?
- Yes.
- Is this a sleeveless shirt?
- I could wear it without pants.
- Exactly.
- Like this.
- Yes.
Jong Kook, didn't you wear
these pants last week?
Yes, I did.
- I've been wearing it every week.
- Hello.
Hi, Ji Hyo.
Hi, So Min.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Where's the elder?
- Where's Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin?
- Yes.
He's lying down.
- He hasn't come yet.
- He's breathing.
Is he not feeling well?
Seok Sam!
- Come on. Hurry up!
- Goodness.
- Stay focused.
- My gosh.
- Wait!
- Seok Sam.
Why are they rushing me like that?
It's still early.
He's wearing a nice hat.
- It's because...
- Ji Seok Sam!
his blood vessels might rupture
if he doesn't wear a winter hat.
- Really?
- You mean, in his ears?
- No, in his head.
- What are you talking about?
It's common for seniors.
That's why
my mother always wears a winter hat.
- You're wearing one too.
- Yes.
Stop lying. That's nonsense.
- While staying in a warm place...
- A sudden temperature drop...
- Haha is right about that.
- The blood vessels can rupture.
- Is that true?
- That's why he's wearing the hat.
- Seniors are more susceptible.
- He's wearing it as it's winter.
- It can be dangerous.
- They die all of a sudden?
Your glasses...
Don't put your prescription glasses
on top of your hat.
- Are those prescription glasses?
- Yes.
- He wanted it to look stylish.
- Really?
Don't put your prescription glasses
on top of your hat.
I can't see letters.
- He's here. Hello.
- Oh, my.
- Hello, Suk Jin.
- Superstar Ji!
- Sir, you're here.
- Hey.
Don't call me that.
Why did you guys gather so early?
- Sir, you're here.
- We had no choice.
- He hit Jae Suk.
- Why did you gather so early?
- His blood vessels could rupture.
- Jae Suk slited early.
- Sorry?
- It's not "slite."
- What do you mean by "slite?"
- It's "slate."
- She's so funny.
- That was good.
- Neck slice.
- Good job.
- Neck slice!
- That was good.
- Did you do that intentionally?
- She's a great entertainer.
- She's amazing.
- Slite.
Oh, look.
- Jae Suk.
- Why?
- I see you bought winter boots.
- Oh, right.
(He bought a new pair of shoes
as winter came.)
- You ruined my shoes last time.
- He must've been jealous of Haha.
- It's from Hunter.
- Haha.
- You wore my shoes last time.
- Haha, he must've been jealous.
And you got yourself
a new pair of winter boots?
- Exactly.
- He must've been jealous of Haha.
You bought winter boots?
- He must've been jealous.
- He bought similar boots.
(The similarity is 95 percent.)
- They're different from Haha's.
- Right. I can see the difference.
- Right. They look different.
- They're different.
Why are you wearing shoes
that are not warm today?
- I forgot to bring them.
- Oh, no.
- I feel bad.
- If he takes off his shoes,
it's over.
- Oh, no.
- He didn't bring them.
- What are you talking about?
- He didn't bring warm shoes.
- Hey.
- Why did you not bring them today?
He was worried
that someone might take them.
- That's why he left them at home.
- He was scared.
I heard you wear them
when sleeping too.
- "My shoes."
- You punk.
- You look good in them.
- They're nice, aren't they?
As expected, young ones
are not covering their ears.
Older ones
are all covering their ears.
- In case their blood vessels pop.
- Hey.
In case their blood vessels pop.
- Gosh.
- You're right.
Suk Jin, you dressed up today.
- What do you mean I dressed up?
- You're wearing long johns, right?
- It's quite short.
- He's wearing long johns.
- I'm not wearing long johns.
- No. Look.
- You're wearing them.
- Hey.
(Detective Jeon is on her way.)
(The long johns squad
is questioning him.)
Be gentle.
- Be gentle.
- He's wearing long johns.
- I'm wearing ones too.
- I'm not.
- Hey.
- He is...
- He's wearing ones.
- He's so weak.
- Hey, long johns...
- I'm not wearing ones.
He's so weak.
Jae Suk,
are you wearing long johns?
- No, I'm not.
- You're not?
- Young ones don't wear long johns.
- Young ones don't wear them.
- People in their 30s...
- Look. It's my skin.
- Come on.
- It's skin.
- He's young.
- That's unusual.
It's not unusual.
I usually don't wear them.
- I'm wearing ones.
- I'm wearing this too.
- You should wear them.
- You're wearing them too.
- His are thin, though.
- I'm wearing ones too.
- Jong Kook is sensitive to cold.
- Yes. He should wear them.
- I'm sensitive to cold.
It's cold.
- We're so young.
- Yes.
- Right?
- You have a muffler, but not me.
- That's true.
- I'm just wearing gloves.
- You're the youngest.
- Yes.
For today.
So Min, why? What are you doing?
I'm going to tuck it back.
It's so cold.
- Don't tuck it back.
- I'm cold.
You said you weren't cold.
Roll it up. Leave it like this.
- She's young.
- You bragged.
- You bragged. Leave it like this.
- Because she's young.
It's cool.
- Hurry and shut the clapperboard.
- Yes. Leave it like this.
Because you bragged about it,
keep bragging about it.
We're wearing them as we should,
but you're young.
- So wear your pants like that.
- We're wearing them...
because we're old.
Since you're young,
you roll your pants up too.
Roll them up.
- Roll them up.
- You roll them up too.
- Roll them up, you punk.
- Roll them up.
What are you?
- Oh, no.
- We...
- Are they calves or thighs?
- Look at his thighs.
Why do his thighs look like that?
Jae Suk.
- Are they calves or thighs?
- Oh, no.
- Why?
- What's wrong with your thighs?
Why? It's fine
as long as it was funny, right?
- It was funny.
- But they were too...
- Why? They're firm.
- They're like calves.
- It was funny.
- Don't worry.
His thighs are as big as his calves.
How is it possible?
(The leader of team long johns
is laughing so hard.)
His thighs are as big as my calves.
His legs are like toothpicks.
- Why?
- How can he walk with those?
- Isn't it okay?
- I'm sad.
- Don't worry.
Don't be sad. I'm healthy.
- But he's the healthiest.
- He's healthy.
- I'm the healthiest.
- He's the healthiest.
- This is nice.
- Anyway, what are we doing today?
- Where are we, by the way?
- Hongcheon.
Is it Hongcheon?
You came a long way
to Gangwon Province.
You're going to enjoy
a winter retreat...
in Gangwon Province,
the snow paradise.
Retreat sounds nice.
Winter this year
feels like real winter.
- It's real winter. It snowed a lot.
- Right?
The snow was beautiful.
It was like a picture on the way here.
- Today...
- It suddenly became "Frozen."
The rules for precious retreat time
are simple.
You will do what we planned.
- What you planned?
- Yes.
No matter
how much you're enjoying it,
you need to stop what you're doing
when the time comes...
to move on to the next one.
- What is it?
- It's the worst.
- I hate it the most.
- Like when the meal time is over,
- stop eating immediately...
- We can't eat?
- to do the next plan.
- That's not right.
Will we get enough time?
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Okay.
- We should follow their plans?
I hated having daily schedules
for vacations.
Then let me reveal
the schedule for the retreat.
- Okay.
- Are there many things to do?
- We should go grocery shopping.
- It's packed.
- We're taking a nap?
- "Opening and grocery shopping."
(Opening and grocery shopping,
moving, lunch, nap, recreation)
- "Opening and grocery shopping."
- Napping sounds good.
- Napping is good.
- Whose idea was it?
- That's amazing.
- Dried pollack kimchi sujebi,
dried pollack,
and Korean sand lance?
- Let's have Korean sand lances.
- It's good.
My father eats them a lot.
(Running Man retreat schedule:
Lunch from 10:30 a.m. to 12 p.m.)
(All sorts of winter delicacies
are here.)
(Dried pollack sujebi, grilled dried
pollack, and Korean sand lance)
- For lunch,
- Thin one.
- should we have this?
- Yes.
Including grilled dried pollack
and Korean sand lance?
- You should grill them.
- Do we have to eat them?
Not long ago,
I saw grilled Korean sand lance...
- on "Hometown Report."
- It's delicious.
- It looked delicious.
- Yes.
- It's good.
- The fish is as big as this.
- Grilling Korean sand lances.
- They're thin.
- Gangwon Province is famous...
- We'll finish the food quickly.
for many kinds of food,
- but dried pollacks are...
- That's right.
- Grilled dried pollacks are good.
- Grilling it over a briquette fire.
- On the gridiron.
- Over a briquette fire.
Dried pollack kimchi sujebi
sounds amazing.
- It's going to be so good.
- With sujebi...
We're going to have dried pollack
kimchi sujebi,
but it's going to become
dried pollack kimchi ramyeon.
- I'm right.
- They're dumbfounded.
- Ramyeon and sujebi are...
- Can't you see "sujebi" here?
- Without eating...
- There must be ramyeon noodles.
- Hey.
- Anyway, the broth is...
The broth is the same.
- Ramyeon...
- We'll take a nap without eating.
Right. We'll take a nap
without eating.
For sure.
Anyway,
I'm excited about this today.
But can we eat within this time?
- Thirty... What?
- Oh, right. Can we do it?
- The time limit looks fine.
- Can we cook and all?
- Are we cooking?
- Do we have to cook?
We should cook.
- We're doing it?
- That's why. Is it possible?
It took three hours to eat
last time.
- But you don't need to make a fire.
- We have to cook?
- What did you say?
- You don't have to make a fire.
- Do we have a gas stove?
- We should make a fire here.
- Don't do that.
- We should make a fire.
- If we make a fire, we can't do it.
- Making a fire...
- Don't do it.
- Right.
We were going to make a fire for you.
Will you make it yourself?
- Let's make a fire.
- We should do it ourselves.
Then we need one more hour for each.
- He's a fire evangelist.
- I mean...
Let's cook and make a fire
separately.
- Yes. We need to make a fire.
- Cook on a stove. I'll make a fire.
- It's his favorite thing.
- Yes. It's so warm.
- Playing with fire.
- Yes.
So it's grilled dried pollack
and Korean sand lance.
Wait. What time is it now?
- We should hurry up.
- It's nine.
- We should go grocery shopping now.
- We should go.
- Let's go.
- The first one is grocery shopping.
You saw the menu earlier.
- We should buy groceries too?
- You should get the ingredients...
that suit the winter trip
to Gangwon Province.
It's only 9:07 a.m.
We did a research
and set the appropriate price.
- How much is it?
It's 65 dollars.
- Come on. That's not enough.
- What?
Things are expensive these days.
- How many do you think we are?
- How much is a dried pollock?
We'll give you dried pollacks.
- Do you have them?
- There will be dried pollacks.
- You should just marinate it.
- How about Korean sand lances?
- We got sauce too.
- We need to get snacks too.
- But...
- We'll just need...
the main ingredients.
Do we have to get radish
and onions too?
This is not enough money.
We can't have chapsal donut then?
If you leave a little bit of money,
you can have them. It's so good.
- It must be good.
- What?
- You must have them at a market.
- I can see it right in front of me.
- Did you eat it already?
- Eat what?
- She had it already.
- She had donuts.
- She already had them.
- Twisted donuts.
- Let's have them later.
You can buy any groceries
with a budget of 65 dollars.
- Let's go to the market.
- Okay.
- Let's do grocery shopping.
- It's cold.
Let's go. Where is it?
The central market?
- Let's have twisted donuts first.
- Come here.
- No, Suk Jin.
We should buy the ingredients first
and get snacks later.
No. Where do they have
twisted donuts?
Where did Jae Suk go?
"Potatoes, zucchini, red chilies,
scallion, onion, radish,"
- "and flour."
- We can take some out.
- No. We need potatoes.
- We need potatoes.
- We should put potatoes in.
- We need zucchini too.
- Zucchini and potatoes.
- Zucchini.
- Let's just take out red chilies.
- Yes. Take them out.
Anyway, let's get twisted donuts
when we have money left.
- Yes. We'll have some left.
- We don't need kelp...
when we have anchovies.
We just need anchovies for broth.
Okay.
- Let's just get the ones for broth.
- Yes.
You can make broth
with dried pollacks.
Where is Jae Suk?
- No. They sell...
- Yes. Buy that one.
- small tablets for broth.
- But...
- Do they have them here?
- Let's get that.
- The tablets?
- Do they have them here?
- You know them too.
- Yes. That one.
Do you know what Jae Suk is doing?
What is he doing?
- He's wearing long johns.
- Really?
It's cold.
Gangwon Province
is indeed Gangwon Province.
Really?
You have a runny nose.
- It's colder than I thought.
- It's cold here.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's go. Where is he?
- Let's have twisted donuts first.
- Yes.
- No. After getting other things.
- Let's have a look at least.
- It's fine. Let's get donuts.
- Get the ingredients first.
We'll have enough money left
for sure.
- Fine. Go ahead.
- We'll have enough money left.
- Let's get twisted donuts.
- Yes. Let's just have one.
Just one for each. Come here.
So Min, come here.
She has the money.
- She has the money. Let's go.
- I have the money.
I have the money.
What's the use of going there?
She has the money. Come here.
- Hey! Come here.
- Come on.
- Come with us.
- Hurry up. The money is here.
Come here. Gosh.
- Come here.
- When did you ever...
We should eat it. Se Chan!
Then... Hey.
- Just let us slide.
- Can you get just one for us?
(Asking the cameraman to get donuts)
I don't have money.
(She failed to get donuts from him.)
Or can we pay you later
when we come back?
They will have money left.
- They will for sure.
- What if they don't?
If not, we'll go to jail.
I like this.
- We'll pay when we come back later.
- Okay.
- We'll pay you for sure.
- This one.
- I'll get this one too.
- Do you want it?
- Yes. I'll have this one too.
- You have this too.
- Yes.
- I'm not eating now.
- Why not?
- If they have money left,
I'll get the two-dollar one.
- That looks better.
- Eat now.
- No. Not now.
- Let's eat together.
Eat.
- I'm not eating.
- Let's eat together.
Let's eat together quickly.
Why do you want
to make me an accomplice?
Eat it quickly.
I'll have the vegetable one too.
Eat. It's fine.
- I'll get scolded.
- This is fun, though.
- No, I mean...
- We should have snacks...
- at a market.
- In case we can't pay.
- How much are these already?
- We can pay. What are you saying?
We can pay it back. This is so good.
(The main culprits
are eating first.)
- Thank you.
- How did you make it so delicious?
Thank you.
How is it?
We'll make sure to pay
when we come back later.
- Okay.
- How is it?
(All their worries about money
disappear after having a bite.)
- What's this?
- It's good.
(All their worries about money
disappear after having a bite.)
- It's delicious, ma'am.
- I'm not doing this for the camera.
- It's so chewy. What is it?
- Bye.
It's glutinous rice.
- No way.
- How can it taste like this?
- There isn't much oil.
- It's crispy outside, moist inside.
It's so clean.
- I should have one more.
- Do you want to have one more?
Haha, no. We can't pay it back.
- What if we don't have money?
- We will pay it back.
- Anyway...
- We...
- can take out some ingredients.
- I don't think we'll leave some.
We can take out some ingredients.
Was it 65 dollars?
Yes. This one is really good too.
Jae Suk is coming.
- Let's make him eat one.
- Feed him.
- Let's make him eat.
(They're going to make
another accomplice.)
We need many accomplices.
Jae Suk.
- Tell him to eat it.
- Jae Suk!
Don't tell him the details.
Have some of this. It's crazy.
It's not oily.
- Really?
- Eat one.
- Could you give us...
- It's unbelievable.
- one more chapsal donut?
- Can we have one more?
- Hello.
- Chapsal donut.
It's really delicious.
Try it.
(One chapsal donut is ready
even before they ordered it.)
- This is the best.
- Try it.
(Jae Suk hesitates.)
- But I want to eat this more.
- Then eat that one.
This is tastier, Jae Suk.
- You don't need to sprinkle that.
- On just one of them.
- Put it on only one. Leave the two.
- Yes. Put it on the other two.
- I'll give you one extra.
- Goodness.
- Thank you.
- Then the total is...
- Take a bite, Jae Suk.
How much is it?
- Okay.
- It's done.
Is it tasty?
(They can now fully enjoy.)
- Have one.
- It's really soft.
(He joins the twisted donut
eating show not knowing the reason.)
- This makes no sense.
- It's really delicious, right?
It's very tasty.
Why are they there
when the money is here?
Let them just watch.
- It's bigger than I thought.
- Yes.
- I've not been to a market lately.
- The market.
I wonder what they have.
It looks great.
It looks delicious.
(They see a display
of various food.)
I love markets like this.
This is nice.
This is how the market looks like.
What do we need to buy?
We need things
like zucchini, red pepper,
green onion, onion, and radish.
- We first have to go to a store.
- That's right.
- A store will have them.
- Or...
you can buy broth at the kalguksu
restaurant here.
The sujebi there.
- What's already made?
- Yes.
- Can we just buy a little?
- It would be nice, right?
They'd have the dough
you use for kalguksu.
The someorigukbap here looks good.
It must be delicious.
- I wish we could just eat it.
- Yes.
Hold on. Where do we have to go?
First,
we have to go to a store.
Excuse me, where can I find...
- green onions? Over this side?
- Over there.
Go to that store.
The store here. I see.
Thank you.
That's where we can go.
- Then...
- It's a big one.
how much of them do we buy?
- Just a little bit.
- One each.
- Yes. One each.
- One onion, one radish.
- Hello.
- Yes. Hello.
- Yes, welcome.
Hello.
(A small store where products
don't have price tags)
- Welcome.
- We need one onion, one radish...
We don't need that many onions.
How much is this?
- It's 4.5 dollars.
- It's 4.5 dollars?
- Goodness.
- Do you not sell them separately?
- We just need one onion.
- Just one?
- Yes.
- Just one.
- Good.
- Oh, dear.
Are you giving us two?
- What's happening?
- He gave us two onions.
- Two onions?
- They have zucchini.
- We need one.
- They sell zucchini separately.
- Could we have one green onion?
- One zucchini...
We need one green onion.
- Do you have potatoes?
- Potatoes?
How...
do you sell the potatoes?
- It's 3.5 dollars per kilo.
- Per kilo?
That's about seven potatoes.
- Okay. Give us a kilo, then.
- Great.
Can we have the smallest radish?
(They're shopping
while trying to save money.)
- That's big.
- The radish is huge.
- It looks good.
- Give us a small one.
This is too big.
- How much is this?
- It's two dollars.
- Two dollars? That's good.
- Let's buy it.
Do you have anchovies to make broth?
- We sell that in boxes, though.
- In boxes?
- You do?
- No, thanks.
- Then...
- What do we do?
Do you have the extract for broth?
- Like those in a tea bag.
- You don't?
We don't sell those here.
You have to go to a place like SSG.
- Somewhere in Cheongdam.
- You should buy it from SSG.
- That's right.
- You only need a few, right?
- Yes.
Do you sell it in small portions
too?
- Well...
- Did I put the whole amount before?
We'll die if you put all those.
- It will become bitter.
- You put so much.
It tasted like the ocean in Busan.
(She brewed poison using anchovies
that can make soup for a month.)
- We were in Busan Port.
- Sujebi?
- We'll make for six people.
- That's enough.
Would this be enough?
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
- Then...
- We bought everything.
Zucchini, no red pepper,
green onion, onion, radish,
flour, anchovies. That's all.
- Is that all?
- Yes.
- Could you tell us the price?
This is one dollar.
Thank you.
It's 13.3 dollars.
(It's 13.3 dollars in total?)
Thank you.
Did you calculate everything?
Here's 14 dollars.
Just give me 13 dollars.
(Just give me 13 dollars.)
You're giving us more discount?
(He rounded down the amount.)
- You're so caring.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Shall we go out this way?
- The one with red beans is good.
- It's delicious.
- It's really delicious,
- The one with red beans is better.
- What do you like more?
- This one is better, right?
- We don't wear masks now.
- It's so nice without them.
- I didn't know it started today.
- But you still have to wear them.
- In hospitals or pharmacies.
- Yes.
- Also in public...
- Jae Suk.
It's someorigukbap.
It would be nice if we just ate
from there.
How delicious would it be?
Gukbap would be nice
to have right now.
- Shall we just have a look?
- Let's have a look.
- Let's check how much it is.
- Let's just eat it.
Can we just put it on the tab again?
- Let's eat it.
- Let's put it on the tab.
(Let's put it on the tab.)
- Are they serving right now?
- Let's go.
- Hello.
- Look at that.
- The food here...
- is nice, right?
- It looks delicious.
- It looks amazing.
- How much is it?
- It's 8 dollars.
- It's 8 dollars?
We can't share one bowl, right?
Our money. Hold on.
- Guys!
- Here's Korean sand lance.
- What is it? Korean sand lance?
- It's Korean sand lance.
- Korean sand lance?
- This is Korean sand lance, right?
- How much is Korean sand lance?
- That one?
It's six dollars per line.
- Give us one line.
- That's right.
How nice.
(They're glad since it's cheaper
than what they expected.)
- Do we wash it before eating?
- You can just eat it as is.
- We can just have it?
- Do we cook it without salting it?
- You can have it salted too.
- I see.
With this amount of money,
we could eat someorigukbap too.
We have enough.
Let's use this money...
and eat a bowl of someorigukbap.
Yes. We've been too sensitive.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Be blessed.
- Happy new year.
- Thank you.
- We'll enjoy it.
- Yes. Happy new year.
- Thank you.
- We bought Korean sand lance too.
- Yes.
We wouldn't need scallions,
would we?
We need to buy kimchi.
What are they doing?
- They're again...
- What are you doing?
How are you eating
when you don't have money?
Jong Kook,
- the owner of this restaurant...
- Yes.
- wanted to give us warm soup.
- But...
How would you eat that
when you don't have money?
We bought almost everything,
- and there's still some left.
- We have some money left.
How much is left?
- Hello. We still have money.
- How much is left?
Let's eat someorigukbap.
- I also wanted to eat that.
- Good.
Jae Suk.
Shall we eat a bowl of gukbap?
I think we can eat.
- But it will take time.
- That's right.
You know,
if the rice cake place opens now,
and you eat the freshly made
garaetteok...
- It's rice cake.
- Sirutteok.
Look at this. It's sirutteok.
- It looks nice.
- Jae Suk,
let's eat this.
- They have pancakes too.
- He sold them in small portions.
(They're forgetting the real reason
why they came to the market...)
We're going to make lunch now.
Why are you trying to eat now?
Our stomachs should be warm
in order for us to work.
Also, come here.
From one point,
you started liking these places
more than Hongdae.
I also hold my hand at the back
when I walk.
I also...
- did that starting one day.
- It's too...
- It's comfortable, right?
- I started holding it behind.
- It's so good.
- You do that...
- to keep balance.
- That's right.
Let's buy snacks on our way.
Thank you for the tea.
This looks great.
- Thank you.
- We enjoyed it.
- This...
- It's really cheap.
- Hello.
- Those are pancakes.
- How welcoming.
- What pancake is that?
- It looks nice. It's buckwheat.
- She's waving at us.
- Buckwheat pancakes?
- This must be bukkumi.
- Hello.
- Bukkumi?
These are bukkumi.
- This looks good.
- Let's eat.
Bukku
Hello.
Is this sorghum bukkumi?
- No. These are pancakes.
- Buckwheat pancakes.
- Buckwheat pancakes?
It's buckwheat.
(Pancakes with sliced radish
wrapped with buckwheat dough)
It's early morning still.
- This is...
- This looks good.
It looks tasty.
- Buckwheat pancakes.
- Pancakes?
- Buckwheat pancakes?
- Buckwheat pancakes.
- Hello.
- These are cut.
- No, cooked.
- You can eat it like that too.
- Right now?
- Would you like some?
- How much is it?
- How much is one?
- Just one.
- It's two dollars.
- Let's eat one then.
- Let's use two dollars.
- We have two dollars.
- Could you cut it for us?
Let's eat the amount
for two dollars.
- Yes. Two dollars.
- Could you cut it?
- Just two dollars.
- Let's get it for two dollars.
Since you're eight people,
I'll give you one extra.
- No, don't do that.
- You don't need to.
Please cut this one
into small pieces.
- We don't have that much.
- How much do we have?
We'll just eat one.
- It was made just now.
- Yes.
- That's right.
We should eat this one.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Could you make it eight pieces?
- It's fine.
- No.
- Don't do that.
- We'll play a game to eat that.
- It's too much.
- It's a rule.
- Don't. It's a rule.
Gosh.
We'll pay four dollars.
(They paid four dollars.)
Give her four dollars.
What should we eat it with?
You can put it in our mouths.
- You can feed us.
- I'll put it in your mouth.
- This is warm.
- Get in line.
- Go behind.
- Stand in line.
Stand in line.
This is warm.
It's delicious.
- It's tasty.
- Is it good?
- It's delicious?
- Yes. It's good.
(Laughing)
- It's delicious.
- This is it.
It's really good.
Thank you.
(The food train is operating well.)
What's in it? It's so delicious.
It's her second turn.
It's tasty.
(She got caught trying to eat it
the second time.)
- Would you like more?
- No.
(The mother bird
takes a bite belatedly.)
- It's tasty.
- You should eat another one.
It's tasty.
(The last piece goes
to the cameraman.)
- Thank you for the food.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- It's tasty.
- We enjoyed the food.
- Okay.
- It tasted healthy.
- We will get going.
- Thank you. Bless you.
Bless you.
Ji Hyo, we need to buy kimchi.
- Hello.
- Se Chan, there are oysters.
It's until 10 a.m., right?
Stop glancing around.
We need to keep our eyes ahead
and focus on our tasks.
Yes. Keep your eyes ahead.
We just need kimchi.
- Ma'am.
- Hello.
- We need to get kimchi.
- It's a kimchi place.
Let's get kimchi here.
We need ripe kimchi.
I think we can buy this.
- Would this one be nice?
- Yes.
We will add it to sujebi.
That would be nice.
- Let's buy it.
- This one.
- There are different types...
- We can taste it.
of kimchi.
- Would it be okay to taste it?
- Of course.
Thank you.
I am full already.
(It would be strange
if they weren't full.)
Back in the day,
my aunt had a store...
- in a market.
- I see.
Whenever I was on a break,
I spent time there.
I sat in the room with a blanket.
It was cold.
Jae Suk.
(Laughing)
- Jae Suk.
- Come and eat this.
- It's so tasty.
It would be tasty with rice.
Look at the color.
You can tell that it's tasty.
It's nice.
It's so tasty.
It would be tasty with rice.
- Let's eat it with ramyeon.
It would be amazing with ramyeon.
- It's so refreshing.
- Let's eat it with ramyeon.
- We need to cook ramyeon.
- If we eat it with ramyeon...
- It's so tasty. Try it.
- It's really tasty.
There are different types of kimchi.
- They are frozen.
- It's so tasty.
- There is young radish kimchi too.
- We will take this one.
I want to carry around
a bowl of rice.
- It would be tasty with rice.
- Right?
Jae Suk, I want to carry around
a bowl of rice.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Thank you, Ma'am.
How much is kimchi?
- It's 10 dollars.
- It's so tasty.
What are these?
They look delicious.
I would be able to finish
a bowl of rice with them.
Sand lance.
I want to taste the dish.
- Taste it.
- Which one? This one?
- Can we taste it?
- Yes. You can taste anything.
We would fill our stomachs.
We would fill our stomachs
at the market.
- Hey, stop eating.
- Stop eating.
- You won't be able to eat later...
if you fill your stomach
at the market.
The vendors are so generous
that they let us try the dishes.
- What's this?
- Isn't it dried radish?
She sells side dishes too.
It's spicy skate.
- Try it.
- It would be tasty...
(He gives Ji Hyo
a bite of spicy skate.)
Hey, Jong Kook.
(One bite for me)
(One more bite for me)
Let's go.
- Ji Hyo.
- It must suit Jong Kook's taste.
- Stop eating the side dishes.
- It's tasty.
It's tasty.
You know what I mean, right?
It would be so tasty with rice.
Thank you.
Jong Kook, stop eating.
- Here.
- Let's go.
It's okay.
- You worked hard since morning.
- It's okay.
Don't do that.
- What?
- Don't do that.
- What is it?
Despite your words,
you aren't stopping her.
Your hands are staying still.
Only your mouth is moving.
- Don't do that.
- It's okay.
- Ma'am, is that a freebie?
- Yes.
- Don't give us so much.
- Just give us half of it.
It seems to suit your taste.
- This is driving me crazy.
- How much is it?
- It's okay.
- She might give us more. Stop.
- We should pay.
- Come on. Stop it already.
- Don't eat what she needs to sell.
- It's tasty.
- Do you have a bag?
- Where is the bag?
- We have a bag.
- It's here.
- Thank you.
- Hurry up and pay her.
- No, it's okay.
- How much is it?
- It's okay.
- We should pay.
We should pay. How much is it?
- I won't accept it.
- Why not?
- We should pay. How much is it?
It's okay. I won't accept it.
How much is it? One dollar?
Two dollars? Three dollars?
How much is it?
It's usually 30 dollars for 1kg.
- Really?
- It's usually 30 dollars for 1kg.
(Thirty dollars?)
- Hey.
- Really?
Why did you do that?
- Why did you give us so much?
- Give us everything we own.
- Subtract that much.
- It's okay.
- Give it to her.
- Why did you give us so much?
- Good.
- Let's go.
- Here you go.
- It's okay.
- Come on. You should accept it.
You should accept it.
We accepted your love.
- It was so tasty. I was surprised.
- We accepted your love.
Keep it.
- Thank you for the food.
- I will see you on TV.
- Bye.
- Ma'am, we will get going.
- Okay.
- It was so tasty.
- Bye.
We will get going. Bless you.
Don't look at anything.
- They keep giving us freebies.
- Skates are expensive.
- It was tasty.
- Jong Kook, why did you eat it?
- We ended up buying it.
- What? I wanted to eat it.
- She...
- I didn't know it was expensive.
- The vendors gave us freebies.
- For goodness' sake.
We need to pay for the donuts.
Come to think of it,
we need to buy ramyeon.
- Ramyeon.
- We should put ramyeon in the dish.
- That's right.
- Or the dish will get ruined.
- We need to put it.
- We need to buy ramyeon.
- Pay back the vendor first.
- Hello.
- Excuse me.
- Pay back the vendor first.
We came to pay you back.
- We came to buy ramyeon.
- Ramyeon.
We will eat ramyeon in the end.
My goodness, we bought everything.
- Welcome back.
- Okay.
We finished shopping
in the set amount of time.
It was nice to feel the love.
- I know. It was heartwarming.
- You know,
- we learned...
- Seriously.
how clueless we were
through Jong Kook.
- I...
- "We will pay. How much is it?"
- "Two dollars?"
- "Three dollars?"
"Did you say 30 dollars?"
I didn't know it was that expensive.
- You didn't know.
- No.
Skates are expensive.
It's impossible not to eat
when you walk around the market.
Seriously. You could easily spend
an hour or two...
- at the market.
- There are so many tasty snacks.
It's fun to spend time
at the market.
- It's fun.
- There is so much food.
- You don't spend that much money.
- That's right.
It would be incredible
to eat gukbap in the morning.
Beef gukbap.
If you order kalguksu at the market,
you get a giant bowl.
That's right.
Imagine eating beef gukbap...
with kimchi.
- It would be incredible.
- My goodness.
Suk Jin, when did you eat that?
I... Beef gukbap and kimchi?
- "I..."
- My goodness.
Suk Jin, come on.
- Why do you keep lying?
- Be quiet.
Why do you keep lying?
I suddenly wanted to eat it.
- It wasn't a lie.
- Suk Jin.
You like Japanese food.
You prefer izakaya.
You are wrong. It's not like that.
You can't eat anything
other than omakase.
That was so funny.
It would be nice
to have a date at the market.
- It would be nice.
- Many people do it.
Many young people do it.
Many young people do it, right?
It sounds great.
- Gen Zers do it.
- Many people do it.
They line up at Mangwon Market
early in the morning.
- Really?
- They keep eating.
Do you know what's funny about Haha?
He always talks about Gen Zers.
Young people.
Gen Zers, those punks like it.
Your nickname, Blowfly, suits you.
- You...
- You punks, do you like the market?
You keep circling Gen Zers.
- Blowfly.
- You know...
You circle them, right?
Gen Zers recognized me.
- Same here. Gen Zers pay me.
- Hey.
When you live stream,
you get 2 dollars and 1 dollar.
That's right. Don't use me.
Seriously.
- I get ten dollars these days.
- I was going to say that.
Why are you begging
when you are a celebrity?
- I can't believe you.
- What are you doing?
To get recognized by them,
I need to accept money.
Someone suggested ten dollars
for saying, "I am a fool."
- Ten dollars?
- Then Haha...
Upon hearing those words,
Haha went insane.
"I am a fool!"
(An actual footage
from his live streaming)
(I got it.)
I am a fool!
"I am a fool!"
(Suk Jin monitored it.)
- I am a fool!
- Hey.
- Haha.
- I have the money.
But ten dollars are a big deal
in that scene.
I can call anyone "Big brother"
for ten dollars.
I can't believe him.
- I sent him money in the beginning.
- Really?
So Haha danced for me.
(A capitalistic talent show)
How do I see it?
I will send you 100 dollars.
If you send 100 dollars,
you will be called the president.
You will be called President Ji.
I will send 100 dollars.
- Get the title for 1,000 dollars.
- It will be insane.
I really want to do it.
- So Min.
- That's so funny.
Haha is drawing a snowman.
(Cute)
- I drew a star.
- A star?
- What will you draw?
- Me?
I used to kiss the window.
- That's right.
- When? Why?
- I just wanted to see the lips.
- The lips.
- Whose lips?
- My lips.
You wanted to see your own lips.
Suk Jin.
- Why?
- The lips.
Why did you make the kissing sound?
Suk Jin, even your lips look old.
- Even your lips look old.
- Hey.
Your lips look thin.
- His nose left an imprint too.
- My nose left an imprint.
Even your lips look old.
In my 20s, I drew a heart like this.
- Why? Were you hungry for love?
- I can't draw a heart.
- Back then,
- Were you hungry for love?
it was a mysterious realm.
Was love a mysterious realm?
- It was back then.
- Back then,
he didn't have much to do.
When Suk Jin was talking,
Ji Hyo did this.
(She cared more about her earwax.)
- Ji Hyo, did his words bother you?
- No.
Doesn't "A mysterious realm"
sound strange?
- He met a woman named Mi Ji.
- A mysterious realm.
- Mi Ji?
- The homophone could be a name.
Lee Mi Ji. It's a common name
from our generation.
- Lee Mi Ji.
Jung Eun Sook, Kim Yoo Kyung...
He is naming his ex-girlfriends.
- It's not like that.
- Are they your ex-girlfriends?
- Bleep out the names.
- It's not like that.
- You don't need to do that.
- Bleep out the names.
- They aren't my ex-girlfriends.
- You are open-minded.
- You are cool.
- They aren't my ex-girlfriends.
- He revealed the names.
- Those names were common.
- How about...
- My goodness.
That name wasn't
from our generation.
- It must be from our generation.
- Did you date...
They should bleep out this name.
You must have dated her.
Please bleep out this name.
- I suddenly remembered.
- The look in So Min's eyes changed.
I suddenly remembered.
- It was my ex's name.
- Seriously.
- We need to cook now.
- Jae Suk,
we won't be able to eat
if we begin building a fire.
All right. Who will cook rice?
- Se Chan and So Min.
- So Min.
The two of you should take
the initiative.
- Let's make the dough.
- The rest of us...
- will make the dough.
- The dough.
Then I will grill...
pollack and sand lance.
- As for the sauce,
- You are in charge of the broth.
- The broth?
- Pollack and...
I am good at making it now.
Ji Hyo, I don't think...
- you should get ahead of yourself.
- I think...
- she should take a nap.
- Consult with the others.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Can you make the broth well
this time?
Yes, Jae Suk.
There is
only a handful of anchovies.
I don't know why...
I thought she was a good cook.
I thought that too.
Can you make a fried egg?
- Of course.
- Really?
I know that you can make it,
but can you make it pretty?
I bet Ji Hyo hasn't made
a fried egg.
You just need to use a lot of oil
to make a fried egg.
- Paik Jong Won did that.
- No.
- Paik Jong Won.
- That's how you fry it.
- That's how you avoid failure.
- Right?
- Hey.
Do you want to try it then?
Do you know how to make it
in the tastiest way?
It's healthy if you use water
instead of oil.
If you are going to worry
about health,
- you should quit smoking.
- Seriously.
That's exactly what my wife says.
I can't say anything to her.
"Why did you open the window?"
"Fine dust is bad for you."
"You should quit smoking."
"Isn't this old?"
"Just quit smoking."
- I see.
- Every household is similar.
- Let's say I call someone.
- Right?
Even if it's about work,
Kyung Eun goes,
"Why are you chitchatting so much?"
(A reasonable doubt)
"Hey, it was about work."
- "I doubt it."
- "Why are you chitchatting?"
- At home?
- Yes.
Jae Suk has so many people to call.
- I have so many people to call.
- Yes.
Your schedule must have been tight
last week.
I was busy last week.
- I was supposed to call So Min.
- He couldn't do it.
- I couldn't do it.
- His schedule was too tight.
I was too busy.
This place is so pretty.
It's nice. It's the best.
It's so pretty.
I feel like I am in a fairy tale.
(The location of their retreat is
at the foot of a snowy mountain.)
Hello.
The air is nice here.
- Hello.
- My goodness.
- Hello. The air is nice here.
- At a place like this...
- Hello.
- My goodness.
- This place is nice.
- It's pretty.
- Hello.
- This place is really nice.
- How pretty.
- We are in Pyeongchang.
- This is the beginning.
- How nice.
- We are in Pyeongchang.
- It's like a chicken restaurant.
The vibe is similar.
There is gas today.
We won't be able to eat on time.
Let's just take a nap later.
- There are pollacks.
- You know what to do, right?
- With a hammer or a bat,
- you need to beat it.
- You need to beat it.
That's right.
You need to tenderize it.
It's really hard.
Do we need to build a fire
when there is a gas stove?
There is a gas stove.
Building a fire is the basic step.
This place is so pretty.
- Now,
- Yes?
- let's build a fire.
- Okay.
(They begin to prepare lunch
before looking around the lodging.)
We have a tight schedule.
Who has the recipe?
For lunch, we are having
dried pollack kimchi sujebi,
grilled pollack,
and grilled Korean sand lance.
Dried pollack kimchi sujebi
sounds delicious.
(The hardest one is the main dish,
dried pollack kimchi sujebi.)
It's dried pollack kimchi sujebi,
but it will become
dried pollack kimchi ramyeon.
How do we make the dough?
Didn't you make sujebi
when you were little?
Sujebi is tasty.
- Yes.
- It's tasty when you make it.
(Rinse the dried pollack and cover it
with a cloth for 10 minutes.)
- Pollack will be delicious.
- Dried pollack is delicious.
You need to grill it
over the briquette fire.
on the gridiron.
(Beat it with a wooden bat.)
(Then tear it
into bite-sized pieces.)
(Will they be able
to follow the process properly?)
Where is the frying pan?
- Are we using a cauldron?
- There they are.
There they are.
- The ingredients.
- The kitchen is here.
- Tell me what you need.
Haha, give me...
- a cutting board.
- A cutting board?
- Firstly...
- You startled me.
- A cutting board and a knife.
- We need to make it.
- We need to make the dough.
- That's right.
Give me a bowl.
The dough.
(Team Cooking
gets the kitchen tools.)
Let's take all of them.
(Team Cooking
gets the kitchen tools.)
Hold on. Now...
(Team Fire gets the torch.)
We should put the kindling
at the bottom.
(Excited)
There they go again.
The two members who love fire...
- A meal of the netherworld.
- Okay.
The two members
who are obsessed with fire...
Good.
- Turn it.
- We should do it there.
Good.
It's working.
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk. Hold on.
Did you add charcoal briquette?
- No.
- You didn't, right?
- You need to use it.
- The firewood...
- Hold on.
- The firewood is dry.
- It catches fire easily.
- I get that. Jae Suk.
Hold on.
Jae Suk, hold on.
- All right.
- Let's put them at the bottom.
- My goodness.
Let's put them at the bottom.
- One? Two? Just one?
- One.
All set. Hold on.
- Be careful.
- Here.
Let's pile them up nicely.
Use these.
- What?
- Use these.
(They met their goggles again.)
These goggles? Okay.
They are working
without being asked.
They are cute. They like fire.
(The woodfire enthusiasts
build a fire happily.)
- What are you doing?
- Now,
we need to peel the potatoes.
- Shall I do it? I will do it.
- I will do it.
It's okay. I will do it.
JI Hyo, you need to remove
the anchovy innards.
Okay. I will do that...
while they build a fire.
Where is the sink?
(They are more organized
than they were the last time.)
I need to take off my shoes, right?
There it is.
Can't we cook here?
(Skilled)
All done.
(While Chef Yang focuses on
preparing the ingredients)
We need to beat the dried pollacks.
(Jae Suk diverts his attention
to the dried pollacks.)
Where should we beat
the dried pollacks?
I will beat the dried pollacks.
You are cool.
(Martial arts with dried pollacks)
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Hey.
(Flippant)
I see that you were born flippant.
He was born that way.
It can't be helped.
You were born flippant.
- He was born that way.
- He was born mischievous.
- He can't help it.
I bet...
Jae Suk kicked a lot
when he was in his mom's belly.
- You did that, right?
- My children are the same.
My children are so mischievous.
- Na Eun too?
- Na Eun is mischievous.
(His children got
the mischievous genes.)
Seriously.
You love fire so much.
- I need to build a fire.
- I feel like peeing.
When I came here,
I felt the desire to pee.
- What did you feel?
- The desire to pee.
- Suk Jin, what's that?
- It's strange.
- The desire to pee?
- Just now...
What do you even mean by that?
I was so surprised.
They say you feel like peeing
when you play with fire.
Shouldn't you feel the desire to eat
when you see a fire?
Let's make the dough.
(He suppresses his desire to pee
and begins to make the dough.)
(He mixes flour and water.)
- Hey, the sujabi...
- What's "Sujabi?"
What's "Sujabi?"
Will you eat a lot of sujebi?
(His tongue got crushed
like the dough.)
My words come out wrong
these days too.
I know how you feel, Suk Jin.
It's not like that.
I don't have a problem at home.
It only happens when I am here.
(While everyone is focused on
"Sujabi,")
(Jae Suk begins to beat
the dried pollacks.)
(Breaking)
Jae Suk, it's falling apart.
Jae Suk, why are you destroying it?
- Hey.
- It should be soaked in water.
- What?
- It should be soaked in water...
before you beat it.
- Hey.
- I thought I could just beat it.
The dried pollack became powder.
I see.
You should have told me sooner.
The dried pollack became powder.
I have never made
dried pollack soup before.
- Don't do that.
- Do I microwave it for a minute?
Isn't this enough?
- Why are you adding rice powder?
- What?
Jae Suk.
- Why are you adding rice powder?
- What?
- Jae Suk.
- It looks like you.
- I can't do it otherwise.
- What should I do?
- You need to rinse it...
and cover it with a cloth.
That way, it becomes moist.
- Is this sticky enough?
- What should I do?
- Add a bit of oil.
- I mean...
- You need to knead it more.
- I need to add water, right?
- Add a bit of oil...
- Give it here.
- to the dough.
- Hey.
- You need to knead it for a while.
- Add a bit of oil.
- It needs to be aged.
- No.
- Here.
It's not like that. Give it to me.
It's not like that.
It needs more water.
- No. Add a bit of oil.
- Water.
- No. Don't add water.
- So Min, what should I do?
- Oil?
- I will go and rinse them.
- Should I rinse 2?
- Rinse 3.
- Give me one more.
- I am done.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
- We can add them now.
- All done.
- I am done.
- Cook the rice now.
Let's eat now.
Cook ramyeon.
We are going to eat ramyeon anyway.
Get the water going.
The dough is ready.
We don't have much time.
(Will they be able
to cook the meal on time?)
I shouldn't have shattered it...
- by beating it.
- I mean...
- Jae Suk, just add it.
- It became powder.
It can be used for the broth.
- Let's make the broth with it.
- The broth.
(Ji Hyo only thinks about the broth
as she removes the anchovy innards.)
- Since it might be a waste...
- We can make broth with this.
(So Min washes dried pollacks
as the recipe says.)
Soak it in water? Wash it and...
(Wash dried pollack and cover it
with a cloth for 10 minutes.)
Wash it?
(Steamy)
Wash it like this?
(She's supposed to wash it,
but she's blanching it.)
Bowl. Suk Jin.
- So Bal.
- Suk Jin.
Haha, you should...
cover this with a cloth.
We will beat it when it's soaked.
Hang on. I'll wash them all.
Cover what with a cloth?
I don't know. I'll wash these first.
Read this.
I'll wash them.
Before you beat it...
We don't have any cloth,
so we will use a towel.
Okay. And get me another bowl.
I'll wash the Korean sand lance.
- Okay.
- Get me another bowl.
(The next scapegoat is
Korean sand lance.)
How should I gut these?
I've never done this before.
This is...
How should I gut these?
I've never done it before. I'm in trouble.
This is...
We will boil water now.
Don't put in too much water.
Of course, I won't.
(His eyes are fixed.)
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- Turn on the gas.
- Okay.
- It's nice to have him for fire.
- Here? I should turn it on.
We don't have time.
We should make broth.
(At this rate, they will take a nap
before they finish cooking.)
All right.
- Good.
- Put this in the center.
There's something in the water.
Is that all right?
- It's okay.
- The pot has some oil on it.
- It won't kill you.
- The pot has oil on it?
- What do we do with the fire?
- It always has some oil on it.
- Do you want me to turn it up?
- Turn it up.
I'll make broth
with the dried pollack.
- Okay.
- That's not a bad idea.
Right?
(He puts it in after discussing it
with everyone.)
(Floating alone)
Put in the whole pollack.
You can't put in the whole thing.
- It's okay.
- You can't put it in like that.
- Just put it.
- You can't do this.
- It's all right.
- No.
Why can't I put it in
when you already did?
(They start squabbling
over the broth again.)
Why not?
Let's not make the same mistake.
Don't do anything
that can upset others.
We already made the mistake before.
It can be really upsetting.
Why can't you tell
the proper amount of water?
No, this is okay.
(People always...)
(repeat the same mistake.)
(As they blame others out of habit,)
(they lose cooperative spirit.)
(They can get
a penalty transfer card?)
Let's make it happen no matter what.
(They have to finish everything
in an hour and a half.)
(They are in a hurry,
so they don't care about the taste.)
(The opportunity ends
once the bell rings.)
(Will they be able to eat?)
(From 12:00 p.m. to 12:40 p.m.: Nap time)
(Cranky)
I'm so annoyed.
(The spoiled members)
(The tight schedule continues.)
(To get the penalty transfer card,)
(they struggle in their bare feet.)
(They get carried away.)
(They laugh.)
(They cry.)
(And they laugh.
It's such a strange retreat.)
(Will it end peacefully?)
(The Precious Retreat)