It's been a long time. I like the smell of firewood.
This is a sunny place.
It's called Running Man Outing Race.
Cameras will film you for 24 hours...
- while you have fun at this house. - For 24 hours?
On the wheel, your names...
will take up a space following a specific rule.
The wheel will be spun tomorrow.
The chosen three people will win the gold.
For lunch, you will make a simple bowl of janchi guksu.
It's easy to make. All we need is anchovy broth.
Did you put in the whole bag of sardines?
Two bags that are this big are enough for six months.
- I feel like I am eating on a boat. - With a lot of kimchi.
- You're good. - Good.
Only his nose is covered with snow.
- Only on his nose. - The snow is only on his nose.
Only his nose. How is that possible?
Hey. Gosh, this is more shocking.
Jong Kook.
- The fire went out.
- Hey, the fire is out.
- Gosh.
- Look at this.
It's really out.
This can't be happening.
- Hey.
- Jong Kook, hurry and come on.
- I can bring it back to life.
- They need to dry their clothes.
It's fun bringing it back to life.
(Laughing)
Jong Kook,
of all the episodes we've had,
you seem most excited today.
(Jong Kook seems
the most excited today.)
This is really fun.
The fire is perking up again.
This is amazing.
(Kim, the steel mill owner
likes to mend the fire.)
- Jong Kook likes this.
- They have good firewood here.
(He's going to use up
all the firewood there.)
Jong Kook really likes fire.
(The fire rises again
with Jong Kook's touch.)
I bet Jong Kook won't be able
to fall asleep tonight.
(His love for the fire
will continue today.)
- Because of the fire?
- Yes. To keep the fire burning.
It's going again.
- It's flaring again.
- He added more firewood.
(Flaring)
Actually, we are burning gas.
- Really? Are you serious?
- Yes.
There's a pipe under the fire.
It never goes out.
Hey, you know what?
- You look horrible now, seriously.
- Who?
- You.
- What's wrong with me?
It's funny you ask that.
You just look horrible.
I'm so surprised.
- I can't believe this.
- This is great.
Haha suddenly came to me and said,
"Hey, you know what?"
"You look horrible now, seriously."
(She tells them
exactly what she heard.)
- Haha did.
- Why did you tell them?
- Haha. Why?
- Yes.
- What?
- Why?
Why?
Suk Jin, look at her.
She looks horrible.
Gosh, this is serious.
This is serious.
This is so funny.
It's worst than you think.
Right.
(Not just a little.)
(You seriously look horrible.)
(Dumbfounded)
It's like this much.
This is how horrible you look now.
It's this much.
It's getting serious.
Right.
(Laughing)
They are like old ladies.
How you described it
was really funny.
The sound of your laughter
is more annoying.
(The two childish guys have fun
making fun of her.)
That's hilarious.
- My clothes are drying.
- I know. It actually works.
Of course.
Gosh, it's hot.
My boots are burnt.
As far as I know,
Haha treasures the boots.
He loves them.
He had to wait for a year
to get the shoes.
But he's not wearing them.
Gosh, you're really obsessive.
What do we do now?
Should we cook again?
We should start cooking soon.
Hang on. Again?
- We need to cook again.
- Gosh.
We should dry our clothes first.
What do we eat for dinner?
- Pork belly.
- And budaejjigae?
That sounds great.
We can cook pork belly here, right?
This one is better though.
We can put it on here.
Are you going to use
a caldron lid or a hot plate?
- Let's use a caldron lid.
- Okay.
- Then we should use this one.
- That one?
That's a perfect size, right?
- This looks really good.
- We should use this one.
Gosh, it's hot.
If you put it on here...
(She tries the sweet potato
they cooked in the morning.)
- How is the sweet potato?
- It's delicious.
It's good, right?
What if you get too full
to eat pork belly later?
You didn't eat janchi guksu earlier.
- I ate some.
- No, you didn't. I saw you.
- She didn't eat?
- Did you eat at the market?
Hey. You...
- So Min.
- Earlier...
- You didn't eat?
- You ate a lot at the mill.
- So Min.
- You ate rice cake.
- Is that true?
- Did she eat rice cake at the mill?
- A little.
- Did you eat rice cake at the mill?
The owner of the mill
told me to taste it,
- so I ate it this much.
- Only this much?
- Yes.
- It wasn't that much.
- How much was it?
- You...
You ate doughnuts.
And you ate two dumplings.
Did they eat?
(They end up revealing
the food they ate.)
- What else did you eat?
- You ate a croquette.
The vegetable croquette.
(They end up revealing
the food they ate.)
(Rustling)
Woo Jae, what are you doing?
- Woo Jae.
- What is he doing?
- He must be hungry.
- Doughnuts? Are you hungry?
He must be really hungry.
- Woo Jae is hungry!
- Hey.
This rarely happens.
- Doesn't he eat one meal a day?
- You said you didn't need to eat.
- What?
- You said you ate one meal a day.
He needs some sugar now.
I guess you've done only easy work.
- The sweet potato is good.
- You always sit...
in a studio and talk,
so you must feel hungry today.
- Okay.
- Is it good?
- I guess you like it.
- It's really good.
(While they all try
some twisted donuts,)
(the Nose Himalaya goes to his room
to warm his nose.)
I'm going into the warm room.
- I should go in.
- My nose hurts.
You should go in.
The size is just perfect.
Aren't you going to turn it over?
(Amazed)
Is this custom-made or what?
It's perfect.
Did you measure the size?
- Are we going?
- Do you have a ruler?
Let's just cook it now.
(Let's cook now
since the lid is set.)
Is this custom-made or what?
- Tell Suk Jin to come out.
- Look at this.
- Gosh, this is perfect.
- Jong Kook.
- Call Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin!
- What?
- Come on out.
Why?
- What's going on?
- Come here.
- We will eat pork belly.
- What's up?
- What?
- You shouldn't do this.
You should turn it over.
- No, this is right.
- No.
This lets us drain the fat.
- I thought it should be flipped.
- Really?
If I were you,
I would've flipped it.
It will drain the rendered fat.
(Protein Kim prefers plain meat.)
Woo Jae.
Yes?
Come here.
You know what?
Chun Hee, Kwang Soo, and Woo Jae.
- They all are similar.
- I don't like Woo Jae though.
Hey, the heat is high,
so you can slice it thick.
- Okay?
- Yes.
(Woo Jae is slicing
the lump of pork belly.)
- Do you want to wipe it with this?
- What's that?
- Oil.
- Try it.
(He wipes the lid with pork fat
before cooking.)
My goodness.
- Is it too hot?
- Look at Jong Kook.
It looks like he moved
to a rural area.
- Jong Kook...
- He's a lodge owner.
Why did you put it on here?
It's like a documentary show.
"Turbo was very popular
back in the 1990s."
"Why did he retire all of a sudden?"
I can work out
my forearm muscles this way.
(He went into a mountain
following the smell of firewood.)
Aren't you Kim Jong Kook?
Yes, I am. Hello.
(Kim Jong Kook: He's lived
in the mountains for 5 hours.)
Hello.
I was seriously ill before.
One day, I went into the mountains.
That day, I could feel
I was recovering my strength.
I was like, "This is it."
So I decided to retire and move.
(Looking for the idol star
from the 1990s, Kim Jong Kook)
This is perfect.
I guess I should wipe it once
before grilling the meat.
Shall we cook meat now?
No.
(Laughing)
Do you want to eat meat now?
I can't wait to cook it.
I'll prepare the ingredients
for budaejjigae now.
To make budaejjigae, we should just
put all the ingredients in ramyeon.
- I'll cut some vegetables.
- Right.
We can boil them all at once.
- We should make it together then.
- Okay.
- Do you need tofu now?
- Bring it.
This is the last onion we have.
(While they slice
the ham and vegetables...)
- Really?
- We should've bought more.
(Woo Jae is cutting the pork belly
in the kitchen.)
I see.
It should go
in the opposite direction.
I get it.
I got the hang of it now.
You're really good.
I guess you were
a butcher in your previous life.
This is better.
You're good at this.
- You're skilled.
- This is it.
(Glaring eyes)
- Jong Kook, hurry and come here.
- Why?
The meat is ready.
Okay. Hang on.
- We shouldn't cook it now.
- We should wait.
- Wait until everything is ready.
- Just put it there.
No, put it in the bowl.
Put it on...
You should bring a bowl.
- If you put it here, it freezes.
- No, not here.
- It's here.
- Hey!
- You can't put it down here.
Woo Jae!
Come to your senses.
If you put it here, it will freeze.
- Woo Jae, here.
- Put it in here.
- Hang on.
- Put it down.
Aren't you using the frying pan?
We don't need a frying pan.
- We're cooking budaejjigae.
- Put it down.
- Go.
- All right.
This is...
(Since they made lunch,
they now know they need water.)
All right. Good. We should do this.
We need plenty of water
because it evaporates.
- Right. We need enough water.
- If it's too bland,
- we can add ramyeon seasoning.
- Exactly.
- We can make it work.
- Of course.
We can take care of it.
(Those from "Family Outing"
sound confident.)
Hang on. We need to balance it.
It's no problem.
- It's tilted.
- Hang on. I'll take care of it.
This is ready.
We can cook dinner
faster than "Family Outing."
(Will they be able to enjoy dinner
with no problems this time?)
- Can you open the lid for me?
- Why?
- To put in the meat.
- Do you want to put it in?
- I should...
- Before the water boils?
Is it right that you put it in now?
When you cook budaejjigae,
you put in the ingredients first
and then add the broth.
Let's do that. Put it in.
Just boil it. Do whatever you want.
- Hang on.
- Here.
- Again...
- Then put in...
- Are you Captain America or what?
- Gosh.
Look at you.
No, you'd be
Captain of Entertainment.
- Are we using this?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- We don't have the broth here.
- Instead of the broth.
- She's right about that.
Really? Okay.
- For budaejjigae...
- So this is what you do.
All right.
- I don't think one is enough.
- Don't we need more?
- But...
- If we use more,
- we can't eat tteokguk tomorrow.
- It's for tteokguk.
- No, it's not just for that.
- We can dilute it like the broth.
- Right?
- Okay. We can do that.
You're right.
We can make broth with the meat.
It's good enough to make broth.
It's okay to use plain water.
(Budaejjigae Avengers use
minced meat to make broth.)
Let's boil it.
- Is it pork or beef?
- This is pork.
Aren't we supposed to use beef?
Is it okay to use pork?
- It's pork.
- Do we use pork for budaejjigae?
We can use pork.
- Shouldn't it be beef?
- I think it's beef.
- Beef...
- No, it's pork.
We can use pork
and all kinds of hams.
Actually, pork is...
Never mind. Do whatever you want.
Then we should
cook some rice as well.
It feels like something's missing
when we don't have rice.
You know we ate noodles before.
We already had a lot of carbs.
Sticking to just the meat
is good enough.
- But he...
- That's your issue, not ours.
- You shouldn't eat it, then.
- We have scorched rice.
- Scorched rice.
- Kook Jong, we...
- Are we at a training academy?
- Are we your fitness club members?
- I just mean...
- This isn't a training academy.
Jae Suk, it's...
Wait. What are you putting in?
- Kimchi.
- Are you putting in random things?
- Go ahead.
- There's kimchi in budaejjigae.
Budaejjigae is another mixed stew.
(Quietly)
- Seriously?
- There's kimchi in budaejjigae.
- Why are you grilling that?
- What are you doing?
If we cook it,
we'll have to eat it immediately.
- We have to eat.
- Our meal needs to start.
Once we grill the meat,
we'll have to begin our meal.
Meat gets cooked fast.
- With rice and...
- Just two strips, then.
Go ahead.
- It'll be an appetizer.
- Get grilling.
It's too early, though.
You can have that first.
- No way.
- The smell is divine.
Let's cook some rice
in the cast iron pot.
But it'll take too long.
I'll get on it.
You're adding
the ramyeon seasoning now?
Yes.
We just need to boil everything.
Hold on.
You're cooking it as you please.
Guys, you shouldn't be cooking it
as you see fit.
Are you already
adding the ramyeon seasoning?
First, we should do our best
to cook it without the seasoning.
- That's right.
- If it goes wrong,
we then add the ramyeon seasoning.
- But you already added it.
- You can't cook with it already.
- It's wrong.
- We can always add some more.
That's not what we mean.
That's not...
Anyway, I'll cook the rice.
- So Min.
- Yes?
Where's the rice?
- It's inside.
- Do we have rice?
- Yes, we do.
- Do we?
I'm good at making steamed rice.
(He talks the talk.)
(Cooking rice in a pot
isn't an easy task.)
(He measures the water
using the middle finger method.)
(Seok Sam is confident
in his ability to cook rice.)
(The twist will be revealed
later on.)
Why won't this latch?
Okay, we're good.
So Min, why are you in tears?
The spice is stinging my eyes.
Should it sting like this?
There's too much water, though.
Don't worry about that.
It'll boil down.
- Are you sure? That's a relief.
- We can add more ramyeon seasoning.
Don't worry.
- Anything we eat...
- Anything...
- outdoors on a variety show...
- That's right.
- tastes like ramyeon anyway.
- Yes, like ramyeon.
Don't worry.
Okay, let's give it a taste.
(How will the broth taste?)
Taste it.
- It's not ready, but...
- It seems good to me.
Let's see if we need more seasoning.
- How is it?
- It's too bland.
- Is it bland?
- Like crazy. This is bad.
- Let me see.
- We need to boil it down.
It's seriously bland.
- Then...
- Let's add more seasoning, then.
We need to boil this down
for a while.
Only then...
There must be too much water.
Who decided on the amount?
- Who...
- It wasn't me.
(They feign ignorance.)
- Hey.
- Who decided on the amount?
- It wasn't like that.
- Right.
I was going to let it boil
and evaporate first,
but you added
the ingredients too early.
- Who added the ingredients?
- You.
No, it wasn't me.
- It was So Min, then.
- What's going on?
Who gave you the order?
- The water?
- That's right.
I didn't decide
on the amount of water.
You should've checked
before adding in the ingredients.
- I said it was too much, but...
- You should've taken some out.
You added the ingredients
before the water could evaporate.
- The water...
- That's right.
(Can this be salvaged?)
- Who was this irresponsible?
- I said it was too much water.
(Woo Jae has been quietly
grilling the meat.)
Once this is done, we need to eat it
along with the sauce.
- Look at this.
- Or else, this will burn.
Who added these strips?
Why are you grilling the meat
when nothing is ready?
You said you were only
going to grill two strips.
This wasn't me.
I only added the two strips.
- Who was it, then?
- Who was it?
(Who added all this meat?)
- Who was it, then?
- Who was it?
- It was me.
- Why?
I thought we were grilling the meat.
Make sure you don't
add the preserver too.
I'll start grilling the meat
once that goes in.
Is it time?
(No one heard
the bomb Ji Hyo dropped.)
(And so the meat
got lined up on the lid.)
(Ji Hyo covered the surface
with strips of meat.)
(Proudly)
- It wasn't time for that.
- Nothing is cooked...
including the rice.
- This is bad.
- But...
I thought it was time
since Woo Jae was grilling some.
- That's only because...
- Why are you causing trouble?
- I thought it was time.
- Didn't I say it about ten times?
Why did you bring more
when there isn't enough space?
(There's no more space.)
Woo Jae, we only grilled the meat
just to get an earful.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
They may have yelled at us,
but they'll enjoy the meat
once we give it to them.
Probably, right?
It smells delicious though.
How good can it be
when it's no longer moist?
This is insane. It's to die for.
- Is it good?
- Try one.
Haha, have one.
I'm not easy to please
since I own a barbecue restaurant.
- I get it, but...
- He's right.
Let's have it
before it gets overcooked.
Gosh, the smoked flavor.
Isn't it good?
(That's what I'm talking about.)
- It's nice and chewy.
- It's absolutely delicious.
(It's so good
that they have forgotten...)
(about giving them
an earful earlier.)
- See? They love it.
- Right.
We made the right choice.
(The duo's grilled pork belly
got everyone's approval.)
We did a good job.
We should have this right now.
Have some of the meat.
What about the budaejjigae?
(What about the budaejjigae?)
We'll have to keep it boiling.
We'll have it tomorrow.
(It'll need to boil
for at least a day.)
I guess we can end our meal
with just that.
- Suk Jin, is the rice cooking?
- Yes.
- Did you turn on the stove?
- The rice?
It'll be undercooked
since we're out in the wild.
That can't be helped.
This should've been cooked indoors.
How clueless are you?
What did you just say?
I had no choice.
The rice will be cooked,
so don't worry.
Be patient,
and you'll have your rice.
- We should wipe this clean.
- Right.
Let's see.
Check the color.
It's stinging my eyes again.
- That's not it.
- It's not the right color.
My eyes are watering.
It'll taste nice
once it's seasoned properly.
How does it taste?
It tastes a little weird.
It's weird?
- In what way?
- Try some yourself.
(So Min gives it a taste.)
- It tastes weird.
- Right? But you can't explain why.
- Try some.
- It's bland.
It's finding its way, though.
It tastes like ramyeon cooked
with too much water.
(1st sign of trouble:
The bland budaejjigae)
- Jong Kook, it's too hot!
- Jong Kook!
- What is it?
- The fire's too hot.
You're burning the meat.
See what I mean?
You have to eat it right away,
but you started grilling the meat
when we weren't ready.
(It's a mess.)
- It's a mess.
- Tell me about it.
(I thought we'd be having
an early dinner.)
- Transfer the meat.
- The flavors are there,
but it's bland.
- The flavors are there.
- I should get this indoors.
Suk Jin, where are you going?
Where are you going?
It shouldn't be cooked outdoors.
- Why not?
- It's just what Haha said.
- It won't be cooked through.
- It'll be fine.
It'll burn at the bottom,
and nothing will be cooked.
It'll be fine. By the way,
who put you in charge?
Why are you trying
to order everyone around?
Are you the owner of this place?
- I own a barbecue restaurant.
- Are you kidding me?
This is laughable by my standards.
Let's compromise.
I'll cook it at a place that is
half indoors and half outdoors.
- Right here.
- That seems like the place.
Happy now?
(The rice will be cooked
on the daecheong maru.)
The meat... Woo Jae!
- Yes?
- I noticed that you burned it.
It's worse now.
(It's heavily burnt.)
- Do you enjoy black meat?
- Despite...
- Did you burn it some more?
- This is pork from a black pig.
- Are you kidding me?
- It's black meat.
- It was burnt earlier on as well.
- Why did you want more fire?
- It was perfect a while ago.
- It's nice and crispy though.
Woo Jae, let me speak.
It didn't turn black
because you burned it.
The soot from the flames
transferred onto the meat.
It's soot, so wipe it clean.
Wipe it with the chunk of fat.
- Wipe it clean.
- The barbecue restaurant owners...
aren't showing any mercy.
It will burn on the outside
but remain uncooked.
It won't be cooked thoroughly.
Black water is dripping from this.
(The pork is turning into coal.)
It's the soot.
Ji Hyo, wipe down
this side of the lid.
Ji Hyo, why can't you stop sniffing?
- When the fire dials down...
- Put this on.
Right, of course.
- I forgot.
Let's grill the next batch
once the fire dials down.
Wipe the lid clean
with chunks of fat.
What you're seeing is soot.
- I agree.
- There's too much water...
in the budaejjigae.
- It's bland and tasteless.
- Let's leave the lid open.
- Take off the lid.
- And boil it down.
- If we keep the lid open...
- We need to boil it down.
- The water will evaporate.
- It needs to be boiled down.
Let's keep it open.
Just like before.
It was beginning to boil down.
Let's do this as well.
- If we keep it open...
- Add some more ham.
We have enough for the entire staff.
- It could feed 50 people.
- You keep making more.
(It is enough
for approximately 50 people.)
We could open
a buffet for the staff.
This isn't
your ordinary budaejjigae.
It's budaejjigae
made in a cast iron pot.
It's not the kind
you get to normally eat.
Actually...
- You can feed a whole squad.
- Exactly.
I mean, when we made lunch earlier,
Ji Hyo put in six months' worth
of anchovies.
If we run a restaurant, it'd fail
because of the cost of ingredients.
You wouldn't even last a month
if you run a restaurant like this.
(They should never start
a restaurant business.)
I put in two packs of meat.
Gosh, my eyes are burning.
Haha, see if we need more ham
if you can see inside.
- I can't see.
- Move.
Can you see inside?
It hurts my eyes.
- Hey, I can't... Gosh.
- Have a look for me.
- See if we have enough meat in it.
- I can't see anything.
Give me that. Hold this for me.
- How do I hold it? Hold on.
- Hold this part.
- You can hold this part.
- I think it's enough.
- Have a look. Wait.
- Move aside.
- Take a look. My eyes are burning.
- Oh, my. It's amazing.
- Do we need more ham?
- Gosh, it's too hot.
(Screaming)
(He touched the broth in the ladle.)
(It's an emergency situation.)
- What's wrong? Tell me.
- He burned his finger.
(An unexpected accident happened
because of the smoke.)
What's the matter?
Why would you put your finger in it?
- I can see it now.
- Are you okay?
(Screaming)
Gosh, that fool.
What's wrong with him?
My eyes are burning like crazy.
This is killing me.
- Give me that. Hang on.
- Gosh, my eyes are stinging.
What did you do?
(All sorts of unusual sights unfold
while they make budaejjigae.)
Hey, I can see it now.
- I can see it.
- Right. I can see it too. Wait.
- Hey, I can see it.
- I can see it too.
This is enough for us
and all of our staff members.
(She keeps tasting the food
without making any changes.)
Hey, it's getting better and better.
- Really?
- Let's boil it down more.
- Does it taste okay now?
- No, it's not okay.
But it's getting better.
- Don't worry. Just trust me.
- We'll make it work. Don't worry.
- I'll trust you.
- I'll adjust the taste at the end.
Don't you worry.
- We should add more ham, right?
- Absolutely. Gosh.
- We'll end up eating ramyeon.
- We should add more ham.
- Don't add more ham, So Min.
- Then what should we add?
Put in some pork belly instead.
- Hey.
- Oh, dear. Your nose is running.
- Trust me. Put in some pork belly.
- It's better, right?
- It doesn't have enough flavor.
- But I put in a lot of meat.
- We should put in pork belly.
- That's why they use bone broth.
- To enhance the taste.
- It doesn't have the ham flavor.
- So we should put in pork belly.
- Then let's add beef bone broth.
- But we should add more ham too.
- No.
- Yes. Let's put in all of the ham.
- Then add more ham.
Let's put in a chunk of pork belly.
- Suk Jin, put in pork belly.
- I'll put it in secretly.
Shall we put in some pork neck?
Should I pretend I didn't hear that?
That he'll put in pork neck?
Open this.
Just put in whatever you want.
- No, don't put it in.
- It's okay.
- You shouldn't put it in.
- Trust me just this once.
- You shouldn't put in fat.
- Trust me.
- It's not fat. It's meat.
- I mean...
- It's not all fat.
- My gosh.
- Come on. That's not right.
- Jae Suk.
- Trust me on this.
- No, you're wrong.
- It'll make the broth taste better.
- No. You shouldn't put that in.
Don't put that in.
- Gosh. He drives me crazy.
- You use beef to make budaejjigae.
- The broth... Listen, Suk Jin.
- They put bacon in it.
- Right. Absolutely no.
- This is my wish.
- Suk Jin, come on.
Come on. Hey, I just...
- I won't let you.
- I just want to make it tasty.
- Please.
- No.
- Ramyeon seasoning will do that.
- I'll do that.
- I'll make it tasty.
- Hey, help me persuade them.
- Let's put in just a small piece.
- Don't worry. Add more ham.
I'll cut the ham into smaller pieces
and put them in.
Hey, can you cut this too
while you're at it?
- Okay. Just a moment.
- Pork neck?
Put it in along with the ham.
It'll make the broth tasty.
- Okay. I'll give it to you.
- Put it in with the ham.
- Place the meat under the ham.
- Put the pork neck under the ham.
What's the reason?
- You put it under the ham, right?
- Yes. Put them in all together.
- They won't know.
- Right.
- We enjoyed it, so it's okay.
- True.
Suk Jin, bring it here.
- He got caught.
- Bring it here.
(He got caught right away.)
- Show me.
- He got caught. He's in trouble.
- What? Those are sausages.
- Show me now. I can see it.
- Why?
- What do you mean?
- I can see the pork.
- Show me.
- I said to put it at the bottom.
I can see it. Why would you hide it?
- Let's just add ham, not the meat.
- Right. Just add more ham.
I think we used too much water.
- Let's add two seasoning sachets.
- Let's do that later.
- Okay.
- Then let's add this first.
- Right. Open the lid.
- Open it for me.
- Let me add just the ham.
- Open the lid.
- I'll do it. Just a moment.
- He caught me.
- I can never fool him.
- Good.
I'll just add in the ham,
not the meat.
Gosh. I can't see anything. Hey...
- Oh, no. The seasoning.
- No. It fell into the cauldron.
- Oh, gosh. Hey. The seasoning.
(He dropped the whole sachet.)
- Hey, the seasoning will dissolve.
- Gosh. I can't see anything.
- Hurry up and take it out.
- Give me the ladle. Move.
- I'll do it. Move.
- Okay.
- I can't see anything.
- Darn it!
(The sachet is being boiled
with the other ingredients.)
- Gosh, seriously.
- Take it out.
- Okay. I found it.
- There's another sachet in there.
- One more.
- One more. Take it out.
- There's one more.
- Where is it?
- Okay. I found it.
- There's another sachet in there.
- One more.
- Take it out. There's another one.
- There's another sachet.
- You take one more out.
- Where is it?
Why would you turn on
the flashlight?
There's one more, Haha.
- I found it.
- Hey, wait.
- This is bad.
- Hurry up and take it out.
No. Wait. This is... Hang on.
- Hey, step aside.
- Give me the fan. Now.
The fan won't do.
No. Just move.
- Gosh. What should we do?
- This is driving me nuts.
Hey, let's take the cauldron out.
Oh... No, that's not it.
Oh, there it is. Take this out.
- Where is it?
- There. On your right. Yes. Okay.
- Yes, Ji Hyo, that's it.
- Okay.
It's all good now.
(Ji Hyo took the sachet out
with tenacity.)
It's not easy to make budaejjigae.
I'm worried.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
You owe us an apology.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
But I couldn't see suddenly.
Making budaejjigae is
stressing me out.
If we have too many,
give some to Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
- So Min, what are you adding now?
- Ham.
- How much more ham will you add?
- So Min, can I have one?
That's enough ham for 50 people.
- Put it all in.
- We're supposed to use beef.
- Don't drop the desiccant.
- Be careful.
- They keep adding ingredients.
- Add all the ingredients you want.
This is enough to feed
all of our staff members.
Who put in tofu?
- It's not tofu. It's ham.
- Really?
That's a big piece of ham.
- It's as big as a block of tofu.
- Simmer it...
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Can you open
two sachets of seasoning?
- Let's put in noodles at the end.
- Of course.
I have more seasoning here.
I collected the seasoning.
Let's add more seasoning. Wait.
Hold on. I think it's enough.
(He's putting in the fifth sachet
of ramyeon seasoning.)
Oh, the color of the broth
looks good now.
- I told you so. Hey, put it in.
- It looks good now.
- Okay. I'm about to do so.
- Put in the vegetable flakes.
- Is it better now?
- Yes, it's better than before.
Jae Suk, how about we boil it down
a little bit?
- I think we should boil it down.
- Shall we? It's totally different.
- Absolutely.
- It's different now.
Let's boil it down with the lid off
even though it'll be hard.
- Right. Let's do that.
- It's not just like ramyeon.
I must say,
the seasoning made it taste better.
- It worked.
- Yes, it's much better.
Hey, hurry up and scoop rice.
We can eat the food now.
(All that's left is
rice cooked in a pot.)
Rice...
The flame is too weak.
Hey, about the rice...
The flame is too weak to cook rice.
That's why I told you
to cook it inside.
I mean, the flame is too weak.
Why won't the rice cook?
(He brings it indoors two hours
after he started cooking it.)
I think the rice isn't cooking.
(He brings it indoors two hours
after he started cooking it.)
It's strange. What's wrong?
Suk Jin, you shouldn't open the lid
while cooking rice like that.
But it looks strange.
Should I add some water?
What's wrong with the rice?
(He adds water.)
(He adds water
three times in total.)
How's cooking rice going?
Why is the flame that weak?
That's strange.
(He added cold water
when it wasn't boiling.)
(And he keeps opening the lid.)
Oh, gosh. I'm worried.
It won't cook.
(He comes back with a worried look.)
My gosh. I can't believe this.
So Min.
Can you come and help me cook rice?
- Okay.
- I ruined it.
- Suk Jin, okay. I'll do that.
- Can you?
- Can you save it?
- I'll try.
Wait.
(Ms. Jeon, the master of cooking
rice in a pot, appears.)
- Oh, I don't think I can save it.
- I couldn't...
The rice won't cook.
- I couldn't do it.
- It's undercooked.
And the flame is too weak.
- That's the problem. Sorry?
- Have you tried changing the gas?
You should put a stone on the pot
to put pressure on it.
- Really?
- Yes. To make the lid heavy.
You should put something heavy
to cook rice.
We need to press the lid,
but we have nothing to use to do so.
- I'm worried. It won't taste good.
- Right. It won't taste good.
(They use a bowl for now.)
- Look. It finally started boiling.
- Yes.
It's finally boiling.
I see steam at last. Gosh.
Hey, when will the food be ready?
Is the rice ready?
- No. Actually...
- I don't think we can eat that.
I think we should cook rice again.
(He confessed honestly.)
- Can you give me more time?
- My gosh. Suk Jin.
- What do you mean by that?
- Give me some more time.
- We need to start eating now.
- Can you give me more time?
- What happened to the rice?
- So Min, why are you grabbing it?
- The flame...
- was too weak to boil it.
- The flame was so weak.
- The rice is...
- How is the rice right now?
It's not cooked yet.
We have to wait for a long time.
- Is it undercooked?
- We'll have no meat when it's done.
Then we should borrow
some cooked rice.
- What's that?
- Chocolate cookies.
- What are you doing? Hey.
- What is it?
What are you doing?
We're about to have dinner.
Stop eating snacks.
Why are you eating it?
Kids get scolded by their parents
when they do that.
We ran out of oil.
Why would you eat cookies
instead of meat, Woo Jae?
Didn't you say
we started cooking too early?
- Right. I'm glad we did that.
- The sun is going down.
It was bright outside
when we started cooking.
I want to go home.
I miss my mom.
I want to lie down in my bed.
I bet everyone feels the same way.
And the viewers must think,
"I must say,
there's no place like home."
- We're giving them a lesson.
- Yes, you can say that.
This is a great show.
Right.
You feel most comfortable at home.
(The sun has set already.)
(The human pressure cooker siblings...)
(have been taking turns
pressing the pot.)
Let's stir the rice and check it.
(The 1st check after 15 minutes)
- Should you put a stone on it?
- Anything to put pressure on it.
It's hard to cook rice in a pot.
Is it good?
- It's good.
- I guess it's not bad.
We saved it.
- We saved the rice, right?
- It's good.
- Is the rice good?
Yes, it's good.
- It's good.
- We're like a rice rescue team.
- Do you want to taste it?
- We can eat this now.
(Meanwhile, the budaejjigae...)
It'll be too salty later.
We have to eat it now.
- Really?
- Scoop the rice.
- Are you sure?
- It's just right. I just said so.
I said it was just right.
It's not just okay. It's amazing.
It's done. It's amazing.
- We're done. Put out the fire.
- It's crazy good.
- It shouldn't boil down anymore.
- It's done.
- Scoop the rice!
- It'll get too salty.
- I want to taste it too.
- Let's take it away from the stove.
- Hurry up and take it away.
- It's good.
Oh, my. It looks so good.
(The budaejjigae
miraculously became tasty.)
It looks great right now.
It's good. It tastes as it should.
- My, it looks amazing.
- This is a good meal.
It's good.
Suk Jin, it's cooked to perfection.
Where else could we have food
like this?
- Hey, Muscle.
- Let's sit close to one another.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Let's eat.
- Come here.
(They sit around the tables
and enjoy a hearty meal.)
- The pork belly is crazy good.
- Ji Hyo, come and eat up.
The pork belly is so good.
- It's crispy outside, soft inside.
- We should cook the rest.
Try a piece of pork belly with rice.
The rice is cooked
to perfection as well.
- The rice is okay too.
- It's so good.
- Pork belly.
- So Min did a great job.
- Woo Jae, come here and eat up.
- Okay.
- Woo Jae, come here.
- Look at him.
I knew he wouldn't eat the food
when he ate the chocolate cookie.
(Slurping)
Oh, my. It's so tasty.
I'm impressed.
The pork belly is crazy good.
Ji Hyo, come and eat.
The budaejjigae is so tasty.
I was surprised
when I tasted the budaejjigae.
Oh, my. What happened to it?
It's so delicious.
- The budaejjigae is so good.
- He did a good job. Isn't it good?
- Isn't it amazing?
- Haha, you should...
sell this. It's incredibly good.
- How much should a bowl be?
- How much?
- About 110 dollars. Considering...
- Really?
I cried so many tears
while making it.
We used the ingredients
that were worth 200 dollars, right?
- It was made with craftsmanship.
- How tasty.
And it has a rich flavor
as I wanted.
Because we used ingredients
that were worth 200 dollars.
- And because we're eating together.
- I agree.
(Woo Jae delivers the meat
that he cooked.)
How sweet. Look at Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae delivers the meat
that he cooked.)
If we cook like this,
a day would pass by quickly.
The meat that he just cooked is
so good.
Why won't you bring any meat
to our table?
- Why? What's the reason?
- Sorry?
You didn't bring any meat
to our table.
- I'm bringing you meat now.
- I only ate one piece.
(He brings a few pieces
as Jong Kook complains.)
Here you go.
- But why? Do you not like us?
- It's not like that.
Is there someone you hate among us?
(Is there someone you hate
among us?)
Who is it?
Why would you do that?
- I wonder who it is.
- Tell us why.
He keeps doing that. Earlier on...
(What?)
(They pause
and give each other a fierce glare.)
My, that's fierce.
- I kept eating like this.
- Right.
- You know that, right?
- It's fierce.
(The two of them finished
their silent conversation.)
It feels like
we've been rewarded for our effort.
- It was so good.
- Because the food was so good.
- I'm happy that we pulled it off.
- Everything was really tasty.
- We all enjoyed our dinner.
- It was a good meal.
Yes, it was successful!
- We made it!
- We really enjoyed it.
- Hey.
- Why...
Who stepped on the back of my shoe?
(The back of Haha's shoe is folded.)
- Who did this?
- Who...
- Who else would do that?
- Was it you, Woo Jae?
That's not yours.
Hey, leave it. That's mine.
(They finished their dinner
at 9:40 p.m.)
- I'm so full.
- I feel like my stomach will burst.
- Let's clean up first.
- Okay.
Let's play a game.
- Let's decide by ourselves.
- We should play a game.
You can play any game you want.
- Let's...
- Will the loser clean up or what?
- Let's choose four people.
- Four?
- Okay. Let's do that.
- Four people will be enough.
We can play palm face down or up
to choose four losers.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- Oh, my gosh.
- All right. Then...
- Okay.
Palm face down or up.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
- Let's begin.
- The four of us with the same side.
- Those four get to rest.
- They're the losers.
- They get to rest?
- No, they're the losers.
- They're the losers.
- They should clean up.
- The rest three get to rest.
- That's correct.
- The team of 3 wins.
- The team of 3 gets to rest.
- The team of 4 loses.
- The 4 of them should clean up.
- Palm face down or up
- No.
- There are five of them.
- We have to do it again.
- This is no joke.
- Now...
- Let's do it again.
- The team of 4 and the team of 3?
- Correct.
- Palm face down or up
Okay. We've got the losers.
- One, two, three, four.
- Wait. What?
Oh, yes! We won!
(Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook
survived.)
(They're free from doing the dishes
in the cold weather.)
Let's go.
We won the Best Couple Award
for a reason.
- Oh, yes!
- The Best Couple Award winners!
- Guys!
- Okay!
(Chucking bitterly)
(Suk Jin, Haha, So Min, and Woo Jae
will do the dishes and tidy up.)
- Well...
- The Best Couple Award winners!
- Let's leave 1 person out.
- How about 2 people?
- Let's leave 2 people out.
- Let's just leave 1 person out.
- Let's leave 1 person out.
- Just 1 person.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Just 1 person will be left out?
- Just 1 person.
- You guys are playing another game?
- One person.
- Yes.
- One winner, right?
- Just 1 person.
- Let's leave 1 person out.
- One winner.
- One winner, okay?
- There's only one winner, okay?
- I just said so.
- No.
- Just one person will be exempt.
- Palm face down or up
Let's go inside. It's cold outside.
- Let's choose 2 people.
- Let's make it 2.
- Two people?
- Yes.
Yes. Two people will be enough
to do that much work.
If there are three,
it'll be hard to divide the work.
- So Min.
- I have a feeling that I'll lose.
Because if there are three people
working together,
- we'll bump into each other.
- I have a feeling that I'll lose.
- Hey, you'll go with another round?
- It's too much work for two people.
- It'll be too much work.
- It'll be too crowded.
- Just one of us will be exempt?
- Yes.
- Would there be two winners then?
- Palm...
- Suk Jin.
(Would there be two winners then?)
(Seom Sam became overly sensitive
and answered in a prickly way.)
- What's wrong with you?
- Why would you get annoyed?
Why did you do that to So Min?
Just think about it, So Min.
Just try to think.
- Could one person do all the work?
- He's being overly sensitive.
- Go ahead.
- So Min.
- Begin the game.
- It'll be hard to do it alone.
The person
who throws the other side wins.
Okay.
- Palm face down or up
- You were too slow. Do it quickly.
- I wasn't.
- Throw it quickly.
- No, I wasn't slow.
Palm face down or up
- Oh, my. Woo Jae is the winner.
- Hey, Woo Jae.
Me? For real?
Palm face down or up
(Woo Jae survived.)
I won. Oh, yes!
(Sardine is elated.)
- Oh, my. Woo Jae is the winner.
- Me? For real?
(Seok Sam and So Min lost.)
- I'm saved. I didn't know.
- You didn't know?
- I thought I lost.
- I told you that.
- I knew he would win.
- My gosh. I can't believe this.
This is the worst.
- This is the worst.
- Hey, you can do it alone.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- You can do it alone, So Min.
- So Min.
- I've done it before. It's doable.
- Hey, So Min.
Make your choice.
What do you want to do?
- You can do it alone.
- Make your choice. It's up to us.
- It'll take too much time.
- What do you want to do?
What do you think?
- Let's do it together.
- Right. Do it together.
- Right. You can't do it alone.
Now, we'll add more slots
on the roulette.
- The camera team chose the members.
- I wonder about the reason.
They chose the members
who were worth filming.
(The camera team chose the members
who were worth filming.)
- Haha, So Min...
- Oh, I see.
(Jae Suk)
Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae)
Thank you.
- The Nose Himalaya.
- I feel honored.
- Of course.
- That was funny, indeed.
The meat is good.
Right. That was a legendary scene.
We'll spin this roulette
tomorrow morning,
- and the winners will win the gold.
- Really?
- I see. The more slots, the better.
- It's important.
- Of course, it's advantageous.
- Three will be chosen, right?
So Min, put it between 6 p.m. and 7 p.m.
What is she doing?
- I'm feeling dizzy.
- Why is she so spaced out?
Could it be because she inhaled
too much smoke?
(Could it be because she inhaled
too much smoke?)
I'm serious.
(Haha suspects that she inhaled
too much smoke from the fire.)
- That's possible.
- I think that might be the case.
Don't inhale too much smoke.
- You look a little...
- It's dangerous.
- Suk Jin, I'll do the dishes.
- Okay.
(It's time for the weakest siblings
to do the dishes.)
- Yes.
- Oh, dear.
I'll start doing the dishes.
- What happened?
- What's wrong?
(So Min slipped and fell suddenly.)
- What's with her, seriously?
- Hey, put out the fire!
- So Min, stop inhaling smoke.
- What's with you?
- Breathe out the smoke now.
- Why...
- Breathe out the smoke you inhaled.
- So Min, what's wrong with you?
She's acting so weird.
So Min, what's wrong with you?
- What's the matter?
- She's acting so weird.
- She's laughing suddenly.
- What is it?
- What is the problem?
- She startled me.
(She's creating an ironic sight
by laughing with a sad face.)
- That was hilarious.
- It was slippery.
It's too slippery.
- You inhaled too much smoke.
- She lost her mind at some point.
We should go inside.
Seok Sam, thank you in advance.
Let's do the dishes.
What should we do about this?
We should put it in a plastic bag
and store it in the fridge.
- Gosh, I'm so cold.
- It's so cold here.
I'm so cold.
Strangely, you and I always lose
when we decide who cleans up. Darn.
- Right.
- It's so strange.
It's funny
how we always get unlucky.
- It's always us. How strange.
- It's really funny.
We all have the same chance of winning.
Then why?
It's so funny.
Gosh, I'm so cold.
I think the dish soap is frozen too.
Gosh. Cleaning up is a lot of work
because everything is frozen.
(So the two tiger moths tidied up
for a long while.)
- Even the dish soap is frozen.
- Gosh.
- I don't get it.
- I don't know.
I should try to do more nice things
for others.
Right.
I feel refreshed now.
Let's make a video call to him.
(Finally, it's break time.)
Yes, So Min.
Hey, Se Chan.
(They're talking to Se Chan
who's on standby on a video call.)
What are you doing?
I'm on standby at home.
(I'm on standby at home.)
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
You will shave your face
before coming here, right?
- I should shave my face.
- Okay.
Your girlfriend is waiting for you.
I like the melody.
But you have to make tteokguk
tomorrow morning.
Of course. I'll make tteokguk.
Great.
I'll see you later.
- It's not bad, right?
- Nice.
(DJ Yoo works hard even in the room.)
Suk Jin is very good at whistling.
Suk Jin, do you have your own trick
for whistling?
Why can't I whistle like you do?
You can't?
I can only whistle one note.
If you're good at whistling,
you wouldn't be cute. That's why.
- But I want to be good at it.
- Because you're cute enough now.
That's true.
- You said I looked ugly earlier.
- You don't need that skill.
- Some ugly things are cute.
Things like a small lump of poop
are cute too.
(Things like a small lump of poop
are cute too.)
(Laughing)
He was listening to me.
(They won't stop teasing So Min
even during the break.)
You two have
a similar sense of humor.
He likes my jokes.
Can I have some bread...
We have bread, right?
- We have bread right here.
- Give me some.
- It's warm now.
- That's good, Woo Jae.
Right. Woo Jae.
There's nothing in it.
I think it's plain butter bread.
- It has a lot of butter in it.
- Try this one, Suk Jin.
Hey.
(It's an empty cup.)
You always prank me
when I'm starting to feel better.
I didn't do that intentionally.
- You just started looking adorable.
- I can't help it.
She can't help it.
(It's a whole new way of
giving someone a hard time.)
(Laughing)
Why is that funny?
(Giggling)
(He can't stop laughing.)
Suk Jin was too...
(She wants to laugh with him
even in such a situation.)
- I mean...
- I want to know why it's funny.
Why do you find it funny? Tell me.
Why else?
I was just starting to adore you.
So I thought it was a shame.
But you blew that chance right then.
- Because of this.
- Exactly.
You missed your chance.
Why would you join them...
You have a problem.
She always...
(A curious girl who hovers around
them despite being teased)
They were having so much fun
and I was curious what it was about.
You missed the chance.
You could've been adored.
It's because you wasted a chance.
It's because I like you.
Each kid is...
Sometime later,
"Why are you not seeing them?"
- Oh, my back.
- It's dangerous. Put it up there.
My back hurts.
She grew so much.
I guess people all feel
like that when their child is young.
I hated how fast my child grew.
She got Na Eun's clothes.
Na Eun's clothes?
You got all her clothes.
She wears her clothes a lot.
(The dads who are weak for their
daughters are talking half awake.)
Actually, you can pass on
children's clothes.
They can't wear them
for a long time.
Right.
It was really tiring.
Tteokguk or whatever, I want to
run away with a bag in the morning.
Do you want to run away with me?
Do you want to?
The accommodation is quite far.
Do you want to run away?
Let's have a drink then.
Let's not even wash up and...
- Come in.
- No.
Come in.
Why did you bring them?
What is it?
- Get it from her.
- It's coffee. Oh, my.
- Gosh.
- What?
We didn't want this much.
- What's this? The table is full.
- We should work hard then.
- You're telling us not to lie down.
- No. It's fine.
- Take a short break.
- All right.
Ji Hyo.
Your hairstyle is intense.
Did you go to a beauty salon?
- Yes.
- It's a shag cut.
It's a shag cut.
Ji Hyo.
- You should flatten your hair.
- Your hair is intense.
Your hair.
- Are you a Super Saiyan?
- Will you be okay today?
It's static.
- That's cute.
- It's because of static.
- Are you okay?
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- You're not, dude.
You're an actress.
Put on a hat or something.
It's because my baby hair...
- became frizzy.
- It's fine as long as you're okay.
- I'm okay. Why?
- We're fine.
Do I look weird, Jae Suk?
(Do I look weird, Jae Suk?)
- Do I look weird, Jae Suk?
- Hey.
- Open your eyes wide.
- I...
honestly like it
when you look funny.
But I didn't hope you
to become this funny.
You look so funny now.
It's my baby hair that is frizzy.
- Hey.
- Excuse me.
- Sir.
- Yes.
- I should stop watching YouTube.
- Put more firewood, will you?
Yes.
- The owner of the cottage...
- My eyes are going to pop out.
has been watching his phone
for two hours.
Have a cup of coffee, Jong Kook.
Okay.
All our faces are red, aren't they?
- His face is puffy too.
- I was sleepy.
He didn't sleep a lot.
- Your face is so puffy as well.
- I slept for two hours yesterday.
You watched a soccer game.
I haven't seen an attic like that
for a long time.
- But...
- It's not...
I'm glad that you're healthy.
We'll get going now.
- Okay.
- We...
We should go back to Seoul
when there's less traffic.
Right. You didn't have to visit me
because it's the end of the year.
- I'm fine.
- There will be a traffic jam later.
- You're doing good after retiring.
- Yes.
You should visit me sometimes.
The rooms are all empty.
- Right.
- Yes.
I'm glad I came to see you though.
Isn't the room warm and nice?
We could come here sometimes.
Yes. Visit me sometimes.
- There are many rooms.
- Okay.
After the award show,
you said you couldn't do it anymore.
- I know.
- It's already been ten years.
Ji Hyo,
you still don't have a boyfriend.
- I'm married.
- She got married. She has a kid.
Really? I didn't know.
Her child is going
to elementary school.
Ji Hyo, I didn't think
you would get along with us.
You must've gotten married
right after I retired.
- She got married immediately.
- Yes, I did.
If I receive one more Grand Award,
I will have 30.
(Bitter)
- He kept receiving it.
- I guess you kept receiving it.
You must've received one every year.
I worked hard after that.
- Right. You always do your best.
- Yes. I did my best.
- Right.
- I...
(Oh, my.)
- Please excuse me.
- This is...
This is comfortable.
- For real.
- Hey.
I'm so tired.
- It's because I'm so tired.
- It reminds me of my grandma.
I mean... Okay. You should get up
when I have a cramp.
- I'll have a cramp.
- I get it. Because you're Suk Jin.
- I'll get up when you have a cramp.
- Try this.
- It smells like a grandpa.
- It's so comfortable.
- It's...
- Under the...
What's wrong with this?
- Right.
- I'm scared.
- Gosh, this is...
- Why does it keep flickering?
- Right.
- Maybe we should say scary stuff.
Is this scary though?
It's not weird or anything.
Do you believe
there are ghosts or not?
- Ghosts? I think they exist.
- They exist.
- But...
- You think so?
just because the light is turned off
or flickering all of a sudden,
- are you scared?
- I'm scared.
- It's possible. It can be scary.
- Is it not scary for you?
What kind of feeling is that?
Are you scared of ghosts?
I close all the doors
except for the room I sleep in.
I believe ghosts exist.
- I turn on all the lights.
- I'm scared.
- I...
- I also close all the doors,
but it's to save heating costs.
You're so...
I can't sleep with the door open.
Because the sensor lights near
the front door would be on suddenly.
- I have the same experience.
- It never happened to me. You too?
- The toilet flushed itself too.
- But those things can happen.
It can happen. It happened to me.
I exercise at 2 or 3 in the morning
at the gym by myself.
- Why?
- You're so disciplined.
- That itself is scary.
- That's so scary.
At 2 or 3 in the morning,
I would go there after work.
- And I start working out.
- Without anyone else?
And this happened before.
You know the hand sanitizer
near the entrance, right?
Yes.
It suddenly released the sanitizer.
(The automatic hand sanitizer
dispenser was turned on itself.)
- It's scary.
- Exactly.
And it showed the temperature.
It only shows when someone comes.
I'm scared
just by listening to the story.
- Are you scared?
- I would've left immediately.
- I would've fainted.
- That's when I...
- I would've run away.
- He would've fainted.
- I won't be able to run.
- I would run to go out.
- What was it?
- Are you not scared?
I'm not scared of things like that.
You should experience it yourself.
First,
it's not scientifically proven.
Once you're possessed
with a ghost...
- You will make ghosts angry and...
- It's like...
They're listening to you.
- Please go to this guy today.
- It's because of you.
Then film a video where you try
to summon a ghost for YouTube.
- By himself?
- Since you don't believe it.
- The ghost will come.
- They will come at night.
- You'll be in trouble.
- Just with a camera by yourself...
The wind is suddenly blowing.
Set the camera by yourself and...
He can't do it.
He would be too scared.
go to a deserted house by yourself.
He can't do that.
- How can he do that?
- He said yes. Look at his face.
- He's not scared.
- You can do it.
The pen will move even when
you're not moving your hand.
- How can it move?
- Will a ring move too?
So try it.
I used to do it with my friends
at school.
Like, "Did you move it
or did I move it?"
- Darn it.
- I told you.
Like, "Did you move it
or did I move it?"
(The lights suddenly turned off.)
They turned it off on purpose.
- No, they didn't do it on purpose.
- Hey.
- Woo Jae, try it.
- Don't talk.
Only the light in the room
is turned off.
(Staff member)
The electricity in the members' room
is out.
(The other rooms are fine.)
It's just this room.
It's fine outside.
Yes. It turned off.
- I can't understand.
- Look.
- What's this?
- What's wrong?
- Is it just this room?
- It's the loose contact.
- Because today...
- Why would the contact be loose?
They're using a generator for the
shoot and they run out of power.
Yes. We're using
a lot of electricity.
- But it's fine outside.
- But...
why when we were talking
about ghosts?
Why is it only this room?
- It's just...
- It's been fine all this while.
It started when we started
talking about ghosts.
So...
My goodness.
(Peekaboo)
(My goodness.)
- Gosh.
- Hyung In.
(Flinching)
(Laughing)
Why did you do that?
You got me surprised.
Why is the light off?
It really hurts.
You didn't do it, right?
- My gosh.
- You didn't turn it off, did you?
That's why I told you
not to talk about scary things.
- I hate scary stories.
- This is enough.
I don't want to talk
about scary stuff either.
There's a problem.
I can't hear you.
We're hearing a weird buzz too.
Don't talk about ghosts.
Really?
(The room with audio equipment)
(They heard a buzz when he was talking
about summoning a ghost.)
(The staff members were scared
for real.)
- Why are you doing this to us?
You must be joking.
No. I came
because we got surprised too.
Don't talk about ghosts.
I want to switch rooms.
- Hey.
- I can't sleep here.
Don't lie.
- I really can't sleep.
- I'm serious.
- Don't lie.
- We were monitoring together.
- Hyung In.
- We were surprised...
when we heard a buzz.
Don't lie.
- Stop lying.
- So I can't sleep here, Hyung In.
- So Hyung In...
- It's because you used electricity.
Those who will sleep here, sleep here.
I can't.
- I can't sleep.
- Don't do that.
They said they were using
a different generator.
They're using a different generator,
but the power was out?
- I know.
- Don't do it.
- Hyung In.
- Let those who are okay sleep here.
- Are you joking or not?
And book accommodation for us.
Don't do it. Just sleep here.
- They're lying.
- The ghost will follow you there.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- I mean...
- I really can't sleep here.
- Me too.
- Don't lie.
- I'm serious.
- Why are you doing this?
I can't sleep.
- Me neither. I'm sorry, Hyung In.
- Just sleep here.
- I'll sleep in the next room.
- Why are you making it a big deal?
You should sleep here though.
What is she doing?
- The power is back for now.
- It's okay now.
It's fine now.
Let's change the mood.
This won't do.
Here...
It'd be better
to keep the door open.
(Why did he open the closet?)
- They're serious though.
- They're serious.
- I know.
- They're really scared.
Why did you fart?
Hey.
Why did you fart with the door open?
Why did you fart there?
I told you he wasn't scared.
Look at him farting.
Why did you fart there?
- You fart when you're scared.
- It's because I'm nervous.
You shouldn't keep farting
while sleeping. Seriously.
I could fart.
You can't prevent me from farting.
Farting is a blessing to him.
It means he digested food.
You should bless him for that.
(Health, happiness, blessing)
Health, happiness, and blessing.
When he farts...
(Thank you.)
Did I have my appendix removed
or something?
(After a commotion,
it already passed 12 p.m.)
So Bal,
when is your boyfriend coming?
Why is he not coming?
Can you go find him?
I can't wait for him to come.
Can we not just go to bed?
I know. I'm so sleepy.
(It's way passed
the usual sleeping time.)
(Tapping)
(Absurd)
- Jae Suk.
- Yes, So MIn.
What's taking Se Chan so long?
We'll resume the shoot.
(At that moment, the production crew
heard Se Chan was arriving.)
(Turning all cameras on
in case the members greet him)
One, two, three.
It's so cold.
(After a week,)
Hello.
(Se Chan appears
with a somewhat haggard look.)
Hello.
(Se Chan appears
with a somewhat haggard look.)
Come here.
Hello.
I grew a petty mustache.
Come here.
- Se Chan's here.
- Se Chan must be here.
He's walking around outside.
Jae Suk.
- Se Chan must be here.
- Se Chan's here.
- Se Chan.
Se Chan's here.
- Are you here?
- Jae Suk and So Min are sleeping.
- Give me my coffee.
- Where are you?
Suk Jin.
There's a karaoke machine. Nice.
Haha.
Come out.
Come on. I'm disappointed. Come out.
- It's cold outside. Come in.
- Look at us.
- Oh, hi.
- My goodness.
- Hello.
- Se Chan.
- What's with the mustache?
- Oh, a mustache.
- That's cool.
Isn't it nice?
I decided to grow a dirty mustache.
So Min is exhausted
from waiting for you.
- Come in.
- What's that?
You look so tired.
- Hey, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
So Min. Your boyfriend is here.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- You should've shaved.
- How was it this time?
Why does your mustache grow
like a goat?
- You look...
- You look like a goat.
- You look Japanese.
- Right?
You look Japanese.
- You don't look noble.
- You look puffy.
- Hey.
- So what's happening?
I have to make you
breakfast tomorrow.
- You?
- Really?
- I have to pick two people.
- What?
Two people to help me.
- Gosh. Hey.
- So...
- Because...
- It has to be me.
- Se Chan.
- All of a sudden, everyone is...
Se Chan.
(No one wants to make breakfast
because...)
(1. They have to get up at 7 a.m.
when everyone is still sleeping.)
(2. They have to make a fire again.)
If you look tired, I can't help
but choose that person.
I'm fine. If you want to make
rice cake soup,
we have a tteokbokki
restaurant owner.
Right.
We have someone
good at making a fire.
- The fire man.
- Personally,
as a man who was on "Family Outing,"
you need someone to guide you.
Jae Suk is a must.
People with "Family Outing"
experience are...
- Jong Kook and Jae Suk.
- I need them.
I need one of them?
You must pick one of them.
But if they're too good,
it won't be funny.
To make it funny,
- Right. One must be clumsy.
- one must be clumsy.
Jae Suk, you're right.
You need to decide that.
I told you.
Rice cake soup doesn't need much.
- Right.
- All I need is the beef bone broth.
Waking up early in the morning is
the hassle.
Woo Jae is good
at making egg garnish.
- You need it for rice cake soup.
- He's...
- Joo the egg garnish.
He's very good.
Or is it going to be someone
good at cooking like So Min?
You all don't want to do it, do you?
That's not it.
That's not it. I don't mind.
How about this? If you suddenly...
- Three.
- say three,
three people gather.
Choose the ones that are left alone.
Or choose between coke and sprite.
Jae Suk.
Do you want me to play
"Round and Round?"
So I can choose it at once?
If you say four.
If we play, "Round and Round,"
- What is that?
- I say three...
and choose those three?
How about this?
Are we really playing this?
Se Chan is...
Do you not want to play? Jae Suk...
What's the rule? Let's be clear.
Let's dance. You have to dance.
(A heart dance
instead of "Hype Boy")
What's going on?
- What's the rule?
- There shouldn't be too many?
What's the rule?
I say round and round.
If I say three,
the one left alone is
going to make breakfast.
Here.
You should stand in the center.
I'll play
"Wheat and Barley Are Growing."
(Changing the song
to "Wheat and Barley Are Growing")
- What's that song?
- Wheat and barley are growing
(The first game to choose
who will make breakfast)
Stand here.
Start moving.
(Off the train goes.)
(Who will wake up first
and make rice cake soup?)
The other way.
(Making a fuss)
Three.
(Jae Suk, Haha, and Woo Jae
make a team.)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Suk Jin
- So Min.
- It's So Min.
All right. The first person.
- So Min.
- It's Jeon So Min.
Why didn't you come?
I was going to,
but then Suk Jin stopped me.
Really?
Three.
(Go away.)
- Good job.
- So, it's So Min.
- It's her.
- Me?
- You come in.
- Zombie?
- Zombie.
- Okay.
Is it over? No second chance?
- It's over.
- Is it over like that?
- You're...
- You're out.
- There will be one more person.
- Am I out?
I should put on my gloves.
He's going to follow the walls.
- Ten seconds.
- Wait.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
(Woo Jae is inside the blanket,
and Jae Suk is trying to fly.)
Six.
- Five.
- I'm going to hold onto it.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start. I'm going in.
(He chose the worst place
while trying to hold onto a pillar.)
I'm going in. I can't see anything.
(The predator look adds tension
to the game.)
(Nothing but breathtaking silence)
Where's that?
(So Min's trying to lure him
towards Haha.)
I heard a sound.
(However)
(I smell a prey here.)
(The predator follows his instinct
and moves forward.)
(They're only 30cm apart.)
(Laughing)
Wait. I heard something.
(The predator stopped.)
(Who's going to be his victim?)
(Chuckling)
Got you.
- Jae Suk.
- Okay.
He couldn't hold back.
He couldn't hold back his laughter.
Hey.
(Jae Suk couldn't help but laugh
at Se Chan's look.)
- Gosh.
- One more.
- This?
This.
The one who is the same as Se Chan.
- We'll play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
What are you going to give?
Who do you want it to be?
- Rock.
- Rock. Okay.
I'm going to give a rock.
I'm going to go for it.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Paper, scissors)
(Woo Jae is out.)
Seriously.
- He's safe.
- I survived alone.
- Am I the only one?
- You're safe.
- One more time.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Scissors, rock, paper,
scissors, rock)
- Okay.
- Suk Jin.
(It's Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin.
(Those who are making breakfast)
- Every time I play this,
- Done.
- It's over.
- it's always you, me, and Jae Suk.
- It's strange.
- I know.
You and I washed
the dishes yesterday.
It's unlucky people again.
- It's them again.
- It's strange.
- Why is it always the three of us?
- Tomorrow morning...
We played games for so long.
- We've been playing for so long.
- It must be the ghost.
- It's the ghost.
- Last time we played,
- it was me and him.
- We had to wash the dishes.
We all played it together.
You broke the odds.
Let's sleep.
Do you want me
to spread the blankets?
- Spread them?
- Spread them.
Anyone need more blankets?
Give me a big one.
- A big blanket?
- Yes, a big one.
- For the floor?
- Jong Kook, do you like this?
- What?
- Do you like this blanket?
Why do you ask? Do you want it?
- Yes.
- Take it then.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
If you ask...
if I like it...
Let me use this blanket.
The three of you can sleep
on those two.
The three of you sleep on them.
I'll sleep here.
He wants to sleep comfortably alone.
I just don't want to bother anyone.
I move around.
Suk Jin, I am sorry,
but do you wake up and run around?
It's not like that. While I sleep...
- Suk Jin.
- Do you wake up and run around?
I put my face
next to someone's feet and such.
We are set.
Jae Suk has the best spot.
Suk Jin, why do you keep wanting
someone else's thing?
That's the best spot.
That means he wants it.
(Their first night together
comes to an end.)
(It's the next morning.)
(The current time is 6:55 a.m.
The current temperature is 12°C.)
(The alarm goes off at 7 a.m.)
(Wriggling)
(My goodness.)
Isn't it really cold?
We need to get the fire going.
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin)
(Laughing)
- Right now...
- Do you want to go out?
Yes.
For goodness' sake.
Let's order a delivery.
Is there a restaurant
that's open at this hour?
So Min, come here.
My goodness.
People must be waiting outside.
You never know.
Gosh.
(Se Chan comes outside.)
Can't we skip breakfast?
I see that it's really annoying
to make breakfast.
- Your shoes are pretty.
- Yes.
- I bought them here yesterday.
- Really?
- Did you buy them here?
- Yes.
- They are pretty.
(He got the shoes
without the owner's approval.)
Hold on.
- We need to build a fire first.
(Suk Jin comes to work
with a haggard face.)
Suk Jin.
Can't we order a delivery?
Who will deliver food at this hour?
(This frog got woken up
from hibernation.)
Everyone is here.
All the members groaned
in their sleep.
The air was cold,
so it felt like
our heads were outside.
Outside.
Seriously.
I felt like my head was outside.
It was so cold. And yesterday night,
- someone kept farting.
- It was Suk Jin.
I couldn't sleep
because the floor kept shaking.
And I don't know who it was,
- but someone dreamed of revenge.
- Who?
Someone ground his or her teeth.
It was Suk Jin.
- Someone dreamed of revenge.
- Who was it?
Where is the torch? Hold on.
- We need to start this furnace too.
- One furnace is enough.
- One?
One furnace is enough.
It's cold.
(Se Chan and So Min
prepare the rice cake for the soup.)
- It didn't freeze.
- Really? We need to slice it.
- Do we need to slice it?
- Yes.
It was made yesterday.
- It's nice.
- We can use it.
(Adding firewood)
Suk Jin. For goodness' sake.
The fire was going. Hold on.
- Stop it.
- Hold on.
That's not how you do it.
- Wait until the fire is going.
- Why did it get on my hand?
Get me a newspaper.
- We need a newspaper.
- Let's add two balls.
Is there a newspaper?
- What?
- A newspaper.
Why do you need a newspaper?
We need it to start a fire.
You can use a paper towel.
Put some cooking oil on it.
- Paper towel?
- Yes.
Hey, a camper says...
we need to put
some cooking oil on it.
- We don't need to do that.
- Really?
- Yes. Suk Jin, give it to me.
Is that what you do
when you go camping?
- The cooking oil froze.
- What's this?
- Just give me the paper towel.
Here you go.
Roll it up.
For goodness' sake.
(The delicate man
hasn't improved at all in a day.)
- Suk Jin has never done this.
- Me?
- Yes.
- I don't enjoy camping.
(He prefers hotels.)
I should slice the rice cake.
(Suk Jin decides to slice
the rice cake instead.)
Suk Jin.
Why is it sticking?
When will you finish slicing
at that rate?
(Eating)
Why are you eating?
You should eat one.
The rice cake should have hardened.
It's sticking too much.
If you keep eating...
It's not like that.
It's sticking too much.
If you keep eating,
when will we finish...
Se Chan, bring me a plate.
Do I put it here?
- It's soft.
- You are slicing it wrong.
I can't slice it otherwise
because it's soft.
Hey, the rice cake in tteokguk...
- Speak for yourself.
- The rice cake in tteokguk...
- That's not how you slice it.
This isn't the joraengi rice cake.
- You are slicing it wrong.
- The knife won't go in.
I can't do it right
because it's too soft.
The rice cake should have hardened.
It didn't harden at all.
It's still soft.
You keep eating.
Suk Jin, if you keep eating...
(So Min eats it as well.)
- Jae Suk, did you start a fire?
- No, I didn't.
Hurry up.
- Suk Jin.
- Are you still doing it?
I am almost done.
- You are bad at this.
- I am almost done.
- You were on "Family Outing."
- Give me some paper.
- Jae Suk, are you still doing it?
- Seriously.
- Hey, I am almost done.
- Why are you so bad at it?
- Why didn't you ask for help?
- I am...
- I am a veteran.
- A veteran, my foot.
- Just you wait.
- You keep burning the newspaper.
The ashes fly all the way here.
- Hey, the ashes...
- Suk Jin.
Just imagine that it's snowing.
- Hey, the ashes...
- I mean...
- Hey.
- What do we do with the rice cake?
- I mean...
This is bad. The ashes are landing
on the rice cake.
- Close the box.
- For goodness' sake.
Shouldn't we call over
the fire enthusiast?
- No.
- He is sleeping.
He is on his phone.
Once the fire enthusiast hears this,
- he will crawl out on his own.
- His ears must be twitching.
Didn't you do it yesterday?
Jong Kook did it.
He is a genius at saving a spark.
(Chuckling)
He can't stand it when a spark dies.
It was my first time seeing him
so excited about saving something.
- It's done.
- We almost woke Jong Kook up.
We finished slicing the rice cake.
We don't need to slice more.
Stop.
- This is enough, right?
- Yes.
Cut a corner.
(They begin making tteokguk
1 hour after waking up.)
Pour it in.
(Gushing out)
Suk Jin, just go into the room.
- Suk Jin, just go into the room.
- I must do this. I promised.
- I think...
- I promised.
- you had enough screen time.
- No.
- Just go back to bed.
- Pretend to slip.
No. Hey, the opening is...
- too small. The broth is frozen.
- What?
For goodness' sake.
(The broth doesn't come out well
since it's frozen.)
Will you eat the back ribs
if I make them?
- Of course, we will eat them.
- Of course.
- I wanted to cook them yesterday.
- It's the dish...
- that contains kimchi.
- Yes.
He said that he is good at making
braised kimchi with back ribs.
Suk Jin, let's grill...
some rice cake for breakfast.
That's a good idea.
- Let's grill it on the gridiron.
- Where?
- The gridiron.
What is a gridiron again?
Oh, that's the gridiron.
- I am sorry. I am not fully awake.
- He is like that in the morning.
(Gridiron is the cookware
for grilling meat and rice cake.)
- This is the gridiron.
- Yes.
- I was dazed for a second.
- We need two.
I dozed off for a second.
Should I pour water in here?
Shouldn't I do that?
- The broth keeps getting reduced.
- We need to start making tteokguk.
We need to hurry up
before the broth evaporates.
How long will it take
to make the braised kimchi?
About an hour.
- Why did you tell the crew?
- It will take about an hour.
- Why did you say you will make it?
- I don't know.
- For goodness' sake.
- Why did you say you will make it?
- Braised kimchi with back ribs...
- An hour with this fire.
It has begun again.
- This happened yesterday too.
- This is driving me crazy.
The broth evaporates,
but the other dish isn't done.
We keep going
because the timing is off.
- Se Chan, get some water.
- We need to eat the dish.
We need to add water
before it evaporates.
This is driving me crazy.
This is a repeat of yesterday.
- For goodness' sake.
- This is bad.
This is bad. Hold on.
We should take this out.
What do you mean?
- It's boiling too much.
- We should take it out.
Why did you come up with this idea?
We can eat the dish once it boils.
- Really?
- Yes.
Once it boils, we just add kimchi
and boil it some more.
- My goodness.
- The rice cake looks tasty.
It will be tasty.
It's too bad
that we don't have honey.
People inside the room
won't be able to eat it.
- Tteokguk.
- We will make honey.
- There is honey.
- Where is it?
- Is there honey?
- Se Chan, add a bit of soy sauce.
- Add a bit of soy sauce.
- There is honey.
- Hold on. So Min.
- Yes?
You don't think you are married...
- to Se Chan, do you?
- The three of us...
Honey.
Jae Suk, there is grain syrup.
Honey, bring it over here
with a bit of soy sauce.
"Honey."
So Min.
If you introduce Se Chan
to your family,
would your parents like it?
- My mom would love it.
- Would she love it?
- Of course.
- You just need to decide.
- Her mom likes Se Chan.
- Se Chan just needs to decide.
- That's right.
- What?
- Se Chan.
- I see.
- What?
- Just ignore what I said.
- Doesn't your mom...
Doesn't your mom talk about...
- So Min?
- Everyone else has decided.
Did So Min's parents talk about
my mom?
- No.
- For goodness' sake.
- So Min's parents...
- My mom?
like you as her boyfriend.
You just need to decide.
- So Min's parents?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Let's say...
you introduce So Min to your parents
as your girlfriend.
How would they react?
They would be surprised.
- Would they be happy?
- They would be happy.
- What does Se Hyeong say?
- Se Hyeong...
doesn't talk about such things.
- He isn't the type to do that.
- No.
What's up with that smile?
Is my brother-in-law doing well?
(The future daughter-in-law
is a bit cheesy.)
It's getting charred, not grilled.
Is the fire too strong?
- I won't be able to eat it.
- It looks tasty.
I won't be able to eat it.
We should grill it on a pan.
- It looks tasty.
- Let me try it.
- It's too charred.
- It should be okay inside.
(Humming in approval)
It's cooked.
It's good.
(He said
he won't be able to eat it.)
Try it.
It's tasty, right?
- Okay. Now...
- It's boiling.
- It's boiling, Se Chan.
- Once you add the ingredients...
No. It needs to boil some more.
(The ribs are boiling.)
- Boil it with kimchi.
- It's cooked.
Once it boils,
I will rinse the ribs with water.
Then I will add kimchi
and braise it.
- It's coming along nicely.
- We need to discard the water.
- Right?
- We can discard it now.
- No.
- Now...
- We don't have much time.
- The fire is steady.
It will take an hour now.
We don't have much time, Se Chan.
- But...
- I can't wait to eat it.
Let's eat breakfast and go home.
(Suk Jin wants to eat
and go home on time.)
- The ribs are ready.
- Suk Jin,
- they aren't ready.
- Look.
- They are still red.
- The impurities came out already.
More impurities need to come out.
- The tasty juice is coming out.
- No.
- Suk Jin.
- All right.
Hurry up and discard the water.
(Se Chan discards the water
upon Suk Jin's insistence.)
(He puts kimchi on the top.)
Let's see how it looks.
- Is that how you make it?
- Yes.
- Let's see.
- It's almost done now.
To here...
You should add some water.
No. I will add some broth.
You shouldn't add so much.
- What?
- You can add everything.
Really?
Se Chan.
Se Chan, it looks delicious.
Suk Jin, please open the lid.
Thank you.
It's boiling.
(He adds Cheongyang chili...)
(and green onion.)
- It smells good.
- Yes.
You know...
(Lastly, he adds minced garlic
and kimchi juice.)
It smells like a proper dish.
It's ready. Close the lid now.
We need to boil it for an hour now.
- An hour?
- Yes.
(Will it be ready
in an hour from now?)
- Close the lid.
- Do we need to boil it for an hour?
Kimchi needs to turn soft.
If we boil it for an hour...
(The cooking time
continues to lengthen.)
Yesterday, we had
the exact same situation.
Let me put it here.
Suk Jin, don't ruin it.
- I am not ruining it.
- Leave it as it is.
It's tilted. Take a look.
It's tilted. It should be level.
Hold on.
- It's Se Chan's dish.
- I have had a feast for 30 years.
Let Se Chan do it.
What are you saying?
- You have had a feast for 30 years?
- You punk.
What?
- What?
- You punk.
- What's that?
- I want to boil the rice.
Do you want to salvage it?
Yes. I will add water and boil it.
We can discard it if it fails.
(So Min brings the leftover rice
from yesterday.)
You shouldn't do that.
(The breakfast menu was tteokguk.)
I think you made a mistake.
- So Min.
- Did you add water?
Wasn't our mission to make tteokguk?
Why are you making braised kimchi...
and rice?
We just needed to eat tteokguk.
Why are you creating more work?
Seriously.
Stop opening the lid.
Do you want to eat?
I am hungry.
(Suk Jin must be hungry for real.)
This is nice.
- What?
- This is nice.
This is...
It's bound to be tasty.
But it tastes bad.
Try it.
It's strange that it tastes bad.
- It's good.
- Is it tasty?
- It's becoming tasty.
- Let me try it.
- Is it becoming tasty?
- Yes.
This is...
- It's bound to be tasty.
- Right?
- It's bound to be a hit.
- It's becoming tasty.
- It's nice.
- It's so tasty.
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
- It's bound to be tasty.
- It looks tasty.
It's bound to be a success.
You said it will be a failure.
- No.
- I didn't mean it like that.
I think he will gnaw on the ribs
like crazy.
- It was salty.
- I said he will only eat the ribs.
It was salty. It became tasty
because we added more water.
You are supposed to add water
towards the end.
- Now,
- I make it all the time.
we can make tteokguk.
- Let's make it.
- Okay.
All right. Hold it.
- Hold on.
- Be careful.
Okay.
My spoons won't go in.
Take off your gloves first.
- No. It's okay.
- Did you say "spoons" just now?
- I said "fingers."
- You said "spoons" just now.
- What's wrong with your hearing?
- Suk Jin did this earlier.
- I said "fingers."
- "My feet are cold."
(He rubbed his hands and said,
"My feet are cold.")
(Suk Jin's body is full of lies.)
I asked him,
"Do you mean your hands?"
And he said, "My feet are cold too."
"My feet are cold too."
Suk Jin is disoriented.
Suk Jin, come on.
Jae Suk, here we go.
One, two, three.
I said "fingers."
How big is it?
- We can put it on the top.
- We should be careful.
- The gloves are fireproof.
- Hold on.
How does it work?
We can put it on the top.
How? Like this?
- Come on.
- Yes. You should go over there.
For goodness' sake.
I told you that they will get stuck.
(He is clumsy until the end.)
- Shall we add the dumplings?
- Let's add the dumplings.
Do we add all of them?
There are too many, right?
- What?
- There are two bags.
There are meat dumplings
and kimchi dumplings.
We need to add minced garlic now.
Se Chan is good.
He is good at cooking.
His cooking skills shine
at a place like this.
- Do you add the green onion now?
- No, add it at the end.
We add it at the end, right?
We need to add the eggs too.
- The eggs.
- Yes.
(It's time to add the eggs.)
The eggs are frozen.
The eggs? It's because it's cold.
I know that.
Why wouldn't I know that?
We should add green onion
to the eggs.
Why are you adding green onion?
- What?
- Why are you adding green onion?
This is how you do it.
- No, you add it separately.
- No, it's tasty this way.
Haven't you made it this way?
Why did you...
Are you making scrambled eggs?
- No.
- Don't you add it separately?
- No, this is how you do it.
- Suk Jin.
- This is a way to do it.
- Green onion...
It's a cultural difference.
Can't you try it this way?
- What kind of culture is this?
- My family makes it this way.
If we do something like this again,
you shouldn't come.
It will be tasty.
- I can't believe you guys.
- So Min,
we should pull them apart.
- What?
- The rice cake slices.
The rice cake didn't harden.
It looks tasty.
- See?
- Why did you add green onion?
It will be tasty. Try it.
I don't see it.
Now...
See? The green onion got separated.
You guys don't know how to cook.
I bet it tastes amazing.
Is it tasty?
Boil it some more.
- It's good.
- It's tasty.
Once we add pepper, it will be over.
It's done. It's time to scoop it
into the bowls.
It's time to wake everyone up.
Shall I tell them to come out?
- Yes.
- Tell them to get up.
- Here you go.
- It smells delicious.
Jong Kook, come on out.
It looks delicious.
It looks amazing.
(They made
the right amount of tteokguk.)
It looks great.
- Guys?
- Yes?
Guys, what are you doing?
Is the breakfast ready?
Wake up. What time is it?
- It's cold.
- We were waiting.
Wake up and come on out.
Let's go.
It's cold, right?
- It's cold.
- The weather is insane outside.
It's too cold.
Don't you want to eat here?
We should eat outside.
How was it done in "Family Outing?"
We ate outside.
Did you eat outside?
(The delicate man
doesn't understand.)
I don't understand.
It smells delicious.
Jong Kook, come on out.
It looks delicious.
It looks great.
(Her hair is a mess.)
Did you set the table?
(They wake up one at a time
looking like they were just born.)
- It's so cold.
- Hey.
All right.
(Looking around)
When you have a place like this,
it wouldn't be hard...
to set up a pull-up bar.
- Hey.
- I always wonder about that.
You just need a screwdriver
to set up a pull-up bar.
Who...
(Sighing)
would use a pull-up bar?
I would love to hang from it.
(He is going through a withdrawal
since he hasn't worked out.)
I would love to work out my muscles.
Hurry up and come on out.
Woo Jae.
(He hears his name
as soon as he wakes up.)
Haha.
(Other members wake up
one at a time.)
Come on out, Haha.
- Okay.
- It's cold, right?
I will scoop out the dumplings.
Go ahead.
The food came out tasty.
(The tteokguk with dumplings
looks delicious.)
Here you go.
Thank you.
We made tteokguk in the end.
(He gives a bowl each.)
- Here you go.
- Come here and eat.
- How many bowls did you prepare?
- The bowls...
- Woo Jae.
(Ji Hyo woke up
with disheveled hair.)
(Braised kimchi with back ribs
is almost ready.)
- What's this?
- Come on over.
- Let's eat.
- Let's eat and go back inside.
I did my best,
so I hope the food tastes good.
I can't believe him.
- Did he prepare it alone?
- He is so annoying.
What's up with him?
- He is so annoying, Se Chan.
- Did you do all the work?
- I did my best.
- He is the hero.
- Suk Jin.
- He is ridiculous.
Suk Jin is the hero
behind the breakfast.
What kind of a comment was that?
Seriously.
- Seriously.
- "I did my best?"
So Min and Se Chan did all the work.
He said it so generously too.
The wall.
My head felt like it was outside.
Since Se Chan joined,
the food improved so much.
Let's eat.
- Let's eat.
Hurry up and eat.
(Tteokguk warms up their stomachs
after the cold night.)
Isn't it tasty?
- Let's see.
- It's tasty.
- Yes.
- It's tasty, right?
Hey, this is so good.
- It's so delicious.
- This is nice.
It's really good.
The rice cake is so chewy.
(Amazed)
- You did well.
- It's delicious.
This is tasty.
- It's really good.
- I know.
This is top-class. I mean the taste.
I should eat it right away.
(Gobbling up)
It feels like we just got here.
How time flies.
The kimchi dumpling is good.
- Everything is good.
- I really like it.
I should eat some dumplings.
The kimchi dumpling is good.
After eating rice cake
and dumplings,
I'll stop by the gym on my way home.
You'll stop by the gym?
That's my plan.
I'll eat some rice cake.
Rice cake makes me stronger.
- Rice cake is carbohydrate.
- Right.
This is good.
- The meat tastes good too.
- Right.
Try the meat. It's tasty.
(It's nice to hear Woo Jae eat something
after a long time.)
- Jae Suk is good at it.
- Right.
(Yoom)
I should sleep shivering with cold
more often.
- Why?
- It gives me an appetite.
- Really?
- Good for you.
I shivered like this while sleeping.
It feels like I exercised.
Right.
By the way...
It's good to be home.
There's no place like home.
He says that to finish the shoot.
- Suk Jin, do you have plans?
- No.
- I saw him make an appointment.
- What's the rush?
"Hey, I think
I'll be there by lunchtime."
He made an appointment.
- It's not like that.
- "Sure."
"Yes. I think I'll be back
by lunchtime."
Hey, that's not true.
They suddenly wanted to cook
braised kimchi with back ribs,
so I blamed them.
"Tteokguk is enough for breakfast."
"Why do you want to cook
braised kimchi with back ribs?"
When we got here yesterday,
I was like...
"How are we going to spend
a whole day here?"
- But time passed quickly.
- Time flew.
I feel like I just got here.
Doesn't it feel like
we just got here?
Time goes so fast.
- Why are you wrapping things up?
- That's fake.
Why are you saying things
to wrap up the shoot?
You know
the value of labor is priceless.
That's because we kept
doing things without a break.
- It's because of busy work.
- So we weren't bored.
- We never stayed still.
- Exactly.
So we're spinning the wheel.
All right.
It's been 24 hours
since we got here yesterday.
Yes.
What is this from last night?
Last night,
those people were chosen...
- by the audio team.
- What did they do?
(Haha was wearing the mic
through the night.)
(Woo Jae made a good sound
cooking the meat.)
(Haha giggled a lot
and made others laugh.)
(Jae Suk played some music
that's good for the New Year.)
Including the 2 slots for the rest,
we have 6 slots left.
You can put the names
you want on them.
- Over here?
- Yes. You can decide.
I have only one name, so pick me.
- I need one too.
- How many? Two, four...
All right then. What about this?
Hang on.
Except these two,
we have slots from 7 a.m. to 11 a.m. here.
We should choose four people
who worked hard.
- Gosh.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- That's not right.
- Why not? What do you want?
We should take a vote as well.
- Among the members?
- Among the members.
What do you think
it should be about?
Those who ate a lot of dumplings.
Eating a lot of dumplings?
- Just say what you want.
- Those who enjoyed the breakfast.
Or the one who worked hardest
to cut the rice cake.
What about the one
who brought rice cake?
I don't think it has to be
about the morning.
It can be something
about last night.
The one who slept well.
- She's talking about herself.
- That's you.
- You're the one who slept well.
- It's you.
Your face shows that
you had a good night's sleep.
- I recommend Suk Jin.
- Why?
Because he woke up looking healthy.
Thank you.
- I'm so grateful.
- When I woke him up this morning,
he didn't get up,
so I was really worried.
Thank you so much.
- Palm face down or up
- Who shows the different one.
It's Ji Hyo.
(Jong Kook enjoyed tteokguk,
Suk Jin woke up well.)
(Se Chan prepared breakfast.)
(Ji Hyo slept well in the cold.
So Min is cute.)
(Ji Hyo won the game.)
We just put up Ji Hyo's name.
- It's her again.
- Ji Hyo is amazing.
Now we will choose the members
to win the prize.
The prize is a piece of gold rabbit.
- It's cute.
- This is nice.
The same name can be picked again.
You will spin the wheel three times.
Okay.
I'll try spinning it.
All right.
Now, President Ji will spin it.
- I'll spin it.
- President Ji will do it.
- Haha, we will give a slap.
- If you complain, you get a slap.
If you complain, you'll get slapped.
- I'm serious.
- You'll get slapped in the face.
I'll spin it.
You spun it well. It looks good.
(The first wheel of fortune
is spinning.)
(Who will be lucky in the New Year
with the gold rabbit?)
- It's here.
- It's going well.
- It's coming to my name.
- Again.
(It narrowly escaped So Min's name.)
Spin it again.
(Spinning the wheel again)
President Ji, gosh.
- This is so thrilling.
- He's good at spinning.
I really hate it
when someone else wins the prize.
This is just about the gold.
(Whose name is
the arrow pointing to?)
(Is it Jae Suk, Haha, or Ji Hyo?)
- It's me.
- Gosh.
It must be me.
Gosh, it's Woo Jae.
(Joo Cinderella wins.)
- Congratulations.
- Okay.
I'll just say one thing.
I accept it.
(The whole time
flashes before his eyes.)
Woo Jae, how many times
do I have to tell you that?
(He had to hear them
call his name the whole time.)
(Woo Jae continued the tradition
of hard-working Long Legs.)
- It's Woo Jae.
- Me?
- Just take it.
- Can we spin it again?
- Woo Jae wins.
- Let's spin it again.
- Woo Jae, it's for you.
- This is the second.
- Gosh, Woo Jae.
- All right.
(The 2nd wheel)
- I just want one.
- Just once.
(Who's the second member
to win the gold rabbit?)
Jae Suk has his name
on three spots.
I'm so unlucky.
(Is the wheel stopping?)
(Is it Jae Suk who got 3 slots?)
One more.
(Is it So Min who's so unlucky
when it comes to prizes?)
(Jeon So Min wins.)
Congratulations, So Min.
Cross!
- Thank you.
- Give me a slap and do it again.
We can do this again
if I get slapped in the face.
- What?
- Let's do it again.
What did you say?
- If you slap me, we do it again.
- Go ahead and spin it.
- This is the last one.
- The last one.
- Please.
- Who's the winner?
Please.
- I really want to get the gold.
- Just this once.
- I have my name on three spots.
- I want the gold.
- Please.
Gosh.
- Jeon.
- Let's do it again.
It's Jeon.
- This is cute.
- Gosh.
(Surprised)
- Darn it.
- This doesn't count.
Is she getting one more?
Thank you so much!
Thank you, everyone. Happy New Year!
- Yes!
- Thank you.
Happy New Year. Thank you.
I want to get slapped.
I want to spin it again.
Woo Jae. My gosh.
- The year 1986, cross!
- Cross!
- But this is...
- She can't win twice.
That doesn't make sense.
Hyung In says it counts.
Even if she said so,
we can refuse it.
Let's go home.
So the 24 hours are over.
Should we ask the guest
how he's feeling?
I bet he liked it.
- Woo Jae.
- He's not a guest. He's our family.
Me? I don't have
anything special to say.
- All right then.
- What?
Don't say anything.
- All right.
- I was...
- going to say something now.
- You don't have to.
You don't have to force yourself
to say something.
- But I...
- You should learn from us.
Right.
Anyway, I was comfortable as always.
Thanks to everyone...
That's a cliche.
- You should've stopped talking.
- Right.
This is enough.
- He's just...
- Just take the rabbit with you.
All right then.
This is the Year of the Black Rabbit.
Let's give our viewers
greetings for the New Year.
- Say Happy New Year.
- Should we make a deep bow?
All right.
- Then...
- Will you bow here?
He's saying that
because he's on a good spot.
It's covered with snow here.
I'll take a step forward and do it.
Suk Jin,
he should bow to the fiery pit.
- Look.
- You're so mean.
- To the fireplace.
- He might burn his cap.
- Right in front of him...
- Hey.
- He doesn't have anything here.
- We should express our gratitude.
- But...
- Just do it.
The fireplace is
right in front of him.
But we wouldn't be on Running Man
if it weren't for our viewers.
Let's go over here
and make a deep bow then.
All right.
This looks nice.
Let's do it there.
Just find a spot
that's good for you.
- Can I be anywhere I want?
- Whatever you want.
Whatever works for you.
- Find a place that works for you.
- All right.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- What about this?
- Find something that works for you.
(They all choose spots
that are sunny and clean.)
Get ready.
- I'll do it here.
- Okay.
This is nice.
I'm okay
because I'm wearing a long jacket.
- All right.
- My gosh.
Suk Jin, don't try
to give a lick and a promise.
You should do it right.
- Why are you doing this?
- You were going to do this.
- You can't do this.
- Why not?
I can make a deep bow like this.
- Gosh.
- I like it here.
- I'm ready now.
- All right.
It's the year 2023,
Year of the Black Rabbit.
- Happy New Year.
(Running Man will keep on running
with big laughter in the year 2023.)
(People fight in life.)
(Fight for energy)
(Fight for food)
(Fight for love)
(For this slack and loose fight,)
(real fighters are here!)
(Choo Sung Hoon, Kim Dong Hyun)
(Jung Chan Sung, Choi Doo Ho)
(Overwhelming destructive power)
(With the beasts
who got out of their cages,)
(two trainers want
to play a big game.)
(The top fighters' salary is...)
(five dollars?)
(That's too little!)
(He boasts
about his dodging skills.)
(Hitting him in the head)
(But their values are dropping.)
I injured my leg.
I'll show you my thong.
What?
Why would we see your thong?
(And the real fight
of the fighters begin.)
(It's a food chain where you get eaten up
when you're off guard.)
(The winner will take the throne!)
(Salary Fighter)