(January 2, 2023,
the first shoot in the New Year)
(At 6:56 a.m.,
near Nodeul Island at Han River)
Thank you.
- Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
(He gives the production staff
greetings for the New Year.)
Thanks to you,
we came to work early today.
It's not because of me. It's just...
(The reason
they came to work at 7 a.m. is...)
(The mission
from the Christmas Special)
(The first shoot of 2023
will be moved up by 10 minutes.)
So we thought it would be good
to see the sunrise together.
- What?
- The sunrise?
(They joked about the sunrise,
but it's finally happening.)
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Hello.
Happy New Year.
All right.
Happy New Year to you too.
Suk Jin, hurry up.
- What?
- Just hurry and come here.
- Hello.
- Happy New Year.
Thank you.
(Everyone is coming on time.)
- Gosh.
- This is nice.
It's nice to be out...
- when it's dark.
- That's fake. It's not nice.
It's too early in the morning.
He was sleeping until 6:30 a.m.
I woke up at 6:30 a.m.
- You can barely open your eyes.
- Right.
By the way, I didn't know
we could see the sunrise here.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
We should've gone straight to
the filming spot. Why are we here?
Maybe to park the cars here.
- Thank you.
We could've gathered here.
Just stop complaining.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Happy New Year.
- Hi. Happy New Year.
- There are benches.
- Hey.
- We should sit here...
- This is cool.
and watch the sunrise.
- Happy New Year!
- My gosh.
The cameras are all set.
- Happy New Year!
- My gosh.
- The cameras are all set.
- You know what?
- He just grumbled a lot in the car.
- About Suk Jin...
In the car, he was like...
"Hey, why did we come
all the way here?"
- "We could've gathered here."
- "Why did we gather there?"
And now he's like, "Happy New Year!"
- That's fake.
- Ji Suk Jin's...
- fake life.
- I wish you all the best.
Gosh, this place is really nice.
Seriously, this spot is perfect
for a special occasion.
- This is nice.
- Go sit. It feels different.
It feels different when you're seated.
You should see it.
- Gosh, Jong Kook.
- Try sitting down.
Have a seat and look at it.
Aren't I right?
Se Chan, imagine you're
sitting here with your girlfriend.
This is crazy.
Hey, So Bal.
- Hurry and come here.
- Happy New Year.
Hi.
- All right.
- Jeon So Bal
- Hey.
- Hey, stop it.
Jeon So Bal
- Happy New Year.
- So Bal.
That's funny.
So Min, the bench is an event spot.
- It's like New York.
- There was...
a couple kissing earlier.
- Really?
- I'm serious.
- Is that true?
- In the morning?
Morning kiss.
- That's amazing.
- Se Chan.
Se Chan, you should go
sit there with So Min.
- You tried it.
- Didn't you see it?
It feels different
when you're seated.
- Try sitting there.
- Did you not watch MBC?
- The golden time is over.
- We should try harder.
We have to work harder.
We should at least kiss.
- We need some noise marketing.
- Hey.
Hang on.
(Running hurriedly)
Watch the sunrise.
- This looks really nice.
- It looks pretty.
- It's so pretty.
- This is amazing.
This is what I need
in front of my house.
(Working hard)
- Look at the photos.
- My goodness.
Send them to me.
- This looks great.
- My gosh.
Guys, it's done.
This will make the main piece.
We got it. This is it.
- Hey.
- We should update it.
I think So Min is serious.
Her feelings are growing.
- Seriously...
- They are growing.
Why isn't Ji Hyo here yet?
Ji Hyo is wandering around here.
- Is she lost?
- So she won't...
- watch the sunrise.
- Is it just us?
- She will miss the sunrise.
- This is just real.
- It's funny she got lost.
- She took the wrong way.
- This can be confusing.
- She's here.
- Ji Hyo.
- You're here.
I'm glad that you made it on time.
What took you...
- It's all right.
- She's holding the microphone.
- It's okay.
- I'm really sorry.
- It's no problem.
- Are you a correspondent or what?
- We know.
- We understand.
- You took the wrong way.
- Seriously...
- I was right over there.
- Okay.
- We know.
- Reporter Song Ji Hyo.
- We went back and forth.
- Seriously, it was really...
- Why are you late?
- Hey.
- You're at the scene...
- so early in the morning.
- I feel like crying.
- Yes.
- It's no problem.
- Don't put it on your jacket.
- Why are you wearing it like that?
- Wear it underneath.
- Don't do that.
Don't pay attention to me.
- I'm so sorry.
- Reporter Song Ji Hyo.
- Don't cry.
- It's okay.
- We know.
- Right.
It was really funny.
The very scene was hilarious.
Thank you, Reporter Song Ji Hyo.
Anyway, Ji Hyo, the sun...
- is not up yet.
- It's not up yet.
Isn't the sun up already?
No. You'll see the round sun.
Gosh, it's really cold.
Hey, get over it.
Why isn't the sun coming up?
Get over it. If you feel cold,
- that means you lose.
- I heard today would be cold.
It's getting brighter.
There it is.
- It's not up yet.
- That's not it.
You just want to say that and leave.
- No.
- Do some computer graphic work.
- Right?
- We need the CG work instead.
(Amazed)
It's not up yet.
You just want to leave.
But it's not up yet.
(Maenggu tries to spread fake news.)
Hey, my ears are cold.
It's coming up.
- It's coming up.
- It's up.
- There it is.
- It's coming up.
- It's really coming up.
- My gosh.
I've never watched the sunrise...
- at Han River before.
- This is my first time.
- It's coming up. I can see it.
- Why didn't we try this sooner?
It's getting bigger.
- Hey, look.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
- Look at that.
- It's really fast.
- It's so bright.
- My gosh.
- This is amazing.
- It's coming up really fast.
- I know.
I didn't know it was so quick.
- Gosh.
- It's dazzling.
The sunrise is unbelievable.
- This is so nice.
- It feels so good.
- It's like a gem.
- Look at the sun.
- It looks like a gem.
- This is great.
I have to take a picture of this.
- It won't look as good as this.
- Take it and share it with us.
It's coming up really fast.
- Happy New Year!
Stay healthy.
- Be happy and stay healthy.
- Stay healthy.
- Happy New Year.
- Be rich.
- Everyone.
- Be wealthy.
- Hey, it's a backlit photo.
- It's done.
- No, it looks good.
- Jong Kook, come closer.
One, two, three.
- Okay.
- It's nice.
Jae Suk has changed a lot.
He wants to take selfies now.
I have to take it.
What is this? Five minutes?
What?
- It's a countdown. Five minutes.
- What?
(The countdown suddenly starts.)
- What is it?
(The production staff
is being silent.)
Tell us.
- What?
- What's that?
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- My goodness.
- What are you doing?
(Out of control)
(A group of men in suits
is coming at them.)
What is it? What's that?
- Darn it.
- My gosh.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Kim Dong Hyun!
(Martial artist, Kim Dong Hyun)
Hey. Stop it.
Look who's here.
- Isn't he Dong Hyun?
- It's Dong Hyun.
(Martial artist, Choo Sung Hoon)
Who are you?
Aren't you Choo Sung Hoon?
My goodness. Hello.
Why are you doing this? My gosh.
- Come here.
- Wait.
Mr. Jung Chan Sung. I'm a big fan.
I'm a big fan.
Why are you doing this?
What's going on?
What are you doing here? My gosh.
- What is going on?
- Gosh.
- What was that?
- I was really startled.
I thought they were thugs.
- Why are you being like this?
- Just get it over with.
(The thugs are here
to finish things.)
We can end it together.
Hang on.
(The muscular men work together
to deal with Little Ha.)
Are we done?
(Giggling)
What?
(A loach with strong viability)
- I was really surprised.
- Where's Jae Suk?
- I think he ran away.
- Did he run away?
- He's such a coward.
- Where did he go?
- Jae Suk is a coward.
- He's up there.
- Dong Hyun, Jae Suk is up there.
- You didn't rip off his name tag.
You should go get him.
- Chan Sung.
- Behind the car.
(He's coming to catch the loach.)
Behind the car. You should run.
- He's up there.
- Go.
The pure fighters are here.
(Will Jae Suk be able to survive
for the next 50 seconds?)
I'll go left.
You go right.
- Look at Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is...
- Hey.
- My goodness.
(Startled)
- Look at Jae Suk.
- He's caught.
What's going on?
- What was that?
- He's such a coward.
You all are surprised, right?
Today's guests are
the four pure fighters,
Choo Sung Hoon, Kim Dong Hyun,
Jung Chan Sung, and Choi Doo Ho.
(Jung Chan Sung, Choo Sung Hoon,
Kim Dong Hyun, Choi Doo Ho)
(Korea's first martial artist
who won the UFC title match)
(Korean Zombie, Jung Chan Sung)
(A martial artist who used to be
the national judo athlete)
(The 48-year-old living legend)
(Sa Rang's dad, Choo Sung Hoon)
(The first Korean martial artist
who entered the UFC...)
(with the most wins in the UFC)
(Stun Gun, Kim Dong Hyun)
(The genius and Korea's
youngest fighter to enter the UFC)
(Super Boy, Choi Doo Ho)
(What's today's race that will
feature the 4 muscular men?)
We have four guests here today.
And we will have
the Salary Fighter Race.
You'll be divided into two teams
with a trainer and a vice-trainer.
- Good.
- The guests selected the trainers.
Se Chan is the trainer,
- and Jae Suk is the vice trainer.
- Are you the trainer?
All right.
(The fighters selected
the petty trainers.)
- Are you the chairman?
- So Min, move over.
- Move over.
Gosh, this is...
You have the face of a chairman.
- This is about salary negotiation.
- The trainer?
So this is like...
- the rookie draft.
- Okay.
- Oh, that thing?
- The baseball thing.
The draft.
That means you should
get on my good side.
(This is a rookie draft
of the 9 athletes.)
First, Se Chan, who is
the chairman here, gets 400 dollars.
- I get 400 dollars?
- That's a lot.
Jae Suk, the vice chairman...
- gets 300 dollars.
- Come on.
Now, the trainers will
evaluate the athletes here...
- and recruit them to their teams.
- The draft.
- You should get on my good side.
- The trainers will pay...
the athletes their salaries
with the money they just got.
You should be in our good books.
At the end of the race,
between the two trainers,
- the one with more money will win.
- I see.
And the trainer who loses
will get a penalty.
- We will get a penalty?
- Yes.
Meanwhile,
the athletes need to earn...
as much salary as possible
through salary negotiations.
The two athletes with
the biggest salary will get prizes.
- And number nine gets a penalty.
- Okay.
Now, the two trainers will start
recruiting athletes.
To sum up, we should try
to pay as little salary as possible.
- That's right.
- And the athletes need to make...
- Get the biggest salary.
- as much money as possible.
- You should make it reasonable.
- We will pay reasonable salaries.
There aren't many athletes
who deserve a lot of money.
You know what?
I don't want those who can cause
a headache on my team.
But this is what I believe.
They all used to be
professional athletes,
so they would remember.
They're just like us.
- Okay.
- The thing is,
a salary is a matter of pride.
Please stay quiet.
- Quiet.
- It's a matter of personal pride.
- Be quiet.
- Silent.
I'm glad he brought it up.
- Pro sports are driven by money.
- Isn't that true?
- That's true.
- I agree.
So you can't just tell me...
- to think of the old days.
- Trainer Yang and I...
are willing to pay
a reasonable amount.
As far as I remember,
Trainer Yoo paid me 10 cents before.
Let's not do that.
- I get it. Just have a seat.
- Chan Sung.
Imagine your pay is lower than mine.
Wouldn't you be upset?
I have a strong sense of loyalty.
So I just get what they offer.
Don't lie.
- Listen to me.
- I know that's a lie.
- "Don't lie."
- Are you serious?
- I never betray my people.
- Wait.
I just need enough money to live on.
Jung Chan Sung, pass.
- All right. Jung Chan Sung.
- That's a lie.
- I like that attitude.
- Right.
- That's not true.
- Enough money to live on?
Listen to me.
- He talks a lot.
- Listen to me.
- Sung Hoon is talktative.
- Go ahead and talk.
I was talking about matches
with him the other day.
He said, "I'm not doing it
if I don't get enough money."
You said this.
- I know.
- All right, then.
Let me be honest with you.
It's all about money
for professional athletes.
- All right.
- My gosh.
- That's true.
- I want to get paid a lot.
- To buy rings and bracelets.
- Now that you say that...
It's your personal taste,
so I don't want to argue about that,
but I think you have
large expenditures.
You're wearing diamond earrings.
- And he's wearing bracelets.
- Aren't you also in...
the moneylending business.
(His flashy jewels catch
the stingy trainers' eyes.)
- "Moneylending business?"
- Look at the jewels.
- With the money he makes...
- You don't seem like an athlete.
Actually, every piece has
its own meaning.
- What meaning does this have?
- This is...
- You're wearing many bracelets.
- What meaning does a diamond have?
I bought all this
after I won a fight.
As a gift.
- When you win?
- I give it to myself when I win.
So it means something to me.
When I lose a match,
I sell one of them.
Really?
- So you don't have many left.
- I have only a few left.
- You have only a few pieces.
- Really?
He will probably lose them all soon.
Right. I have only four pieces left.
- That sounds very reasonable.
- That's funny.
It's a good idea.
- You buy it only when you win.
- You have your own reason.
- And you sell it when you lose.
- Right.
I buy one when I win.
That's what I do.
Sung Hoon, you are amazing.
Your career is impressive.
You used to be a judo athlete.
- That's right.
- That's what he used to do.
- He used to be an elite athlete.
- Right.
It's not like
he was an ordinary athlete.
- What is this?
- What?
What do we do with this?
(Laughing)
I mean... This is a little...
- Hang on a second.
- This...
- I'm not sure if I should read it.
- Which one?
- I'm not sure if this is okay...
- What is it?
"He's known not to wear underpants."
"He even said he would never
wear them for the rest of his life."
"He's known not to wear underpants."
"He even said he would never
wear them for the rest of his life."
What is this?
Are you still like that?
- Hey, it's just...
- Are you still like that?
Yes. I like not wearing underpants.
Actually, you're not supposed
to wear underpants in a judo match.
That's how I got into the habit.
Excuse me,
but are you not wearing any now?
- I'm at work now, so...
- You should wear them at work.
I do wear underpants these days.
But I wear a thong.
That's what I've been wearing.
Didn't you say you value comfort?
- Thongs?
- Aren't they uncomfortable?
Hold on a second.
- Thongs...
- But...
- What's wrong?
- It feels like something is stuck.
- Isn't it better to go commando?
- You just made me uncomfortable.
I'm uncomfortable with all this.
These days,
thongs are the way to go for men.
- Why is that?
- That's what we should wear.
- Men wear them...
to get rid of panty lines.
Doesn't it feel like
you're walking on a tightrope?
But...
- A tightrope?
- Even with men,
it's also important
to have desirable buttocks.
If you wear underwear,
the outline of it will show.
I don't like seeing it on me, so...
- Back in the day...
- Yes?
A friend who works in the field
gave me one as a gift.
A thong?
Yes, he gave me three,
so I went out wearing them.
My wife said it was all right,
saying they were comfortable.
So I wore them.
After ten minutes,
I decided to put them on backward.
(Backward?)
- It was that uncomfortable?
- You put them on backward?
- How does that make sense?
- That's just as weird.
- How can you do that?
- The T part...
- It's pretty much the same.
- Backward...
The T part went in the front?
- I speak from experience.
- Hold on a second.
- Wait.
- The backside is too much.
- That's enough.
- It's just as bad in the front.
We're beginning a year...
- What's so wrong with that?
- talking about thongs.
- Why did you bring that up?
- I can't allocate much time.
Just be done with it.
Anyway, that was Sung Hoon.
- Right. Thanks.
- Next...
- We have Choi Doo Ho.
- The Korean Super Boy.
You...
He has many titles to his name.
You have no idea.
Aren't you the youngest here?
- That I am.
- You're 33.
- Lucky you.
- You're 33, so...
- So Min?
- Lucky him. He's the youngest.
- What are you doing?
- Why are you applying lipstick?
I got lipstick on my teeth,
that's all.
- Is that so?
- We never let things fly.
I'm informing you of this
just in case. He's married.
- Yes, he's married.
- Who?
- He got married in 2017.
You mean, Doo Ho?
- Yes, he is a married man.
- Wait.
I apologize, but...
- Yes, he got married.
- Wait.
I apologize, but...
- He got divorced.
- I'm divorced now.
- Is that so?
- Gosh.
- I'm divorced now.
- Is that so?
(Oh, dear)
Why did you write it down?
Goodness.
- Then...
- Was this really necessary?
Let's start over, then.
You should be on
"Invitation from Bachelor-agains."
- We'll correct that.
- Let us correct the facts.
We'll update his personnel file
with current facts.
Then...
- As of this moment, he's single.
- He's single!
I was married.
- It's been two and a half years.
- It's too funny to edit out.
- He was married, but...
- Sharing correct information...
is always important.
- Correct it online as well.
- Right.
It's not a bad way
to announce your divorce.
- Two and a half years ago.
- It's not so bad.
- We were late updating it.
- Okay.
- Anyway...
- It's understandable.
Being divorced isn't a flaw.
Next week, get ready for
"Invitation from Bachelor-agains."
Doo Ho can be on
- You can be on that show.
- I'll prepare for it right away.
Out of 19 matches,
he won 15 and only lost 4.
(Choi Doo Ho:
19 matches, 15 wins, 4 losses)
- How impressive.
- It really is impressive.
- Four losses...
- Well...
- In 2023...
- That's standard, right?
- There aren't many matches left.
- Dong Hyun's not agreeing.
- To what?
- Four losses.
Everyone here
only lost about four times.
We didn't lose many matches.
How many matches did you lose?
Only four.
- Really?
- You only lost four matches?
- Out of 30 matches, I lost 4.
- Really?
Why does it feel like
you lost more fights?
Why do I feel like I saw you
on the ground more?
We saw you lying
on the ground a lot.
- It feels that way.
- It's because...
the fights I lost
were worthy of highlight clips.
- I see.
- When he lost, he lost big.
I never went out swinging.
- That's right.
- I got knocked out.
- We saw you on the ground a lot.
- I know.
- I would get knocked out.
- You never went out swinging.
Sung Hoon lost seven matches.
That's quite a lot.
No wonder he doesn't have
much jewelry on him.
- Exactly.
- He should be wearing more.
- There should be more.
- I sold a lot of what I had.
Jung Chan Sung is your role model.
- Why is that?
- When I first started out,
people called me
the next Jung Chan Sung.
During the launching event
for the 2022 "Pure Fighter,"
you said this.
"Chan Sung has no funny bones,"
"and there wasn't anything
to learn from him."
(He actually said that.)
He said that
in a matter-of-fact way.
He's not wrong though.
- Really?
- That's the truth.
Isn't he funny at all?
Nothing he does is funny.
Chan Sung, tell us if it's true.
I have nothing to say.
- I also...
- He's sometimes funny though.
And on February 5, 2023,
at the UFC Apex in Las Vegas,
Doo Ho will make his comeback
after four years.
- That's what he has planned.
- That's right.
- The date's not that far away.
- I can't wait.
- It's in less than a month.
- Me too.
Next up is the Korean Zombie...
Jung Chan Sung.
His record speaks for itself.
17 wins and 7 losses.
In 2011, he won
the ESPN Submission of the Year...
- and has great fights.
- And many more.
- His victories were jaw-dropping.
- You're right.
He was the first Korean fighter
to compete in a UFC title fight.
- That's right.
- He fought in a title fight twice.
- Yes, twice.
- One was with Aldo.
There aren't many fighters...
who have fought
in a title fight twice.
- Really?
- It's very rare.
The UFC title fight
is more than just demanding.
- You have no idea.
- It's...
You wouldn't believe it.
- It's unprecedented.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
- Chan Sung is UFC itself.
And not just among Koreans.
- Look at him beaming.
- Out of all the fighters...
- You're loving this.
- Even among foreigners...
He has a lot of fans
outside of Korea as well.
- That's right.
- Is that so?
Every match he was in...
could be selected
as Match of the Year.
Whether he punched
his way to victory...
- Right.
- or won via submission.
He used unique techniques
and moves to win.
- They were cool to watch.
- That's right.
His matches were flashy.
Do you know why
he's called the Korean Zombie?
- Of course.
- Because he never yields.
- He never admits defeat.
- He kept on standing up.
You were known as the Cicada.
- Yes, the Cicada.
- The Cicada.
That was out of the blue.
- Why...
- He hung from his opponents.
- Hold on a second.
- He'd hang from his opponents.
His opponents
didn't have the strength to...
Hold on a second.
Was your name Kim Bong
before you had it changed?
- What?
- Why would you mention that?
Kim Bong?
Were you a pushover?
- Seriously? His name was Bong?
- Hold on a second.
It's written right here. "Kim Bong."
What's the Chinese character for it?
- I mean...
- Is this a joke?
Why would you talk about that
instead of my record?
- Was your name Kim Bong?
- It's not that bad.
Back in the day,
up until middle school,
my name was Kim Bong.
- You were a pushover.
- Until when?
- I'm sorry I laughed.
- I had it changed in ninth grade.
- For real?
- Yes.
My elementary school yearbook says
I am Kim Bong.
Bong.
Bong?
- Oh, dear.
- Dong Hyun.
- Yes?
- Why didn't we know about this?
Can I call you Bong
for the time being?
You should call yourself,
the Cicada Bong.
What?
You could take the market
from Maxbong sausage.
It sounds delicious.
Cicada Bong seems packed
with protein.
- Dong Hyun.
- Right?
Cicada Bong, I'm a pushover
The Cicada Bong.
- It'll bring in a lot of money.
- Bong.
Bong will be a hit.
This is what I went through
at the start of every year,
and that's why I had to
change my name.
At the beginning of the school year,
my classmates and my teachers...
I'd introduce myself as Kim Bong...
At first, the teacher would
put me down as Kim Bong Hee.
- Everyone starts off with that.
- Bong Hee?
I'd correct them and say "Kim Bong,"
and they'd put me down
as Kim Bong Yi.
I'd say that it's "Kim Bong."
Kim Bong!
- Just "Bong."
- It's like Bongyi Kim Sun Dal.
- Kim Bong Yi.
- You seem more approachable...
- thanks to the name.
- But...
Doesn't the name Bong
suit him though?
- Isn't it adorable?
- It's a pretty name.
- Bong is a hilarious name.
- Tell me about it.
You look like a Bong though.
Really?
- But I had too many nicknames.
- Like what?
Jjamppong, Pushover,
Bongyi Kim Sun Dal, and...
(Super childish)
Bongyi Kim Sun Dal?
- Like this.
- Jjamppong?
I called him
Bongyi Kim Sun Dal just now.
- Pushover.
- Bongyi Kim Sun Dal.
It's getting too hot for me.
Can I get a Bongbong?
They'd grab me and say
that they got lucky.
- I got lucky.
- Exactly.
That could also be one.
- The way I see it is...
- The name suits you though.
- It's a good fighter name though.
- That could be your name.
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- It's Bong Kim!
- Bong Kim.
(His ring name makes him look weak.)
- Bong.
- See?
Kim Bong.
He's not wrong.
His record is remarkable too.
He won 22 matches and lost 4 times.
- That's not easy, you know.
- It's insane.
Didn't you make it...
- to 6th in the rankings?
- Yes, 6th.
Ranking sixth isn't easy...
since there are about 300 fighters
in that weight class.
Out of all of them, he ranked sixth
which is remarkable.
- Of course. It's amazing.
- It sure is.
Couldn't your opponents
make it out from under your grip?
- They couldn't. No one was able to.
- No way.
It was the death grip.
- It's that difficult.
- It's a natural talent, then.
When he's all wrapped around you
like a cicada...
and you whisper "Kim Bong"
in his ear...
(The way to escape his deadly grasp)
Can you please stop
with the name jokes?
- Gosh.
- Let's say I was like this.
Are you Kim Bong?
Please stop with the name jokes.
He survived the cutthroat field
thanks to this move of his.
What Sung Hoon is left with
are his thongs,
and Dong Hyun is left with
his name Kim Bong.
(Choo "Thongs" Sung Hoon
and Kim Bong)
We're left with just those two.
Anyway, we were able
to hear from the four fighters.
- What about the rest?
- The rest?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
I don't know
what games we'll be playing today,
but whether I have to be funny or...
I'm good at games
where you need to be funny.
- He's naturally strong.
- He's good with anything...
that isn't forced or fake.
By the looks of it,
we have five fighters.
- The rest...
- The other four are rag dolls.
- Rag dolls?
- How about weaklings?
- Weaklings.
- Still, out of the four...
- Like Jeonsobari.
- I'm still above the other three.
Let us begin
salary negotiations, then.
They will come up to you
in groups of three.
The fighters can choose a prop
to show off their strengths.
They can show off other talents
when requested by the trainer.
First up, we have Choo Sung Hoon,
Choi Doo Ho, and Haha.
- Why is Haha in that group?
- Pardon?
I'm in the same group as them?
Oh, my. Why are you in that group?
Just as we said earlier,
let's not drag out negotiations.
We'll offer
as much as you seem to be worth.
- As much as you seem to be worth.
- Exactly. We'll do so.
He must be in great shape now
if he has a match in a month.
Oh, my. I mean...
He doesn't even have to show us.
We all know how great he is.
- It's an honor for me.
- I'm flattered.
My, this is insane. I'm amazed.
(His body is so muscular.
He's in his best shape.)
He has such a muscular body.
Of course.
He must be in his best shape now.
Why don't each of you tell us...
- Sell yourselves.
- Tell us about your abilities.
Doo Ho, what are you good at?
I have good dodging skills.
- Dodging skills?
- You're good at dodging?
If you throw this ball at me,
I'd never get hit.
- Really?
- Show us how you dodge a punch.
- That's a good idea.
- I'll do it.
- Jong Kook will do it.
- I might get hit if you punch me.
Then you can't say
that you're good at it.
- You can dodge a table tennis ball?
- That's right.
- Even from a short distance.
- Oh, really?
I can dodge it if you're this close.
- No way.
- Come on. I don't believe you.
- You mean, your face only, right?
- Then we'll give you three chances.
- Okay.
- He'll get hit all three times.
- I'll throw it from here.
- Stand closer to him.
- Right. You'll throw at his face.
- You can go closer to him.
- Can I throw it from here?
- Closer than that.
- I think he'll get hit.
Ready. Go.
He didn't get hit.
(He dodged it!)
- That was close.
- He threw it too lightly.
Suk Jin threw it too slowly.
- You should throw it more quickly.
- Suk Jin threw it too slowly.
(He dodged another ball!)
- He's right, Suk Jin.
- No.
- I think he's just bad at aiming.
- I'll throw it hard...
That's not true.
- I predicted your move.
- Okay. I understand.
Here we go.
- He got hit.
- Here we go.
(Strike)
- What was that?
- Forget it.
- Doo Ho, that's enough.
- He predicted my move. That's why.
- I'll offer you 20 cents.
- No. I threw it in the middle.
- I mean...
I didn't predict his move.
I just threw it forward.
He said he was good at dodging.
But what was that?
- What was that?
- And I heard a loud noise.
- He got hit really hard.
- It made a loud noise.
- Doo Ho, are you okay? I'm sorry.
- I'm fine.
We can't pay you much.
Is there anything else
you want to show us?
- Sung Hoon?
- Sung Hoon, it's your turn.
- Well... Then...
- Oh, my.
- Actually, I injured my leg.
- I see.
- So I can't move easily now.
- Okay.
Oh, all right.
That'll affect their offers.
Instead, I will show both of you...
my thong.
(He'll reveal his thong.)
- He'll show one side for each?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Why would he show them his thong?
- What is going on?
- Let's go over there.
- Why should we see your thong?
- I'll show you.
- Why should we see it?
- That's ridiculous.
- Why are you standing like that?
- What are you talking about?
- I can just pull my pants down.
My gosh. I mean, why would he...
- offer to show us his thong?
- Who would do that during a draft?
- Okay. Step back again for now.
- Don't show us your thong.
If things like that count,
I'll show you everything.
Anyway, Sung Hoon, we understand.
- He has an injured leg now.
- Right.
We'll take it into consideration.
- Haha, you're up.
- Haha.
I'll demonstrate
my dynamic visual acuity.
- What did you say?
- The dynamic visual acuity test?
The one
where you put it around your head?
- Do you hit it?
- How does it work?
I'll show you...
I haven't done this in a while.
- I'm not sure if I can do it well.
- How does it work?
Give me a second.
- I can tell he's done it before.
- How does it work?
- What's that?
- I'm ready. I'll start.
Two, three, four...
- I can't do it as I want.
- He's not good at it.
- Wait. Give me another chance.
- No.
(He begs for another chance
after three seconds.)
- That was disappointing.
- I already wrote it down.
I wrote down your salary
even before you came out.
Haha, he'll offer you one cent.
I asked you to offer me
more than one cent. Jae Suk.
You should've demonstrated
shadowboxing, at least.
Now, we'll start the negotiation...
since there's no need to drag it on.
We'll decide on your salaries first.
- We'll start at a low salary.
- You see, this is...
- You should consider that.
- Oh, man.
All right. We're ready.
Ready. One, two, three.
(Trainer Yang's offer,
Trainer Yoo's offer)
- His offer is 4.8 and 3.5 dollars.
- It's strange.
- It's 4.8 dollars and 3.5 dollars.
- What?
- Five dollars.
- That's so low.
- Three dollars and three cents.
- What?
- I wrote 2 cents.
- Only 3 cents?
(Trainer Yang's offer,
Trainer Yoo's offer)
- You increased it by one cent.
- Yes.
I increased it by 100 percent.
I was going to offer him 1 cent.
They're all so disappointed.
It's because we need money
to manage our team.
- Right.
- Doo Ho will definitely join...
- Jae Suk's team.
- Yes. I'm happy with his offer.
- He offered 50 cents more.
- Right.
I'll pay Sung Hoon 4.80 dollars.
- I got the best offers among us.
- I'll pay you 20 cents more.
Sung Hoon seems very disappointed
with our offers.
- He got 300 dollars earlier.
- He received 300 dollars,
- but he offered only 3.50 dollars.
- You offered him only 4.80 dollars?
- It's not even 48 dollars.
- That's too little.
- They received 300 and 400 dollars.
- This is only the beginning.
- We'll give you a raise later.
- Will you give me a raise?
- Yes.
I'll see how well you do.
- We'll negotiate again.
- You'll get a raise eventually.
Don't worry about it.
- I'll choose my team right away.
- Okay.
- Which team is it?
- I'll join Trainer Yoo's team.
- Great. Okay.
- Of course, he chose that team.
- Right. Of course.
- Of course, he wants to get paid...
- as much as he can.
- I offered 50 cents more.
He has less money
but is offering a higher salary.
That's right.
Good. Next up is Sung Hoon.
- Obviously, I choose him.
- Trainer Yang?
- Thank you.
- Trainer Yang? Okay.
- Yes. He offered me more money.
- That's right.
- Of course.
- He offered only 20 cents more.
- Please return to your seat.
- Of course.
- Okay.
- He should pick the higher salary.
- I never thought...
- Whose team will you join?
I'd contemplate because of one cent.
- Seriously.
- Hurry up.
- How the team grows matters.
- Right.
Let's make it work with Sung Hoon.
I'll raise your salary later. I have
100 dollars more than he does.
- What's your decision?
- I'll follow you to the end.
- Okay. Good.
- My gosh. I'm disappointed.
(Haha accepted three cents
and chose Trainer Yang.)
He chose his team for money
after all.
- It matters the most.
- I'll get paid only three cents!
He made his decision
because of money.
Only three cents.
Who are up next?
Jung Chan Sung, Kim Dong Hyun,
and Kim Jong Kook.
- They're all great.
- They're all amazing.
We'll probably offer a lot of money.
- Oh, my. It's intense.
- It'll be a fierce competition.
- I have nothing to show them.
- It's fierce.
- Right. It'll be fierce.
- The three of us are left.
Right. The three of us are left.
- They're similarly strong.
- Indeed.
- They could have a real match.
- Exactly.
(The three of them look
incredibly charismatic.)
- I'll just try this or something.
- First...
We should see what they're good at.
- Let's start with Bong.
- Okay.
I will...
Do something like
eating sausage fast.
- I'm good at that. I can eat fast.
- Right.
But unlike these legendary fighters,
- my specialty is wrestling,
- Yes.
- grappling, and jiu-jitsu.
- I see.
- Yes. So...
- You'll do it right here?
- So...
- How will you do it here?
My point is
that I have good balance.
- I see.
- It's hard to throw me down.
But I can throw anyone down easily.
That's what I'm best at.
So I'll show you how I keep balance.
- Okay. It's important.
- You never fall down?
Having good balance is great.
- Will you stand on it?
- I will...
jump with both feet on this ball.
- Really?
- How?
- For real?
- Go ahead. We'll catch you.
- Grab me if you think you'll fall.
- Okay.
- Grab us if you think you'll fall.
- Okay. I'll start.
- Yes.
I tried this many times
when I was younger.
- Like this. I'll do it again.
- Wait. Didn't you just fall?
- Can't you stand on top of it?
- I think you fell off the ball.
- On top of it?
- Yes.
You fell off the ball.
- I already showed you.
- What we pictured was this.
- Jumping up and standing here.
- I just showed you.
- I thought you'd stand on the ball.
- What was that?
- Exactly.
- Can't you do that?
I stood almost on top of it.
It wasn't so different.
- No. You stepped on here.
- Try again.
- No.
- Try to hold out for longer.
- Yes.
- You need a strong lower body.
- I held out for so long.
- How long will you hold out?
- Try again.
- As long as I want.
- How about five seconds?
- He said, "As long as I want."
- One.
- As long as I want.
- What was that?
- They're all bluffers.
- Right.
(Bong the Bluffer)
- I don't think he can do it.
- Hold out for five seconds. One.
- I made it.
- Two.
- I'm doing it the right way.
- Isn't he standing too low?
- But that's...
- Okay. Bong, that's enough for now.
- It was good enough, right?
- Bong, you can step back for now.
That wasn't really... All right.
- I can stand on top of it too.
- Yes.
- I can do it, but...
- Show us. One, two, three.
- I mean...
- Show us.
- Hold our hands. Ready, go.
- Stand on top of it.
- Like this?
- Yes, that's what we expected.
Clearly, you can't do it.
(Bong lost his balance
and ended up making everyone laugh.)
- Hey, you would never pull it off.
- Okay. Step back for now.
You would never pull it off.
- Next up is Jong Kook.
- Never.
- Yes?
- What will you show us?
I can't think of anything
to show you.
- How about shadowboxing?
- Show them your powerful punches.
- My punches?
- Do shadowboxing.
- Okay.
- He'll do shadowboxing?
- I'll start.
- Okay. Good. Keep going.
- What do you think?
- Keep going.
Hold on.
Wait. Stop. Who is punching here?
- He's a fraud.
- Hold on. What are you doing?
- Why did you tap his gloves?
- What's wrong?
- You did well. That was fun.
- He's a fraud.
- He swung the mitts like this.
- That was good.
- My gosh.
- He's a fraud.
- When you do this...
- He has a fun way of doing it.
That way, you can make a beginner
look stronger.
- Let's do it again.
- That's cool.
(They demonstrate their fake boxing
once again.)
(They have amazing teamwork.)
- It must be harder for Dong Hyun.
- That's good.
- Oh, my. Bong is...
- It's harder for Bong.
I see that
Bong is good at funny acts.
I want to give it a try.
Anyone can be a master
when practicing with me.
I didn't know
that Bong was good at that.
Chan Sung, what are you good at?
- I'll show you my kicks.
- Okay.
- Oh, he'll show us his kicks.
- His kicks?
- Can you hold the mitts for me?
- Oh, my.
- You should do it.
- Do we have one more?
Will you demonstrate a middle kick?
- Yes, a middle kick.
- We have one more.
Make it sound louder.
Sure. I'm good at that.
- They...
- Did you hear what they said?
- "Make it sound louder."
- He asked to make it sound louder.
(Even the international fighter
wants to make a louder noise.)
Don't worry about it.
I'm good at that.
Jong Kook showed his punches, so...
This is really enjoyable, right?
We all should know
that it's an honor for us.
Indeed. They're all
internationally recognized fighters.
- The internationally recognized...
- Oh, my.
- This is really...
- I'm worried his pants might burst.
They're professionals.
- Are you wearing underwear?
- Why don't fighters wear underwear?
- Yes, I am.
- I'm wearing underwear for sure.
- Okay.
Look at his hips and thighs.
(His demonstration starts!)
- I think that's high enough.
- I like the sound.
(Exaggerating)
One more time.
(Bong is practically blown away.)
You exaggerated, right?
You overacted, didn't you?
No, it wasn't like that.
I rarely get pushed back.
Hey, hold the mitts for me too.
- I rarely get pushed back.
- Hold the mitts for me too.
- It's hard to push me back.
- He makes his trainees feel good.
But he faked it.
His gym is really good.
The trainer at this gym is so good
at holding mitts.
(He kicks once in a satisfying way.)
- Let me try it again.
- That was amazing.
- Look. There's a waiting line.
- Let me try it again.
- You're so strong.
- He's so good at this.
- He's so good at it.
- I could feel it in my bones.
Why is he promoting his gym here?
- I just bought a membership.
- Come on.
Don't get fooled.
Are you okay?
(The mitts knocked Suk Jin out.)
(The bold So Min also came
to the popular gym.)
- That was good.
- He's really good at it.
Look at So Min. What is she doing?
- What is So Min doing?
- Good job.
What are you doing?
I want to see
some more of his kicks.
- Chan Sung, show us one more time.
- She's strong.
- She's really strong.
- Show us your knee kick too.
- Chan Sung, show us.
- Five kicks.
- He'll repeat kicks.
- That's good.
(Awesome)
Chan Sung, I want you on my team.
(The two trainers are mesmerized by
Korean Zombie.)
- I want Chan Sung.
- Did you hear that?
- Oh, my.
- Chan Sung, I want you on my team.
- He's incredible.
- I want you on my team.
- That was insane.
- He's amazing.
I'm impressed. That was incredible.
- He's really strong as expected.
- Right.
I can feel it in my bones.
I'll see bruises on my arms
tomorrow.
I like how he described it.
"I can feel it in my bones."
- I mean...
- He responds enthusiastically.
- You're strong too.
- Did it hurt when I kicked?
No, it didn't hurt.
- But I could feel it.
- Really?
You'll improve greatly
if you practice for three months.
(You'll improve greatly
if you practice for three months.)
- My gosh. He's promoting his gym.
- He's promoting his gym.
- His gym is at Garosu-gil.
He says So Min will improve greatly
in three months.
- She's not very strong now.
- He's a businessman.
But she'll be good at kicking
enough to defend herself.
You can see Dong Hyun at his gym.
- Really?
- At his gym.
- He's there occasionally.
- You should go at the right timing.
- True.
- Now...
- I'll spend more money this time.
I'm offering high salaries too.
- I knew it.
- They'll be offered a lot of money.
- Oh, my.
- Ten dollars?
I'm offering Chan Sung ten dollars
because of his kicks.
- Hey, come on.
- About five dollars.
I'll pay Jong Kook 50 cents.
(Se Chan's offer for Dong Hyun:
4.30 dollars, Jae Suk's: 4 dollars)
- My offer is 4.90 dollars.
- I'll pay Jong Kook 50 cents.
- What? Oh, my.
- I'll pay you a lot.
- Jong Kook.
- Fifty cents?
- I'll pay you a lot.
- He's offering me a lot.
It's because
you're as strong as the fighters.
- Oh, my.
- I think you can beat Dong Hyun.
That's why I'm offering you more.
You would definitely beat him.
- I lost to him in many games.
- You see...
I beat him in several games.
- That's right.
- On variety shows.
- I lost to him many times.
- Now...
- Let's start with Bong.
- Okay. Bong will go first.
- Well, four dollars...
- Four dollars.
It's not easy to keep balance
on a gym ball. That's too little.
But think about it.
The starting salary is four dollars,
- but it could keep increasing.
- True.
But it's easier to get a raise
when you start with a high salary.
- Right.
- You talk too much.
- But that's true.
- He talks too much.
- I'll join Se Chan's team.
- Okay!
- Jong Kook, what about you?
- Me?
- It's obvious.
- Yes.
Isn't it obvious? I choose Se Chan.
- I mean, that's a big difference.
- It's a big difference.
- I'm joining Chairman Yang's team.
- Okay!
(He picks Chairman Yang!)
- Then...
- We're on the same team.
- I was mesmerized by your kicks.
- He's offering such a high salary.
- I'd be loyal if I'm paid decently.
- Yes.
- I choose Jae Suk.
- Okay. Good.
- Okay.
- Our team is very strong.
- His kicks were amazing.
- Our team is the best!
- Okay.
- We're so strong.
I'm happy with our team.
Now, let's meet the last group.
(The three weaklings are
in the last group.)
- Good.
- Okay.
Oh, my. What is she doing?
(She tries to impress them
with her unique performances.)
She's trying to make us laugh.
- You don't clench your fists hard.
- Really?
I saw some people holding a lighter
in their hands like this.
(I saw some people holding a lighter
in their hands like this.)
- That's an old trick.
- She...
- She won't be helpful for the team.
- I'm surprised.
- I'll sit on the gym ball.
- Really?
- I won't fall down.
- Even if I push you?
(Falling down)
- What is this?
- What are you doing?
(The last one is
the powerful Ji Hyo.)
- She's so strong.
- His gym will become successful.
I must admit,
your business will be successful.
- What's shocking is...
- Yes.
that the total amount is
less than ten cents.
(The total amount is
less than ten cents.)
My goodness.
(Suk Jin: 2, 3 cents, Ji Hyo:
5, 4 cents, So Min: 1, 3 cents)
My gosh. Three cents and one cent?
Three cents.
- That's just about right.
- One cent?
I have to join the team
for only three cents.
- It hurts my pride so much.
- I...
But I'll join his team.
You can just pay me three cents.
- Seok Sam, you're on our team.
- Yes. I'll join your team.
- Gosh. I'm so upset.
- I...
- choose Chairman Yang.
- I choose Jae Suk.
- Oh, my. Thank you.
- Okay, So Min.
- Welcome to the team. Okay.
- I'll raise your salary later.
- Thank you.
- I'll give you a raise later.
We would've been offered less money
if we went first.
- Think about Haha.
- But it's too little.
Okay. The teams have been decided.
On Team Yoo,
there are Doo Ho, Chan Sung,
Suk Jin, and So Min.
- Well, we...
- Our team is weak.
On Team Yang,
there are Sung Hoon, Haha,
- Dong Hyun, Jong Kook,
- They have strong ones.
- and Ji Hyo.
- The other team is so strong.
The guest ripped off
the members' name tags earlier.
Those who ripped off two name tags
will receive extra three dollars.
(They receive three dollars
for a bonus.)
- Chan Sung has the most money.
- I ripped off two name tags.
After you change into
comfortable clothes,
- we'll begin the race.
- Okay.
- That was so funny.
- Our team is so weak.
Chan Sung is younger than me.
But Se Chan addresses him
as someone older than him.
(Chan Sung is younger than me.
But Se Chan uses honorifics.)
Jae Suk,
Chan Sung is younger than me.
- Chan Sung is?
- Bong!
- I wish you guys were the same age.
- So Min, stop it.
Really? How old are you?
I was born in 1987.
You're way younger than me.
- Are you proud?
- I feel great.
Because he's younger than me,
I feel like I'm stronger than him.
- Right?
- I thought he was older than me.
Let's sit down.
- Please sit with your team.
- Where? Oh, I see.
- Bong!
- Sit there.
All right.
We'll begin the first mission.
It's Pure Brain Fighter.
(The first mission is
Pure Brain Fighter.)
- "Brain Fighter?" Gosh.
- As many times as you get...
the correct answer in the quiz game,
you get to hit the punching machine.
- What about Bong?
- It's a team competition.
- The team...
- We should get many answers.
with the highest score will win.
The other team is at an advantage.
- But you're better at quiz games.
- That's not true.
- We have to get answers first.
- Right.
Bong might not get to hit it at all.
But... I know that I may be...
- below the average,
- Yes.
but I'm on a high level
among fighters.
(I'm on a high level
among fighters.)
- Really?
- I'm on a very high level.
- Including Sung Hoon,
- Really?
- Doo Ho, and Chan Sung, right?
- That's good.
I mean, among all of the fighters,
- I'd be ranked high.
- I see.
- I'm like a Mensa member.
- He...
- What are you talking about?
- Including all of them, right?
(Kim Bong claims to be an elite
among fighters.)
- Is it a difficult question?
- Yes, it is.
- A difficult question?
- Really?
- The topic is general knowledge.
- We can skip this one.
- Difficult questions are better.
- Here's your first question.
- Wait.
- Hey.
I know him. He's an artist.
Isn't he the scientist
from the movie "Back to the Future?"
- I can't see the photo.
- I can't see it.
- As I've aged, I can't see well.
- I can't...
I can't remember his name.
What should I do?
- Oh, he's...
- The Madonna painting.
- Is that person Madonna?
- Oh, him.
My gosh.
You have to write down his name.
(Andy Warhol)
I can't remember his name.
- The Madonna painting.
- I wrote down my answer.
Is that person Madonna?
Madonna?
- "The Madonna painting?"
- Write that down.
- Write that down for now.
- I couldn't hear him clearly.
- "The Madonna painting?"
- Just write that down.
- Hey, Madonna is...
- Gosh. Hold on.
- That's a man.
- Oh, is that a man?
- He's a man.
- Just write it down for now.
- He appeared in a movie, right?
- Exactly.
- That's right.
- There's a movie.
- He acted in "Back to the Future."
- Gosh, no.
What movie did he play in?
It's total chaos over there.
Doo Ho and Chan Sung,
do you know the answer?
I got a feeling.
- Really? Write that down.
- I got a feeling.
I wrote it down.
(Chan Sung's answer is "Lincoln,"
and Doo Ho's is "Einstein.")
- Gosh. I know who he is.
- What movie was it?
- Sung Hoon, did you write it down?
- What... Yes?
- No.
- Give me just one letter.
- We'll show you a related painting.
- Oh, no. Let me...
- Right. That's Madonna.
- Yes, Madonna.
- She's Marilyn Monroe.
- Marilyn Monroe.
Oh, boy. I'm embarrassed.
Marilyn Monroe.
- Marilyn Monroe.
- He said she was Madonna.
- Only the two of us didn't know.
He's the father of artwork.
What did you say? Art?
The father of artwork.
It's pop art, not artwork.
Is it?
Pop art?
Should we write down
the name of that person?
- No, that's not the question.
- I see.
He wasn't searching it
on the internet.
- He asked if that was the question.
- Right.
It's total chaos here.
- Doo Ho got confused.
- Hey, tell me just one letter.
(Did Chan Sung write
the correct answer?)
- You have three seconds left.
- Wait.
- Just a second.
- Should we write her name?
- No.
- You're not allowed to search it...
- Wait.
- on the internet. Put your phone...
- That's not what he's doing.
- "Should we write her name?"
- He's not searching it. Trust me.
No. Wait. My gosh.
- Wait. Give me a second.
- Tell me just one letter.
One, two, three.
Show your board.
Oh, right. It's Andy Warhol.
- I've never heard that name before.
- Ji Hyo.
- Did you copy his answer?
- So Min, did you copy my answer?
- I was the first one to write it.
- I know who he is.
Who is Andy Warhol?
(Chan Sung's answer
he was sure of is "DiCaprio.")
He wrote "DiCaprio,"
and he wrote "Einstein."
- Who is "Taken?"
- "Taken?"
Who's the lead actor of "Taken?"
"Warren Buffett."
"Jason Pop Art?"
Pop art?
(He wrote "Pop Art" as a name.)
- Sung Hoon, what did you write?
- "Jason Pop Art?"
I couldn't write anything. Gosh.
- My gosh. Their answers are funny.
- So Min got the correct answer?
Three members of this team got it right.
So Team Yoo wins.
- We won easily.
- Gosh. I'm so frustrated.
But Andy Warhol is...
Who is he?
Oh, you won't explain to us.
- He's a pop artist.
- Here goes your second question.
- Oh, that's a difficult question.
- Oh, yes.
- That's easy.
- A piece of something.
That's... Don't we all know that?
It's a very easy word.
(What should be in the blank?
The answer: Cake)
- A piece of... What was the word?
- I can't remember the word.
- It means something is very easy.
- It's a very easy word.
- I know many English expressions.
- Do you know the answer or not?
- I know. I've finished writing it.
- Do you?
- Really? You already wrote it down?
- I'm done.
- Chan Sung, Doo Ho, are you done?
- Yes.
They never ask.
(Chan Sung's answer is "war,"
and Doo Ho's is "soup.")
- They...
- In what situation...
In what situation
do you use this expression?
- It's an English proverb.
- I'm not sure.
- One.
- Wait.
That's too quick.
- You should give us time to think.
- Come on, Sung Hoon.
- How much more time do you need?
- I need a lot of time to think.
Jong Kook, do they use
this expression often?
- They say that very often.
- Really?
This is... Wait.
- You don't know the answer?
- It's not a variation.
- A piece of this.
- "A piece of"...
- It's a commonly used expression.
- I see.
This one is easy.
(He smiles after saying,
"This one is easy.")
Is it "pie?"
- Three seconds are left. Three.
- Let's go.
It's 1 of the 2 words... Wait.
- I should go with this word.
- Let's go.
- What do you mean by "1 of the 2?"
- What do you mean?
- I just took a wild guess.
- One. Please show your answers.
- Isn't it "apple?"
- It's "cake."
- Oh, it's "cake."
- It's either "pie" or "cake."
- "Pie."
I wrote "cake,"
but changed it to "pie."
- My answer is "soup."
- Mine is "apple."
- "Cake?"
- My answer is "soup."
- I wrote "soup" too.
- A piece of...
- The answer is "cake."
- Right.
- Isn't "pie" also correct?
- Okay.
- Team Yang wins this time.
(Team Yang wins.)
- I wrote "cake," but changed it.
- The answer is "cake."
I've never heard
that expression before.
- I changed it to "pie."
- How did you know?
- I lived overseas for ten years.
- I see.
- For ten years?
- Yes.
That's funny.
He said "ten years" in English.
- Here goes the next question.
- Let's move on.
(Mom's something disappears
and Dad's wrinkles are gone)
- Mom's
"Mom's something disappears
and Dad's wrinkles are gone."
- Mom...
- Clap, clap
- It's "clap, clap?"
The lyrics are sad. Dad can smile
when Mom's something disappears.
No. Can he?
Mom Su Jung
- Mom...
Mom...
Clap, clap
It's driving me crazy.
- I got it.
- Did you figure it out?
I got it.
I'll give you a hint.
I'm not sure if it's right,
but as Dad's wrinkles are gone,
Mom also...
His wrinkles are gone
as his worries disappear.
- Yes. In 1, 2, 3.
- Mom...
(Mom's worry disappears
and Dad's wrinkles are gone.)
In 1, 2, 3.
Mom's worry...
- Mom's sigh disappears
- I don't know.
The correct answer is "sigh."
Trainer Yoo's team earned one more.
Right. It's "sigh."
- I wrote "second child."
- Right.
"Mom's chest disappears?"
- "Chest."
- Who wrote it?
Why did you write "chest?"
- It's chest.
- Like heart.
- It's the heart.
- The heart.
- The chest.
- Her heart disappears?
I could've written it.
Okay. We won.
(The result of the battle among pure
fighters who listen to their hearts)
- It's 4 to 4.
- Each team can punch 4 times.
- Okay.
- We can win.
You win
when you get the highest score.
All right.
Shall we begin?
You guys go first.
You win
when you get the highest score.
- The highest score?
- Yes.
Then it's good.
- The highest score.
- The one with the highest score?
Gosh.
Look at Sung Hoon's fists.
I must do this.
- I must do this at least.
- You should make it.
Doo Ho.
Who wants to go first?
- I'll go first as I'm the weakest.
- Okay.
- Ssaebssaeb.
- Are we taking turns?
- We'll take turns.
- Can you use both hands?
I heard you can.
- Okay.
- We're on the same team.
Oh, we're on the same team.
I'm sorry.
- We can use both hands, right?
- Yes, you can.
Here I go.
(He wasn't competitive
during the quiz.)
Punch it hard.
- Did you punch it?
- Yes, I did.
The sound is gentle.
- It's gentle.
- Why did you punch like that?
No, it was strong.
(How many points will he get?)
- It's 8,100.
- That's good.
- Seok Sam.
- I'll go.
- It's about 8,100.
- Let me just win against him.
- Only four of us will punch it.
- Okay.
- He has no strength. He's weak.
- It's nice.
Do you usually throw a hook
or a regular punch?
Maybe straight?
He looks weak.
You were almost hit in your face.
- I punched the side.
- Why were you scared?
- It's okay...
as only the highest score matters.
- Okay. It's 7,443.
- It's 7,443.
- Se Chan has the highest score.
- Is Jong Kook next?
- Jong Kook.
- I'm not good.
- It'd be better for me to do it.
- Jong Kook.
- Look at him.
- The other team is...
Like this?
(His punches are strong as he
works out and boxes regularly.)
- He's strong.
- With this waist.
- Like this?
- Yes.
(Will he be able
to set the highest record?)
He's different.
- He didn't punch it precisely.
- He kind of missed it.
- He missed it.
- I missed it.
- It's fine.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- I missed it.
It's lower than Se Chan's score.
- Okay.
- I missed it.
You need to punch it precisely.
Only the highest score
matters anyway.
But having a lower score
than Se Chan is a little...
Exactly.
Dong Hyun.
- Stop.
- I mean...
- Even if you missed it...
- Gosh.
- What was the score?
He plays soccer like this too.
(This is my chance.)
He got bad hands
as well as bad legs.
When I box with someone, he's likely
to dodge it, so I punch accordingly.
Here I go.
(Trainer Yoo is the fourth one
to punch.)
- He punched it well.
- He punched it precisely.
He punched the center.
(He punched precisely.)
- He punched it well.
- Let's see.
- Let's go over it.
- It's near 8,000.
It's 8,055.
(Trainer Yang: 8,100
Trainer Yoo: 8,055)
- It's 8,055.
- We won then.
- Se Chan is in the first place.
- Gosh, Se Chan.
I got golden fists.
This is great.
It's embarrassing to have
a lower score than Se Chan now.
- Sung Hoon.
Good luck. I'm curious.
(The third player from Team Yang
is Sexyama.)
Sung Hoon. Don't waste energy.
(Shadowboxing)
Your bracelet.
(A gold bracelet!)
It flew off.
(Surprised)
- I picked it up.
- No.
- What's the matter?
I picked it up.
It's an expensive one.
It's mine
once it falls onto the floor.
Sung Hoon.
- He's different.
- He often throws short punches.
The way he's shadowboxing
is different.
(How will Sexyama punch?)
- Look. He went for a short punch.
- He threw a short punch.
Sung Hoon, it's...
- Look. He went for a short punch.
- He threw a short punch.
What was it?
- What was it?
- It might be lower than we think.
- It's...
- Because he threw a short punch.
It could be less than 8,000.
What? Eight.
- What?
- It's 7,700.
(He's 3rd among them?)
Se Chan is in the first place.
- Follow me, Sung Hoon.
- Your score is lower than mine.
- He punched it precisely though.
- It's weird.
- What was it?
- What happened?
- Should I retire?
- It's because it was a short punch.
It was a short swing
as you usually throw short punches.
That's why.
Because it was a short punch.
(Compared to his fancy shadowboxing,
the result is devastating.)
For your information,
Chan Sung will use his left hand...
- I'll use my left hand.
- as his right hand is injured.
- You should add 10 percent for him.
- You must score more than him.
- Increase his score by ten percent.
I will win Se Chan.
- Yes, you should.
- You will?
It's weird to hear him
saying Se Chan's name.
He's younger than me.
- It made me proud of you.
- Yes.
I know.
(I will beat Se Chan
just with my left hand!)
My left hand.
- That's it.
- I think he kind of missed it.
No.
(Missing)
- That's it.
- I think he kind of missed it.
He punched the bottom.
(What score will he have?)
(Chan Sung: 5,697)
Come on.
(He's the last place.)
- Come here.
- What?
- This is good.
- What did he do?
- We won.
- I got a higher score than him.
- What is...
- I beat Chan Sung.
All right.
- What's this?
- He won.
All the great athletes...
- can't even beat me.
- What was it?
It's because I'm right-handed.
What did you do?
- He's Wreck-It Ralph.
- He's the punch king.
Se Chan is the punch king.
- What's this?
- This is all for Doo Ho.
What are you doing?
- Mr. Bong.
- Just with one punch.
- Let's go, Bong.
- Each team got one player left now.
- This is unbelievable.
- Each team got one chance.
You know it, right?
- Right.
- Sung Hoon and Chan Sung punched,
- but I'm in 2nd place.
- I'm in 1st place.
Punch the center.
Do it.
(The last player from Team Yang,
Cicada Kim is going.)
Nice.
- Nice.
- That's nice.
- Bong.
- Kim Bong.
He punched it well.
(Superhuman strength)
(Will he be able to beat
Trainer Yang, the punch king?)
He punched it well.
(Dong Hyun: 8,181)
(Stun Gun became 1st place.)
- It's okay. It's good.
- There's not much of a difference.
- It's not that different.
How are athletes different from me?
- What's this?
- The gap is 81 points.
- Hey. You did it.
- Still, he has the highest score.
- We got Doo Ho left.
- Doo Ho.
- Show us.
- I got the hang of it.
- He got the hang of it.
- Okay. You don't know.
- He doesn't know anymore.
- He will miss it.
It doesn't matter.
Let's go.
- Okay. You don't know.
- He doesn't know anymore.
- He will miss it.
He punched it precisely.
He will miss it.
(He punched it precisely!)
- It's good.
- We won.
- We're good.
He punched it well.
- It must be 7,000.
- It's 8,600.
(Doo Ho: 8,631)
(Superboy became the final winner.)
I want to do it again.
I can do well if I do it again.
Now, 8,631 is the score
of an athlete.
You can't call yourself an athlete
with 8,100 points.
- He's different.
- That was nice.
- Thanks to Doo Ho, Team Yoo won.
- Yes!
(Team Yoo won.)
Let's do it again.
- Let's do it one more time.
- We should do it twice.
No. Get rid of the machine.
We'll give the winning team
100 dollars...
- and the losing team 50 dollars.
- Okay.
- Gosh, why did I do that?
- Will the trainer distribute it?
- Of course.
- You'll negotiate now.
Negotiate?
- Okay. Negotiation.
- It's time to negotiate now.
- Do I get a raise?
- Of course.
- This is so annoying.
- Okay.
- It's a bummer.
I'll explain
how to negotiate your salary.
Okay.
Each of you can enter the tent
and negotiate for two minutes.
The trainer can offer their salary
within the budget you earned.
The players will negotiate their
current trainer first.
If they don't like the offer,
they can negotiate with the other one.
If they can't make an agreement
with him either,
the salary will be cut by half.
- Looking at the table...
- It sounds good.
(Trainer Yoo: 386,440
Trainer Yang: 435,720)
I feel so good.
- Suk Jin, come in.
- Yes.
- Should I go first?
Well...
Hello.
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
- Take a seat.
- Okay. You know...
How much are you thinking?
(He goes straight to the point.)
I'm not in a position to talk
about my salary elsewhere.
How much are you thinking?
(Original salary, 3 cents)
About 20 dollars.
That's way too high.
You need to give me
at least 20 dollars.
You need to consider our situation.
That's not the point.
You have 400 dollars right now.
You haven't even spent 10 dollars
on us yet.
I've spent over 10 dollars.
As you know, it's a competition
between me and Trainer Yang.
You're being way too frugal.
I'll keep it a secret and stay here.
- No.
- Listen.
Suk Jin.
You need to consider my situation.
- Or I'm going to leave.
- I'll give you a 100 percent raise.
(3 cent raise)
The salary negotiation is...
One hundred percent raise?
If I was getting 10 dollars,
that would make sense,
but I'm only getting 3 cents.
I'll give you 30 cents.
Wait. Okay.
(In a rush)
If you give me 50 cents,
I'll put up with it.
I'm not asking
for 5 million dollars.
Only 50 cents.
Hey, the market price is so high,
seolleongtang costs 12 dollars.
Give me a dollar.
I'll give you 50 cents. Sign here.
(Angry)
I can't sign it.
My pride won't accept it.
I asked for a dollar.
- I said I'll give you 50 cents.
- A dollar.
You said 50 cents
when I suggested 30 cents.
- That was a mistake.
- You need to leave.
That was a mistake.
Get lost.
"Get lost?"
Hey.
- A mistake?
- "Get lost?"
Get lost.
I'm very offended.
- Get lost.
- Seriously.
- Hey!
- Bye.
- So long.
- Get lost.
- Hey!
Don't ever think
about seeing me again.
- Get lost.
- Hey!
It's cold. Close the door.
- How much do you want?
- Me?
Honestly, I don't care about money.
I'm here because I like you.
You don't care about money?
So keep it the same?
- No, don't do that.
- Okay.
- There are people...
who watch me.
So how much do you want?
Just to save my face,
I want to get more
than the 10 cent range.
You're in the one cent range.
- You're in the one cent range.
- I know that.
Give me at least a dollar.
- That's ridiculous.
- That's ridiculous?
Look. How many times is that?
That's not the point.
That's a 100 percent raise.
I'm...
(What?)
- What did you just say?
- I didn't say that.
- Mr. Haha.
- I never said that.
No swearing.
- That's not it.
- No dollar range.
Look.
You're currently getting 3 cents.
If I give you 30 cents,
how many times is that?
I was worth more than 3 cents
at first.
Look.
Trainer Yoo won't give you
more than 50 cents.
- I know that.
- Exactly.
But I'll make it worth.
Besides,
is that all that I mean to you?
- Fine. I'll give you 50 cents.
- Fifty cents?
That's still a big raise. 50 cents.
Hey. It's me, Dong Hoon.
Hey.
Have you forgotten I'm Dong Hoon?
That's not how it works.
- That's not how it works.
- Se Chan.
- Fine. 60 cents.
- Sixty cents.
Sixty cents. It's time.
Honestly...
I'm telling you. If you do well,
it'll increase by ten times.
What's 10 times 60?
- Six hundred.
- I'll give you 6 dollars.
Can you write that in the contract?
- Add that condition.
- No conditions are added.
Just write you'll increase it
by ten times.
I'm going to rip it.
Sixty cents it is.
You've become picky.
"You?"
Se Chan. Hold it.
Hold it.
Make a fist. One, two, three.
Okay. Haha.
You must not tell anyone.
Thank you.
- Next.
- Se Chan.
- Let's grab lunch later.
- Okay.
How was it?
Ji Hyo, you're next.
(Trainer Yang)
(Haha gossips as soon as he leaves.)
He's a jerk.
My goodness.
Chan Sung, come in.
Chan Sung. Honestly,
I was disappointed in your punch.
What did you think of my acting?
I knew Doo Ho was going to win.
I'm starting to learn
how to make the show funny.
- So?
- I knew Doo Ho had to win...
to make the show funny.
- You did that on purpose?
- You think...
You think I'd miss that
after two title matches?
That was done on purpose.
I'm sorry,
but all I can give you is eight dollars.
Only eight dollars?
I don't mind. It's fine.
I said I'll be loyal
as long as you give me food.
- You're okay?
- I'm loyal.
Okay, eight dollars it is.
The salary negotiation is so easy.
- Can you give me 50 cents more?
- Fifty cents?
A meal costs 8.5 dollars these days.
- Eight dollars and fifty cents.
- I'm...
He doesn't mind
even though it's reduced.
I'm loyal. I...
It's six dollars right now.
- What?
- I was getting six dollars.
- Ten.
- I was getting ten dollars?
It's ten dollars?
- I thought it was six dollars.
- No, sign it.
- It went up.
- Wait a minute.
- It went up, right?
- It went up.
Yes. Sign it.
Hold on.
- Sign it.
- Did it go up?
- Sign it first.
- Did it go down?
Sign it first.
(Trainer Yoo pressures him.)
- I'm still loyal.
- I'm sorry.
Exactly. Okay. Good.
- Do your best, Chan Sung.
- I'll always be loyal.
- Salute.
- Show me this time.
- I'll show you.
- You may leave now.
Okay. Good.
This is...
Good. Doo Ho.
- Did you sign it?
- How much did he offer you?
- How much are you getting?
- Eight dollars and fifty cents.
What? 8.5 dollars for this big star?
Doo Ho. I liked...
your performance.
I got you 100 dollars.
How much do you want?
To be honest,
you should give me 40 dollars.
(Disapproving)
Because I got you 100 dollars.
You're...
asking for 40 percent
of what we have.
That's too much.
But think about it.
I got you 100 dollars.
Didn't you say...
you started after Chan Sung?
That's another issue.
You saw his punch earlier.
I believe a pro player should get paid
for his performance.
Chan Sung recorded a terrible score,
to be honest.
(How much does Trainer Yoo offer?)
Ten dollars.
Hang on.
- Trainer Yoo.
- Yes.
(That's far below
what Doo Ho wants.)
You first offered 10 dollars
to Chan Sung.
Yet I get the same offer
after what I did?
You're currently
getting 3.5 dollars.
Okay, then. You're stubborn.
- You're no ordinary.
- I got you 100 dollars.
I'll give you 15 dollars.
That's the max amount
I can give you.
- Okay.
- I think...
- It's enough.
That's more than enough.
- Okay.
- I'll do my best.
Good.
- This isn't good.
- Because we're too naive,
we signed it too easily.
That's what agents are for.
I had no choice.
If I don't get enough here,
he'll only offer a lower salary.
Right?
- You've seen what I'm capable of.
- Yes.
Bong. Let me tell you this.
You've done
the salary negotiation before.
No.
- No? But you're an athlete.
- No.
Oh, you had an agent.
No, I just get what they give me.
Then keep your mouth shut
and get what I'm giving you.
No. Wait.
You have to be at Chan Sung's level
to negotiate with UFC.
- Okay.
- Or you'll get fired.
- I just got what they gave me.
- I'll listen.
- Listen.
I don't know what's next,
- but let me tell you a secret.
- A secret.
We have four players here.
Jung Chan Sung. He has...
- a bad shoulder.
- He's injured.
Choo Sung Hoon. He has a bad thigh.
He injured his knee.
Choi Doo Ho? He's playing safe
because he has a match coming up.
I have no matches.
I'm not injured. I'm healthy.
I'm in perfect condition.
Look here.
Even if you make a good negotiation,
if the player can't play
due to injuries,
- that's a team owner's skill.
- That's a skill.
You paid a lot,
but the player can't play.
That's a secret.
Okay. So how much do you want?
I want 100 dollars.
I almost cursed.
- What did you say?
- One hundred.
- I'll lead the team.
- How much?
I'll lead the team.
Give me 100 dollars.
I'm sorry, but the door is that way.
- Give me 100 dollars.
- Not a chance.
I didn't have a chance to show you.
Let me show you now.
You were only 81 points higher
than me.
- What?
- You were only 81 points higher.
Look. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(Armed protest)
See that?
- See that?
- What are you doing?
- You're scaring me.
- Did you see that?
- You broke the chair.
- What's wrong with the chair?
Okay. I get it.
Tell me again. How much?
Wait.
Why is the chair broken?
- Dong Hyun. Listen.
- Sorry.
- I was only trying to show you.
- One hundred is too much.
- Listen to me first.
- I don't hold grudges.
How much did you get earlier?
- I was getting 4.3 dollars.
- You were getting 4 dollars.
I'll increase it by ten times.
- Forty dollars?
- Yes, that's still ten times more.
That's ten times.
You haven't seen my kick yet.
Kick?
- Watch my kick.
- Okay.
- I have a good kick.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
- Let me show you my knee kick.
Okay. I get it.
- Knee kick?
- Okay.
- All right.
- I can show you.
I'm giving up on Sung Hoon.
- I like to keep it neat.
- Sixty dollars.
- Sixty dollars?
- No more. Look.
Look.
Even if you go over there,
he won't give you 60 dollars.
I need to get paid the highest
among the players.
UFC...
paid me only a little. I was so sad.
Sixty dollars is the highest price.
- What if it's not?
- Then come back to me.
- Really?
- How much would he offer you?
- I don't know.
- He'd never offer that much.
Not even a chance.
I gave him a dollar
and gave Haha 60 cents.
I'll come back.
- I will leave it here.
- Okay.
(He tries to negotiate his salary
as he couldn't do it at the UFC.)
- Come on in.
- So Min.
I haven't signed the contract yet.
- Is the negotiation underway?
- Yes.
Over there,
he pushed the contract toward me
and insisted that I sign it.
How much are you thinking?
I am thinking about 100 dollars.
About 100 dollars.
Over there,
I was offered a similar amount.
I am serious.
- I am terribly sorry,
- Okay.
- but the door is that way.
- Come on.
- In that case,
- If you ask for 100 dollars...
- please put this down for a second.
- Okay.
- Please put this down.
- Why?
- I showed him my punch.
- Okay.
That will help in negotiating
the salary.
- We don't know what we will do.
- No.
Here.
- My goodness.
- This is how I throw punches.
This is how I throw punches.
I can't believe you.
- This is a knee strike.
- Hold on.
- It knocks out a person.
- Hold on. Okay.
Okay. I got it.
I got it.
Why... Kim Bong.
Hold on.
- Kim Bong.
- This is how I attack.
Did you see that?
Why did you do that here?
- Do you want to see more?
- No, I have seen enough.
I can pick this up and hit people.
Don't do that. I got it.
- I got it.
- Don't you want to see that?
- Kim Bong, I understood.
- Okay.
Kim Bong, firstly...
- I didn't mean to make a scene.
- All right.
I can see
what kind of a fighter you are...
from your behaviors.
- I am a passionate fighter.
- Hold on.
This is my offer.
(How much did Trainer Yoo offer?)
I signed the contract too.
I will tell you...
- how much he offered.
- Ten dollars.
- I will go back.
Ten dollars.
- Over there...
- Do you want half of that?
- I will be honest with you.
- Go ahead.
He offered 60 dollars.
- There is no way.
- He offered 60 dollars.
There is no way
Trainer Yang offered that much.
- When I showed him this trick...
- Ten dollars.
- He offered 5 or 7 dollars...
- My offer is 10 dollars.
at first.
When I punched this,
- the price rose to 60 dollars.
- My offer is 10 dollars.
- Give me 60 dollars.
- This should be enough.
- Why did I come here then?
- Listen.
I will give you 12 dollars.
I will leave then.
Won't you regret this decision?
We don't know what we will do,
- but only I am able-bodied.
- I will give you 12 dollars.
Okay? I will leave then.
I will give you 12 dollars.
Are you looking down
on my monstrous power?
- Give me 30 dollars.
- My offer is 12 dollars.
- Seriously, I will leave.
- I can't give you more.
Hey, you are totally ruined.
(Laughing)
I can't give you more.
- Then I will leave.
- I can't give you more.
Leave.
- I will see if you do well.
- Leave.
You heard that, right?
He offered 12 dollars.
- Isn't it annoying?
- Twelve dollars?
- He offered me less money.
- It's annoying.
- Did he really offer 12 dollars?
- You are still in the industry.
- This won't do.
You shouldn't get less money
than a retired comedian.
He offered me ten dollars.
- How did he offer him 12 dollars?
- He offered Dong Hyun 12 dollars.
This is wrong.
- I feel like I got conned.
- It seems that way.
Go in there and ask him
to rip up the contract.
Then you should talk one more time.
He rushed me into signing
the contract.
I got scared.
I will ask Trainer Yang...
if he is willing to pay the penalty.
That's a good idea.
- And how much he can pay.
- That's a great idea.
- How much are you thinking?
- If I get this deal,
would you give me a dollar?
- I will give you 50 cents.
- You will give me 50 cents.
- How much did you get?
- I can't believe you.
My goodness.
I will go with him.
- You can divide up a dollar.
- That won't do.
- Give us three dollars.
- Come on.
I will give you...
- ten percent of what I get.
- Ten percent.
- Okay.
- Let's get him some money.
It isn't 10 percent per person.
It's 10 percent for the both of you.
- He is a businessman.
- The both of us.
It will still be more
than our salary.
Next.
- Sung Hoon, come on in.
- I heard stories about Trainer Yoo.
Trainer Yang isn't half bad.
He is nice. He is reasonable.
- What are you doing? Hold on.
- Good.
- Hold on.
- Hey.
- What?
- Hold on.
Hey, go ahead.
- What?
- You aren't here as a loan shark.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- I am a trainer.
- What are you going to do?
- Hold on.
- Sit down.
- My goodness.
- This is a negotiation. Sung Hoon.
- I know.
Let's talk well.
- Let's talk well.
- Exactly.
- Listen carefully.
- Okay.
You know that your punch was...
very weak, right?
- It was very weak.
- But...
I will be honest.
For how many years
did you star in variety shows?
- Many years.
It isn't fun
if you do well from the start.
- You need to start out weak.
- There should be a buildup.
I was trying to create a story.
Why don't you know that?
- There should be a buildup.
- Exactly.
How much will you give me?
How much are you thinking?
I think I deserve 50 dollars.
- What?
- I said 50 dollars.
- Do you want 50 dollars from me?
- That's right.
Exactly 50 dollars.
I can't.
I don't think I can do that.
Fifty dollars.
Who are you talking to?
- Listen.
- Okay.
I will give you the highest salary
in the team.
- Okay?
- How much is that?
- I will give you 15 dollars.
- Come on.
(Come on.)
Come on.
You are looking down on me.
- Looking down on you? No way.
- You are looking down on me.
I offered you a lot of money.
If you go over there,
Jae Suk won't offer much money.
- Okay. Let's do this then.
- What?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
Yes. Rock-paper-scissors.
- If I win, give me 40 dollars.
- I will give you 30 dollars.
Forty dollars.
- What if you lose?
- If I lose...
It should be less than 40 dollars,
so give me 30 dollars.
What are you, a thug? Sung Hoon.
You are behaving like a thug.
It makes no sense.
- Why? It makes sense.
- Listen.
No, it doesn't make sense.
I offered 20 dollars.
- But you want 30 dollars.
- If I win, it's 40 dollars.
If you win, it's 30 dollars.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Be manly. Okay.
- Okay.
- There you go. Good.
Okay!
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Scissors.
Okay.
(Trainer Yang won.)
Thirty dollars.
(My goodness.)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Scissors.
Okay.
Did they play rock-paper-scissors?
- Hey.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Who makes a deal that way?
- Even rock-paper-scissors?
- You are the man.
- For goodness' sake.
Good.
- It can't be helped.
You are the man.
- Okay.
Pose for a photo. One, two, three.
(Sung Hoon signed the contract
at 30 dollars.)
- Okay. Thank you.
- All right.
I will give you more next time.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
Trainer Yang,
I have big news.
I will bring Doo Ho and Chan Sung.
- They signed the contract.
- Firstly...
- But they got conned.
- I see.
- Hello.
- Okay. I got it.
- Did you give him 30 dollars?
The two underlings should leave.
Underlings?
- We are their agents.
- Agents? Tell me what happened.
Trainer Yoo insisted
that I sign the contract.
He scared me,
so I ended up signing it.
They didn't know about their worth.
Chan Sung signed the contract
for 22 dollars...
and Doo Ho signed the contract
for 35 dollars.
- They deserve more.
- Did you say 35 dollars?
- Let me ask you this.
Had I come to you first,
how much would you have offered?
- If you had come to me first...
- Let's say I was a free fighter.
Then I would have started
with an offer of 50 dollars.
- Fifty dollars or more?
- Of course.
How about Chan Sung?
I would have started
with an offer of 50 dollars.
You would have offered 50 dollars.
- Of course.
- After a conversation,
- it could have been 70 dollars.
- Or 60 dollars.
Doo Ho, you seem very angry.
- I...
- He is very angry.
- Trainer Yoo offered me ten dollars.
- Do this.
Doo Ho and Chan Sung, what's wrong?
Listen.
Earlier, you rushed me...
into signing the contract.
I am disappointed.
Don't be disappointed.
There is no need to worry.
Once the team wins,
I will give you...
I fell for this trick
at the age of 23.
- I am 37 years old now.
- Come on.
I didn't know
that I would fall for it again.
Chan Sung, you don't need to worry.
- I see why you rushed me...
- Listen.
- into signing the contract.
- Come on.
You must be upset...
because Trainer Yang
must have offered much more.
I pretended to be a free fighter
and asked him.
He offered 50 dollars right away.
- Really?
- Fifty dollars.
After all, Doo Ho earned the team
100 dollars.
My goodness.
- You are open-minded.
- Seriously.
- Of course, I am.
- You don't disappoint.
- We can communicate well.
- Here, okay.
- Let's work hard now.
- Hey.
- Would you give me 20 cents?
- Chan Sung.
Trainer Yoo.
(Jung Chan Sung)
Okay. I saved your pride.
- Are you happy?
- I am very happy.
- Do your best.
- This is a nice amount.
- This is great.
- Do your best, okay?
I will work hard.
- You can go now.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
This is incredible.
- How much did you offer earlier?
- But you rejected me.
Here is the thing with me.
My mind is quite fickle.
I don't like people
who are calculative.
- I am not calculative. I hate that.
- Earlier...
- I offered 60 dollars.
- Yes.
Now,
- my new offer is 20 dollars.
- Come on. Make it 50 dollars.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
If I win, give me 50 dollars.
If I lose, give me 20 dollars.
Let's play Subtract One.
- Rock-paper-scissors. Subtract one.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(Dong Hyun lost.)
Go and talk to Trainer Yoo.
Trainer Yoo.
He is so stubborn.
Are you done?
- Do you need to talk to me?
- Are you going back and forth?
- I am not going back and forth.
- Come here.
I am surrounded by enemies.
That man won't do.
He has a rotten personality.
How much can you give me?
I will give you 15 dollars.
You only raised two dollars.
Then I will go there.
- Go.
- Won't you regret it?
I can't give you more.
Sign the contract if you want.
It's up to you.
How can you give me 12 dollars?
- This is wrong.
- No. I can't give you more.
This is wrong.
(Dong Hyun got driven out again.)
- I will give you 16 dollars.
- Did you say 16 dollars?
It's a considerable sum.
I shouldn't have moved.
Seriously. Hurry up and sign it.
Good.
All right.
- They shook hands.
- Did they shake hands?
- Okay.
- What?
- Did he join the team?
- Did Dong Hyun join that team?
- I had no choice.
- Hey.
- How much did he get?
I recruited him.
- Did you recruit him?
- Yes.
You were too haughty
in the beginning.
That's not true.
He suddenly lowered...
- the offer.
- Stop it.
- You joined the team. Stop talking.
- You are out.
- It's over.
- He offered...
- twelve dollars.
- Stop it already.
- You joined the team. Stop it.
- Just you watch.
- Dong Hyun, why did you leave?
- He offered 12 dollars.
Trainer Yang offered me
60 dollars in the beginning.
Did you say 60 dollars?
- Yes.
- Why did you say no to 60 dollars?
You shouldn't have said no.
- I didn't know anything...
about the market price.
- That was a nice offer.
- My goodness.
- Sixty dollars.
- That was a nice offer.
- I had no idea.
- It was the best offer.
This is incredible.
- What's this?
- It's a ring.
- Did you make this?
- Was it made for us?
- It's scary.
- Really? Wasn't it here before?
- I...
Why did you make such a fancy set?
- I am Jeonchimawa Lee.
- Are we having a fistfight?
He is my friend, Hatbari.
Enter the ring.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hatbari.
- Get ready to fight me.
- Secquiao.
- You little Secquiao.
The other team has more fighters.
It's too bad.
(Team Trainer Yoo hurriedly recruits
Sung Hoon!)
This is good.
I will now explain the rules.
Without knowing
the other team's order of players,
you will send out a player.
- We won't know it.
- Then the Name Tag Elimination...
will take place.
The next pair of players will enter
the ring after 60 seconds.
(Whether they are eliminated or not
doesn't matter.)
- What?
- The last surviving team will win.
The winning team
will receive more money.
- It's like the Royal Rumble.
- I see.
It's like the Royal Rumble.
(The rules are similar
to those of the Royal Rumble.)
Five players will enter
from that team, right?
- It will be 5 versus 5.
- No, 6 players will enter.
One of your players can enter again.
- Can it be anyone?
- Again? Can it be anyone?
- That's great.
- Okay.
- One of us can go again.
- It can be anyone.
- One of us.
- Either you or I should go again.
That's right.
- We have a chance.
- We are set.
- We will win.
- Dong Hyun or you should go first.
- That's right.
- They should go first.
That's right.
- I will go after Dong Hyun.
- Chan Sung.
- His right shoulder is not good.
- You can go again afterward.
- Dong Hyun will go first.
- We need a strategy.
Shall I go first and hold out
instead of going for his name tag?
- Hold out.
- Okay.
Dong Hyun isn't our only problem.
- There is Jong Kook too.
- That's right.
- He has the know-how.
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- He is experienced.
- He has strength.
- And...
he is full of energy right now
because he is excited.
It's a sport.
It's a sport with people
who have black belts.
Yes. You have black belts.
(Only the strong ones will survive.)
Let's do a cheer.
- Let's go.
I am nervous.
I am the most confident.
The year 2023.
Running Man.
The Salary Fighter Race.
Now comes the last mission...
that will be the highlight
of Sunday evening.
The one who rips off the name tag
will rule the ring.
Running Rumble!
(Team Trainer Yoo
versus Team Trainer Yang)
Fighting out of the red corner
is the Stun Gun.
- Let's go.
(Stun Gun, Kim Dong Hyun)
I knew he would go first.
Hold out.
I wonder how it will go.
Fighting out of the blue corner
is the Korean Superboy,
- Choi Doo Ho.
- Hold on.
- Isn't this too early?
- I don't know who will win.
- Let's go.
(A big match came to be
on Running Man.)
This is incredible.
(Superboy versus Stun Gun,
what will be the result?)
- Let's go.
- This is incredible.
- Are we starting right away?
Come on.
(Trying to intimidate)
I can't predict the result.
- Dong Hyun, let's go.
- Are we starting right away?
Come on.
Come on. Are you running away?
Are you running away?
There you go. That's good.
It will be hard
to take off the name tag.
They are
in different weight classes.
(Doo Ho's both hands are caught.)
(He manages to escape.)
This is insane.
(Dong Hyun continues
to charge forward.)
- Dong Hyun, go for it.
- Go for it.
(But Doo Ho buys time.)
Okay.
- Dong Hyun is bigger.
- Oh, no.
I know.
Dong Hyun needs to do better.
Finish him off.
(At that moment)
(He grabbed the name tag!)
It's okay. Grab him too.
(Doo Ho twists his arm
and holds out!)
Finish him off.
- It's okay, Doo Ho.
- Go behind him.
- No. It will be over...
if Dong Hyun takes off his name tag.
(It's a touch-and-go situation.)
Now, the second pair of players
will enter the ring.
Fighting out of the red corner
is Kim Protein.
- Do we just enter the ring?
- Fighting out of the blue corner...
is Sexyama,
- Choo Sung Hoon.
- Hurry up.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Sung Hoon.
What's going on?
- This is good.
- If this goes on...
At this rate...
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- Hey.
- No.
This is the real deal.
Sung Hoon, hold out.
(Their clasped hands show
that they refuse to yield.)
They are so competitive.
(It's a showdown.)
Don't get caught.
(At that moment,)
(Sung Hoon is out.)
- Okay.
- Okay. I ripped it off.
- He got Jong Kook.
- Don't get caught.
- Okay.
(When Jong Kook was distracted,)
(Superboy ripped off his name tag.)
He got Jong Kook.
- Did you rip it off?
- Jong Kook is out.
Did Jong Kook get
his name tag ripped off?
(Sung Hoon and Jong Kook
got eliminated in 15 seconds.)
Thank goodness Jong Kook is out.
- Totally.
- Thank goodness.
Now comes the next pair of players.
Fighting out of the red corner...
is the Puke Tornado, Ji Suk Jin.
(The eye of the hurricane,
Puke Tornado)
Contending against him is
the Korean Zombie, Jung Chan Sung.
- Go in there.
- The Korean Zombie, Jung Chan Sung.
Hold on.
(It's Suk Jin versus Chan Sung,
so the balance of power is gone.)
Chan Sung, help me for a second.
- Chan Sung.
- Hold out.
(Doo Ho is out.)
Hold out.
(Korean Zombie joins in right away.)
(Dong Hyun is out.)
(Team Trainer Yang's
strong players are both out.)
- He ripped it off.
- Let's go.
Hurry up.
Why did you get eliminated?
This is easy.
- Hey.
- Hold on.
Get him.
- Hold out.
- Get him.
(He gets grabbed by the collar.)
Throw him down.
There you go.
(He subdues Suk Jin with one hand.)
Hurry up.
(Suk Jin is out.)
- He got Suk Jin. Okay.
- Now, the next set of players.
- Fighting out of the red corner...
- I got the name tag.
is Secquiao,
Yang Se Chan.
Contending against him is Yootria,
Yoo Jae Suk.
Okay. We are set.
Go and get him.
I got eliminated.
Get him.
We have no choice
but to finish him off.
(They corner him gradually.)
This is bad.
Jong Kook, you need to enter.
Jong Kook might come next,
so we need to finish him off.
We need to rip off his name tag.
Rip it off.
- Hurry up.
- What should I do?
- Grab him.
- Lie down.
- Lie down if everything else fails.
Go to a corner. Run away.
Hold out.
(Se Chan is out.)
It's game over.
Jong Kook remains.
- Fighting out of the red corner...
- Jong Kook remains.
is Kim Protein, Kim Jong Kook.
(Solemn)
Fighting out of the blue corner
is Hatbari.
Come on.
- Haha.
- Hatbari.
- Come here.
Hatbari.
Hey.
(He subdues Haha with one hand.)
Oh, no.
Hatbari.
(Slipping)
(Even with three members,
Jong Kook is formidable.)
Even with three members,
it isn't easy to eliminate him.
Gather around.
- He is too strong.
- It isn't easy to eliminate him.
- Jong Kook is...
- He is seriously strong.
- He is really strong.
- He is too strong.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Eliminate him.
I got him.
(He attacks Chan Sung first.)
(He misses his chance.)
Do your best until the end.
Another set of players
will enter the ring.
Fighting out of the red corner
is Zoned-Out Gregor, Song Ji Hyo.
is Jeonchimawa Lee, Jeon So Min.
- Hey.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, rip off a name tag.
Ji Hyo.
(Hatbari attacks Ji Hyo.)
Why are there so many people?
- Hey.
- No.
(Ji Hyo is out, so Jong Kook
is against 4 people!)
Grab him.
(At that moment)
(Jae Suk is out.)
He did it.
This is incredible.
This is incredible. Let's go.
Hey, Chan Sung.
(Chan Sung, Haha, So Min versus Jong Kook)
- No.
- Hey.
(Can Jong Kook fight
against three opponents?)
- I got it.
- I ripped it.
Hey.
(The moment Jong Kook
grabs Haha's name tag,)
(he got his name tag ripped first.)
(Jong Kook is out.)
- Okay.
- That was so close.
- It was so close.
- We almost lost.
(Team Yoo wins by a whisker.)
- Is it over?
- It's ripped off.
- Gosh.
- We could've won.
- We win.
Jong Kook almost took it off.
- Jong Kook was almost there.
- It was so close.
I didn't know
there would be so many.
- Well done.
- My gosh.
Okay.
- Well done.
- It's not easy.
Team Yoo wins this mission.
- Okay.
- That was so close.
We did well.
- You have to pay me.
- Okay. Don't worry.
The winning team gets 500 dollars.
(Trainer Yoo gets 500 dollars.)
That's a lot.
And the losing team
gets 300 dollars.
You will have a man-to-man talk
for the final salary negotiation.
But the trainers can offer
as much money as they want.
Okay. I get it.
You need to pay
every single player on your team.
Gosh, this time,
I'll be sure to pay you a lot.
- Okay.
- I believe you.
- You can be generous.
- Right.
- He's right.
- Please remember what I did.
- I tried my best.
- I can be reasonable.
I should've won.
I can't help it
if I get picked and eliminated.
But I don't want to come in last.
- Do as he asks.
- The thing is,
I don't have enough money
to beat Jae Suk.
- Right.
- You can't beat him anyway.
- So give us more money.
- Right.
You'll look cool
if you get a penalty like that.
(The trainer with less money
gets a penalty too.)
We have enough money. Don't worry.
Maybe 100 dollars at most.
I guess I can spend
about 140 dollars.
So I'll give you 40 dollars each.
- Really?
- I'll give you 40 dollars.
(The fighters get 40 dollars each.)
I misunderstood you
at the beginning.
- Right. I had no idea.
- It's just...
that I saw the big picture.
- I feel like crying.
- I'm not so stingy.
- I'm so moved.
- Me too.
- We talked about 10 and 20 cents.
- This is so touching.
- The world is still warm.
- Right. I'm moved.
- And you two.
- Yes.
I'll give you ten dollars each.
- Thank you.
- Gosh, this is crazy.
I have a complaint.
Why are you being generous after I left?
I mean, when I was on your team,
you were being very stingy.
This was my plan,
but you left too soon.
- That's right.
- Is that it?
I made up my mind, but you left.
- About the penalty.
- Okay.
The trainer with less money
will get the penalty.
And the member with the least money
And among the members except
for the two who get the prize,
we will randomly pick one
to get the penalty.
There's a lot.
At least one on my team
will get picked.
The penalty we prepared for today...
- can be very cumbersome.
- Is it?
It's something you'd hate.
So I was thinking
we could probably let you...
choose between
the penalty and a low kick.
My gosh. It might kill you.
We won't be able to walk.
The penalty is...
diamond painting
which is very popular these days.
You should glue
little pieces to the sheet.
I'll just get kicked.
- It's better to get kicked and go.
- That's a lot better.
First, I'll announce the results
of the two trainers.
- Trainer Yoo.
- Please.
Yang Se Chan wins.
He has 496.94 dollars.
He does?
(Team Yoo: 496.94 dollars)
Trainer Yang.
He has 591.66 dollars.
(Trainer Yoo: 591.66 dollars)
He has that much money?
- So Trainer Yang wins.
- You could give us 20 dollars each.
He didn't spend any money.
I kept most of the money.
- My goodness.
- Jae Suk.
You got 500 dollars.
How is that possible?
- He distributed all the money.
- I shared it with them.
- Really?
- Before this round,
Jae Suk received a reward,
so he was winning by 40 dollars.
Really? How did it happen?
But Se Chan gave only 0.1 cent
to his team members.
We got 0.1 cent each.
(Getting 0.1 cents and 0.2 cents)
I made a mistake.
All right.
Now I will announce the ninth place...
who will get the penalty.
You announce it first?
It's the athlete
with the salary of 1.5 dollars.
- It's Song Ji Hyo.
- Oh, dear.
And I'll announce
the two athletes...
with the biggest salaries.
- Okay.
- Two athletes.
Gosh, this is...
Number two is...
It must be someone on my team.
It's an athlete with a salary...
- of 116.5 dollars.
- What?
- It's Choi Doo Ho.
- Yes.
- Doo Ho.
- I knew it was our team.
- There you go.
- Good.
- It's our team.
- That's nice.
- He's the salary king.
- The salary king.
- That's amazing.
- I was deeply moved.
- Good.
- That's a lot.
Now I will announce number one.
The winner
with the biggest salary is...
It's the athlete
with a salary of 118 dollars.
- It's Choo Sung Hoon.
- Me?
Congratulations.
- It's Choo Sung Hoon.
- Me?
- Congratulations.
- My gosh.
They're both on my team.
- That's right.
- When did you get so much money?
- He went back and forth.
- Look at that.
You took a lot of money
while going back and forth.
I'm number one? Thank you.
- I'm so moved.
- That's unbelievable.
My goodness.
The rest of you...
should come and pick one each.
- All of us?
- Let's go and pick one.
- Not me.
- I'll take what's left.
- It can't be the one at the end.
- How many of us will get it?
- Only one?
- One.
I'd like you to open it one by one.
(Only 1 of the 6 members
will get the penalty.)
- Haha, you go first.
- I hope it's you.
(Haha opens it first.)
- I can't see it.
- Nice.
- Jeon So Bal.
- Please.
(It's So Min's turn to open it.)
(Sighing)
- Why?
- It's either So Min or me.
- Seriously...
- It's So Min or me.
I really don't understand.
(Penalty)
(So Min gets the penalty
against the odds of 6 to 1.)
- Why is it always...
- It's always her.
- What's wrong with me?
- You're so unlucky.
- How do I do this?
- That's strange.
Like we heard before,
the penalty will be...
either the diamond painting
or a low kick.
I'll go first.
I've done this
with Chan Sung before.
- Are you going to be okay?
- I'll be fine.
Chan Sung does
a lot of variety shows,
so he knows we need good reactions.
Now that I'm at this,
I should do it properly.
Now that it's already like this...
- Right.
- He's taking off his socks.
Chan Sung,
you don't have to take off your shoes.
Jae Suk is bony,
so your foot might hurt.
He doesn't need to use his legs,
- Don't worry.
- so it's all right.
- Are you sure it's okay?
- It's all right.
It can either hurt for days
or hurt just for a moment.
- I'll make it hurt for a moment.
- Make it short.
All right. Don't worry about me.
- All right.
- I think it will be hard.
(Groaning)
- Your buttocks...
- My gosh. Are you all right?
This is Running Man.
(Chan Sung has adapted
to variety shows completely.)
- You flew off.
- My goodness.
- He flew away.
- You just flew.
- Are you all right?
- Did you two work on it together?
- Did you work with him on that?
- You showed good teamwork.
That was great teamwork.
Go catch Jung Chan Sung.
- It was great teamwork.
- Impressive teamwork.
- Hey, come here.
- Gosh, how did he do this?
It's different from when
you kicked me on another show.
- My goodness.
- It hurts only for a moment.
That's amazing though.
When I got kicked before,
it hurt for a long time.
- But it doesn't hurt now.
- It doesn't?
- It lasts only for a moment.
- Right.
- One more time.
- That's a good technique.
Seriously, you're good at this.
- Is it different?
- At first...
- Do you want to try it?
- You should get the penalty.
No, I'll do the diamond painting.
(Frightened)
Jae Suk didn't cry.
Let's give him a big hand.
- Okay.
- He didn't cry.
All right.
Thank you for joining our show today.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine. It was fun, Chan Sung.
(Will)
(Ji Suk Jin)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Kim Jong Kook, Yoo Jae Suk, Haha)
(Yang Se Chan)
(Jeon So Min)
(And Kim Shin Rok)
(The story about a dignified
conglomerate owner family)
(It's something you've never seen.)
(The fierce fight for money begins.)
(Reborn Spitefully Rich)