Hello.
I think this place is
for rich people.
What is this place for?
I think I saw this in a movie.
I think this place is
for rich people.
I think this is for a concert.
- Look at this.
- My gosh.
- I bet it's for a concert.
- My goodness.
I live in Gangnam, but I had no idea
there was a place like this.
- I didn't know that either.
- This is cool.
You don't know
because you rarely go out.
I almost died without having been
to a place like this.
This is really nice.
Why would you talk about dying
so early in the morning?
A joke like this works for you now.
- Right.
- What about it?
- It sounds sincere.
- Now you're old enough...
to talk about the next world.
The thing is, we are having...
IVE for today's guests.
- That's right. IVE is coming.
- I read an article.
I read an article about that.
- There were a lot of articles.
- IVE.
Hey, Se Chan even lost weight...
- because IVE was coming.
- Suk Jin.
- Look at him.
- Think about that.
How can I lose weight only in a week
just because IVE is coming?
He lost weight.
He even went to a beauty shop.
Why would I do that because of IVE?
Se Chan got his hair done.
Suk Jin, you look nice today.
- Do you like this?
- I like your pants.
- When I got these pants...
- They are cute.
Doesn't he look like a gypsy?
There's flour.
- Gypsy? How dare you...
- Suk Jin.
You got some flour on your shoes.
I see. So these shoes are
from back then.
- Back when we...
- It wasn't a long time ago.
- It's from Reborn Spitefully Rich.
- I often wear...
- the same shoes.
- It's flour.
- I see.
- You can wear the same shoes again.
Of course.
You know I'm not so picky.
Hey, are you Daddy Long Legs or what?
(Long)
- What is it you're standing on?
- Hey.
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm wearing heels today.
- My gosh.
- You look so tall.
- Too tall.
- I looked at her like this.
Why are you so tall today?
It's the New Year,
so I'm wearing heels.
- She wears heels a lot these days.
- I know.
Is that because IVE is coming?
- Because of IVE?
- Like you just said, we have...
- special guests today.
- Yes, we do.
They even prepared
a special performance for you.
Really? I love IVE.
We're so lucky.
- I know.
- I love "Love Dive."
- I like IVE.
- Please come on out.
- Where are they?
- There they are.
There's IVE.
- Yoo Jin.
- Hey.
(They are the ones who swept
awards ceremonies with mega hits.)
- Ga Eul.
- Welcome.
LIZ.
(Yoo Jin, Won Young, Ga Eul)
(LEESEO, LIZ, Rei)
They're here.
It's "Eleven."
Are they performing "Love Dive?"
It's "Love Dive."
This is interesting.
We go to the same gym.
It's crazy to see her here.
I often see her at the gym.
They're so pretty.
(IVE wins the Grand Award proving
the power of the 4th generation.)
(2022 Best Song of the Year,
2022 MAMA Song of the Year)
(2022 AAA Song of the Year,
2023 Golden Disc Awards Grand Award)
("Love Dive" swept the K-pop world.)
It's "After Like."
(A Welsh Corgi gets excited.)
("After Like" by IVE was listed
on Billboard's charts for 22 weeks.)
(The single has sold
over a million copies.)
(The first musicians to win the Best
Rookie Award and Grand Award)
Is this a nightclub or what?
They're so good.
You're amazing.
(IVE is writing a new epic
for the girl group history.)
What's after like?
All right.
- IVE.
- Gosh.
They are the members of my gym.
They go to the same gym.
We have IVE today.
Welcome.
(The Grand Award winner, IVE)
We have all six members
on Running Man today.
- I'm so grateful.
- Me too.
- It's so nice.
- I can't believe they're here.
They must be happy to be here
because we like them.
There he goes again.
He says that all the time.
- Seriously, this is embarrassing.
- Let's be honest.
They must be as happy as we're now.
- Yes, we are.
- Of course, we're happy.
And I'm sure they are
happy to be on Running Man.
I'm so sorry.
It's not an overstatement...
to say the year 2022 was IVE's year.
We look forward to their exploits
in this year as well.
So we're going to have
an in-depth conversation with them.
- All right.
- That sounds like a good idea.
It will be hosted...
by the nation's beloved MC,
Yoo Jae Suk...
- and his assistant MC he picked.
- An assistant MC? Then...
- It's definitely him.
- Assistant MC.
Suk Jin does assist me well,
but sometimes he acts up.
- Let's see him assist.
- Let's watch.
Let's see how he does
after "Star Golden Bell."
I used to deal...
- with 20 people at a time.
- Right. He's a star.
I took care of everything myself.
So this is what I wonder.
We have LIZ
and other members of IVE here.
I wonder what they think
Suk Jin's real job is.
- Go ahead and say it.
- Do you know?
LEESEO, do you know?
His real job.
His real job. Just tell us...
- how you feel.
- His real job?
Yes. His real job.
- An office worker.
- A small business owner.
A fertilizer sack.
A comedian?
(A comedian?)
But he was a singer.
- That's true.
- He used to be a singer.
- That's how I started my career.
- He was a singer.
- Really?
- You didn't know, did you?
- I debuted like...
- He started as a singer.
thirty years before you.
(Surprised)
- Do you know "I Know?"
- You're our senior.
My song was released on LP, CD,
and cassette all at the same time.
- I was the first generation.
- He's a senior artist.
Did you see that?
You know what this means.
- "Yes."
- "Enough."
- "All right. It's over."
- They give me a big hand.
"That's enough, so stop it."
And she gives two thumbs-up.
Stop talking.
- This is what it is.
- Stop talking now.
Are you pressing your thumbs...
- against his lips?
- Yes, that's it.
- Like this?
- "I want to shut your mouth."
- Stop talking.
- It's not two thumbs-up.
- I didn't know.
- You shouldn't do that.
I'll pick an assistant MC then.
- I want Seok Sam.
- All right.
- Go up.
- He gets mad if I don't pick him.
He will say something like this.
"Hey, I'm an experienced MC."
(The old rookie is selected
thanks to his experience.)
- Seok Sam, come here.
- I don't say that.
- Go up.
- Assist him.
So we have the six members...
of IVE here on Running Man today.
- Welcome.
- Running Man...
- often has idol guests,
- We do.
But they mostly play some games...
- and leave.
- That's true.
Now that they're here,
- we should get to know them better.
- We don't know them well.
The thing is,
this must be meaningful to IVE.
It's not easy to be on Running Man
as a whole band.
I'm sorry, but...
It's not the assistant MC
who invited them here.
You kind of kill the mood.
- You're supposed to assist.
- Why are you acting out of line?
I think it's a problem...
- when an MC sounds bossy.
- Right.
He sounds too bossy.
- IVE must be feeling nervous now.
- You should make them comfortable.
All right.
She tells you to stop talking.
- Stop talking.
- It's two thumbs-up.
Pressing his philtrum.
I'll talk to them one by one.
- First, we have An Yoo Jin.
- Yes.
Yoo Jin, you were born
in the Year of the Sheep.
- Yes.
- That's the year I was born in.
Really? I was born...
- in the Year of the Sheep.
- Really?
But he's an old sheep.
- He's an old sheep.
- And she's a lamb.
- He's old.
- Are we 24 years apart?
- Is that 24 years?
- Really, 24 years?
My goodness. You're
24 years older than her.
He's such an old sheep.
So...
her specialties are hanok challenge
and singing with an echo effect.
I watched it before.
- You did?
- Singing with an echo effect.
I've never heard of that.
Yoo Jin.
- Like karaoke?
- I know what it is.
- I watched it too.
- She's really good.
- She did really well.
- It's Yoo Jin's specialty. Show us.
- She's different.
- She's really good.
I'll sing "Snow Flower."
Suddenly as I flowed
Your growing shadow
And this is our song.
My boring eyes
The expressionless face
- Isn't this from "Gag Concert?"
- Just stay quiet.
Come on.
(The assistant MC
kills the mood again.)
- It was going well.
- Please.
- Mister!
- Hang on a second.
"My beloved..."
(Suspicion of an homage
to "Gag Concert" from 10 years ago)
- Why would you bring that up?
- That's the worst.
- Mister!
- Hang on a second.
Se Chan, switch.
- "My beloved..."
- Suk Jin, go.
- Go away.
- Just go.
- I can't believe this.
- What was that?
- "Gag Concert?"
- Suk Jin.
- They did this before.
- Stop it.
Did I just get kicked out?
- You sit here.
- Just listen.
Go sit over there.
- What's wrong with what I said?
- You ruined it.
You brought her down.
- Suk Jin.
- All right. Two thumbs-up.
What goes around comes around.
- You're really good.
- Thank you.
They say you have two different egos
as an idol and an entertainer.
You're a good entertainer
on variety shows.
What are you like as an idol artist?
You look so pretty.
That's so flattering. Thank you.
So she sounds modest.
(She sounds modest as an idol.)
She sounds calm.
So she sounds modest.
But what are you like
on a variety show?
You look so pretty.
I know I do!
(I know I do!)
You look so pretty.
I know I do!
(She admits it in a cool way.)
- I'm pretty.
- That's nice.
I feel so comfortable.
- I feel so comfortable.
- I like that.
- She's just like So Min.
- I feel so comfortable.
- I like that.
- She's just like So Min.
- That's nice.
- I'm pretty.
- "I'm pretty."
- She's so cheerful.
I like that.
- That's nice.
- I'm pretty.
I like that, Yoo Jin.
- She's different.
- She sounds just like So Min.
So Min looks so proud.
- So Min and Yoo Jin are similar.
- I know.
- She's just my style.
- She's my role model.
- That's true.
- You're my style.
- She is her role model.
Is So Min your role model?
- Yes.
- All right.
As a lot of people know,
she made her debut on "Produce 48."
- I see.
- That's how she debuted...
- as an idol artist.
- Wait.
Is Se Chan a mascot or something?
I don't have much to do here.
I just need
to listen carefully to him.
"I see."
You're just like us.
We're just like IVE.
- That's why he's good.
- He's good.
I just say things like, "I see."
- He makes an agreeable response.
- I do.
- So...
- To tell me that I'm doing well.
you should just sit there
like a puppet.
- That looks quite nice.
- I know.
So...
- You should read this.
- Which one?
I see.
They say your nickname is
An Yoo Jae Suk.
An Yoo Jae Suk?
- Is that true?
- Because her name is An Yoo Jin.
- Are you a good MC?
- The thing is,
I try to be an MC
when I'm with the members.
What do you think?
Tell us what she's like.
(What?)
Are you tired now?
- Her eyes lost their focus.
- No.
You were spacing out.
- Do you not want me to talk to you?
- I was listening.
- Are you all right?
- Looking straight ahead.
It will be your turn soon.
I don't think Rei was looking ahead.
She was somewhat like...
- What's wrong?
- Rei, relax. It's okay.
Let's move on to Ga Eul.
- Senior Ga Eul.
She's the oldest member of the team.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Who?
- She's 22.
Her introduction is quite unique.
I'd like to hear that.
Your introduction
as a member of IVE.
Hello, I'm Ga Eul of IVE,
the fairy on the team.
- A fairy?
- My goodness.
Aren't S.E.S fairies?
- A fairy.
- A fairy?
- Fairies last forever.
- So Ga Eul is a fairy.
What about you, Won Young?
- Irreplaceable charm.
- Irreplaceable charm?
So you still use
expressions like that.
- Do you still do that?
- The word still works.
- What about you, Yoo Jin?
- I'm Jeon So Min.
What are you?
Jae Suk, let So Min
introduce herself.
- So Min, you have something?
- She came up with this on her own.
What is it?
Hello. I'm Jeon So Min
with an addictive charm...
that you recall
before you fall asleep.
"Addictive charm."
(Lengthy)
(You will recall her shamelessness
before you fall asleep.)
"Addictive charm."
- It's so embarrassing.
- It sounds...
like a very old expression.
- I can work on it.
- It's hilarious.
That was funny.
It's fun.
Do you often eat alone?
But there's one thing
I haven't tried yet.
I never went
to a barbecue restaurant on my own.
- Pork belly?
- You should come to my restaurant.
I ate tenderloin and eels
in a restaurant alone.
- Really? Can you order one serving?
- Yes.
- No, you can't.
- They don't sell one serving.
I ate one serving
and ordered porridge to go.
- You ordered takeout.
- I see.
Then you can order one serving.
They thought I was pregnant.
(They thought I was pregnant.)
So they...
You can't say that
to young girls like them.
- Hey, So Min.
- Wait.
- So Min.
- We don't know how to react.
- I don't know what to say.
- Come on.
People don't usually go
to a barbecue restaurant alone.
My role model.
But I went there by myself...
- and ate meat.
- She's unbelievable.
That's funny.
(You will recall her silly remark
before you fall asleep.)
Back in high school, you were
called The Beauty of the School...
as you looked like Seolhyun
and Actress Shin Hyun Been.
- What?
- She was famous for her beauty.
You were called like that?
I didn't know that.
- The members didn't know?
- No.
I went to girls' middle school
and girls' high school.
- I was popular...
- Among your friends?
Yes. I was popular among my friends.
I bet you were.
- I can imagine.
- They all have pretty faces.
So Min and Ji Hyo
were just like that.
- That's not the case for me.
- They are like your seniors.
- Right. Your senior.
- Not me.
She was just popular.
- She was just popular.
- She was a boss.
Rei, weren't you called
like that back in school?
- Me?
- Yes.
- I had no friends.
- Why not?
(I see.)
No friend at all?
Not even one friend?
Things are not working out with her.
Don't wrap things up yet.
We still have a long way to go.
- Please.
- Don't give up.
Please hang in there.
- I just...
- Please.
I just lost my desire to talk.
- Please, Jae Suk.
- All right.
- We can do this.
- Hang in there. You can do this.
- Okay. We should do this.
Let's move on to Rei.
- Rei, you...
- Are you going to be all right?
I need to pull myself together.
Take a deep breath. Take it slow.
- It can take an hour. Take it slow.
- Okay. Let's take it slow.
- We can do this.
- We have a lot to do today.
Let's do this, Rei.
- You support him well.
- So...
About Rei...
Your real name is Naoi Rei.
- That's right.
- Is that correct?
You're in charge of rapping...
and have a lovely
and unique charm. Right?
You can't just read it.
You should ask questions.
- You're just reading it?
- Please ask questions.
It doesn't happen a lot that I'm
afraid to ask someone a question.
- But I'm afraid.
- Let's go for it.
Okay.
You like four-syllable words.
Right. Four-syllable words.
- Like what?
- She must like idioms.
What I found novel was...
- the word, "anyway."
- Anyway?
The members know that.
- Do you like the word?
- When do you use the word?
- When she needs to make a decision.
- Right.
"I think this will be nice anyway."
She always adds the word.
Why do you like the word so much?
Because it's a four-syllable word.
What?
(Because it's a four-syllable word.)
What on earth?
- "Because..."
- She cut him off completely.
- There isn't a bottom consonant.
- She's not wrong though.
- Jae Suk, get a grip on yourself.
- It's a four-syllable word.
- A 4-syllable word?
- Yes, it's a 4-syllable word.
You sometimes come across
people like her.
- Rei, I hear you.
- You should overcome this.
Yes, I should overcome it. Good.
Give her a book
on four-syllable Chinese idioms,
and she'll have fun all on her own.
What's your take on "gyeoksejigam?"
- That...
- It's a bit too hard for her.
- It's not that cool.
- What about "ilseokyijo?"
- You don't find that cool?
- No.
(What makes you the best
is that you're honest.)
Are you all right?
It's okay.
- She doesn't find it cool.
- You're halfway there.
I get that Chinese idioms
aren't all that cool,
but they're way better
than words like "because."
- Those four syllables...
- But...
- contain various meanings.
- What about "surreptitiously?"
Is it true that you like
the word "whatever?"
Yes, I used to love saying that.
Can you do the longer version of it
with the TV and fridge?
- No, I can't, but...
- I see.
I also like saying
I'm ticked off and...
You both failed,
so step down from there.
- This won't do.
- No, wait.
- Get back here.
- I...
- It's okay.
- Yes, she's hard to win over.
She won't let us in.
Rei isn't an easy one to crack.
So that was Rei.
We'll now move on to Won Young.
- We'll talk to Won Young next.
- Hi.
Hey, Won Young.
Her talent is her prettiness.
- What more can you say?
- No way.
- She can confidently say that.
- It's written down here.
- It's cool that you can say that.
- I see.
- Her talent is her prettiness.
- How does one do that?
Don't you agree though?
- I do.
- I also agree.
Can you do what Yoo Jin did earlier?
She stood up and struck some poses.
Can we ask that of you as well?
Should I mimic the situation
or strike some poses?
- The poses.
- Strike poses of a certain vibe.
- That enhances my looks?
- That's right.
I'm dying to see this.
- Then...
- Could you stand up?
- Can you call for me from behind?
- Okay, I like that.
- Why don't you walk over there?
- Go ahead.
- Here we go.
- I'll turn to this camera.
Sure thing.
- I'll turn around thoughtlessly.
- Sure thing.
What's the time?
Won Young.
Yes?
Who took a photo just now?
(Hold on.)
- Who took a photo?
- Someone took a photo.
Who was it?
(The sound of a shutter
resonated in the silent auditorium.)
(The PR team
couldn't help themselves.)
- Someone took a photo.
- Who was it?
- Show yourself.
(The person
was quickly apprehended.)
- Who do you think you are?
- Who was it?
Who are you?
- He's from SBS.
- I heard the sound of a shutter.
- He's from the PR team.
- Who are you?
- You're inspiring though.
- You didn't just turn around.
- I added a wink.
- You also winked.
- As if something were in my eye.
Let us call for you
in a different way this time.
Go ahead.
Won Young.
(She slows it down herself.)
- She slowed it down herself.
- It was in slo-mo.
That was nice.
- As if I wasn't expecting it.
- I slowed it down.
- I'm impressed.
Like we said...
- She's really pretty.
- It sure is a talent.
- Thanks.
- Mi Joo and I...
- were in the green room...
- Yes?
- when Won Young appeared on TV.
- Really?
She looked at her and said,
"She has it all."
- Oh, no.
- It's true.
Even guys give up when we see men
who are too good looking.
- That was so cool.
- We give you that.
- We can only agree.
- Yes, we admit you're pretty.
- Thank you.
- In 2022...
We'll now move on to LIZ.
- LIZ.
- Your real name is Kim Ji Won.
- Yes.
- And you're the lead vocalist.
I hear you have the most
special talents in the group.
- Yes, I guess you can say that.
- You seem talented.
- What can you do?
- Can you show us something?
- Could it be...
- I have something new to show you.
I practiced this
to present on Running Man.
- Really? That's what we should see.
- We're grateful.
- That's what we should see.
- It's something new.
Here we go.
And go.
Who are you doing an impression of?
Is it Christina?
- Hold on a second.
- Tell us who it is first.
- We should know who this is.
- Was that Italian?
- Let us guess instead.
- You have to guess.
- Is it Christina?
- Let us guess.
Was it Maenggu?
- Was it Maenggu?
Show us once again.
- I wasn't done.
- She wasn't done.
- Liz, try that again.
- Let's listen.
Go ahead.
- It's a quiz.
- All right.
How many people are you mimicking?
- Hold on a second.
- There's no need to confront her.
- Let her finish.
- I'm sure it wasn't over.
- I'm scared.
- You guys are scary.
- It's okay. You can overcome this.
- Are you mimicking three people?
- They're not angry, guys.
- Also...
- What is it?
- It's too strict here.
- This is something new, right?
- Let them be at ease.
- Exactly.
Yes, be at ease.
- We only want to guess the answer.
- Of course.
I hear you can also mimic...
- the sound of an ocarina.
- That's right.
Can you show us?
Here I go.
You did it well earlier though.
(The sound of air)
- You did it well earlier though.
- Try that again.
It's because of her sweaty palms.
Wipe them first.
Wipe them dry.
This is your last chance.
(In comes
another strict drill sergeant.)
I'm sorry about that.
- I'm sorry.
- Hold on.
- Mister!
- Are you the drill sergeant?
- Seriously?
- I'm sorry about that.
It's all right.
We all get three chances.
Go ahead. It's okay.
IVE has been
on many variety shows before,
but I doubt
any of them were like this.
- It's icy cold in here.
- Right.
- We're old-fashioned.
- We're strict.
- Please show us.
- We're mostly strict.
- One last try.
- Okay.
- I heard a sound.
- You're doing it.
- It's working.
- Keep going.
You failed.
- She made a sound though.
- Then...
- I did make a sound.
- I'll erase that...
from your lists of talents.
- Cross that out.
- We got to know about LIZ.
- Lastly, we'll talk to LEESEO.
- The youngest member.
- It's finally my turn.
- Her real name is Lee Hyun Seo.
- She's 17.
- The vibrant youngest member.
Winking quickly is your talent?
That...
- In ten seconds?
- It was a talent of mine,
but Won Young turned out
to be better at it.
- You stole it from her.
- She stole her talent.
- It's understandable.
- We'll cross that one out...
- and say Won Young stole it.
- It was stolen.
Won Young stole her talent.
I want to see it though.
How fast can you wink?
- I'll show you.
- Sure.
- That's really fast.
- You're good at it.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That was fast.
- How fast can Won Young do it?
I do it with just one eye,
- not both.
- Please show us.
- I do it with one eye.
- Is it different?
You're not kidding. No way.
- So Min winks really fast as well.
- With just one eye.
Steal that talent from her.
- So Min, let's see it.
- Have some magnesium.
- You need magnesium.
- You need vitamin D as well.
- She can wink really fast.
- I can do it too.
Go ahead.
- Forget it.
- Your lips twitch up.
Show us.
(Got you, didn't I?)
- Won Young...
- Ji Hyo, hold on.
Why can we see your grinders
when you're winking?
- Won Young.
- Hold on.
That's due to a lack of magnesium
in her system.
- How...
- It's lack of magnesium.
Anyway, we got to know IVE
a little more.
(IVE has been analyzed.)
Thank you.
- We now feel closer to IVE.
- We know them better.
- I know them now.
- Right?
Before we begin today's race,
you will play a game
that will decide your teams.
My Strength Is That
I'm the Best Dancer.
IVE has already been split
into teams of two,
and you will play the game
of Green Light, Red Light.
Unlike the basic rule,
the one who's It
will step forward while dancing.
The other member of IVE
will blow the whistle...
while watching
the Running Man members dance.
That will have you eliminated.
The remaining members
will join that team.
A total of three rounds
will take place.
Won Young and Rei are up first.
- Okay.
- Won Young and Rei.
Okay!
Is Won Young like the referee?
- That's better.
- Watch closely.
- Won Young will eliminate us.
I'll watch you dance
and eliminate you one by one.
Well, we...
We've been dancing
all our lives, right?
- Dancing is my life.
- Of course.
- We'll be on Rei's team, then.
- Even if you do the moves right,
I'll blow the whistle
if I'm not satisfied.
- Decide who you want on your team.
- Don't you worry.
She's strict, isn't she?
Let the music play.
Go ahead.
(She blows the whistle.)
Suk Jin, you're out.
Why?
- Suk Jin, you're out.
- Why?
But... Hold on.
- This...
- Nicely done.
- Nicely done, Won Young.
- Hold on a second.
- Nice job.
- Isn't this because she hates me?
- It seems to me like...
- Nicely done.
- The moves weren't that hard.
- It wasn't difficult.
- What's the reason?
- I love how she put it.
- I liked the tone.
- Hear me out.
His moves were completely off.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Something about him...
- I'm sure she was objective.
- It was this move, but...
- I understand.
I think his palms were open.
- It was this.
- Haha also mentioned this,
but her tone was hilarious.
- Exactly.
- "Suk Jin, you're out."
Suk Jin, you're out.
- Gosh.
- Suk Jin, you're out.
Oh, man. This isn't easy.
(The music is played again.)
- Is this song "Red Flavor?"
- Let's go! One, two!
Here goes a difficult move.
- What do I do?
- Here goes a difficult move.
What do I do?
- You're doing great.
- Oh, good. I'm doing it right.
(Way to go!)
(The whistle is blown.)
- Only he...
- Yoo Jae Suk is out!
(Changing his pose)
- She's so strict.
- Hey.
- Hold on.
- Won Young, you're so strict.
- "Yoo Jae Suk is out!"
- Wait. I'd like to...
- Won Young is quite strict.
- take back my decision.
- Why?
I think it's acceptable.
- Right. You can do that.
- Yes.
- Really?
- It's up to you.
- Yes. I want to let him off.
- Oh, I see. Okay.
But Jae Suk is out, right?
- No, he's not.
- He...
Isn't he out?
- What?
- Suk Jin, you're out.
- Isn't he out?
Am I the only one to be eliminated?
Why won't you let me off?
- "You're out!"
- You get a yellow card instead.
- I'll give you a yellow card.
- A yellow card? Okay.
- Why can't I get a yellow card?
- I'll try harder from now on.
- That's great. Do your best.
- And those at the back,
- You're such a great dancer.
- make sure to do it properly.
- We're doing well.
- We're doing our best.
- Now, play the music.
(The music is played.)
Hey, look at him.
Haha, you're out.
(Haha is out.)
- It's because...
- Yes.
- He looked too much from behind.
- I see.
- She had her reason.
- You stuck out your butt too much.
- Okay. I admit that.
- I'm next to Se Chan.
Referee,
you seem to like Jae Suk...
- too much.
- I did well this time, right?
That's not the point.
- Why...
- You're out.
- Good job!
- I mean...
- She favors Jae Suk.
- That's great.
- Jae Suk gets a yellow card.
- Okay.
- That's what he deserves.
- I didn't get eliminated.
- Right.
- He doesn't deserve to be out.
- And I'm good at dancing.
- He got another yellow card.
- He didn't do so poorly. Trust me.
- You heard her.
- Let's continue.
- Okay.
(There are 5 members left now!)
- Oh, my. They're cute.
- Indeed.
Hey!
(Moon Hee Joon's signature dance)
Wait. What is it? I can't see her.
- Who?
- Song Ji Hyo is out.
No. Why me?
Ji Hyo, she's right.
We can see why you're out.
- After this move, swing your arm.
- Ji Hyo, accept it.
- Was that it? I couldn't see it.
- That's what I did.
- Ji Hyo is out.
- I'm relieved.
- Gosh. I couldn't see it.
- I couldn't see her well.
Even I could see
you were doing it wrong.
- I expected to do this dance.
- I thought we'd do this dance.
- Right.
- Jae Suk, it's too hard for you.
- Understood. She's strict.
- Yes.
It's going to get harder.
(There are 4 members left now!)
- My hair is too short for that.
- My hair is too short.
I can't grab my hair like that.
You have to move further forward.
They're moving
in different directions.
They're all doing well.
(The dancers are starting to
get excited.)
Oh, gosh. What should I do?
- It's difficult.
- Oh, yes, treasure!
(The whistle is blown.)
- It's difficult.
- Yoo Jae Suk is out.
- I can't let you off this time.
- Why am I out?
- Unbelievable. Yoo Jin, tell her.
- Jae Suk was doing well.
- You were over the top.
- That's fair.
- I was doing so well.
- Listen.
- You got too excited.
- She's a fair referee.
- I got too excited? Is that it?
- Jae Suk, come here.
That's right. You were over the top.
- You were too frivolous.
- My gosh. I can't believe this.
That had a sort of American vibe.
But I really like that vibe.
- You're out.
- Gosh.
(The referee tells him
to stop acting up and leave.)
- She's rigid.
- She's so strict.
- She's strict, indeed.
- Won Young is...
- rigid.
- What a shame.
- We're like a mixed-gender group.
- Turbo is back.
- Stand in the middle, Jong Kook.
- We're a mixed-gender group.
- Jong Kook, stand in the middle.
- Okay.
- Let's begin the final round...
- I'm out of breath.
- with these three members.
- This is the final round?
- Those dance moves...
- It's difficult.
- were so difficult.
- The two of you who survive...
will team up with them.
- Only one of you will be out.
- The game will be over.
- Please play the music.
- I don't want to be eliminated.
You know, the two of you...
(The whistle is blown.)
- The member to be eliminated...
- Their foot positions are reversed.
lost her balance at the end.
Jeon So Min is out.
- Hey, we made it. This is great.
- Congratulations.
Jeon So Min is out.
(The final 2 survivors are
Se Chan and Jong Kook!)
- Hey, we made it.
- We made it!
- Actually...
- Are you sure?
- I didn't want to do it again.
- Okay.
- The first team has been formed.
- You see, Rei...
Next up are Yoo Jin and LEESEO.
- Yoo Jin and LEESEO.
- Okay.
- Oh, they...
- Yoo Jin and LEESEO?
- It's a strong team.
- Yoo Jin, do difficult dance moves.
- I danced so hard to survive.
- Please play the music.
- Let's go!
- I'll dance like crazy.
- Please play the music.
- I'm exhausted.
("Swallowtail" by Kim Heung Guk)
Oh, it's "Swallowtail."
(As his favorite song is played,)
(Suk Jin starts dancing
right away.)
A tiger.
(The whistle is blown.)
- Oh, no. I can't do that. Gosh.
- That was too difficult.
Suk Jin, you failed.
- Why me?
- He...
Suk Jin, you failed.
(He's the 1st member
to get eliminated again.)
- She said, "You failed."
- Why?
- But Yoo Jin...
- Why me?
- We didn't do much.
- You...
- Why...
- I didn't like it. At all.
- You didn't like it?
- LEESEO didn't know this dance.
- That's the original dance.
- This is the original dance.
Besides, I saw Yoo Jin
while we were dancing. She...
didn't see anyone else but Suk Jin.
- She looked at no one else.
- She stared at him, right?
- I don't like his dance.
- You don't like it?
- I don't like it.
- Okay.
- At all.
- Okay. Let's keep going.
- Play the next song.
- So Min, you're doing great.
(Play the next song.)
("Crazy World" by Shin Sin Ae)
I like this song.
- Oh, man. This is...
- Gosh, this is so difficult.
- I can't believe she's dancing...
- this dance move to that song.
- What is this?
Hey, this is not the original dance.
(She doesn't know this song
for sure.)
Keep going!
(As the familiar chorus begins...)
(Jeon Sin Ae appears.)
(The whistle is blown.)
- So Min danced as she wanted.
- But it doesn't matter...
as long as Yoo Jin likes it.
Am I wrong?
She just let herself go.
- You did great, So Min. I love you.
- My goodness.
- Then who is it?
- See? It's okay if she likes it.
- Who's eliminated?
- Who's out?
Who's eliminated?
I just wanted to say I liked it.
But she danced as she pleased.
So Min danced a different dance.
- I liked her dance.
- She didn't copy it. Is that okay?
- It's my style.
- Right? I knew it.
- Okay.
- Her dance is a good example.
- LEESEO, you're a great dancer,
- Yes?
but can you do a dance
that suits the songs they play?
- She really is an expert.
- Right. She's an expert.
- Okay.
- But it was a girl group dance.
- So I can just dance as I want?
- Yes.
As long as Yoo Jin likes it.
- Oh, as long as she likes it?
- Yes, as long as I like it.
She altered the game.
- Let's go!
- What is she doing?
(This time, they played a song
that LEESEO would know.)
On, no. It's hard.
(Jae Suk doesn't know what to do.)
- Why?
- Jae Suk, you failed.
Gosh, seriously.
How did he dance?
- You're out.
- I want to know.
- I'm so curious.
- Come here.
- Hey, Yoo Jin.
- How did he dance?
- You didn't do it right.
- I did this move properly.
- I'm so curious.
- But...
He has pride in his dancing skills.
- What are your standards?
- Gosh, seriously.
- He looked like a locust.
- He's cute.
A locust?
That's because I'm dressed in green.
Can you do it just one more time?
- Sorry?
- Can you do it just one more time?
- Why should I...
- How did you dance?
- Just one more time.
- I'm curious.
Oh, my. He's doing well.
I think he's doing it right.
He's trying hard to do it well.
(He's trying hard.)
- I see why he got eliminated.
- Jae Suk, you failed.
You're still out.
- Gosh. I can't believe this.
- He failed.
- Yoo Jin is so picky.
- This is the final round.
- Is it over when one of us is out?
- I really want to join this team.
- I want to join their team too.
- Me too.
- I want to join this team.
- You've got this.
- I mean it. I have a strong desire.
- I want to join their team too.
- I have no idea what Yoo Jin likes.
- This team doesn't suit me.
(The last song is played.)
Hey.
(Excited)
- What are you guys doing?
- LEESEO is dancing alone here.
- Hey.
- Guys, look at LEESEO.
- We have no choice.
- Hey...
(Frightened)
What are you doing?
The game has changed.
- Why are they all here?
- My goodness.
- Why?
- Hey, LEESEO danced alone.
- Right.
- Hey, why...
- Unfortunately,
Haha is out.
- So Min.
- Oh, they're joining this team?
Are you serious?
As a result, the four of them
are on the same team.
- You three have to play the game.
- This is driving me nuts.
We made it! We pulled it off!
- Only two of us will survive?
- Yes.
- So one of us will be alone.
- What happens to him?
- Will he be the weak link?
- Senior Ga Eul and LIZ, right?
- Yes.
- Senior Ga Eul and LIZ.
This is the final...
- I really want to join this team.
- Senior Ga Eul.
- Let's do this!
- I wanted to join this team before.
- I wanted that from the get-go.
- Let's go.
- They're trying to be chosen.
- This is our last chance.
- Senior Ga Eul...
- Let's do a chant.
- One, two, three. We've got this!
- This is our last chance.
- Senior Ga Eul is my favorite.
- If you fail to join this team...
- You'll be an outcast if you lose.
- There's no other team to join.
- We must join this team.
- Senior Ga Eul, I respect you.
- Let's do this.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go. LEESEO.
- Let's go, Senior Ga Eul.
- Oh, she's Ga Eul.
(This is the final game
to decide the outcast.)
- Ddu-du
(Singing awkwardly)
(Middle-aged men in the neighborhood
gathered to dance.)
- Ddu-du
(The whistle is blown.)
- Well... Haha...
- Oh, my gosh.
- His face...
- His face? My gosh.
- That's hip.
- She didn't like his face.
- All right. I guess...
- He's pouting.
- he's out.
- LIZ.
I...
(Who will be left alone?)
choose Jae Suk and Suk Jin...
(She chose Suk Jin and Jae Suk.)
- as our team members.
- Haha failed.
- Haha is out.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's go!
- Okay. Let's go.
- Haha...
- Let's win!
- He's aged.
- He's old now.
- Mister!
- I feel bad for him.
- Haha is left alone.
- Poor Haha.
Why me?
(Why me?)
- Poor Haha.
- We don't want him.
- We won't accept that old man.
- Oh, no.
- It was a dance competition.
- Exactly.
(He lost in the dance competition.)
- Let's bring him into our team.
- Okay.
- Come here.
- Haha.
- Okay. Join that team.
- Haha, come here.
- Join our team.
- Go and join that team.
- Okay!
- He's on Yoo Jin's team.
This team has five members.
After you change your clothes,
we'll move to another location...
- I'm out of breath.
- to begin the first mission.
(Since Seok Sam risked his life
and fought hard to the end...)
Suk Jin is having chest pain.
I'm out of breath.
- He danced for too long.
- That's hilarious.
(Team Won Young and Rei:
Jong Kook, Se Chan)
(Team Yoo Jin and LEESEO:
Ji Hyo, So Min, Haha)
(Team Ga Eul and LIZ:
Suk Jin, Jae Suk)
L to the O and there's more
- Yoo Jin, sit with your team.
- Okay.
Yoo Jin, what are you wearing?
Is it that cold?
- It's warm today.
- Here?
- Hey, Rei.
- This is LEESEO's seat.
Ga Eul, you sit here.
- She looks cute, right?
- Indeed. She looks so cute.
(She spotted the camera
that was filming her.)
I see that you pose like that
automatically in front of a camera.
- We're not good at that.
- She found the camera right away.
Suk Jin would do it
if he gets paid for it.
- He'd do anything if he gets paid.
- As soon as I get paid.
The moment the money is wired,
he'd start striking cute poses.
Suk Jin is grateful for attention,
but money makes him happier.
- Money is important.
- Right.
He'd do whatever he's asked
as soon as he's paid.
- The bus is fully packed today.
- Here you go.
Put on your seat belt.
- It looks like a bear.
- That's right.
Thank you.
- Won Young, did you put yours on?
- Yes, I put on my seat belt.
- "Really."
- Is that the right expression?
- Your seats are switched.
- She's from Nagoya?
But it doesn't matter.
- It's okay.
- It doesn't matter.
By the way, the bus is fully packed.
- Exactly.
- It's nice.
- It hasn't happened in a while.
- It's so crowded.
- It's like a school trip, right?
- Yes.
- Hey, you'd be the principal.
- Teacher.
- Don't act like you're their age.
- If this were a school trip,
- Do they still go on a school trip?
- Haha would be a teacher.
- I'm sure they do.
- He'd be a teacher.
- A PE teacher. No, wait.
- A principal.
- He'd be a chemistry teacher.
- A chemistry teacher?
- I think it suits you.
I bet
he knows nothing about chemistry.
- By the way, So Min.
- Yes?
There's nothing you can teach kids.
What kind of teacher would you be?
- Me? What do you mean?
- Sorry?
I would teach them about love.
(I would teach them about love.)
- You're really something, So Min.
- They're too young to love.
- She's really something.
- They're not too young to love.
- I'd teach them how to love.
- They're too young to love.
Nonsense. Ga Eul here is 22.
- Ga Eul, are you 22?
- Yes.
- Were you born in 2002?
- I'm a World Cup baby.
- You're a World Cup baby?
You couldn't watch
the 2002 World Cup, right?
(You couldn't watch
the 2002 World Cup, right?)
The 2002 World Cup.
I didn't know she was born
in the year of the World Cup.
- You heard that many times, right?
- Yes.
- She's a World Cup baby.
- I'm LEESEO's guardian.
- I don't know why, but...
- LEESEO was born in 2007, right?
- Yes, correct.
- Oh, my. She was born in 2007.
- That means we're quite old, right?
- Exactly.
- I'll tell you the rules in here.
- Really?
The race hasn't begun yet?
- When will we begin the race?
- The race has begun.
Today's race we're having...
with the IVE members
who are as cute as rabbits are...
- Yes.
- Rabbit with No Liver.
- Rabbit with No Liver?
- A rabbit has no liver?
- No liver?
- That's not good.
- I thought she said "no sense."
- I'll give you these first.
- No liver?
- Oh, I see.
- You mean, like in the folktale?
- What's that?
This year is the Year of the Rabbit.
Each team gets a different type.
- These are for Jong Kook's team.
- It's cute.
- These are for my team?
- Oh, rabbit ears.
- It's cute.
- Oh, my. Look at this.
- All idol singers...
- Thank you.
- say it out loud always.
- I like it.
- When they see something cute,
- It's cute.
- they say, "It's cute."
- "Right?"
Rei.
As you can see,
- there are 13 rabbits here.
- Continue.
But among the normal rabbits,
- a Rabbit with No Liver is hiding.
- Of course.
- Who is that?
- Of course, there's a twist.
(1 of them is a spy.)
- Who is that?
- What's going on?
- Really?
- Does the spy know that?
- Is it you, Won Young?
Yes, the spy knows who he or she is.
One of you is
the Rabbit with No Liver.
You'll guess who's the rabbit
with no liver at the end.
- If you're right, you get a prize.
- It'll be hard to figure out.
- Only one of us all?
- Then...
- You have no liver, right?
- Only one...
- You're the spy, right?
- Just one of us?
- Me?
- Is the Rabbit with No Liver...
- I'm not... No.
- already decided?
(I'm not... No.)
- She's suspicious.
- Why? You mean, LEESEO?
- I asked if she was the spy.
- There's one among us.
And she got so flustered.
- Aren't you the spy?
- No, I'm not.
- She stuttered.
- Pretending he didn't hear me.
- We must find the spy by any means.
- Of course.
- Yoo Jin seems suspicious.
- That's awesome.
- We must find the spy by any means.
- Of course.
(Why is she smiling?)
- Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jin seems suspicious.
- Yoo Jin could make a good spy.
- I'm not the spy.
- Oh, it must be Yoo Jin. It's you.
- It's highly likely she's the spy.
- I'm not the spy.
- Okay. Yoo Jin is the spy.
- It's Yoo Jin.
- That's very likely, right?
- Yes, it's very likely.
- I agree.
- It could be LIZ.
- If it's one of us, it's too easy.
- Right. We can just tell.
- How about Rei?
I think they chose the leader.
- Me?
- Since Yoo Jin...
has been on many variety shows,
- she would do a great job. Hey.
- Suddenly...
- No, I'm not the spy.
- So Min seems suspicious too.
- I would've been an obvious choice.
- Right.
- I think...
- Won Young, why are you so quiet?
No, it's not like that.
- She's pretending she's the spy.
- She's suspicious.
- We're all bad at lying.
- Really?
- That's true.
- Yes, it's true.
- It shows when we play a game.
- We can't fool one another.
But Ga Eul, you know what?
Before we joined Running Man,
- we used to be bad at lying too.
- Of course.
- This show made us like this.
- We improved gradually.
So Min.
How did you feel
when you heard you were the spy?
Jong Kook,
I'm too timid to be a spy.
Her reaction is strange, right?
- No, I'm too timid.
- She never reacts like that.
- I do have a liver.
- She said she was too timid.
- Haha, you've been acting weird.
- It could be her.
- Oh, come to think of it,
- You're suspicious too.
- he was left alone earlier.
- No, I'm not the spy.
Jae Suk.
You seem suspicious since you're
asking so many questions.
- Right. That's how you find a spy.
- Won Young.
- That's why you seem...
- I always ask a lot of questions.
- to be at an advantage.
- I agree.
And he looks most similar
to a rabbit among all of us.
- He looks like a rabbit.
- That's true.
- Rabbits are pretty. Take it back.
- Haha is right.
- He's cute.
- There are various rabbit breeds.
- Some rabbits have crooked teeth.
- Rabbits are so lovely.
- So you have no liver?
- Some have crooked front teeth.
- You're so suspicious.
- No way.
- Hello.
I feel like...
- I'm in Thailand.
- Exactly.
- People wait in line to eat here.
- It's interesting.
- I feel like I'm in Thailand.
- Is this a popular restaurant?
- Hello.
- One, two, three, four, five...
Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Hello.
I'm hungry. I'm glad we're here.
I must say, this place is...
I guess
I haven't dined out in a long while.
This place is... I mean...
I know this place
because my wife likes it.
- Oh, I see.
- This is her favorite restaurant.
- I'm so excited.
- Before the shoot,
we asked the IVE members
about the restaurants...
- where they're regulars.
- Really?
- Yoo Jin recommended this place.
- Oh, I see.
- We all like this restaurant.
- Oh, Yoo Jin knew this restaurant.
- Yoo Jin, are you a regular here?
- I like this place too.
Yes, I eat here often.
I wait in line for an hour
to eat here.
- You have to wait in line? Really?
- Yes.
- You will play a game first.
- Okay.
The IVE members said they wanted to
play this game in the pre-interview.
- It's a debate game.
- A debate?
- We're good at it.
- Hold Your Breath And Debate Dive.
- Okay.
You will freely debate
on a given topic...
and make your choice individually.
What more staff members choose
will be the correct answer.
Those of you who choose
the same answer...
- will get one point.
- Okay. That's great.
The team with the highest score...
- will get a hint about the spy.
- Nice.
- The spy should try hard, right?
- Of course.
- Not to get caught.
- The spy should stand firm, right?
- I don't think I can do that.
- That's right.
The spy should be active.
Won Young, are you good at arguing?
I think I can argue logically.
Really? Okay. That's good.
It's important in this game.
- Here goes your first topic.
- Yes.
(What's the definition
of a dog's upper and lower bodies?)
- A dog?
- What's this?
- Oh, boy.
- What's that?
- What part is the upper body?
- I know what it means.
- Those who have a pet dog...
- It's obvious.
- would choose A.
- The answer is...
- Obviously, the answer is...
- It's A.
- It's definitely A.
- This is too obvious.
- A is the correct answer.
- There's nothing to talk about.
- We'll all choose the same answer.
- It's B.
- No, it's A!
- It's A.
- It's B.
- I expected no one to choose B.
- A is the correct answer.
- It's A.
- Of course, it's A. It's too easy.
- No, B is right.
The part where its legs are
should be the lower body.
You should consider
the forelimbs its arms.
But if you think about it,
those are all considered as legs.
- They're front and hind legs.
- That's right.
Let's hear what each of us thinks.
What do you think, LIZ?
- When you put clothes on a dog,
- Yes.
it usually covers the front part
from the neck.
So I think the part that's covered
is the upper body.
- She's right.
- When you dress a dog,
the clothes cover the top...
- Also...
- The belly faces down,
and there's the back.
- What did you say?
- What do you mean by that?
- What I'm saying is...
- Yes.
When you dress a dog,
you put clothes on its back.
Does it only cover its back?
Yes. It doesn't cover the belly.
- That's because they have to pee.
- It doesn't cover the belly.
- But if you look at B,
- Yes.
the upper body includes...
- the butt and the tail.
- That's right.
That means the tail is a part
of the upper body.
That's a good point.
I'm not sure if it's okay to say this,
but the anus...
- The anus is in the upper body.
- should be in the lower body.
- The anus...
- It should be in the lower body.
The anus is in the lower body.
- But the tail...
- Although the tail is included...
- I know this because I have a dog.
- Do you think it's A or B?
I think it's B.
A is the correct answer.
- No, B is correct.
- We have different opinions.
I think A is the correct answer.
- Why?
- Yoo Jin had a dog too.
It's because...
when you train a dog to give its paw,
you say "hand."
- That's right.
- Exactly!
- When you train a dog?
- True.
Then the dog puts
one of its front paws on your hand.
- That's right.
- Therefore,
we should consider
the front paws as the hands...
and front legs as the arms.
The part with the arms...
- That's easy to understand.
- is the upper body.
- Thus, the answer is A.
- I agree.
- If B is the correct answer,
- Yoo Jin has a pet dog.
- a dog would give all four paws.
- Exactly.
- Listen to me.
- Then...
- A dog can be trained differently.
- But that's how we train dogs.
You can train a dog
to give a hind paw...
- when you say, "Give me your hand."
- She's right.
- Dogs can be trained to do so.
- So you think it's B?
- That doesn't make any sense.
- I believe B is the correct answer.
- If compared to a human body...
- Yes.
- The pelvis is in the lower body.
- Of course.
- You said to compare it to us...
- Yes.
- Right.
- But that's a dog in the picture.
- It's a dog.
- So?
- For the dog, they're all paws.
- Right. They don't have hands.
- They don't have hands.
- They don't have hands,
- They...
- They walk with paws.
- but...
- I think it makes sense.
- Right?
- Think that it's a horse.
We call it a front leg.
We don't call it hand.
- Of course.
- We don't call it hand.
- We're humans. But that's a dog.
- Tell them.
- Right.
- We should understand them first.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- So what do you say?
- That's very good.
- I choose B.
- B.
- LEESEO, you tell us.
- It's B.
I'll choose A
because Yoo Jin thinks it's A.
- Say your opinion.
- That's great.
- I mean...
- Look.
- Why would you...
- Why did you follow...
- Yoo Jin's opinion?
- Tell us your opinion.
- Why did you follow her opinion?
- I...
LEESEO.
Humans used to walk on all fours
before evolving.
- And...
- Yes. Go ahead.
- Walking upright...
- Won Young is talking.
I'm talking too.
Won Young is talking.
- Won Young, tell us.
- What's your opinion?
And look. Fundamentally, we call it
the upper body and the lower body.
- "Up" and "low."
- Yes.
- Dogs basically stand like this.
- That's true.
Then isn't this their upper body
and this the lower body?
Exactly.
- That's right.
- If you look it like this,
- But Won Young.
- that's left and right.
- So it's A, isn't it?
- If it's A, it's left and right.
- So it's B.
- This is frustrating.
- If it's A, it's left and right.
- Let's say you took a dog to a vet.
If you say you want to get
the upper body X-ray done,
- Okay.
- then which part will they X-ray?
- This part?
- Right.
- They will X-ray this part.
- That makes sense.
- Why would you X-ray it?
- I'm going back to A.
- Great.
- If you go to a vet...
- Have you taken a dog to a vet?
I've never done it.
- But people know...
- You were lying then.
- from experience.
- You stay still.
You know when you go to a vet...
and tell them their upper body
is bad,
do you think
they will check that part?
- It'd be that part.
- But which part is the upper one?
- This is the upper part.
- Which is "up" in the picture?
- In the picture.
- It's B.
- No.
- A is...
- Won Young is good.
- A is left and right.
It's B.
- Look.
- That was nice, Won Young.
It's confusing because the picture
is put horizontally.
- It's not A.
- Look at this.
No, that's...
- It's more comfortable to look at.
- This is not how dogs stand.
- No. Why would you do that?
- Look at this.
- Do dogs live like this?
- Look at it this way.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- They live like this.
- What do you know?
- "What do you know?"
- Hey, and...
Think that it's cut like this.
It's an awful thing to do to a dog.
- I mean the legs...
- I feel so bad.
Is it not awful
if it's cut vertically?
- It's awful.
- Is it not awful...
if it's cut like this?
- Are you that cruel, Won Young?
- Tell us.
If you go to a pet shop
and ask for pants for a dog,
how do they look?
Have you seen pants that cover
the dog like this?
The pants...
You don't put pants
on the lower part only.
We get pants that cover this part.
- We get pants that cover this part.
- It's A.
- It's A, right?
- How many times are you changing?
- You get pants like this.
Think about it.
Do you get pants like this?
- Suk Jin.
- Why?
Have you bought pants for a dog?
Not even once.
- No, right?
- You don't buy them like that.
He's talking
about something he doesn't know.
- No dog pants...
- I know from my life experience.
- look like that.
- It's like a onesie.
- Ji Hyo raised many dogs.
- I know. She loves dogs.
- But Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
Look at this.
Anyway, they sell pants like this.
- Not this.
- They don't sell those.
No.
- The diaper.
- That's not true.
- Do they sell pants like that?
- You put all their legs into holes.
- Then you zip it up.
- That's...
(Four legs?)
- That's for a walk.
- Hey.
What about dog shoes?
- We buy four.
- They give you four.
- We put them on all fours.
- We don't ask for gloves and shoes.
- Right?
- Yes.
We call it four shoes.
- It's four shoes.
- No.
It's B.
- Right.
- It's B.
- Do you know what's important here?
- We've never heard of dog gloves.
- No. I think it's A.
- It's about if it's the upper...
or the lower body.
This is about separating
the upper and lower body.
It's not about if they have
4 feet or 2 hands.
Then it means feet
can be attached to the upper body.
- Sorry?
- Feet can be attached...
to the upper body?
- Yes. To the upper body.
- Feet are attached...
to the upper body?
But... Okay. Go ahead.
Hey. It's A.
- It's A.
- The nipples.
Nipples can't be attached
on the lower body.
Hey. Someone got nipples
on their lower body.
Who?
- Who?
- Over there.
- Nipples...
- It's B.
(He got it at once.)
Right. It's B.
- No.
- He got nipples on his lower body.
That's not true.
- I want to know the answer quickly.
- Yoo Jin, speak one more time.
- I want to be persuaded.
- Shall we vote?
- We chose B. But we can pick A.
- Should we go for B?
Let's go with A.
- It's A.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- A.
- It's A.
- They picked A.
- Everyone picked A.
- Did they pick A?
- We followed the popular opinion.
- Hold on.
- Only Ji Hyo...
- chose B.
- Only Ji Hyo picked B.
It's B for me.
She's stubborn.
- Hand. Leg.
- The staff members will vote too.
- Please.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Hand.
- A.
- What?
- One of them picked B.
One of them picked B.
One of us picked B too.
Everyone receives a point except
Ji Hyo as A received more votes.
- A.
- Ji Hyo.
This is how you do it.
This is the second theme.
Is human nature fundamentally
good or evil?
This is hard.
- We're going to argue a lot.
- This is hard.
- We'll argue a lot.
- It's definitely evil.
It's neither good nor evil.
I've raised a child.
- I'm neutral.
- You know?
- I think it's good.
- I thought it was good.
- You think it's good?
- A.
- I think it's A too.
- That's...
- Everyone is born with good nature.
- Right. The society.
- The environment and the society...
- can affect it.
- All babies seem to be good.
- I was such a docile baby.
- Okay.
But the society
changed me a little...
- as I grew up.
- How did you change?
- I'm a little evil now.
- Really?
- Yes. I think human nature is good.
- And you used to be nice?
- Yes. I used to be nice.
- That happens.
But the society
and my surroundings...
- changed me.
- So human nature is good...
- based on your experience.
- Yes.
Some evil ones change
and become good people too.
For Haha, before he got married,
- he did so many evil things.
- It's not related to the topic.
After he got married,
he completely changed.
Is Haha's nature good or evil?
(The theory that Haha was reformed
after he got married)
People can change.
I started believing it,
watching Haha.
You can completely change.
How about you, Rei?
Rei.
Yes?
Do you know what it means?
- Yes. I learned it.
- She heard the explanation.
I also thought everyone
was born as good person.
You thought human nature
was fundamentally good.
But everyone is a little evil.
But by watching how others behave,
they learn...
- They can become better people.
- to be a better person.
So you think human nature
is fundamentally evil.
- Yes. I think that's right.
- It's evil.
- Yes.
At school, we learn ethics.
- We learn what's good.
- People learn.
And they realize it.
But people do bad things
even without being taught.
- They already know it.
- Right.
- That's...
- So people are born evil.
- That's right.
- Because...
- if you give a bug to children,
- Yes.
- they don't feel guilty.
- Right.
It doesn't mean they're evil.
- Yes.
- They just destroy it.
- Right.
- They don't know then.
- I used to destroy many things.
- They do it without knowing.
- They naturally destroy things.
- Right.
- No, that's not true.
- I know.
- It's their instinct.
- Some children...
treat even a flower or a bug
with kindness.
- Of course, everyone is different.
- People are basically evil.
Even if they're young...
When there are two babies,
if you take care
of just one of them,
the other one gets jealous
and cries and whines.
- Right.
- Yes.
Jealousy is a negative feeling.
So human nature is more like evil.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- She's smart.
- Yes!
- She's doing good.
Guys, think about this.
People learn very quickly
when they are young.
Yes.
- They learn from others.
- They might've learned to be evil.
Are you saying that people know...
how to hit others as soon
as they're born? It's not like that.
- I know.
- They learn from others.
- This is why humans...
- That's why human nature is evil.
- learn from people around them.
- Okay.
That's why human nature is good.
It's because they learned to do so.
Right.
They might've learned to be evil.
The moment a baby is born,
do they smile?
- Right. They cry.
- Or do they frown?
- They frown and cry.
- They frown.
- Come on.
- They cry when they're born.
- We wish we were born good.
- It would've been nice.
- But we were not. We can't help it.
- We want to believe...
that our nature is good.
But I'm saying human nature
is more evil than good.
- Anyway,
- Let's vote.
it's A or B.
- B is evil.
- A is good.
- A is good and B is evil.
- B is evil. Okay.
- One.
- It would be half and half.
- No. I don't know.
- When people are born...
Guys, let me say the last word.
Everyone is good.
- Everyone is evil.
- Everyone is good.
Don't consider them evil because
of their instinctive behaviors.
- Everyone is evil.
- Everyone is good.
- They cry when they're born.
- Right. They cry when they're born.
Everyone is restraining themselves.
You know it.
- Put it up.
- Put it up on the count of three.
In 1, 2, 3.
Everyone is restraining themselves.
- Human nature is evil.
- We're restraining our evil side.
Am I the only one who picked A?
- We're restraining ourselves.
- Yes. We're restraining ourselves.
Only Jae Suk thinks
human nature is good.
- Yes.
- The staff members will vote too.
Everyone...
- is born good.
- Don't listen to him.
People cry when they're born.
- No.
- For real.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- I wish we were good.
- What?
- A!
- It's A!
- They chose A.
- Two, three.
- I wish we were good.
- What?
- A!
- It's A!
- They chose A.
- It's a miracle.
- No way.
- It's A.
Jae Suk spoke too much.
- What is this?
- Dear people.
- This is nonsense.
You will be blessed.
It's A.
- Did you choose Side A?
- Yes.
(Hold on.)
- Isn't he the Rabbit with No Liver?
- Did you choose Side A?
- The Rabbit with No Liver.
- He doesn't have a liver.
- The Rabbit with No Liver?
- Isn't it him?
- He's the Rabbit with No Liver.
- It was a mission.
- He did it on purpose.
Everyone has to go
with what he chooses.
- He chose something else.
- Right?
That's right. I guess they have
to go with what he chooses.
He's the Rabbit with No Liver.
They were influenced by what I said.
- No.
- I persuaded them.
- That's not true.
- It makes no sense.
- It doesn't.
Let's ask someone.
Why did you come to that decision?
Why did you think so?
(He's flustered.)
- Myung Sub, tell us.
- Tell us.
- Say it on behalf of the staff.
- Hold on.
- Right.
His child was born.
- His child was recently born.
- He has a child.
- But...
- It's only been a month.
- One month?
Of course, you would think
the child is like an angel.
- You wait.
- That's a cute phase.
Wait until the child takes other's things
and starts crying.
- This makes no sense.
- So,
- the winner in this mission...
- No way.
is this team.
He won this?
- It's our team. We won.
- Good.
You can take this hint
about the Rabbit with No Liver.
- Only the four of you can see it.
- We're the only ones who can check.
He should win if he wants to keep
his identity hidden.
- He has no liver.
- It's strange.
- Keep it to yourselves.
- Okay.
(Team Jae Suk received a hint
about the Rabbit with No Liver.)
What does this mean?
Okay.
It's not clear-cut, right?
(The hint is confusing?)
Why are you reading it
until the last moment?
- Have you understood it?
- Yes.
Okay. Don't say anything.
- They might figure it out.
- I think I get it.
Jae Suk is acting strange.
- Right?
- Yes. He's acting strange.
This is really...
- It's amazing.
- It's great.
We have to watch closely
when they eat.
- I almost misinterpreted it.
- Right?
You have to be attentive
when they eat.
You don't have a liver
or a gall-bladder.
- He's suspicious.
- The food we prepared...
- Yes.
is the signature menu of this place.
It's Lang Zaab,
a Thai dish of steamed bones.
What is that?
It's Yoo Jin's pick. I should try it.
And fried rice with crab meat...
- seasoned with Thai soy sauce.
- I like that.
It looks nice.
That's amazing.
Can we all eat it?
- Enjoy it as much as you can.
- We love it.
You can eat it.
They'll just give it to us.
I'm hungry.
- They're making it.
- It must be delicious.
I'm hungry.
What is this?
- That's Lang Zaab.
- It's Lang Zaab.
- It looks nice.
- Is this steamed bones?
What is this?
This is crazy.
- I've never seen this before.
- That looks amazing.
- It looks great.
- It looks tasty.
- Each team can eat together.
- Can we eat?
You can start eating
when all the dishes are out.
- Okay.
- Eat.
- Is this spicy?
- I guess so.
I think it will be a bit sour.
It looks so good.
I'll enjoy it so much.
- It's pepper.
- How does it taste?
- Is it not your taste?
- Try it.
It tastes bland.
- Is it?
- It's bland?
It doesn't look bland.
When are the rest coming?
(Team Jae Suk observes them.)
- Look.
- When are the rest coming?
When are the rest coming?
- Is it delicious, So Min?
- It's not what I imagined.
I thought it will be sour,
but it's not.
It's very spicy.
- It's spicy?
- It's spicy.
- There's a lot of chili pepper.
- What else does it taste like?
- Can we taste it?
- Let's taste it.
I think we should try it.
Don't start eating yet.
They said something about eating
when they received the hint.
- Something about eating.
- That's right.
(Jae Suk told them
to observe when people eat.)
(Detective Kim caught that.)
Someone has to carry out a mission.
Is the mission to eat first?
What?
Why did So Min eat just now?
You've no liver.
You ate when we were told
not to eat yet. You have no liver.
She's the one with no liver.
The dishes are all out.
You can enjoy your meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
It's really delicious.
Is this how you eat this, Yoo Jin?
This is good.
- It's delicious.
- It's tasty.
- It's really good.
- It's delicious.
This is tasty.
(Everyone is enjoying the meal.)
Hyung In...
(Detective Kim is investigating
alone.)
told us to eat together.
There's a reason for that.
I'll eat the bones first.
- I'll eat the bones first.
- Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook is standing.
- He's not eating.
- Jong Kook.
- Eat, Jong Kook.
Why aren't you eating?
I am going to eat.
- I should take one.
- Should I give you one?
- Should we try this?
- Yes.
I should eat it like this.
It has a scent.
(Will he be able to figure out
something this time?)
It's so delicious.
(Enjoying)
(They all forget about the rabbit
with no liver and enjoy the meal.)
It's tasty.
It's bland, isn't it?
This is delicious.
Is it just ours?
This...
It's not delicious.
- Isn't it bland?
- Yes.
Is the stew spicy?
This is delicious.
(Observing)
This is really delicious.
You can learn it.
(But Haha in the same team
is enjoying the food.)
It tastes authentic.
It's nice.
(Finishing)
Jae Suk finished it.
He's finished a plate.
- It's clean.
- He works hard.
Isn't it suspicious?
- Our food is really delicious.
- Why?
I'm eating well
because it's very delicious.
- Is it just ours?
- This...
What's wrong?
Does it taste different?
I think the dishes taste different.
I think they all taste different.
- I think the tastes are different.
- Ours is very bland.
- Yours is bland?
- Yes. A little bit.
- What is this?
- I guess there's something.
- What is it?
- Why?
- Hold on.
- It's that bland?
- Is yours all right?
- Salt is bad for your liver.
What are you talking about?
- What does it taste like?
It's not seasoned!
- Ours is seasoned.
- It's not seasoned.
- Why?
- Ours is seasoned.
- Whose dish?
- Look.
(The rabbits with no hints
have found out something strange.)
(The hint that Team Jae Suk got...)
(The team with the rabbit with no
liver will eat unseasoned food.)
I think this will taste better
with sauce.
- It needs sauce.
- It's not finished.
Could you give us some fish sauce
and some chili pepper?
(The dish of all the teams
looks the same.)
Could we get some soy sauce
and chili pepper?
Just a little.
You don't have them?
It's Ji Hyo's team.
Their food is not seasoned.
- The team next to us?
- Yes.
So everyone on our team has a liver?
- We all have livers.
- We do.
- One in this team has no liver.
- The one with no liver...
I think it's one of the IVE members
in this team.
There's one in your team.
- It's So Min.
- I think it's So Min.
I told you earlier
that So Min is strange.
You've not seen the hint.
Stop...
(He's started
his staring investigation.)
Stop acting like you know something.
You have not even seen the hint.
Why are you acting like you know it?
Don't think everything you know
is real.
It's not real.
"Not seasoned"
sounds like "there is no liver."
- It's not seasoned.
- Not seasoned.
- Just enjoy the food.
- You have not seen the hint.
Why make such poor guesses?
(Suspect 1. He said it's authentic
while eating bland food.)
(Suspect 2. She tasted it
without permission.)
(Suspect 3. She publicly said
the food is bland.)
(Suspect 4. She puts suspicion
on the Zoned-out Crazy Sisters.)
(Suspect 5. She's just sad
that the food came out bland.)
(Which of these five rabbits
is the spy?)
This is so delicious.
I ate a lot. I ate well.
I'm full.
Now that we have...
- all eaten...
- It feels nice.
We've grown close.
- That's right.
- My goodness.
- Food is essential.
You know, I was really surprised.
Yoo Jin ate like crazy.
Won Young ate like crazy too.
- Yes. She ate with gusto.
- Won Young.
Won Young, how do you remain skinny?
I don't put on weight easily.
I see.
- I envy you.
- That will change once she hits 40.
Why are you talking about
the age of 40 already?
I am just saying.
- LEESEO is 17.
- Jae Suk.
- Won Young hasn't graduated yet.
- That's right.
- Haven't you graduated yet?
- No.
- My goodness.
- It must be coming up.
- Suk Jin, give her a present.
- That's a nice idea.
Make a promise.
- Yes. Make a promise.
- Thank you.
- All right. LEESEO.
- What will you buy her?
- What would you like?
- Did you make a promise?
- Yes. What would you like?
- Suk Jin.
- Anything would be nice.
- Won Young...
Won Young has everything
anyone could ever want.
Won Young,
aren't you richer than me?
She is an ambassador
for luxury brands.
- Right?
- Yes.
I will give you a present.
My goodness.
All right.
- That's heartwarming.
- There you go.
- That makes me look bad.
That doesn't make you look bad.
- Won Young is successful.
- Right.
The successful ones should pay.
- That's right.
- I agree.
That's nice. I envy her spirit.
Youth.
Won Young, is it exciting...
- to be successful?
- I am grateful,
- of course.
- What kind of a question is that?
- Seriously.
"Is it exciting to be successful?"
- What's wrong with you?
- He sounded so shabby.
- It's not like that.
- Maybe he doesn't have a liver.
- I have never experienced...
- Suk Jin.
- You don't have a liver, do you?
- It seems that way.
- I mean...
- You don't have a liver or pride.
It's not the liver.
- He doesn't have a sense of shame.
- Seriously.
- I have a liver.
- What was that?
- That's so funny.
- This is fascinating.
- What's fascinating?
I watched Running Man
in childhood and thought,
"Will the show be present
by the time I become an idol?"
- We should keep going.
- Yes.
- Please keep going.
- I will root for the show.
At the year-end award ceremony,
Lee Gyeong Gyu said something.
You don't need to leave
when people are clapping.
You don't need to do that.
People clap for you
when you leave anyway.
Seriously. We need...
(A different point of view)
- That's so funny.
- Listen.
That's the important thing.
LEESEO, don't you agree?
When you leave,
people don't tell you to go away.
They clap for you.
We need more than our will
to keep the show going.
People clap for you
when you leave anyway.
That's not true. You might disappear
without anyone knowing.
- You never know.
- No. People usually clap for you.
I am sorry about
this line of conversation, LEESEO.
- I am sorry.
- You will understand...
- It takes more than your will.
what we meant...
- about 20 or 30 years later.
- It's true.
Even after 30 years...
Even after 20 years,
she will be younger than I am now.
Even after 30 years,
You know, we locked up
IVE members in the middle.
- Seriously.
- For real.
- We feel like criminals.
- Why are you giving them a lesson?
In any case...
- He sounds like a real adult.
- Now that we are at it,
why don't you take turns...
and ask the senior celebrities
a question?
- That's a good idea.
- You might have some questions.
- I love it.
- Ask a question each.
- That's a good idea.
- It's a precious opportunity.
- Rei, why don't you go first?
- We will tell you anything.
If you don't have any questions,
you can pass.
Pass.
(Pass.)
(I don't have any questions!)
- Hey.
- She is good.
- Jae Suk was so serious.
- Hey, Rei.
Good job.
- I can't believe you.
- Good job.
- Everyone might choose to pass.
- Seriously.
She said it in a specific tone too.
- "Pass."
- It was good.
- It was good, Rei.
- It was amazing.
- It was funny.
- Everyone might choose to pass.
- Okay. I got it.
Jae Suk's ambitious segment
got shut down.
"Let's start with Rei."
- "Pass."
I can't believe it.
Now, the segment with IVE...
Realistic Advice is over.
Do you remember this place?
(B sundae gukbap restaurant
at Eonju Station)
- We haven't been here in a while.
- Gukbap.
Did you visit here often
because your agency was nearby?
- Yes.
- Really?
- I see.
- That must be why you came here.
- That's right.
That must be why you came here.
You are at the restaurant
LIZ frequented as a trainee,
- B Sundae Gukbap.
- I was right.
Why did you frequent
this restaurant?
I felt like recording went well...
if I ate gukbap beforehand.
So I always came here
and ate gukbap.
- I see.
- I came here before recording.
- It became a ritual.
- Yes.
- It will be delicious.
- Rei.
Hot gukbap is perfect in winter.
- It's a hearty dish.
- A hearty dish.
I will explain the mission.
The mission is the Bomb Relay Dance.
A member from each team
will stand in a line.
Then the first person
will dance to the music.
After some time, the first person
will move to the back of the line...
and the next person will dance.
When two minutes are up,
the music will stop.
The member who was dancing then
will get eliminated.
- It's Pass the Bomb with dancing.
- I see.
This time, the teams
that placed 1st and 2nd...
will have a chance
to switch members.
- Switch members?
- That's sudden.
- It's understandable.
- It will help us catch the spy.
- That's right.
- It will narrow down the search.
- I see.
The first round will be
between the IVE members.
The second round will be
between the Running Man members.
The third round will be
between everyone...
except for the two people
who got eliminated.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- LIZ, let's go.
- Legend, let's go.
It tickled
- It tickled
- Bunnies.
- Raise the volume.
(Round 1 begins.)
- My goodness.
- Don't go easy on them.
("Into the New World"
by Girls' Generation)
Time
(The countdown
for 2 minutes begins.)
Time
Girls' Generation.
Then the person at the front
will move to the back.
Like that?
(Then the next person will dance.)
When two minutes are up,
the person who was dancing
will be eliminated.
- Say goodbye to sadness
(Goodbye)
There you go.
- She can dance well.
- She is good.
She is good.
(Fast forward by 2 times)
(Double speed)
The bomb is about to go off.
They have time.
- Rei.
(They are past the 1-minute mark.)
- There you go.
- My goodness.
Okay. That's good.
Why isn't it going off?
Hey, move out of the way!
(Being pressed for time
makes her raise her voice.)
She is scared.
How are two minutes so long?
- Come on.
- You need to dance.
You need to dance.
Don't move to the back right away.
Ga Eul.
Okay.
She is brave.
Dance a bit more.
You need to dance for a bit.
Don't move to the back right away.
- How are two minutes so long?
- You need to stop and dance.
Look at Ga Eul.
(Time's up.)
(Screaming)
Isn't it LEESEO?
- It's Ga Eul.
- Is it Ga Eul?
- It was close.
- Ga Eul.
It was a matter of 0.5 seconds.
- It was close, Senior Ga Eul.
- I stepped aside.
You got caught
even though you stepped aside.
- You should have stopped sooner.
- Ga Eul, come here.
Ga Eul, you are out.
The second round will be...
- between the Running Man members.
- Okay.
We will win.
- Let's go.
- So Min.
- So Min. Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
Please play a song we know.
I will rule the solo shot.
- I will stay there for a long time.
- Okay.
- I will stay there forever.
- Of course.
- I love solo shots.
I am addicted to solo shots.
- Let's go.
- I am addicted to solo shots.
- Music, please.
- Play something we know.
(How refreshing
will their relay dance be?)
("Touch My Body" by SISTAR)
My body
(Taking off)
(She starts the dance
in a sexy way.)
She loves it.
You look like an IVE member.
You are just as good as them.
This song isn't by IVE.
It's by SISTAR.
Ji Hyo.
(She squeezes out her fresh charms.)
- We have two minutes.
- Two minutes.
Move out of the way.
(Ji Hyo enjoys the solo shot
since she knows the dance.)
Hey, move out of the way.
Hey, you know the dance.
- Let's go.
- Touch my body
- Hey.
(Here comes the grasshopper.)
(He is extremely excited
because he likes the song.)
My goodness.
(Twerking)
What was that?
- Twerking.
- Move out of the way.
Okay.
It isn't ending.
(There are no brakes
for his excitement.)
Move out of the way already.
(He danced solo for 30 seconds.)
For goodness' sake.
Okay.
(Here comes Se Chan the rabbit.)
(His dance moves are cheeky,
not refreshing.)
No. I should get back to the line.
(1 minute passes.)
It's almost done.
Okay.
That's "Swallowtail Butterfly."
(His dance moves become big
so that people wouldn't notice.)
(The muscular rabbit
shakes his body too.)
Jong Kook, you need to move
out of the way.
Move out of the way.
- So Min, move out of the way.
- There you go.
- Not yet.
You are as good as them.
(Her dance became oilier.)
What's the order?
- I go before you.
- All right.
- Why isn't it ending?
- Do we still have time?
It's about time.
Move out of the way.
- It's almost done.
- It's about time.
(2 minutes are almost up.)
No!
(The man who is addicted
to the center position got caught.)
Hey!
I mean...
(Jae Suk becomes the second member
to get eliminated.)
- Hey!
- What?
- Why did you...
- He grabbed me.
- Why didn't you move to the back?
- Why did you dance?
- Why did you grab me?
- He didn't grab him.
- He did.
Why did you grab me?
- You jerk!
- You cheated.
You jerk!
I forgot that he was on my team
and grabbed him...
- because it was fun.
- Why did you grab me?
Suk Jin loved it.
- I forgot that he was on my team.
- Come on.
I grabbed him too.
- Jae Suk, you are out.
- For goodness' sake.
For the last round,
everyone will dance for two minutes.
- Not many teammates remain.
- Seriously.
That was too much. He cheated.
Please pound on my shoulder blades.
I got a cramp since I danced...
- after a long while.
- Did you get a cramp?
- Here?
- Yes. I got a cramp there.
It's because I shook my body
after a long while.
My shoulder blades... Hold on.
- My cramp is moving.
- Are you okay?
It's here now.
(Making a fuss)
- Hold on.
- Is it moving?
Why is my cramp moving?
My shoulder blades.
The part that goes in.
- Yes. That's the spot.
- Is your cramp moving?
- My goodness.
- Are you okay now?
It felt strange. I am okay now.
- Did it move to your neck?
- What kind of a cramp moves?
- Let's mix ourselves up.
- My cramp moved.
Okay.
If you have a song request,
we will play it.
- A song by IVE. "Love Dive."
- A song by IVE?
A song by IVE. "Love Dive."
- "Love Dive."
- That's right.
Play "Love Dive."
- Does it go like this?
- Yes.
- Do this for "Love Dive."
- After this...
- "Love Dive."
- I like this dance.
It reminds me of Jang Woo Hyuk's
Hammer Dance.
I don't know what it is.
- Don't you know H.O.T?
- Let's begin.
I can't believe it.
I feel so old.
Music, please.
(Round 3)
(The original singer's
facial expression changes.)
- She is a big rabbit.
- Tick, tock.
(It became a headband
you use to wash your face.)
What are you doing with your eyes?
- There you go.
- This dance is hard.
(Nervous)
Am I doing it wrong?
I am doing it right.
(After the magic show,
the rabbits dance.)
I don't know this part.
Is this right?
(Relaxed)
She is really tall.
(Hold your breathe
and take a love dive)
(Rei appears with the 2nd verse.)
Seriously.
Our song is three minutes long,
so we will nearly reach the end.
(Ji Hyo enters.)
(She forgets what she learned
and does the Indian Dance.)
Isn't that Chakra's dance?
Chakra.
The song is long.
She is done.
What's up with your face?
(His eyes show that
he is overly absorbed.)
(Then he does
the "Swallowtail Butterfly" dance.)
He is such a middle-aged man.
This dance is too hard.
(Or the Swa Swa Dance.)
That's it.
(Se Chan perfectly recreates
the Mirror Dance.)
- Do this.
- All right.
There you go.
How does he know
all the dance moves?
(They watch Se Chan's dance.)
(He forgot about the time limit.)
Hurry up.
- Done.
- There is a time limit.
Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- Jong Kook, step aside right away.
- Step aside right away.
- Hurry up.
(The ninja-style dance time
began once more.)
(Calm)
It will end soon.
Why isn't it ending?
(Time's up.)
(Se Chan got eliminated
in his attempt to get a solo shot.)
- Okay.
- You should have stepped aside.
- Oh, no.
- We placed first.
- Nice.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- LEESEO, good job.
(Team Ji Hyo placed 1st
since no one got eliminated.)
- Okay.
- It ended when I posed.
- Exactly when you posed.
- Seriously.
- You got a solo shot.
- Exactly when you posed.
- It ended when I posed.
As soon as you did this...
(Team Jong Kook placed 2nd
since Se Chan got eliminated.)
Thus, Haha and Ji Hyo's team
placed first.
(Team Ji Hyo, 1st place)
We placed first.
- Team Jong Kook placed second.
- We can switch the members.
Okay.
- Did we place last?
- Yes.
The 2nd-place winner can get
1 new member from each team.
- One member from each team.
- Yes.
After the 2nd-place winner is done,
the 1st-place winner...
can get one new member...
- or keep the team as it is.
- Let's see how it goes.
Let's choose after them.
- Okay.
- Team Jong Kook, which members...
do you want to switch out?
- Which members will it be?
- If the four of us aren't a spy...
Are some of us being switched out?
Yes, we are.
One member should be
from the team that got bland food.
Then...
(There is a Rabbit with No Liver
in Team Ji Hyo.)
- Let's switch the members.
- My guess is Yoo Jin.
- Yoo Jin?
- Yes.
- Okay.
We will switch Won Young and Yoo Jin.
- Yoo Jin.
- As for Rei...
- What?
- Won Young and Yoo Jin?
- Hello.
- Really?
Yoo Jin?
- Why me?
- And?
And we will switch Suk Jin and Rei.
- Oh, yes. You are a cutie.
- Come on.
- All right.
- Let's whisper.
You are the team
that has a Rabbit with No Liver.
- That's right.
- That rabbit is in your team.
Then it must be her.
Me? No.
(Why did Ji Hyo point So Min out
right away?)
No, it isn't me.
Let's do this.
You want to send her away, right?
Yes.
- We need to switch up the members.
- Then send me to that team.
- Send me to that team.
- In that case...
- We need to switch up the members.
- Then send me to that team.
(Why does she want to go
to the team Yoo Jin moved to?)
- No.
- Switch places with Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Why?
- You shouldn't do that.
- You made it confusing.
- Why not?
- With whom?
We just don't want her on our team.
- We want one member from...
- Am I being switched out?
- Yes.
- We are set then.
Now, the food will be prepared.
- Okay. Sit down.
- Okay.
- It will be confusing.
- This game is so hard.
Okay.
I can't wait.
Me too.
After eating this dish,
you will catch
the Rabbit with No Liver.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The gukbap is the last hint
to find the spy.)
This is the last hint.
We will know once we eat this dish.
I don't know. Let's eat.
I am curious.
We will know once we eat this dish.
It looks so tasty.
I will taste it first.
(The team with the rabbit
without a liver...)
It looks delicious.
(will eat bland gukbap.)
Okay.
(Which team has the rabbit
without a liver?)
- Let's go.
- It looks delicious.
Please eat the dish now.
I am sorry, but won't you give us
radish kimchi?
- No.
- Thank you for the food.
- We just got gukbap.
(Kimchi got excluded
for a definite hint.)
It's tasty.
It's really tasty.
It's hard to remove
the unpleasant odor of meat.
That's right.
It's really tasty.
I normally can't eat food
with bad odor.
I can eat this with rice.
I want to eat it with rice.
I am too scared to taste it.
- Seriously. I am too nervous.
- Please enjoy the dish.
(Did Team Ji Hyo lose
the Rabbit with No Liver?)
- The unpleasant odor of meat.
- I thought it would be spicy.
It wouldn't be spicy.
Does it suit your taste?
Thank you for the food.
Ji Hyo.
(It's good.)
(Did Team Ji Hyo get tasty gukbap?)
(It's tasty!)
(Did Team Ji Hyo lose
the Rabbit with No Liver?)
Suk Jin.
Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food.
It hasn't been seasoned at all.
- Not even the sauce?
- We don't get any side dishes.
I didn't try the sauce.
- Please enjoy the dish.
- It's hard to remove...
(Did Team Jong Kook get
bland gukbap?)
Please. Gukbap shouldn't be bland.
- It looks delicious.
- Yes.
(The two strong candidates
taste the dish as well.)
It's tasty, but I don't know
how it compares to other gukbap.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
You don't have a liver, do you?
- Be honest.
- It isn't me.
- Do you like gukbap?
- Seriously.
- Isn't it tasty?
- Really?
Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- What?
- What is it?
- Isn't it bland?
- It's bland.
- Don't engage her.
- It's one of them.
- As I said, you need to act.
My goodness.
(Team Jong Kook
got the definite proof.)
I think it's tasty, Yoo Jin.
I am serious.
- Really?
- It's tasty.
(So Min keeps saying
that it's tasty.)
It's really tasty.
My goodness.
(Is she acting to keep it a secret
from other teams?)
It isn't me. It really isn't me.
Now, we will remove the boards.
It looks like
everyone finds it delicious.
- It's tasty.
- Is it tasty?
- So Min, is it tasty?
- It melts in your mouth.
It's really tasty.
- Really?
- It suits my taste.
It's really tasty.
Why...
It contains the soul.
- This restaurant is nice.
- It's So Min.
So Min?
Jong Kook, don't make a mistake.
It really isn't me.
Okay.
It contains the soul?
Totally.
It contains the soul.
It would be tastier with sundae.
Sundae.
Yoo Jin, you must be full.
I ate too much earlier.
I could finish the entire bowl.
Yoo Jin, are you eating well?
(Jae Suk sees
if Yoo Jin is enjoying the dish.)
- All right.
- It's tasty.
It's sweet.
I have no clue.
The Rabbit with No Liver
can act well.
- It's really tasty.
- This is a nice restaurant.
I feel like I am in Busan.
Are you enjoying the dish?
- Yes.
Soon, you will write down
the name of the person...
you think is
the Rabbit with No Liver.
As I explained, the members
who failed to guess correctly...
will carry out a penalty.
The Rabbit with No Liver
will receive a prize...
if more than half of the members
fail to guess correctly.
When we give you the ballot,
write down the name
and give it back to us.
I narrowed it down to two members.
But there is only one.
I don't know which one it is.
I am torn between two members too.
Which members are you talking about?
Seriously.
- It isn't me.
- You and who else?
It isn't me.
You have it all wrong again.
It really isn't me.
- This is bad.
- It's you.
(She asked to be
in the same team as Yoo Jin.)
- It isn't me.
- Do you like gukbap?
(She insisted
that the gukbap was tasty.)
(Was it a strategy
to avoid suspicion?)
It's really tasty.
It really isn't me.
- This is bad.
- It's you.
Is it Yoo Jin?
This is a nice restaurant.
(Is it Yoo Jin, the member
who insists on being innocent?)
It's really tasty.
(She acted like
her gukbap was tasty.)
(Why was Yoo Jin passionate
about suspecting So Min?)
It's so confusing.
There is only one.
(The vote begins.)
All right.
- Give it to me.
- I voted.
- Will I be in trouble...
- It's not me.
- if I write two names?
- Just write one.
It's not that you'll be in trouble.
But you can't win the prize.
- I see.
- You don't get in trouble.
Are you done?
- I just wrote one of those two.
- I did too.
It must be one of the two.
We took a hint on the spot anyway.
- Right.
- There was no hint, but...
I just picked it up.
Seriously, I will follow my gut.
- My body's response.
- I followed my gut.
- All right.
- I want to catch the spy.
Let's do this.
- All right. All votes are in.
- I'm so curious.
(All votes are in.)
I have no idea.
- I'm so nervous.
- I'm really curious this time.
I'll first announce who will...
win the prize.
Five people.
(They need 7 people
to exceed the majority.)
(Who will win the prize?)
- An Yoo Jin.
- What?
- LIZ.
- Rei.
- What?
It's all them.
And Ga Eul will win the prize.
- Yes!
- We did it.
- Is it over like this?
- I knew it.
Did they give the correct answer?
The Rabbit with No Liver
who made you eat...
food without salt is...
An Yoo Jin.
- Was it Yoo Jin?
- My goodness.
Today, we will look
for Rabbit with No Liver...
who's hiding among ordinary rabbits.
And, Yoo Jin,
you are the Rabbit with No Liver.
The team
with Rabbit with No Liver...
will only get dishes without salt.
(Yoo Jin already knew
about dishes without salt.)
I'm not good at lying.
(She said she wasn't good at lying,)
(but she pretended
not to know anything.)
(If she was switched alone,
she would get caught.)
- Send me to this team.
- Then...
(But she escaped the crisis
when So Min voluntarily joined her.)
(Then she accused So Min
of being the spy.)
- Was it Yoo Jin?
- My goodness.
I thought it was
either Ji Hyo or Yoo Jin.
- It's so...
- I thought it was So Min.
This isn't just right.
So Min got eight votes.
They don't trust me.
Did I do anything suspicious today?
So Min had a strange look
on her face.
Was it An Yoo Jin? My gosh.
- Yoo Jin!
- I mean,
- Yoo Jin sounded so nonchalant.
- Your tongue...
- So Min.
- I guess So Min's tongue is numb.
- She really liked the food.
- So Min said...
- the food was tasty.
- It was really delicious.
It was really bland,
but she really liked it.
It could've been perfect
if we didn't have So Min.
- Gosh, So Min.
- When Haha sent So Min,
I thought we were doomed.
I was thinking of Yoo Jin,
but I changed it at the last moment.
Her facial expression
was somewhat unnatural.
This is so bad.
- I can't believe this.
- It's unbelievable.
So it was Yoo Jin.
- Yes!
- We did it.
Didn't you like the food?
We win the prize!
- I'm so disappointed.
- This is disappointing.
- That was so close.
- It really was.
Please bring in the prize.
- What is it?
- What?
We prepared the finest
chocolate and macaroons.
- My gosh.
- It's so nice.
- It's chocolate.
- My gosh.
It looks so delicious.
- I'll announce the penalty.
- What is it?
We've decided to focus...
on promoting the new airtime
of Running Man in January.
So today's penalty is...
to shoot a video to promote
the new airtime of Running Man.
It takes a really long time.
This is the worst.
We will make a video with a phone
and post it on social media.
How many people?
It can't be one person.
Those who got it wrong...
- All of us?
It's all the members of Running Man.
Yes. It's all of us.
- At least one of us...
- It was so close.
- This is fun. It's really fun.
- We totally fell for it.
All right.
Please get ready for the penalty.
- Thank you.
- Good work today.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Thank you, IVE.
Let's begin.
- Where should we look?
- Is this six?
- Look at the phone.
- This phone?
The phone?
Should we look at the phone?
We should stand closer.
Please stand close together.
You stand here, So Min.
- Can you see us?
- I'll be compared to them.
- I don't dance as well as they do.
- You should stand here.
- He's right.
- Then it will be funny.
- I mean, this...
- It helps promote our show.
They dance so well.
It will be funny?
Seriously...
- You're doing this for the show.
- They can't see us.
- You're not on the video?
- We just need to stand close.
You should be on the video.
Actually, we didn't know
so many members would lose.
So we prepared a small background.
- I know.
- We will stay close.
Should we just do this in the back?
- Jae Suk...
- Okay.
- That's a good idea.
- We will do this.
- Like this.
Let's begin.
(The shoot begins.)
LEESEO, we're...
(Showing off his gums)
(Only the ones in the front row
are dancing well.)
(Dancing roughly)
(Even his hands are wrong.)
Let's begin now.
- What's after like?
At six!
You guys are doing it all.
What was that?
Hey.
(A mysterious canyon)
(The weaklings
who want to be strong)
(A teacher is coming
to teach them a lesson?)
(A master of martial art, Jang Hyuk)
(Shall I warm up?)
(With the amazing introduction,)
(the authentic
action school begins!)
(Scene 1: The protagonist
training jeet kune do)
You should wrap it around like this.
(Wrap it around...)
(What?)
You're about to kiss it.
(An ugly scene)
(Scene 2: The protagonist
starting a real fight)
(Shouting)
(Feeling strange again)
(It's hard to tell
what genre it is.)
(It's a scene
of a rough and tumble fight.)
(And that's when...)
(the real master of martial arts
shows up.)
(Action star, Donnie Yen)
(Masters of Colorful Martial Arts)