(More friendly)
(More novel)
(2023 Running Man)
- Hello.
Why do you have so much stuff?
Why do we need a suitcase in the New Year?
It's so contrived.
It's not like
we're going on a long trip.
It's cold.
Hello. It's so cold today.
The weather is really cold.
Suk Jin is getting on a plane soon.
Why are you...
Hey, it will be just an overnight trip.
- Are you moving? Why is it...
- Because it's cold.
- We need a lot of clothes.
- You and I are being reasonable.
Suk Jin, I have one more suitcase
that's bigger than this.
- One more?
- Yes.
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- This is piquant.
- He also brought a big one.
- This is enough.
This is piquant.
Why do you have such a big suitcase?
You have Na Eun's suitcase.
Hey, is it that only those who
experienced "Family Outing"...
- brought big bags?
- Suk Jin.
You brought something compact.
- Compact?
- You brought something compact.
Your glasses steamed up.
- Where's Haha?
- Gosh.
- There he is.
- Hello.
- Haha.
- You look better now.
- I feel much better now.
I'm all good.
Are you feeling better?
I heard Se Chan would come later tonight.
- Tonight.
- After work.
We all caught COVID-19 before,
but I don't understand...
why everyone pretends to be fine
when I call them.
- Even when they're obviously ill.
- That's...
Look at me.
- They don't want to look weak.
Se Chan said
it wasn't so bad this time.
- Right.
- That's a lie.
- Is it a lie?
- It almost killed me this time.
- Really? I didn't know that.
- He just pretended to be tough.
Anyway, we have things to celebrate.
- Of course.
- So...
- Thank you.
- Jae Suk did it again.
- Congratulations.
- I won the Grand Award.
I know. I was watching you.
Thank you.
(He won the Grand Award after
running hard in the year 2022.)
Thankfully, I won...
- my 19th Grand Award.
- That's crazy.
- This is really crazy.
- I said this as a joke.
"Are you going to win
the Grand Award 20 times?"
- And it will probably happen.
- He did say that.
It will happen this year.
If things go well,
it will really happen.
Actually, now that it's already like this,
I should try hard this year.
- Let's make it 20 times.
- You win the award this year...
and retire next year.
- What are you talking about?
- After winning 20 Grand Awards,
you just quit.
Why would you say
something so awful?
- Just leave.
- No way.
I'm too young to retire yet.
You promised you'd leave
at the age of 60.
- Right.
- I'm not 60 yet.
- You should do that.
- So...
Like I said that day,
it means that Running Man
won the Grand Award.
- That's what I believe. So...
- All right.
you can keep the trophy
for a week each.
- In turn?
- Like a tour.
- Are you serious?
- And...
we will decide
who will inherit the trophy later.
So I'll get it in six weeks.
- You can take it first.
- Can I go first?
I'll be the last one to go.
You also won the Best Couple Award
with Jong Kook.
That's right.
- That's amazing.
- That's true.
(The Grand Award Duo won
the Best Couple Award together.)
Yoo Jae Suk and Kim Jong Kook.
Congratulations.
(Their sweet and brutal chemistry
was finally recognized by SBS.)
(Lifting)
- It finally paid off.
- Seriously, I...
- I didn't see this coming.
- This is something new to me.
- I was surprised.
- Have you won...
- the Best Couple Award before?
- What?
- The Best Couple Award.
- No.
- No?
- It was his first time.
- I won the Best Rookie Award...
- He's like Messi.
- He wins all kinds of awards.
- You're so greedy.
- You're Messi.
- My gosh.
One thing came to another,
and I ended up...
winning all the awards.
Now you need to win
the Son and Daughter of SBS Award.
- No.
- That's the only thing left.
I was really surprised.
The Son and Daughter of SBS Award?
Rather than
the Son and Daughter of SBS Award...
I want to win...
- the Best Couple Award with Ji Hyo.
- I want it too.
- What are you doing?
- What is she doing? Hey.
- The Best Couple Award.
- That's not...
- how you win the Best Couple Award.
- Not that kind of couple.
It shouldn't be
so contrived like that.
You should show your affection
in a natural way.
- Jong Kook and I...
- Hey.
Do you think you two look natural?
- Of course, we do.
- We're natural.
- We look natural.
- We really mean it.
- He's Messi.
- To celebrate the New Year,
we prepared a new race
with a fresh heart.
It's called Running Man Outing Race.
Running Man Outing.
The members of Running Man
will spend a whole day together.
It's like the old TV show,
"Family Outing."
- That's what Jong Kook and I did.
- Right.
It was a wild outdoor variety show.
Actually, Running Man is
a kind of outdoor variety show,
but Seok Sam has led
a sheltered life.
I haven't done this for a long time.
He isn't the type of person
who burns firewood.
Look at the size of my bag.
The size of my bag shows
that I don't know anything.
Those who did "Family Outing"...
- They are different.
- You might wonder...
why we'd need so much stuff
for an overnight trip.
- What's in it?
- But we brought...
a lot of thick clothes just in case.
- You have thick clothes in it?
- Yes.
You know what?
Do you know why I've been
in this field for 30 years?
- Why?
- I manage things...
so we won't have to stay outdoors.
We just need to win games.
- I don't think that's it.
- No?
- Isn't it like that?
- We don't know it yet.
- We're not playing games.
- Isn't it like the other TV show?
I didn't know...
Are you talking about things
like Sleeping Indoors or Outdoors?
- It's not like that.
- No?
(Stay tuned in.)
Since Se Chan is
joining us a little late,
we invited a guest
who's like a family member.
- Our family?
- A family member.
A guest who's like family?
- Family?
- Family.
A guest who's like family?
There's Long Legs.
- Hey, you're here.
- Come here.
- You've come a long way.
- We raised you.
- Right. You...
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Seriously.
It's true that he's like family.
- What?
- Like family.
- "What?"
- It's begun already.
- Just come here.
- I mean...
- That's how they introduced you.
- Come here.
- That's what they said.
- Hey, you...
- Gosh.
- Come here.
Now that you've got some money,
you're wearing expensive clothes.
- Hey, this is a luxury brand.
- This is expensive.
You're wearing designer clothes.
Don't wear it.
This doesn't suit our show.
I wear it only when I come here.
You will burn firewood later.
- You'll get holes in that.
- It will get ruined.
- It will get holes.
- You'll be chopping wood later.
I'll buy another one.
You didn't watch "Family Outing."
You'll get holes in your clothes.
We will make a fire in a fireplace.
- You'll make the fire.
- I can do anything...
as long as it's for Running Man.
By the way, you're...
Jong Kook, why are you
looking at him like that?
I think I've seen that look before.
- I have something to tell you.
- What?
Seriously... It's been...
- ten years since my debut.
- Okay.
It was my first time attending
the awards ceremonies this year.
You mean yesterday?
He came to the SBS Entertainment
Awards as a presenter.
- Right.
- And the first ceremony I joined...
was the SBS Entertainment Awards.
- So I went to present the award.
- And?
I went on stage to present
the award feeling happy.
- I danced as I showed up.
- Okay.
And the day before the ceremony,
I called Jong Kook...
to talk about Gym Jong Kook.
We had a talk the previous day,
so I...
The thing is... What was that?
- What are you trying to say?
- What is he saying?
- Hang on.
- What's with you?
- Let me finish.
- We already give you a chance.
- What I'm saying is...
- You had your chance.
- Hang on.
- You had your chance to talk.
(What Woo Jae is
trying to say is...)
(He showed up feeling all excited,)
(but his mind went blank
when he saw Jong Kook.)
So we booked a place
to stay tonight.
You'll get to the place in a van.
- Okay.
- All right.
Then you should've told Woo Jae
to come to the place.
- Just to say this.
- For the opening.
"Come to Yeouido."
He could've joined us
at the place instead.
He didn't have to come
all the way here.
- He needed to say hello.
- I see.
Let's go, Woo Jae.
Go and buy us some bread.
What I want to say is...
- Let's just go.
- Enough. Stop talking.
- So I went on stage.
Just go.
It's nice to have Woo Jae here.
- I like Woo Jae a lot.
- When Woo Jae is here...
It feels like we have
someone to rely on.
(Now they give him
a sincere welcome.)
But it's not like...
you're just happy to see me.
- I'm happy to see you.
- Okay.
What I like about Woo Jae is...
It's not like
I know a lot of models, but...
How should I put this?
Even when he's around,
I don't feel so small.
- I feel confident.
- Right.
- When Woo Jae is here...
- For some reason...
It's like...
That's subtle.
- I mean, I feel comfortable.
- He makes me confident.
Right.
- It's not like he's superior.
- I mean...
- I feel comfortable around him.
- I don't believe this.
He's like a bad example
of a good-looking model.
- Seriously... I mean...
- Where's the bread?
- What?
Over there.
I have to make sure.
That's what Se Chan does.
Actually,
she thinks of Se Chan
as her boyfriend.
- I miss Se Chan.
- When she's tired,
she says she misses Se Chan.
- She's really funny.
- And Se Chan...
I miss Se Chan.
- Actually, Se Chan is...
- He's thoughtful.
Unlike how he looks...
Why would you mention his looks?
Anyway, Se Chan is not
like how he looks.
- Se Chan is unbelievable.
- He's modest.
- I know.
- He's popular.
- And he has high standards.
- Women find him attractive.
- Right.
- It's crazy.
- Se Chan is...
- He's really attractive.
- I get that a lot.
- It's important...
It's important to have
your own charms.
A lot of people said
that I was attractive.
You were even good-looking before.
- Right. I really was.
- You were charming.
- I was kind of lovely.
- Right.
And you're funny.
And you're sophisticated.
- I have my own charms.
- Haha was...
He was handsome when he was Z-KIRI.
Why can't you say anything
at a time like this?
I was going to say something.
- He was just...
- Why can't you say anything?
He was just... Gosh.
(Speechless)
Before he became popular,
he was a mess.
(Before he became popular,
he was a mess.)
- Seriously, he was...
- Was he lonely?
He was totally lonely.
You know, I've known
Suk Jin for a long time.
He was like...
When women saw him...
It's not like women liked him a lot.
- He kept talking until it worked.
- Until they liked him.
- He and I...
- He never stopped talking.
- We just kept talking.
- Actually,
he's the type of person
who could be popular in the 1990s.
Suk Jin wore a striped shirt
and white pants, right?
- Exactly. You know that, right?
- It looks good on you.
- I saw you at a nightclub.
- Right.
He looks sophisticated,
even during that time.
- I saw him.
- Right.
My waiter served your table too.
- Really?
- So I saw you.
I saw Jae Suk
open the door and shout,
"I picked up some girls!"
- Are you serious?
- That never happened.
Do you think I'd do that?
That's not what I'd do.
(While they have a friendly talk
in the New Year,)
What was really funny was...
(they arrive at a snowy village
in Yangpyeong.)
Let's go in.
Let's go.
- This is nice.
- All right.
- This looks good.
- It's been a long time.
I like the smell of firewood.
- Let's go in.
- This is a sunny place.
This is very nice.
Come here.
So there's no mission.
We just stay here.
- This is...
- Okay.
- My bag is...
- Gosh.
Gosh.
The front yard is still
covered with snow.
Woo Jae, you should
shovel the snow later.
This is nice.
- Woo Jae.
- Yes.
(Leaping)
You should shovel the snow.
(She starts running around.)
She's excited to see the snow.
(It's a disease that she wants
to crunch through the snow.)
- She seems excited.
- That's...
You know So Min, right?
She will get exhausted soon.
"Jae Suk, I'm so tired."
- This is really nice.
- My gosh.
- We have this thing.
- What?
This one doesn't work.
- No. Let me try. This is...
- That doesn't work.
- We have a snowman "machine."
- I can't make snowballs.
- It's done.
- So it works.
I did it.
(She makes a snowman
with childhood innocence.)
- Yes! I did it.
- It's a snowman.
Come on, Suk Jin.
- We should get a fire going.
- When people...
come to a place like this,
do they usually do this?
- Isn't this unnatural?
- What?
Making snowmen.
- I think this is natural.
- It was here.
- I saw it here.
- Do we do this?
- Of course.
- It fell over.
My boots finally get to shine.
- Hey.
- Gosh.
(He's wearing his favorite boots.)
This place is nice.
- My goodness.
- What?
- What do we do?
- Look at this.
We have sweet potatoes
and corn here to cook up.
This is really nice.
- It's so clean.
- This is nice.
- It looks warm in here.
- It's perfect.
(The members are impressed
by the kitchen.)
This is really nice.
- Woo Jae.
- Yes.
Hey, guys. Scoop some soup.
(This place is where
Woo Jae and Seok Sam will work.)
- Look at this!
- This is really good.
We will sleep in here.
Where do we sleep?
- This is where we sleep.
- It looks pretty.
- The room is nice.
- It's good. It's so cozy.
It must be warm.
Clapping your hands
(This is where they will have fun
and sleep together.)
This is really nice.
This is nice.
It's nice here.
- No way. What's this?
- This place is great.
- This place...
- It's nice and clean.
- What's this room?
- Inside, it's...
- It's a modern setup.
- It's crazy.
- Really?
- Exactly.
This place is amazing.
It's what you'd find at a hotel.
Take a look.
- Gosh.
- What...
(Crash)
Woo Jae, my suitcase!
I bet you did that on purpose.
(The paper doll got blown away
along with the suitcases.)
- He wanted that to happen.
- Woo Jae, seriously?
Hey!
Don't force things.
You made it seem too obvious.
- Did he do something funny?
- Yes.
Those of you who haven't been on
"Family Outing" wouldn't know.
- I don't.
- But take your suitcases in first.
- Woo Jae, take them inside.
- Where?
- The girls and boys...
- This room must be for sleeping.
- Will we be in the same room?
- Probably in separate rooms.
- Only this one will be warm though.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Got it.
- In the same room?
- On "Family Outing,"
everyone bunked together.
- Suk Jin.
- Do we only get one room?
I doubt sleep will come to me.
- You'll be knocked out.
- I bet someone will snore.
- We should get some sleep.
- Who's a snorer?
- Me.
- Probably everyone.
Some will snore
and some will grit their teeth.
- And some will talk in their sleep.
- I snore severely when I'm tired.
Like I informed you earlier,
this is the Running Man Outing Race.
Cameras will film you
for 24 hours...
- while you have fun at this house.
- For 24 hours?
The current time is 11 a.m.,
so the race will end
tomorrow at 11 a.m.
Really?
So that you receive good energy...
as we begin 2023,
the Year of the Black Rabbit,
we have prepared
a gold rabbit of 3.75g.
- Really?
- A rabbit?
On the wheel, your names...
will take up a space
following a specific rule.
The wheel will be spun tomorrow.
The chosen three people
will win the gold.
We must be playing games
or something.
Being 1 out of 3 is doable.
- I agree.
- I think so too.
The wheel will be spun three times.
However,
one can be chosen three times...
- and win all the gold.
- Really?
No way. Don't get your hopes up
because I won't be sharing...
- if the gold ends up as mine.
- I'm excited about this.
Since you're here, for 24 hours,
you will be cooking for yourselves.
However, you must make
what was chosen in advance.
- We don't get to choose.
- Lunch and dinner for today...
and breakfast for tomorrow.
For lunch, you will make
a simple bowl of janchi guksu.
In what world
is janchi guksu a simple dish?
- It's actually easy.
- It's easy to make.
- All we need is anchovy broth.
- It's easier than you think.
- We'll do it in no time.
- I'll take charge.
It's even better with some ramyeon.
- The noodles don't work.
- We need to make...
- pickled radish.
- Hear me out.
- Janchi guksu with ramyeon.
- But I want spicy fish stew.
- I bet you haven't had it together.
- I haven't.
We need pickled radish
to have with janchi guksu.
For dinner, you will have
pork belly and budaejjigae.
- That stew is my favorite.
- Budaejjigae...
- It's the best.
- What a bummer.
Must we make it though?
Yes, you must also build
a stove too.
- Just mix everything in.
- It's not that hard.
Shouldn't we be making
chueotang at least?
Would you like to make that?
On "Family Outing,"
I caught the loach myself...
- and ground it up to make soup.
- Stay put, will you?
- Don't you remember that?
- Gosh.
- You caught the loach yourself?
- Yes.
I can't believe it.
Here we go. It's working.
(It turned out to be true.)
Tomorrow morning,
you will have tteokguk...
- to celebrate the new year.
- Tteokguk's easy.
- I...
- We only need beef bone soup.
It's exhausting.
You're giving us too much work.
- Both So Min and Ji Hyo...
- It's all right.
- are good at cooking though.
- They're good cooks.
I'm terrible at cooking,
- but So Min's good at it.
- So Min's a good cook.
Se Chan is good at cooking,
- but he'll be here at noon.
- Stop talking about him will you?
Are you talking
about your boyfriend?
He's a good cook.
We can get it done too.
- Of course.
- We'll be able to manage.
The ramyeon seasoning
makes everything taste good.
Seriously?
Also, while cooking...
(His blind faith
in ramyeon seasoning...)
(began during his days
on "Family Outing.")
Gosh, it's hot.
What on earth?
(He added ramyeon seasoning
to every dish...)
(which solidified his love
for the sachet.)
You will be shopping
for groceries as well.
- Groceries?
- Yes.
Since you said that So Min
was the best cook among you...
I can't say I'm that good.
Please choose
who you want to go shopping with.
- Me?
- You can count on me.
Are we shopping
just for the janchi guksu...
- or everything else?
- And the budaejjigae.
- Don't forget the ramyeon.
- Ramyeon?
And pork belly.
Get ready to shop
for groceries then...
and choose a partner.
I choose Haha and Woo Jae.
Those staying behind
will build a stove...
- and cook the broth.
- We need a stove.
Jae Suk and Jong Kook,
show us how it's done.
- Sure.
- Do you have money?
- Let's go grocery shopping.
- Let's go.
- Sit up front, Woo Jae.
- Are you in the back?
You and Haha can sit in that row.
We need to remember
to buy onions and zucchini.
- Sausages and spam.
- Right.
- And also bacon.
- Pork, beef, and bacon are needed.
- We need minced meat, kimchi,
- That's right.
- and baked beans.
- Did you know that...
- the recipes vary in regions?
- I like the Uijeongbu style.
They can be different.
One uses a clear broth while...
I like the kind
that adds baked beans.
Let's not make it
too hard on ourselves.
- Beef bone soup and...
- To that, we'll add the tteok.
We also need pepper.
And tteok.
Should we add tofu
in the budaejjigae?
They sell homemade ones around here.
It won't be budaejjigae
without tofu.
- And tofu.
- Homemade tofu?
- Nearby?
- Yes, there's a shop nearby.
We'll get tofu
that has just been made.
Doesn't it sound delicious?
Why don't we eat one?
Must you even ask?
- Homemade tofu?
- That's right.
I love homemade tofu.
I was excited to know that
Se Chan would be cooking for us.
- He's quite the cook.
- He's good at it.
- Se Chan.
- Hey.
- When will you get here?
- Is that Se Chan?
I'll arrive in the evening.
In the evening? We're going
grocery shopping right now.
Do you need anything?
How sweet of her.
There's nothing I need.
Well...
- Se Chan, hey.
- Yes?
So Min must want to be good to you
since Woo Jae's here.
Se Chan, it's Woo Jae.
- Hey, Woo Jae.
- So Min wants you here badly.
- Is that so?
- But only when I'm present.
- Exactly.
- Only when I'm present.
- That's not it. Woo Jae...
- I'm jealous, guys.
- Yes?
- As you know, he's the youngest.
- Love with all your heart.
- Right.
But he hasn't been doing
what the youngest member should do.
In what year did she debut?
- I don't know.
- I debuted 18 years ago.
I've been in the industry
for 18 years.
- Eighteen years?
- Yes.
(He ate a big slice of humble pie.)
How would you like
fried ribs for dinner?
- Fried ribs?
- Yes.
I don't know if the grocery store
would have back ribs.
- Really?
- Right.
(During the short break they took)
In 1, 2, 3.
You can get ripe kimchi
at the supermarket.
- It's good.
- Put that in a pot...
- And just boil it?
- With a huge chunk of pork,
- boil it for two hours.
- That will be good.
If we go on an overnight trip,
we'll buy the pork and...
- I'll make it for you.
- Sure.
Suk Jin, you'll be blown away.
- By what?
- Braised kimchi with back ribs.
That sounds delicious.
(Se Chan promised
to blow them away.)
Call me once you get there.
Sure.
Would they have back ribs though?
- Se Chan offered to fry them.
- But...
First...
We should stack these first.
- We should put gloves on.
- How should it be done?
Where should we build the stove?
Let's start with a single layer.
There's a lot to do
at places like this.
Why is there so much to do?
This is why I love
staying in hotels.
Right?
Rotate them at an angle
so that there's room for air.
Doesn't air need to flow?
Yes, that's why we need
an opening too.
Good.
We never made a stove
on "Family Outing" though.
- This wasn't our job.
- I can't believe we're making one.
We can always cook...
- on a portable gas stove.
- Exactly.
- Why must we be primitive?
- Why must we cook on a fire?
- There are nice stoves out there.
- This is such a cliche.
A cliche in variety shows.
Unbelievable.
Make some room between the blocks.
That's the issue we have though.
- Make some room like so.
- We do it all while complaining.
Everything we must do
is a task on its own.
- One would think we'd give up.
- Working in silence is no fun.
- Like us...
- Jae Suk.
- Coming.
- Yes?
- One must complain.
- Why are you making another one?
Gosh, thanks.
- What are you making?
- We were told to make two stoves.
Two stoves?
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Hold on a second.
We can make the stew
after grilling the meat.
We can cook the rice on a gas stove.
But rice tastes better
when cooked in a big iron pot.
- A big iron pot?
- Hyung In.
Do you cook rice at home
in a big iron pot?
- I bet she doesn't.
- Jae Suk, here.
Right.
Why are you only bringing me
two at a time?
They aren't that heavy, you know.
- Here are four.
- Gosh.
(He delivers four bricks this time.)
(Humming)
He's pretending to be happy.
- I'm trying to get myself excited.
- Come on.
There was nothing natural about it.
- Don't pretend to be happy.
- This is a first for him,
- so it's not fun for him.
- I'm trying to get myself excited.
Those watching are the ones
that should be having fun.
Our time on "Family Outing"
wasn't all for nothing.
There's something else
other than the pot.
Wait. The pot should fit in that.
It won't fit.
- Where?
- Hey.
- The pot...
- What's wrong?
(Seok Sam claims
that the pot won't fit.)
It only has to cover the hole.
I doubt it's big enough.
Won't it sit on the stove?
(Groaning)
Take it, will you?
- Let's lift it together.
- All right. Hold it here.
The pot has to fit on this?
It should,
but I doubt it's big enough.
The upper layer should be removed.
Hold on a second. No, it'll fit.
It'll fit. There you go.
Lift it up again.
- That's good enough.
- We're good.
I see your time on "Family Outing"
wasn't for nothing.
- We're experts, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
It has enough holes
for air to flow as well.
Gosh, it didn't even take long.
- We're experts.
- Make it bigger.
- Here.
- It doesn't even take us that long.
- Jong Kook and I...
- Right.
It's nice to have people
who have done this before.
- That's a good bottom layer.
- Should we light a fire, then?
- Hold on a second.
- There are briquettes here.
We have a torch, briquettes,
and everything else we need.
This is nice.
- We experts can tell by the sound.
- Yes.
- You call yourself an expert?
- It's dry enough.
It burns well when it's dry.
Or else, it smokes a lot.
We should put this
on top of the briquettes, right?
- Give me that. We can use a torch.
- Briquettes? Right.
Right. Give me the torch.
But we don't have gas.
I know where it is.
- We don't have gas?
- We have a torch here...
- Hey.
- What are you talking about?
- Anyone from "Family Outing"...
- But gas...
- knows where it would be.
- But we don't have gas.
Do we have gas?
He really is an expert.
He knows where to find stuff.
- Of course.
- He found it.
- We've done it on "Family Outing."
- He knows everything.
- I couldn't have found it.
- I know.
- We have two experts here.
- It's easy as they have experience.
This is so great.
Everything is going so smoothly.
- It's great.
- It's easy, Suk Jin.
Maybe you should adjust it.
Okay, it's done. Go ahead.
- My, look at that.
- Okay.
(Surprised)
Suk Jin, don't play with fire.
You'll pee yourself in your sleep.
Only those with a healthy prostate
like us should do this.
- Right. A healthy prostate.
- Hey.
- You should be able to control it.
- You need a healthy prostate.
- Yes.
- Come on.
- Don't do anything with fire.
It's like concrete.
- Never play with fire.
- My prostate is healthy.
Suk Jin had to go to the restroom
several times during the ceremony.
- You need a healthy prostate.
- Absolutely.
It's fun to make a fire, you know.
- Really?
- It's really fun.
What's so fun about it?
You have to pay attention
to keep the fire burning.
It feels like raising a child.
That's how it feels.
It's not different from
setting paper on fire.
No, you're wrong. It's different.
(But the firewood
isn't catching on fire.)
Is it supposed to be upside down?
The bottom part catches fire fast.
- We have a fan, Jae Suk.
- Let's put some paper under it.
- And on top of it...
- Right. Do that.
- Crumple a few sheets for me.
- Okay.
You can just throw the newspaper
in it.
- No, that's not how it works.
- No. That won't help.
We know this from our experience
on "Family Outing."
- My goodness.
- Yes, that's good. Okay.
- Good. That's enough.
- Hey.
You keep bragging about
your experience from the show.
- Make sure there's enough air.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- Suk Jin, come here.
Suk Jin, come and help me
crumple the paper.
You don't have to do that.
Just tear it and put it in here.
- No. It doesn't work like that.
- No, Suk Jin.
- Just tear it and put it in here.
- No.
(It doesn't work like that.)
- It still catches fire.
- If you don't crumple it,
- it doesn't help to start the fire.
- What role does kindling play?
As it burns, the fire comes upward.
This doesn't help do anything!
- Oh, I see.
- Hey, wait.
- Put the cauldron on here now.
- You use kindling... Wait. Stop it.
- Jae Suk, it's crazy in there.
- Yes?
- Oh, no. This is bad.
- You should've crumpled it.
- This is why you shouldn't do this.
- Hang on.
How about we cover it with this?
No.
Bring the cauldron and put it on.
(They start fanning the fire.)
- My gosh. I can't believe...
- Oh, man.
In front of you... Ji Hyo.
- I knew it. Why did you...
- I'm sorry.
Ji Hyo, bring the cauldron.
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
- I told you not to do that.
(Seok Sam's newspaper flower bloomed
in an instant.)
- It's snowing! Look at the snow!
- Please don't do that.
(The smoky snowflakes)
- Stop fanning!
- Hey, it's snowing.
(Heavy snow falls unexpectedly.)
- I told you not to do that.
- Give me that, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, give me that.
- It's snowing!
- If this keeps up,
the ground will get all sooty.
- Why did you fan the fire?
- Jong Kook, move aside.
- I put a lot of firewood here too.
- Hey, wait.
- We shouldn't put it on there yet.
- No, we should do it now.
(Jae Suk moves the cauldron
to solve the problem.)
We shouldn't keep it empty
on the fire. Let's add some water.
Seok Sam, can you bring some water?
Water? I can use this basin.
I'll do it.
And then...
(Let me see.)
I met Ji Hyo for the first time
when she came on "Family Outing."
You're right. That's when I met you
for the first time.
Oh, I don't have to take this
over there.
(Grunting)
(He's having a 1-on-1 battle
against the hose.)
(It's not an easy opponent for him.)
What is Suk Jin doing?
How do I do this?
Ji Hyo,
you shouldn't do it halfheartedly.
- Sorry. I was looking at Suk Jin.
- Ji Hyo.
What is Seok Sam doing?
(Seok Sam catches everyone's eye.)
- Ji Hyo, keep doing it.
- Okay, Jae Suk.
We have to split the firewood
to make it burn well.
Hey, can you... The lid...
Can you open the lid for me, Ji Hyo?
- We shouldn't keep it empty.
- We shouldn't do that.
(It took him ten minutes
to bring water.)
- It's okay as we have butane gas.
- It smells bad.
Why did you fill only a third
of the basin?
We just need to keep the cauldron
from being empty.
- It's not easy starting a fire.
- It's burning well.
- It's a lot of work, Jae Suk.
- Indeed.
It must be hard for our cameramen.
The smoke is going toward them.
Look at them.
They don't care about it.
The smoke is going that way,
not toward us.
That's a relief though.
- What did you say?
- Suk Jin.
- Why did you go back on your word?
- Which one did you mean?
How many personalities do you have?
Now, I'm regretting what I said.
It's burning well.
I did a great job.
Nice. You made a proper fire.
(The strong one finished
starting a fire.)
- Right?
- Yes.
My, this is nice, Suk Jin.
Look at that.
You would have a blast if you were
alone with your girlfriend.
Of course, I would have so much fun.
- Right?
- Yes, of course.
Your girlfriend would be sitting
over there, right?
- Reading a book.
- She'd be sitting on my lap.
(Chuckling)
He's such a sweet guy,
but he's still single.
- He's so sweet but lives alone.
- Oh, man.
- I pictured it, and it was gross.
- Gosh.
I'd let my girlfriend sit on my lap
the whole time. Don't be ridiculous.
- Really? But be careful.
- Yes.
- If you marry her,
you'd have to keep letting her
sit on your lap.
- That won't be a problem.
- Can you do that?
- Of course.
- It'd be exhausting.
- That's why I work out.
- I'm impressed.
He works out hard so that he can let
his girlfriend sit on his lap.
- That's romantic.
- Of course.
It's very comfortable.
Why don't you try sitting on my lap?
No, I'll pass.
- Woo Jae, take this shopping bag.
- Yes?
- Here's our shopping bag.
- Give it to me.
- Then first...
- Let's go.
- Well... Let's eat something.
- I'll carry it.
- Sorry?
- What shall we eat?
(They plan to have snacks
before shopping.)
I heard there were
a lot of famous places here.
- Haha. That sikhye looks good.
- Yes?
- Oh, my. It looks good.
- Shall we buy some?
- Let's pick it up on our way back.
- Let's do that...
- since it's heavy.
- How much money can we spend?
- As much money as we want.
- No limit?
- Shall we buy everything?
- Let's buy everything we want.
I can't sleep
without a particular type of pillow.
They sell blankets too.
- Se Chan said to buy pork belly...
- Yes?
- and another part...
- We should buy pork belly.
- Meat.
- Pork belly and minced meat.
- He told me to buy minced meat too.
- Yes. Let's buy a lot of meat. Hey.
How about
we eat homemade tofu first?
- Shall we? We can buy meat later.
- Shall we eat first?
- Let's eat first.
- And back ribs.
- How much do we need?
- I expected to go to a supermarket.
There's a supermarket too
as far as I know.
There's a supermarket too.
- Haha, look at those donuts.
- Hello.
- It must be a famous place.
- It's famous.
- Those dumplings look so tasty.
- Let's try some.
- It looks good. Oh, croquettes.
- Hello.
- Let's buy some twisted donuts.
What shall we buy?
Can we get...
- Hello.
- nine twisted donuts...
and dumplings...
Let's not buy any dumplings
since we have to cook.
- Okay. Then can we get nine...
- Our dumplings are the best.
- Pardon?
- Dumplings are our specialty.
- Please give us dumplings too.
- Okay.
(He ordered dumplings too
without thinking.)
- Half and half, please.
- Yes, half and half, please.
Can I have one of these, Haha?
- Just one croquette?
- Sure. Go ahead.
Eat whatever you can eat here.
Excuse me. Can I have one croquette?
Then I'll have salty and sweet food.
Can I have one chapsal donut?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Would you like
one with red bean paste?
Yes, of course.
- It's so good.
- Would you like sugar over it?
Of course, I'd like that.
- Thank you. Oh, my.
- Goodbye.
- It looks so good.
- It looks good, indeed.
How does it taste, Haha?
Is it good?
Is it sweet?
It's so chewy and nice.
Try it. Is it good?
(Meanwhile, the small eater doesn't
look like he's enjoying the food.)
- It's chewy and nice.
- I like the oily smell of a market.
- My, look at those dumplings.
- Look at the dumplings.
Oh, my. They look so tasty.
- It looks so good.
- Can I try one?
- Since we use fresh vegetables,
- Thank you.
the vegetables are still crisp.
It's too hot.
Look at this. It's full of filling.
It has a texture that I've never
tried before. I'm not lying.
How can a steamed dumpling have
a crunchy texture like this?
I swear. I'm not lying.
I swear on three generations
of my family. It's crunchy.
- Can I try one with kimchi too?
- Sure.
- It's really good.
- I'm impressed.
Was this originally
a dumpling place?
Was it changed to a donut place?
You crave salty food after eating
sweet food, and vice versa. Amazing.
I could stand here all night long,
eating everything they make.
- It's so good.
- Are we doing a product placement?
- Sorry? No.
(Haha's excessive reaction made him
think it was a product placement.)
- It's really tasty.
- I'm eating this dumpling... Hey.
- You're just like my second son.
- Are you still eating that?
- Who?
- You.
- You're full, right?
- My son is a reluctant eater too.
It's really good.
- You mean, So Wool?
- Yes.
I see that it's a bad idea
to wear an expensive jacket.
- Exactly.
- Because of sparks from the fire.
It's really good.
It's burning well.
You don't have to worry about it.
You've done a great job
in raising your child.
Suk Jin, you should keep paying
attention to the fire.
It's like raising a child.
You have to keep an eye on it
even when it's burning.
- You can leave it for a while.
- No. I just told you.
You have to keep watching it.
It's burning well by itself.
What's wrong with you?
- It's not like that.
- It's burning well.
It's so good.
(But he can't seem to leave the fire
like a helicopter parent.)
- It's burning so well.
- Is everything going well here?
It makes me happy.
- Listening to the crackling sound,
- Right. I like that sound.
- I can zone out while watching it.
- Exactly.
It's amazing.
Now, we should start making broth.
Where is it? Where is the fridge?
Oh, the fridge...
- The fridge is in there.
- Where?
- I see sardines and anchovy there.
- I found sardine.
- Give me sardine and anchovy.
- Sardine and anchovy.
Let's make broth with those.
- Hold on.
- We should pour some more water.
We should pour some more water.
- Oh, my. The water is boiling.
- My, look at that.
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
(Suk Jin saw something
in the water.)
- Don't dump the water there.
- Where else should I dump it?
- It hurts my eyes. Where else?
- The ground will freeze.
- No, it won't.
- Suk Jin, trust me.
- Suk Jin, the ground will freeze.
- You shouldn't dump it there.
- It'll freeze the ground. Stop it.
I can't believe him.
If you pour water there,
the ground will freeze. Stop it.
- It'll freeze?
- Of course.
Gosh. Then where...
Darn it. That's hot.
It's too hot. Darn.
Then should I dump it over there?
He's only been on variety shows
filmed in a studio.
There's nothing we can do.
It's too late to teach him.
(He has 31 years of experience,
but still has a lot to learn.)
- How many times should I do this?
- Suk Jin.
- When we were on "Family Outing,"
- You might scoop out all of it.
- we ate food with dirt in it.
- That's right.
- It's all natural.
- The water looks clear, indeed.
- Can we drink this as it is?
- He's scooping out all the water.
- It's not like that.
- You shouldn't do that.
- Look. There's dirt in the water.
- That's okay. It won't kill you.
- It's okay.
I'm telling you,
the cauldron is not clean enough.
I said it won't kill you.
Suk Jin, you...
Let's just eat out.
(He's tired of arguing.)
It's really hard to shoot
a show like "Family Outing."
- A show like "Family Outing?"
- When you watched it at home...
I often said,
"They get paid for having fun."
- Exactly.
- But there's a lot of work to do.
- That's enough.
- We shouldn't waste the fire.
- I'll put a cauldron on it.
- Right. It's burning well.
Hey, let's wash it first.
- What do you mean?
- The cauldron.
- We should wash it first.
- Okay.
Shall we fill it with water
and move it there?
Let's carry it together.
Fill it with water first.
Suk Jin,
from this angle, you look...
Oh, my. You look like...
(A strong flow)
From this angle, you look like...
(He looks like a tough guy.)
- My gosh.
- What do you mean?
- From this angle, you look like...
- I know.
- Suk Jin...
- Do I look incredible?
- The flow can't be that strong.
- Right.
Suk Jin, you look incredible.
(The middle-aged man shows off
his health using the hose water.)
- Isn't this enough? It's too much.
- Right. It's enough.
I'll add the ingredients
for the broth.
Where?
- In that cauldron.
- Oh, we have the ingredients.
(Ji Hyo's broth recipe)
(Add sardines and anchovies together
to make a rich flavor.)
- Okay.
- I rinsed it. It'll be okay, right?
- It's okay. We'll boil it anyway.
- Right?
- Put it in.
- Okay. I'll put it in.
Yes. It's okay.
- Good.
- Where's the lid?
My, it's burning so well.
Whose coffee is this?
It's mine, Suk Jin.
She put this...
Oh, no. Hey, Ji Hyo.
Did you put in
the whole bag of sardines?
Yes, I put all of it in. Why?
(Cheerful)
(Earlier on)
(She put in
the whole bag of sardines...)
(and all of the anchovies they had.)
(No wonder why
the pouches looked so big.)
We'll add ramyeon seasoning anyway.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Don't worry.
- We'll add ramyeon seasoning later.
- Good job.
That's not the point.
- You did well.
- We'll add ramyeon seasoning later.
That's not the point.
- We'll eat them all anyway.
- Hey.
- It's okay as long as it's tasty.
- That was a big bag.
- We can even use plain water.
- Did you put the whole bag?
- It doesn't matter.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
Two bags that are this big are
enough for six months.
For six months.
- We have to take one out.
- We can just eat it as it is.
- Let's just eat it as it is.
- It's okay as long as it's tasty.
- Will you open up a restaurant?
- I mean...
- No. It's okay, right, Jae Suk?
- You know what I mean.
Ji Hyo,
I see that you were not joking.
- I wasn't joking.
- You really are bad at cooking.
- I really am bad at cooking.
- You weren't joking.
- I was so surprised.
- I mean...
- We can still enjoy the food.
- You're right.
- We can just add ramyeon seasoning.
- Ji Hyo.
Did you put the sardines
and anchovies in separate bags?
Or did you mix them
and put them in two bags?
- I put them in separate bags.
- You brat.
- Which one should we take out?
- You did well.
I can't decide.
- Why should we take one out?
- We should use...
You need to mix them
if you want the broth to taste good.
But we have to take out one of them.
- Should we take the sardines out?
- No, don't take out any of them.
Since we already put them in,
take the anchovies out.
And put them in the other cauldron.
Wait. Which bag has sardines in it?
This one must be it.
- Open the lid. I'll move it there.
- Listen to me.
Okay.
Why didn't we come up with this idea
when we were on "Family Outing?"
(The members will enjoy
the rich taste of each.)
- It's nice. Jong Kook.
- Oh, dear.
- Yes?
- Wear these. Your eyes won't burn.
- Those remind me of Turbo.
- My eyes are burning.
- Try them on.
- It's warm.
- Gosh. My eyes are burning.
- This is nice.
- Oh, it really works.
- Your eyes won't hurt anymore.
- Aren't you a member of Turbo?
- Exactly.
(Turbo is back.)
Aren't you a member of Turbo?
- Turbo.
- My gosh.
The water started boiling.
I think it's boiling now.
It's totally boiling.
Good.
- Shouldn't we take the lid off?
- Why...
Why are you fanning
the inside of it, Ji Hyo?
(She's fanning the cauldron
for a mysterious reason.)
- Ji Hyo, why are you doing that?
- Why are you doing that?
- Why are you fanning it?
- I want to see inside,
but I can't see anything.
- I can smell it.
- Oh, to see inside?
- I see.
- I can smell the scent of anchovy.
Of course, you can smell it.
She put in the whole bag.
- It'd be weird if you can't.
- Ji Hyo, it has a strong scent.
If we boil it for too long,
- it might taste bitter.
- That's right.
The fire is amazing.
Look at the fire. I'm impressed.
- But it smells good.
- We could cook a chicken here.
- Shall we cook some sweet potatoes?
- No.
Hey, prepare some sweet potatoes.
- Shall we cook some?
- Yes, let's do that.
Wrap some sweet potatoes in foil.
- Look at these sweet potatoes.
- Suk Jin.
- They look yummy.
- You should wrap them in foil.
- Sorry?
- Aluminum foil.
That's not necessary.
We can just dust it off.
- That won't work.
- No.
- You'll burn them.
- Darn it.
- I said it wasn't the right way.
- You'll burn them.
- Really?
- You should wrap them in foil.
Don't they just eat it
while getting all sooty...
- when you cook it in a fire?
- You're from Seoul.
I'll cut it for you.
Earlier,
he complained
that the cauldron was dirty.
But he's willing to eat it
while getting all sooty?
Does foil have
a front and back side?
I can just put them in there, right?
Can I put them anywhere?
- What are you putting in there?
- The sweet potatoes.
Suk Jin put the sweet potatoes
over it like cooking pork belly.
- What's wrong with him?
- He drives me crazy.
Come on, Suk Jin.
- Look. He put them on the top.
- You shouldn't do that.
- You should've put them under it.
- They'll burn.
You should've put them
in the corner like this.
- But...
- Even I know that much.
They've all scorched already.
- But I wrapped them in foil.
- I'll show you.
- You put it in the corner.
- Really?
You place them at the bottom
by the flame like this.
Roasted sweet potatoes will be
so delicious, right?
(They must be feeling
a little hungry now.)
By the way,
the broth might boil down.
Shall I try calling them?
What's taking them so long?
Suk Jin, call So Min right now.
(They haven't heard
from the Grocery Team.)
- Could they be eating something?
- My gosh. So Min, that brat.
I'm sure they're having some snacks
at the market.
That's possible.
They're not even picking up.
- That's a rice cake shop.
- It's a rice cake shop.
- Oh, my. Hello.
- Hello.
- That jeolpyeon looks so tasty.
- This must be a famous shop.
This is a famous shop, right?
A lot of celebrities have come here.
- We'd like to buy some rice cakes.
- We're about to pull it out.
- Pull it out?
- Yes.
You can watch
how we pull out garaetteok.
- Will you show us?
- You can try it too.
Are you the director?
(Are you the director?)
I see there's another camera here.
Since celebrities are here,
I want to film you all.
- Can we go in there?
- You speak like a director.
My gosh.
I'm excited.
(They will watch
how rice cakes are made.)
This is fascinating.
I've never seen this before.
- Oh, my.
(Freshly made rice cakes)
It's fascinating.
It looks good.
- That's baekseolgi.
- If you...
- Is a small piece of it baekseolgi?
- No.
- No?
- You make tteokguk...
with thin slices of that.
Oh, that's not baekseolgi.
Ma'am, you look so busy.
- She's filming us...
- Put it down for a while.
while making rice cakes.
I'm the busiest person in this shop.
Even Chan Hee can't do that.
- My, look at this. It's coming out.
- It's coming out.
That's awesome. Look at that.
I'm getting so excited.
That's interesting.
Are you two siblings?
- Yes.
- She's my older sister.
(The two of them are siblings.)
How long have you been
working together?
For about ten years.
- It's been over ten years.
- I see.
How long have you been
a camera operator?
- Today is my first day.
- I see.
She looks like a veteran.
(Yangpyeon Kang Chan Hee is modest.)
- The color changes.
- Can we try some?
Yes, just a little.
Thank you so much.
Two pieces would be enough.
Oh, my. Woo Jae, pick a piece.
- It's too hot.
Gosh, it's too hot.
Enjoy.
(Awesome)
Thank you.
- Woo Jae, why aren't you eating?
- I'm touched.
- Eat some more.
- It's amazingly good.
- Finish it.
- Can you...
Can you tell us why you're touched?
What about the rice cake
makes you feel that way?
- I'm curious.
- It's...
I think this is his first time
trying rice cake.
You know a pure taste, right?
What have you been eating?
- Do you know what pure taste is?
- Right.
Jong Kook, stop adding firewood.
It's because... You know...
Are you trying to melt the cauldron?
No.
- It's just...
- That's enough.
- You're wasting our firewood.
- That's why I asked...
- We should save some for tomorrow.
- I asked earlier...
if that would be enough.
- The firewood...
- I'll have to go gather firewood.
- We won't have enough firewood.
- Jae Suk.
I think
I'll have to go gather firewood.
- I'll go get some more firewood.
- I mean why...
- I'll cut down a tree.
- Look what you've done.
I might meet a fairy while doing so.
- I might meet a fairy there.
- Stop putting it.
- The fire is too strong.
- I mean...
It's because Jong Kook finds it fun.
Yes. It's nice to do it
after a long time.
Why are you putting so much?
Wait. We should boil noodles too.
- The noodles are...
- We should boil noodles too.
- But...
- We should put noodles in,
but the water keeps evaporating.
They're taking forever.
The water is evaporating.
But we should boil noodles.
- We can boil them here.
- Let's boil them separately.
- Here?
- But we don't need to do that now.
Why not?
If we boil them now,
they'll get all soggy.
- Yes. We don't have noodles anyway.
- We just wanted to boil water.
We don't have noodles?
- They went to buy them.
- What's this conversation?
- Hey. They went to get them.
- I mean...
- What are you doing?
- We...
- Why?
- We don't have noodles.
But you're talking
about boiling them.
- What are you talking about?
- They went to buy them.
- We don't have noodles here?
- The guys went to get them.
- That's what we were talking.
We don't have noodles?
I said we should put noodles in,
but the guys weren't coming.
Why were you boiling the broth
if we didn't have noodles?
- I mean...
- We were doing it in advance.
We thought they would come soon.
Why are you boiling the broth
when we don't have noodles?
They should be back in five minutes.
- I know.
- That's why.
- But they're taking too long.
- Detective Kim.
You should go get them.
- Now...
- Go get them.
You should go get those guys.
Go get them. Grab their collars.
I should go get them.
- We should catch them.
- These punks.
- Detective Kim.
- Yes.
(A team to arrest Best Couple
is formed.)
Let's go get them.
- Let's go.
- You should go...
- You should be back quickly.
- to intimidate them.
- We should go get them.
- Wear black.
- You should get them.
- I can wear the goggles, right?
Yes.
- Wait. Let's go.
- I'll wear them.
- This won't do. Go get them.
- Let's go get them.
- Give me a towel.
- I'm so upset.
I'll go get them.
- Ji Hyo, keep an eye on it.
- Yes.
- I'm so mad.
- Detective Kim can intimidate them.
Right.
- Let's go.
- Grab their collars.
- I'll go and grab their collars.
- Let's go.
Let's go get them.
With an axe?
- Let's go.
- Go get them.
- These punks...
- See you later.
- Let's go, Jae Suk.
- See you.
These guys are slacking.
- We got a perfect car for a chase.
- This is nice.
- Let's go, Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- With a small car...
- Right? Something like a Pride.
We should go quickly and grab
their nape to drag them back.
Please go.
I'll grab the back of their neck.
- We...
- I'm wearing cotton work gloves.
- Good job.
- I didn't take them off.
I'll pinch Haha's cheeks
and rub some charcoal.
We should catch them
and put them in the backseat.
In the back.
(They're going to put them
in the back over there.)
We should put them in the car
and come back.
Hey. Let's buy clothes.
You need to buy clothes.
No. I don't need it.
- You should get one.
- They only have that kind of style.
- No. You need to buy clothes.
- You should get clothes.
There are many things here.
- Now, the weather is cold...
- There's a photo studio too.
and it's a weekday.
But this downtown...
There's a sushi place too.
This place is so...
- This must be the main street.
- This is the main street.
I understand
why they would go crazy here.
That's Burger King.
Yes. This is definitely downtown.
It's busier than Anyang.
There is a camera.
Can you stop here?
(He found a cameraman on the way!)
- Hold on. These punks...
- These punks...
- When they come out...
- Where are they?
- Don't get off now.
We should catch them
when they're here.
- When they're off guard.
We should get them
when they're off guard.
When they're having fun
knowing nothing.
- This won't do.
- These punks.
(The time is now!)
- Where are they?
- Are they kidding me?
(Two detectives went out
to arrest them.)
This looks warm.
This looks really warm.
(Black pants caught
Detective Kim's eyes.)
Wait, no...
(He's back
on the arresting mission.)
These little...
(He starts searching
a grocery store nearby first.)
- I don't think they're here.
- They're not here.
I think they went somewhere else.
(They didn't even come
to a grocery store yet?)
- They're not here.
Where are they?
(Staff members are here,
but no one is shopping there.)
- Where did they go?
(Staff members are here,
but no one is shopping there.)
Where are they hanging out?
Is Woo Seok doing well?
He's doing well.
I told him I was appearing on
Running Man yesterday.
You did?
- Who is he?
- Byeon Woo Seok. His friend.
He came with Woo Jae last time.
The good-looking one.
- The one with a small face?
- Yes. He's very handsome.
Hey, this place is better.
You're right. We can't help it.
(You always find something better
after getting something.)
This is why we should buy something
after looking around.
- The size is much better.
- This one is funnier. Let's go.
Where are they hanging out?
Did they go to a karaoke?
You said there are ingredients
for the sauce, right? Chili powder.
- At home.
- Hey.
- You little...
- Come here.
- Where did you go?
- Where...
- We've been shopping.
We just put the grocery in the car.
Look at the grocery we got.
- We're so tired.
- Look at the things we got.
- There are so many.
- What did you do?
What have you been doing?
- We got meat.
- Come here. What did you get?
There's nothing. I swear.
- The items are over there.
- We're innocent.
You bought this.
- We didn't. This is a shopping bag.
- It's a shopping bag.
It's a shopping bag.
Where did you go?
This is so unfair.
- We really went to a mill.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk. Look at this.
- What...
- Look at that.
- What is this?
- Come here.
- Look at him. It's him.
- I got nothing for real.
- Come here.
Look at this.
This is for Se Chan.
- What's this rice cake?
- We bought the rice cake.
- Jae Suk, we got fresh rice cake.
- We got the fresh one.
- That's why it took long.
- What?
- We got fresh rice cake and...
- We came to Yangpyeong and...
- Hey.
- Kim Young Chul...
We were boiling the broth
and waiting for you for an hour.
- We were boiling the broth.
- It's all evaporated.
The pot is going to melt.
- We made a fire and...
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- You're making us feel bad.
Hurry up and get in the car.
- We should get tofu.
- They kept asking us to eat.
- You didn't get tofu yet?
- Handmade tofu.
- We should get handmade tofu.
- It's a famous place.
- The handmade tofu... Yes.
- If we get it, we're all good.
- We got twisted bread sticks.
- We got 9.
- For real.
- We got chapsal donuts.
- Why are you smiling?
- The one you like.
Jae Suk.
The dumplings? They're no joke.
- He likes it. What will you get?
- Steamed dumplings.
- Did you eat them?
- There is...
- No, we didn't.
- You ate, right?
- They just gave it to us.
- They gave it to us.
- It was on TV. The rice cake is...
- I'm telling you.
It shines like...
- If you make tteokguk with that...
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- Handmade tofu.
- Let's go, Detective Kim.
Let's go to the handmade tofu place
for now.
- It's no joke.
- But...
- Handmade tofu.
- You guys...
should get it together.
- We were working so hard.
My gosh.
(His heart is burning
as the broth is boiling.)
The broth is yellow.
I see yellow things floating.
It's hot.
Water.
How many times did I pour water?
It keeps boiling down.
My goodness.
Gosh. The water is...
(He keeps pouring water
to the broth.)
Is it okay for broth
to look like this?
The broth is too dark now.
Is it too dark?
Is it too weird?
(Seok Sam gives it a taste.)
It's too fishy.
Would it be okay if we season it
with salt? Isn't it fishy?
It'd be perfect
when seasoned with salt.
You think so?
- Of course.
- You're generous about your food.
Add soy sauce and salt.
It'd be good.
This is how sardine broth tastes.
It's anchovy.
Is it anchovy?
This one is sardine broth.
It's fishy.
I still can taste the fishy taste.
It's like I had some salted seafood.
- It's like I had sand lance sauce.
- It's not that bad.
- It's honestly not that bad.
- I'm not joking. I'm serious.
Can we make it better?
(As the broth was about
to become salted seafood,)
(Seok Sam tries to call
the detectives.)
These guys must be eating.
- They're not picking up.
- Try calling others.
I tried calling everyone,
but no one is picking up.
Why are they not coming as well?
(The reason why no one
is picking up his call is...)
My gosh.
(because they're doing this.)
Woo Jae.
Let's break this record. 916 points.
- Try it.
- Put coins in.
Put coins in.
Keep putting them in.
(The five of them are busy playing games
while the broth is boiling.)
- That was nice.
- So Min, can you give me money?
- So Min. Give it to us.
- I only got a ten dollar bill.
The broth keeps boiling down.
What? The broth keeps boiling down.
- We should go.
- They can keep adding water.
- We should get dumplings, no, tofu.
- You can pour water into the broth.
- Let's stop and get tofu quickly.
- Put coins in.
- We should break the record.
- Come on.
I mean...
Jae Suk, stop. Get it together.
- We should break the record.
- We should do it.
Can you just give me a dollar?
We should drive a car.
- I...
- Indonesia?
Yes. Indonesia.
- Should I go get tofu?
- I got Thailand.
Should I go get tofu?
- You? Okay.
- Should I?
Go get it.
I'll get tofu.
Go.
I'm coming.
(The race begins.)
There you go.
(The two detectives forgot
about their duty a long time ago.)
Okay.
(Four mischievous guys
were driving for a long time.)
They said they came to catch us.
I think they came to hang out.
Hello.
- I'll get two tofus.
- Sure.
- Hello.
- It looks so warm.
It was made just now.
It must be delicious.
(She got steamy handmade tofus.)
It looks so good.
(A bite of freshly-made tofu)
This is really good.
I think we're boiling it too much.
Let's take out the sardines.
- Yes. Let's do that.
- Don't you think we should do it?
Aren't we boiling it too much?
Take them out now.
I think I should take them out.
(They finally decided
to take the sardines out.)
If we boil them too much...
(As soon as he opens the lid,
the scent of the sea bursts.)
It's no joke. Look. It's fishy.
Gosh, it's fishy.
I can't believe this is broth.
(Messy)
We got broth from the bones too.
The anchovies disappeared.
Can you give it to me?
What?
- Are you going to season it?
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo is trying to make
the fish bone broth better.)
I'll try it. Watch.
Do you know how to season it?
Hey.
Hurry up.
I'm tired.
- I'm so tired.
- Ji Hyo.
Guys.
- I'm really tired.
- Why would you be tired?
- I mean it.
- Stop lying.
I have to lie down there.
I'm so tired.
(Ji Hyo tastes the broth.)
Suk Jin.
I don't think we can eat this.
Why?
It's bitter.
Forget it.
What is it?
- What's so hard about making broth?
- Try it.
Just eat ramyeon.
- It's fishy.
- It smells good.
(Suffering)
Does it taste bad?
- I don't think we can eat this.
It's so fishy.
(It's become an extract.)
Jae Suk. We can't eat this.
It smells good.
- Ji Hyo seasoned it.
- Really?
Where is everyone?
- It tastes good.
- Is that so?
Try this.
- This one is tasty.
- It's seasoned?
This one is seasoned.
Is it okay?
Is that so? That's a relief.
It's delicious.
(Others also give compliments.)
- It's very delicious.
- It is very tasty.
This is really nice.
This is the broth.
- You're going to season it?
- Yes.
Yes. You should put a lot of that.
(Ji Hyo seasoned the anchovy broth
before the members arrived.)
That's right.
(Ji Hyo seasoned the anchovy broth
before the members arrived.)
- Let's use this.
- Ji Hyo.
- Let's make it with this.
You should put six months' worth of
ingredients to make broth.
How many did you put in?
- To make broth,
- I put in a lot.
you should put in six months' worth
of ingredients.
(Only the anchovy broth
survived in the end.)
Should I put the noodles
in this one, then?
- Is it boiling?
- It's boiling.
- Should I put it in then?
- But this...
broth isn't good.
We're not going to use the broth
anyway.
- Aren't you going to use this?
- We're using that one only.
Should I put it in?
- Put it in. We can't use this.
- It's enough.
- You should put everything in.
- Put everything in.
When are we going to make lunch?
- Just put it in.
- Dinner should be...
We have to make noodles anyway.
Just put it in.
Do you have chopsticks?
Chopsticks. I put the noodles in.
I put it in.
(Jong Kook is increasing the fire.)
(Flaring)
It must be very hot.
The noodles are getting cooked quickly.
(The fire is very strong.)
(She tries the noodles.)
Come, Haha. I think it's ready.
- Should I take this? Okay.
- Yes.
We'll put it in cold water.
I'll get the noodles out.
The noodles.
(She takes out the noodles
cooked in the stove.)
It's cooked.
The noodles are amazing.
You're recording this, right?
Could you put the sieve closer?
Here.
- We should do it quickly.
- It's full now.
Let's make the toppings.
Pour out some here.
How many portions is this?
Why did you cook all this?
- Did you put it all in?
- Yes. I did it just in case.
(Zoned-out Crazy Sisters
put in everything they see.)
Could you turn on the tap, Woo Jae?
Pardon?
Is Woo Jae the servant
of this place?
- Woo Jae.
- Yes?
Divide this, Woo Jae.
You shouldn't do it like that.
The noodles will get overcooked.
Woo Jae. Onions and zucchini...
- Woo Jae.
- Yes?
(Everyone looks for Woo Jae.)
- Woo Jae. Hand me the sieve.
- Yes?
How many times did we tell you
to give us the sieve?
He's Lee Chun Hee
in "Family Outing."
He's Lee Chun Hee in "Family Outing."
Woo Jae.
He's the servant.
Don't use this path.
I placed the noodles here.
Who cools down noodles like that?
(The noodles are finally done.)
Try this. It's really bitter.
- It's bitter?
- It's bitter.
Add some more water.
Let's dilute it.
- Hold on.
- Should I put more water?
Add more water.
Pour more water.
Add a lot of water.
It would be nice
if we can use this broth too.
Yes. It's a waste to throw it out.
It tastes nice.
Add water two more times.
It tastes good now.
It tastes good?
Then leave it for a while.
This broth tastes good now.
(The broth tastes good again.)
- It's better.
- It tastes good.
- Right? It's tasty.
- We could make noodles with this.
It has revived.
It's better with more water.
The flavor is weaker
after the noodles were cooked in it.
It's weird. The Yangpyeong market...
had a janchi guksu restaurant.
It would have been easy
to buy food from there.
Goodness.
- What time is it?
- It's 1:30 p.m.
It's 1:30 p.m. I'm starving.
Goodness.
You must be hungry.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Let's put ramyeon
in the janchi guksu.
Ramyeon? In the janchi guksu?
It tastes amazing.
You haven't tried it, right?
It's really amazing.
Really? But we're supposed to eat
janchi guksu. That's the mission.
Why would you make ramyeon?
It's new.
It's not just ordinary ramyeon.
It's nice to eat with janchi guksu.
- You'll make janchi guksu here.
- Yes.
Then I'll make ramyeon janchi guksu
here.
- Should I put the ramyeon?
- Hold on.
It looks nice.
It will taste good
if you put the ramyeon seasoning.
(They make the ramyeon first.)
(They add the magic powder
in the anchovy broth.)
It's really delicious.
This...
smells really good.
- Really?
- The anchovy broth and...
(The master's noodles
with strong curls)
- It's done.
- Put eggs.
Give me some noodles.
It's fusion food.
It's really delicious.
Don't cook it.
I'm not cooking it. It's done.
It's done?
(How does this fusion dish
look like?)
I'll use this ladle.
Use it. Put the broth.
We have to eat this now.
(He adds warm broth
to the well-cooked noodles.)
We have to eat this now.
- It looks delicious.
- We have to eat this now.
It's janchi ramyeon.
(He gets excited
and tastes it first.)
How does it taste?
Is it good?
(It's tasty?)
(Seok Sam also tries
after hearing it's tasty.)
- It's strangely delicious.
- Right?
- It's like...
- It's like udon.
It's like udon.
Katsuoshibu.
Yes. It tastes like udon.
- Like...
- That's true.
- It tastes like udon.
- It's delicious.
(Ramyeon with janchi guksu
tastes like udon.)
It's interesting.
- Come here.
- Let's eat first.
- It's going to get soggy.
- Come here, Woo Jae.
- I really want to eat it.
- He doesn't have an appetite.
But I'm working on something.
- Woo Jae.
- He doesn't eat much.
It's delicious.
(The broth chef
also tries the janchi ramyeon.)
(Exclaiming)
What's this? My nose.
(It takes away the cold.)
- It's delicious.
- It's good, right?
Doesn't it taste like udon broth?
It's nice.
I'd buy it if it's sold.
If you add janchi guksu and ramyeon,
it tastes special.
The ramyeon seasoning
is really amazing.
(Janchi guksu with ramyeon
is receiving lots of compliments.)
- The broth is like medicine.
- It's really delicious.
- Woo Jae. Come and try this.
- Yes?
(The small eater is making eggs.)
This will burn if I leave.
- You're good at cooking.
- We have to cook this.
I'm from Olive.
- He used to cook.
- He's good at it.
It looks like a pancake.
He's from where? What's that?
- Woo Jae is good.
- We can cut that now.
You have to cook the zucchini.
We should make janchi guksu now.
(So Min prepared the vegetables.)
Cook them.
(Woo-derella is cooking
the vegetables.)
You're doing good,
but why do you look so petty?
Woo Jae.
You look petty
while cooking the vegetables.
Be bold.
You look like a sardine.
Sardine?
He looks like a sardine.
What's a sardine?
A sardine?
Something bigger than an anchovy.
It sounds nice. Sardine.
It's nice. My name is Sardine Joo.
Variety is about building character.
Wear warm shoes.
What is it?
He should wear warm shoes.
That's right.
- It goes well with my clothes.
- Yes.
- Hey, you should take those shoes.
- Seriously.
Jae Suk, they look good on you.
I like these shoes.
- Haha could give you such shoes.
- Of course.
I waited a long time
for those shoes.
Hey, should we make spicy noodles?
We have too many noodles left.
- You can use kimchi.
- But we will eat dinner soon.
That's right.
But we will eat dinner soon.
We will have to start making dinner
as soon as we put this down.
Spicy noodles and pork belly...
- will be delicious.
- Okay.
Isn't it funny?
Top the noodles
with zucchini and egg garnish.
You are good.
- Woo Jae is good at working.
- He is good.
- Woo Jae is incredible.
- Yes.
He can cook.
- Put the egg garnish on the top.
- Egg.
- Okay.
- Use this. It's pretty.
Make it pretty.
We worked haphazardly,
but the dish looks impressive.
It looks like something
you get at a restaurant.
It looks delicious.
Come here.
Shall we pick up the chopsticks
and dig in?
- Ji Hyo worked on this broth.
- Is it good?
(He is excited
about the improved broth.)
Why didn't you eat much?
- My goodness.
- Isn't it...
- I am really full.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Doesn't it taste a bit fishy?
I don't think it's tasty.
- Yes.
- It tastes a bit fishy.
- It tastes fishy.
Let's make a good shot.
- Jong Kook, it's very fishy.
- Eat it with kimchi.
I feel like I am eating on a boat.
That's a nice way to put it.
(He can smell the sea
from the janchi guksu.)
The noodles aren't soggy, right?
The noodles aren't soggy.
(He has to eat kimchi
after a bite of the noodles.)
What's up with the taste?
- Ramyeon was much tastier.
- I am so full.
This is my first time having
sardine broth...
that tastes so fishy.
I didn't know sardine
could be so bitter.
I see that this punk is very bitter.
- This is funny.
- What?
This is funny.
Do you know
what's unique about this dish?
You can't eat it without kimchi.
It's good with kimchi, right?
- It's good with kimchi.
- Kimchi is the main dish.
To enjoy the noodles,
you can't eat one piece of kimchi.
(A heap of kimchi)
It's like accompanying the noodles
to the kimchi.
- You numb your taste buds.
- Seven parts kimchi...
and three parts noodles.
Wouldn't it be better
to add noodles to the kimchi?
What we had earlier
was much tastier.
- Ramyeon?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- What we had earlier was so good.
- That's right. It was insane.
- I know.
I hadn't had
that kind of soup anywhere.
But this is...
Still, it's tasty.
It's nice to eat outside
for the first time in a long while.
- Look at him.
- Why are you so obsessed with fire?
- He has been that way for a while.
- It's like hellfire.
Hey, stop it already.
- Hey. This cauldron...
- Hey.
- Why do you keep stoking a fire?
- Do you think this is a sauna?
- Seriously.
- I need to save the fire.
- Hey.
- This isn't a steel mill.
He wants to temper iron.
Stop it already.
- Jong Kook.
- It's too hot.
I love it.
I can't see the soup
because of the steam.
I haven't seen that side
of Jong Kook before.
Look.
He is obsessed with fire.
He isn't satisfied
with simply keeping it going.
- It's like a smelting furnace.
- It has to burn up.
Jong Kook, my eyes are stinging
because of the fire.
Jong Kook, I want some fresh air.
I am in the countryside,
but my throat hurts.
Aren't cameras on that side
meaningless?
They won't be able to film anything.
- They can only film from this side.
- The steam blocks everything.
- The heat is nice.
- Cameramen don't even know...
if the focus is out.
Let's take out this cauldron.
- Is there a thick towel?
- Let's do it later...
when the fire dies down.
- I think I can do it.
- Let's do it later.
It could lead to an accident.
- Jong Kook, do it later.
- Shall I do that?
- Come here.
- I stoked the fire too much, right?
It's no wonder
the two of you received an award.
- What a pair.
- In that case,
- shall I sit down?
- Sit down.
Look at how strong the fire is.
Look at it.
It didn't look like that before.
It's incredible.
I am full.
- It's nice.
- The fire heats up the air.
My goodness.
It's pretty cold when I lie down.
You can go into the room and rest.
Shall I do that?
Do we have the time?
Is the room warm?
(Is the room warm?)
- Of course it is.
- Is the room warm?
- Is it warm inside?
- Of course it is.
Let's see.
It's warm inside!
(It's warm inside!)
It's nice.
(The warm floor
chases away the cold.)
It's nice and warm.
Gosh, the floor is warm.
I bet Suk Jin will fall asleep.
- Then let's keep filming.
- Should we let him sleep?
(Grabbing)
(He gets ready to go to bed.)
It's nice.
Gosh, the floor is warm and nice.
(He falls asleep in 10 seconds.)
I am 100 percent sure
that Suk Jin will fall asleep.
He did strenuous work.
He won't wake up, will he?
(Thus, Suk Jin went on
a journey to the dreamland.)
Don't I look like...
a camping expert?
Do you want coke?
This is it.
- Where is your cup?
- Here.
Did you drink some?
Give it to me.
- Do you want sikhye?
- It's here.
(Rummaging)
(The protector of the fire
has no intention to rest.)
- I will rinse it.
- It's okay.
You said thought about me
Will you use it?
(He approaches the target
as he hums.)
- I will rinse it. Don't shake it.
- Gosh.
- It's frozen.
- Is it frozen?
Did it freeze
because we kept it outside?
My goodness. Haha, it will spill.
(He adds two pieces of firewood
to the burning fire.)
(Laughing)
After comforting you
who grew gaunt in a few days
I love the lyrics.
- I headed back home
Hey.
Stop adding firewood.
- Hey, stop adding firewood.
- Let's turn this into a sauna.
Jae Suk, the height is nice now.
My socks are wet.
(Dirty)
So Min, I think they stink.
- No, it's the smell of sardines.
- Sardines.
Look at the fire.
- It's no joke.
- It's like the fiery pit.
- Yes.
- Yes. The fire of the fiery pit.
We can leave it as it is now.
(Proud)
It's a song for Chan Hee.
Shouldn't we play
an older song then?
- This song is totally old.
- Really?
Let's listen to it.
Shouldn't we play an LP record?
That's right.
Jong Kook, the fire is dying.
(Startled)
It's okay.
- He loves old songs.
- I said that the fire was dying...
and he got up so fast.
("Because I Love You"
by Lee Jung Suk)
(It's a masterpiece of a song
that was released in 1987.)
Thank goodness
I haven't listened to it before.
Why do you need to leave
when you love the person?
You are leaving
because you love the person.
Then that person...
- won't love you anymore.
- I released a remake of the song.
That's why you leave.
(The sentimentality of the past)
That's messed up!
Why would you leave...
when you love the person?
- What was that sudden outburst?
- Seriously.
What was that?
Are you mad?
- Seriously.
- Are you mad?
What was that sudden outburst?
I became angry...
- because of the lyrics.
- We were enjoying music in peace.
- What was that sudden outburst?
- The atmosphere was nice.
Isn't So Min hilarious?
("Hype Boy" by NewJeans)
Woo Jae,
you can dance to "Hype Boy."
- Woo Jae, you can dance...
- This is bad.
to "Hype Boy."
(Looking around)
- Jong Seo is good at that dance.
- Really?
- Jong Seo is really good at it.
Jong Seo, where are you?
- Jong Seo, come here.
- Watch Woo Jae's dance.
It has been a while
since I did the dance.
- Go ahead.
- Sardine's "Hype Boy."
- Let's see it.
- Sardine.
- Here I go.
- Let's go.
One, two.
(He can dance pretty well,
but his limbs sway too much.)
- You are good.
- You dance too halfheartedly.
You are good.
(Charming)
- All right.
- One, two, three, four.
(Let's see.)
Jong Kook had the exact same face
at the award ceremony.
- Jong Seo, come here.
- Hey, a celebrity should do better.
Do you want to see
our producer do it?
- Watch.
- Jong Seo, come here.
- Watch Jong Seo dance.
- Come here.
- He is in charge of me.
- He is no joke.
- Play it from the start.
All right. Let's go.
Watch Jong Seo dance.
- Watch him.
- Just now...
This is how well our producer dances.
Watch.
- Watch.
- Check out how well he dances.
(Haha is seeing it
for the first time.)
- He is getting ready.
- Oh, yes.
- Where should he stand? Here?
- Where?
(Here comes
a non-celebrity's "Hype Boy" dance.)
What's up with him?
- Hey, watch.
- I can't believe it.
Watch.
- My goodness.
- Jong Seo is really good.
(Fancy)
How is he so good at the dance?
- How did he memorize everything?
- How is he so good at the dance?
Jong Seo is really good.
How is he so good at it?
How did he memorize everything?
What's up with him?
- What?
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go.
One, two.
(The highlight)
How did he memorize everything?
(The Sardine Hunter)
What's up with him?
Watch.
What's going on?
- Why?
- Watch.
(Highly satisfied)
Watch.
You didn't dance as well.
He can dance so well.
(Shocked)
How is he so good at it?
He is good.
He must be a dancer.
- Look at his moves.
- He is really good.
(The perfect finale)
- Your dance was subpar.
- You are a celebrity, you brat.
- You punk.
- Did you see that?
- A producer can dance better.
- Just edit out my dance.
- Did you see that?
- Don't dance so halfheartedly.
- Did you see his moves?
- I didn't dance.
Don't dance
if your skills are subpar.
- Don't do the "Hype Boy" dance.
- A producer can dance better.
A producer can dance better.
- Let me say this about "Hype Boy."
- That's right.
- All celebrities, don't dance it...
- if you aren't as good as Jong Seo.
- Don't do it.
- A producer can dance that well.
Don't dance on Running Man
if you aren't as good as Jong Seo.
Of course. Why would you dance
if you aren't as good as a producer?
That was so funny.
Woo Jae prepared us
for the highlight.
Sardine,
Jong Seo shined thanks to you.
- Yes.
- I don't feel exactly happy.
Jong Seo can dance really well.
I made a living out of this
last year.
He can dance really well.
He has a talent for it.
Suk Jin came out.
You guys were being boisterous.
You guys were being boisterous,
so I came out.
Did someone dance?
We will show you.
Suk Jin will show you.
That's a good idea.
- Suk Jin.
- Stop it.
- Show us.
- You should dance.
- I mean...
- So Min should dance instead.
Suk Jin, you should dance.
- Why would I dance?
- You can dance well.
- You have to dance to this song.
Which song is it?
It's an old song.
"Swallowtail Butterfly."
("Swallowtail Butterfly"
by Kim Heung Kook)
"Swallowtail Butterfly."
Show us your dance.
Let's show them.
(The song was released
33 years before "Hype Boy.")
Everyone should dance to a song
that suits his or her era.
Come here.
(He begins to dance.)
Let's show them.
- Let's show them.
- Okay.
Let's show them.
(Suk Jin takes the lead
and 7 butterflies begin to fly.)
- This is our "Attention."
- Shove it to their faces.
(The NewJeans of the 80s and 90s
can dance as a group.)
You should dance.
- Good.
- Fly well.
Let's fly.
This is the highlight.
(The group dance)
(Suk Jin complained,
but he became the most excited.)
- That was good.
- That was funny.
- It was a group dance.
"It's a Crazy World"
by Shin Shin Ae.
We should show another dance.
- So Min can dance to it.
- This song...
- This song rivals "Hype Boy."
- We can dance in sync.
Gen MZers, watch carefully.
How do I know the dance?
- It's a masterpiece.
- Yes.
It's a masterpiece.
("It's a Crazy World"
by Shin Shin Ae)
That's the vibe.
(Look at So Min.)
There she goes.
(The crazy lady is ready to go.)
- It's So Min's turn.
(There goes So Min.)
Is that how the dance goes?
- She is good.
There you go. You got the vibe.
That's "Hype Boy."
Is she imitating Han Min Kwan?
There you go.
- Your eyes should look like that.
- Look at her facial expression.
Look at her facial expression.
(She channeled Shin Shin Ae.)
So Min doesn't disappoint.
- Good job.
- It was popular in the past.
- So Min.
- Good job.
- That was funny.
We showed them.
- We showed them.
- Yes.
- It was "Hype Boy" of the past.
- That's right.
That was funny.
- My stomach hurts.
- Can we take a break now?
No. We need to get back
to filming now.
- Can we take a break now?
- Wasn't that a break?
- No, it was work.
- That was a break.
We need to prepare dinner now.
- It's a busy day.
- Let's work fast.
That's the "Family Outing" style.
You stay busy throughout the day.
I don't want to eat dinner.
- What's this?
Kim, Song, Yoo, Ji?
- What?
- Kim, Song, Yoo, Ji?
- Why...
Where is Haha?
Why is Shopping Team missing?
What's this?
Kim, Song, Yoo, Ji?
- Kim Jong Kook, Song Ji Hyo,
- We worked so hard.
Yoo Jae Suk, and Ji Suk Jin.
We worked from 11 a.m. to 3 p.m.
We worked too.
- We did all of this.
- We worked too.
Some members are on the roulette...
because they were chosen
by the scriptwriters...
for having the best understanding
of the composition.
- Understanding of the composition.
- Yes.
(The members who understood
the composition of the episode)
To make janchi guksu in a cauldron,
Jong Kook built a stove...
and stoked the fire persistently.
Ji Hyo added enough sardines
to make 50 servings of the broth...
- and created a funny situation.
- It was funny.
Jae Suk created a situation
that was different...
from "Family Outing"
for screen time.
Suk Jin is funny since he keeps
forgetting about the composition.
- I am like that.
- That's right.
- How about us?
- I guess we didn't do much.
- We worked too.
- It wasn't like we played around.
I just danced
to Shin Shin Ae's song.
- It will go into the next one.
You will have a mission...
- for a break.
- Okay.
Through a mission,
- you can win a two-hour break.
- What's the mission?
It will be a team competition,
so discuss when
the break should take place.
Those with the same opinion
will team up together.
We can put it here.
Around 11 p.m.
Will we be able
to fall asleep early?
If you want to get up late...
- I prefer getting up late.
- We should get up late.
It would be better to sleep
and wake up early.
But we won't be able to sleep early.
Why don't we take a break now?
If we take a break now,
we will feel more tired later.
I am sorry,
but why do you keep wearing my shoes?
Aren't they warm?
- Seriously.
- They were here.
(Shameless)
- They are mine.
- They were here.
Haha cherishes those shoes.
Yes, he does.
Come here if you choose 11 p.m. to 1 a.m.
- I choose 11 p.m. to 1 a.m.
- Same here.
Let's choose to rest now.
Okay. I want to rest now.
You keep joining the young ones.
I am a Gen MZer.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- We are Gen MZers.
(We are Gen MZers.)
You joined them
when they went shopping too.
He is dressed like a man
who sells briquettes.
You look like a servant, okay?
Let's move
to the neighboring front yard.
- Shall we go?
- Okay. Our team is bound to win.
Of course.
- Are we playing basketball?
- Okay.
- I will explain the game.
The mission is
the Basketball of Hardship.
A representative from each team
will shoot free throws.
The team that scores more goals...
- will win.
- How many seconds do we get?
The opposing team can throw snow
to disturb the player.
The winning team will decide
when the break will take place.
Let's go. Okay.
Once you choose the first player,
put on the goggles.
The goggles.
- I won't score a single goal.
- She is bad at it.
Seriously.
So Min is bad at it.
- I heard that.
- We just need to do well.
- So Min?
- I heard that.
- You said I am bad at it.
Yes. You are bad at it.
Who said it? You did, right?
We said it's your turn.
Can I see better
if I put on these goggles?
They will keep the snow
from entering your eyes.
Should I throw with bare hands?
No, wear gloves.
I won't get the hang of it
if I wear gloves.
You won't get the hang of it anyway.
That's not true.
(The crazy lady goes first.)
Are you ready?
It's so far.
It's so far. This is bad.
Get ready.
- Get ready.
- Jong Kook.
(They prepare big shovels.)
This is bad.
(She begins.)
Good.
(They scatter snow for fun,
not to disturb.)
One goal.
Come on. One goal.
(No one expected So Min
to score a goal!)
- Two goals.
(She even scored the second goal!)
(They can't believe the skills
of the forever referee.)
You are doing well, So Min.
- Keep going.
- So Min.
You are cool.
(Both sides are having fun.)
Keep going. You are cool.
(Even if it ends now, it would be
So Min's best performance.)
Keep going. You are cool.
- She...
- Three goals.
(She scores another goal.)
She doesn't care about the snow.
- Three goals. You are cool.
- You are doing well.
She doesn't care about the snow.
(She keeps her eyes wide open.)
- Four goals.
This is too much.
She is covered in snow.
- Five goals.
Hurry up.
I am out of balls.
I don't see the balls.
(The round ends
as she digs for balls.)
I don't see the balls.
- I don't see the balls.
- So Min is so funny.
I don't see the balls.
Haha, the balls got buried.
- That was funny.
This is bad.
The next player will suffer.
- You were cool. You persevered.
- I focused on the task.
- That was funny.
- So Min, are you okay?
Yes, I am okay.
Who will go next?
Jae Suk should go next.
Okay.
(The mischievous man
who brought shovels will go next.)
Woo Jae gritted his teeth.
So Min.
- So Min is annoyed.
- Okay. Bring it on.
Bring it on.
Gosh. Hey.
All right. Bring it on.
Let's do this.
Ready.
(Start)
(Hitting the bull's-eye)
Sorry.
(While they make a big fuss,)
Don't do this.
(the attack isn't so impactful.)
(She's putting snow in the bucket.)
One.
(He scores a goal.)
(Despite their lame attacks...)
- Hey.
- You should look at the rim.
He's not scoring.
Gosh, this is...
(The snow is getting
through his open teeth.)
Jae Suk, you should score
at least one more goal.
(He finally explodes
with his cold teeth.)
(Strangely, his shots are accurate
when he aims at the heads.)
(He shoots the ball into the hoop again
with 5 seconds left.)
Gosh, I'm cold.
How many goals did you score?
- He scored two goals.
- What?
- Two?
- Two goals.
- Gosh, you...
- I'm so cold.
Your feet are safe.
What?
The shoes are nice.
(Thanks to the luxurious boots,
his feet are warm.)
- The shoes...
- My feet don't get wet.
- They don't get wet.
- I want to borrow them.
This is... They are really nice.
I'm sorry,
but can I borrow the shoes?
- What?
- Can I borrow them?
- He wants to borrow them.
- Can I?
Do all of us have to try this
at least once?
Isn't it two people per team?
Should all of us try it?
(Woo Jae's team has 3 members,
so he has no choice but to try it.)
- All right. Let's go.
- Who's next?
The basketball genius, Haha.
Should I go next?
(The little giant of basketball,
Haha)
My goodness.
- Gosh.
- Put it in.
- Oh, dear.
- We should do this.
Haha, you should start
before they fill the bucket.
It'll be the same anyway.
- Look how spiteful Jae Suk is.
- Look at him.
He looks so spiteful.
- He's spiteful.
- Why don't we start?
Why don't we start?
- Are you ready?
- Not yet.
(He got carried away with the snow.)
I really don't want to do this.
What should I do?
Hey. Go ahead and start it.
(There's another madman
who waits for his prey.)
I'm going crazy here.
Hurry and start it.
(The fireman joins them
with a fire extinguisher.)
- Hurry.
- Let's start.
- We're waiting.
- Can we really do this?
They are blocking my view.
Let's begin.
- They are blocking my view.
- Let's begin.
Ready.
(Start)
(He manages to weave
from the start.)
Haha is good.
(He starts a unique strategy
where he gets rid of the balls.)
- Nice. One goal.
- One goal.
There's no ball.
(The second half begins.)
Give me the balls.
(Filling the basket
with snow instead of balls)
Give me the balls.
Darn it.
(They interrupt him
with their perfect team play.)
Here.
(She attacks him from up close.)
They can't do this in front of me.
(His great shot doesn't go in.)
(He's becoming a snowman
without displaying his ability.)
In front of him.
(He's becoming a snowman
without displaying his ability.)
Nice.
- In front of him.
- Is it done?
(Time's up.)
- Haha...
- He scored three goals.
You scored three goals.
- Three is good.
- He did well.
- Okay.
- Let's just say we lost.
- Just like this?
- Yes.
- Should we rest now?
- Shall we?
You can rest whenever you want.
I think that's a good idea.
My socks are all wet.
Hey, you should wear good shoes.
You can't do this in slippers.
Who's next?
Should I go next?
- Yes, you go.
- Jong Kook?
Wait. I should gather some snow.
- If Jong Kook gets upset...
- He's scary when he's upset.
(The next player to go
is feeling nervous.)
- Ready.
- Jong Kook, score five goals.
Go.
You brat.
What was that?
We can't let this happen.
- Look at him.
- We should attack him right away.
Woo Jae. We shouldn't be doing this.
- Two goals.
- Hang on.
You can't do that with the shovel.
(Jong Kook, are you watching me?)
- Good.
- Well done.
Good.
- Look at So Min.
- Why are you doing that?
Look at Jeon So Min.
- What are you doing?
- Jeon So Min.
Good.
Jong Kook, over here.
Good. That was nice.
- Hey. Nice.
- Jong Kook is good.
He's like Jordan.
- He scored nine goals.
- Yes!
- It's over.
- Okay.
Hang on. Gosh.
- Just go. Don't budge.
- Kneel down.
- No, open your eyes.
- Open your eyes.
That was too short.
They are hitting his face.
Woo Jae, go ahead and do it.
- Woo Jae, do it.
- Woo Jae, stand up.
Where's the rim?
Over there. Watch carefully.
- Take a look.
- You should see it.
Do something.
Okay.
- You should play it again.
- You do it again.
- We will give you one more chance.
- Do it again.
Someone else should do it.
- Woo Jae, we'll give you a chance.
- Why?
- Someone else should do it.
- Why would you give us a chance?
(Let me see...)
Woo Jae.
Suk Jin doesn't have to play...
- I know.
- because you already won.
- Gosh.
- But he has to do it.
No, it's okay.
No. I finally got the hang of it.
- No. The winner is decided already.
- We never know.
We should do this until the end.
We have to do this.
- Seok Sam, you go.
- We should try our best.
- What are you talking about?
- Why are you being like this?
We should try our best
until the end.
Where are the goggles?
Go easy on me.
It's already settled. Okay?
It doesn't seem like match-fixing,
right?
It doesn't seem like
we're losing on purpose, right?
Hey, your face...
What do we do with your face?
Hey, now you use your face
to be funny?
- Your face...
- Did you put makeup on?
- You can't do this with your face.
- Now he even uses his face.
- Gosh, he's so weak.
- I want to use my face to be funny.
(Seok Sam steps up confidently.)
I can just do this.
Good.
It's hard to get the distance right.
Ha Ryong.
- This is hard. Hey.
- Ha Ryong.
You don't have to interrupt me.
It's not going in anyway.
What are you doing?
- Are you playing house?
- This is so fun.
I'll do it like this.
- It will be cute.
- Are you ready?
Start.
(Start)
(Sprinkling)
(He came up with a crafty trick that
doesn't require a lot of energy.)
Hey. There's Mr. Um Hong Gil.
- Keep doing it.
- That's good.
- This is nice.
- Mr. Um Hong Gil.
This is like the movie,
"The Himalayas."
It's the movie, "The Himalayas."
(He climbed the Himalayan peak
in 5 seconds.)
This is hilarious.
This is the movie, "The Himalayas."
He's Mr. Um Hong Gil.
Jae Suk,
only his nose is covered with snow.
Only his nose. How is that possible?
(Only his nose is
covered with snow.)
The snow piled up only on his nose.
- Only on his nose.
- The snow is only on his nose.
(The variety show deity is
blessing Seok Sam.)
This is so funny.
(Time's up.)
Hey. Gosh, this is more shocking.
(Even he finds himself shocking.)
- Petty.
- That was hilarious.
- It's funny.
- Didn't I score one?
You scored nothing.
- Nothing?
- I won.
- I won, right? I scored one.
- I think I scored one.
How did the snow pile up
only on his nose?
That was so funny.
The Nose Himalaya.
(The miracle of the Nose Himalaya)
A dunk shot
So Team Sleep Early wins.
Okay.
You can put "Rest"
on the place you want.
Okay.
The fire probably went out.
Let's go.
Right. The fire.
The fire probably went out.
We should hurry.
I'm hungry again.
(The cauldron recipe is
getting more daring.)
(Adding delicious things
in delicious things)
(Are they finishing the long day
with a successful meal?)
When Se Chan arrives here,
if everyone's asleep,
it will be really funny.
Is anyone there?
(The man with a mustache
arrives late.)
- Se Chan is here.
- I'm disappointed.
(But the day is over for them.)
(Se Chan should cook breakfast.)
And I should pick two people.
(He recommends the fire boy.)
(He raises doubts
about So Min's stare.)
- She's good.
- She was so sad.
If you look tired,
I will have to pick that person.
(The night is long.)
(The single room league is
more fierce than ever.)
(They talk about
the old days all night.)
(And...)
(Who will spend the second day
with Se Chan?)
(Running Man Outing Part 2)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)