In 1962,
starting with selling gourd bowls
in the corner of a market...
- Korea's export...
- Excessively high interest...
IMF, International...
- During the IMF Crisis...
- Exporting...
They established new goals for the
40th anniversary of the founding.
That's how Soonbak Group
grew to become a conglomerate.
As the chairman of Soonbak Group
who died not long ago...
left a will,
the Soonbak Group family
has gathered.
What time is it now?
Why are they not here yet? These punks.
I should teach them a lesson.
What time is it now?
(1-0: Ji Suk Jin, the eldest son)
By the way, should I make a pool
in front of this place?
(Three people are coming in
while complaining.)
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
(1-1: Yoo Jae Suk, the 2nd son)
(1-2: Kim Jong Kook, the 3rd son)
My gosh.
It's cold.
Why did they call me
when I'm busy? My gosh.
(1-5: Song Ji Hyo, the 2nd daughter)
(The daughter
the chairman cherished the most)
(1-6: Jeon So Min, the 3rd daughter)
Gosh. What is going on?
(And the youngest son
of the conglomerate family)
(1-7: Yang Se Chan, the youngest)
That's how the seven siblings
gathered...
at the eldest son's house.
My gosh. Why are they not coming?
Seriously.
Here they are. Why are you so late?
- Well...
- You...
How old are you?
- Me?
- You look like the youngest...
judging by the hat. How old are you?
- I'm the 2nd eldest.
- You're the 2nd eldest?
- How have you been, brother?
- We're a family.
- Why did you call us?
- Why were you so late?
Don't block the camera.
How many years
have you been in the industry?
Why are you blocking the camera?
Why did you call us?
- Okay.
- "Why did you call us?"
- Where do I sit?
- It's an important day.
- Come here, Jong Kook.
- Here?
Come and sit here.
- Suk Jin.
- Until when will you... Why?
Why did you not prepare any food?
It's for tea.
- What do you mean there's no food?
- I mean...
I prepared this sandwich for you.
No one in the family
eats sandwiches.
- I mean...
- Come on.
He really doesn't suit
a character who is rich.
I've never been rich.
- I can't act like one.
- The role play...
We're not a conglomerate family.
- It's not going well.
- We...
- So we don't know.
- I was cold in the helicopter.
Because most of us are self-made,
- It's hard.
- we can't play the characters well.
Honestly,
all of us grew up in poor families.
When I was little,
my mom would give me hot water...
so that I could wash up
in the kitchen.
- Oh, my.
- You came.
- What?
- Oh, gosh.
- She looks like Jung Hye Young.
- Right.
- Joong Ki's mother.
- His mom.
- She does?
- Yes. Joong Ki's mother.
- Wait.
- I'm Joong Ki's...
- It's "AM Plaza."
- mother?
She's Patti Kim.
- "AM Plaza."
- You are barefooted.
It's winter.
Don't they need to change her voice?
I'm sorry,
but is that a UFO on your head?
Hold on.
- Our youngest sister.
- Hello.
Suk Jin, I stopped by
the salon today.
- Why did you go to the salon?
- Yes.
- I need to anyway.
- Grandpa.
- "Grandpa?"
- I'm the eldest son.
- He's the eldest son.
After our father died...
- The role-playing...
- None of us were rich.
No one here grew up wealthy.
We don't know what it's like
to be rich.
Who's who?
What rich kid wears a hat
like this one?
- He also...
- Are you a painter?
- Look at him.
- No one rich dresses like that.
Are you the bodyguard?
- It's good to see you all.
- You call him a rich guy?
- My goodness.
- No way.
Chauffeur Yang!
Chauffeur Yang,
you aren't supposed to be here.
What...
No one would think
he's from a rich family.
I'll be the one to buy Soonyang.
(How shameless can he be?)
- Jae Suk...
- Come on.
I heard someone over there
call me "Song Choong Yi."
- This is hilarious.
- Chauffeur Yang!
- Is he the youngest son?
- Hey.
- Woong's father, sit down.
- Butler Yang.
- I can't believe it.
- It's like this.
You're like the uncle...
of the friend...
of the youngest son
of a rich family.
The ugliest friend of that uncle.
I'll buy it.
Then...
will Suk Jin be inheriting
the company?
- It's not like that.
- No, it's mine.
- Didn't you watch the show?
- You should know...
- It's mine.
- I met with my lawyer.
Why isn't anybody here to greet me?
(Around that time...)
I might freeze to death.
(Someone is here
in hopes of inheriting the company.)
I'll make the announcement
when everyone gets here.
- No way. Are you kidding me?
- Who is it?
- Seriously?
- No way.
- Jin Hwa Young?
Shin Rok!
But I already bought
the Soonyang Department Store.
- Soonyang Department Store.
- She's the real deal.
- Hello.
- Goodness.
- Shin Rok.
- No way.
Our second... No, third.
Gosh, it's been a while.
Why haven't you been in touch?
- What's the matter with you?
- Hold on.
- We're family.
- What are you saying?
He's my brother.
- She's my sister, you know.
- Shin Rok.
(In the series "Reborn Rich,")
(Kim Shin Rok played Jin Hwa Young...)
(from the Soonyang Family.)
(From her egotistical ways
and bullying of others...)
(to playing the immature
sweet daughter)
(She also played a vagabond
in "Hellbound"...)
(which was
a completely different character.)
(Scene-stealer Kim Shin Rok)
- Hello.
- Please have a seat.
There's the son of a rich man.
Her acting is phenomenal.
I can't believe Shin Rok is here.
- I didn't expect this at all.
- You have such a sweet look.
- I didn't expect it either.
- Give it up for her.
- Applaud!
- Thank you.
We begin the year...
- with a superstar.
- Exactly.
- My gosh.
- "Dad!"
- You know...
- I found you so annoying.
- That's how good she is.
- Her acting is this good.
She's that good.
You seem so charming
and warm right now.
It's because she is smiling.
- I was told to play a character.
- Shin Rok...
That had me nervous,
but I guess it wasn't the case.
- We're bad at role-playing.
- We're terrible at this.
We didn't grow up
in wealthy families.
I started off
with nothing to my name.
- Please introduce yourself.
- Tell us who you are.
Hello, I'm Actress Kim Shin Rok.
(They applaud a second time!)
Your name Shin Rok
is quite unique though.
- Is it your real name?
- That's right.
- No way.
- Shin Rok.
- Let's take a brief moment...
- Yes.
- to get to know her.
- Sure thing.
- Shin Rok's life story...
- Yes?
Her life so far
has been extraordinary.
- There's nothing normal about it.
- Really?
I have no choice...
- but to tell people this.
- What is it?
- She graduated from SNU.
- SNU?
- Really?
- She got a master's degree.
- She graduated from SNU.
- Why are you surprised by that?
Hwang Seog Jeong graduated
from SNU too.
Shin Rok also graduated from
that university.
- And...
- What did you major in?
- Geography.
- That's right.
- Geography?
- Geography.
- I almost wet my pants.
(I almost wet my pants.)
That's so embarrassing.
(His 1-dimensional thinking
is too vulgar.)
You almost wet your pants
because she studied geography?
One could even study the outback.
Geography and studying the outback.
All I know is puffer fish stew.
Shin Rok...
hoped to be a lawyer,
a diplomat, or the president.
- That's understandable.
- Of course.
You can hope to be that
if you get good grades.
I'm impressed.
But then she suddenly
took upon acting.
- Why though?
- Out of the blue?
- You got good grades.
- Your parents must've disapproved.
- We need to talk.
- Why though?
- Shin Rok, come on.
- What a waste.
Your parents
must've been disappointed...
when you told them
you wanted to be an actor.
- Her father is a stage actor.
- Really?
She should answer that. Not you.
- I want to hear it from her.
- I know everything about her.
Let Shin Rok answer.
- Is he a stage actor?
- Shin Rok, tell us.
- I looked her up online...
and gathered the facts.
He acted in plays before I was born.
When I was in middle school,
he took me
to a local theater company...
and suggested that I have
some fun acting on stage.
He wanted me...
to learn about life
more than the theater.
"Learn about life."
The overall tone of her voice...
and the certain words she uses...
make her seem classy.
I need to seem more graceful.
There's something classy about you.
Let's do this.
You do seem classy.
It's like reading
the New York Times.
She sounds intelligent.
You sounded like
the leader of women.
I say this because of what I heard
during her acceptance speech.
- That gives it away.
- What does?
- This is how classy she is.
- The words?
- Listen to this.
- What did she say?
"I ponder about people and the world
through plays."
- "Ponder?"
- What did you mean by that?
- "Ponder."
- Through plays?
"I ponder about people
and the world."
- "Ponder?"
"Ponder?"
Do you know what that means?
- Ponder.
- Do you get it?
She ponders.
I know what it is to share.
Sharing is when we divide something
between us.
- Meanwhile, pondering...
- I know what it is.
Is it like living vicariously
through someone?
What the...
- I shouldn't be doing that.
- Pondering.
That's not it.
This is how you ponder.
Is it "to think?"
- I'm curious though.
- Hold on a second.
You said you pondered.
But shouldn't you speak in words
that most people can understand?
I'll stick to "think" from now on.
(She levels it down for them.)
- Check this out as well.
- What is it?
- This is also just as mesmerizing.
- It's implicit and witty.
- What did she say?
After winning an award
at the Baeksang Arts Awards,
she said that the latter half of
her life was like an energy booster.
("The latter half of my life
is like an energy booster.")
I love that expression.
- A friend like an energy booster
- Nice!
- I love that expression.
- An energy booster.
Like milk thistle.
Like Omega-3.
Like probiotics.
Like a stimulant drug.
You love to read in your spare time.
(It couldn't be classier.
She loves to read.)
In other words,
I don't do much in my spare time.
She isn't like us, is she?
She lived the life
of someone with rich parents.
- I'm sure it's not all you like.
- Reading.
What's the latest book you read?
- Sorry?
- What's the latest book you read?
The book I've been reading...
I've been aiming
for a miracle morning, so...
- A miracle morning?
- Yes.
- A miracle morning.
- Getting up early.
Yes, it's about
starting the day early.
- Dong Hoon.
- The morning...
- I thought it was breakfast.
- Don't ask...
if you know you can't
understand the answer.
You need to explain these things
in layman's terms.
They wouldn't know
what a miracle morning is.
I doubt those two
know what it is either.
So Min, have you been practicing
miracle mornings?
Getting up miraculously
in the morning?
(Getting up miraculously
in the morning?)
That's right. Exactly.
- So Min.
- Come on.
I thought of the breakfast meal
at the fast-food joint.
I thought she meant a good morning.
What's a miracle morning?
In the morning,
- you wake up early to...
- Please tell us.
Just say that
you wake up early, then.
Why use tricky words?
Stop making us ponder!
We're nothing like the people...
- you associate yourself with.
- A lot, actually.
You're right though.
It's about waking up miraculously.
Do your eyes open wide
almost instantly in the morning?
No, not really.
What I mean is that...
My head's killing me.
Let's ponder.
- Ponder.
- Let's ponder.
Anyway, Shin Rok
came to greet us in the new year,
- and we're happy to see you.
- It's nice to meet you.
Anyway, joining us today
is Shin Rok.
I will now read...
the last will and testament
left by the CEO of Soonbak Group.
- Finally.
- The game has begun.
- It's our father's legacy.
- By Chairman Jin Yang Cheol.
(Who will inherit
Soonbak Group's assets?)
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- Wait. Are you the lawyer?
- You got a promotion.
- It's Mr. Hype Boy.
- Dance to "Hype Boy."
(It's the dancing lawyer.)
Dance for us.
It's Mr. Hype Boy.
- He's such a good dancer.
- Mr. Lawyer.
- Are you all present?
- Yes.
Then I will read...
- His acting is terrible, isn't it?
- the last will and testament...
- left by the CEO...
- Terrible, right?
- His pants are...
- Look at his pants.
- Hold on a second.
- They seem like dancer pants.
They're too wrinkled.
His acting will be atrocious.
What's with the chin hairs?
Are you all present?
- Yes, we're here.
- That we are.
You can see that we are gathered.
Then,
I will now read
the last will and testament...
left by the CEO of Soonbak Group.
I will now read
the last will and testament...
left by the CEO of Soonbak Group.
- It's Soonbak Group.
- Soonbak Group?
"Last Will and Testament."
- "Last Will and Testament."
- I can't wait.
- "Over the years..."
- Over the years,
I have watched Suk Jin
execute his business projects.
It is why I have decided
to abolish the rule...
that says the eldest
inherits the company.
"To abolish the rule that says
the eldest inherits the company."
That sounds good.
Dad, wait.
- We knew it.
- After all the promise I showed?
Everything depends on luck,
not effort.
The one who is lucky...
will inherit Soonbak Group.
It all depends on luck?
You, me, and So Min have no chance.
You will be given
eight subsidiary companies...
that I hold different amounts
of shares.
It is up to you
to split them among yourselves.
Use what you have
to buy more shares of the group...
and become the true successor
of Soonbak Group.
"Become the true successor
of Soonbak Group."
(Luck will decide
who the successor is?)
- Good.
- Got it.
Got it.
- What's this?
- Hold on.
- What is it?
- The subsidiaries.
Our father had a soft spot
for the adorable ones.
He likes what is adorable.
He had too many lines for someone
whose acting is atrocious.
You should've danced
to "Hype Boy" while exiting.
- What are the subsidiaries?
- Here we go.
- We have a rental car company.
- Nice.
- An investment company.
- Soonbak Investment.
An investment company?
- Electronics.
- That I should have.
- A cultural foundation.
There's also FC Soonbak.
- A soccer club.
- That's mine!
We own a soccer club.
Soonbak Entertainment.
- Oh, an entertainment agency?
- I want the entertainment agency.
And Soonbak Daily.
So there's a newspaper company too.
- A lodging business.
(Soonbak Lodging)
(The shares for each subsidiary will
be revealed...)
(after the choices are made.)
- You see, guys...
- Yes?
Honestly, I don't want much.
- Even when I saw those...
- Really?
Then the lodging business is yours.
- Thanks.
- It's yours.
- Doesn't he run one already?
- He got the lodging business.
- Just go and cook some meat for us.
- Can you start a barbecue fire?
Just cook some meat for us.
- All right. Settle down.
- Go out and start a fire for us.
I'll take the entertainment agency
and get lost. Give it to me.
- She said she'd get lost.
- You'll get lost...
- if you get the company?
- I'll get lost if you give me that.
- Then the entertainment agency...
- Give me a chance to pick one too.
- Why would you distribute them?
- I mean... Suk Jin.
- Why are we distributing these now?
- It's not like that.
Shouldn't we play
rock-paper-scissors or something?
Each of us should get
what we're interested in.
- I want the electronics company.
- Sorry?
You want the electronics company?
- Suk Jin is the only person...
- Yes.
who graduated from
a four-year college...
- among the cast members.
- That's true.
- And he's got class.
- He is, indeed.
- That's true.
- He's a well-educated man.
- He gets the cultural foundation.
- Yes.
Hey, that was the worst one
in the drama.
It was the worst one.
This is what they offered
to Joong Ki's father.
- No!
- It turned out to be a good one.
- No, I don't want it.
- Then...
I don't want
the lodging business either!
Hey, it has three bedrooms.
- Then you have it.
- It's not like what you think.
It's just a cabin! Darn.
- Hey, list it on Airbnb.
- Give it back to me.
- Right. List it on Airbnb.
- You said we were rich.
- A conglomerate owner family.
- You can get 1,000 dollars a month.
- Let's start over again. Then...
- I didn't mean I wanted that.
Shin Rok,
which business do you want to run?
Jae Suk,
I want the electronics company.
- My gosh.
- Many of us want that company.
- Let's decide randomly.
- Many of us want it.
- I want to make a lot of money.
- It's a profitable business.
- The electronics company is good.
- Then... Hold on a second.
Since Shin Rok wants
the electronics company,
how about those of you who want
the electronics company...
- play rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's do that.
How about those of you who want
the electronics company...
- play rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's do that.
- Now...
- All right. Then...
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Who wants Soonbak Electronics?
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay. Shin Rok and I won.
- Let's...
- The winner gets the company?
- Yes.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Screaming)
(Shrieking with disappointment)
- Hey, just give it to her.
- What was that?
I remember her screaming like that.
- She screamed like crazy.
- The 1st person to win 2 rounds?
- Give it to our dear little sister.
- Right.
- You can have it.
- Okay. I'll give this to her.
- No, you don't have to do that.
- It's okay, Shin Rok. You have it.
Since he gave it to you,
you can have it.
- Really?
- Of course.
Soonbak Electronics is the biggest
of all.
- I want the entertainment agency.
- True.
- I want that too.
- I want...
- the entertainment agency.
- As for the entertainment agency...
Since So Min was the first one
who said she wanted it,
- she gets the entertainment agency.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- I want Soonbak Daily, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- Soonbak Daily?
- Yes, Soonbak Daily.
She wants the newspaper company.
Okay.
- A newspaper company...
- I want Soonbak Investment.
- Here you go.
- A newspaper company is good.
- It's a good business.
- Give Jong Kook the soccer team.
- Jong Kook, you can have it.
- But I don't think...
- it's very profitable.
- You should have it.
How nice would it be to have
your own soccer team?
Exactly.
- Hey, give it to me.
- Next up is Soonbak Rental Car.
- I want Soonbak Rental Car.
- Wait.
Give me Soonbak Rental Car!
- I might get Soonbak Lodging.
- Soonbak Lodging.
- I want Soonbak Rental Car.
- Let's...
- choose the rest randomly.
- Randomly?
- Okay.
- That's a good idea.
- Let's do that.
- Then you choose first.
- This is...
- I pick the one in the middle.
The one in the middle?
- Soonbak Cultural Foundation. Okay.
- Oh, that's not bad.
- A cultural foundation sounds cool.
- Okay.
- Soonbak Lodging is the worst.
- All right.
But the lodging business...
- might be very profitable.
- I think we'll use our shares...
- Gosh. I got Soonbak Lodging.
- Great. It's Soonbak Rental Car.
- I knew he'd get that.
- I got Soonbak Lodging.
I got Soonbak Rental Car.
You have distributed
the eight subsidiaries.
- The share ratio is what matters.
- Yes. The total amount...
of the shares takes up 70 percent
of Soonbak Group's shares.
- And the shares have been...
- Did you say 70 percent?
- Yes. It's been divided randomly.
- I guess so.
I should take all those shares
from the others to win.
Each of you will go...
- and check your share ratio now.
- Oh, I get it.
But it could be different from
what we expect.
- Maybe Soonbak Lodging...
- If you look at the history...
- You're right.
- Rather than a large company,
- A small company...
- in many cases, a small one...
- is the holding company.
- There are many such companies.
I'll go first.
- I wonder if he has many shares.
- Maybe you have the most shares.
(The owner of Soonbak Investment
goes to check his shares first.)
(Song Choong Yi puts on airs
as he appears.)
Soonbak Investment.
I'll buy that company.
(Soonbak Investment)
The share ratio
of Soonbak Investment is...
What percentage did you say?
Out of 70 percent? That's the worst.
Why did I pick this company?
The next person can go now.
- You don't seem very happy.
- You look...
- You can take turns and check.
- You look a little upset.
- Go and check your shares.
- Shall I go next?
- You look really upset.
- No, I'm fine.
I have a feeling this company
will make me rich.
I don't think
it's just a small business.
I think there's someone
who has only one percent.
(Next up is FC Soonbak.)
I chose it because I loved soccer.
But soccer isn't
a profitable business.
I would rather suffer losses.
- Your share ratio is...
- Yes.
- eight percent.
- What percentage again?
Eight percent.
Out of 80...
I mean, out of 70 percent,
I only have eight percent?
Darn it.
(Next up is Soonbak Rental Car.)
What's my share ratio?
It's five percent.
(Soonbak Rental Car Shares:
5 percent)
You received one R coin
per percent stock share.
This is driving me nuts.
Gosh. I can't believe this.
Darn.
- Suk Jin.
- There must be large differences.
- Why do you look...
- You're done for, right?
- Right. He looks upset.
- Oh, no.
Your business went bankrupt?
Seok Sam is done for. I can tell.
- He's done for.
- He's dirt broke.
- Shin Rok, I'll go next.
- No.
- See you later.
- You can't tell by my face.
- I bet he's done for.
- That was funny.
Right. He looks disappointed.
All right. Let's go and check.
- Let's go.
- He...
He's bad at hiding his emotions.
I'll be able to tell by his face.
- Right. He can't hide it.
- Absolutely.
I'll tell you what he does.
If he gets disappointed,
he'll smile when he comes back.
If he gets more than he expected,
he won't smile.
- Isn't that what you usually do?
- He can't smile...
That's what I do.
(He confessed how he behaves
unintentionally.)
I thought
you were talking about yourself.
- He's similar to me.
- Exactly. I was surprised.
(The 2nd son lost
in the fight for a good subsidiary.)
Tell me how many shares I have.
Soonbak Lodging has...
(No one wanted Soonbak Lodging.
How many shares does it have?)
eighteen percent.
(Soonbak Lodging Shares: 18 percent)
I knew it.
(Soonbak Lodging turns out to be
a hidden treasure!)
I knew it.
- Hey.
- He can't hide his emotion.
- He got a lot.
- He's pretending he's disappointed.
- Stop pretending you're upset.
- He's pretending.
- Okay.
- I can tell he's so happy now.
- I bet he got a lot of shares.
- Jae Suk.
- That's unexpected.
- He's elated.
I think he got about 20 percent.
Usually, the front six teeth show
when he smiles.
- But ten of them are showing now.
- Go ahead, Shin Rok.
- My gosh.
- I bet he got a lot of shares.
- Did you get a lot of shares?
- I'm sure he did.
- I made it.
- Did you?
I see that Father...
- My goodness. Why did Father...
- hid the shares here.
What's with his tone?
Why are you speaking
in an arrogant tone suddenly?
- "Father..."
"This is where Father hid those."
- His tone doesn't match his outfit.
- Soonbak Investment.
(Next is Soonbak Electronics,
which she went through hoops to get.)
Soonbak Electronics has...
(Soonbak Electronics)
Oh, my. Should I take this with me?
You received one R coin
per percent stock share.
- So 1 coin is worth 1 percent?
- Correct.
Do I really have...
(Does Soonbak Electronics own
a high share ratio as expected?)
- Shin Rok is back already.
- That was quick.
- She's carrying it with her.
- She's carrying it with her?
- Shouldn't I? Oh, I should hide it.
- She brought it with her.
- It's okay, Shin Rok.
- I brought mine too.
I bet she only has a few coins.
- Oh, she didn't get many shares.
- I think she has 3 or 4 coins.
- Her pouch looks thin.
- Right.
- I should've hidden it.
- I could tell at a glance.
- No, that's not the case.
- Soonbak Electronics isn't so good.
I could just tell.
- She has 4 or 5 coins.
- I see. Okay.
I know how many she has. Okay.
- No, you're wrong.
- Okay. Got it.
- Good. I got you.
- Where should hide my pouch?
- Jong Kook went there earlier.
- I see.
(The rest of the members have
checked their shares as well.)
Soonbak Daily's shares...
- Yes.
- You have...
(Soonbak Entertainment, Soonbak
Daily, Soonbak Cultural Foundation)
Today, we're going to decide
which of the eight siblings...
will be the successor
of Soonbak Group.
It's Reborn Spitefully Rich.
- Oh, I see.
- You have to get...
as many shares as you can
to increase your chances...
- of becoming the successor.
- Yes.
The number of shares you hold
at the end of the race...
will determine the number of boxes
your name is written in.
We'll choose two numbers...
to choose the chairman
and the vice chairman.
The two of them will receive
different prizes.
You can obtain more shares through
general shareholders' meetings...
- or in missions.
- Yes.
The team that wins in a mission...
gets to take four percent
of the losing team's shares.
- My, that's a great benefit.
- Indeed.
Before each mission,
you will team up with the siblings
you want.
The person with the most shares
on each team...
- will be the major shareholder.
- I see.
I said the winning team
got to take four percent, right?
- Yes.
- The major shareholder will...
choose who they will take it from.
- Really?
- Yes.
That means that after one game,
someone could...
Someone will go broke at once.
In other words,
someone will be forced out
on the street.
Someone could go broke at once?
Okay.
- I want to be a major shareholder.
- Before we begin the first mission,
you'll be divided into
2 teams of 4 members.
For your information,
in the first mission,
the total number of shares held
by the members of each team...
will determine the winning team.
- The more shares, the better.
- Yes, the team with more shares...
- The team with more shares?
- The team with more shares wins.
Just like that?
(There's always a factional dispute
in a conglomerate family.)
(Join forces with the sibling
who's at an advantage.)
Let's leave Shin Rok out.
- Let's leave her out.
- That's a good idea.
- We'll leave you out, Shin Rok.
- That's a good idea. Seriously.
- We shouldn't team up with her.
- I swear.
Shin Rok, is that a good idea?
It's a good idea.
- I bet she only has a few coins.
- I know.
- I have an idea.
- I have quite a lot.
Since Shin Rok is our guest,
for the first mission,
let's let her choose
her team members.
- Let's do that.
- Okay.
- If she chooses 3 members,
- She'll pick 4 members. Oh, right.
- the rest four will team up.
- Let's do that.
- I think that's for the best.
- Okay.
- Just follow your hunch.
- To pick the ones with many shares.
- Yes.
Is Soonbak Entertainment doing well?
Yes, it's not bad.
I think
she has quite a lot of shares.
- She picked So Min.
- Her first choice was So Min.
- How's yours?
- You won't be disappointed.
What about you?
I have quite a lot,
but I don't want to join your team.
- I pick Haha.
- Why?
I think you have many shares.
(Shin Rok chose Haha.)
- It's good enough.
- Okay.
- Ten teeth showed when you smiled.
- When I smiled?
I'm bad at hiding my emotions.
Then I choose Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- I see.
She didn't even ask me and Se Chan.
- I already chose three members.
- Right.
- Do you have many shares?
- Yes.
- Okay. She's made her decision.
- Okay.
- You're divided into two teams now.
- Yes.
- Which team has more shares?
- Here go each team's total shares.
- Each team's total shares?
- Okay. Tell us.
The teams that were just decided,
right?
The cutline is 35 percent, right?
Our team has...
Soonbak Daily,
Soonbak Cultural Foundation,
Soonbak Lodging,
and Soonbak Electronics.
What a mess.
- Soonbak Lodging...
- That's a mess.
- and Soonbak Cultural Foundation.
- Soonbak Cultural Foundation.
I'm confused about the identity
of this group.
If we have more than 35 percent,
we'll win.
- Out of 70 percent.
- Right.
(Current shares)
(Shin Rok made a good choice.)
- She picked the right members.
- I said I had quite a lot.
As a result, Team A wins.
- We must be bad at hiding emotions.
- That's great.
- Almost twice as much as we have.
- They have a lot of shares.
One of them must have
more than ten percent.
- Right. I'm sure that's the case.
- Yes.
The major shareholders
of the two teams are...
(Is it Soonbak Electronics
or Soonbak Lodging?)
Team Shin Rok's
major shareholder is...
- Jae Suk.
- I knew it.
(Current shares: Jae Suk 18,
Shin Rok 11, Haha 10, So Min 9)
(Who is the major shareholder
of the losing team?)
(How many shares
do Ji Hyo and Se Chan have?)
And Team Suk Jin's
major shareholder is Jong Kook.
(FC Soonbak, Kim Jong Kook)
- Me? Are you sure?
- He must have very few.
I'm the major shareholder?
- They have less than ten percent.
- This is a total mess.
- What?
- My business is not so bad.
My gosh. They have so few shares.
Jae Suk, you can take four percent
from anyone on the other team...
- and decide how to distribute it.
- Yes.
But you can't have all of it.
You must pick at least two members.
- I must share it with someone else?
- But...
- It's only the first mission.
- You have to share it.
- I knew he had a lot of shares.
- Someone will go broke.
Clean one of us out.
- I think Suk Jin will go broke.
- He'll go broke at once.
- I...
- Suk Jin will go broke at once.
- I think so too.
- I'll take Seok Sam's shares.
- Hey.
- I've made my choice.
- I bet he's broke now.
- I'll take his shares.
- How could you?
- I think...
- I think he lost all of his shares.
- I think so.
- Come on, brother.
- Listen, brother.
- I'm your elder brother.
- He's broke now.
Just relax and enjoy yourself
for the rest of your life.
- That's nonsense.
- Suk Jin.
- They have more shares than I do.
- You should...
- It's fun to watch them arguing.
- just go on trips now.
- Hey!
- I'll pay for everything.
- You'll take four percent?
- Yes.
- You took four percent from him.
Choose the members
you want to share it with.
- Jae Suk.
- Will you reveal everything?
I wish our team had won.
- Jae Suk, help me out.
- Since it was Shin Rok...
who formed our team,
I'll give her one percent.
I'll give Shin Rok one percent.
- I bet he'll keep the rest.
- She's smiling at him.
- My goodness. Her face.
- Look at her.
What's with that face?
- She's smiling at Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
I haven't been able to pay
the building maintenance fee.
- All of the artists left my agency.
- Jae Suk.
I won't ever ask for your help again
if you help me out this once.
- I want to say the same thing.
- Trust me.
Is your entertainment agency
struggling a lot?
Yes, indeed.
She's dating an idol singer,
you know.
She brought it upon herself.
- He's dating the agency owner?
- Haha.
The idol singer is dating the owner
of the agency he works with.
- Haha. Let me explain.
- You're supposed to work with him.
- You should work with him. Why...
- I mean...
- Why are you dating him?
- Well, right now...
- Hey. She's dating...
- It's not like that.
- You should work with him.
- She's dating an idol singer?
- He's an experienced idol singer.
- Hey.
- I asked you not to tell anyone.
- Why would she date him?
- And not long ago,
- It's ridiculous.
Ji Hyo stopped an article about it
from being published not long ago.
- I mean...
- You stopped the article for me.
- You should be grateful to me.
- I know.
Since it's so complicated,
- I'll have the rest three percent.
- Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk.
- Didn't you know he'd do that?
- I promise I'll never do it again.
He must have a lot of shares now.
- Jae Suk.
- That's not all. Hey.
Just because
we have different mothers,
you can't treat me like that.
I mean... Right.
(Surprised)
- Honestly...
- Hey, I saw Shin Rok...
- She looked like this.
- She was surprised.
- I didn't know that until today.
- And...
- It's different in dramas.
- They have different mothers.
- Did everyone else know that?
- They usually have different dads.
I didn't know either
because Dad kept it from me.
Jae Suk,
you don't do that to your family.
You should share everything
with your family.
Hey, he just took all of my shares
when we're family.
I'm dirt broke now because of him.
- He could've chosen someone else.
- Suk Jin.
- He could've chosen Muscle.
- Go on trips...
- He holds a lot of shares.
- You can just go on trips now.
- I don't have a lot.
- Enjoy your life.
- I was surprised to know...
- Go on trips.
I was so surprised.
Go on trips and enjoy yourself
for the rest of your life.
You have distributed the shares
that you obtained.
The general shareholders' meeting
will begin shortly. Before that,
- please change your clothes.
- Got it.
- That was hilarious.
- Rich people stay rich forever.
- I have so few shares.
- I thought I picked the worst.
- Is it warm, Jae Suk?
- Yes, it's warm.
- Is it warm?
- Yes.
My, this is good.
There's nothing like...
- a cup of hot...
- You're taking herbal medicine.
A cup of hot Americano
makes me happy.
Life is simple.
If I can afford to have a cup of coffee...
- and three meals a day...
- Really?
and have a home to keep me warm,
that'd be good enough.
Then why do you always check
real estate prices?
- Hey.
- To make the most profit.
- I mean, it doesn't make sense.
- He's a liar.
If you think you don't need much...
- I feel empty.
- to keep yourself happy,
- why would you check the prices?
- I feel empty. That's why.
Before the next mission,
you will attend
the general shareholders' meeting.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(The 1st
general shareholders' meeting)
(The ones
who influence stock market prices)
At the venue,
- you'll see 40 pinatas.
- Pinatas?
In each pinata,
there's a random percentage of shares...
out of the 30 percent of shares
held by minority shareholders.
- I really should get some shares.
- Yes, you should.
When you break open a pinata,
if there are shares in the pinata,
you can choose Go or Stop.
If you find shares
in all the pinatas you open,
you get all the shares you found.
But in some pinatas,
there's flour instead of shares.
If you open one of those,
you should pay a fine of two percent...
- out of your shares.
- But you know my personality.
I would keep going no matter what.
- I know. He wouldn't stop.
- Me too. I wouldn't stop either.
- I'd stop if I get a good one.
- Of course.
If you get floured
after opening several pinatas,
- What happens to those shares?
- the fine of two percent...
- and the shares you got before...
- We lose all of those shares?
- We'll lose the shares.
- will be moved to another pinata.
- Really?
- I'll choose Go to the end.
That could make another pinata
a jackpot.
I see. It'd be great
if I go last and hit the jackpot.
To attend
the general shareholders' meeting,
you must hold
more than 15 percent of the shares.
- What?
- I see.
- We have to gather our shares.
- I don't have enough shares to go.
If you're not qualified
to attend the meeting,
you can gather shares
with other members.
- We still won't have enough shares.
- Not many of us...
- can attend the meeting.
- We have only 18 percent now.
- Suk Jin is broke already.
- Even if we gather our shares...
The eldest son gets one chance...
to attend
a general shareholders' meeting...
- alone.
- Really?
- I'm the eldest son, you know.
- Only Suk Jin gets the chance?
- I'm the eldest son.
- Only the eldest son?
- Those of you who want to attend...
- Can we go now?
Yes, you can go and play the game.
- Really?
- I think Jae Suk can go alone.
- Right?
- Go and have some fun.
- He must have more than 15 percent.
- I hope you get floured.
- Then I'll...
- Okay. Go ahead.
- I'll go alone.
- Okay.
- He's going alone? My gosh.
- He's going alone.
- Oh, he...
- Are you going alone?
I hope you go broke. I really do.
- I'll hit some pinatas.
- Okay.
I hope to see you covered in flour.
- See you later.
- It looks like...
Oh, yes.
(The one who's 1st in rank
walks confidently.)
Let's go hit some pinatas.
(The one who's 1st in rank
walks confidently.)
This is it. Where is it?
- You hold more than 15 percent.
- Yes.
- You're qualified to be here.
- That's right.
Please enter the conference room.
Yes. Thank you.
(10 out of the 40 pinatas have
flour in them.)
- You chose number one.
- Yes.
(He chose number 1.)
I'll open it. One, two.
(Will he get lucky this time again?)
(1 percent)
One percent?
(It's not a lot.)
Congratulations.
You obtained one percent.
Would you like to choose Go or Stop?
I choose Go no matter what.
I never choose to stop.
I keep going forward no matter what.
Okay. Let's try again. Number two!
I'll start.
(He chose number 2
right next to the pinata he opened.)
One, two.
Oh, no. Zero percent?
Yes, but you didn't get floured,
so you can keep going if you want.
(Since he didn't get floured,
he can keep trying!)
- Then would you like to go with me?
- Take me with you.
Sure. But what about him?
I'll leave him here.
Really? I see. Okay.
- Wait.
- I won't go with you.
- Can we go with them too?
- Do you have enough shares?
- I can choose one of them, right?
- Yes, you can.
- Really? Haha, I lied.
- I didn't know that.
- I was just...
- She said she lied.
- Don't go back on your word.
- It's not like that.
She's our guest.
She was just trying to help me.
- Because she's our guest.
- Sorry?
She's our guest. So what?
Hey, I have an idea.
- We see each other every week.
- Hey.
- The meeting...
- Go with me and two more members.
- Including you? Why should I?
- I don't want that either.
- Why should I do that?
- It's my loss. I won't go with you.
Shin Rok, let's go together.
You two have 15 percent?
- If we gather our shares.
- Do you really have enough shares?
- Well, my shares alone...
- I have nine percent.
- What percentage is yours?
- Oh, my.
It's a secret.
Should I tell you that?
Do we have enough shares
to attend the meeting?
- Yes, we do if we combine ours.
- Okay. Then let's go.
- The teams don't matter?
- Of course.
- I'm not sure.
- We'll know when we get there.
- They teamed up together.
- Oh, they...
Hey, do you guys have 15 percent
if you combine your shares?
Let them go.
I'm sure they'll get floured.
I'm sure of that.
They're like trains with no brakes.
You're right.
They don't know when to stop.
(While the sisters and brothers
formed their alliances...)
(Jae Suk chose Go again.)
I'll pick the number in the middle.
I'll go with number 11.
- I picked a dud.
- Pull it down.
Oh, is this how we play the game?
Pull it down.
- What?
- He got more shares again?
- I picked zero percent again. Gosh.
- He might pick all the good ones.
- Gosh, seriously.
- He might open all the good ones?
I'll open one more.
(He might break open
all the pinatas.)
Okay. Number 30!
(This is his 4th attempt.)
I'm ready. One, two.
- I hope it's a dud.
- Zero percent.
- He picked zero percent.
- My gosh. Zero again?
(He got no shares 3 times in a row.)
Are you sure you put as many shares
as you should in the pinatas?
I opened 4 pinatas,
but I got only 1 percent. It's not fair.
- Jae Suk, choose Go.
- Go!
(Keep going
until you hit the jackpot!)
It's about time I hit the jackpot.
I'll go with number 26.
- A number in the middle.
- Until we hit the jackpot.
Let's keep going
until we hit the jackpot too.
Because we have to share it.
- It's hard to share one percent.
- Right.
(What's in number 26?)
- It's zero percent.
- Darn it!
(Again?)
(He keeps picking out the ones
with 0 percent.)
He picked them all out.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- He's helping us.
- I picked 4 of them in a row.
- Pick out 1 more for us.
- One more!
- Okay. I'll open one more.
- Okay.
- You're the man.
- I'll go with number 21.
(He's unstoppable like a tiger moth
darting into a fire.)
- Get floured.
- One percent.
- Oh, he got one percent.
Okay. I got one percent.
I'll stop here.
- Would you like to choose Stop?
- I choose Stop.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Shin Rok and I will participate.
This isn't easy.
Thank you.
The pension owner knows how to play.
The pension owner.
Pick one of them. A number.
Is there a lucky number you like?
No,
but there's ten percent in this one.
- Really? Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
I hope they get a flour bomb.
Pull it.
In 1, 2.
- In 1, 2, 3.
In 1, 2, 3.
I think it's flour.
Pull it.
(Dud)
I didn't expect that.
Hey.
- My gosh.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- Jeon So Bal!
- You two failed...
- Shin Rok!
to acquire your share.
- How did you pick that one?
- Okay!
- You failed!
Please pay the fine...
- with two percent of your share.
- Each of you should give it to us.
You failed.
- You failed.
- I'm sorry.
- I should've changed my mind.
Okay.
I mean...
- Each of you should give them two.
- Right now?
Shin Rok is unlucky as well.
- How did she...
- Shin Rok.
- You're really unlucky.
- No. I will win.
Out of so many of them,
how could you...
Jae Suk opened five,
- he didn't get a dud at least.
- That must've been our worst.
- We... It might be me.
- The two...
Many of them
could have flour, right?
Okay. Let's go with number 14.
- Number 13. Yes.
- Number 13?
All right.
(The youngest chooses number 13.)
Fail.
(The owner of the pension ruins it
even before it begins.)
Fail.
- Success.
- Fail.
(The classy eldest daughter
joins them.)
(She got used to Running Man.)
- Success.
(They got competitive
with the ritual battle.)
Fail.
- Fail.
- Number 13.
Pull the string to see the result.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Get a dud.
- Get a dud.
- Get a dud, please.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Flour. Yes!
(It's a dud.)
You failed.
- You failed to acquire your share.
- You failed.
Give us two percent of your share.
(Each of them should pay the fine
with 2 percent of their share.)
- I'm so excited.
- Later, the remaining pinatas...
- Jae Suk, you did amazing.
- What?
I did amazing.
How did you do it?
Let's go.
- Can we not try again?
- This is nice.
I'm excited.
Okay. He is coming.
- I can tell from his expression.
- He sounds quite happy.
- Didn't you get the flour bomb?
- No, I didn't.
I opened about six pinatas.
- Did you get shares every time?
- Really?
- No way.
- You didn't get a flour bomb?
No, I didn't
- You're amazing.
- So you should try it quickly.
- I mean he's...
- Should I do it quickly?
Shin Rok got a flour bomb.
- She got it.
- Yes, I did.
Jae Suk isn't usually lucky,
but he's lucky this time.
Shin Rok turned out
to be an unlucky one too.
- As soon as she picked it...
- So I should do it next time.
I had a good feeling, though.
Look at her.
You look good.
- It serves you right.
- We should get it next time.
- This is why we play this game.
- It serves you right.
I was crushed.
- Gosh.
- At once.
So Min looks like she got
more flour than anyone else.
I'm sorry. I'm unlucky.
This is good.
Another mission will begin.
The heirs and heiresses
should have knowledge in many areas.
- It's about common sense.
- I'm doomed.
- So...
- It's advanced common sense, right?
- It is advanced common sense.
- Okay.
It's advanced common sense.
Yes.
The mission we prepared this time...
is Conglamorate Family Quiz Class.
One of them will guess the answer...
and three of them
will give them hints.
- It will work then. Shin Rok...
- One of us will guess the answer?
- That's okay.
- After seeing the word given by us,
the three of you should write
a word related to the answer...
- to give a hint.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Each of us?
Hey.
- But we should know the answer.
- Can we write a random word?
- Why don't you come this way?
- Let's go.
Who will go first?
Before we decided
who will go first...
- Yes.
- We will order delivery after this.
Delivery sounds good.
We'll order what the major shareholders
from each team want.
We'll discuss it.
- Let's have noodles.
- Let's have something healthy.
- How about salad?
- Bossam?
- Salad sounds good. It's healthy.
- Pork cutlet.
- Or a sandwich.
- Let's have Korean food.
I'm sorry, but the two of us...
- will decide.
- I want pork cutlet.
(Lifting)
- What do you want to have?
- What do you want?
- What do you want, Jong Kook?
- I'll have what you want.
- What should we have?
How does bossam sound?
- Something nutritious or...
- Incorrect.
I know a place that has
delicious braised short ribs.
- Incorrect.
- That's a no.
- Fried rice.
- Fried rice is...
If it's incorrect,
that means there's a correct answer.
Tell us.
- It means he thought of something.
- Say what you want.
I want braised short ribs too.
- Incorrect.
- Braised short ribs.
Seolleongtang.
Seolleongtang?
Gamjatang.
- Seolleongtang doesn't sound bad.
- I did it.
- How about you, Shin Rok?
- Sundaegukbap.
- Bossam.
- Bossam?
Bossam is incorrect.
Then what do you want to have?
What do you want?
- What do you want?
- Shin Rok.
- I'm the major shareholder.
- What do you want to have?
- I... Wait.
- I'm so curious.
- The weather is quite cold.
- It's cold.
Because it's cold...
- What do you want?
- I'm sure he will say kalguksu.
- Seolleongtang?
- It's 100 percent noodles.
- How about jjamppong?
- Come on.
You always have
either ramyeon or jjamppong.
- How about jjamppong?
- Come on.
You always have
either ramyeon or jjamppong.
- He's right.
- I want to have something else.
- I always feel bloated on Monday.
- Okay. Give me a suggestion again.
We only had noodles.
It drives me crazy.
What about baeksuk?
It's famous around here.
- Baeksuk.
- How about chicken bone soup?
Chicken bone soup
or braised spicy chicken.
But they...
- Why? What about them?
- They're on a tight budget.
- Right.
- The budget...
- It's not a big difference.
- You pay for it then.
Yes. That sounds good.
- You pay for it.
- You're okay with it, right?
Why don't you treat us to a meal
after a long time?
- I can treat you, but...
- He can treat us.
I can treat you.
- It's on me.
- Then it's on Suk Jin today.
- It's on Suk Jin.
- My gosh.
It's on me.
- No.
- Sushi?
- Let's have something simple today.
- Yes.
- Jjamppong.
Please. Just once.
- I'm sick of it.
- I don't like it.
- Why?
- I'll have mapo tofu, then.
I want to have rice.
- I'm sick of it.
- Just have the same one.
I don't like Chinese food.
Then have fried rice.
She wants to have fried rice.
- Ji Hyo, are you okay with it?
- Fried rice.
- Yes. Fried rice.
- How about you?
- Rice.
- Jjamppong with seafood.
I'll have rice too.
- Raise your hand. Jjamppong rice.
- Rice.
I'll have fried rice.
- Jjamppong?
- Jjamppong.
Don't order things like tangsuyuk.
- Pleaser order tangsuyuk.
- No.
- Why not?
- We won't finish it.
- We won't finish tangsuyuk.
- Right.
- That's not good.
- Let's just order one then.
Shin Rok is here too.
Don't you want some tangsuyuk?
- Will you not have tangsuyuk?
- You want it, right?
You want to have tangsuyuk, right?
- Will you not have tangsuyuk?
- You want it, right?
- If you want it, just nod.
- Shin Rok, will you have tangsuyuk?
- Say it comfortably.
- Tell us what you want, Shin Rok.
Tangsuyuk...
- That's a no.
- What's wrong with her?
What's wrong with her?
- Mister.
Do you not want it?
- You don't want tangsuyuk?
- Okay.
- Shin Rok doesn't want it.
- No way.
- Okay.
- "No way."
Let us order fried dumplings
at least.
- Let's have fried dumplings.
- Yes.
Okay. We'll order them.
Which team will do the quiz?
They'll go first.
I want to see how it goes
with those who are good.
Okay. Let's do it first.
Even without
a professional explanation,
- he might know.
- He would guess.
- Is it hard?
- But I can't think of words easily.
The first question
is about current affairs.
- Current affairs.
I'll show you. Go.
(The first word is revealed.)
(Financial Independence)
This is...
They've seen it many times.
I think they will know.
(Financial Independence,
Retire Early movement)
- One, two,
- They will know.
- three,
- We've seen it many times.
- I think they will know.
- four,
five.
- Hold up your hints.
- Times up?
- Hold on.
- Even Haha knows it.
- Hold up your hints.
- Are you done?
- Hold on.
- Even Haha knows it.
Show us.
- Are you done?
- Hold on.
(I was fired from my job,
Golden retirement, Fire family)
What kind of retirement?
Show us.
What retirement?
- Five.
- It's golden retirement.
Four.
- Three.
- Wait. The FIRE movement.
(Correct)
- Is "fire family" okay?
- "Fire family."
- Is "fire family" acceptable?
- I mean...
- The correct answer is FIRE.
- Is "fire family" okay?
- "Fire family" is a little...
- I'm sorry, but...
- What's "fire family?"
- What?
Isn't this too direct?
- "Fire family." "FIRE."
- FIRE is...
It's not that fire,
but it's still fire.
Here...
- "Fire."
- What's "fire family?"
- The answer is all here.
- I'll be careful.
But he didn't see it anyway.
Why did you not look at me?
But you know...
- She's just a weak link.
- "A weak link."
You should go easy on me too then.
- We have a weak link too.
- Okay.
It's Art and Culture this time.
This one sounds easier.
I'll show you.
- Five,
- I know it.
- four,
- I knew it.
- three, two, one.
- I don't know what it means.
Hold up your hints.
- What is it?
- It's...
Put it up.
Hold up your hints.
(Stone plate grilled)
(A warm and strange hint)
What is it?
Stone plate grilled.
Life is but a dream.
(Hill, Life is but a dream)
- But...
- Life is but a dream.
- Four.
- Stone plate grilled.
- Three.
Dream in the oven?
- Stone plate grilled.
- Life is but a dream?
- These hints are better.
- Dream in the oven?
("The Cloud Dream of the Nine")
These hints are better
if you know what it is.
- Dream?
- Three,
two, one.
- Okay.
- What is that?
"The Cloud Dream of the Nine."
- "The Cloud Dream of the Nine."
- "The Cloud Dream of the Nine?"
(The hints are useless.)
- "The Cloud Dream of the Nine."
- "The Cloud Dream of the Nine?"
Life is but a dream, hill.
Why did you write
"stone plate grilled?"
Because it's grilled.
Don't look at hers.
She's just there for fun.
Why would you write
"stone plate grilled?"
That was the only word
that came to my mind.
That's how you're going to play it?
Okay.
- Because it's grilled.
- Yes.
You can guess the answer now,
Shin Rok.
- Me?
- Come here.
- Yes. This could work.
- So frustrating. We can't draw.
How does it become
"dream in the oven?"
I'll give you the next word.
It's about politics and economy.
Politics and economy.
It's politics and economy, Shin Rok.
- This is difficult.
- I don't know anything.
Don't look at So Min's hint.
Haha.
Start.
(Santa Claus rally)
(A calendar effect in which
stock prices rise around Christmas)
(It's a difficult question.)
This is an economic term.
Three, two, one.
(She just writes even though
she doesn't know the term.)
Show us.
What did you write?
(Christmas continues)
You can take off the eye patch.
Christmas. Stocks.
- I don't know.
- She doesn't know.
- Christmas.
It's Christmas.
- Shin Rok.
- It continues.
- Five, four,
- It continues?
- three,
Christmaaas.
Christmas continues.
- It continues?
- It continues.
Christmaaas.
Shin Rok!
- Christmas.
- It's Santa Claus rally.
- Am I doomed?
- It's so difficult.
What did you mean
by Christmas continuing?
- Santa rally.
- Rally.
Rally meaning going and coming back.
- But this is difficult.
- It's difficult.
I'll show you.
(Stock option)
Five, four,
three, two...
- One. Show us.
- This one is easy.
(It's an easy question.
Would we get useful hints?)
This is a bit difficult.
- Show us.
- This one is easy.
(Stocks that you additionally get
on the side.)
- Should I take it off?
- Yes. You can see the hints.
(She checks the hints.)
It's easy.
What did you write?
Detox?
(She just used
similar-sounding words.)
Haha's hint is easy.
The right to buy stocks.
Detox?
Stock option.
(Stock option)
(She got "stock option" right
from the hints.)
- Whose hint did you see?
- Detox.
Detox? She got it right
after seeing "detox."
You get it additionally on the side?
- That's how you get it.
- It's the right to buy stocks.
Black swan.
(Shin Rok continues to get
the correct answers.)
"Les Miserables."
- That's right.
- Nice.
- Kim Shin Rok.
- How do you know that?
- Very good.
- That was good, Shin Rok.
Seoul National University,
Department of Geography.
Kim Shin Rok, the best
from the department of Geography.
Great.
- You're really good.
- Am I?
It was so difficult.
This is...
- It's difficult.
- We...
will do it like that.
- I'll try to guess it.
- That's right.
- I'll guess it.
- Focus on the first letter.
- Just ignore mine.
Okay. I'll just guess it.
We should phrase it well.
Okay.
- I don't want to eat jjamppong.
- Me too.
I don't like Chinese food.
I'm tired of it too.
I ate it yesterday as well.
If it was bossam...
Jae Suk is looking at us.
(The jjamppong lover
is glaring at them.)
I can't digest it.
Really?
- Hyung In,
- Then...
could you get us two seolleongtang?
They want seolleongtang
because they can't digest it well.
He doesn't want to eat jjamppong.
He's 44 years old now.
He could want to eat seolleongtang.
We have Shin Rok with us today.
She said she'll eat jjamppong.
- She...
- She wanted bossam.
That's right. She wanted bossam.
When did she say that?
You're the one who wanted bossam.
- She wanted bossam.
- Do you want to eat bossam?
(Exclaiming)
Tell me if you want to eat bossam.
It's okay.
- See.
- He's the one who stopped her.
(While the jjamppong haters
make a protest...)
The first question is about economy.
I'll show you.
(The first question
is about economy.)
Goodness, this is nuts.
- This is...
- This is hard.
- Four,
- I'll write.
- This is hard.
- Four,
- three,
- You know this, right?
two, one.
Show us.
Let's see.
Here.
(North pole, bird)
North pole.
- Think about it one by one.
- You'd know if you know.
- You know it.
- What did you write?
A bird that lives on ice
and can't fly.
It can't fly? Penguin?
It can't fly.
What is this question about?
It's an effect.
I'll give you five seconds.
- It's very easy.
- Look at the sentence.
- The one in your mind.
- Four,
- It's correct?
- Yes.
- It's easy.
- Penguin effect?
Okay.
(Penguin effect)
(He guessed it right.)
They shouldn't do it like this.
You should explain what it is.
- You should explain.
- Why should I?
- I just need to say the answer.
- You should explain.
You should explain the answer.
- I just need to get it right.
- That's right.
Penguin effect...
is when people buy goods
after watching other people buy it.
- That's right.
- Yes. You follow what others do.
Penguins follow other penguins
like this.
That's what it is.
- "I'll buy it too."
- That's not what it is.
When one penguin jumps into water,
the crowd also follows.
That's right. That's what I meant.
Then why did you imitate
how they walk?
(He randomly walked cutely.)
- He doesn't know the term.
- That's the penguin effect.
- He got it right.
- Yes.
I don't know economic terms.
- I did okay, right?
- You did well.
That was a good start.
The next question
is about current events.
- Current events?
- Current events.
(Noblesse oblige)
- This one is doable.
- But this one is...
Two, one.
It's what you don't keep at all.
- Show us.
- Let's see.
(Will he be able to keep his honor?)
(Rich foreigner)
(Exclaiming)
This is what it is.
Give?
(A rich person giving
as fitting his class)
(I know!)
I'll give you five seconds.
- Five, four,
- You know it, right?
- three,
- It's easy.
- It's not Buenos Aires.
- two,
(Buenos Aires?)
- It's noblesse oblige.
- Is this about capital cities?
- Don't you know that?
- I know.
I know, but I couldn't remember
what it was.
Buenos Aires?
What is he talking about?
He just said that to be funny.
- Why Buenos Aires?
- You wanted to be funny, right?
Noblesse...
- You wanted to be funny.
- No, I didn't.
You do it.
- It's difficult.
- But you know more.
I know noblesse oblige.
Noblesse oblige.
But she counted down so suddenly.
It made me nervous.
What's Buenos?
The capital city.
Where? I don't know.
- The capital city of Argentina.
- Argentina?
(She learns something from this.)
- I knew it was wrong. It just came.
- It's because...
- Noblesse...
- It sounded similar.
It was noblesse oblige.
I'll show you.
(Metaverse)
Hold on.
- Five, four,
- Okay.
- three, two,
- Do you know it? Is it easy?
- It's super easy.
- one.
- Okay.
- Show us.
- You should get it right.
- Lift them up.
(You have to get it right.)
- It's easy, right?
- I couldn't write the front part.
(Where we invested)
- You know this one.
- Metaverse!
- That's right.
- Yes!
(He got it right immediately.)
We invested in metaverse.
- Let's go!
Ji Hyo wrote, "Seoul Tayo Bus."
(She really wrote that.)
- Bus.
- Let's see.
- Seoul Tayo Bus.
- Bus.
- It's a bus.
- She used "bus."
How could he not see Jong Kook's...
and get it right
from "where we invested?"
That's amazing.
Where we invested. Metaverse.
- Let's go.
- This one is about current events.
- That's great.
- I'll show you the word.
(Genome)
Five,
- Is it doable?
- This...
- four, three,
- You should write it, Se Chan.
two, one.
(Ji Hyo confidently writes.)
- Show us.
- What was that?
Ji Hyo is awesome.
Seriously.
Your handwriting.
Baby. What's that? Child?
- What did you write?
- Child.
Child?
(Various words inspired
from the word "genome")
This...
That's right.
(His hint is useless too.)
- Project.
- It's germandeuk.
- What?
- Five,
(Germandeuk, Project This Brat,
That Brat, Baby Child)
What? This is about current events?
- That's right.
- "Ge" is the first word.
Three.
(He's the only one
Suk Jin can rely on.)
- Geo...
- Wrong.
- Genome.
- That one is funny.
No one said anything about genes.
- Germandeuk.
- Genome.
- No one wrote genes.
- Ji Hyo.
There's something
called Project Genome, right?
- Baby, child?
- Project Genome.
It's correct.
Genome. Baby, child, and genome?
- That's right.
- This is crazy.
Baby, child, genome.
It goes in gradation.
- It was a gradation.
- That's right.
- I totally understood.
Shin Rok's team won.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
Okay.
The major shareholder
of the winning team...
can take four percent.
That's nice.
I thought we would win this time.
- Seriously.
- I worked hard.
- Don't worry.
- I am hungry.
- Whose shares should I take?
- I only ate flour-based food.
- This time...
- Jong Kook has the most.
How about one percent
from each member?
I will take one percent
from each member.
- One percent? In that case,
- Yes.
- give him one coin each.
- Thank you.
- One coin each?
- Give me one coin each.
- Now?
- Yes, give him one coin each.
- One coin each?
- It's in my bag.
Maybe Suk Jin doesn't have it.
- Maybe he doesn't have it.
- One coin each?
- Hey.
- Here you go.
Well...
(With 1 percent,
Suk Jin is close to bankruptcy.)
- He is close to bankruptcy.
- What happens then?
- Does he go home?
- You just participate in the games.
I just participate in the games.
It doesn't mean anything.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Give me another one.
- Another one? Okay.
He has one. He showed it to me.
- It's Soonbak Group.
- Suk Jin, do you have a coin?
Of course. The eldest son
has one more chance.
It's my only coin.
(Jong Kook submitted 1 percent
instead of the eldest son.)
- One percent each.
- Thank you.
Are we doing the pinata now?
Jae Suk, do it.
- We got it!
Stay.
One, two.
(Se Chan and Jae Suk picked a dud
at a general shareholders' meeting.)
(The eldest and the youngest
are close to bankruptcy.)
(Soonbak News, the end)
I will give you
the current shares...
- of each team.
- Okay.
Jong Kook's team has...
- ten percent.
- What?
(Their total is 10 percent.)
(Their wealth became quite small.)
Ten percent?
- Where did my shares go?
- Ten percent?
- My goodness.
Hold on. Are you saying
these 4 have 10 percent?
(1, 2, 1, and 6 percent)
(They lost a lot of shares
at the meeting.)
We need to stay together.
I see that Jong Kook doesn't have
a lot of shares.
I gave Jae Suk two coins earlier.
Then we should mix up the members.
If Jong Kook remains
the major shareholder,
he will get coins.
The other team has 57 percent.
(Team A has 57 percent.)
If you have
a moderate amount of shares,
you will be the major shareholder
in this team.
Totally.
I have one last chance.
I have a benefit as the eldest son.
- Father...
- You keep talking about it.
- That lousy benefit.
- I am the eldest son.
- Seriously.
- Father didn't give me shares.
But he did give me an advantage.
An advantage.
The eldest son's advantage.
- It's here.
- It's here. The food is here.
- Jjamppong is the best in winter.
Look at the color. It's amazing.
The soup looks delicious.
I ordered seolleongtang for them.
They have an upset stomach.
Good job.
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy the food.
- Thank you.
Do you even feel like eating?
(Current shares: 1 percent)
What? I need to eat.
- Let's eat before work.
- That's right.
Thank you for the food. Is it tasty?
Yes.
- Is it good?
- My goodness.
(The noodle lover became happy.)
It's so nice.
- It's so tasty.
- Radish looks tasty.
(The siblings of the Soonbak family
enjoy the 8-dollar jjamppong.)
It's so tasty.
- It isn't too far.
- It's nice.
(The siblings of the Soonbak family
enjoy the 8-dollar jjamppong.)
It's so tasty.
It's really tasty.
Soup is the best in winter.
- This is a nice restaurant.
- It's tasty.
It's nice.
Look at this. Father bought...
- a big house.
- This place is so pretty.
I didn't know such a place existed
in the backyard.
I have lived here for 50 years,
but there are places I haven't been.
- This place is nice.
- My goodness.
- It's nice.
- Yes.
Hold on. Let's stand
with our teammates.
You guys...
Team Beggars, go over there.
- What? Team Beggars?
- Don't say that.
Please give us a chance to recover.
- It's time for the second mission.
- Okay.
It will be another team competition.
Team up with members of your choice.
- Shall we change things up?
- Shall we do that?
Jae Suk, let's switch the members.
- Let's do that.
- We should stay as we are.
- That's right.
- They won't take too much from us.
- Hold on.
- We need members with more shares.
If we lose,
they will take coins from me only.
- That might happen.
- Right?
Of course,
they will take coins from you only.
In the previous round,
I submitted one more coin.
- Send us two beggars.
- That's right.
We will send you two members.
We became a team of beggars.
- The beggars should go.
- Yes. Come over here.
- Okay.
- Shin Rok, go over there.
- Shin Rok.
- Haha should go.
- Even if I switch teams...
- Right?
- We can do the pinata together.
- Switch coats with me.
- We can still team up.
- This is small.
- It's okay.
- Stop picking on me.
- It's nice and tight.
The team members have been decided.
As a result,
Team A's major shareholder
is Jae Suk.
- You can't beat him.
- Move back.
- Team B's major shareholder is...
- Haha.
- Is it you?
- It's him.
- Look at you guys.
I knew it would be him.
- I came to save the team.
- Yes.
- Save the team.
- Team A has 36 percent...
- and Team B has 31 percent.
- Okay.
- It's neck and neck.
- What?
- The shares are similar now.
- Okay.
Then the two of them...
- Then the two of them...
- Why did you give them the total?
Then they would know
how much we have.
They brought nothing
but their mouths.
Why did you give them the total?
How much does our team have?
- Our team has 36 percent.
- It dropped so much.
- The shares are similar now.
- How did it drop so much?
- My goodness.
- Haha has a lot of shares.
- There is a balance now.
- Haha does.
- Shin Rok contributed too.
- My situation isn't half bad.
- My goodness.
- I see.
And you... I am sorry, but...
- What?
- I will tell you later.
- Tell him now.
Shin Rok and Haha.
What about them?
- A hot pack is in the pocket.
- Yes.
Would you give it to me?
(He asked Haha to return
the hot pack.)
It's cold.
- Was that what you wanted to say?
- That was unbelievable.
- Seriously.
- I mean...
Would you give me my hot pack?
- All right.
- It's here.
Since our jackets were changed...
All right. Return the hot pack.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Okay. I didn't mind.
- Okay.
I was going to ask later,
but it entered my mind.
The next mission is...
the Deflated Heir.
The swan is the number one treasure
of Soonbak Group's chairman.
Deflate it and put it
in a plastic container.
- You must close the lid completely.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- Those are inflatable swans.
- You use them at a pool.
- Let's win.
- Here it is. There are two valves.
- One is on the neck.
No, there are three valves.
Two on the wings
and one on the neck.
You use them at a pool.
- Where will you go?
- It's fun.
- I want to go sledding.
- Go ahead.
It would be hard
to use it as a sled.
(They begin to race on the snow.)
He must play with Na Eun like that.
- Jae Suk, it's so much fun.
- My goodness.
(He plays with Ji Hyo
as if he is playing with Na Eun.)
- He sure is a dad with a daughter.
- It's so much fun.
- Hold on. We...
- Hey.
What are you doing? Look at them.
(Hitting)
They are different.
It's because he is single.
- A single man is different.
- Most dads are like that.
He is different.
- When dads are energetic...
- He is so different from Jae Suk.
(Shin Rok rides the tube too.)
- Do that for me.
- My goodness.
Se Chan.
- Se Chan, do that for me.
- It's nice.
- Do that for me.
- You need strength.
- It's nice.
- We put it in this box, right?
- Make sure you close the lid.
- This is fun.
- Please listen to me.
- Where are the valves.
Let's focus.
Please focus.
- Okay.
- Focus.
It would be fun
to ride it down the hill.
I know. It sounds fun.
- I want to do it.
- Go ahead and do it.
- Really?
- Is there a hill?
Hyung In told us
to go ahead and do it.
- On top of the hill?
- Yes.
It's fun to ride a tube like this.
- It does sound fun.
- It's so much fun.
I can ride it by myself.
- Is there a hill?
- Yes. You just need to push it.
- There he goes again.
- Do it.
He will get hurt.
- Don't get hurt. Be careful.
- Why...
(His mischievous side comes out
when he sees the snow.)
There you go.
- Yes. That's how you do it.
- It hurts.
Let's please play the game.
Why can't you focus?
- Go ahead.
- Please focus!
Let's play the game.
I am sorry.
All of us were born mischievous.
- Do we deflate it now?
- Are you ready?
- Let's go.
- Do we begin now?
Let's divide up the sections.
- Take the biggest section.
- Okay.
- I will take the head.
- Get ready.
- How many valves are there?
- Are there four?
- Get that one out first.
- Take it out.
- Take it out first.
Take it out. There you go.
This one too.
My goodness.
- Deflate this part.
- I can't get the valve out.
- Can't you get it out?
- There is one here too.
- I can't get it out.
- There is one on the head.
There is one here too.
My goodness.
- I didn't get it out.
- Did you get it out?
The valve needs to come out.
For goodness' sake.
(At that moment,
Se Chan gets the valve out!)
- Se Chan, I got it out.
- Did you get it out?
- Press down on the head.
- It needs to come out.
- Use your teeth.
- My teeth?
- I got this valve out. Deflate it.
Is it out?
(Thanks to Suk Jin's teeth,
air begins to come out.)
Hey, get the valve out first.
There we go.
- Ouch.
- Move out of the way.
- So Min.
Move out of the way.
- So Min, get the valve out.
- There is a valve on the head.
- We are going fast.
- Air is coming out.
- Good.
It will come out soon.
- It's in so deep. There we go.
- There we go.
This is hard.
We need to press the area around it.
For goodness' sake.
Is it coming out, So Min?
I will deflate the wing first.
- Is this wing separate?
- Okay.
Look at them.
The air is coming out fast
since I gained weight.
- Jong Kook, look at them.
- They are almost done.
What should we do about them?
- I will fold this part.
- Here.
- We need to fold it.
- Get up.
- Se Chan.
- Fold it.
- We need to fold it.
- Wait a second.
- Hey.
- Fold it. Wait a second.
What are you doing?
- Wait a second.
- Good job.
- What's wrong with her?
- Shin Rok.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
(She returns
after throwing the container away.)
- We need to deflate it more.
- I mean...
- For goodness' sake.
- They aren't done yet.
Hey, put it in here.
It isn't completely deflated.
- Put it in the container first.
- Let's deflate it further.
- The tail part.
- Where is it?
Hey.
- The tail part.
- Where is it?
Hey.
- Come on.
- Hey.
Good job.
(Running away)
Hey.
For goodness' sake.
You are so mischievous.
(Shin Rok perfectly adjusted
to Running Man.)
For goodness' sake.
I can't believe her.
(A real smile
people couldn't see in the drama)
How am I supposed to bring it?
(Ouch)
There are thorns.
- Bring it here. Open it.
- Open it.
Let's put it in the container first.
- Put it in.
- If we put it in, the valves...
Deflate it.
(They plan to deflate the swan
as they put it in the container.)
- One, two, three.
- Most of the air is out.
Most of the air is out.
- Okay. Suk Jin, bring it here.
- Again.
I think it will go in.
Hurry up and bring it.
Step on it.
Suk Jin, put it inside.
Come on.
Hurry up and put it inside.
(Haha stole the lid
right before they put it in!)
- It won't go in.
- We need the lid.
- Where is the lid?
- Here.
It's ours. Oh, you are my teammate.
The lid.
- Run.
- Shin Rok.
The lid.
(Haha passed the lid to Shin Rok.)
- Hey.
- The lid.
We just need the lid.
- We just need the lid.
- Suk Jin.
We need to put it in.
(Suk Jin tries to stop them.)
- My goodness.
- How is she so strong?
Hey.
(It doesn't occur to him
that he is weak.)
- Hey.
- My goodness.
- It broke.
- He broke it.
Why am I putting it in? Hold on.
He is putting it in.
What am I doing?
- Jae Suk, there is the lid.
- Jae Suk.
- What?
- Where?
- Hold on.
- What happened?
She is so mischievous.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk, close the lid.
- Here.
- Is it in?
- No.
It needs to be brought to the front.
No!
- He did it.
- It's done.
- We closed the lid.
- Success.
- It's done.
- We closed the lid.
- Success.
- We did it too.
- We brought it to the front.
- We did it perfectly.
- Let's see it.
- Good job.
- We almost lost.
The team that put away
the tube perfectly,
- Suk Jin's team won.
- I finally won.
Do you know what startled me?
I went over there to stop them
and began to put the tube in.
I became flustered.
- "Why am I putting it in?"
- He was helping us.
- He was a helper.
- Good.
The major shareholder,
Jae Suk, can take...
- four percent.
- Four percent?
- Take Haha's coins.
- Haha.
I will take Haha's coins.
- Is Haha the richest?
- Give him four coins.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Shin Rok has a lot too.
- Now,
why don't you give us
two coins each?
- What?
- Come on.
Two coins each? That's nonsense.
- Two coins each.
- Even if he does that...
- Get lost.
- You won't even have six coins.
What did you say?
- You wanted two coins.
- "Get lost?"
- There are 4 members.
They have a lot of shares.
- Where are my coins?
- They must be in there.
- Right?
- There is no way you lost them.
(Shin Rok lost her money pouch.)
This is my scarf.
Come on.
Look for it.
You rolled around on the snow earlier.
- It must be there somewhere.
- Go over there and look.
- Go.
- I will be back.
(Shin Rok goes to find her pouch.)
(Why is Se Chan grinning?)
- I have Shin Rok's pouch.
- Really?
She needs to find it.
(They exchanged their jackets
before the mission.)
(Thus, Se Chan obtained
Shin Rok's money pouch.)
Shin Rok.
- It's missing.
- Shin Rok,
give me two coins if you find it.
- He must have it.
- No.
It isn't me.
I can't give it to you otherwise.
- You must have it.
- No.
Will you give me a coin?
- This is mine.
- Really?
- I will give you a coin.
- Give me a coin.
He is good.
- It was in the pocket.
- He has good business skills.
It's not over until it's over.
My goodness.
- What was that?
- You got fooled!
What was that?
- You should have taken one out.
- You should have done that first.
You got fooled!
It's not over until it's over.
- Take that!
- This is ridiculous.
Do Jun, you punk.
(Do Jun tricked her in the drama,
so she took it out on Se Chan.)
Okay. I got it.
- Thank goodness.
- How annoying.
- That was refreshing.
- Good job.
- Okay.
- Now, Team B's major shareholder...
became Shin Rok.
Is it Shin Rok now?
Let's go and have the last
general shareholders' meeting.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's go.
(They set off for the last
general shareholders' meeting!)
It's finally the last one.
I have a benefit.
Let's do this.
Let me join you guys.
You poor thing.
Shall we let him join us?
He is pitiful.
- Okay. You can join us.
- You can join us.
- All right.
- Just like the last time,
you need 15 percent or more
to attend the meeting.
- Fifteen percent or more.
- The eldest son's advantage.
The eldest son's advantage remains.
Those who want can participate.
- Who wants to go first?
- We need three members, right?
We should go
after people get a flour bomb.
- That's right.
- We should go...
- after the shares add up.
- Going first has pros and cons.
- I need a big break.
- Will you get a big break...
or a flour bomb?
- The 3 of us will go.
We let Se Chan join
since he looked so pitiful.
- He looked so pitiful.
- Do you want to go first?
- Yes.
- Go first.
- I will go next.
- No, don't go first.
- It's more advantageous.
- We need to lose some flour bombs.
- No. It's more advantageous.
There are pinatas with a big prize.
That's right.
It's more advantageous.
- Seriously.
- A pinata with a big prize.
The two of you should go then.
- We can't.
- We can't. We need one more person.
- Hurry up.
- Haha.
- Let's not go right now.
- I can't get 3 flour bombs.
- Let's pick number 35.
- Give me a chance.
- Number 35.
- Let's go with number ten.
- Haha.
- I like number 8.
- Let's go with number 8.
- Number 8? Se Chan is unlucky.
Let's go with number 8.
It's number 8.
I hope they get a flour bomb
right away.
- I know.
- Three flour bombs.
It will be so funny.
- One, two, three.
- Flour.
- What?
- There is something inside.
- Something came out.
- Zero percent.
- One percent.
- Okay.
- They got one percent.
- Go.
- They should keep going.
- Let's go with number ten.
- Let me pick it just once.
- Number 35.
- Let's have Se Chan pick it.
- Sure.
- Number 3.
- Number 3?
- How about number 4?
- Number 4?
Okay. We will live if we try to die.
- Let's go with number 3.
- Number 3?
Number 4 and number 3.
Can we open them at the same time?
- No.
- No?
Open one at a time.
What kind of nonsense is that?
For goodness' sake.
Had that been allowed,
we would have gone together.
- We would have gone together.
- This one?
- Can I open them with both hands?
- That was nonsense.
- Not number four?
- Let's go with this one.
- Let's go with number four.
- All right then.
- Number four.
- Go.
- I don't think it's number 4.
- Go with number 3.
- Number three.
- For goodness' sake.
One, two, three.
Flour.
- One percent.
- One percent. Go.
- We now have two percent.
- Go.
- One percent per person.
Let's open number four.
Number four? Okay.
We will live if we try to die.
- One, two, three.
Two percent.
- Two percent.
- Go or stop?
- We now have four percent.
- Go.
- This had better be a bomb.
- I hope they lose it all.
- Then it will be redistributed.
- Seriously.
- Lose it all.
- Please.
- A flour bomb.
- Shall we go with number ten?
- Let's go with number 10.
- All right. Gather around.
- Number ten.
All right.
One, two, three.
No way.
- Two percent.
- Two percent. We have six percent.
- Go.
- Two percent.
- How did it happen?
- Go.
Will you keep going?
They are unbelievable.
- They are getting lucky.
- I am impressed with their guts.
I would have stopped no matter what.
If they gather the shares
and get a flour bomb in the end...
- Haha, how about number 22?
- Okay.
- Number 22. It's a good number.
- I am a bit nervous.
- Come. Number 22.
- Number 22.
- Let's go.
- So far, the odds are good.
A flour bomb.
Number 22, let's go.
- One, two, three.
- Flour.
I shouldn't have teamed up
with an unlucky punk.
- One, two, three.
- Flour.
(They got a flour bomb.)
- I got unlucky.
- That's it.
That's it.
(Laughing)
Why did you pick number 22?
Redistribute the six percent.
- Why did you pick number 22?
- You had gathered 6 percent.
Since a flour bomb went off,
we will put the shares
in other pinatas.
- Turn in 2 percent each.
- Okay.
- A flour bomb went off.
- Here goes the eldest son.
- Will you go in there?
- I will go in there.
- Let's go.
- Here goes the eldest son.
- I...
- I am bankrupt.
So Min and I will go again.
- We will go again.
It's meaningless
unless I place first.
- It's over.
- Soonbak Investment is over.
- Finally...
- Soonbak Investment...
- is out of business.
- Se Chan is done.
The youngest one...
- is done.
- I am done.
(Se Chan went bankrupt.)
I was nearly there.
Will the eldest son go in?
Is it better to go now
or after another round?
- He would stop after a big prize.
- A big prize.
- I am not the type to take risks.
- I would stop after a big prize.
- Do you want to go?
- Then I will go first.
- My goodness.
- Will you go first?
- He is showing his ambition.
- The eldest son.
Unless I place first,
it's meaningless.
I will stop after opening
15 pinatas.
Fifteen pinatas?
The odds would be crazy.
The eldest's hope.
(He's been keeping his position
without any performance.)
The eldest.
(He's been keeping his position
without any performance.)
Because he's the eldest?
Suk Jin is gambling big time.
The eldest son chose number 14.
The eldest.
The eldest's privilege.
- Yes. It's two percent.
- Okay.
- Awesome.
- Five percent.
- It's two.
- It's the other way around.
- What are you doing?
- Two percent.
- It was upside down.
- Suk Jin.
(He begins
with dim sight and 2 percent.)
- Number 11.
- Next to the bomb...
You don't know how the show works.
They never leave a bomb
next to a bomb.
We didn't know.
- Get ready.
- You need to step forward.
- You were right. It's five percent.
- Five percent.
- Awesome.
- Okay!
(Suk Jin is getting closer
to his big picture.)
This is bad.
Seven. I'm still hungry.
- Please let it be a bomb.
- Seven percent.
There's still a big shot left.
- It's getting nervous.
- The big one still remains.
If I hit the jackpot, I'll stop.
- It's the flour.
- What are you doing?
- He's amazing.
- I don't think...
- Have you decided it?
- there's flour here.
- What's the number?
- It's 17.
Okay. It's the lucky number.
- Flour.
(What about this time?)
He failed.
(It's flour.)
- Why didn't he stop?
- He failed.
You should've stopped.
Didn't you get seven?
You should've stopped
after getting seven percent.
(Suk Jin got 7 percent, but he lost
everything for being greedy.)
- Is he left with nothing now?
- That was amazing.
- Suk Jin has nothing now.
- His car rental...
- is closed as of today.
- Seven percent.
- That was a bummer.
- You should've stopped...
- after seven percent.
- He's got nothing.
It's my turn now.
It's about time to get covered with flour,
Mr. Major Shareholder.
I can't believe he's shopping alone.
- That's cool.
- He must have so much.
Once you grab it, it's over.
Okay. Here.
- Number 28.
- One, two, three.
- It's 14.
- How did he find it?
- It's 14 percent.
- Is it 14?
(Jae Suk found 14 percent at once.)
- It's 14 percent.
- How is that possible?
Is it 14?
It's 14.
- It's 14.
- It's 14 percent.
That upsets me.
- Are you stopping?
- It's noblesse oblige.
- I'd stop if I were you.
- What happened?
Do it again.
- Do it again.
- Stop.
- No.
- Keep going.
- Stop.
- Stop. There are still more.
- Seriously.
So Min and me.
That's awesome. 14 percent.
That's awesome.
If you lend us three,
we'll go hit the jackpot.
We'll go together.
If you lend us, I'll take him too.
No, that's not right.
- Haha.
- Stay quiet, you unfortunate boy.
My brother will kill you.
- Fight for real.
- Yes.
If you give me three,
I'll take them with me.
- I'll go with him.
- If you take me...
- Give us three.
- You should go together.
- Okay.
- We'll pay you back.
- Here are three.
- Got it.
- Thank you.
- I got it.
- We have 15.
- Let's go there after this.
- It's 39.
- Just trust me.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
Seriously. It's so annoying.
Jae Suk.
(It's flour again.)
What is this?
Lend me five.
So Min. Let's go for number 24.
- One, two, three.
- Flour.
- It's 11 percent.
- Let's open one more.
- One more?
- I'm going to be rich.
- Let's take it to the end.
- Let's go!
- Please.
One, two, three.
(It's flour again.)
Let's shout "rich."
- Rich.
One, two, three.
(They face ruin in the end.)
(Jumping)
It's a festival.
- We should do it now.
- About five...
It upsets me so much.
- Jae Suk. I'll join them.
- I'll give it to you.
Go away.
Let me play for the last time.
Those beggars.
- Hey...
- I was the major shareholder.
I was the major shareholder,
but I hung out with beggars.
That So Min beggar and I...
Hey. So Min.
(Looking pitiful)
You...
(Blaming)
How many are there left?
Two jackpots and two flour.
- Two jackpots and two flour.
- See?
We just need to hit the jackpot.
(There are 4 pinatas left.)
(Among them, only 2 are jackpots.)
- Two jackpots?
- Yes.
Two flour?
Among the four?
It's a 50-50 chance.
- I can't do it.
- We have to do it.
- Give us a chance.
- Because I hung out with beggars...
- We have to do it.
Jae Suk.
- We're family.
- Hey.
- Give me one last chance.
- Go away.
Oh, Jae Suk.
Hey. Shall petty shareholders
gather together?
We just need to make 15.
- How many do you have?
- Three.
- I have two.
- I have four.
- Four? If we're going to play...
- You should work together.
Jae Suk.
Just one more round.
- It's heavy.
- It looks heavy.
Right?
Do you think this is light?
This is ambiguous.
The two feel different.
Yes. Hang on.
- The way they shake...
- They shake.
It looks about right.
You can't shake them.
- Okay.
- They're heavier.
- Why are you shaking them?
- I want to leave.
- No way.
- You should leave.
- It's a 50-50 chance.
Two flour and two jackpots.
Twelve? 35?
- Yes.
- Let's go for it.
Whatever.
You touched it already.
One, two, three.
(Number 35 was a dud.)
- Jae Suk. Give me one last chance.
- Jae Suk. Just this once.
- I'll do anything you say.
- It's your era.
Please.
The jackpot is guaranteed.
You're the energy of Soonbak.
It hit me right in the face.
I can't believe it ends here.
You look like a white tiger.
Thank you.
- I'm going in again.
- How many do you have?
- After this, I have 17.
- Let me go play.
Seven.
- How many do you have?
- I have three.
If anyone with two joins us,
we can go in.
- I have two.
- Come join us.
- The four of us should go.
- What?
We're going in.
- There's only one bomb.
- Suk Jin.
- Can you let me in for once?
- Let's remove two.
Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin. Please let me play.
- Let me join you.
No. We collected everything we got.
- We have four people already.
- The major beggars must leave.
- Thank you, Suk Jin.
Go away, you beggars.
- Go away.
- Let us join you just this once.
Let's just do it.
- Six people.
- Let's go for 6 and 7.
- How about 6 and 7?
- Hey.
Here we go.
Haha. Come here.
One, two, three.
(Will the petty shareholders
turn the tables?)
Two, three.
- Okay.
- What is it?
It's 22.
- Okay.
- What is it?
(They hit the jackpot.)
It's a jackpot.
(Jealous)
- Let's do one more.
- How many are there left?
One 16 percent.
- It's one of the two, right?
- Yes.
- One is flour and that's the other?
- Let's come back.
- Let's go for it.
- No.
- We have to go for it.
They should go for it.
You need to go for it right away.
Suk Jin. Let's stick to 22 percent.
- Stick to it?
- Yes.
- Let's come back.
- Okay.
- You weak cowards.
- Stop.
How many do I get?
- What?
- Right. You should stop.
Honestly, you should take less.
Let's split them.
I don't mind taking less.
- We'll split them.
- You may split them.
The major shareholder
should distribute them.
- Wait.
- Let me do it.
- I'm the major shareholder.
- She should take them.
The major shareholder
should distribute them.
- You should distribute them.
- Okay.
- How many do we get?
- We got 22.
Take four first.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- That's fair.
- This is enough for me.
- Four times five.
I'm good.
Here's one more
for the one you lost earlier.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Done.
- It was 22. Okay.
(Happy ending)
- It's the last chance.
- It's really the last chance.
- I feel confident.
- There's a number I have in mind.
- We'll only succeed.
- Jae Suk. Help us.
- We won't fail.
Give us one more chance.
- Jae Suk.
- They...
- It's the last round.
keep telling me to play.
- Jae Suk.
- I said no.
- Just this once.
- You're the energy of Soonbak.
- They've gone crazy.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
- Good. Haha, come here.
- Seriously.
- Okay.
- Let's hit the jackpot.
- Haha.
- Which one is it?
- I'll hit the jackpot tonight.
- Seriously, these kids.
- It's all about one shot.
How can you manage the company
like that?
We'll turn the tables.
Haha. Do you think it's number six?
- It's not number six.
- No?
- Number 36.
- Stay still.
We were going to choose
number six next.
- What if we went for it?
- Go for number six.
- I'll give you the chance.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Not her.
She's possessed.
She needs an exorcism.
She's darn unfortunate. It's crazy.
Go away!
Go away, you prick.
She looks like a ghost right now.
They've lost their minds.
- This is why...
- One last chance.
- This is why gambling is scary.
- Right.
- It's really scary.
- Yes.
You should've gone for it.
Number 36 won't move.
- Look.
- Number six.
- The line is long.
- We'll go for number six.
Okay. They'll go for number six.
Number six.
One, two, three.
- It's 16.
- It's 16. Good.
(They succeed
in drawing 16 percent.)
- I'm lucky.
- Number six.
We should've gone for number six.
- It was a jackpot.
Let's bring in the heir board.
This is so much fun.
I shouldn't team up with So Min.
Do you all remember Soonbak's motto?
- Yes.
What is it?
Everything depends on luck,
not effort.
It's
"Everything depends on luck, not effort."
I got it. Give me one.
I still got it.
I was the first one to say it.
Why do I want it so badly?
I can pull it all day. I love it.
- Me too.
- Why is it so fun?
It was
"Everything depends on luck, not effort."
We'll decide the heir
by following the motto.
Numbers 1 to 100 are written
on the heir board.
You'll put as many stickers
as your share.
We'll draw a number,
and the person's name on the number...
will become Soonbak's chairman
and vice chairman.
- Okay.
Your chances are so high.
The person with the most shares
will put his name first.
I'll reveal the share ratio.
- Why would you?
- It's Jae Suk.
The person with
the most shares is...
Jae Suk with 45 percent.
- He has nearly half.
- He took most of them.
- That's amazing.
- Next is Shin Rok.
Second place goes to Kim Shin Rok
with 16 percent.
She has 16 percent.
There are more than one third place.
- With eight percent...
- Did I place third?
He placed third.
Song Ji Hyo, Yang Se Chan,
and Ji Suk Jin.
We borrowed so many.
- Well done.
- I placed last.
Next is So Min with six percent.
Next is Jong Kook with five percent.
Last place goes to Haha
with four percent.
- Darn it.
- Go away.
I was once a major shareholder.
Wasn't he a major shareholder?
I was a major shareholder,
but after I met these devils...
He kept paying the penalty.
- It's upsetting.
- That was hilarious.
- That was funny.
- That's life.
- You never know.
- My goodness.
(Laughing)
It's annoying.
- Right. Draw a line.
- Really?
Are you going diagonal?
- That's a good idea.
- Yes.
- X? That's cool.
- Draw an X like a bingo.
- That's 20.
- That's cool.
- I know.
- It's nice to have a lot.
- He still has many left.
- That's 20.
- Thirty six.
- Do I put it anywhere?
I'll draw one more here.
Eight is mine.
Fifty six.
I'm taking seven.
Sure. Take it.
Shin Rok.
- Take it.
- Ji Hyo.
What if Jae Suk doesn't become one?
- That might happen.
- That's also his luck.
I'm getting nervous.
Will I become lucky?
(Who will become the owner
of Soonbak?)
In the end, it's a family fight.
(Who will become the owner
of Soonbak?)
- Is this the chairman?
- Yes.
The first number becomes
the vice chairman.
The second number becomes
the chairman.
- The first one is the chairman.
- The vice chairman.
- The first one's the vice chairman?
- They both might be his number.
What if he gets both numbers?
Then he'll take both positions.
- Really?
- Okay.
Go.
- But as a major shareholder,
- Pick one.
the first number should be
the chairman for a higher chance.
- You're right.
- That makes sense.
- If you say so.
- Am I right?
Who will pick the number?
The guest?
- The guest?
- Okay.
- Are we picking the chairman?
- It's the chairman.
- The chairman?
- The chairman.
- We'll pick the chairman.
- Are we picking the chairman?
- Yes.
- The guest will pick one.
- It's mine.
Jae Suk. Don't complain.
- Of course.
- Don't complain later.
- Number 74.
- He can't help it.
- Okay.
- It should be my number.
- The chairman.
- Number 74.
(Jae Suk was on a roll
with his extreme luck.)
- How is that possible?
- It's 14.
(He even stopped himself
unlike usual.)
(Will Jae Suk with 45 percent
become the chairman?)
You never know.
- Lady luck is never on my side.
- You never know.
- Number 14.
- That means I'm unfortunate.
- Stay still.
- I'm nervous.
- What is it?
- Will I be lucky?
The chairman?
What's the number?
- Number 9.
Yang Se Chan.
I'm the chairman.
- Number nine.
- What?
(Chairman Yang Se Chan)
I'm the chairman.
- That's unbelievable.
- I won.
- He...
- I'm the chairman.
(A bolt out of the blue)
(Jae Suk failed even though
he has 45 percent.)
The youngest son is the chairman.
He was a beggar.
How many do you have?
- He only has ten percent.
- Four?
- You never know.
- Chairman Yang.
You must not forget me.
I let you join at the end.
Chairman Yang.
- Don't forget I gave you one more.
- Well done.
- You never know.
- Chairman Yang.
- How is that possible?
You know I let you join at the end.
- Of course, I know.
- You know?
Chairman Yang.
- Se Chan.
- Chairman Yang.
- You're amazing.
- How dare you.
You're truly amazing.
Let's pick the vice chairman.
- You're awesome.
- Oh, my.
How did you pick that
of all numbers?
- Does it make sense?
- Pick one, sir.
- Pick one.
- Now, it's the vice chairman.
- Let me pick one.
- If I don't become one...
You're picking your assistant.
- I have so many shares.
- Please pick number 87.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- What is it?
- The number is...
Tell me the first number.
- The first number.
- Two digits or one?
- Two digits.
- What's the first number?
- All right.
- Fifty...
- Gosh.
- I'm not there.
- It's Jae Suk.
- Fifty.
- It's you.
- It's Jae Suk.
- There's no tension at all.
- The vice chairman.
- He became the vice chairman.
- Only if I didn't switch it.
Hey. Go be his assistant.
- Hurry up.
- Congratulations.
The chairman to lead
Soonbak Group is...
- Yang Se Chan.
- You're amazing.
- It's honey.
- It's meat.
Korean beef for the chairman.
Luxury honey for the vice chairman.
(Prime Korean beef and honey
for the chairman and vice chairman)
- Let's hear from the chairman.
- Yes.
Thank you.
How did that beggar
become the chairman?
- I'm the chairman.
- He doesn't look like one.
It's the same as the drama.
Song Joong Ki takes all at the end.
- He's the youngest.
- "Song Joong Ki."
You look so different
from the drama.
- I may look different.
- He's the real life version.
I didn't become the chairman alone.
You all helped me.
- Right.
- It's amazing.
He even learned a lesson.
- There was none.
The first number was supposed
to be the vice chairman.
- He changed it.
- But you changed it.
Everything depends on luck,
not effort.
Shin Rok joined us today.
It was so much fun.
- Thank you.
- Tell us what you thought about it.
It was so much fun. It snowed.
I haven't played in the snow for so long.
It was so much fun.
Let's give it up for Shin Rok again.
- Thank you.
Well done.
(2023, the Year of Rabbit)
(13 rabbits gathered.)
(IVE is here.)
(Ga Eul, Jang Won Young, An Yoo Jin,)
(Rei, LIZ, LEESEO)
You're so pretty.
(I know I'm pretty.)
(The earnest and bold
variety show idols...)
(and pro entertainers volunteer
to become their role models.)
(The national MC approaches
them smoothly.)
Were you popular back in school?
I had no friends.
(I see.)
(Time to check their talents)
(Blowing)
This is your last chance.
(Even the national MC struggles
to lead the show.)
(He turns over a new leaf.)
Say pass if you don't count.
Pass.
(It's going to be a long day today.)
Bunny.
(The two groups never get along.)
(Will they become friends?)
(Despite the chaos,)
there's one rabbit
with no liver hiding.
(Who's the intruder
that fooled everyone?)
(Rabbit with No Liver)