(Please dress
for a vacation this week.)
(2 days before the shoot)
(Jae Suk's stylist says, "Okay."
Jong Kook's stylist says, "Okay.")
(Suk Jin's stylist says, "Okay."
Haha's stylist says, "Okay.")
(Ji Hyo's stylist says, "Okay."
So Min's stylist says, "Okay.")
(Se Chan's stylist says, "Okay.")
(And on the day of the shoot,)
(the weather forecast said
it would rain.)
(Summer rain wets Namhansanseong
as the weather forecast said.)
- Hello.
The rain feels refreshing.
Good morning.
- It's early summer.
- I'm doing this for Kwang Soo.
Seok Sam, you come here.
- Why am I Seok Sam?
- Hello.
Seok Sam. Aren't you a kid?
- I'm not a kid.
- Hello.
I thought you were a kid.
- Today...
- Vacation?
- We are going on a vacation,
- Yes.
but I guess
there was a misunderstanding.
Why? This is for a vacation.
Come here. I'll hold you.
I'm good at holding babies.
- There, there.
Good boy. You're such a good boy.
- He's a good boy.
- He looks lovely.
- You are strong.
- What?
I'm strong enough
to hold you upside down.
- And I can even spin you.
- I'm very impressed.
I thought you were our new member.
- I know.
- Will you join us?
- Join us.
- We're looking for new members.
I'm not cutting the hair
on the back of my neck.
- Why not?
- To replace Kwang Soo?
Someone has to do it.
That's right.
I should grow a mustache then.
- It looks like So Min is...
- I know.
- Is this a sheep ranch or what?
- She's doing a photoshoot.
- She's all dressed up.
- She's serious about this.
Are you shooting a drama here?
(A delusional girl
who wore a sundress on a rainy day.)
I thought you guys
would all dress up.
But I was surprised that
you all dressed normally.
- You know we never dress up.
- Hey.
- What?
- You're dressed to go to a gym.
This is how I look
when I go on a picnic.
His shirt has yellow on it.
- See? It's bright.
- This is how he always looks.
- It's bright, isn't it?
- Let me be honest.
I must say this...
as an entertainer.
- It's a cliche created by TV shows.
- I agree.
- Our stylists...
- Right.
- should think about that.
- Sure.
Just look at her.
- We don't dress up like So Min.
- Don't use words like "cliche."
- They're getting flustered.
- Cliche?
Cliche?
Cliche.
Doesn't that mean it's awkward?
I think...
- only five of us know the meaning.
- What's wrong with you?
Only five of us know what it means.
His yellow eyes were staring at me.
"Look at him."
Suk Jin.
Even if we make fun of Suk Jin,
- he won't yell at us today.
- Why not?
He needs to take care of his voice.
He has to sing.
- No.
- So, today...
- Why would you say that?
- No matter how much we tease him,
What a great singer.
he will never...
This is crazy.
- My gosh. You...
- What a great singer.
On YouTube,
he stopped ripping off name tags...
- and started singing.
- All of a sudden?
He doesn't even raise his voice.
(How the super rookie saves
his voice)
- He's saving his voice.
- I knew you would bring that up.
You should wear something
around your neck
- What do you do?
- Wear something around your neck.
- No, no.
- MSG?
We start fighting here and there
as soon as we meet.
I'm recording a song today.
- Are you recording it today?
- Today...
So what are we doing today?
I heard it has something to do
with vacations.
Today,
- we are going on an early vacation.
- Okay.
And we have two delightful women
who will enjoy the vacation with us.
- Delightful women?
Two delightful women.
(Who are the delightful women?)
That looks amazing.
It's the van only for stars.
I want to go on a vacation
with my family in that van.
There's the product placement van.
Who are they?
- They must be stars.
- They are here.
Who are they?
(Who are the stars in the van?)
Isn't that Chae Young?
Han Chae Young? My gosh.
- Who are they?
- Han Chae Young?
It's been so long.
Isn't she Young Ji?
- It's Young Ji.
- My gosh.
(The two guests for the vacation!)
Han Chae Young?
- She's a delightful woman.
- "Delightful Girl, Chun Hyang."
They're dressed according to
the cliche created by TV shows.
- Hey.
- It's the cliche from TV shows.
Come on here.
Hello, Young Ji.
- How have you been?
- Hey, Young Ji. Welcome.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time.
- Stand in the middle.
- This is my first time seeing them.
- Young Ji.
This is too much.
Did you get your bangs cut
at a barbershop?
Young Ji and Chae Young.
Before we start...
I think I'm the only one
who heard this.
- What?
- What's the matter?
- Chae Young.
Don't be surprised.
"Hey, isn't she..."
"the living BB cream?"
BB cream?
(The living BB cream)
What?
He meant a Barbie doll.
- A Barbie doll?
- Suk Jin, it's a Barbie doll.
(When the guests first appeared)
(Suk Jin, Yellow Eyes,
"Isn't she the living BB cream?")
- My gosh.
- Hello.
(Casually greeting the BB cream)
What was that?
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
- That's how we greet guests.
- The living BB cream?
You should get used to it.
The living BB cream?
The living BB cream.
I meant...
I meant she has glowing skin.
He sounded so urgent.
He wanted to say something
that he knew first.
(He wanted to show
what he knows about the guests.)
The living BB cream.
I can't think of proper words
these days.
- It's driving me nuts.
- The living BB cream.
I've never met her before.
(She's a Barbie doll with
glowing skin and great proportions.)
I'm going nuts. What do we do?
- He meant she has good skin.
- Of course.
Pure skin.
They are our guests
for the Vacation Special.
It's been so long
since the last time we met them.
We have Han Chae Young and Young Ji!
(Han Chae Young and Young Ji
are here for the Vacation Special.)
By the way,
isn't this your first time
on our show, Chae Young?
- This is my first time.
- I knew it.
- Really?
- Seriously?
This is my first time.
Thank you for having me.
You know I fit right in
with the summer vacation vibe.
Is that why you asked me here?
(What?)
Wow, the living BB cream!
It speaks!
- The BB cream speaks!
The BB cream is so pretty.
"Is that why you asked me here?"
(Unlike her cool looks,
she sounds somewhat frivolous.)
So we have the living BB cream,
Han Chae Young.
- We also have the Youngji Mushroom.
- Hello.
- I'm Young Ji.
- She's so cute.
- It's been a long time.
This is my first time as well.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Then where did we meet?
I saw you on many different shows.
- I see.
- Why am I talking casually to you?
Where did I see her?
- We met a lot.
- I saw her a lot.
So this is your first time
on our show.
How did you feel
when you got a call from us?
I'm feeling nervous to be
on public TV after a long time.
Are you?
I've only been
on YouTube channels lately.
And it feels strange
to see Se Chan here.
- Why?
- Where did you see him?
- I host "Comedy Big League."
- That's right.
- Oh, right.
- So I see her...
- every week.
- We meet every week.
In the show, he sounds like...
- "Hey, guys."
- Hey!
Hey! Don't do that.
That's what he does.
- Gosh, that's annoying.
- But here...
- He acts like a leader.
- He's really...
(He acts like a leader.)
At "Comedy Big League,"
there's no one above me.
- Are you the senior?
- Yes, I am.
But you look like the youngest one.
- I'm the youngest here.
- He's the youngest here.
He's the youngest one here.
So he bosses people around
over there.
I should boss him around here today.
- That's...
- For Young Ji to see.
I'd like them to lift up the mood...
with their hit songs.
- My hit songs?
- Oh, right.
- Unnies.
- She was a member of Unnies.
- That's right.
- With Sook.
Do you remember the dance moves?
No, I don't.
(She says she doesn't remember,
but her eyes...)
Will she remember?
She gave me the chills.
(She passes her hat.)
She's changed.
(He takes it anyway.)
- You took it naturally.
- BB cream!
The BB cream is stepping up!
- The living BB cream.
The living BB cream.
Something is a bit strange.
(She starts dancing to the rhythm.)
(Somewhat clumsy)
What is this?
What was that?
- What?
- It's a little slow.
It's somewhat...
(Her moves are listless
like sweaty BB cream.)
But her dance is...
She's not a good dancer though.
(Only does well on
the signature dance move)
I love this song. It's a good song.
There she goes.
(Charging)
(Swinging her hips as if she's squeezing
a tube of BB cream)
She's charming.
- That was fun.
- What is this?
It was fun. You know what?
When Chae Young passed this to me,
- I expected something amazing.
- Me too.
I never imagined
that she'd dance like this.
(The Barbie doll showed
rather frivolous dance moves.)
I expected something amazing.
I've never seen Ji Hyo
look so confident before.
- I can pull this off.
- Sure.
- Actually,
- She can pull that off.
Chae Young was a member
of a girl group.
- But Young Ji here...
- She's really good.
- She was an idol member.
- She's an idol artist.
She was a member of KARA.
- Can you show us, Young Ji?
- Sure.
I've never seen
Young Ji dance before.
(Youngji Mushroom's dance)
This is great.
(Her energy is a bit different
from the living BB cream.)
This is nice. Great.
- Let's go.
- Cool.
Go, Youngji Mushroom!
(Youngji Mushroom steps up.)
(Shocked)
(Startled)
She has resentment.
She's dancing out of resentment.
(Youngji Mushrooms are even better
than organic pine mushrooms.)
- That's right. She was an idol.
- Wow.
- She's good.
- She's great.
There you go!
(Her hips announce
her comeback as an idol star.)
- It's her original job.
- She's different.
She's really good.
She's good at her original job.
It's not over.
Mamma Mia!
(The variety show peddler's energy
on public TV)
- Nice expressions!
- She didn't forget the moves.
I love her facial expressions.
(All the men fall for Young Ji.)
(Youngji Mushroom is in season.)
She's still got the moves.
This is so cool.
- She's an idol artist.
- Dominate the cameras.
- She's...
- Stare at the jimmy jib.
She doesn't dance like that
on cable channels.
- To the jimmy jib.
- She does that only on public TV.
She's dominating the jimmy jib.
(Young Ji's dance came to public TV
for a vacation.)
That's who she is!
- She's so good.
- She's so energetic on public TV.
You don't do this on cable TV.
- You're not like this on tvN.
- I didn't know she'd dance so well.
- Her face changed right away.
- She was so serious.
Chae Young might feel like
Young Ji is trying...
to make fun of her.
It's not like that.
- I just thought...
- Right. She made her look bad.
I was just relieved
that I danced first.
I can't dance after this.
But this is all I can remember.
- I know.
- I could tell that...
- Young Ji sure was an idol artist.
- She's good.
- She couldn't hide it.
- How did she not forget it?
I miss KARA. I really do.
- He's seriously not talking today.
- That's not true.
- He's trying to save his voice.
- Right?.
I'm just waiting
for the right time to join in.
This is where
you should cheer for them.
- Right.
- I did cheer for them.
- Something like "Gosh."
- But I did.
- You should say something.
- No, it's not true.
I was just surprised.
- He's a singer just like her.
- That's not it.
- They're your seniors.
- Then why don't we...
- shout out loud together?
- Good.
Shout out loud.
Let's shout Running Man.
1, 2, 3.
- Running Man!
- You didn't shout.
- Make it louder.
- I did.
- I can't believe this.
He's the worst since Myung Soo.
- It's not like that.
- He's the worst.
- He's just like Myung Soo.
- This is what Myung Soo did.
Myung Soo wasn't this bad though.
(He's the worst since Myung Soo
who didn't say "Challenge.")
You should speak.
I'm doing things the same as usual.
- Just be comfortable...
- That's awkward.
This is so awkward.
Suk Jin, you're not yourself today.
His head is full of
"How Do You Play?"
- That's not true.
- Seriously, he's...
It's not like that.
Even "How Do You Play?"
doesn't want you to be like this.
(Too much affection puts
the show's host on the spot.)
- I'm trying my best.
- Why does he...
keep messing with my shows?
That was my mistake.
(Crocodile tears on the quiz show,)
(too much affection
on the playing show)
Today is the Delightful Men
and Women's Vacation Race.
You will have missions
for the vacation bonus.
You'll be divided into three teams.
You can't go on a vacation with
more than five people these days.
That's right.
So you'll be split into teams
of 4, 4, and 1.
- 4, 4, and 1?
- Only one person?
- 4 people?
The 1-person team will be decided
through a game.
Even if you go solo,
you can win with a good strategy.
So don't give up.
The 1-person team will be so lonely.
At the end of each mission,
there will be a Mr. Unpleasant Poll
where you choose the worst member.
- Mr. Unpleasant?
- Oh, my.
We already chose
Mr. Unpleasant in the beginning.
- We sure did.
- Because of his BB cream joke...
His BB cream joke made him...
- I mean, why are you doing this?
- He wouldn't say.
Why suddenly change
the style of our show?
What's with this poll?
Even his tone of voice
sounds annoying too.
- Indeed.
- My gosh.
- He's so annoying.
- His tone of voice is...
Stop trying to speak politely!
Who speaks like that
on a variety show?
You'll end up bowing like this
when you say hello.
- Gosh.
- Why is he so funny these days?
- I mean, just speak as usual.
- Gosh, seriously.
With every Mr. Unpleasant Poll,
two people who get
the most votes will get a penalty.
We'll spin a roulette with the names
of the other seven people,
and the person who is chosen
will receive the vacation fund.
The winner will get
a cash prize today.
Each of you will receive...
a different amount of vacation funds
according to the game results.
All of you will begin
with 50 dollars.
- It triples if you win first place.
- It triples?
It doubles if you win second place.
Since you will team up
with different people in each round,
if you win 1st place in every round,
you'll get 27 times more money.
That means you can get
up to 1,350 dollars.
(The maximum amount
they can get is 1,350 dollars!)
- That's the maximum?
- I should do my best.
- Then let's divide you into teams.
- Okay.
A 1-person team
could be better than four.
We need to know
what games we'll play.
- What's this?
- It's like the ladder game.
- I guess that car will decide.
- It follows a black line, right?
- Yes.
- How do we play this game?
I guess that car will follow
one of those lines.
- By itself? It moves by itself?
- I think it will follow a line.
The mission for choosing
the 1-person team is...
That car follows a black line...
- using a sensor in it.
- It has a sensor in it.
- That's fascinating.
- That car?
Write down your names
at the end of the nine lines.
The person chosen by the car
will be the 1-person team.
- The person that the car chooses?
- Correct.
Then here... I'll write Haha's name.
Jong Kook, Seok Sam,
So Min, the living BB cream,
Youngji Mushroom, Ji Hyo,
- Jae Suk, and Se Chan.
- Jae Suk.
Here we go.
- We'll do this just once!
- Yes.
- Here we go.
- That's so fascinating.
- My, this is fascinating.
- Oh, wow.
(Se Chan, Jae Suk, Ji Hyo,
Young Ji, Chae Young)
(So Min, Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Haha)
- It's following the line.
- This is state-of-art.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- This is so amazing.
- Keep going.
- Go right. Go right!
- Seok Sam!
- Gosh, seriously.
- Go right.
- Go right!
- It started moving already.
Where will it go?
That's great.
(Where will the train that carries
everyone's desires stop?)
- Let's go.
- This is so amazing.
- Keep going.
- Go right. Go right!
- Go right.
(The train turns left
where there isn't Seok Sam's name.)
(1 of these 4 will be
the 1-person team.)
- Let's go.
- This is so amazing.
- Keep going.
- Go right. Go right!
- Ji Hyo!
- It's Ji Hyo.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my. Ji Hyo?
- Oh, no. It's Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo will go alone?
- What is she going to do?
- Oh, no.
(The wishes of Seok Sam's fans
didn't come true in the end.)
- Can't we try it again?
- But...
- You know...
- Wouldn't that be better?
- It's Ji Hyo.
- I think we should try it again.
Let us try it again.
- Ji Hyo will be so lonely.
- Let's try again.
- It goes to the same line.
- This one is a little darker.
- Then...
- How about we make them darker?
- Shall we?
- Yes. Draw a line on top of them.
Right. Fill that area.
- Oh, that area?
- That's Seok Sam's line.
- Why?
- He drew only on Seok Sam's line.
(Only on Seok Sam's line.)
Only on Seok Sam's line.
- Suk Jin, why did you hit him?
- You're trying to make me alone.
- What's wrong with you?
- This is the last attempt.
- This is really the last attempt.
- Okay. Let's do this.
Hey, anyone can notice...
Even the viewers can tell
that it's darker than the others.
That's not true. Here we go.
We have to accept
the result this time.
Whoever is chosen this time,
- let's accept the result.
- Okay. I agree.
Okay, okay.
- Okay, okay.
- So Min, it turned toward yours.
Really? No,
I think it'll go toward Suk Jin's.
(Will the train go the way
they want it to?)
- Youngji Mushroom?
- No, no.
- It should be separated.
- You said it was the last attempt.
- Our guests are the exception.
(They get very calm
at the unwanted result.)
- Then just put it to a vote.
- She's our guest.
She's our guest, you know.
- Why are the guests an exception?
- Hold on.
- Hold on a second.
- Why is there a bump here?
Let's just close our eyes and...
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Wait and see.
- I'm fixing the names.
- We should fix the names.
- Write Seok Sam's name on the left.
- Okay.
That's better.
- Just tell me to do it.
- No.
Just tell me.
- We should keep it fair.
- It's a random choice.
- Stop pretending to be scientific.
- To be fair...
- Use plenty of nano-tech.
- I wonder who will be chosen.
(They play until
they get the result they want.)
- Just say it's me!
- Seok Sam.
- Suk Jin.
- I'll gladly do as you want.
Speak louder, will you?
I'm practically shouting, you punk!
- Louder than that.
- Speak even louder.
In a variety show tone!
- This is... So Min's line.
- That's... So Min, Ji Hyo.
- I'm so excited.
- Stop pretending it's fair.
We'll accept the result this time.
- This is fair.
- We won't manipulate the result.
Now it's fair.
- This is the real deal.
- This is driving me nuts.
My gosh. This is so exciting.
- Fine. All right.
- Seok Sam.
All right. I'll do it.
Okay. It's Seok Sam!
(With his fan's interference,
Seok Sam has been chosen!)
It's Seok Sam!
Why did we even do this?
Just take it to a vote.
- We couldn't let our guest...
- Or the director could've chosen.
be alone from the beginning.
- That's just an excuse.
- You know that.
- We'll change the teams each round.
- Do it just this time.
- Okay, okay.
- Don't worry.
- Then I will...
- It's coming up.
- I'll divide you into two teams.
- Suk Jin. Okay.
Divide them into 2 teams of 4.
Go ahead.
Today, we'll play games,
like on "Family Entertainment."
That's a good idea!
- Let's do this.
- "Let's check the scores!"
The teams will be divided by gender.
- Okay!
- Team Boy versus Team Girl.
Yes.
- We don't know what game it is.
- Right.
(Team Boy, Team Girl, Team Seok Sam)
Where should each team sit?
- Team Boy is on this side.
- Team Boy...
- We're divided by gender, right?
- Yes.
- "Family Entertainment."
- Gosh. I'm alone.
What?
What is this? There's a camera...
Oh, what's that?
- What is that?
- Will they observe us?
- He's in there.
- You see a lot of this in Gangnam.
Stop acting cute.
- You can take off your mask.
- Take off your mask.
(Laughing)
- Chae Young.
- What is it?
(She suddenly bursts out laughing.)
- What was that?
- What made you laugh?
What made you laugh?
- Exactly what made you laugh?
- Well...
I didn't know everyone except me was
wearing a mask earlier.
But this time, I was the only one
who was wearing it.
- Chae Young is...
- She has a unique sense of humor.
Chae Young is always
one step behind.
- She's funny.
- Exactly.
- She's always one tempo behind.
- She's really unique.
She saw that all of us were
wearing a mask.
So she put on a mask hastily.
And when we aren't wearing
a mask, she is wearing one.
- She's one tempo behind.
- I'm cute, right?
She said, "I'm cute, right?"
(I'm cute, right?)
"I'm cute, right?"
(She boosted the energy
with her unique tone of voice.)
Okay. The first mission
that will make your vacation...
- more fun and exciting is...
- Yes!
The Midday Dancers.
- "Dancers?"
- Oh, we're going to dance?
- Dancing?
- But this place is too...
(They must copy the dance moves
on the screen to win.)
- Oh, we're going to dance.
- Really?
But aren't they at an advantage?
Chae Young and Young Ji
have experience.
(An idol singer's groove)
I learned how to do that too.
- Show us.
- Oh, my.
- She's so stiff.
- She's dancing.
- Okay. Very stiff.
(Bowing)
- Ji Hyo.
- Look at Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo...
- She looked like she was bowing.
They're trying to get the drop
on me.
- That's nothing. We can do better.
- Of course.
- This is too easy for us.
- We can do this so easily.
They're good dancers too.
- Let's do that too.
- All right.
Let's do it. Here we go.
Here we go.
Stiff. Stiff.
(The wave encountered obstacles.)
I think Ji Hyo is
a little bit better than Chae Young.
- Right? I'm better than her, right?
- Yes.
- I'm better than Chae Young.
- What was that?
That's how we finish up.
- There are three teams in total.
- Yes.
2 teams will have a match at a time
and there are 3 rounds in 1 game.
- Okay.
- Three rounds?
One person from each team will
come forward to have a match.
But there's no one else
on Suk Jin's team.
- He'll represent his own team.
- Gosh. Why is it a dancing game?
Suk Jin, will it be okay?
You're a balladeer.
- It's okay.
- Exactly.
He's a balladeer?
- Balladeers hate dancing.
- True.
(The great balladeer's dance
can only be seen in this game.)
The 4-person teams can change
the player...
as many times as you want
during the song.
- Really?
- I see.
- That's great.
- Nice.
Maybe you will have to dance
the entire song.
(He already seems tired.)
The first match is
between Suk Jin and Team Girl.
(Team Suk Jin versus Team Girl)
- What song is it?
- The order of players is important.
Who will go first?
- If Chae Young comes out...
- Here.
Chae Young, you should go first.
- Chae Young will go first.
- Go, Living BB cream!
(The balladeer chose
the living BB cream.)
- Go, Living BB Cream!
- You can do it!
- We have the living BB cream!
Go, balladeer!
Go, living human being!
If Suk Jin sees it...
She looks like a samba dancer.
- Here you go.
- Let's begin.
She really looks
like the living BB cream.
Amazing!
- She's the living BB cream.
- Yes, she is.
The living BB cream looks amazing.
We'll start the game now.
It's started.
Step forward.
Oh, gosh.
- Suk Jin, raise your arms.
- You're doing great.
- That's great!
- Raise your arms!
Suk Jin, you should raise
your arms like that.
This is so difficult.
Hey, this is too difficult.
I can't keep up.
You know...
That's incredible.
- How...
- She keeps getting the blue one.
This doesn't make sense.
(Chae Young is doing well.)
You can actually learn choreography
by playing this game.
(His body is moving
in a disorderly manner.)
- How does it track their movements?
- There it goes.
Aren't there any Korean songs?
(The shaggy dog keeps failing.)
He's so bad at this.
You can do this, right?
Just repeat. It's the same moves.
(Team Girl's 1st change of players)
(Here comes Song Jeoktoma.)
Ji Hyo came out! Song Jeoktoma!
(Good)
That's great.
Here comes Song Jeoktoma!
Oh, wow. Ji Hyo is doing well.
Move powerfully.
(The shaggy dog is dancing
as he wants now.)
Ji Hyo, you're doing great!
- What is Suk Jin dancing?
- I know, right? What is he doing?
What is... What is that move?
(To the right, to the left)
What is he doing?
(He turned it into an old dance
in the end.)
- The balladeer is excited.
- Go, balladeer!
The excited balladeer.
My gosh. What dance move is that?
The ballad singer is excited!
(Shouting)
- What is he doing?
- He's just an excited old man.
What's going on?
(The balladeer became very excited.)
Yoo Yaho!
Am I doing it right?
(But he ran out of energy quickly.)
- There's a lot of purple ones.
- Don't press the button.
(She starts dancing abruptly.)
(As his daughter-in-law
is dancing excitedly...)
Why does he keep moving
in the opposite direction?
He keeps moving
in the opposite direction.
What are you doing now?
- You should face forward.
- Face forward.
- So Min, face forward.
- They're excited.
- So Min, look at the screen.
- Face forward.
You're not there
to show off your dance skills!
- Hey!
- Move aside. Move!
- A daughter-in-law...
- A daughter-in-law?
(Despite her help,
Suk Jin runs out of energy again.)
- And a father-in-law.
- The balladeer is doing well!
(Game over)
The balladeer...
- You see...
- I'm out of breath.
- It feels like a national holiday.
- I mean...
(It was neck and neck at the end.
How will the results turn out?)
(1st, Team Girl, 2nd, Team Suk Jin)
- What?
- The orange player won.
(Team Girl won.)
Really?
(He danced for his life but lost.)
Suk Jin, you kept moving
in the opposite direction.
- Did I?
- You couldn't dance precisely.
- You went up when they went down.
- Why didn't you look...
- at the screen?
- What's funny is...
- It wasn't like that.
- that they won by a small margin.
It's because I couldn't tell...
It was nice to see you dancing
with your daughter-in-law...
- after a long time.
- Exactly.
She kept blocking my view.
By the way,
Ji Hyo turned out to be the ace.
She's the ace of our team.
She's a dancing machine.
Let's begin the second round.
Team Suk Jin versus Team Boy.
Okay.
You should boost your energy.
Suk Jin, boost your energy.
- Boost your energy.
- Okay.
- Is Suk Jin going to play again?
- Get ready. Get your energy up.
- Start the game right now.
- That's great.
Excuse me, Director,
let the other two teams play first.
Left and right are reversed.
How do I do this?
(His vision is becoming blurry.
He keeps seeing the grim reaper.)
- The balladeer versus the producer!
- "The producer?"
- Yoo Yaho versus the balladeer.
- Yes.
You can do it!
- I don't think I can do this.
- Go for it!
- You can do this!
(Suk Jin, Jae Suk)
What is this?
- Get on your horse.
- What's this?
- This character is you.
- Like this?
- This one.
- What's this? My goodness.
- Oh, my.
(The racing horses start running!)
Giddy-up, giddy-up!
My gosh.
Try to dance on beat.
They're both doing well.
Up!
They're doing well.
You're doing great!
This is fun. This is fun.
- They're doing well.
- This is fun. This is fun.
(Knee kick)
Now to the other side.
(It somehow makes you want to
dance along.)
You're doing great!
- What's that?
- You should jump over him.
Jump over him. Jump.
(Suk Jin crashes into Jae Suk.)
- You're up.
- Here you go.
- Are we allowed to change players?
- Yes, let's switch.
What's going on?
Jump.
(He crashes into Jong Kook as well.)
Gosh.
(The old horse can't even get
1 leg over him.)
Why can't he jump over anyone?
Hop on!
(A piggyback ride)
- Move on to the next move.
- Come down.
This is so funny.
(Panting)
(Suk Jin is in critical condition
and can't even see clearly.)
A match between the boys and girls
would've been fun.
Run!
- That's good! Keep running.
- Jong Kook is enjoying this.
(Unlike the energetic owner,)
Okay!
Great!
- Run!
- Keep going!
(the shaggy dog follows
far behind him.)
Okay, let's go!
(The owner and the dog
run toward the climax.)
Oh, okay.
(The owner and the dog
run toward the climax.)
What? What's going on?
Run!
(The final spurt)
(Please... No more.)
Nice. That's good.
Superstar!
- Superstar!
- That was great!
Bravo!
- Bravo!
- That was great!
- Se Chan, help me lift him up.
- Oh, my.
- It's good exercise.
- Se Chan, help me lift him up.
- We... Is it us?
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- It's good exercise.
- Are you all right?
- Great.
- We won.
- We made it to the final?
- Okay!
- We won? I see.
Even his character on the screen
seemed tired too.
- Who won?
- We'll compete with Team Girl now.
- You see, this is...
- Young Ji.
(The final match begins right away!
Team Boy versus Team Girl)
Nice!
(Perfectly synchronized)
(Thanks to the former idol singer
Young Ji's great performance...)
We won.
Team Girl won.
(Team Girl won.)
- We won. We won.
- Great job!
- It was neck and neck.
- It was.
- You did a great job.
- Toward the end...
- Young Ji did so well.
- Right.
- She sure was an idol singer.
- As a result,
Team Girl that won 2 rounds
wins 1st place.
(Team Girl is in 1st place.)
Team Boy is in second place.
Oh, gosh. We lost.
Team Suk Jin is in third place.
- You see...
- Suk Jin, are you okay?
- It was hard enough for me...
- Are you okay?
to dance to the entire song.
But I had to play two rounds
without a break.
(He miraculously came back to life
after the intense match.)
Those on the winning team get
3 times as much as the fund.
- We got 150 dollars.
- The 2nd place gets double.
And the third place gets
the same amount.
Now, it's time to vote.
The 1-person team gets 4 votes.
The members of the other 2 teams
get 1 vote each.
You can vote for Mr. Unpleasant.
Everyone did well though.
Don't say that while looking at me.
Everyone is looking at me.
You showed off your dance skills
instead of playing the game.
- You were supposed to focus...
- I mean, she was...
- on the game. But you were like...
- Exactly.
- She got so excited.
- She showed off her dance skills.
And how she bit her lower lip was
extremely unpleasant.
- That's funny.
- I mean...
I hated how she bit her lower lip
while dancing.
Since I have 4 votes,
I'll give 1 person all my votes.
Okay.
No, I'll vote for two people.
Good. I wrote Suk Jin's name.
- Really?
- He's so unpleasant.
He was sitting next to me.
- Oh, okay.
- And it was very unpleasant.
- I'll cast all four votes for you.
- Okay.
Suk Jin's pale legs annoy me too.
- They're so unpleasant.
- They look so pale.
His sneakers annoy me as well.
Right? That pink color is too much.
Maybe I should go tanning.
Yes, I think you should.
- Okay.
- Turn it on...
and place the car in the center.
It may choose a line right away.
- Okay.
- It's random.
- All right.
- Right in the center?
Why are you putting it
toward my name?
It may move right away.
We can't predict it.
(The car moves
toward Haha and Young Ji!)
(Which of them will go solo?)
- Oh, my. It's Young Ji.
- It's Young Ji.
- Okay.
Then Young Ji is
on the one-person team this time.
I have a feeling
that she'll do well by herself.
- I think she'll do well.
- Exactly.
- Especially today.
- She's on her own.
- Young Ji, divide us into teams.
- Okay. I'll do that.
Then...
(Glancing)
- My hair...
- Suk Jin, she's looking at you.
What? Why?
I have blue hair on my head
from the wig.
It'd be funny if Suk Jin joined
that team alone, Young Ji.
- Considering his hormone levels...
- Please join this team.
- What?
- Please come.
- That team?
- Yes.
- That's great.
- I'm sure it's not just me.
- I'm sure of it.
- Are you serious?
- It will be interesting.
- They're all avoiding eye contact.
(The girls avoid making eye contact
as Suk Jin walks toward them.)
- Suk Jin...
- You're perfect for the team.
You're the most feminine of all
on that team.
- You're the cutest one.
- Right.
If you look only at his legs...
- He's perfect for the team.
- Well...
Since Se Chan and Haha seem to have
good chemistry...
Right. Separate them.
Se Chan and Chae Young,
switch teams.
- Chae Young.
- Really?
Now, we'll go and have lunch.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Oh, wow. It's very spacious.
- It smells like a new car.
It's good to be in the same car
as you guys.
The four of us have never been
on the same team, right?
- Oh, that's true.
- I think this is the first time.
- Right? I'm happy to be with you.
- I think so.
But honestly,
I really like this combination...
- as we're in different age groups.
- True.
Let's see how it turns out today.
If it works out well,
- we can team up again later.
- That wouldn't be so bad.
- But today,
- I like the idea.
Suk Jin is not as energetic
as usual.
He's refraining
from speaking loudly.
We would have a chance
if he can act like always.
- It's a shame. We teamed up...
- Hey, stop.
See? You should sound hoarse.
(Shouting)
You should sound hoarse like this.
Try it.
But we're inside the car right now.
- See?
- Right?
Who would speak so loudly in a car?
- My gosh.
- That's ridiculous.
Is it because of "How Do You Play?"
I'm disappointed.
We've been working together
for over ten years.
What are we to you, Suk Jin?
You didn't make this much effort
for our theme song "I Like You."
- I was so upset...
- That's different.
when I found out
that Suk Jin commented...
on the other members' posts
so often on social media.
- Whose posts?
- Like Wonstein and Lee Dong Hwi.
Has he ever commented
on our social media posts?
- Never.
- Right?
- Do you like Wonstein that much?
- It's not like that.
Let me explain.
They commented on my posts.
- I commented on your posts too.
- They commented so many times.
So I thought I should do the same
in return.
I think
Suk Jin is embarrassed by us.
- You're embarrassed by us, right?
- No, I'm proud of you guys.
He's practically whispering.
Your voice makes me feel sleepy...
- because you speak in whispers.
- You don't speak loudly in a car.
Gosh. I can't believe her.
Whenever you speak, I feel sleepy.
There are times
when you should speak loudly.
(It's hard to stay awake
because of his whispers.)
- I can't stay awake.
- Oh, Suk Jin.
- Hey, wake up.
- Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
- Hey, wake up!
- That's good, Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- Wake up!
I'm sorry.
Please speak a bit louder.
All right. Okay. I'll do that.
- That's more like it.
- Okay. Let's go!
Let's cheer up!
Suk Jin, drink a lot of water.
"Hyeonchon?" What is this place?
Are we at Namhansanseong?
- I can't hear him.
- Right?
- Me neither.
- Suk Jin.
- We can't hear you.
- Can you speak a little louder?
We really can't hear you.
Suk Jin, we can't hear you.
Why do you keep on mumbling?
- We can't hear you.
- We can't.
There's a certain volume
the show airs at.
A certain volume?
When it's edited,
my voice will sound louder.
The scheduling team?
I can't hear you.
The scheduling team
turns up your audio?
I really can't hear you.
- A little louder.
- Can you speak up?
- Okay, we've done enough.
We have all we need for today.
1, 2, 3.
- Good.
- 1, 2, 3.
We're back.
The camera's rolling again.
Suk Jin...
Stop it already. They don't use
much of this footage anyway.
1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
Nice.
We won't know what they'll use,
so we have to keep filming.
Why are you speaking so loudly?
On the other side...
(Young Ji, who's alone,
is filming a vlog.)
They seem happy.
(They seem happy.)
Meanwhile, I'm all alone.
(I'm all alone.)
My situation is different...
from Suk Jin's earlier on.
He had to battle loneliness...
in a sad way,
but for me,
it's like...
(Young Ji's Vlog)
It's like I'm getting
the VVIP treatment.
(The VVIP treatment)
(However,)
(no one's around to hear her.)
The head manager at my agency...
told me to stick close
to Suk Jin today...
because he's been trending lately.
(But it's been hard to hear
the trending balladeer's voice.)
I haven't been near Suk Jin today.
(She tries to film
enough scenes for herself.)
You can rest, you know.
There's nothing for me to do.
(While Young Ji films
a sad vlog entry...)
Chae Young used to figure skate
in the US.
- Right.
- Figure skating?
- Didn't you know?
- Gosh, no.
- She used to live abroad.
- When I was really young.
Just so you know, Chae Young...
was a figure skating prodigy.
- Really?
- That's not true.
But judging by her dancing earlier,
it didn't seem that way.
- Figure skating?
- Really?
I guess you can say
there's a difference.
Good dancers
usually have good lines.
I have good lines too.
You were stiff though.
You have good lines
when you stand still.
- When you move, though...
- Really?
I have good stamina though.
(She cuts in with another brag.)
How she speaks is addictive though.
- It's addictive, isn't it?
- Yes.
It's been a while
since I woke up this early,
so I'm tired.
(There's no way
to predict her comments.)
Chae Young,
I thought you were going to say
something important.
I thought something was up.
- I thought something was wrong.
- You're tired?
- But you're just tired.
- Unbelievable.
I mean...
Her way of talking
is so addictive...
that I might suffer from withdrawal.
- Aren't I adorable?
- Right.
You know,
you're not at all how you seem.
- You seem cold and chic.
- Exactly.
And one would think
you'd be smug in a way.
Well,
when I was young,
I liked being called
chic and sophisticated,
- but now...
- Not anymore.
- I like to be called cute.
- I see.
Okay, noted.
- Duly noted.
- Got it.
You're funny too.
- You're adorable.
- You're cute.
Don't say it all at once.
Throw it in from time to time.
You have cute nails.
- Look at that.
- I've been thinking this,
but her ribbon is cute too.
I mean it.
Just so you know...
- Can I call you Jong Kook?
- Call me whatever you want.
Behind me...
- You didn't know it was him?
- No.
Really?
- Who then?
- Who did you think I was?
I don't pay attention
to my surroundings.
- You're adorable.
- You are.
- Chae Young, how cute of you.
- You're adorable.
- I really didn't know.
How cute of you.
Who did you think was talking then?
- She didn't know but...
- I knew someone was there, but...
Shall we get out then?
I really had no idea.
How adorable of you.
- How cute.
- It was a long drive.
Namhansanseong is known
for its creek.
Gosh, I haven't been here
in a while.
We're at the creek.
It's been a while
since I was at a creek.
Eating samgyetang here is the best.
Watermelons cool down
if you put them in the water.
To be honest,
I don't like being at the creek.
There are too many mosquitoes.
Yes, there are a lot here.
You're always so fussy!
- I'm also...
- You don't like it here either?
I tend to go inside.
Then why not just stay home?
It's why Yong Man,
Suk Jin, and I...
- have fun together.
- I see.
- No wonder.
- We're always on the same page.
- Anyway, Young Ji is here.
- She's here.
- She runs in a cute way.
- Grab your bangs...
as you run!
What took you so long?
This is nice.
I've missed greenery like this.
- This place...
- And the sound of nature.
Our audio director...
is having a hard time
recording our voices.
Water, hush!
(What?)
- Is that possible?
- Are you trying to rule nature too?
What?
He's trying to rule nature too.
- Are you a deity?
- He's trying to rule nature too.
But the audio director...
- I think we need the sun.
- He's having a hard time.
Can you tell the sun to rise higher?
Up with the sun!
- Up with the sun?
- Water, be quiet!
Okay, go.
(Sliding in)
Move over. It's wet over there.
(The balladeer who saves his voice
gets pushed to the side.)
You're so unpleasant.
- Suk Jin...
- Unbelievable.
Can you please wear some underpants?
Can you see inside?
Who wears underpants?
I can see your underwear.
Beef up your thigh muscles
or wear tighter shorts.
- Suk Jin, you look...
- Do one or the other.
How long should my underpants be?
- Should they stick out?
- Goodness.
Your shorts are too loose.
It's an unpleasant sight!
You're disgusting us.
Then don't look!
Let us vote.
Let's vote for Mr. Unpleasant.
It's an unpleasant sight!
Shouldn't we give him a blanket?
- What is the meaning of this?
- Gosh.
Unbelievable.
In this next game,
you will be oversharing...
while surrounded by
this scenic view.
It's Majority Rules Truth or Dare.
- Majority Rules Truth or Dare.
- Truth or Dare?
All members will participate.
When given a question
with two options for an answer,
you will choose one simultaneously.
You will win a point if your answer
is the majority opinion.
- Majority rules.
- I know how the game works.
Points will be added for each team.
So the staff will be
asking the questions?
Yes, about things
that seem like oversharing.
However,
if all players
choose the same answer,
Young Ji from the one-man team
will win ten points.
- So that should be avoided.
- A unanimous answer?
That's a sweet deal for you.
- It won't happen easily.
- That's why...
some things are better
when you're alone...
and some are better
when you're on a team.
- Just answer honestly.
- Got it.
Beware of oversharing.
"When I shower,"
"I scrub the bottoms of my feet
with soap every time."
- Every time?
- "I scrub them every time."
Is it number one for yes?
- Is it number one for yes?
- One for yes...
and two for no.
1, 2, 3.
- Of course I scrub my feet.
- Me too.
Yes for me.
(Do you scrub the bottoms
of your feet with soap every time?)
(3 people picked number 1,
6 people picked number 2.)
Yes for me.
Those who chose no
will receive a point.
- Nice!
- Okay!
"No" is the majority?
- Seriously?
- You don't scrub your feet?
Not every time.
- No?
- Don't you usually...
let your feet do the work?
- Like this.
- Of course not.
Soapy water travels down
to your feet,
so you rub them on the floor.
What?
I do.
- Haha,
- I do.
- you should rub your feet like so.
- That's what I do.
And then you let them dry.
- What if you trip?
- Chae Young, don't you do it?
Not every time.
Washing your skin too often...
can make it dry.
(Washing your skin too often
can make it dry.)
- Right?
- How adorable!
- That's adorable.
- I get it.
- That was a cute way to put it.
- How adorable.
So Min...
- How do you shower?
- In my case,
I wash my body like this.
I'd rather not see this.
And then I scrub my feet.
Do you use the loofah
on your feet too?
- Yes, I then let it dry.
- But then...
- Really?
- You could do that.
I see you usually use a shower ball.
I go for the longer type.
(He prefers a loofah that's long.)
Old man Yu!
Then travel down with it.
Don't you do this too?
(Front and back)
Hey!
- Are you insane?
- That was unpleasant!
- This is unpleasant.
- You'll burn your skin.
That's something I don't do.
- That will hurt.
- It'll definitely hurt.
This is oversharing,
but do you hit your face
when you wash it?
- I do.
- I don't do that.
- In my case...
- One should hit the face.
- I do.
- Like this.
- Jae Suk,
- do you make noises when you wash?
- How?
Like that.
I know what he means.
Some do that.
- I know what you mean.
- At the sauna...
- Exactly.
- You're like that, aren't you?
- Don't you make that noise?
- I don't.
- Dads do that.
- I wash my face quietly.
I hit my face with water.
- Splash, splash!
Like that.
Old men do that.
Here's the second question.
You went to a fortune-teller...
to ask about your compatibility
with your boyfriend or girlfriend,
Oh, this question.
but you were told...
- that one of you would die.
- Die?
Hold up one if you would break up...
and hold up two if you won't.
- Two for not breaking up?
- That's right.
This could be unanimous.
- We need a strategy.
- It's sad though.
We have to be smart about this.
- All right.
- One,
2, 3.
(Would you break up...)
(if a fortune-teller
told you that one would die?)
(They all choose 2.)
You all choose number two.
(1-person team Young Ji
receives 10 points.)
This is why I wanted
to choose the other option.
I thought of that too.
So, Young Ji wins ten points.
If I'm not in the best of health,
I may consider breaking up.
If I know I'm sick, I mean.
I was told that
my wife and I weren't compatible.
- Your wife?
- Yes.
That's true from her point of view.
Seriously?
- Hey...
- It's true.
We didn't get along
during the first three months.
During those first three months,
I was too busy playing Starcraft.
Do you know how to play Starcraft?
- Of course.
- Then...
Exactly, right?
- You were the worst.
- She says you're the worst.
Check your compatibility
before getting married.
You never know.
Suk Jin's wife...
You shouldn't completely
ignore these things.
All right. "I use the bidet..."
"in the bathrooms
at the TV station."
Choose number 1 if you do
and number 2 if you don't.
I use it sometimes.
1, 2, 3.
- You use it?
- I don't.
- I use it.
- Of course I use it.
- You don't?
- No.
(3 people picked number 1,
6 people picked number 2.)
- I don't use it.
- 6 people who chose number 2...
- get one point each.
- All right!
I picked number two.
Of course I use it. Don't you?
- No, I don't.
- Why not?
I use the one at home.
I don't think bidets outside...
- Really?
- are clean.
- I'm not comfortable using it.
- It's a little uncomfortable.
It's not pleasant.
It doesn't suit him.
Why does he only use it at home?
- What? Then what should I do?
- What about you?
Should I relieve myself on the floor
over a newspaper?
Should I wash myself with my hand
like this?
Hey! I use a bidet at home too!
- You look like you'd use a leaf.
- A leaf?
We live in the 21st century!
You look like someone who'd crumple
a newspaper to wipe your butt.
No way! I use a bidet too.
Don't you tear off a calendar
to wipe yourself?
What do you mean?
I use a bidet from Chungho Nais.
- I'm using it nicely!
- Oh, really?
The ink from the newspaper
might be stained on your butt.
(They're sharing
too much information.)
After your first kiss
with your girlfriend or boyfriend...
- After the first kiss?
- Yes.
You have bragged to your friend
after your first kiss.
- Choose number one if you have.
- Brag about it?
- If you have bragged about it...
- Why would I brag about it?
Choose number one if you have,
(Remembering her first kiss)
and choose number two
if you never have.
- You brag about your first kiss?
- Why would I brag about it?
- How about sharing instead?
Sharing is bragging in a way.
Talking about it
is considered bragging.
I mean, my friend would ask me,
"So did you..."
That means you've bragged about it.
- I'm sure you have!
- I hesitated to tell.
- "I mean..."
- Your tone tells that you have.
- Let's choose it now.
- No, I've never bragged about it.
- That's what you call bragging.
- I'm sure he has bragged about it.
- I can tell from his face.
- "You kissed her?"
- I'm sure you have.
- "It's not that."
- "Of course."
- You see? He's done it for sure!
You can't call this bragging!
- No, that is bragging.
- How is this bragging?
- You put on airs.
- I only answered his question.
1, 2, 3.
- More people will choose number 2.
- No, they'll choose number 1.
(Which one is the majority opinion?)
5 people chose number 1.
- 4 people chose number 2.
- All right!
I picked number 2 on purpose.
I've never bragged,
but I chose number 1 to win points.
- You've never bragged about it?
- No, never.
I kept it quiet.
- It's different from what we know.
- It's more like sharing.
According to what Park Hyung Man
from Washington DC reported,
you bragged about the kiss you had
under the overpass in Suyu-ri.
I know! He has bragged about it!
(Got you!)
- You've bragged about it!
- He remembers it.
(Did I do that?)
(Episode 508,
viewers' reports about the members)
(Jae Suk's friend Hyung Man
who lives in Washington DC...)
(made a report.)
- This one is true!
- "The story I'll share with you..."
(A scoop from the States)
(This story is about
where Jae Suk had his first kiss.)
("I remember how he told us
at the school store the next day.")
(He bragged about it
at the school store the next day.)
You love bragging.
Why can't you be honest?
- Listen.
- An overpass? That's so funny.
If social media existed back then,
he'd have bragged all over it.
- Hey.
- Under an overpass?
I told Hyung Man
because he was my close friend.
I didn't brag about it.
The fact that you shared it
is bragging.
It must be convenient
for you to kiss...
since you don't have to
lean forward that much.
Right, he just needs to
brush past her.
- Even if you move slightly...
- He can only brush past her.
- I know.
- It must be really convenient.
- You can kiss faster than others.
- The same goes for you, right?
I know what it's like. I get him.
You can kiss faster than others.
All right. Here's the next question.
You've lied to your boyfriend
or girlfriend...
that you're sleeping...
but went outside to hang out
in secret.
I know this one!
But you have to be really honest.
- I'll be really honest.
- You can't lie for points.
- Don't lie about it.
- I'll be honest.
I'm sorry, but what if I went
to the gym instead of hanging out?
- That's considered the same.
- That's the same thing.
- That's considered hanging out.
- You have to be honest, So Min.
- Honestly, if you say you haven't,
- I'm sure everyone has done it.
you're lying to yourself.
I don't do that
because I get caught anyway.
- Right, I don't do it either.
- I don't lie at all.
But I've never lied
that I was sleeping.
I told her
that I was working though.
- I've never lied...
- We won't get a unanimous answer.
1, 2, 3.
I think I have.
- I chose number 1.
- More people chose number 2.
Young Ji, Se Chan, and Suk Jin
chose number one.
- Yes!
- I was being really honest.
- More people chose number one?
- This...
- I can't play this.
- This doesn't make any sense.
You hypocrites.
I'm not the type to
go through the trouble of lying...
- just to hang out.
- Me neither.
- You know me, right?
- I think you have.
You've never done it before,
Jong Kook?
- I tell her that I'm working.
- That's considered the same.
- But I've never said I'm sleeping.
- Chae Young, you've never done it?
- No, never.
- Really?
(Stern)
I'm sorry.
I've never done it before.
- He apologized right away.
- I don't lie...
- because it shows.
- Me too. It shows.
- Right?
- It's risky to lie.
Have you done it before, Young Ji?
- Yes, I have.
- Where did you go?
My boyfriend didn't let me
go and hang out.
- So?
- So I told him I'm exhausted,
- And?
- and I went bowling.
- But this is...
- That's wholesome.
If they scold you
for every little thing,
- you can't help but lie.
- That's wholesome.
- That's right.
- So you shouldn't be controlling.
- Right.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
I've never done it before.
I actually sleep.
- Of course.
- She sleeps for real.
- You're so honest.
- She actually sleeps.
- Right, she does.
- That was funny.
- She really falls asleep.
- She actually sleeps.
I lied that I was sleeping
three times,
and I lied that I was sick once.
I get caught if I keep lying
that I'm sleeping.
There are days when men
hang out by themselves.
You need to start acting...
- that morning.
- That's right.
- "Gosh, today..."
- You start acting in the morning.
- "I..."
- "I'm not feeling well."
But your girlfriends know.
- They pretend to fall for it.
- I've never lied to go outside.
But if you're going to lie
that you're sick,
you need to start acting
two days in advance.
What's that?
(He needs to act
two days in advance.)
- I do that too.
- I can totally relate to it.
- You're so mean.
- I'm sure all men can relate to it.
You need to act in advance.
If you say that you're sick
on the day of, they get suspicious.
- You need to act like you're tired.
- You need to act in advance.
You need to act sick.
"Gosh, my ears are..."
Did your ears hurt?
- That's right.
- That's so right.
I hate it.
"My ears keep getting inflamed."
(He needs to sound
as serious as possible.)
We did that a long time ago
when we were still young.
- Here's the next question.
- Okay.
Before you fall asleep,
right before you fall asleep,
your girlfriend or boyfriend
texts you.
Choose number one
if you read the text.
If you don't,
then choose number two.
How many texts did she send?
1, 2, or 3?
If it's just one,
you can read it in the notification.
This one's easy.
1, 2, 3.
- Why wouldn't you read it?
- Of course you shouldn't.
- That's...
- 1, 2, 3.
(Number 1, you read the text,
number 2, you don't read the text)
- Why wouldn't you read it?
- I wouldn't read it either.
Young Ji and Suk Jin
chose number one.
This must be why
I never got replies.
Don't be upset, Young Ji.
- But...
- Calm down.
I didn't ask for much, did I?
I only said I couldn't fall asleep.
"I can't fall asleep, sweetie."
That's all I said,
- and he doesn't reply?
- Good one, Young Ji.
I've never gotten any replies.
This is why you shouldn't read it.
If you reply to that,
you have to keep exchanging texts.
That'd make her upset.
- "Why do you want to hang up?"
- That's right.
You might end up fighting.
It's better to not read it.
It's better to call in the morning
and say you fell asleep.
Even if you read the text
in the morning, you can go,
"I'm not feeling well."
Jae Suk.
That's so annoying of you.
Jae Suk always acts like he's sick.
Remember how he talked about
getting an IV?
He always acts like he's sick.
He's an expert in playing a patient.
It'd be perfect if her house
is around here.
I'm a fan.
I wish I had a boyfriend like him.
Chae Young doesn't check
the text either?
It's not only applicable
to my boyfriend.
I just can't be reached after 9 p.m.
- Oh, is that so?
- She's very strict.
Oh, so she can't be reached.
- That's why...
- How cute.
What?
Isn't it so cute
that she can't be reached after 9 p.m.?
So she goes to bed
at a certain time.
It's raining
more than we thought it would.
It's raining a lot.
Let's go inside to have lunch.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Let's go inside.
(As it starts to pour,
they sit under a tent.)
It's pouring all of a sudden.
(There's a smell of grass
and rain in the air.)
- Now...
- Yes.
We moved because it started to pour.
- It's nice!
- Yes!
We're going to have lunch now.
But there are even scores,
so let's do a quick question first.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
Please hand out the boards.
- Please ask a sentimental question.
- A sentimental one?
- Yes.
- The one that suits the weather.
I think
So Min is going to cry again.
- Then why don't you...
- Go ahead and cry.
Why don't you give us one, So Min?
- Me?
- I think So Min is the one...
going through menopause,
not Suk Jin.
I'm going through it
faster than I thought.
Is there anything you want to ask?
- A question?
- Yes.
"I want to see him now."
I choose number 1.
Choose number 1
if you have someone you miss,
Choose number two if you don't.
- After taking a shower,
- There's another one?
you clean your shower drain
right away.
That's a good one.
- Right away?
- Choose one if you do.
If you leave it for days,
choose number two.
1, 2, 3.
- Of course it's number 1.
- Number 1.
- You didn't choose number 1?
- Number 2.
I don't clean it right away.
Of course it's number two.
- You didn't choose number one?
- I don't clean it right away.
- All right.
- I clean it right away.
Only Ji Hyo and Jae Suk
picked number one.
- Yes!
- I don't clean it right away.
You don't clean it right away?
But you should clean it right away.
- No, no.
- Otherwise, it doesn't drain well.
You need to wait a few days
until more hair piles up.
It feels good if you clean up
after your hair piles up.
- When you remove it...
- You know that feeling, right?
When you do it after a few days.
You feel great if you clean it
after a few days.
If you swirl the hair
out of the drain hole,
- you know,
- That's the reason I shower.
you can drag it out like this.
Wait a minute.
If you drag out that much,
that means it's a woman's hair.
(Zipping)
That means it's a woman's hair.
(He zips his own mouth.)
You said you like women
with bobbed hair.
If you drag out that much,
that means it's a woman's hair.
- You live alone, don't you?
- Yes, I do.
I only need to drag out this much.
Doesn't everyone clean it
right away?
But I think my wife cleans it
right away.
That's why you never do it.
Actually, I...
So you never clean it, do you?
You have a nice wife.
My wife is probably happy
that she married me.
So you don't have to care
about that.
Don't mind her.
Okay, you're right about that.
Chae Young, you're married,
so you must know. Only one of you...
Why are you
speaking to her casually already?
We've gotten a lot closer.
Right, Chae Young?
- Did you ask if she's okay with it?
- Wait a minute.
- Did you ask her?
- How many times...
- have you seen her?
- Chae Young.
I saw her for the first time today.
- Why are you casual with her?
You can choose.
Can I speak casually with you?
(Can I speak casually with you?)
Well...
I hope you won't be too casual
with me.
(She sternly asks him
to address her formally.)
- I'd appreciate it if you do that.
- Okay, okay.
- Good one, Chae Young.
- Well done.
- He's very uncomfortable.
- If that's what you want...
- She finds it uncomfortable.
- She's drawing a line.
Okay, I got it.
I've seen you many times,
- so it's okay, right?
- Of course.
- I'll speak casually to you.
- When I see you next time...
It's more natural for you
to address her formally.
Okay. Next time I see her...
- It's way better.
- And don't speak casually...
- to Young Ji either.
- Right.
I've seen her a lot.
I've seen her
at Jun Ha's restaurant too. Right?
But you didn't pay for us.
(He didn't do anything for her
when he met her.)
He didn't?
- He's the worst.
- I'm kidding.
- But honestly...
- We are way older than her.
- Why didn't you pay for her?
Young Ji, I only heard
that you were at the next table.
- Still, you should've paid for her.
- I didn't even see you.
People usually pay
for the younger ones.
Then why did you say
you saw her at Jun Ha's restaurant?
What? I just heard
she's at the next table.
I pay for my juniors
in every region.
Good for you, you punk.
What did you call me?
- Calm down.
- What did you call me?
- He's so pathetic.
- I'm warning you.
Don't go around
and pay for everyone.
It's 2 on 1.
- I can't hold it anymore.
- Calm down.
- You should calm down.
- You want a piece of me?
- Calm down.
- You're carrying me so stably.
- Wow, Jong Kook...
- Jae Suk is finally on his back!
- You're carrying me so stably.
- Calm down, Jae Suk.
- You're so stable.
- I was really going to...
- You should stop paying for people.
I really like Chae Young though.
- Address her formally!
- It's Ms. Han for you!
Call her Ms. Han!
- Ms. Han.
- Don't address her informally!
She's so good
at doing variety shows.
- He keeps speaking casually.
- Respect.
- We have the result.
- All right.
The team in 1st place won 20 points.
(1st place)
It's Team Green.
- Yes!
- All right!
- Really?
- Good job.
- That's impressive.
The one in second place...
- won 17 points.
- It must be Young Ji.
- Or us.
- Could it be me?
- It's Team Red.
- Really?
Young Ji, why did you get
so many questions wrong?
Young Ji, you're in 3rd place
with 15 points.
But Young Ji
got the ten-point question.
- She earned big points though.
- I guess that wasn't enough.
- Let's vote right away.
- Oh, right. Mr. Unpleasant.
- Mr. Unpleasant.
- Yes, Mr. Unpleasant.
We need to vote for Mr. Unpleasant.
Can't we just raise our hands?
I know who to vote for.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
- He was really unpleasant.
- I agree.
The most unpleasant moment for me...
was when I saw his underwear
inside his shorts.
It was really unpleasant.
Don't go stirring people up.
Stirring people up?
I have no intention to do that.
Give it to me.
One person should collect them.
Chae Young, is your name spelled
with "ae" or "e?"
It's "ae."
- I wrote it correctly.
- Right?
Did you write my name?
Of course not.
Your funds have been multiplied.
The vacation funds
of Team Jae Suk tripled.
- All right!
- Yes!
- Team Suk Jin's doubled.
- All right!
- Yes!
- This is nice.
We'll serve you the food
once it's ready.
My gosh, look at that.
The side dishes look so good.
Is it chicken soup
with sarcodon mushroom? It is!
(This dish
has all the good ingredients.)
I really wanted to have
potato pancakes.
Yes! Acorn jelly!
- Let's eat now.
- Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
It's seafood pancake.
If you need some more...
Chae Young,
do you want some seafood pancake?
The potato pancake is crispy.
- The potato pancake is really good.
- It's so good.
- The potato pancake is so savory.
- Wow, it's so good.
You can tell how good the restaurant
is from its radish kimchi.
It's already seasoned.
It looks good.
The broth seems really thick.
(Even Jae Suk, who doesn't like
eating by the creek, is mesmerized.)
It's so good.
- Can I have a bite?
- The broth is so good.
Is it amazing?
- It's good. The broth is good.
- It's amazing.
You need to dip it in salt though.
It's so nice to eat by the creek
while listening to the water.
- It's so nice.
- The sound of the water.
The potato pancake
is made with potatoes only.
I think so too.
Chae Young has the most funds.
She has 450 dollars.
- Really?
- How come she has so much?
How cute.
- The number is so cute.
- Even the amount is so cute.
- How cute.
- It's so cute, Chae Young.
And we'll pick two Mr. Unpleasants.
One of them is already decided
as he received the most votes.
(One of them is already decided.)
The first Mr. Unpleasant...
(Mr. Unpleasant is decided
after just two votes.)
is Suk Jin with 16 votes.
He won all the votes
now that Kwang Soo isn't here.
I can't believe it.
He got all the votes.
Now we need to vote.
(He won...)
(6 votes in the 1st round.)
(In the 2nd round,
he won up to 10 votes.)
It's been decided.
The problem is,
the second place is neck and neck.
(One of them will be voted
as Mr. Unpleasant.)
People in 2nd place are Jae Suk,
Haha, and So Min with 2 votes each.
- Why did they vote for me?
- It's neck and neck.
Se Chan and Chae Young
are in third place.
We got one vote each. All right.
Your place could change dramatically
in the last vote.
- Let's decide this now.
- All right, go ahead.
We'll decide who'll go solo.
You can start.
(The member who'll fight alone
in an important mission)
(Se Chan, Chae Young, Jong Kook,
Haha, Ji Hyo, Young Ji, Suk Jin,)
(So Min, Jae Suk)
(Jong Kook)
Jong Kook!
(It's Jong Kook.)
All right!
(The strongest 1-person team
has been formed.)
You picked the right direction.
It doesn't seem
that disadvantageous for him.
- He can fight against everyone.
- It seems advantageous for him.
Let's move to play the last mission.
- Let's go.
- Jong Kook likes it.
All right!
Let's move to the next spot.
This is a vlog.
(The gym lover's vlog starts
with his smiling eyes.)
All right!
Getting on the amazing Staria!
I should shake off the dust.
That's good manners.
(Gym Jong Kook)
All right. That's good manners.
(Good manners)
The door is automatic.
(He seems to have the wrong idea
about vlogs.)
(He was different
from the beginning.)
This is really nice.
- This is our last mission, right?
- Yes.
We should think carefully
about who to vote for.
Suk Jin is done for.
He's been decided already.
- The remaining...
- We have to vote for one more.
We're not going to betray
each other, are we?
- Come on.
- Hey.
- We don't do that.
- It's all about peace here.
I'd never vote for you, Young Ji.
- Young Ji, that means...
- That's right.
they're going to betray you.
- That's how they start?
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
- There's more coming.
- That's a big misunderstanding.
I just got the chills.
He spoke exactly the way
I expected him to.
Why would we betray you after having
chicken soup with you?
Don't say that
on a nice day like today.
- We enjoyed the potato pancake too.
- It's exactly the same.
- I have something to tell you.
- What is it?
2 people are to receive the penalty,
and we need to pick 1.
So Min,
you and I are in second place.
You want to pick Jae Suk?
We don't need to say it, right?
No need. It's been decided.
Aren't you upset that Jae Suk
drove everyone to pick you?
- Let's vote for him.
- Gosh.
- Yes, it's upsetting.
- Let's vote for Jae Suk.
- What do you think, Ms. Han?
- Shall we do that?
- How about voting for Jae Suk?
- Shall we?
Of course we should.
Jong Kook's vote must be crucial...
- since he has four ballots.
- His vote is important.
I'm sure...
he'll listen to you, Ms. Han.
Then you should convince him.
- Me?
- Yes.
(They try to convince Jong Kook
with Chae Young in their corner.)
- Hey, Suk Jin.
- Jong Kook.
Ms. Han...
wants to ask you a favor
for the first time in her life.
- To whom?
- Hang on.
- She has something to ask you.
- Me? Okay.
I wanted to ask you a favor.
What is it?
Shall we all vote for Jae Suk?
What do you think?
It's my first time on the show,
and I'm asking you a favor.
(She's a novice negotiator
who only has cuteness as her card.)
Is that so? Then I guess...
Okay, I'll do that...
since you asked.
You mean it, right?
I'll vote for Jae Suk then.
Tell him that he's so cool.
Right. You're so cool, Jong Kook!
(She forces herself
to compliment Jong Kook.)
All right, Jong Kook.
We have a deal.
You've been decided
to receive the penalty.
It doesn't matter me.
Please help us, Jong Kook!
Help us out.
(They arrive at the last spot.)
The weather is so nice.
The view...
- is incredible.
- The view is amazing here.
It's so green.
Se Chan, hit an approach shot.
That was a good shot, Jong Kook.
- Hit an approach shot.
- Nice approach.
Until when are you going to film
your vlog?
They didn't take the camera away,
so I'm just filming with it.
I'm practicing for my channel.
This is the last mission
for a fruitful vacation.
It's an upgraded version...
- of the quiz we played.
- What is it?
It's the Nerve-wracking Quiz.
- But why...
- We're playing a quiz again?
would you let us play a quiz
after forming a team?
(Why let us play a quiz
after forming a team?)
This is driving me crazy.
After Kwang Soo left,
- I'm the only empty head here.
- This is driving me crazy.
Our team is better, isn't it?
- Our team is better.
(They're more or less the same.)
We're playing a quiz? Okay.
It's better to play alone.
It's an upgraded version...
of a quiz on units.
We're done for.
We added some symbols
on top of the units.
But we don't even know the units.
- Tell us what the unit is...
- We're in trouble.
as soon as you see it.
- Something like milliliter.
- Wait, is this a math quiz?
Yes, it is.
(It covers units and symbols
in all areas.)
No, it's more like a science quiz.
Oh, really?
Young Ji studied in New Zealand...
- Don't talk about that!
- when she was young.
Is that so?
- She can speak English.
- In that case...
- And you know about Chae Young.
- She studied abroad too.
- Up until her teen years...
- She used to live in Chicago.
- Hi.
- That's it?
- That's all.
- Goodness.
Each member will give it a go,
and if they read the unit correctly,
they earn a point.
If they get it wrong,
the chance goes to the other team.
- What about him?
- He can answer...
four times in a row.
- I can do that?
- Yes, you get four chances.
- Let's see how good they are.
- Right. Let's see.
Let's go first then.
All right. We can do this!
- We're going first?
- Let's do this!
We'll show the unit
to Team Jae Suk first.
If you don't answer
on the count of three,
- you are out.
- Okay.
Please count to three slowly.
- Here comes the first question.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk will be given
the first question.)
Will it be hard?
Cue.
1, 2, 3.
- Decibel.
- You answered too late.
- I knew that one.
- Decibel is a unit...
- even I know.
- Decibel.
- I should have gone first.
- I didn't know.
You should count it
as the correct answer.
- No.
- I got it right.
- DB Insurance.
- Decibel.
Isn't it DB Insurance?
Insurance?
- Listen.
- DB.
Bo Pil.
- You are strict.
- You should be more lenient.
You are strict today.
The charm of this game
lies in the quick answers.
Charm? Charm?
- Charm.
- Charm?
Calm down.
- Calm down.
Why are you so offended?
For goodness' sake.
- Charm.
- I am really bad at this.
- Jong Kook, you are up next.
- Me?
- Okay.
- He won't get more than two right.
- DB Insurance.
- Here comes the question.
(Team Jong Kook's first attempt)
Cue. 1, 2, 3.
Newt? What is that?
- N.
- N?
- Isn't N from N and S?
- N.
- Newton.
- Correct.
Newton. Gosh, I got to "Newt."
Newton.
- Hold on.
- I got to "Newt."
- The first one should be easy.
- Should Chae Young go first?
- You should go first.
- Haha.
Chae Young,
let's see what you can do.
- Let's see it.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- The first one should be easy.
I will go first.
Please give me an easy one.
- Chae Young, go first.
- The easiest one.
Chae Young will go first.
All right, Chae Young.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
Gram...
- Gigabyte.
(Gram?)
- Even I know gigabyte.
- It's gigabyte, Chae Young.
- Gigabyte.
It was too fast-paced,
so I felt pressured.
- Even I know that one.
- Chae Young.
Decibel and gigabyte.
- That was cute.
- It suddenly feels so hot in here.
Chae Young, that was cute.
That was cute.
- That was cute.
She almost started...
- with "Grand."
- It's our turn again.
- Grandfather.
All three teams have zero points.
- Bring it on.
- Will Jae Suk go first?
Jae Suk.
- Let's go.
I hope they fail.
(I hope they fail.)
Isn't that going a bit too far?
(The magical fairy puts a curse
on them with a selfie stick.)
Set, go.
- 1, 2...
- Sine.
(Jae Suk is correct.)
- Two...
- Sine.
Isn't it just "Sin?"
Thank goodness I didn't get it.
I thought it was "Sin."
- Like thin pizza.
- I know.
- Sin.
- Sine.
- It's sine.
- Sine from sine and cosine.
I am about to throw up.
- Let's go.
- I got one.
She said she is about to throw up.
- She said she is about to throw up.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
Jae Suk, you are cool.
- We are off to a good start.
- Young Ji.
Let's go.
- Here comes the question.
- Don't be nervous.
Cue.
1, 2, 3.
Mountain.
(Mountain.)
(Mountain?)
(He gets a sudden headache.)
(They laugh because it seems like
she is wrong.)
- What is that?
- Sigma.
Sigma.
- You should have given me that one.
It's okay not to know that one.
- It's okay not to know that one.
- It's okay.
- It's a hard one.
- No!
I am not very well-educated.
This is nothing.
You just need to answer quickly.
This is doable.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
Let's go!
(Looking at the other team
gives them confidence.)
- That was funny.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
So Min can't laugh.
Let's do this comfortably.
(It's loud,
but the selfie stick fairy focuses.)
- Let's do this comfortably.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
- I will get an easy one.
- Set, go.
- 1, 2...
- Watt.
(Watt)
Watt.
- Set, go.
- The easy ones are disappearing.
(The next question)
- Let's go.
- Hertz.
There you go.
That's right.
- Give me the easy ones.
- Why didn't I get that one?
Let's go.
- What is that?
- Pascal!
- Pascal.
Why didn't I get that one?
I should have gotten it.
- Pascal.
- Why didn't I get that one?
- Don't answer after taking a beat!
- No.
You keep pretending to know
after a beat.
- Stop it.
- P, A, K, A, L.
- Pascal.
- Se Chan.
What's pascal?
- That was too much.
- What's pascal?
That was too much.
What's pascal?
- Don't corner him like that!
- What's pascal?
- It's...
- Isn't it a unit of measurement?
Isn't it a unit of measurement?
You know,
- Bo Pil is something else.
- He is unbelievable.
"What's pascal?"
Did you have to go that far?
- He cornered me.
- Just because you are educated...
(Se Chan got humiliated
for "Pakal.")
What's pascal?
Is Jong Kook leading right now?
- Did he answer 2 questions?
- 2 questions.
Shall I go first?
Yes. Let's try to get
one question right.
This is hard for me too.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Get ready.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
- Ear hair.
- Get ready.
(Jong Kook films his ear hair.)
What are you doing?
Ear hair. I am filming it.
- Film it.
- I don't have ear hair.
- Ear hair.
- It's because of you.
Film his ear hair.
- I don't have any!
- Don't cut it.
- Ear hair.
- Stop it.
Jong Kook,
you are working hard today.
The viewers might be curious.
You are working hard today.
I thought it was a fist.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Let's do this.
Let's go. This is nothing.
That's right.
We use those units in real life.
- We use those units.
- Don't be nervous.
- I just need to be alert.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Take it on.
- Bring it on.
- Okay.
- Here comes the question. Cue.
I know what this is. Gertz.
(He says the wrong answer
in a cheesy manner.)
- Gigahertz.
Gigahertz.
Get up, get up, get up, gertz.
- Gertz!
- Gigahertz.
(Jae Suk is dying of laughter.)
- Get up, get up, get up, gertz.
- Gertz!
- Isn't it gertz?
- I thought you would get it right.
- Gertz!
- He was close.
The Great Gertz.
- Gertz!
- I had high hopes.
- He was close.
- Gertz!
- It was an easy one.
- He needed to put them together.
- It's our turn.
- Get this one right.
Let's get another one right.
Do you want to go first?
- Ji Hyo, go first.
- Ji Hyo.
Okay. I will go first.
Let's go the opposite way. Okay.
Let's go the opposite way.
Ji Hyo, let's go.
- All right.
- Look at Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- I like that look in her eyes.
- She is determined.
- Come to your senses.
- I can do it.
- You can do it.
That's so funny.
- Get ready.
- Ji Hyo, let's go.
- An easy one.
- Here comes the question. Cue.
1, 2, 3.
- Root.
(Root)
(It's incorrect
since she went over time.)
- Why didn't you answer faster?
- Root.
- She answered too late.
- She still answered.
- Root.
She still answered.
The symbol looks strange.
Why is it so short?
You answered too late.
Move out of the way.
I know it's a root.
You answered too late.
- You answered too late.
- Put the camera away, okay?
- Root.
- Put it away.
You answered too late.
I want to take that camera from him.
- Just answer comfortably.
- Jong Kook has an advantage.
- The next question.
Okay.
The next question.
- This one's for me.
- Cue.
Kilogram.
(Kilogram)
Kilogram?
Everyone knows that.
- I am jealous.
- He is using the camera well.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
Everyone knows that.
- I am jealous.
- Kilogram?
I can't believe he got that one.
- Here comes the next one.
- Just answer comfortably.
- He has an advantage.
Here comes the question.
Cue.
- 1, 2...
- Cos... Cos!
Cosine!
(He just read the unit as it looks.)
- Costco.
- Cosine.
Isn't it a clothing brand?
- Isn't it a clothing brand?
- Cosine.
- Costco.
He said Costco instead of cosine.
Isn't it a clothing brand?
It's my favorite clothing brand.
Jae Suk is happy.
I thought I wouldn't see that
since Kwang Soo is gone.
Add a clip of Kwang Soo next to him.
(The tall man's mockery)
It's quite old.
Add a clip of Kwang Soo next to him.
Then, will I go...
- after Jae Suk and Young Ji?
- Yes.
I don't think I will get a chance.
- Then come here.
- Give it a try.
I will show you.
Most of the things I know
have already been asked.
Only two things remain.
Get ready.
Here comes the question. Cue.
- 1, 2...
- V.
- Volt. Isn't it volt?
- "Robot Taekwon V."
"Robot Taekwon V?"
(Volt)
- Volt.
Jae Suk, it's volt.
Everything I know has been asked!
Only pi remains.
- Volt.
- V for victory.
V.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
Just answer comfortably.
You don't need to be nervous.
This is nothing.
You use these units in real life.
- Are you talking to yourself?
- Yes.
Being alone suits Jong Kook.
- It's okay.
- It gets confusing.
- Here comes the question.
- It's nothing.
Cue.
- 1, 2...
- Pi.
(Pi)
It's the only one I know.
Everything I know has been asked.
(He only had pi to depend on.)
- Same here.
- Everything I know has been asked.
I give up now.
Everything I know has been asked.
- It's the same for me.
- I give up now.
Only one remains.
There is one more thing I know.
You use these units in real life.
- All right.
- Everything I know has been asked.
Shall we resume?
Here comes the question. Cue.
1, 2, 3.
- Ton.
- Tangent.
(Another trigonometric function)
I was reminded of a tanning salon.
(The mockery mode is on.)
- You didn't even know volt.
- Tangent.
V, come back in.
Tangent.
Sine, cosine, tangent.
(He doubles over with laughter.)
The man who was born in Germany,
Haha will go next.
- The man who was born in Germany.
Let's go.
- Show us what you can do.
- Here comes the question.
- This is nothing. Don't be nervous.
Cue.
- Mile.
- You got it right.
(Haha is correct.)
- He is happy.
Ha Dream!
- Ha Dream!
I am your father!
Stay tuned!
For goodness' sake.
Let's resume.
Chae Young.
Here comes the question.
(Chae Young is up next.)
Cue. 1, 2...
Centimeter.
- Centimeter.
- Hold on.
- That's...
(Is cm really one of the questions?)
Is that really the question?
- Hold on.
Isn't that question too easy?
- Listen.
- Come on,
- that question was too easy.
- Come here.
Grab his neck.
- Grab his neck.
- How could you ask what cm is?
- It's too much.
- It's too easy.
- Even I know this.
- Did you hear that? "Centimeter."
For goodness' sake.
- "Centimeter."
- Aren't you annoyed?
I am very happy. "Centimeter."
(He suddenly conducts
a street interview.)
Why? Why are you annoyed?
- I am so annoyed.
- You are annoyed, right?
- How about you?
- I am annoyed.
- I am happy.
(Han Chae Young,
the person answered correctly)
(She feels good
since she earned a point.)
- You are cute.
- Cutie Chae Young.
- Chae Young.
You are cute.
Cutie Chae Young.
My goodness. It's our turn.
We need to get a question right.
You should go.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Jae Suk.
I am good
when it's someone else's question.
You get nervous.
It's easier
when it's someone else's question.
- You get nervous.
- Jae Suk.
Don't look at it directly.
Look at it sideways.
- Look at it sideways.
- It isn't my question.
It isn't your question.
When it's my question,
I can't answer the simplest thing.
Look at it sideways.
- There you go. That's good.
- It's someone else's question.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Cue. 1, 2, 3.
Fahrenheit.
(He is correct.)
- Fahren-heat?
- Fahrenheit.
- How did he know that?
That one was easy.
We are off to a good start.
- Young Ji, you are next.
- Okay.
Here comes the question. Cue.
- 1, 2...
- Oh, that's...
- Hey.
- Young Ji.
- Liter.
- That's...
- She is a total Empty Head.
(Liter)
(She speaks nonsense...)
(and collapses on the floor.)
(She is a total Empty Head.)
That question was
practically a freebie.
- Hey.
- It's easy.
- Hold on.
- Even Empty Heads know that much.
Young Ji, what was that noise?
I am going to go home.
You should have answered "Lotte."
- Lotte.
- Hey.
(Young Ji's ignorance
shakes up the Empty Head Land.)
(She attacks Jae Suk's thighs.)
Your face. Are you okay?
- I am okay.
- Are you okay, Young Ji?
It's okay.
- Oh, no.
- My goodness.
Don't be so nervous.
Isn't liter abbreviated as L?
- That's an L.
(Liter)
(This is an L.)
- That's an L.
- Young Ji.
- Young Ji, keep your mouth shut.
- She should be protected.
- You aren't like kids these days.
- Edit this out.
- She should be protected.
Young Ji.
You know, in this segment,
- you filled up Kwang Soo's spot.
- Seriously.
She is good.
You filled it up.
- My goodness.
- All right.
- Jong Kook.
- Me?
Answer comfortably.
You use these units in real life.
- Jong Kook has an advantage.
- You see these units in real life.
- Here comes the question.
- Okay.
Cue.
1, 2, 3.
Gosh, that one.
- It's pound.
- That's right.
- Is that pound?
- It's written on fitness equipment.
I can't believe I got it wrong.
- How is that pound?
- Why?
- Are those letters L and B?
- Why is that the abbreviated form?
Isn't that Red Velvet?
In Korea, we use kilograms.
- But in the US, they use pounds.
- Really?
You should have gotten it right.
I can't believe I got it wrong!
(Gym Jong Kook becomes upset.)
(The fitness fairy
is disappointed in himself.)
I...
(Now is our chance.)
(Furious bicep workout)
I work out so much.
I see that symbol every day.
Hey. So Min, you can do it.
- So Min, you are smart.
- Let's go.
So Min, you can do it.
So Min. Here comes the question.
Cue.
1, 2, 3.
Lexy.
(Laughing)
X-Large.
Lux.
(She mentioned a popular singer
from the 2000s.)
It's a unit of illuminance.
(Men are the same)
(They are babies)
Lux.
We have the results.
(The Nerve-wracking Quiz ends.)
Team Jong Kook has five points.
Five points.
Team Green with Chae Young has...
3 points. This team has 2 points.
(Team Jae Suk has 2 points.)
It's best to work alone.
Okay.
Jong Kook will get
triple the prize money.
As for the other teams,
it's two times and nothing.
Let's begin the last poll.
Okay.
(It's time for the last poll.)
With 16 votes, Suk Jin became
Mr. Unpleasant.
Don't waste your ballot
by writing down my name.
Write down someone else's name.
So Min? Haha?
(The 12 ballots will determine
the 2nd Mr. Unpleasant.)
This is hard, right?
- Who is in second place?
- Can I trust you guys?
Of course.
- It's the only way.
- Really?
Of course. It goes without saying.
- Yes.
It can't be helped.
(Team Suk Jin came up
with a plan in the car.)
(Their goal is Jae Suk.)
(They even roped in Jong Kook
with 4 ballots.)
(If things go as planned,)
(Jae Suk will receive 8 ballots
and become Mr. Unpleasant.)
I wrote down his name too.
- What?
- Show me all the ballots.
I am telling you the truth.
Look at his eyes!
Look at his facial expression!
- This is driving me crazy.
- His facial expression.
- Haha.
- I am telling you...
that I wrote his name.
- Then why do you...
- How annoying!
She drives me crazy.
(They suddenly become distrustful.)
- Why do you keep acting?
- I even showed you.
- Okay.
- Here you go.
How could you write my name
when I am right here?
- All right.
- Why are you acting?
Did you see Jae Suk hit me?
(I am innocent.)
I am not acting!
Why are you so distrustful?
Hey.
- But...
- Show me what you wrote.
The results will be revealed
at the place of the penalty.
Will the penalty come right away?
If you look here, there is a creek.
The penalty will involve
experiencing the creek.
Simply put,
you'll need a new pair of underwear.
That's right.
A new pair of underwear.
Suk Jin will carry out the penalty
since he received 16 ballots.
It's set.
It's a matter of who places second.
- Let's see what happened.
- I will announce the results.
- So Min.
- What?
- Me?
- Everyone is acting.
- Haha.
- I didn't write your name.
- No.
- Haha.
Jae Suk.
It's a match between So Min and me.
- I can't believe Haha got out.
- I know. It makes no sense.
Jae Suk, Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk receives
3 consecutive votes.)
It's game over.
- It's refreshing.
- This is important.
- Jae Suk.
- So Min.
So Min, So Min.
(So Min also receives
3 consecutive votes.)
It's neck and neck.
(Jae Suk's teammates voted
for So Min.)
- Why...
- It's over.
- How many ballots remain?
It's a tie. Four ballots remain.
Four ballots.
(So Min has 4 votes.
Jae Suk has 4 votes.)
(If things go as So Min planned,)
(she won't receive more
than 4 votes.)
It isn't me. I wrote down his name.
- It makes no sense.
- It's a tie.
It's a tie. Four ballots remain.
(The 9th ballot)
So Min.
- Really?
- So Min.
So Min.
- Really?
- So Min.
(The 10th vote goes to So Min
as well.)
(Jong Kook gave Jae Suk and So Min
2 votes each.)
Jae Suk.
If the last one has my name,
I will never trust Haha again.
- What are you talking about?
- Seriously.
You saw it. Jae Suk,
you saw me write your name.
- I will never trust Haha again.
- Jae Suk saw me write his name.
(Jae Suk looks resigned.)
If it's 6 to 6,
we will choose one person at random.
Hold on.
So Min, calm down.
(Who received the last vote?)
I bet it's a tie.
Who will receive the penalty?
(Jae Suk has 5 votes.
So Min has 6 votes.)
Who will receive the penalty?
So Min.
Really?
Come on.
(So Min became Mr. Unpleasant.)
- Hold on.
- Oh, no.
- Is it you?
- No.
(Haha said he wrote
Jae Suk's name.)
(15 minutes ago)
(Haha wrote So Min's name
in the corner and pointed to it.)
- It isn't me.
- So Min, listen.
We wrote the same thing.
- I'm sorry, but...
- Haha betrayed you.
Can I see the votes?
No.
- Jae Suk hit me.
- Why?
Hang on. I'll pay.
- So Min.
- I'll give you my pay.
Wait. I'll offer you my pay.
- Jae Suk.
- Just go.
- Let go of me.
- Just send a text message.
I don't have extra underwear today.
I'll give you my pay.
- So Min.
- I don't have extra underwear.
You betrayed her.
No, I didn't.
I wrote Jae Suk's name.
You saw it.
While these two
experience the creek,
our guests will tell us
how they enjoyed our show today.
Suk Jin does things like this
with So Min quite often.
We're getting along well these days.
- Make it quick.
- Okay.
And make a short speech.
(Mr. Unpleasant makes
unpleasant jokes until the end.)
- Let's do this.
- The Great Gertz.
- It looks cold.
- Gosh, it's cold.
- He's Entertainer Gertz.
(They can't help but scream
in the cool water.)
Gosh, it's so cool... My gosh.
(Giggling)
Let's not do this.
- They look so close.
- I know.
- They look happy.
- It's so cold.
This is cool. I love it.
Go ahead and end the show.
I forgot something important.
We need to decide the winner
with a roulette.
It's so cold. I can't stay seated.
No, you should sit.
- Hey.
- Stay seated.
- The Great Gertz.
- Just stay there.
We will spin the roulette,
and the winner will get...
the prize money.
We get as much money
as it says here.
- Let's begin.
- Go ahead and spin it.
As you know, we will wire
the money right away.
Really?
(The roulette to decide the winner
starts spinning.)
Let's go.
(Who will get the vacation bonus
after the delightful vacation?)
It's Young Ji.
(Hur Young Ji)
- That's great, Young Ji.
- I'm in last place though.
- You get 150 dollars.
- It's okay.
You saved your money, SBS.
We will wire 150 dollars
with the tax deducted.
- With the tax deducted?
- Hey, just give her 150.
- With the tax deducted.
- That's true.
- Is she really getting the money?
- Yes.
- Young Ji is really...
- It could've been Chae Young.
This is amazing.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
It's not so bad to sit in here.
(Dried young pollack)
(Dried Pollack Race)
(So this is all about talking?)
(It's a race
for those who love to talk.)
Tell us about your past.
(They go back in time.)
(Talking about love stories,)
(they warm up the talk engine.)
(11 a.m., in the van)
(1 p.m., in the village hall)
(3 p.m., in the bar)
(They keep chattering...)
(in many different places.)
You're the only one who's talking,
you punk.
(The members are happy
that they get to talk,)
(which flusters the young pollacks.)
(What will their day be like
with all the talking?)
(Talk Nightmare,
The Day of Chattering)