Hello.
What's going on?
What made you come all the way
to the beauty shop to see me?
What is happening?
- Hello, Se Chan.
- Nice to meet you.
- You went to the beauty shop.
- Right, I did.
I went to the beauty shop
to look good today.
Why are you kidnapping me?
Where are we going?
- Hello. Nice to see you.
- Hello.
Hello.
Take this phone first.
Gosh, this is...
(All the members get
the latest model smartphone each.)
What are we going to do
with this phone?
A lot of our viewers like...
- your talk during the opening.
- Okay.
So we reflected their opinions
for today's episode.
We will start the opening
with an online group chat.
What?
- My gosh. With a group chat?
- Yes.
- Hang on.
- While you're in the car...
I'm not good at this.
My gosh.
You know I'm good
at online chatting.
- An online chat?
- Yes.
I'm not familiar
with the messaging app.
The 1st and 2nd one.
By the time I'm done typing,
they already changed the subject.
(We will now show you
the group chat...)
(of the talkative members
of Running Man for 3 minutes.)
I'll send a photo.
"Hello. Good morning."
(Haha: Hello. Good morning.
This is crazy.)
- He sent a photo.
- My gosh.
(Haha: Hello. Good morning.
This is crazy.)
"Hello."
(Se Chan: Hello.)
I should take a photo.
(He feels a lot more confident
after visiting the beauty shop.)
Done.
(Jae Suk: Dirty Mustache)
It's clean.
Se Chan looks good today.
Se Chan looks handsome
in the picture.
Gosh, I'm startled.
(Haha: Surprised)
(Jong Kook: Se Chan's picture
looks great.)
(Ji Hyo: It's So Min.
Jae Suk: It's a ghost.)
He calls her a ghost.
(Haha: It's like "The Ring".)
She looks like a Chinese ghost.
He calls me a ghost.
Why? Do I look different today?
I think I look pretty.
That's why they tease me.
(So Min: This is how I look today.
Haha: Oldie, jinks.)
(Se Chan: Suk Jin,
what are you doing?)
"I don't think
he knows how to text."
"He's old."
The Cheonjiin typing...
(The Cheonjiin typing...)
(The Cheonjiin lover is still not
used to the new culture.)
How can I use the Cheonjiin typing?
(The Cheonjiin lover is still not
used to the new culture.)
It's done. They are taking photos.
(Suk Jin: Mind your own business.)
"Mind your own business."
"Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
(Jae Suk: I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
Haha: Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong.)
(Suk Jin: I changed the keyboard
setting to Cheonjiin.)
(So Min: There's a rumor that
Suk Jin is learning Excel.)
(Jong Kook: I keep making typos.
Jae Suk: Have a nice day.)
Should I take a photo
and send it to them?
(Jae Suk: Thank you. I wish
they noticed it back then.)
(Jong Kook: I want to hang around
with him in Anyang.)
"What's with your nose?"
(Haha: What's with your nose?
Ji Hyo: He looks like a delinquent.)
(Jae Suk: I'm still a star.)
"I'm still a star."
(Se Chan: There's Mr. Jee.)
(Suk Jin:
My nose is a little puffy.)
(So Min: Jae Suk said this before.)
(Se Chan: It is swollen a lot.)
(Ji Hyo: What did you
eat last night?)
(So Min: Suk Jin's nose.
Suk Jin: Hey!)
(So Min: LOL)
(So Min: A gourd dipper.)
She calls it a gourd dipper.
That's funny.
(Jae Suk: I want to eat with you.
Se Chan: Buy us a meal.)
(Their talk has no common thread.)
"Jae Suk, don't be serious."
(Jong Kook: Why did you butt in?
Haha: LOL)
"Mint chocolate."
(Jae Suk: Do you guys like
mint chocolate?)
"Do you like it?"
"I like it."
(Ji Hyo: Yes.)
"I'm a mint chocolate lover."
(Haha: I'm a mint chocolate lover.)
This is so funny.
We are all old, so it takes us
a long time to do the typing.
(Suk Jin: I will teach
Jong Kook a lesson.)
(Se Chan: Can you still teach
Jong Kook a lesson?)
(Se Chan: Sexy)
(Jong Kook: Aren't you the extra
from the movie, "1987"?)
(So Min: He's handsome.
Haha: I got it. Jae Suk's mom!)
(Se Chan:
This is when he was clumsy.)
"He is cool."
(Jae Suk: He is cool.)
(While they are busy
chatting online...)
Gosh, Jae Suk.
"The opening talk is over.
Now we have two Mafias..."
"in the chat room."
(There are 2 Mafias
in the chat room?)
"The opening talk is over."
"Now we have two Mafias
in the chat room."
(Now we have two Mafias
in the chatroom.)
- What?
- Two Mafias?
(Among the 7 members in the
chat room, 2 of them are Mafias.)
There are two Mafias?
(They suddenly heard
about the 2 Mafias.)
"They successfully
carried out their mission..."
"during the chat.
For the next five minutes..."
(The 2 Mafias successfully
carried out their hidden mission.)
Hang on.
(While they were busy
talking about useless things,)
(the Mafias carried out
their hidden mission.)
Yang Se Chan.
Se Chan gave us
a lot of information.
He talked about many things.
I think it's Se Chan.
I bet he's the Mafia.
(They all start to suspect Se Chan.)
It's Se Chan.
Because he talks too much.
The one that talks a lot
must be the Mafia.
That's how it works
in the Mafia game.
(Are the photos Se Chan uploaded
the mission for the Mafias?)
I just sent them a lot of photos.
(I have to do something.)
Guys, I'm telling you
I'm not up to anything.
Please believe me.
I'm on my way!
Se Chan is the Mafia.
It's Se Chan.
(His unreasonable excuse
makes them more suspicious.)
It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan: What about Jae Suk
talking about mint chocolate?)
(At that moment, Se Chan
suspects Jae Suk.)
Right. It's strange that he suddenly
talked about mint chocolate.
"Mint chocolate."
(Jae Suk suddenly asked them
if they like mint chocolate.)
"Do you like it?"
Jae Suk is strange.
He was being too serious and polite.
Can you believe this?
"I want to eat with you."
That doesn't sound like Jae Suk.
(The polite message
doesn't sound like Jae Suk.)
They will definitely pick me.
I was being serious.
(Jae Suk shows a mysterious smile.)
Hello.
I got a message.
"You're the first Mafia."
(You're the 1st Mafia.)
Today,
we're having
Prisoner's Dilemma Race.
You and another member
are the first Mafias.
What will happen then?
I'll give you the first mission.
What is it?
The hidden mission
for the Mafias is...
They will have no idea.
They will totally fall for it.
(Jae Suk carried out the hidden
mission without anyone knowing.)
You get 300 dollars
for carrying out the mission.
(He got 300 dollars
for carrying out the mission.)
(The Mafias start taking
the lead with the black money.)
It's Yoo Jae Suk and Yang Se Chan.
I pick Yang Se Chan and Yoo Jae Suk.
(Suk Jin also names
Yoo Jae Suk and Yang Se Chan.)
Yang Se Chan and Yoo Jae Suk.
- I think Yang Se Chan...
- They all seem suspicious.
- The voting results are in.
- Okay.
Jae Suk, you've been named...
as a suspect for the Mafia.
The other suspect is not revealed.
(There's one more person
who's named as a suspect.)
(But they don't know
if the suspect is the Mafia or not.)
But in this Mafia game,
you're not eliminated
just because you're chosen.
(The game doesn't end
when the Mafia is arrested.)
The two members
with the most votes...
will be interrogated by the other
members in different rooms.
After the interrogation,
the two suspects will choose...
between silence or confession.
They can either win or lose money
according to the results.
Let's say the two suspects
are both Mafias.
If they both remain silent,
there won't be any change.
So they will stay as the Mafias
and carry out their missions.
This way, they can make more money.
But if one of them confesses,
and the other remains silent,
the one who confessed
will get money,
but the one who remained silent
will lose 1,000 dollars.
And there will be new Mafias.
(The Mafias will be replaced)
If they both confess,
they will lose 500 dollars each.
In this case, the Mafias
will also be replaced.
So the two suspects don't know
about each other.
If they both remain silent,
it will be the best choice.
If one of them confesses, he or she
will be the only one to make money.
And the other will
suffer a great loss.
- If the other suspect is innocent,
- That's right.
he or she will have no choice
but to remain silent.
In this case, if you remain silent,
nothing will change.
If you confess,
you will lose a little money,
and the other Mafia
will suffer a great loss.
(Mafia 1 loses 100 dollars,
and Mafia 2 loses 500 dollars.)
(For Jae Suk, it is important
to know who the other suspect is.)
So the Mafias should
confess together.
I have to make them confess
no matter what.
(The 5 members will interrogate
the suspects as detectives.)
So it's possible that both of
the two suspects are not Mafias.
(The detectives have to make
someone confess to earn money.)
It's interesting already.
First, Jae Suk, you will
go to the interrogation room now.
My goodness.
(Mafia Jae Suk goes
to the interrogation room first.)
(The suspects are moved separately,
so they can't see each other.)
(The other suspect might not be
the one I thought of.)
(Mafia Jae Suk is curious
about the other suspect.)
I will have to keep insisting
that I'm innocent.
(Mafia Jae Suk goes
into the interrogation room.)
(And the second suspect goes
into the other interrogation room.)
(Both suspects are
in the interrogation rooms now.)
(The quiet interrogation rooms
are waiting for them.)
I became the suspect
all of a sudden.
(Interrogation Room 1)
Stochastically, it is difficult...
to spot both of the Mafias.
Even though I'm picked,
it is possible that
the other suspect is innocent.
(Jae Suk thinks there is a citizen
in the other interrogation room.)
I will risk it.
(I will risk it hoping there is
a citizen in the other room.)
(Interrogation Room 2)
- What should we do to catch them?
- What?
What should we do
to catch the Mafias?
I have to see their faces first.
I need to look them in the eye.
(Who is the second suspect?)
Who is it?
- Se Chan.
- Hello.
It's not me.
Hey, sit down.
- Sit.
- Seriously, I'm not the Mafia.
I should turn off the camera first.
Why would you turn it off?
- This is nothing like that.
- What do you mean?
Have a seat.
This is an interrogation.
Let's go to the Room of Truth.
- You...
- Why Room of Truth?
This is what I said earlier.
I said I really didn't want
Jong Kook to come into this room.
- Why are you so dressed up?
- What?
- You're all dressed up.
- I just...
got a haircut.
And they did my hair there.
And you're wearing
fancy clothes today.
That's not true.
You think you're the main character
in today's episode.
Think about it. If I were the Mafia,
why would I show that?
You're just dressed like a Mafia.
No.
I can explain. In Gangnam...
I don't need your explanation.
- Don't bother.
- You go...
- to the same beauty shop with me.
- No.
Listen to me. I was going
to get a haircut today.
But I didn't want to leave the shop
only after a haircut.
So I got my hair
and makeup done there.
Then I heard about the mission.
- That can't be true.
- This is what it sounds like.
"I got my hair
and makeup done there."
- "Then I was told I'm the Mafia."
- That's not true.
- It's not me.
- You know what I mean.
I'm not the Mafia.
And one of you two is
trying to frame me.
Don't do that.
Don't give me that look.
Looked at objectively,
what he says doesn't make sense.
Do you know why?
Because I'm flustered.
You guys are cornering me
when I'm not the Mafia. It's not me.
He's overreacting.
I don't think both the suspects
are the Mafias.
But one of the suspects might
be the Mafia.
You think?
"One of the suspects might be?"
- "One of the suspects might be."
- You're a word magician.
I'm acting strange
because you're cornering me.
But it's not me, seriously.
I'm not the Mafia.
Where is he?
Hey, Yoo Jae Suk.
It's good to see him.
It's you.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- Me too.
I'm telling you again.
- Excuse me.
- You made a wrong guess.
That's not true. We are right.
Take a look at this.
Listen, Jae Suk.
We were talking
about Suk Jin's nose.
That's what you like to talk about.
Because you like...
to make fun of Suk Jin.
- I see.
- Right?
- That's not true.
- But...
You had a good chance
to tease Suk Jin here.
While we were making jokes,
- you suddenly...
- Eating.
"I want to eat with you guys."
- He suddenly said that.
- I was serious.
And...
while we were confused,
you suddenly asked
if we liked mint chocolate.
You punk!
Why, you punk?
"Why, you punk?"
I've never seen you...
talk about mint chocolate
for the past 30 years.
It's just that
people like to talk...
- about mint chocolate these days.
- I don't know about that.
- Why did you suddenly bring it up?
- What's with mint chocolate?
I wanted to talk...
- about random things.
- Why?
- I told you.
- Because it was your mission?
It wasn't a mission? I just...
hated the flow of the conversation
in the chat room.
A few of us were leading
the conversation.
That's what you did.
I'm telling you again.
I just hated it.
That's why I brought that up.
- That's what you do.
- It's just strange.
You don't usually
talk about random things.
That's because I hated
the way the talk went.
From the beginning, you were like,
"I'm Yoo Jae Suk."
Does that sound like you?
- By the way, he is...
- What?
Do you even have
a license or something?
I do, you punk.
Why do you keep
calling me like that?
You're being like this
with your weak fingers.
You punk.
(Upset)
Let go of it.
- Let go!
- All right.
- That's true.
- I know.
So...
you shouldn't do this with force.
Who do you think the Mafia is then?
- I thought it was Seok Sam.
- It's not me.
But it's not Seok Sam.
- I'm not the Mafia.
- Then...
- I think it's him.
- Se Chan.
- He suddenly picks me. Okay.
- Yes.
- It might be him.
- It's him.
- He talked a lot.
- Seriously, he is...
- Honestly...
- I'm serious.
- You.
- He's so gullible.
- Hey.
- Seriously...
- Ji Hyo.
- It's you.
He's strange.
All right. Se Chan
will confess anyway.
I'm sure he will.
All right. Se Chan
will confess anyway.
What will you do?
(Is it Yang Se Chan?)
See? You're dumbfounded.
- He will confess.
- You're the Mafia. Tell us.
It's not me.
- He will say your name anyway.
- No.
Jong Kook, listen. When we chatted
in a group chat before,
- I shared pictures too...
- See? He's talking about the past.
He behaved as he always does
on purpose. Do you see what I mean?
"I have always behaved like this,
so I won't get caught."
- He thought that if he were quiet,
- He improvised.
he would be suspected.
- So he chatted as he always does.
- You know I wouldn't do that.
- Come on.
- I bet he's taken aback now.
- No. That's not true. Okay.
- Try to talk calmly.
- Go ahead.
- I can tell he's the Mafia already.
- So try to calm down a little bit.
- I'm not the Mafia.
Just confess to us on the other one.
- You'd better do that.
- Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
Look at this.
The Mafia who confesses gets
100 dollars. That's better, right?
- Yes. Of course.
- Right?
- That's better.
- My gosh.
The Mafia who chooses silence loses
1,000 dollars, you know.
Hey, listen. Locust, we'll help you,
so just tell us.
- Tell us.
- Right.
I'm not the Mafia.
Why are you guys... This is crazy.
I'll give you information to clarify
the rules. In every mission,
there's only one Mafia
in each interrogation room.
That is, there's only one Mafia
in this room.
(There's only one Mafia
in each interrogation room.)
(That means Jae Suk is
the only Mafia among them.)
Besides, it'd be weird if I confess
when I'm not the Mafia.
That sounds suspicious too.
- I'm not lying. I'm not the Mafia.
- What do you mean by that?
- It'd be weird.
- What do you mean?
Why can't you speak
as well as you usually do?
I get nervous
when I'm with Jong Kook.
You see...
You know me. Wouldn't I have
told you if I were the Mafia?
Do you think "I want to eat
with you" is a funny comment?
He's the Mafia.
I'm 100 percent sure of it.
- The other one will snitch on you.
- No.
I'm telling you, Se Chan will
snitch on you anyway.
- Right. Snitch on the other one.
- Snitch on the other one.
- Just tell us.
- Should I show you again?
- If you don't...
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
- Seriously...
- Come on.
- Darn it!
- What's wrong?
- Darn it! I can't believe this.
- Darn!
- Hey, calm down.
- Wait. What is it?
- Why?
- Darn it!
- What is it?
- Gosh!
- Calm down.
- You little...
- Why are you doing this suddenly?
- Are you trying to...
- Hold him.
- What's the matter?
- Hey, don't harm yourself.
- Hold on a second.
- You see, I...
- Call Detective Kim.
- What do we do?
- We should calm him down.
- All you have to do is confess.
- It's okay. That happens.
- Just tell us.
- Things happen. You'll be okay.
- Tell us who the other one is.
- Tell us and get 100 dollars.
- This is so unfair.
- Seriously.
- You got involved in a crime.
- But that can happen.
- You must've been flustered.
- That can happen to anyone.
- I got involved...
Now, Jae Suk, you have to choose
between silence and confession.
You should choose to confess
no matter what.
(What could be
Mafia Jae Suk's choice?)
- I'm not the one. I have no choice.
- If that's true... Hey.
Listen. If he's not the Mafia,
- I said I'm not.
- he has no choice but to be silent.
- That's right.
- Yes, if he's not the Mafia.
- Then you chose silence, right?
- Yes.
- All right.
- He stayed loyal to the end.
- That's not it. I'm not the Mafia.
- Hey, guys.
I don't think he's the Mafia.
Hang on. Jae Suk...
- Will you confess?
- No, I can't. I'm not the Mafia.
- It's because we've been...
- I choose silence.
- He would've confessed if he's one.
- Yes.
- Se Chan chose...
- He confessed, right?
- Did he choose to confess?
- silence.
Oh, my. He chose silence?
- Both of them chose silence? Yes.
- Then there won't be a change.
The Mafias will get
another hidden mission.
I'll explain the rules
when everyone gathers.
Maybe we were wrong.
- But...
- I'm sure Se Chan is the Mafia.
I have no idea.
Today, there are Mafias
in each round.
It's Chaotic Running Man.
You will receive prize money
according to your ranking.
The Mafia gets 300 dollars
for completing a hidden mission.
- I see.
- The Mafias of the first round...
already received 300 dollars
while the others have no money.
After each round, you choose
two people to interrogate by vote.
You have to make them confess
to succeed.
The citizens get 200 dollars
if they catch the Mafias.
If the Mafias confess
and get caught,
the next Mafias are randomly chosen.
The final top 2 will get a prize,
and the bottom 2 will get a penalty.
- I don't know.
- Wasn't So Min in our room?
Hey, why did you say,
"Buy us a meal?"
- Exactly. Why did you say that?
- What do you mean?
- He said he wanted to eat with us.
- Yes, I did.
- He said that.
- I meant that.
Because he said that,
- I just replied.
- Didn't you try to help him?
- Who? Me? Why would I help him?
- Yes.
- Hey, if you point that out...
- You didn't have to...
You were the first to reply
when he asked about mint chocolate.
- True. You said you like it.
- That's right.
- Right.
- True. But after that...
- I've been suspecting him too.
- Right.
I mean... Listen to me.
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, and I...
The four of us were in the room.
There's one among us
and another among the others.
- We were told so.
- Really?
There's only one Mafia in each room.
- There can't be 2 Mafias in 1 room.
- We weren't informed of that.
- Then I'm off the hook.
- You're suspecting me?
- Me?
- It's weird that he brought it up.
- Why me again?
- He brought it up suddenly.
- We were talking about the nose.
- Believe me. I'm not the Mafia.
- She hasn't done it in a while.
- I think So Min is the Mafia.
- Right. I just realized it.
- What she said opened my eyes.
- "They never let me be the Mafia."
- This is driving me crazy.
- Is it you?
- Pardon? Me?
They never choose me
as the Mafia, you know.
- I'm not the Mafia today, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, you're so smart.
- You saw through her.
- In the next round,
- So Min will confess.
- I think so too.
- You're done for.
- Let's see if you confess or not.
- Why is everyone suspecting me...
- Choose her as a suspect.
- when I've done nothing?
- She'll confess if she's the Mafia.
- All of us haven't been one...
- We should check her comments...
- to find out what her mission was.
- You sent the photo as a reply.
- You might have...
- Okay. Then interrogate me.
I'll remain silent.
- What?
- Just know...
- that I'm not the Mafia.
- If we interrogate her,
- she'll tell us everything.
- She'll confess.
- Both of them will confess.
- Actually...
- She'll tell us everything.
- Absolutely.
- So Min can go home now.
- True.
- That's true.
- So Min will go home now.
- She'll tell us everything.
- Say goodbye to the viewers.
- Okay.
- It was a mistake.
- I'm stressed out.
- Once he suspects someone...
- It's really stressful.
- I know.
"You are the Mafia.
With Mafia Jae Suk..."
(So Min was chosen as the Mafia
along with Jae Suk.)
("You are the Mafia.
With Mafia Jae Suk, carry out...")
"You are the Mafia.
With Mafia Jae Suk,"
"carry out the hidden mission."
Am I the Mafia?
I'm the Mafia?
"Make an acrostic poem
with your name."
What's this?
"Write sentences starting with
your initials in the chat room."
(Making acrostic poems
with the Mafias' initials)
(The Mafias made acrostic poems
with "YJS" and "JSM".)
(Just like this.)
(Suk Jin has been learning to use
Excel according to rumors.)
I'm done.
(My, I'm embarrassed.)
I can be very funny
when I chat online.
(Yoo Jae Suk is here. Joyful shoot.)
(Seok Sam will be with us.)
(You should've seen me as a star.
Jae Suk said that before.)
What sentence should I make
starting with "S"?
That's Suk Jin's photo. Good.
"Suk Jin's nose..."
(You should've seen me as a star.
Jae Suk said that before.)
(Suk Jin's nose.)
It looks like a gourd dipper.
"Just so you know,
I'm still a star."
I can't think of any word
starting with "S".
"Small wishes of mine."
(Small wishes of mine.
I want to eat with you.)
"Small wishes of mine.
I want to eat with you."
What's this?
They'll notice something's going on.
Mine is really natural.
"Mint chocolate.
Do you guys like it?"
They won't know what I'm doing.
They'll be completely fooled.
- Great job.
- They won't know.
- I did a really good job.
- They can never figure it out.
It sounds so natural.
Since the others were talking a lot,
it was easy for me
to make it sound relative.
(But she faced a crisis right away.)
(Detective Kook's eyes are
already fixed on So Min.)
Please change your clothes. We'll
give the Mafias a new mission.
- Then we'll gather again.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- I'll keep an eye on So Min.
She'll try to complete
the hidden mission.
(The Mafias won't be replaced.)
(And the 2 Mafias will be given
a new hidden mission.)
You'll be given
the second hidden mission.
- You have to carry it out later.
- I see.
It's Speak in Melody.
What's that?
- My package has arrived
- Oh, I see. Okay.
The 2 of you should make
more than 5 comments like this.
- In total?
- Yes.
- Each must do it at least once.
- Understood.
Got it. They all know
about the hidden mission now.
I'll get the money if I complete
the mission, right?
(Jae Suk is moving
to the mission location.)
Jae Suk, the hidden mission is
so difficult this time.
Did you read
my acrostic poems earlier?
You should be loud enough
for everyone to hear you.
What should we do?
- Hey, So Min.
- Yes?
I'll start singing,
and you answer me.
You know what I mean, right?
Right?
(Jae Suk who is famous
for his playfulness will initiate.)
They'll suspect us anyway.
- You never know.
- Let's see how it goes.
Let's see how things go first.
- What?
- It was funny.
The two Mafias are here already.
Welcome
(Jae Suk sings to welcome him
as he walks in.)
Here we go
What is this? What are you doing?
The two Mafias arrived before us.
- The Mafias are already here
- Look at him.
- We're so excited
- This is strange.
You're really something else
Why are you acting so arrogant?
Are you carrying out
a hidden mission or what?
- You're a know-it-all
- Are you singing?
La, la, la, la, the two Mafias
(He joined them in singing
without knowing what's going on.)
I am not the Mafia
I am not the Mafia either
I think you two are the Mafias
- That's not true
- You two are the Mafias
- Why are we the Mafias?
- You are wrong
I am not the Mafia
- Neither am I
- You're "Ma," you're "Fi"
You
- I'm "A"
- I am "Ma"
- She's "Fi", and you're "A"
- I'm "A"
- Ma, Fi, A
Ma, Fi, A
- Welcome
- It's good to see you again
- The Mafias were here when I came.
- I see.
- Seok Sam is the Mafia
- You got caught
- He got caught
- He's "Ma," and she's "Fi"
- He's "A," Ma, Fi, A
- Ma, Fi, A
- Are there three of them?
- Yes.
That means
there are three Mafias here.
Two Mafias are enough.
No, he's "Ma," and she's "Fia"
- You're "A," Ma, Fi, A
- That's not true
What's going on? Please sit down.
Seok Sam is so funny.
- I know.
- Suk Jin is so funny.
- You're so funny, Suk Jin.
- Sorry?
I'll give you the first mission
right away.
The first mission is
Keyword Adventurer.
- What?
- "Keyword Adventurer?"
- I know a lot.
- I don't like this.
We'll give you...
- two keywords.
- Oh, gosh.
Discuss together to choose the one
that's been searched more.
- One that has been searched more?
- Yes.
If you look at this website,
when you enter two keywords,
(They'll use this website that shows
the search volumes in 16 regions.)
- Oh, it shows tallied volumes.
- it compares the search volumes...
- in the 16 regions in the country.
- Really?
- In different regions.
- You have to pick the keyword...
that's been searched more
in more regions to win.
The results are different
in those regions, right?
If it's searched more
in nine regions,
it's the winning keyword.
- That's the winner.
- Correct.
You get one point whenever you pick
the winning keyword.
And you'll be ranked in the end.
The person in 1st place gets
500 dollars,
and the person in 2nd place gets
400 dollars.
- The 3rd place gets 300 dollars.
- Okay.
- The bottom two won't get any.
The Mafias will get 300 dollars each
if they complete the hidden mission.
I see.
The Mafias will carry out...
- Are they doing it right now?
- their own mission...
- other than this one, right?
- Yes. They got a hidden mission.
(The citizens were reminded of
the hidden mission again.)
Have you been doing it
the whole time?
I'm not the Mafia.
I'll keep an eye on So Min
to find out what her mission is.
- Let's keep an eye on her.
- I'm really not the Mafia.
- I'll keep an eye on her.
- I'll look only at So Min.
- That's a good idea.
- I'll do the same.
I'll keep an eye on So Min too.
(Could they be able to sing 5 times
without being suspected?)
- Look.
- There are no lenses
(There are no lenses)
(The Mafias' Hidden Mission 1,
There are no lenses)
Jae Suk seems so energetic today.
- He's really energetic today.
- Indeed.
- He surprised me.
- He's so energetic.
- He won't take a break.
- There are no lenses
Why? Are you anxious
because you're the Mafia?
Yes, I'm the Mafia, I'm "Ma"
- I'm "Fi," and he's "A"
- She's "Fi," and you're "A"
- Ma, Fi, A
- There are only two Mafias here.
Not three.
- You're "Ma", and you're "Fia"
- It's confusing.
- Those who aren't the Mafias,
- You're "Ma"
- say that you're not the Mafia.
- You're "Ma", and you're "Fia"
(The Mafias succeeded twice
thanks to the naive Big Nose.)
Is it you?
Here go the first keywords.
(The 1st 2 keywords
will be revealed.)
- Ji Suk Jin versus...
- What?
- Ji Suk Jin?
- That's a weak competitor.
(What could be the other keyword?)
- I'm sure it wasn't searched a lot.
- I agree.
The other keyword is...
(The keyword
against Suk Jin's name is...)
- Yang Se Chan.
- I have a chance to win.
I have a chance to win.
- But you never know.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I might lose.
- Hey.
- You're no match for me.
- He became more popular...
- through "How Do You Play?."
- If I had to compare...
the search volumes to water,
they're trickling.
How dare you?
We compared the search volumes
in the past 12 months.
- In the past 12 months?
- I see.
- Hey.
- He drew attention recently.
Suk Jin may be popular
among those in their 50s and 60s,
but people in those age groups don't
use the internet often.
Teenagers and people in their 20s
would search my name.
But since he became
famous on social media,
they've looked up on him a lot.
Let's start by sharing
our own experiences...
- before discussing further.
- Okay.
The data
based on our own experiences...
can be realistic.
Did you search
Suk Jin's name recently?
- Never.
- Me neither.
What about you?
(They don't remember doing it.)
- Did you search his name recently?
- As for me...
I have never done it in my life,
not just recently.
- Not even once.
- Hey.
- That's sad. It's so hurtful.
- I've never searched yours either.
- Although he's my close friend,
- Have you searched your own names?
I never search his name
on the internet.
Me neither. Do you think I search
yours on the internet?
I searched Jong Kook's name
once a day several times.
- Why?
- Because of his YouTube channel.
- To check his subscribers?
- Exactly.
- I check that very often.
- I see.
The fact that I'm competing
against Se Chan itself...
- hurts my pride.
- I've searched Se Chan's name.
- I don't want to lose.
- Right? Your pride is on the line.
- I don't want to lose to him.
- It's because...
Suk Jin is famous but not popular.
He's that kind of celebrity.
Why? It's true.
- You know that.
- I see what you mean.
- That's comforting.
- You know, right?
- You know what I mean, right?
- You see...
I think we're neck and neck.
- The period makes it even harder.
- That's right.
- Although it was another show,
- Exactly.
- he became very popular.
- It made him much more popular.
- Since it's a year...
- If it's based on the past year,
his appearance on that show must've
had a great influence.
I can beat you without that.
- Without that...
- You'd be at the bottom without it.
- You wouldn't have a chance.
- Why is he acting so arrogant?
I can beat you.
Come on. You can't beat me.
Hey, how many followers do you have
on social media?
I have a little more than 700,000...
Not so many.
- Did you say 70?
- What? No.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- If he has 70 followers...
The staff members of this show alone
are more than 100.
Don't think that they all followed
your account.
All of you, follow my account
if you haven't yet.
- It's not too late.
- Seventy sounds just right.
- It's perfect.
- That's a good point, but...
- I have 2.3 million...
- You have 230 followers?
No, I have 2.3 million followers.
It's time to make a choice.
He's been popular lately.
- Also...
- Whatever the reason was...
Also, he became more popular
because he cried on TV.
(He gained popularity by crying.)
- That's true.
- He cried on TV shows.
Anyone would've felt bad.
- Using tears is...
- But that's...
- It's called "using sympathy."
- Oh, I see.
- Tonight
(Tonight, you and me alone together)
- Let's have a party
(Tonight, you and me alone together,
let's have a party)
(He started singing
inspired by the expression.)
- Do it one more time.
- Wait. Why did you sing?
(Wait. Why did you sing?)
- It sounds similar to "party."
- Oh, my.
- You got caught.
- You're "Ma," and you're "Fi"
It sounds similar to "party."
- He did the same thing earlier.
- You got caught.
(He did the same thing earlier.)
(Se Chan started to suspect
Mafia Song that he improvised.)
- He sang this.
- What was that?
- So Min sang with him, right?
- Yes.
- I just sang along.
- Actually...
- Before you guys came,
- Singing DJ DOC's song?
Suk Jin sang the song.
- Is that the hidden mission?
- He sang it.
You're so smart as always.
- Did he say "scary?"
- It sounded like "scary."
- "Scary?"
- I'm not scary.
- I just took a guess.
She is my only target.
- Right. I know.
- I don't worry about you.
- I agree with you guys.
- Just say you're sorry.
- Catching her will solve all.
- Absolutely.
She'll tell us the other one.
You know how the police catch
one drug dealer...
- and arrest so many others too.
- Jong Kook.
- Why would you...
- Look at So Min. She got rash...
- on her chin because of stress.
- If you're not...
- the Mafia, it'd be a good thing.
- I'm not the Mafia.
- It'd be a good thing.
- I wonder why he always picks me.
- That's not true.
- I'm "Ma"
(Jae Suk started singing the song
that guarantees success.)
- No, you're "Ma," and you're "Fia"
- There are two Mafias here.
There are only two of them.
Stop confusing me by singing that.
(Moving back and forth)
Why am I stuck between them? Gosh.
- The age group is important too.
- True.
Haha, you should pick my name.
Aren't you a young man?
Se Chan is more popular than him.
- Exactly. He's popular and famous.
- Suk Jin has been...
- working in this industry...
- He's famous too.
- for a long time, you know.
- He's more popular than me?
- Hey, you punk.
- Like I said before,
- he's not popular, and Se Chan is.
- They're so serious.
- Even when I'm wearing a mask...
- But Se Chan isn't so famous.
(Composed by Yoo Jae Suk,
Which one is more popular?)
(It's me)
(I don't know, it's definitely me)
Check if his mic is turned on,
Sound Director.
- But I think
- Why does he keep singing?
(But I think that Se Chan is)
(This much more popular
than Suk Jin)
(Nonsense, that's ridiculous)
(I am more popular than him,
do you know why?)
(I am more popular than you,
I can assure you)
- I'm more popular than he is
- Just make a choice already.
- You're C-class, I'm A-class
- Do you know...
he didn't say why?
Why didn't you write the lyrics
after "Do you know why?"
Why didn't he write the reason?
(It's because he's bad
at improvising)
(Chorus Se Chan,
Quit being a comedian)
(Chorus Haha,
Where did all my ideas go?)
(Help me find my ideas
that left my head)
(The reward is 200 dollars)
- Just quit
- That's too little
(The veteran comedian is
still excited.)
(Thanks to Big Nose, the Mafias
completed the hidden mission.)
Should I choose Suk Jin's name?
You should make your choices now.
We don't have much time.
- I choose my name.
- Ji Hyo.
I choose Suk Jin.
- I choose Suk Jin.
- I came to the same conclusion.
- I think it's his name.
- I choose Suk Jin too.
- I choose Se Chan.
- Hey!
- I'm the only one who chose him.
- It's because...
We both have a protruding mouth.
- I wonder who wins? I'm so curious.
- I'm curious too.
Can we really check that?
- It's fascinating.
- Do they really have such data?
I'll type Suk Jin's name first.
This is the result.
Now, I'm going to type
Se Chan's name.
- We'll see red spots on the map.
- Right.
If there are more red spots,
does it mean I win?
- Let's find out.
- Here we go.
(The star with 2.3 million followers
who gained fame with tears)
(Yang Ssaebssaeb who is popular
among young people)
- It was early August, right?
- Three, two...
When he was on the show
as MSG Wannabe...
Oh, my. Suk Jin wins.
That's amazing.
It's an absolute victory.
Hey, you can't... But you won
in Gyeonggi Province.
In Incheon...
(Suk Jin wins.)
(The winning keyword is
"Ji Suk Jin.")
In Incheon, Daejeon,
North Chungcheong Province,
and Busan, Se Chan won.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Se Chan must be sad.
- Thank you.
I knew it.
- You see...
- I lost to Suk Jin.
- That was the whole point.
- Right.
It is what it is.
Here go the second keywords.
"Jeon So Min" versus "Haha."
Obviously, So Min wins.
- No way. I think...
- Haha wins.
- that Haha wins.
- I don't think so.
It's because Haha has been doing
so many unnecessary things.
- Haha...
- Yes.
really does
a lot of unnecessary things.
- Haha...
- He's seen at a lot of places.
There's a rumor
that he does anything...
- for chump change.
- That's right.
- Everyone in the industry knows.
- True.
- Just a little...
- That's true.
I'd do anything for money,
but not for chump change.
- That's true.
- I have pride.
- He does almost everything.
- True.
- Not for chump change, you punk.
- Really?
I'd do anything for money.
Listen up, everyone.
- I'd take any jobs for money.
- Hey.
But I won't do it for chump change.
- Listen.
- It was unexpected.
Unlike your expectation,
Suk Jin would...
sign a contract
only if you offer a lot of money.
- Not chump change.
- That's why...
he's been stacking
a bad reputation in the industry.
- I cost more than you think.
- Right.
A lot more than you think.
This time around, I choose me.
I'll take the other route
and choose Haha.
I choose Haha too.
- I choose So Min.
- Ji Hyo.
- You're choosing So Min?
- Why?
Because...
- she's someone who...
- She stands out.
She's an eccentric character,
so people would look her up
out of curiosity.
- I'm not that well-known.
- Have you looked her up?
- No.
- They could have...
since they don't know her.
- They don't know me well.
- That's how it could be.
This is nerve-wracking in a way.
(Whose name
was searched more online?)
- It's obvious.
- Haha.
Who's in the lead? Haha or So Min?
- Haha has more votes.
- Then I choose So Min.
- I'm taking an aggressive approach.
- You're on the offence.
You've made your choices.
- It has to be Haha.
- I bet it's So Min.
Then I should've chosen Haha.
- It's So Min.
- The red...
- There's a huge spike.
- It's So Min.
- Gosh.
Look, So Min won.
(Haha, Jeon So Min)
(So Min wins.)
- You should be grateful...
- Gangwon Province.
- to those in Gangwon Province.
- And Gwangju.
What's that small region?
- Gwangju.
- Gwangju?
Gwangju, I love you!
Gangwon Province, I love you!
- Doesn't it feel great?
- It does.
- Both times...
- It feels great.
South Jeolla Province...
and Seoul!
(So Min is clearly ahead
in three regions.)
- Goodness.
- In South Jeolla Province.
- South Jeolla Province and Seoul.
- Jeolla Province.
- Of course.
- She filmed something there.
- You're right.
- Thank you, people of Wando.
She clearly took the lead
in North Gyeongsang Province...
- with 74 percent.
- I got it, all right?
- Hey.
- It's 74 to 26.
- That's enough.
- It serves you right...
- for teasing me.
- I get it.
- So much for teasing me.
- You sure aren't popular...
for someone who mimics
the dialect a lot.
I'm upset, you know.
That's exactly why
they don't like you.
- Gyeongsang Province!
- That's why they hate you.
Gyeongsang Province,
are you kidding me?
- That's why they hate you.
- They hate that tone.
Could we do one with Haha and me?
Yes, we can set it up.
- Me and Haha.
- Se Chan and Haha.
- Haha and Se Chan?
- Me and Haha.
You've got to be kidding me.
- His numbers were pretty low.
- Right?
It's why I challenged him.
His numbers were really low.
He lost to So Min 74 to 26.
Should we scrap the idea?
Would it only hurt your pride?
Let's do it.
Let's do this. I choose me.
- I choose Haha.
- It was close.
(A special match between
Haha and Se Chan)
- I choose Haha.
- Haha?
- I choose Haha too.
- Me too.
I choose Haha as well.
(I choose Haha as well.)
(He's the only one
who chose Se Chan.)
Let's see.
Did everyone choose Haha?
If everyone else chose Haha,
I'll switch to Se Chan.
Thank you.
The way I see it,
it could be a strategic choice.
Why are his numbers higher?
(Whose name was searched more?)
- There you go.
- Se Chan...
- See?
- Haha won.
Isn't it enough to make you crawl?
- See?
- Haha won.
Isn't it enough to make you crawl?
(Isn't it enough to make you crawl?)
(Grunting)
It must feel great to be popular.
Being popular...
Lucky you!
I didn't expect such a landslide.
- Hold on a second.
- I must still be popular.
- Nicely done.
- Haha,
Suk Jin must be way below you too.
- Right.
- Let me challenge Suk Jin.
No, don't.
Let's take a look.
- It won't even be close.
- I can beat Suk Jin.
- Go ahead then.
- What do you say?
- Let's do it.
- I choose me.
- I choose Haha.
- Haha.
- I choose Haha too.
Haha, of course.
- I'll bet my entire savings.
- I choose Haha.
The result won't be the same.
(The two winners go head to head.)
Look.
Crawl. Grovel at his feet!
(The whole nation is blue.)
I didn't expect
the difference to be this big.
- Darn it.
- Gosh.
I still have it.
You're still very well-known.
You're the best.
At least two are
less popular than I am.
Why do you find me so charming?
You're not as charming...
as So Min.
- But Se Chan and Suk Jin...
- You're more charming than them.
- That's your charm.
- You're right.
- Nice.
- It's right.
I'd like to see...
Suk Jin versus mint chocolate.
Mint chocolate?
How about Jae Suk and Pengsoo?
Why does he keep mentioning
mint chocolate?
- Jae Suk and Pengsoo?
- No, mint chocolate.
Look.
No, mint chocolate. Look.
- Mint chocolate.
- Mint chocolate won.
(Mint chocolate wins
by a large margin.)
Mint chocolate won.
- Mint chocolate won?
- Mint chocolate won.
Mint chocolate won.
Gosh, mint chocolate won.
But no one can...
- beat mint chocolate.
- I love mint chocolate.
We were only curious.
How can one beat it?
- I love mint chocolate.
- Jae Suk and mint chocolate.
(Jae Suk vs mint chocolate)
It's absolutely beatable.
- Mint chocolate got crushed.
- It's absolutely beatable.
- I won against mint chocolate.
Let's see Jae Suk and Pengsoo.
Even Pengsoo...
- Nice!
- Even Pengsoo...
- Maybe last year, but...
- What about Bboongbboong?
Let's try Suk Jin and water bottle.
- He'd definitely beat that.
- Water bottle.
Water bottle?
(Suk Jin's last shred of dignity
is on the line.)
Water bottle won.
Water bottle won?
(Water bottle is more popular
than Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin, do better, will you?
What about Suk Jin and a pebble?
(Suk Jin vs Pebble)
- I'm only joking.
- See?
He lost to water bottles...
and then to pebbles.
Let's see Haha and water bottle.
Haha and water bottle.
- Please let me win.
- I hope Haha wins.
Of course he'll win.
- Please.
- Haha will win.
You can tell by the numbers.
- He won.
- Haha won.
(Groaning)
You could tell by the numbers alone.
How can a water bottle
be more popular than you?
How is that possible?
Watch.
Call it "sir."
Suk Jin, address it as "sir."
How can this be?
Always grab one
with two hands from now on.
- Water bottles...
- My gosh.
How can this be?
(The battle only left
Suk Jin in scars.)
What a nice way to wrap up a game.
Right now,
two are tied for first place.
Haha and So Min.
(Tied in 1st place
are Haha and So Min.)
I guess a lot correctly though.
- Okay.
- Next,
in third place is Ji Hyo.
(3rd place: Ji Hyo)
And in fourth place is Jong Kook.
Se Chan and Jae Suk
will receive 100 dollars each.
Suk Jin receives nothing.
- Suk Jin receives nothing?
- That's right.
Seok Sam is at zero dollars
I kept choosing wrong.
- You're the smartest investor
- Seok Sam is at zero dollars
It's fine. The game's not over yet.
- The Mafia's secret mission...
- They completed it, didn't they?
- Yes, they completed it.
- Both of them?
- See? It's not me.
- Mint chocolate, the singing...
- Near the end...
It's you.
You suddenly started singing.
Once we get So Min,
- we'll find out the rest.
- You suddenly started singing.
We can kill two birds
with one stone.
- With one stone.
- It really isn't me.
(Will the citizens be able
to catch the Mafia?)
- Is it really not you?
- No.
Got it.
The two I suspect? It's...
So Min and Jae Suk.
I still suspect Jae Suk.
He mentioned mint chocolate again.
Also, I trust Jong Kook's hunch.
I choose So Min.
- So Min and...
- Jae Suk.
- Jeon So Min.
- And Jae Suk.
I'm sure of it.
(The suspects: So Min and Jae Suk)
The vote has been tallied.
You have been suspect as the Mafia.
(Will they be able to protect
each other by remaining silent?)
Let them question me already.
I'm one of the people they suspect.
Hey, Jong Kook.
- Jae Suk and So Min.
- That's what I wrote.
Yes, those two.
Only this seems right.
You all wrote Jae Suk
and So Min, right?
- Of course.
- So Min will snitch on him.
Jong Kook should
take care of So Min.
I'll get her to snitch.
I know I can get her to talk.
Come on in.
- So Min, you must be exhausted.
- Of course.
That's right. I'm the Mafia.
- Yes, we know.
- I'm the Mafia,
- so have a seat.
- Get talking.
Have a seat.
- You sure gave up fast.
- Sit down already.
The thought of being grilled
must've eaten you up inside.
Whose name did you write down?
- Apart from me.
- Jae Suk, of course.
- You too, Ji Hyo?
- Of course.
- It's the same for all of us.
- You too?
We all wrote down you and Jae Suk.
We already knew you were the Mafia.
That's why Se Chan
had to remain silent.
You were obviously the Mafia.
And now, Jae Suk will rat you out.
Does he know I'm a suspect too?
- Of course.
Is Jae Suk a suspect?
- Or is it another Mafia?
It's Jae Suk.
- You're out of options.
- Just snitch on him.
You can remain silent,
- but that will only hurt you.
- If both remain silent,
nothing will change.
- Gosh.
- If you snitch,
- you can at least get 100 dollars.
- Go ahead.
If you choose to remain silent,
but he talks,
you'll lose 1,000 dollars.
So this is why it's asked.
I bet the situation is upsetting.
- It's your second time here.
- You know that...
So Min will talk for sure.
(Suk Jin and Se Chan
use tiger moth as leverage.)
No, I don't know that.
The Yoo Family of Gangneung.
Just end it right here.
Wait, are you a comedian?
(He suddenly kicks off
a B-grade comedy sketch.)
This isn't a police station.
I've been wanting to do that.
- Right.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes, I'm a comedian.
- I see.
- You like being cheeky.
- That's right.
No wonder
he kept teasing others by singing.
- I love being cheeky.
- Right.
This is hilarious.
- I do.
- I love it.
(Detective Airhead
loves his character.)
Just snitch and be over with it.
Well, you see...
You'll know that she'll talk.
- I...
- So Min will snitch.
- I can't do it for free.
- Then?
Pay 100 dollars each
and offer me 200 dollars.
(The snitch suddenly asks
for a deal.)
Our money?
- Forget it.
- You're bold, aren't you?
- Look here.
- You love being cheeky.
- I don't have any money.
- Same here.
So you won't pay me?
Then don't talk.
- Just think about it.
- But know that So Min will.
So Min will talk.
Detective Jong Kook
went to handle her,
and he's determined
to get an answer out of her.
I'd like to hear
why you think I'm the Mafia.
- We're not going to tell you.
- Because I did nothing suspicious.
I won't say.
- I won't tell you.
- Why not?
- I won't tell you why?
Why must there be a reason
when you're the Mafia?
Why though?
- It means nothing.
- Why?
She gave up at first,
but now she's trying another route.
She thinks...
- she can get out of this.
- That's not it.
- I don't have any hope.
- Don't be hopeful.
- I'm not hopeful.
- Just know,
that we've made up our minds
about you being the Mafia.
We're here to only
hear you snitch on Jae Suk.
There's nothing else to talk about.
The best option for you
is to confess...
and for him to remain silent.
- Then you'll make more money.
- You should stick with that option.
If you choose to remain silent
and he confesses,
- you'll have to pay a lot.
- That's right.
The safest option
is the intersection.
I can't confess for free.
Then what?
What do you want us to do?
The 3 of you
should pay me 100 dollars.
- You want 100 dollars?
- Hey.
Why would you want us
to give you 100 dollars?
But you're at a disadvantage.
Since he knows that you're
a suspect, he'll confess for sure.
- I'm sure he will.
- Forget it.
- He'll confess for sure.
- Let's just go. Just let her be.
Let's go. Get up.
Get up, guys.
- Hold on.
- Get up.
Jong Kook. We should talk...
- since you're here already.
- But you said you won't confess.
- But...
- You said you won't confess.
Are you going to confess or not?
No, right? Let's leave.
- If you say you will, we'll help.
- We gave you a chance.
- I'll confess. I really will.
- You will?
(So Min ends up promising to confess
due to the pressure.)
- I will confess,
- Okay, good.
but I need someone on my side.
- We'll be on your side.
- We're on your side.
Then you should defend me.
- How?
- How do you want us to defend you?
Well, you need to protect me.
So this means...
if she decides to remain silent,
she'll lose 1,000 dollars.
- So give me 50 dollars each.
- The tiger moth is about to...
- We have nothing to spare.
- How much do I have?
You have nothing.
(The senior detective is penniless.)
- Why are the have-nots here?
- We don't have any money.
- Se Chan has 100 dollars.
- And you want 50 dollars from me?
- You...
- That's ridiculous.
- You should give him 100 dollars.
- No, I can't do that.
You're going to
win the prize money anyway.
- This puts me in a pickle.
- I guess we've been too nice.
- What should we do?
- What will you do?
Are you going to get beaten again?
(Moving slowly to punish him)
- Are you serious?
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Relax your arm.
Why are you...
Why are you twisting my arm?
He's horrible at doing
improvisation.
- Relax your arm.
- I mean...
Why would you twist my arm?
- Suk Jin.
- It's so upsetting that I couldn't.
You're not even a real detective.
Why would you twist my arm?
Just give me 50 dollars each.
- Make it 100 dollars.
- I told you. I have no money.
Are you going to confess?
(The moment of choice
is drawing near.)
- So Min, if you don't confess...
- For me...
- You don't have to confess.
- You can remain silent.
You'll take the fall.
It doesn't matter to us.
- If Jae Suk doesn't confess,
- Hey.
- Stop it. Leave her be.
- then I'll sell my house next week.
- Let her make her own decision.
- Make your choice now.
Why would you tell her that?
I just wanted to help her.
Stop it.
- I guess I care about you a lot.
- Let her make her own decision.
Gosh, this is so frustrating.
- Don't tell her.
- They're infuriating.
- I just wanted to help her.
I'm telling the truth.
- Stop it.
- I'll confess.
(I'll confess.)
(She surrenders completely
and repeatedly says she'll confess.)
- I'll confess.
- You'll confess everything?
- Will you confess everything?
- I'll tell you everything I know.
I'll tell you
all the necessary information.
I wanted to remain silent because
I was infuriated by Jong Kook,
but I chose to confess
because of you.
(Jong Kook's aggressive strategy
made her confess in the end.)
- You're seriously...
- Get up.
Are you not going to confess?
Let's get up.
(Jong Kook's aggressive strategy
made her confess in the end.)
I'll confess everything.
- Gather your power and confess up!
Just tell me
who is in the other room.
- Jae Suk...
- Let's see.
I'm sure he's going to confess too.
(The only choice remaining
is Jae Suk's.)
If you give me 100 dollars,
- I'll confess.
- Give him 100 dollars.
You're going to get 200 dollars.
- That's right.
- For you,
you'll be getting
an extra 150 dollars.
- Are we getting 200 dollars?
- Yes, you are.
You see?
Then I'll accept it.
I'm going to take it back
if you don't confess.
- Okay.
- Let's give him 50 dollars each.
- We'll give him 50 dollars each.
- All right.
- Good.
- Who is the Mafia?
It's So Min.
- You're the Mafia too, right?
- Yes, I am.
Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk...
- I'm sure he confessed.
confessed that So Min is the Mafia.
(Jae Suk confessed.)
- He didn't remain silent?
- I knew he'd confess.
- He would never.
- Why would he not remain silent?
- He'd never remain silent.
- Why would he?
- Of course he wouldn't.
The Mafias who can't trust
each other and confess...
- will lose 500 dollars each.
- I get it now.
It's fair that you two
lost the money together.
The citizens get 200 dollars each
for arresting the Mafias.
(The detectives get 200 dollars each
for arresting the Mafias.)
- Let's go have dinner.
- Thank you.
We should go eat now.
There's no need to even think.
I'm sure she confessed.
It's a given. I'm sure she did.
- It's time for lunch.
- Okay.
The Mafias have hidden missions
during lunch.
When you return to your room,
- we'll choose new Mafias.
- Of course.
- Are you picking them randomly?
- Yes.
We'll give them new missions.
- Then we'll have lunch.
- Got it.
He can become
the Mafia again, right?
- That's possible.
- I could.
- He can become one again.
- But that'll be difficult.
- It's difficult to become one.
- It's difficult.
(They're done selecting new Mafias.)
(Who are the Mafias that received
the new hidden mission?)
(A special place
for Running Mafias...)
(who are easily moved
by chicken feed)
This is insane.
- This place is so nice.
- Look how fancy it is.
It's so nice here.
"Presidential"...
It's really nice.
- This is incredible.
- This is good.
(And various dishes
placed in the middle of the room)
Suk Jin always orders lamb
for room service.
Thank you for the food.
You can freely move around the room
as you eat.
The Mafias are carrying out
the hidden mission.
Did you pick the Mafias randomly?
We picked them randomly
from the box we brought.
Then can the ones who already
played Mafia be picked again?
Where is the lamb?
Suk Jin always orders lamb
whenever he goes abroad.
- I should go over there, and...
- I love lamb.
I love it too.
- When we went to Mongolia,
- Mongolia.
he couldn't eat lamb.
Is the hidden mission to eat
someone else's food?
Is that the mission?
Doesn't your table have this?
We don't have this dish.
- You guys have different dishes?
- Yes, they're different.
Oh, are they?
- Se Chan, is there water?
- Sorry?
- Why would you ask him?
- Water?
So Min, are you at ease now?
I feel so much better.
I feel so relieved.
Earlier, you were
sitting in the corner.
I'm sure they are
doing their mission right now.
Come sit here.
Is that so?
Suk Jin is acting strange.
- You guys have this too.
- It's just what's in your head.
- You have this dish too.
- Everyone is acting strange.
- He's really strange.
- Isn't he acting really strange?
He's really strange.
What he just said was so awkward.
- I've been here before.
- Oh, is that so?
- There must be something here.
- It's so pretty here.
Can I take a look around the room?
- It's been so long...
- This is good.
since I ate in a hotel.
It feels like I'm on a trip.
I know.
There's abalone too.
Haha must be the Mafia.
(Detective Kim fixates his radar
on Haha at once.)
Haha is the new Mafia.
Me? Fine.
- I'm the Mafia.
- Yes, you are.
You're acting up a little.
- That was...
- Haha is the Mafia.
the first time I opened my mouth.
- Detective Kim is suspecting you.
- Fine.
- Of course.
- I swear...
(Detective Kim could be the Mafia.)
- Detective Kim is really scary.
- I'm sure he'll confess right away.
- What did you say?
- I dropped an apple.
All right. He'll confess right away.
Mister, don't move around!
- I mean...
- Gosh.
Then move to the other table.
Move.
You're the spy.
("Spy"?)
"Spy"?
- It's "Mafia".
- Not Mafia?
My goodness. Fine.
- He's the Mafia.
- I mean...
This is good.
(Laughing)
- Fine.
- Detective Kim is on him.
(The word "spy"
awoke the sleeping viper.)
I think you're done for.
Okay, fine.
- It's Haha.
- Fine. Let's see who wins.
- Let's go the full distance.
- "Spy"?
He said "spy".
My gosh. This is infuriating.
So Min, can you give me
some of yours? That one.
- This?
- Yes.
It's delicious.
- You keep asking for their food.
- He keeps asking for our food.
- Is your mission to eat their food?
- Can the same person...
What do you mean? I can even go
to that table and eat there.
Let's switch seats then.
So Min, can you give me
the new bowl of rice?
- Wait. You take it.
- You're acting strange.
- They keep bringing their food.
- You should take it yourself.
- Then I'll ask Ji Hyo to move.
- Take it yourself.
I can't make Ji Hyo get it for me.
- Thank you, Ji Hyo.
- I'll go get it.
- You asked Ji Hyo?
- That's not it.
- I know. That's why...
- He's being really strange.
You've never asked Ji Hyo
to do anything.
I was asking So Min.
Se Chan is acting strange.
He asked her to bring him
the bowl of rice.
He was in a hurry too.
Jong Kook is so scary.
He said you're scary.
- Okay, fine.
- You...
- I'm not the Mafia.
- Let's see.
- His vibe changed a little.
- He seems different, right?
He's a little elated.
- When he's given a role...
- He's a little elated.
The other Mafia must be really glad.
(The other Mafia
must be really glad.)
who is really glad...)
- We're done choosing new Mafias.
- Okay.
You're the new Mafia.
(Suk Jin is the Mafia.)
It's finally here.
The other Mafia is...
He's good.
Your hidden mission
is to remain seated...
if the other Mafia is standing.
So if both of you are standing
or seated, then you'll fail.
It's too difficult.
- It's so difficult.
- If the other one is standing...
(The hidden mission was given
to the Mafias.)
- You're only eating.
- You're suspicious.
- Then you should put it down too.
- Okay, I will.
- You can't stop him from eating.
- Exactly. That can't be a mission.
- I'll eat it.
- Here.
Your mission
isn't to have rice, right?
Seriously. Can you stop him?
I can eat the rice, can't I?
- No, you can't.
- Then give me 50 dollars.
Come on.
(Right then, Suk Jin sits down.)
(When Suk Jin sits down,
the other Mafia must stand up.)
Can you pass me the spoon?
- Sorry?
- The new spoon.
He keeps asking for things.
This is what I find strange.
- Right?
- You asked me?
It's not that I keep asking things.
The spoon is over there, that's why.
He keeps asking for things.
It's really strange.
- Just give me half.
- He's really strange.
After the interrogation,
we returned to our rooms, right?
(Detective Kim
is still suspecting Se Chan.)
He wasn't saying anything
but spacing out.
- He was thinking of what to do.
- He came into my room.
- The shoot was over too.
He didn't say anything,
- The Mafia...
- and he kept watching TV.
- is next to Jong Kook.
- Then you guys...
I wouldn't go into your room
if I were the Mafia.
Think about it.
I would never go into your room.
That's why you came to my room.
It's so strange that he asked
Ji Hyo to get something for him.
The rice was on the other table,
so I asked So Min,
but she didn't give it to me.
- So Ji Hyo brought it for me.
- I'll try giving the rice to him.
- What are you doing?
- I'm observing him.
- Are you sure you're observing him?
- Yes.
- Who are you observing?
- Ji Hyo is just eating.
Can I take this?
(Can I take this?)
- Can you bring me some rice?
- No, you can't take it.
(Haha suddenly sits down,
and Suk Jin runs out of ad-libs.)
He's acting really strange.
I'm telling you, I'm not the Mafia.
- I swear I'm not the Mafia.
- Is this mine?
What about Suk Jin?
- I'm not the Mafia.
- I swear I'm not the Mafia.
I'm not the Mafia.
- It could be Suk Jin.
- You and I are the targets.
(As Suk Jin sits down,
Haha gets up.)
(The Mafia's thrilling tiki-taka)
- It could be Suk Jin.
- You and I are the targets.
Suk Jin was acting weird
in the beginning.
- Right?
- I'm serious.
I'll pay for this if I'm the Mafia.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- Do you mean it?
- I'm not the Mafia.
But with what Se Chan is making,
- Of course he can.
- he can pay for this.
- I'm sure it won't cost much.
- He said I can pay for it...
with what I'm making.
He's seriously...
He never gives me a break.
He's more than capable
to pay for this.
- Of course he can.
- He can pay for this.
- He's more than capable.
- Of course.
But I don't think Suk Jin
can manage to pay for it.
(But I don't think Suk Jin
can manage to pay for it.)
(Even when they're talking
and laughing,)
(they're secretly carrying out
their hidden mission.)
- With what he's making?
- Suk Jin...
With what Suk Jin is making,
he won't be able to pay for this.
- It's too much for him?
- No, he can't pay for it.
You brat.
- So Min, you're okay, right?
- Aren't you having the rice?
Sorry?
What is he doing?
Don't touch my rice!
What's with this rice?
Is there a hidden mission?
Why isn't he eating it?
Why are you obsessed with rice?
- Why did you ask for it then?
- Wait a minute.
(Wait a minute.)
Isn't Suk Jin moving around a lot?
- Yes.
- What?
He tosses it to you.
- He rarely moves around.
- Then you toss it back to him.
- Then he gives it back to you.
- It's because you think it's me.
- Hey!
- You toss it back.
- Then he gives it to you.
- It's because you think it's me.
- I just got goosebumps.
- Why?
I'm sure Jae Suk is not the Mafia.
Who is the person that's behaving
in a way that he or she never does?
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin rarely gets up
from his seat.
- I know.
- Wow.
(Flustered)
But he went through the trouble...
- to move around.
- He kept moving around.
Suk Jin never does anything.
I know him.
When I go somewhere, he'd ask me
to get something for him.
- "Hey."
- Exactly. He always asks.
He orders everyone around
except for Jong Kook.
You get what I'm saying? He asks
everyone except for Jong Kook.
(Glaring)
- Hey.
- He got you!
- Hey!
- Wait a minute.
- Jong Kook!
- Prosecutor Yoo.
- You make it look like I'm it.
- Shall I change my target to you?
I swear. It's not me.
Jong Kook turned his attention
to him.
- Today...
- I'm not the Mafia. Hey, Jae Suk!
If you keep saying that,
we can't catch the Mafia.
Your face is blushing.
We can edit this out.
- I had to...
- It's definitely Haha.
- I had to move around.
- It's Haha.
If you keep pointing
your finger at me,
- He suddenly changed his stance.
- then it looks like I'm the Mafia.
If you keep insisting, you make it
look like I'm the Mafia.
- Suk Jin.
- I was just walking around...
for the rice.
Then why can't he be the Mafia?
You see? He's accusing me now.
That's not what I'm doing.
Fine. Just pick me.
- Jong Kook.
- Just pick me. Whatever!
I won't do anything from now.
Just pick me. I'm serious.
- He's acting.
- Make sure to pick me.
- He gets mad when he's accused.
- Why would you be so upset?
What are you looking at?
Move!
- Hey. Haha.
- Whatever!
- Haha.
- What?
Are you going to confess or not?
I will. I'll make sure to confess.
Why are you venting it on me?
You pick on me for everything I do.
Why are you doing this to me?
You should vent it on Jong Kook.
Please make sure to send me
to Haha's room.
- What's strange...
- This is hilarious.
is that Suk Jin laughed the most
when Haha said he'd confess.
- Gosh, I laughed too much.
- Fine. Just pick me.
You'll think it's me if you
keep insisting. Don't be fooled.
Why would you think it's me
when Se Chan is being accused?
- I know.
- It's...
- Let's pick him.
- I'm sure this time.
- Come here.
- Why?
Why do you keep staring at me?
- Because you kept acting strange.
- You must be the Mafia.
You're the Mafia, and you're looking
for a reason to make everyone...
think I'm the Mafia.
- Suk Jin.
- Come on.
(He burps while reasoning.)
That's cheating.
How can he burp while talking?
It's gross.
How can he burp while reasoning?
What was that?
What kind of reasoning is that?
It's so gross.
- I can't take this.
- This is...
It's so gross
regardless of the game.
I've never seen anyone like that
after Myung Soo.
Let me explain.
I could burp because I was relaxed.
- Because you were relaxed?
- I was really surprised.
No, you couldn't digest
because you were nervous.
Suk Jin, did you sit at this table
in the beginning?
No, he was at this table.
- I told you.
- So Min, you were here.
- Yes.
- You two should switch seats.
I told you.
- Come here, So Min.
- Suk Jin is not that type.
What are you talking about?
I kept moving because of the rice.
I know Suk Jin the best.
Suk Jin doesn't move much.
Are you sure it's not you?
- What?
- Are you sure it's not you?
I think it's Haha and Suk Jin.
One of the people accusing me
must be the Mafia.
- I think it's Haha and Se Chan.
- Jae Suk...
is just suspecting me.
- I think it's Haha and Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- You saw how he accused me, right?
- It's really not me.
Anyone up for Coke?
Jae Suk is just...
- Okay, I'll take one.
- Okay.
I want one too.
I'll just drink until today.
Gosh, Jong Kook.
He's driving me crazy.
His eyes are on you.
He isn't singling us out
because he wants to act sharp.
- He's suspecting everyone.
- I know. He's not singling us out.
- This is so good.
- Here's your Coke.
Right. This is how you usually are.
You weren't like yourself
when you asked for the rice.
That's not who you are.
- But...
- You're well-mannered.
- Ji Hyo, tell them.
- He couldn't move because of me.
- That's right.
- I don't know about that.
I'm sure it's Suk Jin for now.
- I think it's Suk Jin too.
- You keep...
- The fact that he moved...
- I get where you're coming from.
Jae Suk suspects me for no reason.
Then who do you think
is the Mafia for certain, Haha?
(Who do you think
is the Mafia for certain, Haha?)
Is there a reason
why you're not the Mafia?
Look at him.
- He does things like that.
- You asked me!
- Look at that punk.
- Wait a minute.
- Just pick me then.
What is it?
Why does one get up
when the other sits down?
(Why does one get up
when the other sits down?)
Then we'll be seated
at the same time.
- We'll be seated at the same time.
- Wait a minute.
- Why did you get up? What is this?
Hang on a second.
- What?
- Wait a minute.
- Is that the jumping dance?
- What?
- Hey!
- The jumping dance.
- Hey! When one sits...
- Is that the jumping dance?
Both of you, sit down.
(Even Detective Viper is shocked.)
- Is that the jumping dance?
- These guys...
Wait. That's the jumping dance!
Hey! You brats!
(When Suk Jin sits down,
Haha gets up.)
What did I do?
- I got you.
- What do you mean?
- I got you, you punks!
- My gosh!
This is driving me crazy!
Why do you keep suspecting me?
(The two Mafias' hidden mission
got revealed in the end.)
What's so strange about this?
- What's so strange about this?
- Stop it!
- I mean...
- My gosh.
- What's so strange about this?
- I know.
What's so strange about this?
- This is driving me insane.
- Come on.
- Don't do this to us.
- This was the mission.
Fine. Then just pick us two.
Just go with us.
- Just go with us.
- They're the Mafias, right?
I got you!
Just go with us then.
This is nonsense.
We pick Haha and Suk Jin.
- Just go with us then.
- This doesn't make any sense.
Gosh, I nearly died laughing.
It was hilarious. I couldn't
stop myself from laughing.
It was so funny when Jae Suk
found out about the hidden mission.
(He finds it absurd.)
How did he find out?
You've successfully completed
the hidden mission.
Hey, Haha. I was about to call you.
Hey, Suk Jin.
- We should remain silent.
- We should.
- If we remain silent,
- Right.
- Then nothing will happen.
- then we can play one more round.
Right. Suk Jin,
I swear on my son's name.
I won't betray you.
If I betray you this time,
you don't have to see me
for a while.
(Laughing)
Don't laugh. I'm serious.
If I... Okay, fine.
I won't swear either.
Just trust me.
Let's remain silent together.
I'm going to trust you.
Okay. You're the strong one,
and I'm the fast one.
We should remain silent
and accuse Se Chan and Ji Hyo...
of being the Mafia
in the next round.
Or we could accuse Jae Suk.
Whoever it is, I'm going to choose
to remain silent.
- Okay. Let's do this.
- Okay.
- I'll remain silent.
- Promise me.
- I promise you.
- Okay.
(They give each other
a firm promise.)
Should I trust him or not?
(As soon as he hangs up)
I'm going to trust Suk Jin.
I'll never yield to them.
I trust him.
Suk Jin is as good as caught.
Old man.
How dare you call me old?
Let's not stall for time.
I'll just say this out loud.
I told you so many times
that it's not me.
Sir.
- You came to the wrong person.
- Sir.
- I'm sorry.
- So...
This is so frustrating.
The Mafia on the loose.
- All right now. Shut your mouth.
- I'm not the Mafia.
You were born in 1966, right?
- Am I a criminal or something?
- This sounds real.
No, I'm not saying that. Your
surname is of Chungju Clan, right?
- Yes, it is.
- Okay.
You went to
Suyu Elementary School, correct?
And you went to
Shinil Middle School.
Your nose is 7cm tall
and 5cm wide. Is that correct?
(He questions Suk Jin's nose size
out of the blue.)
- What on earth...
- This sounds real.
- Yes, it is.
- We're asking these questions...
- to check on the details.
- Sure.
Excuse me.
It looks like...
all the soft-hearted ones are here.
- The soft-hearted ones.
- But we have you.
- We have you.
- One of you could be the Mafia.
- I'm not the Mafia.
- Mr. Mafia.
- I told you. I'm not the Mafia.
You arrogant Mafia.
You're acting arrogant even in here.
Are you going to confess or not?
Oh, you're here.
- Look at you.
- Why are you...
Your tone is arrogant.
- This is baffling.
- Baffling?
Why do you think only two of us
came into your room?
That means one of us is the Mafia.
- What?
- One of us?
I think it's Se Chan.
You're such a good liar.
Don't put your legs on the table.
His surname is of Jinju Clan.
He's 168cm tall? He lied.
Who wrote that? I'm 171.5cm tall!
- Hey, 168cm.
- Where did you get this info?
- You're short. Shut your mouth.
- What are you talking about?
- Keep quiet.
- Hey, you punk!
- My pride is at stake here!
- Give it back.
- Don't be arrogant.
When I'm in good condition,
I'm 172.5cm tall!
Don't call me 168cm ever again.
- Haha.
- Tell us honestly.
Why don't you just confess now?
No, I won't. Why would I confess
when I'm not the Mafia?
You are the Mafia.
- No, I am not.
- Who do you think is the Mafia?
- I think it's Se Chan.
- Why?
I voted for Se Chan.
You will saw it on TV later.
- What?
- "You will saw it"?
You will saw it on TV later.
(Excuse me?)
You will see it.
- I am serious.
- All right.
- I am not the Mafia.
I am not the Mafia,
so I am confident.
Usually, the Mafia or spia...
Oh, that came out wrong.
I meant to say "Spy".
- What was that? Are you tired?
- Usually, the Mafia or spia...
- He is nervous.
- No, I am tired.
- You are flustered.
- Not at all.
- How did I behave suspiciously?
- Earlier,
why did you do that with Suk Jin?
- It was funny.
- I bet you didn't even hide it...
- because you got caught.
- It's not like that at all.
- This is your chance. Confess.
- Whatever.
- You won't? Let's go. Get up.
- Do you know why I won't confess?
- Go.
- All right.
- Go. I am not the Mafia.
- Won't you confess?
- Won't you confess? All right.
- I won't confess.
I can't because I am not the Mafia.
You are the Mafia.
I am not the Mafia.
Do you want to make a bet?
What will you do if I am a citizen?
Do you want to hit me
across the face?
- Are you confident?
- Yes.
- I will hit you for real.
- Sure.
- Are you ready to take a punch?
- I am not the Mafia.
- Do you want to take it now?
- If Jong Kook is the Mafia,
can you hit him across the face?
- If he is the Mafia?
- Yes.
I can't do that.
- I can't do that.
- Then why will you hit me?
I think I will win
if we have a fight.
- Seriously.
- You will definitely win.
- I think I will win...
- if we have a fight.
- Seriously.
You are unbelievable.
I think you are most likely
to be the Mafia.
Look over here. Haha is the Mafia.
- Let's say that I am.
- Suk Jin is in the other room.
- Why did you pick me?
- You behaved suspiciously earlier.
- That was...
- You admit it, right?
I didn't do anything.
How did I behave suspiciously?
You were so obvious
when you carried out a mission.
- What do you mean?
- You sat down and stood out.
- Do you think it was a mission?
- Of course it was.
- Haha told me...
- They were like a seesaw.
When one sat down,
the other one stood up.
- Such a mission doesn't exist.
- Yes, it does.
- We just witnessed it.
- Such a mission could exist.
I doubt it.
- I am not the Mafia.
- Your face is very red right now.
- Your face is very puffy.
- Yes.
I had ramyeon last night.
I was too hungry.
My wife was at her parents' place.
- I see.
- I ate other things too.
- Was she at her parents' place?
- Yes.
- She doesn't let me eat at night.
- I bet it was like a festival.
(I bet it was like a festival.)
A party.
There was nothing to do,
but it didn't feel half bad.
- I bet it was like a festival.
- Yes.
(The suspect reveals information
about his family matters.)
She went there late at night.
It was past 9 p.m.
- I will say this.
- Okay.
Even if you don't confess,
Haha will.
- You...
- You know that.
You need to remember that.
- But I am not the Mafia.
- You saw what happened earlier...
with me and So Min.
We kept the damage at 500 dollars.
If you don't confess,
you will lose 1,000 dollars.
- You have 150 dollars right now.
- You have 150 dollars.
- You will be in debt.
- What do you want me to do?
You will be 850 dollars in debt.
I am not the Mafia,
so I can't do anything about it.
I don't know who the Mafia is.
Just remember what will happen...
- if Haha confesses.
- In any case,
I am not the Mafia.
- So you don't care.
- No.
- Okay. Then...
- I don't care.
we are done here.
If things go south,
you will lose 1,000 dollars.
Why would I lose 1,000 dollars
when I am not the Mafia?
I am not the Mafia.
Can't you see how relaxed I am?
- You are suspicious.
- I am not the Mafia.
- Haha.
- Okay.
- It's him.
- Suit yourself.
- Suk Jin is in the other room.
- Okay.
- He is bound to confess.
- If you remain silent...
- I don't care.
- I am not the Mafia.
- Stop it. We got the point.
- Why would I confess...
- Suk Jin is in the other room.
when I am not the Mafia?
Hey, I think...
- Suk Jin isn't the Mafia.
- Why would I do that?
- Then tell Suk Jin...
- It must be So Min.
- to confess.
- Listen to me.
It seems like...
- Haha is the Mafia.
- This is driving me crazy.
But he is certain
that the other one can't confess.
Then who could be the Mafia?
It's either Ji Hyo or So Min.
Judging from his demeanor,
- he is certain...
- He knows he won't lose money.
- that...
- This is frustrating.
the other Mafia didn't get caught.
Haha definitely is the Mafia.
- He is confident...
- So it's 1 of the 2.
because he knows
that the other one can't confess.
- See? He is confident.
- He is relaxed.
- That's the only explanation.
- It isn't too late to confess.
What is it going to be?
He won't confess.
- Sir.
- Make the decision in one minute.
You don't have much time.
If you don't confess,
you will lose 1,000 dollars.
Do you think you will get
two more rounds? That won't happen.
- Haha will confess,
- I don't have anything to confess.
and you will lose 1,000 dollars.
Haha is bound to confess.
- That goes without saying.
- Remember that.
A civilian can't confess.
All right. Don't confess.
It's over. We are done here.
- Please make the final decision.
- Okay.
Will you confess or remain silent?
- Haha is bound to confess.
- That goes without saying.
You know what Haha is like.
If I am the Mafia...
- You are the Mafia.
- Let's say that I am.
- Let's say Haha and I are.
- Okay.
Then Haha will confess, right?
- Of course.
- I am 100 percent sure of it.
- Suk Jin,
I am 300 percent sure of it.
I am 1,000 percent sure of it.
You are torn...
because your partner is Haha.
If I am the Mafia,
I have every reason to confess.
- Of course.
Please make the final decision.
(What will be the Mafia's decision?)
- I will remain silent.
- Fine.
Suit yourself.
(Haha chose to remain silent.)
Otherwise...
Ji Hyo might be lying.
(Haha even used a trick
to defend himself.)
- The result is out.
- Okay.
- Haha remained silent.
- Yes.
The Mafia in the other room,
Suk Jin...
(What did Suk Jin choose?)
Suk Jin confessed.
(Suk Jin confessed.)
(He confessed?)
(Suk Jin betrayed Haha
and confessed.)
He is a fool. He really is a fool.
You lost 1,000 dollars.
You lost 1,000 dollars!
Please make the final decision.
- Okay.
- He will confess.
Will you confess or remain silent?
One, two, three.
I will confess.
(Whispering)
(I will confess.)
Good job.
I don't want to be betrayed again.
- My feelings will be hurt.
- It's understandable.
- Haha...
- Read it again.
That can't be the result.
- That can't be the result.
- Haha is the Mafia.
Perhaps you meant to say
that he is confused.
He confessed.
How did you trust Suk Jin?
You should have seen this coming.
(Unlike the usual times,
he had too much trust in Suk Jin.)
You will be at the bottom.
This is the worst result.
Seriously.
Why did you trust Suk Jin?
- The result is out.
- Okay.
- He confessed.
Haha in the other room...
remained silent.
(Haha in the other room
remained silent.)
(What?)
Did Haha remain silent? Why?
(He sold out his partner
to save himself.)
In any case, congratulations
on winning 100 dollars.
- You did well.
- Suk Jin,
- you won money.
- You won 100 dollars.
I know, but I feel bad.
Why?
Haha lost 1,000 dollars.
Suk Jin, here is 100 dollars.
I don't want to receive
100 dollars like this.
- Why not?
- Take it.
- You won 100 dollars.
You said Haha will confess.
- I thought he would confess.
- You are the worst.
- Why didn't he confess?
- Seriously.
I will end you!
Suk Jin!
(Haha's angry shouts
fill the place.)
Listen.
Let go.
- Hey.
- I will end you!
Suk Jin!
(Suk Jin!)
Hey!
- He is here.
- Come on out.
Old man!
Old snake!
You told me to trust you.
- You told me to trust you.
- It's not like that.
These three are...
the absolute worst.
How could you do this to me?
We were so close!
- I had set up a trick.
- How?
I had gotten them
to suspect Ji Hyo and So Min.
They were beginning to get confused.
Had you stayed silent,
we would have gotten another round
without getting caught.
We could have done the mission...
- in the open.
- Really?
(Really?)
Hurry up and give me 100 dollars.
I have to take it from you.
I am so annoyed.
I will give you 100 dollars.
I remained silent.
How did you do that?
Did you change the character?
I didn't change the character!
Don't you have any trust in me?
(The Mafia duo got caught
due to the lack of trust.)
Please enter the room.
I hope I don't become the Mafia.
I really hope
I don't become the Mafia.
(Since the Mafias got caught,
2 new Mafias get chosen.)
The last Mafias are chosen.
(The last Mafias are chosen.)
You are the Mafia.
(Who are the 2 last Mafias?)
The hidden mission is...
(What is their hidden mission?)
The Mafias get caught
no matter what.
The Mafias will get caught
(Who are the 2 Mafias?)
I didn't doubt you.
You can trust me from now on.
I am not a bad man.
For the last mission,
jump over the bar...
using the Fosbury flop.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- What's the Fosbury flop?
- What?
Like this?
(The Fosbury flop is...)
(a high jump technique
in which one lies backward.)
(Woo Sang Hyeok showed...)
(a textbook example
of the Fosbury flop.)
Your best record will be your score.
This is impossible.
As for the female members,
we will add 30cm.
- Really?
- If you clear 80cm,
your record will be 110cm.
- Let's start at 80cm.
- All right. Eighty centimeters.
- High jump is hard.
- Adjust the height afterward.
Anyone can jump over that.
- Anyone can jump over that.
- I know.
You should go first.
Anyone can jump over that.
You should be able
to jump over the bar.
It's just a simple jump.
You just need to jump lightly.
Jump lightly.
(He cleared 80cm as he promised.)
Nice.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo, 80cm)
What is up
with everyone's facial expression?
(The 1st slapstick comedy
at the baseline)
- Okay.
- That was funny.
- Out.
- How did that happen?
Ji Hyo, that was funny.
- Ji Hyo, that was funny.
- You are good.
- All right.
- You are out.
Ji Hyo, good job
with slapstick comedy.
I don't think I will need to run up.
Just jump.
- Yes.
- Go.
(She gets ready
in a haughty manner.)
(So Min, 80cm)
(Success)
Will you jump?
(With a blank facial expression,)
(she jumps in a cheesy way.)
So Min, you ran strangely.
What was that?
Her facial expression was
really strange.
So Min, you ran strangely.
You ran like this.
(Her father who is an athlete
would be appalled.)
It was cool, right?
Shouldn't I raise the bar?
- Go ahead.
- I need to beat her.
Raise the bar.
I need to beat her.
- Raise the bar.
- I will be at the bottom otherwise.
Please raise the bar to 111cm.
Did you say 111cm?
- Hold on. I will do it.
- It's 1cm more than my record.
- I think he will fail.
- You can't touch it.
I think he will fail.
- Okay.
- I think he will fail.
That's it. Jump like this.
Let's go!
Did you learn the mask dance?
Will you jump like this?
There you go.
How do I do this?
- You guys are incredible.
- Put it up.
He is a funny old man.
(The sneak peek
leaves everyone excited.)
- The icon of longevity.
- Longevity and health.
We are rooting for you.
- That's good.
- Come on.
- Promise.
- Rev yourself up.
That's good. Rev yourself up. Okay.
- That's good.
- Put your heart into it.
(Screaming)
Put your heart into it.
(He goes down with a shout.)
Suk Jin.
- He got scared.
- You jumped with two feet.
- It's impossible to jump that way.
- Why couldn't I jump with one foot?
That was great.
- Your legs didn't go up.
- Why couldn't I jump with one foot?
I think Ji Hyo will succeed.
- Be daring.
- You need to run faster.
- I run up and jump like this.
- That's right.
- But you need speed.
- Really?
Let me tell you how it's done.
Run up and jump
as if you are lying on my bed,
okay?
That's how you do it.
- "My bed"?
"My bed"?
"My bed"!
(I want to be
the bed in your room for a day)
"My bed"?
(He ended up feeding them again.)
- "My bed"?
- No.
I meant to say "Your bed".
Run up and jump
as if you are lying on your bed,
Does that mean
she has lied on your bed?
I meant to say "Your bed"!
"Your bed"!
(Se Chan and Haha show
a cute group dance.)
(Biting his lips)
- He started it.
- No.
- So Min started it.
- No, I didn't.
Why don't you put her at ease
by doing what you always do...
and lie down
with your arm spread like a pillow?
(Lie down
with your arm spread like a pillow.)
(Jong Kook is ready
to cut off his arm.)
- Like a pillow!
- He really startled me.
- My goodness.
- Not yet.
- Ji Hyo, jump.
Jump as if you are lying
on your bed.
(Ji Hyo, 111cm)
- Put your heart into it.
- That's good.
(Screaming)
(She crashed into the bed.)
Her face was so funny.
- Ji Hyo.
- That was funny.
- How did she do that?
- That was pure slapstick comedy.
Did you learn
slapstick comedy somewhere?
(They wonder
if she has taken lessons.)
Her slapstick comedy was funny.
You are funny.
Your hairstyle resembles
Dr. Oh Eun Young's too.
- That was great.
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk, let's go.
- Grasshopper.
I think you will succeed
if you have confidence.
I have no confidence,
but I will succeed.
(Jae Suk, 111cm)
(No one has cleared 111cm.)
Let's go.
(Let's go.)
(He unfortunately fails.)
You failed.
I could see that he was scared.
- I could see that he was scared.
- Could you see it?
- Yes.
- He was like, "Let's clear 111cm."
- All right.
- He failed.
Go. That's good.
He got this.
It was scary.
It was scary at the end.
- He got scared.
- It was so scary.
(The fearless Jong Kook
attempts to clear 111cm!)
(A clean success)
You succeeded.
It was a proper flop.
It's called the Fosbury flop.
- A flop?
- Who is next?
- Okay.
- Se Chan.
(Se Chan, 111cm)
(He must have watched
a lot of high jump competitions.)
(He is collecting energy
to clear mere 1m.)
Give me more energy.
He isn't intimidated
by the competent high jumpers.
- He will attempt to clear 235cm.
- Let's go!
Yes. Let's go.
(The short high jumper imitates
Woo Sang Hyeok's passion...)
He is enjoying himself.
(and gets revved up.)
(He screams to bring up his energy.)
Hold on. Isn't that a mission?
Hold on.
- It's not a mission.
- Hey.
You are lying. Hey!
- It's not a mission.
- Hey.
- High jumpers do this.
It looked a bit like a mission.
- Seriously.
- I was gathering courage.
When do high jumpers do that?
- I have never seen it.
- Don't high jumpers do that?
- That came out of nowhere.
- So you just copied it?
- It's something I do.
- He suddenly did a mission.
(Se Chan is suspected
of being the Mafia.)
It's not a mission.
Here I go.
Go.
(Se Chan, 111cm)
- Of course.
- Okay.
(Light)
(He cleared 111cm after Jong Kook!)
Good job.
Jong Kook, jump after you get
a round of applause.
It will give you courage.
- Isn't it hard?
- No.
- I think I will fail.
- You know,
Se Chan, you will have to compete
against Jong Kook...
- to the end.
- That's right. Try it today.
- I think I will lose to Jong Kook.
- Se Chan is good at this.
He is too flexible.
The height should be 121cm.
- Really?
- Let's keep it tight.
I raised it. Go.
Can you jump over it?
- I will.
- Can you jump over it?
Se Chan jumped over the bar
with ease earlier.
(Se Chan, 121cm)
Here comes So Min's boyfriend.
Stop it already.
- That's just wrong.
- Stop it.
- For goodness' sake.
- So Min.
So Min, please move to the side.
His hair came out well today.
I used to do tracks.
- Really?
- Yes.
I learned the high jump too.
- Really?
- You need speed to jump over.
You did tracks
in elementary school, right?
- Yes.
- You didn't go to middle school.
(Swearing with his eyes)
Look at his face.
He is about to hit you.
- Use your anger to jump.
- Watch what you say.
Don't get scared.
Don't get intimidated.
That's right.
He will succeed.
(Will he clear 121cm
with his experience in tracks?)
He will succeed.
He succeeded!
That was perfect.
(He succeeded with ease!)
(Impressed)
That was...
(Dongducheon's track team,
are you watching this?)
- Se Chan is the best.
- He is like a professional.
("Nobody" dance ceremony)
(What?)
- No.
- Isn't that a mission?
My nose is runny.
- "Nobody".
- I was expressing happiness.
Is doing the "Nobody" dance
in front of the camera a mission?
His ceremony was a mission.
It wasn't a mission.
- His ceremony.
- He did this.
The camera zoomed in on me.
His ceremony was a mission.
- His ceremony.
- Come on.
Let's do this.
Se Chan has good movement.
(Jong Kook is Se Chan's only rival.)
Here I go.
(Kim Jong Kook, 121cm)
His energy is overflowing.
(He jogged...)
(and did the vertical jump.)
His energy is overflowing.
- Let's try 135cm.
- Just raise your legs a bit.
- Okay.
- Let's try 135cm.
I won't be able to succeed.
When you jumped earlier,
there was enough space.
You will succeed.
You jumped with ease earlier.
Hey, So Min.
What are you doing?
Are you watching a movie?
I want to give Se Chan energy.
- You want to give Se Chan energy.
- Yes.
Se Chan is really good.
(Dongducheon's track team member
will attempt to make a new record.)
Track team.
Let's see.
You are cool!
- You are cool!
- Hey.
(He cleared 135cm.)
(It was the perfect Fosbury flop.)
- Good job.
- Seriously.
- That was incredible.
- You jumped properly this time.
He really was in a track team.
- Don't be scared.
- Seriously.
- He is cool.
- He is really cool.
- That was sexy.
Se Chan, that was incredible.
Forget it.
(Jong Kook, 135cm)
One, two, three.
(He is the only rival
to Dongducheon's Woo Sang Hyeok.)
(He succeeded.)
That's impressive.
While he wasn't in a track team,
he jumps over with brute strength.
I can't win against him.
(The mission ended
when they failed to clear 140cm!)
The first-place winners,
Jong Kook and Se Chan
will receive 1,000 dollars each.
- Okay.
- Did you say 1,000 dollars?
- That's a lot of money.
- I have zero dollars.
Do some people have zero dollars?
Now, it's time to announce
the result of the hidden mission.
The hidden mission...
(If their guess is correct,
Se Chan carried it out.)
failed.
- What?
- I knew it.
(Did the hidden mission fail?)
The Mafias didn't do it.
They gave up.
- They gave up.
- They did it to stay hidden.
- So it wasn't the clapping.
- Of course not.
The last interrogation
will be kept short.
Follow your cameraman...
and vote for the two Mafias.
Then the interrogation will ensue.
It means the Mafias
didn't carry out the mission.
It must be Jong Kook.
If I must pick two people...
(What does
Jae Suk's intuition say?)
Jong Kook and Se Chan.
So Min and Jong Kook.
(Suk Jin suspects
So Min and Jong Kook.)
That's my vote.
Se Chan and Ji Hyo.
Se Chan.
I vote for Se Chan.
I need to get his confession.
- Here is the man I suspected.
- Seriously.
You got it all wrong.
- Don't be like that.
- You ruined it.
- Just confess.
- You got it all wrong.
- Jong Kook.
- I am serious.
Here is what I think, Jong Kook.
You are the only one
who would ignore the mission.
- That's not true.
- Everyone else would attempt it.
- Like who?
- You said that earlier.
- When?
- "You can just not do the mission."
I did say that. I guess
the Mafias followed my advice.
Let's take this slow.
You were born in 1976, right?
- You were born in 1976.
- That's right.
Once you start to suspect someone,
you harass the person
until the end...
and tire him or her out,
is that true?
Yes.
You know my style.
If I were the Mafia,
- I would tell you the truth.
- Who do you think it is then?
I can't hide it.
I'm sure it's Yang Se Chan.
(He protests his innocence
and names Se Chan.)
- And I'd suspect you.
- Me?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Jong Kook.
- What's with your hands?
- What's with your hands.
- Jong Kook.
I'm tired. Let's make it short.
- I know we're tired.
- So...
Listen. I'm not the Mafia.
If you are done, just get out.
- Hey.
- Get out. I don't want to talk.
Talking to him doesn't work.
He is...
- So Min is...
- Hey, shall we go to Room of Truth?
- What?
- Room of Truth.
Can we please go to Room of Truth?
(The suspect is glad
to hear about Room of Truth.)
- This is the Room of Truth.
- Please go to Room of Truth.
- Come here.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Gosh.
Wait.
(They go into Room of Truth
where the truth is revealed.)
Good. That was okay.
We found out the truth.
It is like an old comedy skit.
- This is what I used to do.
- We found out the truth in there.
- I'm telling you.
- But...
It's not me and neither are you.
- I'm not the Mafia.
- And it's not you.
- Is it you?
- It's not me.
And it's not me. Then who is it?
How would I know?
- I think it's you.
- It must be you.
There won't be the next round.
This is the last one.
You saw what happened to me.
If you...
Listen to me.
- He was born in 1966.
- Yes.
Don't say that.
That's all you can say.
- I see.
- He was born in 1966.
- All right.
- And I was born in 1972.
- You guys are old.
- I know.
- We are older than you.
- That's why they're here.
- You should listen to us.
- You punk.
Have you made up your mind?
- Silence.
- He chose to remain silent.
Aren't you the mafia?
I'll definitely remain silent.
- All right.
- No matter what.
(The last Mafia is not arrested.)
- My gosh.
- Who is it?
Who is it then?
I'll announce the results then.
- The last Mafias are...
- Who are they?
(Who are the two Mafias
that have survived?)
Kim Jong Kook and Jeon So Min.
See?
(Kim Jong Kook and Jeon So Min)
I was right
when I talked about So Min.
- I was right about that.
- See?
Their hidden mission was...
drawing a stroke on your name tags
to change your names.
I couldn't do it.
Jae Suk, she kept trying to do
something on my name tag earlier.
Really? You did it?
No. I didn't. I had to use
a permanent marker, but I couldn't.
I'll announce
the final results then.
I hope I'm not the last one.
Number one is...
Kim Jong Kook with 1,600 dollars.
I got a lot of money
at the last minute.
Number two also came from behind.
Yang Se Chan with 1,450 dollars.
(Number 2 is Yang Se Chan
with 1,450 dollars.)
So these two members win the prize.
- The prize is...
- What is it?
It is the high-quality chocolate
that will make you feel better...
after the confusing time.
My goodness.
- That's nice.
- It must be sweet.
Among Haha, Jae Suk, and Suk Jin,
two members will get the penalty.
(Among Haha, Jae Suk, and Suk Jin,
two members will get the penalty.)
- Is it me?
- I hope it's me and Suk Jin.
- You two...
- Why?
- All right.
- Suk Jin?
The last two members
to get the penalty are...
(Who are the two members
to get the penalty?)
My son will love this place.
(Haha and Suk Jin are
getting the penalty together.)
What is the best one here?
- This one looks nice.
- I know.
- Shall we buy this one?
- I'll have two of these.
Yes.
This is important. Here?
Okay.
Thank you.
- One each.
- Thank you.
It feels like this is for us.
I'll give this to you
during the opening.
- Congratulations.
- Enjoy.
(The gym is in danger
of going bankrupt.)
(You should come early
and work out hard...)
(to make the national team.)
(Look at you guys.
What time do you think it is now?)
(The old gym users
don't feel nervous at all.)
(They are
a rag-tag bunch of loafers.)
(New members show up at the moment.)
(Mi Joo, Lee Young Ji, Lee Sang Jun)
Do squats.
(With the unusual new members,)
(the gym is reviving.)
(Then they have an election
for the captain.)
The captain should have
a sense of responsibility.
(Those who are
loyal to Jong Kook...)
(can enjoy a comfortable time
in the gym.)
(Otherwise...)
(you'll go through harsh training.)
(Will Trainer Jong Kook be able
to revive the gym?)
(Gym Revival Project,
Trainer Jong Kook and National Team)