- This way? - Are we going this way?
- Is there something in there? - Why are we going in there?
Hello.
- What? - Come on in.
- I'm nervous. - What's all this?
"In Suyu-dong..."
"With his whimsical charm..."
- "The grand award..." - It's Jae Suk.
2005 KBS Entertainment Awards.
Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jae Suk. - Yoo Jae Suk.
Yoo Jae Suk of Running Man.
Yoo Jae Suk.
Congratulations.
There's Jong Kook.
Why are we doing this?
- That's Jong Kook. - When did they...
Hey, what's all this?
2020 SBS Entertainment Awards. The grand award goes to...
Kim Jong Kook. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
- What's all this? - There's Jong Kook.
- Hey, what's all this? - Hello.
- Hello. - What's this?
- Hey, I was born... - What is this?
- I was born in Yongsan. - What's going on?
- What is this? - Is it a biography?
- A biography? - Where should I look at?
It says "He was born in Suyu-dong, Gangbuk-gu."
This is a museum.
- What is this? - What's going on?
This is... My gosh.
- And what is this? - He's not Admiral Yi Sun Sin.
- What's all this? - What are we doing?
This should be in front of a statue like that.
Gosh, the people who didn't win the grand award are getting upset.
- This is... - What are you doing?
It's not like I was born here.
Is it about his biography?
"He claims that's when he had his first kiss."
- He claims? - What are you doing?
- Did he claim that? - Why did you add that?
My gosh.
I was born in Yongsan.
I'm from Seoul.
Just let it slide.
- It's a good day. - What's all this?
- What is this? - Why?
- I'm wearing it because I'm cold. - What's with this?
What's that jacket?
- What about it? - It's like a flower garden.
- It's... - What's that?
Still, it's cool.
I think I should take this off.
By the way, Suk Jin...
- Why? - Why are you taking it off?
- Suk Jin. - I was just about to start.
I didn't get to say anything.
- Because... - I was about to start.
This is what I'm supposed to wear.
This cardigan belongs to my aunt.
Se Chan, weren't you wearing this shirt earlier today?
I knew it. Someone stole my shirt. Suk Jin!
I couldn't wear it.
Suk Jin, this is Se Chan's.
- You can't wear that. - Hey.
- That's not true. - It's mine.
After his stylist, Ha Na who got paid per case quit,
- he got a new stylist. - I know.
Stop talking about the "per case" thing.
- Why? - I'm not the one who paid her.
- Still... - Oh, it was your agency?
We have a member who gets paid that way.
He gets paid by the hour.
- By the hour? - Hey.
- Is that you? - He gets paid by case?
- This is crazy. - By case.
Right. Suk Jin gets paid by the hour.
- By the hour. - That's right.
Anyway, I believe Ha Na will be doing well...
- because she's talented. - Sure.
She's not the type to boast.
He forgot about her already.
- Who? - He forgot about Ha Na.
How would I forget Ha Na?
- You had Min Hee before. - Do you remember Min Hee?
- Min Hee. - Sure.
- Suk Jin is... - When you met her before,
she said hello to you, and you made a bow to her.
- She worked for him for five years. - That's impossible.
- After five years... - That can't be right.
He's lying.
- That's ridiculous. - That's absurd.
That sounds just like Suk Jin.
Yesterday, Suk Jin was...
I guess he's made up his mind.
He wants to remember the names of our crew members.
- Seriously? - Right. He kept asking me.
"Hey, what's his name?"
So I was like... His name was Sun Myung,
but I said Sin Myung.
- And he tried to remember the name. - That sounds exciting.
And I told him his family name is Namkoong.
- I was... - Is he Namkoong Sun Myung?
I asked Se Chan about a crew member's name.
She was a woman, but he said her name is Ko Chul Bong.
Her name is Bong Pal.
He asked what her job was.
- So... - No one tells him the real names.
He asked me about her job, so I said she made window frames.
- "She makes window frames?" - All of a sudden, Suk Jin...
Window frames?
So you guys, don't be surprised...
if Suk Jin calls you by a weird name.
- We will... - Ko Chul Bong.
Hey, Bong Pal.
I asked, "Is she a writer or a director?"
And he said "She's in charge of the jimmy jib."
I said things like, "She makes window frames. She drives a truck."
- A truck? - He's so mean.
This is the only variety show that has...
two Grand Award winners.
- Right. - That's cool.
So we'll have a special episode for Yoo Grand Award and Kim Grand Award.
It will start in their memorial hall.
- Their memorial hall? - This is a memorial hall.
It's not a memorial hall. My gosh.
These two are very shy when we do stuff like this.
I hate stuff like this.
- Gosh, I really hate this. - A memorial hall?
- What's all this? - A memorial hall.
I'm no match for him though.
I just won the award once.
Jong Kook is another grand award winner.
So today...
They are the pride, the core, and the heart of Running Man.
With these two grand award winners,
we will have the Dignity of the Grand Award Race.
- Finally. - We have two hearts.
- This is... - We're finally doing this.
First, Jong Kook and I feel uncomfortable about stuff like this.
- He looks very shy. - I'm feeling uncomfortable.
As you probably noticed,
Jae Suk is the captain of Team Yoo Grand Award.
And Jong Kook is the captain of Team Kim Grand Award.
So there will be teams.
The rest of the members will...
choose a captain they want before each mission.
I feel uncomfortable already.
Do we get to pick the captains?
You should never sulk.
Then...
Gosh, Jong Kook.
There will be missions...
where the number of team members won't matter.
So it's okay even if one team has more members.
Oh, really?
You can just pick whichever team you want.
Can we pick teams after hearing about the game?
No, you can't.
Why not?
- It won't be easy. - The members...
of the winning team...
will get double the number of members in points.
But if you lose,
you will lose the exact number of members in points.
So the member with the highest score will be the winner.
And the two members with the lowest scores...
and one member picked by them will get a penalty.
- Really? - Is it picked?
But the member with the highest score is exempt.
Now I want the two captains to sign a written oath...
that says they will never get mad...
- no matter what. - That's good.
I'm telling you. I won't be mad.
You can't control my feelings.
So you can just pick a team you want comfortably.
- Bring the written oath. - Let them sign.
- All right. - Even after the shoot.
I don't think I need many team members.
Exactly. You don't need many.
I've never seen a contract like this before. You shall never sulk.
I won't sulk. We've been together for a long time.
You should never glower at me.
- I should read this carefully. - What is the addition for?
The other members can add conditions that they want.
You can't say, "Okay. I get it." It's forbidden.
- "Okay. I get it." - "Okay. I get it."
"Okay. I get it."
Don't stare at us for over two seconds straight.
- You can't say our full names. - Don't call our names.
You can't whisper to others while looking at my face.
You can't stare at us for over three seconds.
- That's good. - Don't glower at us.
Don't stare at me with snake eyes.
Okay. That's good.
Hang on. You can't do that. Look at that.
- Snake eyes. - You can't do that.
- Don't glower at us like that. - I won't do that.
I can stare at you because I like you.
- You stare at us like this. - You can't do that today.
They are not exactly "the apple of my eye".
To get a star...
- You don't have to read that. - He's changing the conditions.
Jae Suk won't let things like this slide.
- He's changing it. - Isn't it that you should...
- talk to your attorney? - I check contracts thoroughly.
You're amazing.
"I can't pick the stars for our members..."
"who are like the apple of my eye."
"Even though I can't do that, I do care about them."
"Whatever decision they make, I won't be mad..."
"Or resent them."
It depends.
Hey.
He can't change everything like that.
I didn't change a lot.
What's this? "As much as possible."
- Just sign it. - "For the members..."
I can see their characters. He checks everything thoroughly...
while Jong Kook just signed it.
"I respect their opinions."
- All right. It's done. - Don't say my full name.
- Not the full name. - Read it for us.
I wrote it down. "I won't stare at the members for over three seconds."
"I won't say, 'Okay, I get it.'"
- I got goosebumps. - You startled me.
That sounds so natural.
That's the tone of your voice.
- Se Chan, give this to them. - Okay.
All right.
Like I said before,
you can pick the captain of your team today.
The two captains will wait in their own rooms.
The rest of the members will go to their rooms in turn...
- Okay. Let's do that. - This is Jae Suk's room.
- And this is Jong Kook's room. - All right.
- "Okay, I get it." - "Okay, I get it."
- "Oh, Yang Se Chan." - "Oh, Haha."
- "Oh, Lee Kwang Soo." - "Suk Jin, I get it."
It's not like today is our last day.
- Hey, we have to add this. - Write this down.
"It's not like today is our last day."
- Write it down. - We have to write it down.
Gosh, it's suffocating already.
Honestly, I'm not acting cool.
I think two will be more than enough.
If no one comes, can I play alone?
My gosh.
Gosh. It's possible that no one shows up.
I should brace myself for that.
Gosh, this is...
It's cold today. Where should I go? Should I go into the room?
There's something I heard.
Today, the penalty will be very harsh.
And the two losers get to pick a person for the penalty.
Unless you win the game,
you might get the penalty.
- If you don't win... - We should do this right.
We have to win no matter what.
- We have to win. - I should be on the winning team.
We don't even know what it is. Can you tell us what we're doing?
It's like a choice between brain and brawn.
Jong Kook is smart too.
What? Are you saying Jong Kook is dumb?
- Okay. - You can't say that.
- Are you saying Jong Kook is dumb? - Haha!
We can't do this to each other.
I'll go. I've made up my mind.
- Okay. You go on ahead. - Hang on.
I think...
one of them will get more members.
This is hard to choose.
You should appreciate this. Look.
- Are you choosing me? - As soon as I got in here...
- You're still out of breath, right? - My gosh.
You picked me right away.
- I know. I came right away. - Okay. Good.
Jong Kook, I got in here even before the cameras were ready.
- That's great. - It was quick.
You should remember that.
Today, I'll be nice.
I thought you were dressed too lightly.
I'll keep you warm. You know what I mean.
- I was worried about you. - Jong Kook.
I got here even before you sat down.
- How did you come in so quickly? - I didn't even hesitate.
That's amazing. What's with you, So Min?
They were still talking.
- Suk Jin even said this. - What did he say?
Look at the sky The white snow is falling
Se Chan.
Good. Okay.
Okay. This is nice.
I came here without hesitation.
You were later than So Min, but...
- I came right after her. - Okay.
This is enough for me.
I don't need more.
Hang on.
I see a silhouette.
- Hey. - My gosh.
Hang on.
This isn't bad. It's 4 to 4.
- Song Jeoktoma. - Ji Hyo, this is...
This is enough. We're ready.
We don't need useless members.
I don't need the tall one.
Two would be more than enough.
I don't know what games we're playing though.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
That would be perfect.
I just need Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
They are very smart.
- And I... - We all are wearing white socks.
- We're a team. - Next is...
- What's happening there? - It's all white.
This is crazy.
Gosh, it's hard to choose.
It won't be physical from the beginning.
- Are you alone in here? - Gosh.
You must've been so lonely.
You...
What's that?
Why don't you look grateful?
- Gosh, I should go. - Haha, come back here. Haha.
They're having a party over there.
Come here, Haha.
I don't need many members. I want only two.
It will be hard to have a lot of members.
It's hard to have many members.
- Jae Suk. - Hey.
You picked a captain whom you can be comfortable with.
He's here.
- I'm here. - You want to be at ease.
- My gosh. - Hey, Jae Suk.
This isn't so bad.
Sure. This is good enough.
- I really like my team. - This is really good.
I can control these guys.
I guess Haha went to the other team.
- Haha is... - He didn't come.
He's...
Is he using me? Is it just business?
- I think so. - Exactly.
So this is what Haha did.
I'm realizing it today.
I think he's using your generous and cool personality.
Exactly. He uses me.
He uses me to attract investors.
I get it. Okay.
All right.
Did they go to the other room?
Gosh. What are you doing here?
I want to win the race.
- Right. He is... - He's realistic.
I heard there will be a harsh penalty today.
Suk Jin doesn't want Jae Suk to be his captain.
That's not true. It's not like that.
That's not why.
- I had to come here. - Sure. That's a good choice.
I never imagined...
But if we lose the first game, I'll move to the other team.
We can't lose with so many members.
- Were you the last one to go? - I was the last one.
I was talking about Haha.
- Haha picked the other team. - Haha is...
Suk Jin, don't you agree?
- Jong Kook. - I think...
- he's been using me. - He's using you.
- He's using me for business. - Right.
I can't deny it.
- Right. - I just realized it today.
- Jong Kook is... - This isn't what you shouldn't do.
- That's why you signed the oath. - I know, but...
- Don't be mad. - I'm not mad.
But I just can't help it.
Suk Jin is done making his choice.
- Really? He went there? - Seriously?
Good.
- We are the elite members. - I see.
We are the elite members.
- You could've been really lonely. - We are the best ones.
Gosh, Jong Kook will be...
We're the best members.
I have to do a TV show with him this week.
Why?
Things are becoming clear now.
This is just perfect.
- This is the first mission. - What is it?
I just hope it's not something physical.
- Nothing physical. - The first mission is...
one of the things that shows the dignity of grand award winners.
It requires power, agility,
- Power? - and craftiness.
It's called Two-body Hide-and-seek.
- What? - Hide-and-seek?
Two-body?
The team members except the captains...
can hide in any place you want within this pension complex.
And the two captains will be...
connected to each other with a rope.
And they will look for the members of their opposing teams.
As soon as you find a member,
the member is out right away.
There will be only one round.
The tagger who finds out all the members first will win.
They will be connected with a rope?
- So it's about strength. - This is...
- He will be dragged along. - This isn't right.
It's about strength from the beginning.
We can't do this from the beginning.
I chose Jae Suk because I thought it wouldn't be about strength.
We will be connected with a rope?
That's good for us.
Sure. I can drag Jae Suk around.
Jong Kook can drag him around.
We're going to win.
- We will definitely win. - We will.
- It's between me and Jae Suk. - Right.
- I can drag him around. - You should drag him around.
Hey, we have an advantage though.
Even if we lose,
we don't lose as many points as they do.
If we lose, will we lose six points?
No, only three points.
- Three points? - See?
- That's what I mean. - You like mud.
- Can you stay under the mud? - Hey.
- I don't like mud. - You do.
- Who would want to be in the mud? - He's crazy about mud.
Stay under the mud. You'll never get caught.
Hey, if you go into the mud today,
your feet will freeze.
- Hey. - I shouldn't have heard that.
- That makes me want to do it. - Hang on.
We will lose only three points.
So let's just think we will lose the first game.
We should be strategic.
I don't want to lose the first game.
- I'll win no matter what. - I'm just saying...
it's okay to lose. It's only three points.
Don't try too hard. You know what I mean.
- I want to try hard. - Just enjoy.
I just realized...
that you're not popular.
I know.
He would've been in trouble if I didn't come.
He was sitting all alone here.
If you and I didn't choose Jae Suk,
he would've been dragged around the whole time.
- No need to play the game. - Guys.
Like I said, you guys should hide well.
- Okay? - Yes.
So we should hide.
- We can win. - We should hide well.
We can disguise and everything.
Just stay in a place where we can't see you.
Please change into team uniforms.
- Okay. - All right.
I'm sure we will win.
Our chances of winning are like 80 percent.
- What's this? - It's pink.
This is...
Jong Kook's face looks big on Jong Kook.
- But this looks small. - It looks small.
There aren't many places where we can hide.
It will be annoying to have to search each car.
I think Jong Kook will stop me from checking the cars.
Exactly.
I'm sure he will do that.
If they all hide in the cars,
and you can't go to the parking lot, we will lose.
That's right.
- They're doing it already. - Why did you choose me?
What are you talking about?
Why would you say that?
I mean, you guys should do a good job. Okay?
You're the one who will look for them.
I know. I'll find them.
Why would you say that folding your arms like that?
- You already gave up. - I didn't give up.
I'm telling you, let's just relax.
I really want to win in a situation like this.
You should take off the flippers.
What? What flippers?
- What flippers? - Hey.
- What flippers? - Your feet are huge.
No.
- Shall we go? - Yes.
- Let's go. - Do we not have any plans?
- Try your best. - You...
I'll try my best. And you know,
I have no strategy.
I'll just go see what happens.
I'll fight against the world.
Hey.
Things always don't go as planned.
I just fight against them.
You should at least fight.
So...
- You are on your own. - Don't get beat up.
You know what I mean.
- It's an old saying. - We should take care...
Exactly. Okay?
- Okay. - Make sure to survive.
Jae Suk, regency by the queen mother.
Okay.
A fresh breeze and a bright moon.
It's a fresh wind and a bright moon.
- A fresh wind and a bright moon. - Okay.
Gosh, I picked the wrong team.
Darn it. I'm doomed.
- You won't be here next time. - Of course not.
Anyway, you will...
- Don't let him open it. - Okay.
Jong Kook, so...
- It's not like... - You're right.
- I will... - I'll stop him from coming here.
We will hide in the closet or something.
That's right. You should.
That's what you should do.
Okay.
- Hey. - Excuse me.
Let me tell you something.
- You can't do things by force. - Jae Suk,
I don't do that.
But if that's...
what the directors want,
I have to try my best.
I'm not telling you not to try your best.
- I have to work hard anyway. - Just don't be...
- so rough. - So what do you think?
- If that's what the directors... - It's not like that.
- We should follow them. - That's not true.
You're wearing a black outfit today.
You look like a wild animal.
A wild animal?
I'm just trying to make things go...
as the directors planned. It's not like...
You may start hiding.
- Got it. Okay. - You may hide now.
We have only three minutes.
- Is that enough for us to hide? - Three minutes.
Much water runs by the mill that the miller knows not of.
What? Se Chan is there.
There's no way they come in here.
I'm running out of time.
10, 9, 8...
9, 8...
He's crazy about mud. Stay under the mud.
I really want to win.
I'll risk my life to win this.
He'll never be able to find me.
Go.
Go away!
Get lost!
2, 1. Go!
Let's go.
- Can I take this off? - Yes.
- Let's go and find them. - Let's go.
Wait. Your side... Oh, is that your team's house?
This one is mine, right?
- This is your team's house. - Correct.
Then I can just stop him from coming into our house.
- Gosh. We won't go in there. - All right.
- We'll go to mine too. - Let's go to yours first.
- Let's check yours first. - Let's do it the other way around.
- Yours is closer. Let's go. - Let's go to your house first.
Let's go in.
- Come back here. It might snap. - Come here.
- Come here now! - Hey.
I said, come back here.
- This rope might snap, you punk! - Come here.
It won't snap. Just come in.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- Come here already. - You can't do this. It's not fair.
- Gosh. Hey, Bo Pil! - Stop it. Come over here.
- Gosh, seriously. - Come on in. Take off your shoes.
- This is driving me nuts. - Let's compromise with each other.
- Why are you doing this? - Like I said,
we should create a situation that our staff wants.
Gosh, seriously.
- That's how things work. What? - Hey, they both left.
What do you mean? Did they go out of here?
We don't have time for this. We have to go around outside.
We have to go around outside.
- What? - Who is that?
Hold on.
- Why... - Why are you here?
Why are you here?
- Hey. Hey! - Suk Jin? What's going on?
You should've stopped him from removing the blanket!
You should've stopped him...
from removing the blanket!
- What is he doing here? - I mean...
- What's wrong with you? - What is this?
- You're supposed to be in my room. - Listen, Jong Kook.
That's not the point here. Why are you here?
Why is he here?
- You're supposed to be in my room. - It's a trick, you know.
Why would you keep it to yourself?
- You should've told me. - I'm speechless.
- I can't believe him. - Hey, remember what you said?
Obviously, I thought there would be only the other team members here.
You should've stopped him from lifting the blanket.
I was lying on the bed confidently.
- What's wrong with him? - Exactly.
You should've stayed at my house. Why did you come here?
This is driving me crazy.
- Why were you hiding here? - You're driving me crazy.
- I'm speechless. - Go away! Go!
I can't believe this. Hey!
- Be honest with me. Why here? - Am I out?
Of course, you're out.
Did he do it on purpose?
- Is he a spy or something? - Why would he do that?
Did he try to help me?
Is he a spy or what?
I'm not a spy. I wasn't trying to help the other team.
But why...
Why did you try to help me?
- But can you really hide here? - Hey, go out and hide.
I'll lie down here.
Where?
- Are you okay? - Yes.
- Haha, it's not noticeable. - Right?
- I didn't know you'd help me out. - Don't come between us.
- Why would you come between us? - My gosh.
I'm pretty sure that someone is hiding in this room.
I told you both of my team members went out of the house.
Wait.
Of course, you can do that.
Anyway, thank you, Suk Jin.
- Why was he hiding in that room? - Exactly.
Thank goodness.
He didn't find me.
Someone is hiding here.
There must be someone here.
I'm sure there is.
- I found So Min. - Hey!
Why are you all...
- Why are you all here? - Hey.
- Is this a prank? - It's odd. Hey.
- This is driving me nuts. - Why would they help me?
Hey, So Min!
- That's not the case. - I mean...
Why did you come to this house, Jong Kook?
- Hey. - Why were you hiding in this house?
- I didn't... - Why did you want to come here?
- It's because this is your house. - But why...
It's because this is your house.
- But why... - I came to find your team members.
- But we found your team members. - This can't be happening.
Jong Kook, hurry up and find his team members.
- This is ridiculous. - We must win the first game.
- How did this happen? - Hang on. Then...
This doesn't make any sense. What's going on?
What's going on?
It's a bit strange. I think it's a conspiracy.
- Right? - It's a conspiracy.
- I mean, why would they do that? - Your team members...
I'm pretty sure that the tall one...
Wait, Jae Suk. I'm sure the tall one is around here.
Seagulls are flying in the sky.
Seeing that those migratory birds are flying away,
I think that winter is finally over.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you all did a great job this winter. I mean, the entire year.
Somewhere on the mudflat between rocks,
Kwang Soo is hiding.
Kwang Soo, don't cross the river.
That is your house.
That's right. This one isn't mine.
- Gosh. - Come over here.
- What are you doing? - Let's take a look around here.
We should search outside.
It must be hard for the tall one to hide.
Wait. I think...
- I think someone's here. - They're the sound team.
Nam Joong is here too.
- Why is Nam Joong here? - Why is he here?
I'm not feeling well.
- No. He's on my team. - It's Se Chan.
- He's on my team. - It's Se Chan.
It's Se Chan.
Hey, you punk!
Why didn't you stay inside?
Hey, why are you helping me?
Why did you come here?
- Why are you helping me? - I don't understand.
Why did you come here? Why?
Have you noticed that they were acting so awkwardly?
I told you guys to act naturally!
- You were all looking so awkward. - I noticed...
that something was weird about the staff members sitting here.
I get that, but why were you hiding out here?
What's wrong with you all?
You could have just stayed inside the house!
Why did all of you come out? What's wrong with you?
I was afraid you two might come into the house.
All you guys had to do was stay inside the house.
- Hey, by the way... - I mean, why...
Why are you helping me?
This doesn't make any sense.
I was going to go in a different direction.
This makes no sense.
Jong Kook is already upset.
The tone of his voice...
He's definitely upset.
Why didn't they stay inside? I didn't go there to protect them.
I just don't understand.
They could've stayed in the house.
My gosh. Those punks...
You know...
Why would they...
- Hey, don't kick it. - I don't understand.
- What if someone is under there? - What? Hold on.
What? Hold on.
Wait.
- Oh, my. Look at him. - That was perfect.
It was perfect.
- How did you know I was here? - Indeed.
I heard you guys leaving earlier.
Who covered you with the blankets?
There must've been someone who covered him.
Gosh. Why was he hiding in there?
I just have to find Ji Hyo now.
That tall punk.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo. - That tall punk...
Ji Hyo!
Wait.
I think it's likely that the tall one...
is hiding on the mudflat.
- That tall punk. - Ji Hyo.
I think he's over there.
Where is he?
- He must be somewhere around here. - What?
She's not here.
I'm pretty sure that Kwang Soo is somewhere around here.
Where's Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo! - Follow me.
Ji Hyo!
I should find Kwang Soo.
He must be crouching down in a corner.
I felt like my heart was going to stop.
Where's Ji Hyo?
Go away!
Where is she?
- Where on earth is Ji Hyo? - Gosh, that tall punk. Wait.
Gosh. Where is she hiding?
- Let's find Ji Hyo. - Where is he?
Wait.
No, wait. Stop.
Aren't you Ji Hyo?
Why were you hiding in a place like that?
Gosh, seriously.
- Team Yoo Grand Award wins! - Oh, yes!
- Why were you hiding there? - Jong Kook.
I saw Kwang Soo running toward the ocean.
- What? - Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, come out now!
Kwang Soo, we won!
Gosh, it's cold. It's so cold.
I'm so cold.
Oh, man. It's so cold.
I want to go home.
Gosh.
Oh, the tide is coming in.
- Kwang Soo, it's over. - Yes?
- It's over? - Yes.
We should get out of here now. The tide is coming in.
- I didn't get caught, did I? - No.
Oh, yes.
Did he actually go to the mudflat?
He went into the mudflat.
- What? - He's unbelievable.
He's amazing.
He practically gave himself a penalty.
Hey, did you say he went into the mudflat?
Why did you go all the way there?
- What happened? - We won.
We won? Yes! Okay!
I think that you guys planned all this.
- That's not true. - I think it was intentional.
- No. Don't be ridiculous. - We tried to hide well.
I'm sure that you guys conspired together.
- Never. Trust me. - That's not true.
Go away! I'll be alone on my team.
- Don't forget that you signed... - Go!
- the oath. - You promised not to get mad.
- Go away! - Come on, Jong Kook.
- Go! - Show him the oath.
- He told us to leave. - Give me the oath. This won't do.
Jong Kook is looking at the mudflat.
- He's looking at the mudflat. - Jong Kook, please.
- He must be so cold. - I'm so cold.
- I'm so cold. - Put this on.
Put on your jacket. Why did you...
- First of all, - What's wrong with you?
- you should've set the boundaries. - It's so cold.
- How could I find him? - Put it on.
Move!
Besides, I told everyone...
that I wouldn't let Jae Suk go into my house.
Keep your promise, Jong Kook.
- I don't need any of you. - Actually...
- Take off your jackets. - Don't be like this.
- I don't need you guys. - Come on. Don't take it off.
- I can't do this anymore. - Don't be like this.
What's the point of signing the oath?
I was wrong.
- You... - I didn't expect them to win.
Don't even think of joining my team. I'll be alone.
- I can't believe her. - She already moved to that team.
She moved to that team already?
Jong Kook, look at this. And don't get the wrong idea.
I think she did this to make us laugh.
But I thought it'd be helpful.
- Show him. - What did you write on it?
She painted over his eyes, crossed off "Kim", and wrote "Yu".
- I had no expectations from her. - That's unbelievable.
When she came into my room and buttered me up,
I felt that something was fishy about her.
Team Kim Grand Award lost five points,
and Team Yoo Grand Award earned six points.
- Okay! - Good job!
- You can turn the game around. - Exactly.
I'll make my team lose and choose one person.
I'll choose one of the members who joined me in the first round.
- He can't seem to drop it. - I'm serious.
- I've made my mind. - Show him the oath now.
- I'm willing to get a penalty. - Give me the oath.
- I'll receive a penalty. - You signed this 30 minutes ago.
You, Mudflat! I'll teach you a lesson.
- Me? Why? - You irk me more than anyone else.
Why?
I'm going to choose you. You irk me for no reason.
- Why? - "For no reason".
- What do you mean by that? - Keep up the good work.
You even went into the mudflat. Why didn't you dive in the ocean?
- Why? - You see,
- I searched with Jong Kook. - I won't team up with you guys.
- I understand why he's upset. - Of course.
As soon as we started searching, he took me to my house.
And we saw Suk Jin just lying in the bed.
- You call that hiding? - He wasn't even hiding.
Did you faint?
- You should've made an effort. - He was so halfhearted.
It wasn't like that. Listen.
Ji Hyo was just standing outside.
I was confidently telling you that I was there.
It was your fault. You shouldn't have taken the covers.
Why were you hiding in his house not mine?
I clearly told you guys that I wouldn't come into my house,
and that you should stay in the house.
When did you tell us that?
What do you mean? I told you that I wouldn't let Jae Suk...
go into my house since we would be tied together!
Ji Hyo, are you okay?
That was scary.
Read the oath again.
- Why did you even sign it? - There's no point.
What's the point of signing it?
- Here you go. - I won't win the race.
"I, Kim Jong Kook, hereby assure that I dearly love..."
"all the cast members to the point that I'd pick the stars for them."
"I promise not to get upset even if they don't choose me."
"I also promise to listen to and respect their opinions."
- Yes, I know. - You signed here.
You also promised not to glare at us...
or speak to us in a threatening tone.
- He broke his promises. - You signed this.
- What's the point? - He broke them so many times.
Let's drop it. That's enough.
It's time for the second mission.
Before we begin the second mission, you will choose your team again.
We won the first round despite the disadvantage.
- Absolutely. - You're amazing, Yoo Grand Award.
We won eventually.
Shall we go to our rooms now?
The team leaders should go first.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Please put on a blindfold and leave in the same order as before.
Why should we put on a blindfold?
I've already made up my mind. I'll choose the same team.
Let's get some good energy from him. Okay.
Hello, Yoo Grand Award.
- Oh, my. Welcome, my comrade. - Oh, my.
Of course. I'm too scared to join the other team.
My dear comrades.
The other team is so scary.
I should be loyal.
- Let's do this! - Suk Jin.
I'm a loyal man. I decided to stick with you.
You said you'd leave my team if we lost. Why did you come back?
We'll win this time for sure.
- But you should know... - No, we won't.
that no one else will join this team.
- Someone's coming. - What?
Se Chan, I knew it.
Don't give him things like this.
- Please take this. - Don't give me that.
Please trust me. You know it was a good place to hide.
- Seriously... - We don't need any more people.
The three of us would be enough. Let's do this.
Jong Kook, I won't let you down this time.
Hey, Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo is here too.
The same goes for her. She should've hidden in the house.
- Let me explain. - Why were you out on the path?
- I thought... - Why were you out on the path?
The beacon does not shine on its own base.
That's ridiculous. The cameraman was...
filming you sitting out there.
Exactly. Hey! Where is he?
That cameraman was so slow-witted. Who was that?
- It was Yun Sang. - Stop it.
You could just tell he was filming someone.
It's okay. We can win this time.
What should I do? What would be the best move?
I can't think of a solution.
Next, please go.
What should I do? I'm off.
Why did Jong Kook get mad at me when I wasn't on his team?
He yells at me regardless of whether or not I'm on his team.
What does he want me to do? Does he want me on his team or not?
Next, please go.
I hope one more cast member of our show wins the Grand Award.
My gosh.
Who could that be?
Who is it?
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
Yoo Grand Award!
- You're just unbelievable. - Yoo Grand Award!
- My gosh. She's... - I've made up my mind.
- I know. - Yes.
- What? - Hello!
- Kwang Soo, you chose our team? - Right.
- Good. - I always wanted to join this team.
- Kwang Soo is here. - Why did you come here?
- I always wanted to join your team. - Let's win this time.
- Hey. - I'll make sure we'll win.
- You irk me most. - Why?
You and So Min are in the bottom two.
- Don't hate me. - I will...
- receive a penalty today. - Don't say that.
- Why will you get a penalty? - All I'm thinking about is...
which of you two I should choose to get the penalty with me.
- It'll be a segment of the show. - I didn't have enough time.
- "A segment of the show"? - Yes.
Who else joined the other team other than Haha?
- So Min. - So Min? That team is weak.
- Shall we go now? - Everyone.
- Yes? - Yes?
I'll explain the second mission.
The first game was too advantageous for the other team.
- True. - But fortunately,
- with the other team members' help, - Yes.
we won.
- Stop bringing that up. - Are you talking about me?
Don't mention it again.
- You see, - I know I was wrong.
it helped me let go of my burdens,
so I think I can be more relaxed throughout the shoot.
My gosh. He moved to the other team. Gosh, that brat.
- So Min, you surprised me. - But...
I didn't accept him fully in my heart...
when he joined my team in the previous round.
- You were ready to let him go. - Exactly.
- That team wasn't right for me. - I know.
Through the second mission,
we'll see how witty and smooth...
the two Grand Award winners are as MCs.
It's Do As I Say.
- What is this? - Do As I Say?
- What is it? - It sounds difficult.
One member from each team will play each round.
The players stand facing each other with a bowl of water between them.
Okay.
When the MC calls out a certain body part,
the players must touch it with both hands.
When the MC says, "Bowl",
the one who grabs the bowl and pours the water on the opponent wins.
The game requires agility.
What does the abilities of an MC have to do with this game?
- It requires agility. - I see.
I'm not good at games like this.
Jae Suk gets extremely nervous whenever we play games like this.
- I'm not good at games like this. - So Min is the worst.
Each of you has to play several rounds.
And Haha, since you have an injured back,
- please be an MC. - Understood.
- Okay. We'll definitely win this. - Okay.
- Jong Kook, just enjoy the victory. - We'll win this for sure.
- I'm not expecting that. - We'll definitely win this.
Jong Kook, don't be like that.
- Let's see how it goes. - Don't be like that.
I have one simple question.
I want to know if Kim Grand Award is upset right now.
I want to know if he's upset.
- No, I'm not. - What?
- I'm very excited now. - Of course.
- He says he's not upset. - He's smiling.
- I smile all the time. - He denied it.
- I smile all the time, you know. - Your team members look...
- He's smiling right now. - Okay. I accept that.
- Don't get the wrong idea. - Exactly.
By the way, why do the team members...
- comfort and encourage the leader? - That's not true.
Isn't it usually the other way around?
Well... I know.
So who'd like to compete first?
- First... - How about Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo, set an example. - Got it.
- Then... - Jae Suk or So Min...
Okay.
- Jong Kook, you'll host the game. - Me?
Kwang Soo, you have to do well...
if you want to get on Jong Kook's good side.
- I'll win for sure. - Got it.
- Let's do this. - Touch the body part he names.
Grab the bowl only when he yells the word "Bowl".
Okay.
Here we go.
- Eyes. - This isn't easy.
Nose.
Mouth. Knees.
Right toes.
Now, left toes.
Left toes, right toes.
Hold on a second.
- What? - Stop walking toward it.
- You were moving forward. - This is wrong.
- Got it. - That's wrong.
- Right toes. - That's how he lived his life.
Left toes.
Left toes, right toes.
Top of the head.
Please stand back up.
- Please stand back up. - He's close to calling it.
- He's close to calling it. - Left chest.
Right chest.
Left chest.
- Jae Suk, lower your hands. - Lower your hands!
- You... - Lower your hands.
- Hey! - Your hands were up too high.
- Your hands should be here. - Don't be ridiculous!
- Lower your hands. - That's absurd.
They should be down here.
- Right here. - No way.
When you work out at the gym, I bet you go like this.
No way. Hey!
Jae Suk.
Are you kidding me?
- Like this? - Grab where your chest is at.
Grab where your chest is at.
- Seriously? - Grab where your chest is at.
Got it.
- Left knee. - All right.
Left knee, right knee.
Left toes.
Right toes.
Left heel.
He'll soon call it.
Top of the head, bowl!
- What? - Look.
I ducked.
- Kwang Soo wins. - Nice!
- Okay! - Good job.
- Nice. - Only one bowl remains.
That was close.
The score is 1 to 0.
- Good. - That was close.
Kwang Soo, you're doing good.
I didn't expect him to say it without pausing.
All right.
Ears.
Eyes, nose, knees.
Left knee, right knee.
Right shoulder, left shoulder.
- You should stand up straight. - Hey!
- Are you kidding me? - I was just getting ready.
- Stop that. - Got it.
- He doesn't take sides. - Right chest.
- Stand up straight. - Lower your hands.
This is the spot.
This is the actual spot.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
It's already quite low.
- This is the spot. - That's quite low.
- My nipple is here. - Okay.
Head.
Stand up straight. Head, shoulders, knees,
the buttocks, bowl!
It's a tie now.
- The score is 1 to 1. - Who's up next?
Okay. You did well.
- Then... - Hold on.
Why am I against Suk Jin again?
I always seem to be up against him.
He sensed that So Min would be up next,
so he volunteered.
- Jae Suk will host the game. - Okay.
Sure.
Here we go.
I've been going up against Suk Jin a lot lately.
Bowl!
No, wait.
I was taking off my jacket.
Why...
Nice one. We scored, right?
- That counts. - No, it doesn't.
I was taking off my jacket.
How is this fair?
- That's not fair. - But the game was on.
The game's supposed to be between those two.
- That's 2 to 1. - All right.
That's why...
- How is this fair? - You should've called a time-out.
Why didn't you call a time-out?
And he's the one who got splashed.
- Why are you still dry? - Suk Jin, what was that?
Why did you take off your jacket at that moment?
Anyway, good job.
- Good job. - Okay.
- Nice teamwork. - Good job.
- Talk about good teamwork. - Let's go.
- Unbelievable. - Please take a step back.
Call a time-out if you need one.
- You need to overcome this. - And go.
Pants.
Pants?
Yes, pants.
- Wait. - Don't be flustered...
and grab your pants.
Just grab your pants.
What would you have done if I were wearing a skirt?
- A skirt? - Unbelievable.
That's so annoying, you know.
All right.
Thankfully, they're both wearing pants.
Head.
- Shoulders. - Shoulders.
- Ears. - Ears.
Second toe.
Second toe?
Grab it with two hands.
- I like how he is detail-oriented. - With both hands.
All right.
The right fifth toe.
Darn it.
Mouth.
Mouth?
What the...
- What? - After touching our toes?
- Jae Suk. - What's wrong?
I can't believe he made them touch their mouth.
I mean...
- After the toes... - He's just being a menace.
- That was a good one. - What was wrong with it?
- There are hygiene issues. - That was a good one.
- Be careful with it then. - The mouth after the toes?
Who cares, right?
Be careful with it.
- Why? - You've got this.
But I won.
Let's move on to the next round.
- Should I go next? - Sure.
- Haha, go ahead. - Okay.
- Is Jae Suk playing? - From this point on,
you'll play one round each.
- Se Chan will probably win. - Here we go.
- Let's begin. - Let's keep the winning streak.
Let's agree to this being our basic pose.
- Okay. - This will be our basic pose.
Good idea.
He can hinge at the hips well.
Look at how flexible he is.
- Check that out. - Look.
- All right. - It hurts.
Please shake hands.
- Sure. - Good game.
High-five each other.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
- Play fair. - The game will begin.
Applaud!
- Massage each other's shoulders. - Each other's?
Yes, each other's.
You're giving us useless orders.
Those are some weird orders.
I like the friendly vibes.
Please rub your forehead.
- Okay. - All right.
- Now your eyebrows. - Okay.
- And applaud. - Applaud!
- Hike up your pants a little. - Got it.
While eating kalguksu with manila clams.
- Kalguksu. - All right.
- We're eating. - And...
applaud!
Are we at a market?
Pants, pants,
pants, pants,
pants, pants, pants, pants,
p, p, p, p,
p, p, p, p, p.
- P, p, p, p, p. - P, p, p, p, p.
Nice!
Nicely done, Haha.
Good one, Se Chan.
Don't forget you're playing this game.
- Nice. - Keep going.
- Pants. - Go, go.
Bowl!
Nice!
Your performance was great though.
- Nice. - Your performance.
You were too invested in your performance.
- Next up are So Min and Ji Hyo. - Okay.
Nice one.
Okay, show her what you've got.
Ji Hyo, I'll have my eyes on you.
- Jong Kook... - You can make up for this.
All right.
- Right. - Here we go.
Let's go!
- Let's keep it speedy. - I'll start off with an easy one.
- Head. - Ji Hyo will definitely win.
Shoulders.
Knees.
Stay on alert.
Toes, knees.
- He's close. - Toes, knees.
Use your upper body too.
Toes, knees. Toes...
- Is this a workout? - Why are you making them work out?
This isn't a workout program.
- Your upper body should... - Is this a workout?
- Unbelievable. - What's with the hands?
- Why... - They aren't here to work out.
- Quality over quantity. - Don't make them do squats.
Do it properly.
Toes, knees, toes, knees. Like this.
- Why are you making them work out? - Just do it for me.
Lift your torso up slightly.
Toes, knees.
- You're not a gym teacher. - Toes, knees.
Is this a workout program?
They're listening to his instructions though.
Grab your knees.
Toes.
- Knees. - Check him out.
- Toes, knees. - He's loving it.
- Toes, knees. - Look at them.
He's close to saying it.
Seriously?
Just say it already.
- The game should be played. - Right.
How long must this go on?
She's right.
- Right. - I wanted you to work out.
- An exercise... - She's right.
I just wanted you to work out.
Ji Hyo, just bear with him, okay?
Take deep breaths.
- Ji Hyo, you've got this. - Take deep breaths.
You have the perfect pose though.
Ji Hyo, I'm glad you did it.
Ji Hyo, good one.
Toes, bowl.
- Wow. - Nice.
Nice.
You gave her a hint, but it didn't work.
You did well though.
The score is 4 to 4.
- Okay. - So this'll be the last round.
- One last round. - Right.
- It'll end with this round. - Right.
- This'll decide who wins. - Yes.
- This'll be the last round. - Our team will host the game.
But Suk Jin once hosted "Star Golden Bell".
But it's our turn...
to host the game.
Let Se Chan do it this time.
Sure, Se Chan can host the game.
- Let Se Chan do it this time. - Sure, Se Chan can host the game.
- Nice. - We've done it many times,
- so Se Chan... - Suk Jin should.
Suk Jin seems disappointed.
No, I'm good.
- Suk Jin. - I'm good.
Let Suk Jin host the game.
- I'm fine. - Suk Jin's sulking!
Let him do it, darn it.
- I'm fine! - Seriously?
- Guys, wait. - Just go ahead.
Suk Jin, go ahead.
He's the former host of "Star Golden Bell", remember?
Let's go!
- Remember "Six Heroines"! - "Six Heroines".
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
Here we go.
This'll decide who wins, right?
I like your tone!
- Let's go, let's go! - Let's win this.
- Let's go! - It's the final round!
Okay!
Here we go, here we go.
- Let's go, let's go! - It's the final round!
- Catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak - Squeak, squeak
- This will decide the game. - I like his tone.
- I like your tone! - Let's win this.
Head.
Ears.
Nose!
Eyes. Eyes, nose,
ears. Ears.
- He fell asleep! - Jae Suk!
Nose, ears.
- Ears. - Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk! Wake up! - You're in the middle of a game!
- You're playing a game! - Give him some time.
- Hey! What are you doing? - You're in the middle of a game!
- You're in the middle of a game! - What do you think you're doing?
It was so boring.
- He fell deeply asleep. - It'll get fun soon.
- Give him some time. - Jae Suk.
- He was hosting it. - Jae Suk!
- I'm so sorry. - Give him some time, Jae Suk.
- I apologize. - Give him some time, Jae Suk.
- I can't stand it when it's boring. - You know how he's like.
- It'll get better soon. - He has his own style.
- He was just getting warmed up. - It'll get better soon.
Everyone!
Everyone, if you play with that mindset, it's bound to be boring.
- You need to be open-minded. - Jae Suk...
I knew he'd do that the moment he let Suk Jin host it.
He was going to do that.
I guess you're enjoying this.
- I'll let you enjoy all you want. - Okay.
- Are you serious? - Of course.
I can't stand it when it's boring.
- Do you find this fun? Okay. - Yes.
- It's okay. - He was about to say...
something fun right after that.
He has his own tactics. You should all give him some time.
I'm sorry that I fell asleep.
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. - If you keep this up,
- it'll get boring. - I'm sorry.
- Give him some time. - Eyes.
- Nose. - Nose.
- Ears. - Ears.
- Poke your nostrils. Mouth. - Poke your nostrils.
My gosh.
Poke your nostrils.
- Poke your nostrils. - Mouth.
- This is not fun. - Sir, please get up!
- Ears. - This is terrible.
- Aren't you having fun? - Sir, please get up!
- Excuse me. - Hey, hey!
- Hey! - He passed out. Hey!
How can you pass out when we're rolling?
Sir, please get up!
- Hey! - He passed out. Hey!
How can you pass out when we're rolling?
You shouldn't fall asleep.
- You shouldn't fall asleep. - It's not time to be sleeping.
- Get up. - Did you find that boring?
- Wake him up. - Were we in the middle of a shoot?
- But... - Get up, you guys.
- Get up! Get up, So Min. - Wake them up.
- We are in the middle of a shoot. - Wake them up.
- Get up! - We were rolling?
- What's wrong with me? - If you give me more time...
If you play with that mindset,
- it's bound to be boring. - Get to your senses.
Who told you that you can fall asleep during the shoot?
Who dares to fall asleep?
Who...
Who told you that you can fall asleep during the shoot?
- Gosh, that was so boring. - That's enough!
- What's wrong with me? - I said that's enough.
Let me open the door. Let's get some fresh air.
- Let the fresh air in! - Come on.
Please open the door.
- Why am I so sleepy today? - It's okay.
It's okay, everyone.
Everyone, come here. You need to wake up.
We need to wake up!
- Did you get some fresh air? - Yes, it's nice.
- Nostrils? That was... - My gosh.
Look at these ungrateful jerks.
- Why would you curse at us? - No, I meant...
You're having so much fun, aren't you?
- I'll make this fun. - Okay.
- Knees. - Knees.
Knees, toes.
- I'm so excited. - Knees, toes, toes.
Put your foreheads together.
- Put your foreheads together. - What?
- Put your foreheads together. - You can't fall asleep here.
Put your foreheads together!
- Put your foreheads together! - But...
Just do as you're told!
Put your foreheads together!
Do the finale pose for Andre Kim's shows!
- But we're wearing caps. - But...
- How could we... - You should've checked...
You should check in advance...
- before telling us anything. - He's right.
- Everyone, if you keep this up, - Okay, okay.
it's impossible for you to have fun!
- Hey, hey! Kwang Soo! - What's wrong with you?
- Don't pass out. Kwang Soo. No. - Kwang Soo...
He's sleeping with his eyes open!
- Don't fall asleep! - Hey.
Don't fall asleep!
- What was that? - Don't fall asleep.
- Kwang Soo, you can't. - Were we in the middle of a shoot?
Oh, we were rolling.
Don't fall asleep.
- Don't. - Okay.
- Don't fall asleep. - Are you okay?
Are you okay? Okay, I got it.
Okay, I got it. Since the atmosphere is all ruined, I'll finish it fast.
- I'll finish within 3 seconds. - 3 seconds? Okay.
- I'm not in great condition. - Forehead.
- Forehead. - Eyes.
You're not sleepy, are you?
Forehead, eyes. Knees!
Forehead.
Guys!
Eyes, ears.
Nose.
Bowl!
Ears. Nose.
Why aren't you grabbing it?
- Yes! - Are you asleep? He's asleep!
- He fell asleep! - He's asleep.
Ears. Nose.
Bowl!
- Yes! - Are you asleep?
- He fell asleep. - He's asleep!
- We won! - He fell asleep.
- Is it over? - We were in the middle of a game!
It's over?
But I just dozed off!
It's over already?
- Yes! - But I just dozed off!
- We won. - Isn't that cheating?
I dozed off only briefly!
- You should take responsibility! - Why did you doze off?
- What a shame. - Listen!
- Were you sleepy? - I dozed off only briefly.
- You must've been sleepy. - I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Haha.
- We won. - I had no idea.
So he had a strategy all along.
- Of course. - That was his strategy.
That was his strategy.
- He used his skills though! - But this is...
- It's cheating! That's right. - It's cheating.
Didn't he hypnotize me?
It's not fair! He made us fall asleep.
But Jong Kook overcame the boredom...
- and rightfully won. - I had a good sleep in a long time.
- That's good. - That's why I didn't fall asleep.
That's the power of deep sleep!
Thanks to Suk Jin's hosting,
Team Kim Grand Award won.
- Yes! - It's not fair.
- I guess there's no other option. - Yes!
Everyone on Team Kim Grand Award earned 10 points.
And everyone on Team Yoo Grand Award got minus three points.
- So what's going to happen? - So Min...
Look at So Min.
The team she's on always loses. I'm sorry.
- What do I do? - So Min,
- it's okay. - What do I do?
- I have such few points. - I feel so refreshed.
Thank goodness I had a deep sleep last night.
- I had a pig dream last night. - I had a good sleep.
We'll now have lunch.
- Okay. - Wow.
The team leaders should wait in their rooms.
This time, there aren't any points on the line.
The rest of you will step outside,
and you'll head to the room you want with your bowl of rice.
- You can have your lunch there. - Okay.
- Since we won't... - Someone I want to have lunch with?
Since no points are involved, this is a popularity contest, right?
- That's right. - All right then.
- Let's go. - Oh, we're just having lunch.
- It's not about our looks. - I slept too much.
Everyone had a good sleep.
What's this?
Oh, it's ramyeon.
Ramyeon is good enough for us.
We don't need to eat much for lunch.
I love the menu.
Are they having ramyeon too?
What do I do?
- What do I do? - I've made up my mind.
- Who are you picking? - I want to eat comfortably.
You're picking Jae Suk? I also want to eat with Jae Suk.
But you have to think carefully. He'll get upset for real.
- But lunch is okay. - Don't think about that.
- Lunch is okay. - Lunch is okay.
- So only when we play games... - But you'll go to Jong Kook...
and be adored by him.
I'm not one to be adored by anyone. He should be adored by me.
What are you saying?
- You did a lot of cute acts today. - He's right.
It's humiliating.
- He did cute acts when he's 50. - That's not true. I didn't do that.
With eyes filled with love,
- he wanted to be adored. - I'm not the one to be adored.
He's just a younger brother who needs a pat on the back.
Then I'll go first.
- You can go next. - Let's just close our eyes.
- I'm off then. - Okay.
I'll go next.
- My goodness. - My goodness, Se Chan.
I should eat with you...
- to be comfortable. - Of course.
Se Chan...
He doesn't eat ramyeon, you know.
Of course we should have ramyeon.
There you go.
The girl who likes soups is here.
We're having ramyeon.
- I love ramyeon, Jae Suk. - I make delicious ramyeon.
Who is going next? You should set off, Haha.
I'm going to Jong Kook's room.
I'm picking Jong Kook too.
Which room are you picking?
I don't know. What should I do?
Which room are you picking? Let's divide the members in half.
If too many people go to Jong Kook's room,
- I'll go to Jae Suk's room. - To Jae Suk?
Yes.
- I'm loyal to you, Jong Kook. - Suk Jin.
Our lunch is like the penalty.
Our lunch is the penalty. Look at this.
We prepared the foods Jong Kook likes.
You can have chicken breast and low-sodium food for lunch.
He doesn't eat like this! He loves tangsuyuk and fritters!
I eat cup noodles these days.
- That's right. - He doesn't eat these.
How can we have almonds with rice?
Why did they give us almonds?
We could've been in big trouble.
If he ate this alone...
That'd be horrible.
If that happened, I'd have removed the photo of us smiling...
that's hanging in our restaurant.
But this is just a game.
- No, it's not. - Okay?
Don't put your entire life on this.
You picked Jae Suk for both rounds.
- That's... - You could've picked me once.
- Don't you agree, Suk Jin? - Haha.
If you remove Jong Kook from the photo, put me in.
Suk Jin, why would you grab that chance?
Suk Jin, go ahead.
You can go ahead.
My goodness. So Min.
Can I put the noodles in?
Where? The water is not boiling yet.
Do you have ketchup?
- I love... - The ketchup is here.
how you're being considerate.
- "Can I put them in?" - Thank you, Ji Hyo.
Aren't we kind?
If it was Jong Kook, he'd have said this.
"Don't put it in."
- "It's not good for your health." - "Don't put it in, you punk!"
"You're so thoughtless."
He'd have said that.
This feels like a ramyeon club.
- Right? - Yes.
The egg looks like a flower.
It looks like thick clouds.
I've never seen anyone who makes meringue out of ramyeon.
I love how no one is negative here.
- Let's eat now! Get your portion. - No one is negative. Now?
Look at this.
- This is how you should eat. - Oh, like that?
- Thank you. - The noodles are cooked perfectly.
There's more, so help yourself.
- How did he make it so delicious? - This is amazing.
The noodles are so chewy.
- Let's add gochujang. - Add the chicken breast here.
That's the worst.
It seriously is. How do you eat it like that?
It tastes okay because the chicken breast doesn't smell.
It doesn't smell at all.
- This is good. - You're smiling?
Try it. Try it like this.
- It must be good. He's smiling. - Okay, okay.
- Kwang Soo, try it. - I like it.
Try it like this. It tastes okay. Try it, Kwang Soo.
Try it with the shake.
Please come out!
I feel sleepy now.
Goodness, I'm so full.
We had chicken breast.
I heard you had chicken breasts.
This place serves good food. We had ramyeon,
- meatballs, and sausages. - We had meatballs too.
- Sausages too. - We even added eggs to ramyeon.
How will you face Jong Kook now?
What? It's okay, it's just a meal.
But Jong Kook is really upset right now.
I won't see him then.
- I'll run away. - You've got some guts.
I decided to stay on this team for good.
Ji Hyo must be sleeping in the room.
- Really? - She's really sleeping?
She must think we are at Boracay.
Ji Hyo, wake up.
We're going out?
- She's unbelievable. - She must think we are at Boracay.
- Hey. - We're not at Boracay, Ji Hyo.
- You fell asleep? - What's happening?
We're not at a vacation spot.
- Why did you fall asleep? - What's wrong with you?
Why did you come out of that room?
Come to your senses, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo has been sleeping since earlier.
She fell asleep when you were hosting, and she just got up.
- I made you fall asleep? - I'm sorry.
- She even missed lunch. - Thank you, Suk Jin.
I slept soundly thanks to you.
My youngest daughter hasn't been able to sleep well recently.
Could you host the game at my place once?
I'll pay a visit.
- Oh, gosh. - What's wrong?
You see? Someone just fell asleep again!
- She fell asleep because of you! - Hey!
We need Jae Suk here!
- Suk Jin will get mad for real. - Don't do that to Suk Jin.
Why do so many people pass out these days?
Go and wash your face with the seawater.
Washing your face wakes you up right away.
Is today's special about superpowers?
Did you take a potion or something?
Is today really about superpowers?
All right. Now this will be your last mission.
Your choice of team will be very important.
- That's right. - I'll go first.
It's cold outside, and they're taking longer than I thought.
Oh, dear.
- Ji Hyo. - Gosh, it hurts.
Hey, are you okay?
Why would you greet me with your foot?
- Hey, well done. - I was glad to see you.
- You made the right choice. - You see, I...
Your last team should be my team.
I should be with you until the end.
Right. Well done.
Jae Suk.
- Hey, Suk Jin. - I chose your team at last.
I think your team will win the last mission.
Gosh, you and your skill to make everyone sleep.
I'm choosing you no matter what.
- My goodness. - It depends on the game though.
I think...
we'll be having a quiz. See? They set up everything for it.
Gosh, I think I'm really quick-witted.
This is insane.
Jae Suk!
- Darn it, it's Suk Jin! - Hey, Haha.
- Hey. - Haha is loyal.
- My goodness. - I'm loyal, aren't I?
- My goodness. - I ate with Jong Kook, but...
- Haha. - Hello, Jae Suk.
- Hey, Jae Suk. - You're here, Kwang Soo.
- The empty-headed ones are here. - I'm back home.
- Gosh. - Kwang Soo.
You ran away from home though.
This is what they set up for the last game.
- You need to sit here. - It's a quiz.
- It's a quiz. - It's the last game, but...
We'll win no matter what.
Another one is here.
Hello, did you enjoy your lunch?
- My goodness. - This is driving me crazy.
- Everyone's joining Jae Suk? - I can't believe it.
- This is driving me crazy. - Everyone's joining Jae Suk?
We're family since we ate together.
- You decided to just... - This is driving me crazy.
- There are six of us. - You should've gone there.
(Feeling nervous to have many Empty Heads)
- You should join his team. - Why?
Look what they set up here.
- What's happening? - Another one?
- You decided to just... - This is driving me crazy.
Look what they set up here.
- What's happening? - Another one?
- Hey! - Oh, no.
What's happening?
(Another member chose Jae Suk?)
- What's happening? - Another one?
(Even So Min is joining Team Yoo Grand Award?)
- Hey! - Oh, no.
- What's happening? - But Jong Kook...
Ji Hyo is the only one...
(If So Min is here as well,)
But Jong Kook...
(then Ji Hyo is the only one who's with Jong Kook?)
Ji Hyo is the only one...
There's only two of them?
(For real?)
- Jong Kook must be really upset. - Too many people are here, Bo Pil.
Too many people are here.
Jong Kook must be extremely upset.
- I'm sure he's furious. - Jong Kook must be upset.
Then we...
(Right then, the door opens again.)
- Oh, gosh. - You scared us.
(The camera team enters.)
(Very tense)
- Oh, gosh. - You scared us.
(They thought it was angry Kim Grand Award.)
- You chose us too? - Jae Suk.
- Darn you! - Jae Suk...
Open the door quietly!
Jae Suk is totally scared.
(While Yoo Grand Award is scared of Kim Grand Award...)
What's going to happen? I'm feeling anxious.
Everyone has chosen their team.
- They're done? - Your team member...
is Ji Hyo.
Let's proceed with the third mission.
(It's just the two.)
Jong Kook!
It's okay. Don't worry. Well done.
It's fine. I made up my mind...
(He's not okay at all.)
- But... - to play alone anyway.
What's going on, seriously?
(With Ji Hyo who's half asleep,)
My gosh.
(he's on his way to meet them.)
How could everyone...
Gosh. Fine.
I've already chosen who'll get the penalty.
(The door to Team Yoo Grand Award's room has finally opened.)
(He's here.)
- Hello. - Oh, gosh.
(They avoid his eyes.)
(Look at these guys.)
Oh, gosh.
(We can only hear them dry coughing. The atmosphere is icy-cold.)
Hey, Jong Kook. Don't look at us like that!
Don't look into my eyes for more than three seconds.
- Why not? - It says so on the contract!
(No glancing is allowed.)
- 1, 2, 3. - No, I'm not looking at you.
- What's wrong? - You're only allowed two seconds.
Ji Hyo, come. Where do you want to sit?
- Where do you want to sit? - Why did everyone...
(On eggshells)
- Come sit in the center. - You're wearing matching shirts.
Of course we should.
(He's okay to pretend to be Ji Hyo's boyfriend.)
My goodness, this is...
I thought we'd be playing a game Jae Suk is good at.
(Suk Jin gives excuses.)
- I see. - My goodness.
Sure, I don't mind. This is another segment anyway.
(But Jong Kook only cares about the segment in the segment.)
- I think they're giving us a quiz. - I think so too.
(They all chose their last team.)
All right. You can turn the tables through this mission.
(They can turn the tables with the last mission.)
- My gosh. - Can I just turn them over?
Can I just turn them over?
(They're about to be turned over by Jong Kook.)
That's not what he meant.
Don't forget our contract.
(He's forgotten about the written oath a long time ago.)
- I have a contract to protect me! - What? What's wrong?
(He's glancing again.)
Your eyes are...
Don't stare at us for more than 3 seconds.
(Reminding him of the written oath)
The way he talks...
If they lose this time, they'll...
- lose a lot of points, right? - Minus six points.
That's right. They'll lose six points.
I'm sorry, but are you his girlfriend?
- Is she... - They look good together.
(They became a couple only for the last mission.)
You look good together!
- You really do. - You look good together.
(They look like a couple from the 90s visiting Ganghwa Island.)
- They look good together. - You look good together!
I can't hold his arm because his arm is too thick.
(Into the skit)
We've been dating for a long time.
- You've dated for a long time? - Yes.
- That's cute. - We've been dating for a long time.
(They immerse into a skit fast after 11 years of experience.)
- We've dated for a long time. - That's nice.
- How do you date for so long? - Don't we look like a family?
"How do you date for so long?"
You can turn the tables through the last mission.
(Here's the last mission that can turn the tables.)
It's a mission to check the intelligence of two smart men.
(Two grand award winners' brain battle)
- It's a quiz. - It's called The Uncanny Quiz.
(The Uncanny Quiz)
- Yes! - It's a quiz!
(Yoo Grand Award is good at a quiz.)
Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk! - Yoo Jae Suk!
(Empty Heads have Yoo Grand Award.)
- It's okay! Don't worry. - Yoo Jae Suk!
- It's okay! It's fine. - Yoo Jae Suk!
(Ji Hyo is frozen after hearing that it's a quiz.)
However, it's not an ordinary quiz.
We've prepared fun questions where you can use...
(The questions require reasoning skills and creativity.)
your reasoning skills and creativity.
We'll give you a point if all of you put your heads together...
(If they put their heads together and answer first,)
and manage to find the answer first.
(they'll get 1 point each.)
(Put our heads together?)
- We need to put our heads together? - That sounds a bit off.
But I have no reasoning skills at all.
(Yang Se Chan, 0 reasoning skills)
Empty Head!
Okay. Okay, I got it.
(They're in trouble too.)
Maybe they'll tell us to write a letter each.
(The 6 members don't have enough to put their heads together.)
- But that's... - Then it will be...
- a total mess. - Six fools are... Oh, no.
What did you just say?
Six fools are... Oh, no.
What?
(A perfect mistake at the perfect timing)
- Hey, come here. - Let go!
(The six fools flew into a rage.)
- Hey. - Darn you.
- Darn you. - Hey, come here.
- Let's drag him out of here. - Hey, you.
- Hey, did you call us 6 fools? - "6 fools"?
(How could you say that?)
- It's "having many fools". - I'm so offended.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. He meant to say that to us!
(The six fools feel offended after counting.)
- Did you call us fools? - He meant to say that to us!
But he was looking at me when he said it.
- All right. - He meant our team.
(The mistake broke fools' hearts.)
Nice job.
It's a mission where you need one genius rather than many fools.
(They need one brain rather than many fools.)
- Okay. - You'll get...
- a chance for each question. - A chance.
(There is a chance for every question.)
If you can't answer within three minutes after hearing the question,
(If no one answers in 3 minutes,)
one member of the team can go outside...
(one member from each team can go outside and look for the hints.)
and look for the hidden hints...
for three minutes.
- Okay, okay. - We are good at finding hints.
Are you telling me to run around all day long?
Se Chan, it's cold outside.
Put on a jacket.
(All the surplus manpower will be searching for hints.)
Put on a jacket now.
You might have to run outside.
Ji Hyo, let's wear a coat.
(Ji Hyo, let's wear a coat.)
Let's wear a coat.
(The Empty Heads are getting ready to go out before the quiz mission.)
It will be nice to stay warm.
It will be a 1-on-1 match between me and Ji Hyo.
(Segment in segment Empty Heads' Outing)
Kwang Soo, put a jacket around your shoulders.
It will be a match.
- I will reveal the first question. - Okay.
(Here's the first question.)
The first question.
(Move one match to complete the equation.)
(However, don't touch the equals sign.)
What?
(Thinking)
(Slapping the table)
(Does Jae Suk have an idea?)
- The equation... - Let me answer.
- Will you answer right away? - Yes.
(Did Jae Suk figure out the answer already?)
What?
Let me answer.
I will move the match here.
That works.
You can't touch the equal sign.
(It's incorrect because he changed the equals sign.)
- Gosh. - Let me answer.
Let me answer.
(Move one match to complete the equation.)
There is a plus sign, right?
Move the vertical match so that it becomes an equal sign.
(However, don't touch the equals sign.)
No! Let me answer.
(Suk Jin changed the plus sign to an equals sign.)
- 1 equals 1 equals 1. - Let me answer.
- Correct. - Okay!
(It's correct.)
The multiplication sign.
- No, no. - The equal sign works.
The equal sign works. 1 equals 1 equals 1.
(Suk Jin completed the equation by moving one match.)
Okay.
(Move one match to complete the equation.)
All right!
(However, don't touch the equals sign.)
1 equals 1 equals 1.
(Team Yoo Grand Award won 1 point.)
Okay.
(Bitter)
Haven't you figured it out yet?
(Move one match to complete the equation.)
- What did he say? - I figured it out.
- It just stood out to me. - You make the same sign.
(However, don't touch the equals sign.)
Se Chan, you make the same inequality sign.
I thought you had to make the multiplication sign.
(He just claps.)
I get it now.
But why is 1 equals 1 equals 1?
The numbers are the same.
(A fool who finds a basic equation hard...)
- We did it! - Okay.
(and other fools who just skip it)
- Let's go! - Let's keep going.
Did we win?
- Yes. - How did it end so soon?
- Do you get it now? - No.
Let's keep going.
- Jong Kook, it's okay. - It's okay.
(Team Kim Grand Award lost a point to the 6 fools.)
Let's keep going.
- Here comes the second question. - Okay.
(The second question)
(Move 2 coins so that the vertical and horizontal lines make 70 cents.)
(However, you must maintain the shape of a cross.)
- Let's make it. - 70 cents.
As it is, the vertical line makes 70 cents...
(The vertical line makes 70 cents...)
and the horizontal line makes 50 cents.
(and the horizontal line makes 50 cents.)
- This works, right? - Do we need to move two coins?
Yes.
Do we need to move two coins?
Like this?
(Kim Grand Award stacks the coins.)
That's right.
You must maintain the shape of the cross...
(It's still 70 cents vertically and 50 cents horizontally.)
and have each line make 70 cents.
No.
In total?
That's right.
(6 fools put their heads together.)
You must maintain the shape of the cross...
and have each line make 70 cents.
- And we can only move two coins. - Yes.
(Suk Jin is thinking by himself.)
This isn't easy.
- And we can only move two coins. - Yes.
(They move the coins around.)
Should we stack the coins?
If we do that...
(70 cents and 60 cents)
This isn't easy.
Should we stack the coins?
If we do that...
(The vertical line makes 70 cents...)
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
(and the horizontal line makes 60 cents.)
- It's 60 cents. - Get another coin.
Move two coins.
If we stack two coins...
We did it. We are done.
(Are they done already?)
We are done.
This is how you do it. Let me answer.
Stack the top coin and the bottom coin in the center.
(Suk Jin got it again.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Stack the top coin and the bottom coin in the center.
(The problem required creativity.)
You stack the coins.
Hey.
(The man who keeps answering the questions flushes.)
I solved it, but Suk Jin butted in at the end.
- We solved it together. - That's right.
(We all worked together.)
- We solved it together. - This is great.
Ajou University!
(The man who went to Ajou University did well.)
This one will be hard.
(There's still a chance to turn the tables.)
Team Kim Grand Award, here comes the question.
I will go and find the hints.
You will get a piece of paper.
(What's the third question that requires paper?)
Connect the dots in a single stroke...
(Connect the dots in a single stroke.)
without going over the same dot twice.
What?
(Connect the dots without returning to the line you already drew.)
In a single stroke?
Can you return to the line you drew?
(You cannot go over the dots twice.)
No, you can't.
- You can't go over the dots twice. - No.
You can't go over the dots twice.
(With bated breath,)
How do you do this?
(everyone focuses on finding the solution.)
Like this?
By the way,
are we entering a program for gifted children?
This is so hard.
I feel dizzy.
- I have no idea. - I think I have motion sickness.
(He shows signs of illness from using his brain.)
I feel dizzy.
- Try again. - I am done.
(Did Suk Jin solve it again?)
- I am done. - Let me see.
I did it.
- I think I solved it. - Really?
(He demonstrates the answer with confidence.)
Is he a genius?
Suk Jin is on fire today.
(The old genius makes them exclaim.)
I will give it a go.
He is incredible.
- Watch. - Okay.
You make a horizontal line first.
(He draws the line in the center first.)
- Okay? - Okay.
Then you go here.
Here, here, here,
here, here,
here, here, here, here, here.
- I did it, right? - You missed a dot.
- He did it. - I did it.
(Did Suk Jin solve the question at once again?)
- What? He did it. - Suk Jin, you missed a dot.
He did it.
I just need to connect it.
- I can do it again. - Did he succeed?
- I did it. - What is up with Suk Jin?
(Genius Suk Jin tries to show it perfectly.)
Really?
- What? - Suk Jin was a genius.
"Finding Genius".
(Suk Jin, the finally found jewel)
He became a genius at the age of 56.
- Watch. - Go ahead.
- What? - Suk Jin was a genius.
What is up with him?
(He demonstrates the answer again relaxedly.)
- You make a horizontal line first. - "Finding Genius".
He became a genius at the age of 56.
Here, here, here,
here, here, here,
here...
(But he failed.)
That wasn't what you did.
Here, here,
(He would have succeeded had he gone up.)
here...
(He ended up going to the side because he was in a hurry.)
That wasn't what you did.
(They failed to win a point.)
That wasn't what you did. You succeeded earlier.
(He did well at first.)
- For goodness' sake. - Try again.
No, no.
No, no. You fool.
If you follow this method, one part gets left behind.
I couldn't do it on the board.
(He did well at first, but he forgot how to do it.)
- This is hard. - Here, here...
(The old genius has bad memories.)
I couldn't do it on the board.
- I did it. - I did it.
(Did Jong Kook succeed?)
- You did it. - Let me show you again.
- I did it. - I did it.
- You did it. - I said it first, right?
(Jong Kook was a bit faster...)
- I did it. - It worked.
(than Suk Jin who eventually realized what was wrong.)
I was mistaken. I did it.
I can do it. I can do it.
(After making a horizontal line,)
- Watch. - Okay.
(After making a horizontal line, he connects the outer dots.)
That's right.
- Go up. - Okay.
(Go up!)
That's right.
Here.
(Jong Kook got it.)
- Okay, okay. - I did that first.
- That's right. - okay, okay.
(The old genius ended up giving the answer to someone else.)
I did that first.
- Suk Jin. - I didn't draw the last line.
- You were so close. - Why didn't you draw it?
(Why did you miss it?)
I didn't draw the last line.
(He stopped right before the answer.)
- Why didn't you draw it? - Seriously.
I gave him the hint on the horizontal line.
What's the point of being a genius if you can't get a question right?
I didn't look at what you did.
Come on, Suk Jin.
- I figured it out right away. - Why didn't you draw the last line?
"Finding Genius Suk Jin".
For the next question, I will give you the props first.
(The current score is 2 to 1.)
What is this?
(They need tools for the next question.)
It's like "Die Hard".
(Move one cup to mirror the bottom arrangement.)
Move one cup...
to make the bottom arrangement.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(Now they...)
Let's arrange the cups.
(accept the question.)
- Okay. - So 2, 3, and 4...
- should be filled. - Firstly...
So we can either move a cup...
(Genius Suk Jin thinks carefully.)
or pour out the water from a cup.
(Find a way to put 3 full cups in the middle.)
- Shall we begin? - Yes.
- Is this possible? - I am sorry, but...
(Move one cup to mirror the bottom arrangement.)
- We can only move one cup, right? - Yes.
I can pour out the liquid...
and put the cup here.
(He reached the answer the fastest.)
Okay.
- What? - What?
I can pour out the liquid...
and put the cup here.
Okay.
- What? - What?
(After seeing such a simple solution,)
I did it, right?
(6 fools are dumbfounded.)
Okay, okay.
Everyone knows that!
What was that?
(Empty Heads complain after understanding the answer.)
Everyone knows that!
- What? - I did it.
Anyone can pour out the liquid and put the cup at the end.
The last question was much harder.
Why didn't you do it if you knew the answer?
(He earned the point for his action rather than thinking.)
We were thrown off because the last question was hard.
(There's only a slight difference between genius and ordinary person.)
Why were you thrown off? It was so easy.
By the way,
you guys are surprised, right? We are really good at this, right?
We are good at figuring out tricks.
(Unlike production crew's expectation,)
Now comes the last question.
(they're doing well without hints.)
(The last question will determine the result.)
The palm is facing up.
From that pose,
(With your palm facing up,)
keep your wrist and shoulder unmoving...
(keep your wrist and shoulder unmoved...)
and make the palm face down.
You start with the palm facing up.
(and make the palm face down.)
- Can't we just do it? - Both hands?
No, one hand.
But you can't turn your wrist.
So we need to make the palm face down.
- Hold on. This is... - This is...
So we can't turn the wrist.
(Make the palm face down without moving the wrist?)
Like this?
We can't turn the wrist.
The back of the hand needs to face up.
This isn't how you do it, right?
Hey, isn't this the solution?
From here,
(Falling)
you can lean forward.
Then your arm will get twisted.
(He tries to twist his arm instead of flipping.)
You will hurt your back.
The hand needs to be like this.
(How does it work?)
The body will stay the same.
How?
- How about this? - You can't turn the wrist.
(They try to flip their palms...)
- Like this. - You can't turn the wrist.
(with all kinds of poses.)
So you can't do this.
Doesn't this count?
I figured it out. Come here.
- How? - Let me answer.
(Haha figured something out.)
- Come here. - How?
- Put your head down. - What?
Your hand is like this, right?
(He lies Kwang Soo down...)
- Come here. - What are you trying to do?
(and asks for help.)
- Get him up. - What? How?
1, 2, 3.
Like this?
(The tall man is upside down.)
Is this the solution?
Like this?
(He feels like he has been forced into a roller coaster.)
Is this the solution?
- Is this the solution? - Keep your head down.
- Incorrect. - Is it incorrect?
(It's obviously incorrect.)
- Is it incorrect? - Hold on.
(The human roller coaster is abandoned after doing his job.)
You can't use the wrist.
Don't turn the wrist.
(There is a way to make the palm face up.)
Don't turn the shoulder.
(The answer)
(Bend the arm at a 90-degree angle 6 times.)
From here...
- From here... - You can't turn the twist.
(What if you roll forward?)
(The hand stays the same!)
Nice.
How does it work?
That doesn't work.
- Like this. - What is this?
Like this.
Can't you do it without moving the shoulder?
(Suk Jin got a hint from Jong Kook's movement.)
Oh, the wrist.
- Like this. - Let me answer.
Let me answer.
From here,
- do this. - Okay.
Then you do this and this.
- Do it again. - Right? From here...
It's correct.
- Right? From here... - It's correct.
(Suk Jin came up with a unique solution.)
- It's correct. - Go down and come up.
- It works. - It works.
(It works.)
From here, fold the arm.
(Fold.)
- Go down. - Go down.
(Fold, go down.)
- Then do this. - Come up.
(Fold, go down, and come up.)
(Suk Jin's answer is correct.)
(The old genius got the last 1 point.)
- I can't believe it. - Suk Jin!
I can't believe it.
(The perfect answer expected by the production crew)
(A new answer by Suk Jin)
From here, fold the arm.
- Go down. - Go down.
- Then do this. - Come up.
Jong Kook gave away the answer.
I can't believe Suk Jin.
(Kim Grand Award gave away the answer unknowingly.)
You did this.
It was an answer we didn't expect.
(They win the mission with a creative answer.)
Really?
- This didn't occur to me. - It's fascinating.
When you get this kind of question correct, you look sexy.
- You look sexy. - You look different.
(Suk Jin won the Empty Heads' envy.)
Our score is high.
This team won 12 points each.
(Team Yoo Grand Award will get 12 points each.)
Well...
This team lost two points each.
(Team Kim Grand Award will lose 2 points each.)
The first place will receive a prize and be exempt from the penalty.
(The 1st place will receive a prize and be exempt from the penalty.)
(7th and 8th place will get the penalty...)
The 7th and 8th places will receive the penalty.
(along with a person of their choice.)
As for the penalty, we put three flags outside.
(Today's penalty...)
(is to retrieve the R flags in the mudflat.)
- Bring one each. - What?
Where are the flags?
- That's the worst. - The flags are in the water.
(The members get nervous about the difficult penalty.)
- Okay. - I will announce the results...
(Dignity of Grand Award Race)
(The result is on the board.)
on the board.
- It's right. - What is up with So Min?
- The points... - Kwang Soo.
(Jae Suk 15 points, Suk Jin 17 points,)
(Jong Kook 3 points, Haha 15 points, Ji Hyo 3 points,)
When did that happen?
(Kwang Soo 28 points, So Min 4 points, Se Chan 20 points.)
With 28 points, Kwang Soo is the 1st place.
(Today's 1st place is Kwang Soo.)
Okay!
He is exempt from the penalty.
(The 1st place will receive a prize and be exempt from the penalty.)
I will now present the prize.
- What is that? - It's a trophy.
(Big Thumb Trophy)
- What is that? - That's incredible.
- He loves prizes like that. - What is this?
(The gold-toned prize makes his eyes go wide.)
- What? - It's a trophy.
We didn't know who would win. I will write down the name now.
- What is that? - On a piece of paper?
- What is that? - That's...
- It looks authentic. - Is that gold?
(The director writes down the name with his bad handwriting.)
Are you writing down the name?
2021 SBS Running Man, Real Grand Award.
(He wrote the name without much consideration.)
- Congratulations on winning. - Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
(Lee Kwang Soo, congratulations on your Grand Award.)
The big toe resembles Kwang Soo.
It's not a big toe. It's a thumb.
It's made of iron.
Iron.
(It's made from heavy iron.)
This is...
- When some time passes, - I know.
if would be hard to find a place for it.
(It would be the hardest to find a place for it.)
The members at the bottom are Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook will get the penalty today.)
Pick a member...
(They can choose one more person except for Kwang Soo.)
who will receive the penalty except for Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo survived.
(So Min tries to avoid their eyes and run away.)
Okay!
Get ready, okay?
- The one with long hair. - The one with long hair.
(The long-haired bat gets caught.)
Get ready.
Okay!
(The 3 people who'll get the penalty are chosen.)
- This is great. - Game over.
- The other members can go home. - Okay.
(The rest can go home.)
(The penalty will be executed at the mudflat.)
- I feel bad. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you.
(Difficulty level: Flag 1, low, Flag 2, medium, Flag 3, high)
The weather is warm.
(The trio gets ready to enter the mudflat.)
Do we need to put on rubber boots?
One of you needs to take off the rubber boots.
(1 of them will have to enter without the boots.)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- All right. - Play or lose,
- rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins.)
Okay!
- I will take them off. - Okay!
From head to toe
You are lovely
(So Min the traitor gives an annoying ceremony.)
- She is such an eyesore. - I am proud that you are my woman
I can go in barefoot, right?
Bring a flag each to complete the mission.
(They head off to retrieve the flag.)
I will go that way!
Gosh, this will make me so healthy.
Be careful. Your feet will sink.
(Staggering)
Your feet will sink. Be careful.
(She got stuck.)
What should I do? I am stuck.
(While Ji Hyo was staggering, So Min took the first flag.)
Let's get off work. Let's go home.
(She's rushing to go home.)
Let's hurry up and go home.
Bye.
(Yoo Grand Award is the one in my heart.)
(She gives an annoying ceremony and goes home.)
Bye.
Let's go home.
- Okay. - Okay.
(The last duo retrieves the flags as well!)
I got the flag!
The entertainment industry is suffering these days.
(This time, they open agencies!)
We are looking for our first actor.
(4 new agencies appear!)
- No way. - Just come in here.
(To sign a contract with an A-list free agent,)
Kim Star.
I follow my heart. You don't need this piece of paper.
(they use all sorts of methods.)
We do need that piece of paper.
- Jessi. - These free agents are big.
(A big-time free agent, Jessi)
- What are you doing, Ms. Jeon? - You seem frustrated.
(Soliciting)
- Good job. - Join...
(A big-time free agent, Woo Young)
the E-Ticket Entertainment.
(After signing a contract with the stars,)
Move for me, move for me, move for me, ay, ay, ay
(they work hard to bring up their price.)
It's the best!
- He has low nipples - He has low nipples
(They reveal Jae Suk's weakness for the audience!)
I really want to recruit Se Chan.
(They succeed to bring up the price!)
9.5 to 0.5? It's too high.
(But their contract price...)
- You swindler! - 6 to 4? Isn't that insane?
(continues to skyrocket.)
9.5 to 0.5.
We were good, weren't we?
(Some agencies even go out of business.)
I think you are done. You are out of business.
Your hairstyle gets on my nerve. Can you get a unibrow?
(The proud celebrities continue to make excessive demands.)
- These celebrities are too much. - He cut his hair.
(Kwang Soo cuts his back hair!)
- Why? - It's weird.
This is passion!
(In this cut-throat industry,)
- Where are you going? - No!
(will the CEOs be able to save their agencies?)
I will get ready to sue them.
- Why? - You ridiculed me before everyone.
No!
(Catch the Stars among Free Agents, Stars' Contract War)