(A sunny day with no fine dust)
(The members are gathering
around the SBS building.)
- Hello.
Hello.
SBS is the best.
(Who's the first one to arrive?)
Hello.
(She checks her temperature
and sterilizes her hands.)
Oh, hello.
Hello. Come this way.
Did you eat?
Yes.
You can order some coffee
and snacks at this cafe.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's why we're shooting
the opening here.
Are we doing product placement
for the SBS building in Mok-dong?
No, this isn't product placement.
You can order what you want.
And we have the credit cards
of the members...
- and the main producer.
- Okay.
(The credit cards of the 8 members
and the main producer)
(Please give the members' cards
to our production crew...)
(as soon as you get
to the filming site this week.)
(Haha's manager: Okay)
(Okay, I will.)
(That's how they got
the members' cards beforehand.)
(Why do they have the cards
of the members and the producer?)
You can pick any card you want...
and spend as much money as you want.
Why do we have
the producer's card here?
There's the producer's card.
What happens if I use
the main producer's card?
You'll see.
You can just choose a card you want.
Song Yi. Where's Song Yi?
No one's here. Where are our staff?
Do you want to eat anything?
What do you want?
Do you want something?
Bong Jo, this is a good chance.
- What do you want? Coffee?
- An IA.
- An Iced Americano?
- Yes.
- What do you want to eat?
- Fruit juice.
- Fruit juice?
- Yes.
- What do you want?
- An Iced Americano.
Then 3 iced Americanos
and 2 fruit juices.
What do you want?
A caramel macchiato.
You sound firm.
A caramel macchiato. Okay.
Whose card are you going to use?
(Whose card does she want to use?)
(She picks the main producer's card
with no hesitation.)
This is on me.
You should remember that.
I'm buying this for you.
I'm buying.
I'd like to order. This is amazing.
Six iced Americanos.
Two orange juices.
And a caramel macchiato.
Would you like to drink something?
It's on me.
This doesn't cost a lot.
(She's being generous
with someone else's card.)
(Receipt: 32.20 dollars)
It's not much.
Hello.
- Hello.
What is this?
(She's on alert as always.)
- This is my card.
- Right.
I'll use the producer's card then.
Are you serious?
(Tilting her head)
What's going on?
Does anyone want a hot dog?
(Me.)
Seriously?
(Me too.)
Okay. Hot dogs are on me.
I'll have eight hot dogs.
And one earl grey please.
(She pays 31 dollars.)
Thank you.
Can we really do this?
You can pick any card you want.
And can I pay with it?
Well, today...
(He hesitates for a moment.)
I'll have fun
with Jong Kook's card today.
It's gold.
I'll spend Jong Kook's money.
(He looks like he will go
on a spending spree.)
(He buys expensive cookies
that Jong Kook would never buy.)
I'll have five of these.
- Is this a secret?
- Yes.
Hello.
(Se Chan leaves with his cookies,
and Kwang Soo shows up.)
Here's my thought.
Actually, Jong Kook wouldn't mind...
spending some money on his friends.
I'm serious. That's true.
He loves it.
And he doesn't like it...
when I pay for my own food.
So I'll pick Jong Kook's card.
(He chooses Jong Kook's card.)
I'll have one iced Americano...
and this cookie.
And a mini cream puff.
Will he find out right away?
No, he won't.
Then I'll have one more.
Aren't you spending too much
with Jong Kook's card?
What are you doing?
(Paparazzi Yang shows up.)
(He secured the evidence
of Kwang Soo's spending.)
Done.
You're over. You're doomed.
- Hey.
- You'll... Forget it.
- I'll give you the money.
- You're doomed.
You're done for.
Gosh, he spent a lot.
- This is delicious.
- Right. It's warm.
(So Min and Ji Hyo are enjoying
brunch on the rooftop.)
If I know we'd be doing this,
I would've called my parents.
To use my card?
- I didn't use your card.
- Really?
(She lies.)
(Hesitating)
I'm sorry.
The assistant directors are mean.
I guess they told him right away.
- I got text messages.
- He got text messages.
(I got text messages.)
(Choi Bo Pil, 32.20 dollars,
Choi Bo Pil, 31 dollars)
I didn't think of that.
They offer 15 percent discounts
to employees of SBS.
Did you get a discount?
No, I didn't.
You should've asked for it.
I'll do it later.
- Should I keep it a secret?
- Of course.
You'll see. I'll do you a favor.
They bought a lot of stuff.
It's a meal.
- What is this?
- Whose card did you use?
- That's a secret.
- We already came clean.
You didn't use mine.
I didn't get a text message.
Right. I didn't use yours.
Oh, right. We'd get a text message.
(Flustered)
- Do they send text messages?
- Sure.
You're done for.
(He teases Kwang Soo
pretending to be calm.)
What's this?
Do they sell food that costs
this much here?
I didn't think of text messages.
(He hasn't adapted
to the age of information yet.)
Jong Kook would say this
as soon as he comes up.
"Hey, someone bought food
with my money."
"Okay. I got you."
- "It's you, right?"
- "It's you, isn't it?"
I'm getting off to a bad start.
(I'm getting off to a bad start.)
It's like I stepped in poop
as soon as I got off the car.
(He eats his cookie
with mixed feelings.)
Look at him.
He's...
(Giggling)
He's afraid someone might say,
"Why did you buy
something you won't even eat?"
- So he forces himself to eat it.
- This is a contrived situation.
"Why did you eat it
when you didn't want to eat it?"
So I'm forcing myself to finish it.
- There's one more.
- Not to make it look contrived.
You used Jong Kook's card.
I usually don't let
the younger members pay.
But it feels like...
Jong Kook is older than me.
- I'll pick Jong Kook's card.
- Okay.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
- What did you eat?
- I bought food for our staff.
I used Jong Kook's card.
What?
- Jong Kook's card.
- You did?
- Yes.
- Jong Kook is spending...
a lot of money this morning.
Really?
Did you use his card too?
I thought you'd use Suk Jin's card.
(Jae Suk gets a text message
at that moment.)
My card...
I guess someone used your card.
- Gosh, he is...
- How much is it?
- It's 184 dollars.
- What?
- Really?
- What did he buy?
- My goodness.
- How is it possible?
I'll spend a fortune with this card.
2, 4, 6, 8, and 10.
That's 15. I'll take them all.
Blend all 15 of them.
And...
I'll buy all of these.
(He's an expert at heavy buying.)
Here. Take one each.
You must be hungry. Here.
I bought fruit juice
which is good for your health.
It's the most expensive thing.
Our crew members are working
really hard.
How would he possibly spend
180 dollars at a cafe?
Did he have the coffee delivered
to his house?
(Furious)
How could he...
With my card... My gosh.
(184 dollars spent at a cafe is
an unbelievable amount.)
Actually, this would be...
better for me.
- It's war.
- It's war now.
I knew it.
- "Bring it on."
- Exactly. "Bring it on."
Can you believe that he spent
184 dollars at a cafe?
I...
really like this guy.
But sometimes, he can be annoying.
I've never seen him spend his money.
If he at least tries to pay,
I'll stop him right away,
but he never does.
I hate him
when he's being like that.
I should teach him a lesson.
He's spoiled.
- Hello.
- I'll buy everything you have.
(I'll buy everything you have.)
Can I withdraw cash with this?
(He even tries to withdraw cash
with the card.)
They're working hard.
This is on Kwang Soo.
(He even offers drinks
to the receptionists.)
Thank you.
Try this drink, sir.
(He's forcing Kwang Soo
to do good deeds.)
- I appreciate your hard work.
- Ji Suk Jin.
I should use
the oldest member's card.
I'll have one iced Americano.
There's nothing expensive.
(All the drinks at the cafe
are relatively cheap.)
Hang on.
By the way...
Some people used my card.
What did they buy here
that they paid that much money?
I spent only three dollars
to buy an iced Americano.
They spent a lot.
(He's getting furious
about the money they spent.)
What did they eat?
Hello, Jong Kook.
You seem very upset.
What's there to spend
more than 10 dollars on?
- Really?
- He got it.
- What?
- He got you.
What's there to spend
more than 10 dollars on?
He's angry again.
I saw something.
They bought cookies.
How much are cookies?
- They are like eight dollars.
- What?
I saw them share cookies
with others.
He wouldn't even eat them.
It's just too contrived.
I told you this would happen.
I knew he'd say it's contrived.
I shared them with others.
Why would you buy
something you won't eat?
- Hey, that's enough.
- You like to buy us food.
- I said that's enough.
- I'm okay with that,
but it's just strange.
Did you use Jong Kook's card?
You should be reasonable.
- I already talked about this.
- Hey.
- Just apologize.
- I was...
- I'm sorry.
- Good.
It's over as soon as you apologize.
Why go on about it?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Someone spent 184 dollars.
- Who?
What?
With whose card?
He's not even generous with money.
- How could you spent 180 dollars...
- He spent 184 dollars.
How is it possible?
So all of you paid...
with a member's card or mine.
This is
what you're going to do today.
A member who wins the missions
will be a decision-maker...
and pick a card to pay
during the race.
It will take place
in the SBS building all day.
It's called When You Go
to the TV Station Race.
You will be shooting
various TV shows...
in the building all day long.
And all the expenses
for the TV shows will be paid...
with these credit cards.
- That sounds great.
- And...
depending on whose credit card
you pick,
the number of people
to get the penalty...
and the chances of
getting the penalty will change.
(The number of people and the odds
of the penalty will change.)
If you stay loyal to your friends...
and pick only the main producer's
card throughout the race,
all of you will get a prize,
and only one person
will get a penalty.
That's easy.
- There's no way we can't do this.
- This is so simple.
If we pick the producer's card,
we all get a prize.
We should use Bo Pil's card.
- There's no reason not to use it.
- I know.
There's no reason.
We should definitely use
Bo Pil's card.
I'll tell you why you'd want
to use someone else's card.
The member to get a penalty...
will be decided at the ending.
Do you remember
the game with marbles...
- that you found very interesting?
- Of course we do.
That's how we will decide.
It will be exciting.
- One person will get a penalty.
- Really?
And you all will start
with one marble each.
And the winner of each mission
will pick a credit card to pay.
If you pick the producer's card,
the number of people to get
the penalty remains the same,
but you will get one more marble.
(If they pick the producer's card,
they get one more marble.)
How could you...
That's horrible.
- Gosh.
- We won't pick the card then.
- No one could use it then.
- You're evil.
But if you pay
with another member's credit card,
one of your marbles is deducted,
and one marble is added
to the credit card owner's.
That is, you can reduce your chances
of getting a penalty...
while increasing
someone else's chances.
- That means we have no choice.
- We have no choice. Gosh.
- Darn you. You petty punk!
- This is ridiculous.
- What is this?
- Hey, treat us for a change!
- Hey!
- Hey, this is too...
- Gosh, you. Don't join the game.
- My gosh.
- I can't believe this.
- Why didn't you just tell us...
- not to use your credit card?
- Let's just leave yours out.
- What's the point of having rules?
- I don't like this.
Listen, everyone.
If you think about it rationally,
one more marble won't increase
your chances that much.
- It'll make it from 1-8th to 2-9th.
- Nonsense.
- That's just nonsense.
- You don't want us to use yours.
- You just don't want that.
- That's not convincing at all.
- That's what you mean.
- We should have no marble.
- That we'd better not use yours.
- We can just use ours.
- Let's use ours.
- It's obvious.
What's the prize? If it's good,
it'd be worth trying.
The prize is Korean beef.
- I want it.
- That sounds great.
- I want to get the prize.
- That brand's meat is delicious.
How about we let one of us get
a penalty and aim for the prize?
Let's do that.
Can I use my credit card
instead of another member's?
- I doubt you would do that.
- You wouldn't do that.
- Hey.
- I've decided how to play this.
- I've made up my mind.
- What a joke.
You'll use your credit card?
Then we'll begin the first round.
- Look at this.
- What is this?
These must be presents for us.
- So Min, there are ball lights too.
- Oh, my.
What's all this?
I see a coffee brewing kit too.
- What are those poles for?
- I have no idea.
- There's a tent here too.
- Why...
The first round is...
- "Law of the Jungle."
- What?
(The first round of the race is
"Law of the Jungle.")
This is our base camp.
- Right here?
- Really?
Aren't we in the middle of the city?
- Here?
- We're surrounded by buildings.
- Try to think you're in the jungle.
- This is driving me nuts.
(The rooftop of the TV station
turned into the jungle.)
In fact, where we are now is
the true jungle.
That's true.
- We're in the wild.
- We're in the jungle.
- We face the intense reality...
- You're right.
I agree.
- This is the jungle in this era.
- Yes, it is.
- We all live intensely, you know.
- That's right. We do.
We all do. Look at Suk Jin.
He lives so intensely.
- No, I don't.
- His clothes are even ripped.
Exactly.
- I take it easy.
- As if he'd been cast away.
- He has holes in his clothes.
- He's managing somehow.
How many patches did you put
on your clothes?
This is considered fashionable.
- There are so many patches on it.
- Vintage never goes out of style.
- You know that.
- You just look poor to me.
You don't look stylish.
You just look poor to me.
He's Poor Ji. Right.
- Poor Ji?
- Yes.
- Poor Ji.
- Your English name is Poor Ji now.
- That suits him.
By the way, Long Legs...
Long Legs, what's with that patch
on your jacket?
- What is that?
- You mean this?
- What's that?
- Is that...
- Is it a charity badge?
- Is it?
- Is it a mountain?
- Hold on.
- Did you...
- I think it looks like an idiot.
- An idiot.
Does this look like
an image of an idiot to you?
- It looks like a school uniform.
- It's just a badge.
- Hey, Long Legs.
- Is it your old school uniform?
- Long Legs, did you...
- Why do you call me that suddenly?
- Long Legs, is it a school uniform?
- It's because you have long legs.
This badge came with the jacket.
(They're criticizing
one another's outfits as always.)
Isn't he wearing clothes
from the same brand as mine?
You're right.
- That's from this brand.
- Isn't that a knock-off?
- That's a knock-off.
- What do you mean?
His jacket is from
the same brand as mine.
- You mean Kwang Soo's jacket?
- That's a knock-off.
This isn't a knock-off.
(The same brand labels were found
on their sleeves.)
You're wearing a knock-off.
- What are you saying?
- I can tell that that's authentic.
- Mine looks like an authentic one.
- Indeed.
- I can tell that.
- We're wearing different jackets.
Comedians never wear
knock-off clothes.
- That's true.
- Hey, stop it. That's enough.
- I'm a comedian too.
- My gosh. That's enough.
(Kwang Soo finally admitted
that he's a comedian.)
This is not a knock-off.
- What's that?
- Fine.
- Hey, stop it now.
- What's that?
What's wrong with this badge?
- Just leave him be.
- All right.
- Isn't that a crab?
- Guys, stop it.
- I think it's a crab.
- Stop it.
- I mean...
- Is it a crab?
- Let's love one another.
- Hey, guys.
- I love you all.
- Isn't it a crab? I think it is.
I'll take it off! Gosh.
That's enough.
- That's not a heart.
- Hey,
if you take that off, you lose.
Don't take it off to the end.
- Stop it.
- Right.
- Long Legs, you punk.
- Why is Suk Jin's jacket so short?
- Look at his shoulders.
- You have no fashion sense.
- Poor Ji.
- It's sagging too much.
It looks cool because it's short.
Yours is too long.
- I'll show you...
- I think his outfit looks nice.
- I think it's nice.
- Are you serious?
That's a playful style.
- It's simple and nice.
- He looks cute.
(He suddenly started
acting playful.)
- That style suits him.
- It looks nice.
He looks so cute.
(He's jumping to the side
to tease Poor Ji.)
- He looks cute.
- Rascal, Rascal.
- He dressed up cute today.
- This is...
from an expensive brand.
- As you can see,
- Suk Jin, you should try this too.
he kept the color combination
simple.
- With a bright color.
- The colors look good on him.
I just can't speak to those
who have no fashion sense.
It's a calm color.
Jong Kook likes this style.
- And it's oversized.
- Yes, it is.
- He looks cute in it.
- Indeed.
- Look how cute he is.
- I look even cuter if I do this.
- Exactly.
- He looks like a little boy.
- He looks so cute.
- I look even cuter...
- when I wear it sideways.
- He looks so cute.
- He's best at teasing others.
- Look at him.
Haha, you know, right?
You have a good fashion sense.
Be honest with me.
Would you have this or that?
- I'd choose that one.
- Be honest... Gosh.
Would you have this or that?
(I would have that one.)
You guys are all so pretentious.
- Sorry, I had to choose this.
- Does he look cute or not?
- I had to in this situation.
- You look cute.
- Given the situation...
- That was the only reason, right?
- Right?
- He looks cute.
Oh, it was customized?
Actually, I heard that this style is
in style.
They usually wear a vest like this
without a T-shirt under it.
- But...
- Which one?
I was supposed to wear this best
on my bare skin.
- Forget it.
- I mean...
- Hey!
- On your bare skin?
- That's how they style this vest.
- You made me picture it.
- On your bare skin?
- Are you a member of Solid?
- You're talking nonsense.
- You must've lost your mind.
- What is she talking about?
- On your bare skin?
- You must've lost your mind.
- Are you a member of Solid?
Even men don't wear a vest
on their bare skin.
I wore this T-shirt under the vest
because our show is rated PG.
Are you saying that you'd wear it
on your bare skin otherwise?
- People usually wear it...
- Stop it.
- Keep it together.
- Why are you guys so conservative?
- Don't do that.
- We're not conservative.
Stop saying nonsense.
- You sound like an old man.
- You brat.
Don't do that. Don't do it!
Look at Ji Hyo. She's dressed
like a girl in the 1960s.
- Look at her, you brat.
- She looks so feminine.
She looks so diligent.
- She looks diligent too.
- Why? I...
- Like a perfect daughter-in-law.
- True.
You wear revealing clothes too
on "I Can See Your Voice."
- What? That's different.
- On "I Can See Your Voice."
- That show has a different concept.
- He dresses casually only on here.
He dresses like this when he's asked
to dress like a romantic boyfriend.
- Why? Hey!
- Go and shave your mustache.
What's wrong with this style?
It could be a personal trainer.
Must all boyfriends dress up?
- It's never-ending.
- Personal trainers dress like this.
(The new definition of the style
goes right into his ears.)
- Hey, am I bleeding?
- It's never-ending.
- Hang in there. It'll be over soon.
- I think I'm bleeding.
- Hey!
- Look at his body.
I'm like G-DRAGON
among personal trainers.
- Jong Kook.
I thought you were a singer.
- Are you a personal trainer?
- No.
He mentioned the boyfriend style.
- There could be a boyfriend...
- By the way,
I met Kim Jin Ho of SG Wannabe
not long ago.
I found out that he always dresses
just like you do.
- Has he been working out lately?
- He likes to wear black.
Really?
- KCM dresses like that too.
- Exactly.
- Some men like to wear black.
- Everyone has his own style.
- That's funny.
- We haven't even started it.
- Let's stop chatting now.
- You're right.
- Stop it!
- Let's stop chatting.
(Unlike what they said,
they like to have a chat.)
As I told you,
this is our base camp.
You got a text when someone used
your credit card.
You'll exchange your phones
in the order of payment.
- What does that mean?
- Now,
So Min, give your phone to Ji Hyo.
- My phone...
- Ji Hyo, give yours to Se Chan.
Se Chan's goes to Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo's goes to Jae Suk.
Jae Suk's goes to Suk Jin.
Suk Jin's goes to Haha.
Haha, give yours to Jong Kook.
- Here you go. This is my phone.
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook, here you go.
- I don't have it now.
- I'll give it to you later.
- Oh, I should give it to So Min?
Yes, that's right.
- And then?
- Here you go.
- Me?
- Yes.
(Kwang Soo to Jae Suk)
I couldn't even imagine that.
He was holding his phone like this.
I wondered what he was doing.
By the way, this is...
Wait. Someone gave this to me
instead of his phone. What is this?
Oh, that?
- It's a flip phone.
- Yes. That's my phone. Take it.
(The unprecedented flip phone
made of plastic)
- That flip phone is so cool.
- You answer it like this?
- It's from S brand, right?
- Yes, it's the latest model.
He must look down on me
seeing that he gave this to me.
That phone has such a big screen.
(Here you go!)
The first mission is to decorate
the base camp...
using the given item regardless of
the location and size of the area.
All of these? Really?
The staff members who went
to shoot "Law of the Jungle..."
will choose the person who made
the biggest contribution.
(The chosen member will have
the right to decide how to pay.)
You have two sets
of every camping item.
So you'll be divided into
2 teams of 4 members.
Jae Suk, since the largest amount
was spent on your credit card,
you can choose three members
you want to team up with.
(Jae Suk will select
his team members.)
- So it's a competition.
- Oh, I see.
And the person who did the most work
will decide how to pay.
Setting up a tent is very difficult.
I was a Boy Scout.
For the honor of all Boy Scouts...
- I need Jong Kook to set up a tent.
- Right.
- I'll choose Jong Kook.
- I was a Boy Scout.
- The Three Good Deeds Promise.
- He was a Boy Scout.
(Another former Boy Scout appeared.)
Doing three good things every day.
- I promise!
- Join my team.
- Yes!
You see... I was a Boy Scout too.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Did you go on backyard camping?
- Of course.
You did?
You should tie up toilet paper
with the string not to trip over...
- at night.
- That's right.
I was a member of Aramdan.
- Aramdan? Join my team.
- Aramdan?
- She's on our team.
- We need someone like you.
- Her outfit looks like the uniform.
- It looks like Aramdan uniform.
- I just need the beret.
- Indeed.
I was a member of Aramdan too.
We're on the same team then.
Come here.
- I... I have...
- I have no such experience.
- I've done some volunteer work.
- You're good at this, right?
- Setting up a tent.
- I joined Aramdan.
- Of course.
- All right.
I'm a little worried.
You have to set up 1 tent, 4 chairs,
shelves, 1 table, 1 parasol,
and 1 hammock. That's all.
- Okay.
- Let's move.
Really? It won't be so easy.
What should we do first?
We should start with a tent, right?
- Oh, my.
- Kwang Soo!
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Let's move this first.
We need tools like a hammer.
- To stick stakes in the ground...
- Oh, I see.
And we need to
put these poles together.
We rarely go camping.
- We're not that type.
- It looks like a hassle to me.
I don't know why I joined Boy Scout.
Why did I join Boy Scout
when I didn't even like camping?
Se Chan appeared
on "Law of the Jungle."
(Three years ago, Ssaebssaeb joined
Byung Man's Tribe.)
Where should this go?
Just put them all together for now.
I'll tell you the basic skills
for setting up a tent.
- I should build up the frame first.
- Correct.
And then...
I think we need some more space.
Kwang Soo, move those boxes.
Move faster!
I'm trying.
Bring me one of those small ones
to stick it in the ground.
(Bring that small one over there.)
Place it here. Right here.
- That's good. That side too.
- Be careful not to get hurt.
Run over there
and place another one.
You should grab the corner,
you punk!
- Wait a minute.
- Okay.
- Boy Scouts aren't like him.
- What kind of Boy Scout were you?
- This isn't what Boy Scouts do.
- What kind of Boy Scout...
I was a Boy Scout leader
at my school.
I had so many badges...
that I had no space
for another one on my vest.
Are you sure you didn't take
those badges from other kids?
- Are you?
- My badges...
Hey, my team members are working
quietly and well.
Come over here. Like this.
That's good.
- Should I start at the bottom?
- Put it in here like this.
(The tent duo quietly started
setting up a tent.)
- Got it?
- Yes.
(Okay.)
I'm done.
- Are you?
- Good job!
Okay. Nice.
How does this work?
Put that... That goes to the front.
- It goes this way, right?
- Yes, finish the bottom part first.
Oh, gosh, seriously. Darn!
(Oh, gosh, seriously. Darn!)
Gosh!
(He's groaning
while grabbing the one-touch chair.)
Gosh. I can't put them together!
(He's struggling
while holding the legs.)
Gosh. Why can't I do this?
We have a manual for that chair,
Suk Jin.
Oh, man.
(He's wasting his energy
without reading the instructions.)
Gosh.
There's a manual for that?
- Oh, gosh.
- Gosh!
(He threw a tantrum in the end.)
- Read the manual.
Gosh. What's wrong?
(He got so frustrated
that he blurted out a swear word.)
Suk Jin, you should probably put it
through that.
(He's living another intense day.)
Suk Jin, let's do it together.
Should I put it here first?
I think I should.
- It should be reversed, Suk Jin.
- Really?
- This side should go up.
- I see.
- You're right.
- Yes.
- Oh, right.
So Min, move a little to this side.
- This is it. Okay.
- Wait there.
- We're almost done.
- Yes, this is it. Good.
"Law of the Jungle" with the cast
of Running Man.
This is a house for me and Se Chan.
It's our house of love.
- I refuse.
- Hey.
I would definitely sleep outside.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- One chair is done.
- Done.
Okay.
Suk Jin,
why don't we set this one up?
Let's do it together.
- Do the same on that side.
- This is so nice. It's comfortable.
It's done!
- Let's move it to this side.
- Good job!
Let's adjust the shape.
And now let's make a door.
- Awesome.
- Let's make a door.
- Hello. I'm Yoon Do Hyun.
- Yoon Do Hyun?
Gosh, they've probably only stayed
in hotels.
Hey. What can you guys do?
Look at this.
We already finished setting up
the tent and a chair.
Suk Jin,
it wasn't you who set them up.
My gosh. I set up the chair.
Okay. It's done.
- A chair?
- Yes.
Let's set up the chairs now.
(Hammering hard)
Hey, you're hammering so hard...
Is there a storm coming
or something?
No, I thought it could help to get
some extra points...
- from the staff members.
- Great. Go ahead.
Go ahead and try.
Hammer it hard, you punk.
This one too.
Good.
- Hold on.
- Give it to me.
- I mean, he's acting weird...
- Watch me.
Hit it right in the middle,
you punk.
(Meanwhile, Team Suk Jin finished
setting up a hammock.)
- Look at that hammock.
- Oh, yes!
The hammock looks great.
- There you go.
- Nice!
(The hammock looks great.)
- Hey, get out for a second.
- Why?
Once we finish setting something up,
Suk Jin comes to try it.
- Just move.
- Why?
I want to lie in it.
I was lying in it.
(Wobbling)
Awesome. I always wanted this.
(Laughing)
(The greedy man bursts out laughing
on the hammock.)
They got so excited
when it's not so hard to set it up.
- Exactly. They're showing off.
- I can't believe them.
- My gosh.
- They're showing off.
They know nothing about camping.
(The frame fell on his foot.)
- Jae Suk.
- Are you okay?
- It's okay. Pretend you're okay!
- I'm fine.
You'll lose points.
Don't act like it hurts.
- He didn't get hurt.
- Right.
What did they learn as Boy Scouts?
- Don't act like it hurts.
- What are they doing?
- I think this is right.
- We should put this one vertically.
- That's right.
- Vertically?
- Put the legs down.
- Aren't these legs?
- Yes, they are, but they're...
- I'll show you.
Aren't they legs?
(Kwang Soo is getting in
to see where the legs should be.)
I get it. We should hang it here.
- Try it.
- We should hang it here.
Try it. Leave the frame as it is.
- Kwang Soo, get out.
- Get out, you punk.
- Hey, get out now.
- I said, get out!
- Get out.
- Bend it backward.
- Put the legs down. Kwang Soo, go.
- Okay.
- This is it.
- Put the legs down.
- Put them down.
- That's good.
- Like this?
- No, it goes this way.
- It's almost done.
- You're right.
- We can just put these together...
- Don't do anything!
Put the legs down.
I don't think we're doing it right.
We should bend them like this.
I shouldn't have joined Boy Scout!
- How?
- Kwang Soo, hold this.
- And spread it.
- Oh, this is it.
Spread it widely, Kwang Soo!
- Okay?
- Good. Put it down.
- Move aside.
- Move, you punk.
No, not there.
- Move.
- It's done.
Gosh, I love camping.
Hey, come and lie in it
so we can see if it's safe.
- Oh, right.
- Come and lie in it.
- Let's see if it's safe.
- Wait.
Good. Is it okay?
- My, it's nice.
- Okay. Get out now.
- It's so nice.
- Get out now!
- My gosh.
- Okay. Get out now.
(If it's okay, get out!)
- Great.
- Get out.
- Get out!
- Do you call this camping?
- Go away, you punk. It's done.
- Kwang Soo.
Hey, we have to decorate it too,
don't we?
Let's do that now.
(Jong Kook aims to gain extra points
by setting up the parasol.)
It's weird.
There's no shade over the hammock.
- Jong Kook.
- The sun is above our heads.
- The sun moves, you know.
- It's right above us.
Let's set up the parasol too,
Suk Jin.
Don't copy us!
Don't be ridiculous.
We have the same items...
(Would you look at this guy?)
We're not copying you.
We have to set it up eventually too.
What was that, you punk?
What did you say?
I was talking to him.
What?
Okay.
You hit me just because you won
the Grand Award.
What?
(Picking up a pole)
Don't cross this line. The pole.
- Let me ask your team a question.
- Don't cross the pole.
- Don't cross it.
- Do you have Grand Award winners?
Hey. That's... Hey.
(Hey. That's...)
Hey, I'm eligible to get
the COVID vaccine.
- I'm a research test subject.
- What?
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, Suk Jin.
- Thank you.
- He's the first...
- to get it among us.
- Tell us how it felt.
(Jong Kook turned around
after applauding him.)
(Kwang Soo takes out a tissue.)
We might trip and fall at night,
so I'll tie tissue around the pole.
(I'll tie tissue around the pole.)
(He's trying to impress the judges.)
- What are you doing?
- Pardon?
- They're watching us.
You did well. Go ahead.
(He ties a tissue just for show.)
- We won't trip over the pole now.
- Okay.
What are you looking at?
(He puts a pinwheel
on top of the tent this time.)
I'll put a pinwheel here
so we can tell how fast the wind is.
The judges aren't there.
Aren't they the judges?
(Aren't they the judges?)
Who are those ladies?
(He gave his lengthy, silly speech
to the wrong people.)
Done!
- It looks quite nice.
- It looks great.
Good. Kwang Soo, you're doing great.
Thank you.
- What is this?
- Tie it up there.
Oh, no. Goodness. I'm sorry.
(Oh, no! Goodness! I'm sorry!)
(The hammock fell down.)
I tripped over it accidentally.
It's true.
(He tries to sabotage the other team
right in front of them.)
Oh, no. I'm really sorry.
- My gosh.
- I apologize.
- How could you...
- I'm so sorry.
- You did it intentionally.
- I'm sorry.
- Be careful, Jae Suk.
- Sorry.
- What was that?
Are you starting a fight?
Come on, are you from
the Green Mothers' Association?
(They set up the base camp
amidst a war of nerves.)
We'll give you ten more minutes.
All done!
We should hang the ball lights.
I forgot about the shoot
for a moment.
- I forgot about it too.
- I'm having so much fun.
- Me too.
- I like things like this.
So do I.
My, it's pretty.
I'm becoming more attached to this
since we've set it up now.
Kwang Soo,
this pinwheel is spinning so fast.
- Indeed. Jae Suk.
- Great job.
I should adjust the length.
- It's amazing that we did this.
- Right?
- Okay.
- This is hard to believe.
I have never set up a tent
or anything like this before.
This is my first time ever.
But did Suk Jin do anything
to set those up?
Suk Jin?
All he did was try what we set up.
He just watched us working.
- It's so nice.
- Why is Suk Jin so excited?
This is why I hate camping
with dads.
It's so nice.
If I have a place to lie down,
food to eat,
and time to rest,
isn't that what happiness is?
What else could it be?
Cut that nonsense. You told me...
that only money can
bring you happiness...
and that you are looked down on
when you're poor.
That's a total lie.
He's such a good liar.
Happiness isn't far away.
This is what happiness is about.
Shall we drink something?
It's nice.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- We have non-alcoholic beer.
- Where?
(- We have non-alcoholic beer.
- Where?)
(She sounds so cheerful.)
- Hey.
- She never sounds that cheerful.
It's my first time too.
- Whom is she talking to?
- Ji Hyo, here's non-alcoholic beer.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- Beer is essential for camping.
- I was so surprised.
Absolutely. It's essential.
- Do you like it?
- It's so good.
Ji Hyo just sounded so cheerful.
- "Where?"
Hey.
Are you guys still working?
This makes me feel so happy.
So Min, are you still working?
- I'm enjoying this.
- She's knitting something.
- All four of you should be working.
- Exactly.
- Oh, great. It's so relaxing.
- That's what I'm trying to say.
- She likes doing things like this.
- That's true.
I like things like this.
Look how they're lying around
just because their work is done.
We told her not to do it,
but she insisted.
- This helps me relax.
- Stop. You're making us look bad.
This helps me relax...
- Stop liking things like this.
- The other members...
- Stop it. Give me that.
- Come on. I'm really enjoying it.
- How many times did I tell you?
- What's wrong with you?
I want to do it. Don't take it away.
Don't do it even if you want to.
We're in an awkward position.
It looks as if we made you do
all the work.
This is fun.
Then say it out loud
so they can hear you.
I'm enjoying this!
Good.
(She was forced to say it.)
- So Min, you're having fun, right?
- Yes, this is so fun.
Keep saying that out loud.
Or else, you'll make us look bad.
Keep saying
how much you're enjoying doing that.
- I'm happy that you're enjoying it.
- My, this is so much fun.
- How nice.
- This is really nice.
I see why people like camping
so much.
This is so nice.
By the way, you two...
look a little weird together
with that thing behind you.
What's that?
- Aren't those for babies?
- Hey, you guys...
(Aren't those for babies?)
You two look like...
Where did our child go?
You should've watched our child.
- Where did our child go?
- Oh, let's clock out for a while.
(She announces she's clocking out
from childcare for today.)
(It suits her perfectly.)
This is the beauty of camping.
- Isn't the why people go camping?
- This is great.
(While everyone enjoys
a laid-back camping trip)
(Abruptly)
Why don't we neighbors
raise our glasses?
Here. How about some beer?
- Well...
- You must know how to have fun.
Aren't you having any beer?
Come on.
- Here.
- Hold on a second.
- Did you speak informally to her?
- Sorry about that.
Are you out of your mind?
- She's a stranger to you.
- Well,
- she looks like someone I know.
- Unbelievable.
Okay, then. Cheers.
- Mister.
- Yes?
We'd like our peace,
so please get lost.
Just join me for a drink.
- Hold on.
- We're not here for that.
I'm here with my subordinates.
That's now what we're here for.
We're to clear our heads
from a bad event.
So what brings you by here?
How do you four know each other?
(Gulping down)
- He...
- Unbelievable.
- Is he drunk?
- Are you drunk?
No, I'm not.
- This is to die for.
- He's in a drunken frenzy.
This is good.
I feel bad for him.
- Suk Jin.
- No one wants him there.
- Just get back here, will you?
- It's sad to see you this way.
They can't possibly
harm me physically.
- Here.
- What's up with him?
- This is great.
- Your time is up.
This is nice.
(They've completed
their base camps.)
They're constantly
writing things down.
We're being evaluated.
If only I had a guitar here.
When, when, when
- When the stormy sea
- Calms down
Will you come to me
Here we go.
- From across the sea
- Only you
- I'll await
My love, I will always
Await you
(While the laid-back trio sing,
the others change clothes.)
This is why people go camping.
It feels real thanks to
the non-alcoholic beer.
- Right?
- Yes.
Would you like a beverage?
We have our own, darn it.
Why are you acting like
we're the enemy?
Can't you say it more peacefully?
Why be prickly
when we're only being generous?
Shut it!
There's no need for this.
Look at him cozying up to Jong Kook.
I wouldn't mind smacking him.
That lanky...
- Hey!
- Seriously?
(He falls on his back.)
- Hey!
- Seriously?
Stop that, will you?
(He ends up washing his face
with alcohol.)
You're being like Suk Jin.
(All they can do is laugh
at Kwang Soo's mishap.)
- That was too much, wasn't it?
- Sorry about that.
Look at how embarrassed he is.
He's embarrassed.
Can I do anything to help?
Camping isn't complete without beer.
Guys,
there is a staff member
who's been watching you from afar...
that always rolls with
"Law of the Jungle" team.
For every episode? Really?
Out of the eight of you,
he'll announce the member
that contributed the most.
That member will choose the card
to pay for this all with.
- Se Chan worked hard.
- I bet it's someone from our team.
(Who will get to choose
the credit card first?)
The member
who contributed the most is...
It's Se Chan.
- It has to be Se Chan.
- Se Chan worked hard.
(Will it be Se Chan
who led his team...)
(using what he learned
on "Law of the Jungle?")
Today, we collaborate
with Running Man.
(Will it be Kwang Soo
who only did chores...)
(that made it seem
like he was contributing?)
(Or will it be Jong Kook,)
(the former Boy Scout member
who hotly ordered everyone around?)
I forgot that we were
filming Running Man for a second.
(Will it be So Min
who decorated the tent...)
(as if it were actually hers?)
(Who did the jungle expert choose?)
It's Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan)
(The experienced jungle explorer
was chosen.)
- Him?
- How did he contribute?
But...
Se Chan,
please head to the cashier...
and pick a credit card...
to pay for the camping equipment
used in this round.
Just so you know, the total cost...
is 300 dollars.
- That's quite a lot.
- It's a lot.
(The equipment
would've cost 300 dollars.)
That's a lot.
(The equipment
would've cost 300 dollars.)
It's a lot.
I'll get going then.
Hi there.
(Se Chan heads to the cashier.)
I'm still on the fence.
You start with only one
being up for punishment...
and a marble each for every member.
If I use someone else's card,
my marble will be taken away.
If you pay
with someone else's credit card,
your marble will be added
to that person,
and one more person
will receive the punishment.
(1 more person
will receive the punishment.)
But if...
I choose to pay with
the head director's credit card...
If you pay with
the head director's card,
the number of people receiving
the punishment will stay the same,
but a marble
will be added to your name.
I can't have that.
(Paying with the director's card
will give him an additional marble.)
(Se Chan chooses someone's card.)
I'd like to pay now.
They're written down as LOL.
LOL.
(300 dollars has been paid
via credit card.)
You weren't kidding.
(Whose credit card
did Se Chan choose?)
- Can I go now?
- Sure.
That person now has
an additional marble.
Got it.
They weren't kidding.
(Someone now has
an additional marble.)
I'm back, guys.
The credit card was used
to actually pay for everything.
- For real.
- Is there a payment terminal?
Yes, there's one.
I even saw the receipt come out.
Wait, I felt a gentle vibration.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
(I'm good, right?)
- Is it for real?
- Yes.
(Haha checks the phone he has.)
Yes, that one.
It's for real.
- What do you mean?
- 300 dollars.
Really?
Wait, is this 30 dollars?
How many zeroes are there?
- 300 dollars.
- What is it?
Suk Jin, I had a blast.
- Thanks for everything.
- Exactly.
(What?)
You sure know how to set an example.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Suk Jin.
Thanks to you, we got to go camping.
Thanks.
Suk Jin, thank you.
- It's for real.
- What did I tell you?
Hey. Seriously, Yangsebari?
Thank you so much.
- I had a blast.
- Thanks.
This much I can understand, but...
What...
do you think you're doing?
(Se Chan is down a marble
while Suk Jin has 1 more.)
I'm glad that you had fun.
- This is great.
- Could this be any better?
- This is why...
- Maybe I should go camping.
This is why people wish to live
in a house with a yard.
With a dog, right?
Yes, with a dog to keep you company.
(His eyes are fixed.)
Later on...
(Jae Suk's ready to attack.)
(Suk Jin avoids eye contact.)
Suk Jin gets nervous
when you look at him,
- so don't.
- It's okay.
Look all you want.
Stare at me.
- He's nervous.
- Later on in life,
after I retire,
I'll go and live on an island.
Sure.
(Jae Suk ends the conversation
with a half-hearted answer.)
Give him a warmer response.
- But he...
- He might cry, you know.
What's there to be upset about?
All right.
Now it's time for the second show.
- We're busy today.
- You'll be playing for lunch...
in the "Alley Restaurants" round.
- "Alley Restaurants!"
- This is the real deal.
- Right.
- I'm hungry.
There are a total of two dishes,
and you'll play a game
to see which two will pay for them.
- Right.
- Not one.
Each winner will get to choose
a credit card to pay with.
We looked up some games
to play while out camping...
and found a variation
of the strawberry game.
- Unbelievable.
- A variation of it?
- Jae Suk, thanks in advance.
- Thanks, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, we'll enjoy the food.
Jae Suk, three.
(The one with strawberry-phobia)
(When his condition worsens,
he breaks out odd tunes.)
(- Is he really this bad at it?
- His only flaw.)
(- He could do it better off-screen.
- He's only good at hosting shows.)
(His run at the strawberry game
only stirred up controversies.)
(Today, you'll get to see
his true gaming ability.)
The strawberry game?
Just like the original version,
you can attack others
by saying the name...
and a number.
To defend the attack,
you must say
the right amount of strawberries...
starting with the first beat.
Unlike the original version,
you must say
the number of strawberries...
and fill in the rest of the beat
with claps.
(One must say the right number
of strawberries first.)
And then attack.
- It's too difficult.
- So we can say up to eight.
It's easier.
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
(The two winners of the game
will choose the credit cards.)
We'll choose two winners
with this game.
Jae Suk, three.
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
(He's beginning
to feel the pressure.)
Let's not do more than four.
- It's too difficult.
- Keep it at 3 or 4.
We'll start with Se Chan
who won the last game.
Points will be deducted
if you get it wrong.
Ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
Jae Suk, two.
Strawberry-strawberry
- Isn't that right?
- You were late.
- It starts immediately.
- Was I late?
Let's give him one free pass.
Jae Suk, that's how it's done.
- Strawberry-strawberry
- The beat goes like so.
- That was an easy one.
Consider it a practice round.
- This is for real now.
- Here we go for real.
I'll say "Jae Suk, two."
- All right.
- And go.
- I like strawberries
- It's sad that he agreed to it.
Jae Suk, three.
Strawberry
(Se Chan's trick...)
(has Jae Suk crumbling.)
2 and 3 are practically the same.
- It's the same.
- It's still the same beat.
- Strawberry
- You start at the first beat.
Strawberry!
Jae Suk, thanks for lunch.
Strawberry-strawberry
- Strawberry
- Strawberry-strawberry
Just start saying strawberry
on the first beat.
- I like strawberries
- Suk Jin, four.
- Strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Jae Suk, two.
What?
- How many was that?
- Three.
That was adorable.
- She said two.
- Two strawberries.
Just say strawberry twice.
Don't tell me you're upset now.
- Unbelievable.
- There's...
no confidence in his voice now.
This game and I don't go together.
- Doesn't it?
- This game isn't for me.
- What about other games?
- Got it.
I'm good at other games.
After this one,
let's play a game that you want.
What about apples?
- What about apples?
- Yes, that one.
Anyway, ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
- Jong Kook, four.
- Strawberry-strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, three.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
- Ji Hyo, two.
- Strawberry-strawberry
Incorrect.
Just start off at the first beat.
- We managed a rally.
- Jae Suk, nice.
Jae Suk's gotten
the hang of it now.
- Ji Hyo, do better.
- He's gotten the hang of it.
Gosh, strawberry!
- Do it well, Ji Hyo.
- His lips were all purple,
but they're back to pink now.
- Do it well.
- He's been revived.
Let's start with So Min.
- I'm going to attack you, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- I'll call 4.
- 4?
Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry
I'm calling four. Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
- Suk Jin, five.
- Strawberry
Suk Jin, five.
(Startled)
(He suddenly sang a taryeong
by So Min's surprise attack.)
- Don't let your guard down.
- Suk Jin.
- Well done.
- You...
Strawberry
Don't let your guard down.
- Let's start with Suk Jin.
- Okay, then.
- I keep calling his name.
- I'll call So Min six.
- Six? Okay.
- Let's go.
Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
Kwang Soo, six.
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
- He's good.
- Haha, eight.
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry
Jae Suk, one.
(He missed the first beat again.)
Wow.
(He was just gaping at them,)
(and he missed his turn again.)
- Strawberry
- I pity him now.
- Just yell "strawberry" first!
- But I wasn't going to...
- call him this time,
- Don't call him for a while.
- but I'm used to saying his name.
- Don't call him.
Let's leave him out and do a rally.
- He's already done for.
- I'm used to calling him too.
Let's start. Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
- Suk Jin, three.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, two.
(His name was called again
only 5 seconds after the ban.)
- I just...
- You said we should leave him out!
- He is...
- Don't do this to him!
- I mean...
- We're used to calling him!
I wasn't going to call him,
but it just came out.
- He's upset.
- Jae Suk is upset.
- Let's not call him.
- Don't call him.
- It can't be helped.
He didn't say it at first,
but he went,
strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
(He said it vaguely,
pretending to be a little late.)
- Strawberry-strawberry
- He wanted to do well.
- I can't do it.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
- Let's play again.
- Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
- Kwang Soo, two.
- Strawberry-strawberry
Se Chan, four.
Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry
- Haha, four.
- Strawberry-strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry
- Ji Hyo, seven.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
(She missed the beat.)
- You punk.
- Jae Suk is going to treat us.
- You're so mean.
- Why?
It just can't be helped.
- Okay, you're dead.
- Do whatever you want.
I'm going to attack you now.
She's going to attack
Jae Suk instead.
- I think she'll attack Jae Suk.
- She'll attack Jae Suk.
- Ji Hyo, calm down.
- I read her face.
- Everyone attacks Jae Suk only.
- I've never seen him so down.
I like strawberries
- He really didn't want to play it.
- It's not easy.
- You want to go home, right?
- I hate this game.
- He focuses too hard.
- I really hate it.
- 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
- Jong Kook, two.
- Strawberry-strawberry
- Why is he so good?
- Ji Hyo, two.
Strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, two.
- Strawberry-strawberry
Ji Hyo, four.
(He defended well,)
(but he failed to attack back.)
- Hey.
- Hey!
(They can't continue playing
this game.)
What's wrong with you?
Just give up already!
- I can't play this game.
- He gets really nervous.
I'm just bad at it.
He gets really nervous.
- Is there a game you want to play?
- Sorry?
- The game you want to play.
- Let's play it.
What's the game you want to play?
- How about Silent 007?
- Something you're good at.
- Shall we?
- Or we can play Silent 3, 6, 9.
Let's play Silent 006...
No, Silent 007.
- "Silent 006."
- Silent 006?
Will you please relax?
- Let's play that game.
- Why are you so tense?
- Can you give him some medicine?
- But...
- Let's play Silent 007.
- But if you show your teeth...
- and laugh, you lose.
- Okay, you'll be out.
- Let's make a circle.
- I'm good at this game.
It's better
than the strawberry game.
- We're playing Silent 007.
- You need to point clearly.
- Let's start with this.
- You lose if your teeth are shown.
- This is how we start.
- You can't laugh.
- You'll be out if you do.
Ready, go.
(0, 7, bang)
(0, 0, 7, bang)
(So Min keeps picking herself.)
(Bang)
(He did "Argh"
when he's not next to Jae Suk.)
Let's not play this.
Let's do strawberry again.
- I'm not good at it.
- We got him.
Stop picking yourself only.
- You're quite good.
- You're good.
You're so annoying though.
- She's good.
- Jae Suk...
He's become brighter.
Jae Suk...
- He's finally smiling.
Jae Suk is finally clapping.
- I got this.
- He likes it.
- I got this. This is perfect.
- Point at others clearly.
- All right.
(0, 0, 7, bang)
He just smiled.
He showed his teeth.
(Chuckling)
(Fail)
He showed his teeth.
You're the one who suggested
the rule.
Did you see him?
- It was so weird.
- Why did you do that?
Is he a fool or what?
- He was having fun.
- He was so happy.
- Hey.
- What was that?
- And he laughed like a fool.
- It was so fun, that's why.
- Why did you do that?
- I forgot that I shouldn't smile.
- That was so funny.
I'm okay as long as it's not
that strawberry game.
I forgot.
I'm okay as long as it's not
that strawberry game.
- It was so funny.
- This is...
- You look so relaxed.
- I wasn't supposed to laugh.
- Of course. I'm finally relaxed.
- Why did I do that?
- But he's...
- Now I'm having fun.
Because the game is so old,
- there's not much movement.
- It's not fun.
- I like strawberries
- Right.
- Look at Jae Suk.
Fine, let's play it.
Let's play it.
All right. Ready, go.
- It's so hard.
- Shall we play the strawberry game?
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
Jong Kook, four.
Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, three.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
- Is it correct?
- It is.
Jae Suk!
(He did it correctly,)
(but he asked if he did it right.)
- You did well!
- Don't give up!
- Why did he become so timid?
- You did well!
- You did really well!
- It was correct.
- Why did he become so small?
- I don't like this game.
He thought he did it wrong.
He just couldn't believe
that he did well.
- Why can't you play this game?
- He was embarrassed.
- This isn't my game.
After two beats,
call someone's name.
Got it.
Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
- Wait, wait.
- You're not ready?
- Ready...
- Ready, go.
- Go.
- I like strawberries
- There he goes again!
- Sing it loudly!
- He's doing that again!
- Don't move like this.
- It needs to be exciting.
- I need to focus.
- Ready, go.
- He needed some time to think.
- I like strawberries
- Kwang Soo, seven!
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, six.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Kwang Soo, eight.
- Don't get mad at him.
- "Kwang Soo..."
- It's, "Kwang Soo, eight."
- This is driving me crazy.
- I was going to let it slide.
- "Kwang Soo, eight."
- Why can't he play it?
- Then you should've continued!
- Hey!
- He is...
- Why didn't you continue?
- It's not that.
I was watching him,
and after he said six correctly,
he wasn't sure
if he did it correctly or not.
And after he said it wrong,
he looked at me sharply.
- "Kwang Soo, eight."
- Hey.
You should've continued.
Why didn't you?
I calculated your scores again
including the result of this game.
Okay!
Currently...
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook
must be in first place.
They must be in 1st and 2nd place.
The Winners who'll pick
the members to treat lunch...
are Jong Kook and So Min.
- Wow.
- I'm in second place.
Jong Kook and So Min will pick
two people to pay for lunch.
- Congratulations!
- All right!
- I knew you'd win!
- Jong Kook, I knew you'd win!
- Jong Kook, my brother.
- You're good.
- They were bound to win.
- Let me take a photo with them.
- Pink suits you.
- Let me take a photo.
- Pink suits you well.
- I knew they'd win.
- I want to take a photo with you.
- Shall I pick you?
- No, no.
- I didn't mean that.
- I'll pick him.
You should take a photo of this.
- We got it. They took it already.
- No, no.
- I pick you.
- Wait a minute.
Jong Kook and So Min,
who are
in 1st and 2nd place respectively,
can pick the menu and members
you want to have lunch with.
- I can pick the members too?
- Today's lunch...
is fried chicken,
which everyone loves.
The second option is skewers
and cup noodles that suit camping.
- I want to have skewers.
- Skewers sound nice.
Then I'll pick fried chicken.
- Please pick the members too.
- The members I want?
I'll pick the team members
I played games with.
- Okay!
- Nice.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- All right, I like skewers.
- You'll have skewers,
and they'll have cup noodles.
- Cup noodles...
- We'll prepare the skewers for you.
- Okay.
- All right.
Wait, what's this?
It smells delicious.
- Wow! Isn't this that brand?
- By the way...
- Hey, hey!
- It's the brand...
- Stay still!
- Lee Yeong Ja is advertising.
- Stay still.
- Don't say it!
- You'll be edited out anyway.
- The condition of this PPL...
- is to exclude you.
- Jae Suk.
- You should stay out of it.
- I love fried chicken.
- This is...
- People in my neighborhood...
- only talk about this brand.
- Hey, hey!
- Hey. Don't say anything!
- What?
Jae Suk, there's sauce too.
We have a spicy sauce.
I prefer boneless fried chicken.
Me too.
This is the one.
It's spicy, sweet, and salty
all at once.
You're right.
- At first, it was kind of sweet.
- Right.
- Right, it's sweet.
- Right?
Then I tasted saltiness,
and spiciness remains in the mouth.
What's this?
It's good, right?
It's spicy, sweet, and salty.
It got all three flavors!
(Laughing awkwardly)
(PPL is the best.)
That's enough, you punk.
(While the PPL monster goes all out
with advertising phrases...)
They'd be jealous of us.
- I know, right?
- It looks crazy good.
Can you start grilling
chicken skewers?
It really feels like we're camping.
How much did you spend, Suk Jin?
- I...
- You spent 300 dollars, right?
- He didn't spend much.
- I did spend 300 dollars.
Yes, yes. I can treat you...
"Yes, yes?"
- "Yes, yes."
- I can spend...
- much more than that for you guys.
- Yes, yes!
- Yes, yes. Yes, yes.
- But...
(Making fun of him)
- Please continue. Yes, yes.
- Hey.
- Stop teasing him!
- Yes, yes.
Suk Jin is annoyed
because of you guys.
- Yes, yes.
- Shall we grill some sausages too?
- Yes.
(The skewers are getting grilled
perfectly by Se Chan.)
Wow, Se Chan. You're so cool!
You're good at grilling meat.
- I like this kind of stuff.
- Did you...
run a skewer stall or something?
I know.
- He's so good.
- He knows how to grill them.
(Fancy two-hand handling)
He's got the skills.
- Please sit down. They're ready.
- This place...
Haha is sitting so quietly. Look.
- I know.
- Right? It's so cute.
- He's so cute.
- You're cute!
They're all done now.
- Are they cooked?
- Yes.
Let's eat!
Thank you for the food.
Sure thing.
- Look at the color. It's cooked.
- It's cooked.
Wow, Suk Jin!
- Is it that good?
- It's really good.
- Have the skewers.
- It's good.
It's so good.
So Min,
it's time to pick a credit card.
- Right now?
- Go ahead, So Min.
- You know whom to pick, right?
- So Min.
Don't pick anyone from here.
(With a solemn face,
she promises not to pick them.)
(I believe in you, So Min.)
So Min.
Yes, hello.
It's the second payment.
We calculated again.
Suk Jin has two marbles?
Yes.
I will pick...
(Suk Jin already spent a lot
on the camping gear.)
(Whose card will So Min pick?)
(It's Suk Jin's card again!)
Suk Jin's card.
The skewers are 80 dollars.
- 80 dollars?
- Yes.
- We'll take out your marble.
- Thank you.
And add one to Suk Jin.
- Oh, he gets more marbles?
- Yes.
I'm going to go pay now.
(Jong Kook has arrived
at the station to make payment.)
(Stealing a glance)
If I get rid of my marbles
and if Kwang Soo gets two...
- They wouldn't know, right?
- No.
That could work.
I shouldn't make Suk Jin pay
for everything.
I'll pick Kwang Soo's card
this time.
All right.
I'll use Kwang Soo's card.
I'll use it to pay for the chicken,
take your marble out,
and add a marble to Kwang Soo.
Now we have one more person
to get the penalty.
Got it.
(Current number of marbles
and people to receive the penalty)
(3 people are to receive the penalty
as of now.)
(Timetable)
(Period 3, "Master in the House")
(Unlike other days,
there's a big TV in the front.)
- What's that?
- What are...
- these cushions for?
- We must be playing quizzes again.
What's this? "Live chat?"
- What's this?
- A chat?
What's this?
- What's going on?
- Live streaming is starting soon.
- What's this?
- No. We're live streaming.
- We are live streaming.
There are so many people
tuning in already.
- 18,000 people are watching?
- We're going live on YouTube?
All right. The third period...
is "Master in the House."
We've been running a survey
for three hours to ask...
which member seems to be the best
in communicating with their fans.
The viewers have been casting
their votes.
- Really?
(Running Man Surprise Live Show)
(2021 Running Man Surprise Survey)
(Who do you think will be the best
at communicating with fans?)
(As soon as the survey was posted,
many people participated.)
- Really?
- I'm the best communicator.
- I'm good at it too.
Depending on the result,
four members with the least votes...
will have a talk with Director Choi,
the variety department director.
- Really?
- What did you say?
- Why would we?
- Hey!
- The legendary director?
- Hey.
(The legendary director?)
(The legendary master,
Director Choi Young In...)
(is the final boss who announces
the Grand Award winner...)
(at the year-end entertainment award
every year.)
First of all,
I want to thank Director Choi.
(The winners of 2019 mentioned
Director Choi the most)
(Her name was
on the most searched word list.)
(He's thanking Director Choi
when he's never even seen her.)
(The legendary master,
Director Choi Young In)
(Do you know
what I'm not happy with?)
(The master of variety shows
is honest and straightforward!)
(The members will spend
precious time with her soon.)
- Why would we meet her?
- The lowest four?
- Why are we doing this?
- Are you serious?
Why are we doing this?
- It must be uncomfortable.
- Is it for real?
- Out of the blue?
- This is...
- We're having a talk with her?
- It'll be uncomfortable.
- Why would we talk with her?
- Please, please!
- To help them with the vote,
- I'm a good communicator.
we prepared
a surprise online fan meet,
which has been requested
for a long time.
- Really?
I've never done it before.
There are 17,000 people
tuning in right now.
Through YouTube Live,
you'll communicate with your fans...
for ten minutes.
The winner of the survey
will pick a card to pay.
Four people with the least votes
will have a talk with the director.
- A talk?
- Oh, my gosh.
The four of them
will get a marble too.
(The 4 members with the lowest votes
will get 1 more marble.)
During the ten-minute fan meet,
you can't ask them to vote for you
in any way.
If you do,
five percent of the votes
will be deducted in the end.
I should be careful.
- If you're ready, let's start.
- Sure.
Okay, you can start it.
It's fascinating.
I've never tried it.
I've never done
live streaming before.
(Nervous)
You can start now.
(The live streaming starts.)
(It's streaming live
around the world.)
- I've never done it before.
- It's not a good time slot.
I've never done
live streaming before.
You can start now.
- It's nice to meet you. Hello!
- Has it started?
- Hello!
We didn't know about it either,
but we're doing
a surprise live stream.
Actually, it's our first time to
do live streaming together.
- Right. It's our first time.
- Yes.
Everyone, this is Haha.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
- You can't do that.
- I'm just saying hello.
- I'm just greeting them.
- Hello, this is Big Nose.
- Don't you hate that nickname?
- You don't like that nickname.
I like it. I'm Ji Suk Jin.
Hello, everyone. I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
- This is Kwang Soo.
- It's being aired now.
Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo!
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hello, I'm Yang Se Chan.
Wow, over 20,000 people
are watching this right now.
- Sometimes, Haha does...
- There are 22,000 people now.
live streaming in his bathroom
when he's drunk.
- Yes, I do.
- That's right.
- I love talking with my fans.
- Don't do such things.
I always want to talk with my fans.
- Come on. Don't lie.
- Don't lie.
"Suk Jin, I voted for you.
Please give me some pocket money."
I will. How should I give it to you?
"Don't doze off
when Big Nose preaches."
(Don't doze off
when Big Nose preaches.)
- I shouldn't doze off, seriously.
- It's a trend.
It's okay even if you do.
What matters is that we're together.
They want us to introduce ourselves.
- Shall we?
- Who should we begin with?
- Kwang Soo will start.
- Okay.
- Hello, everyone!
- Make it short.
- This is Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- Are you done?
- That's enough.
- Your turn is over.
Hello, this is Se Chan.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Good. Next is Ji Hyo.
Hello, this is Song Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- Next, So Min.
Hello, I'm Jeon So Min.
Hello, I'm Kim Jong Kook!
Hello, I'm the eldest member
of Running Man.
- And...
- No, just say your name only.
- It's too long.
- He finished his introduction.
- I'm Ji Suk Jin.
- Just say your name.
Hello. Thanks to you guys,
we're having...
- That's enough.
- Jae Suk.
You said we'll keep it short!
Can't I at least thank them?
- No, you can't.
- I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
Hello, I'm a father of three kids
who live in Mapo-gu.
- I'm Haha. Bang, bang!
- Hey, hey!
- Stop that.
- Someone asked this.
"Kwang Soo,
can you do the 'Rollin'' dance?"
- Kang Mun Deok. Get up now.
- Kang Mun Deok asked this.
- Just do it.
- Mun Deok,
Kwang Soo doesn't know
the "Rollin'" dance.
- I do!
- Ready, go.
(He starts communicating with fans
as soon they request it.)
- Rollin', rollin', rollin'
- That's the dance.
Well done.
They want So Min
to do the "Rollin'" dance too.
- So Min, dance to "Rollin'!"
- "Rollin'."
The stingray dance.
Hey, hey!
(Running Man Surprise Live Show)
(What's with her hands?)
- So Min!
- Hey!
- That looks weird.
- You surprised them.
- This just fell.
So Min.
- This just slipped.
- She's indeed different.
- They want Ji Hyo to dance too.
- They want you to do the dance.
- The "Rollin'" dance.
- They're all asking that.
Do you know the dance, Ji Hyo?
- Do you know?
- Ready, go.
(Ji Hyo's version of "Rollin'")
- Good job, good job.
- The stingray dance.
- Is this how it's done?
- She knows a lot of stuff now.
- She knows a lot now.
- You're good, Ji Hyo.
- She does.
- You've improved.
- She knows a lot now.
You're no longer
living under a rock.
The number of viewers
keeps increasing.
- There are 33,000 people now.
- Thank you so much!
- You've done it a lot.
- Kwang Soo.
Did you go to a wedding?
Yes, last weekend.
Hey, don't go to weddings.
You'll ruin the mood.
- What?
- Why would you ruin their day?
- I was officially invited.
- Why would you ruin their event?
Don't go ruin their day.
They said they saw you from the back
and you were over 2m tall.
- I know.
- You can't hide it.
I'm not that tall.
On a good day,
he looks like he's over 3m tall.
- Come on, Jae Suk!
- That's true.
- I'm not that tall.
- I mean it.
Look at that.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes.
They want you to recommend
a stock item.
They want
a stock item recommendation.
I can't tell you specific items.
They'll buy every item
except the one you recommend.
- Everything except that.
- Oh, except that?
They're so funny.
Many of my friends asked that too.
They asked why Suk Jin
is so bad at investing.
- I can't...
- Somebody asked this.
- "Se Chan."
- "What's orange in English?"
- You guys are so harsh.
- He's not that ignorant.
- I'm not.
What is it then?
- Tell us the spelling.
- You have to answer them.
- Answer them.
- Do you want to write it down?
- Try it.
- Darn it.
- Darn it. Seriously?
- Yang Se Chan.
You can do it, Se Chan!
- Okay, okay!
- Just continue on.
I need three minutes.
- Hey.
- You need three minutes?
- Kwang Soo.
- Make that happy yet sad face.
They want you to make that face.
- Later. He can't do it right away.
- It's been a while.
Make three faces. Happy face,
sad face, happy yet sad face.
- Okay. Happy face.
- Happy face.
- Sad face.
- Happy yet sad face.
(Happy yet sad)
(He gets happier every time
he makes that face.)
(I'm scared that he might
appear in my dream.)
(He's an actor and a comedian.)
Now, we only have a minute left.
(1 minute
before the live streaming ends)
(With their active communication,
the results keep changing.)
One minute left!
- I'd like to...
- Look at all those hearts.
thank all of you.
I'm sad that there's only 1 minute.
I want to do it for an hour.
- Right.
- So...
I want to do it separately later.
- Yes, please do that.
- Guys.
Let's wrap it up and say goodbye.
Kwang Soo, go first.
- Let's say goodbye.
- Shall we say bye one by one?
- Everyone!
- That's enough!
- We don't have much time.
- You're making it too long.
Haha, go first.
Everyone. Nothing else matters.
Just stay healthy.
I'll work even harder.
- Guys.
- Yes, please do that.
Guys, thank you!
(Guys, thank you!)
- Why would you say it so casually?
- Why are you so informal?
- Suk Jin!
- Guys, thanks.
I love you guys.
That's how it's usually done.
- What's wrong with you?
- My mom is watching it too.
Don't you know?
This is how you communicate.
- Who communicates like that?
- You can't be rude though.
- That's so rude of you.
- I love you guys.
- You can't say it like that.
- Don't be so rude.
- I know.
- You need to use honorifics.
- We're being polite to each other.
- That's how it's done.
- No. You should be polite.
We're courteous people.
You can't be rude.
- Guys.
- Why would you call them rudely?
- Why would you do that?
- This is...
- Apologize to them now!
- They hate rude people.
- Why would you be condescending?
- Right. Don't do that.
- We're so sorry.
- I was really surprised.
- Wait.
- And thank you.
- We're so sorry.
I hope what Suk Jin said
doesn't cause controversy.
- I know.
- That's not it. You usually...
- We're sorry.
- We're so sorry.
- We apologize.
- Suk Jin was being ignorant.
- On my YouTube channel...
- Just stay healthy!
- We're not rude like him.
- We're so sorry.
- He's the only one who's rude.
- Right.
- So Min.
I want to say that I have nothing
to do with Suk Jin.
- That's not what I meant.
- Ji Hyo, you're next.
I apologize on behalf of Suk Jin.
- Everyone is apologizing.
- Please keep supporting our show!
- Yes!
- See you next time!
(It's my turn now!)
(What about me?)
Stay... Stay healthy!
What? It ended?
- It ended.
- We said goodbye already.
Why didn't you say goodbye faster?
- But I should've said goodbye.
- You should've joined in fast.
I said the closing comment.
I said, "Keep supporting our show."
- It's over.
- It's time to reveal the result.
The poll is now closed.
- Please.
- I don't want a meeting.
It will be funny...
if Suk Jin has a meeting
with Ms. Choi.
I would feel uncomfortable.
The members who have
a private YouTube channel...
- would have an advantage.
- You are right.
- That's right.
- They have the image...
- of being good at communicating.
- Seriously.
Having a private YouTube channel
should help.
Please. I mean,
I like Ms. Choi very much,
I would feel uncomfortable.
- You would be alone too.
- I am not close to her.
If Ms. Choi canes your calves,
would you take it?
Punishment is necessary at times.
- If that solves the problem,
- Punishment is necessary at times.
I would feel at ease.
If I must have a meeting
with Ms. Choi...
for ten minutes...
Ten minutes is a long time, right?
You wouldn't have anything to say.
It would be hard to spend
ten minutes with Ms. Choi.
The results are in.
Please.
- Please.
- As long as I am not included...
I am good at communicating
with the fans.
- I would get chosen.
- You and I...
- All right.
- Seriously.
First place.
(90,000 votes came in
over the course of 4 hours.)
Just stay healthy.
(To receive more votes,)
(they acted cute
during the live broadcast.)
(Whom did the fans choose?)
- I bet it's Haha.
- No.
- It isn't me.
- Haha.
This member received
about 23,000 votes.
- 23,000 votes?
- No way.
That's 26 percent of the votes.
- A lot of people voted.
- It could be Jae Suk.
I am the king of communication.
(There are a few masters
of communication...)
I am good at communicating.
(who made an effort
through YouTube, social media, etc.)
(Is the first place among them?)
- The first place.
- Haha.
The member who seems to be the best
at communicating with the fans is...
It must be Jae Suk.
Ji Hyo.
- What?
- What is this?
- This is ridiculous.
- Is this a popularity vote?
- This makes no sense.
- This is a popularity vote.
- Seriously.
- She doesn't do anything.
- This is ridiculous.
That means
you don't need to have a meeting.
She doesn't do anything
to communicate with the fans.
- You don't need to have a meeting.
- This makes no sense.
This makes no sense.
Even Ji Hyo is surprised.
- She is surprised.
- You are surprised, right?
She is confused.
The second place.
This member received
23 percent of the votes.
- Please.
- It's important...
- to be included in the top 4.
- The 2nd place.
- The top 4.
This member received
23 percent of the votes.
You need to be included
in the top four.
- Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- The result is strange.
- This is a popularity vote.
- Seriously.
- I did it.
- This is wrong.
- Listen, Bo Pil.
Aren't four members too many?
- Suk Jin.
- Four members are too many.
She said four members isn't enough.
- Really?
- Ms. Choi said that.
- The third place.
- It's too bad.
This member received
15.8 percent of the votes.
- This should be me.
- This is a popularity vote.
- This should be me. Suk Jin.
- Kwang Soo?
- Jong Kook.
- Thank goodness.
- This is a popularity vote.
- What is this?
Thank goodness. I communicate a lot.
It'll be so uncomfortable
if Haha, Suk Jin,
- So Min, and I have to go.
- Only one slot remains.
- Right?
- The ones who are active...
- on social media got left out.
- Seriously.
- I'm active on social media.
- Me too.
I'm on YouTube, Instagram,
and everything.
Come to think of it,
Haha and Suk Jin...
I communicate
as if my life depends on it.
My job is a YouTuber.
- I post one video per week.
- He even does it in the restroom.
He even communicates
with the fans...
- in the restroom.
- I use TikTok too.
Why didn't Suk Jin get included?
I communicate so much.
The last place has...
- a little over 2,700 votes.
- Is it me?
There is a difference of 10 votes
between the 7th and 8th places.
(There is a difference of 10 votes
between the 7th and 8th places!)
They received
3.2 percent of the votes.
(The two bottom members)
Suk Jin and Se Chan.
This is a popularity vote.
Is there a difference of ten votes?
Who is in the last place,
Suk Jin or me?
With 2,765 votes,
Suk Jin is the last place.
With 2,783 votes,
Se Chan is the 7th place.
Listen.
- He is the king of communication.
- These days,
- Suk Jin...
- He does it all the time.
- I know.
- Seriously.
He is the king of communication.
- You know,
- He mostly...
he gave up his daily life
for communication.
He mostly lives
on social media platforms.
Ji Communication.
He spends more time there
than in reality.
He spends
most of his hours communicating.
I feel so victimized...
because I use
all existing social media platforms.
YouTube, Instagram,
- TikTok... I joined Clubhouse.
- All right now.
- Suk Jin is almost a cyber person.
- A cyber person.
(The 21st century has Big Nose,
the king of communication.)
I hoped I would be the fourth place.
Now, I will announce
the fourth place.
It's either Kwang Soo or Haha.
- Is it So Min?
- It will be either So Min,
- Kwang Soo, or Haha.
- Please.
- It can't be me.
- This person won't have a meeting.
The fourth place...
unfortunately won't have a meeting.
It's truly unfortunate.
This person won't get encouragement.
The fourth place received...
- 11.3 percent of the votes.
- All right.
It must be Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
How disappointing!
(Screaming)
- I will tell Ms. Choi.
- I am disappointed.
- I am so annoyed.
- So Min is the fifth place...
and Haha is the sixth place.
- You know,
- Are you the sixth place?
I find it so funny...
that Ms. Choi and So Min
will have...
- a talk.
- I don't have anything...
to say.
I don't know that person.
- I don't have anything to say.
- Seriously.
"That person."
Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- Let's do this.
I don't know that person.
I feel like...
- I will get scolded.
- Think of her as a teacher.
Just say that you are sorry.
The masters of communication
got left behind.
- Ms. Choi...
- Put this on the table...
and have a meeting
until the sand runs out.
Just how much
do people want me to communicate?
It's so funny.
- Communication...
- Here are...
a rose and a Swiss roll.
I can't believe...
- Suk Jin and Haha...
- Right now...
got left behind.
The four members will move first.
The first place will pay...
and move to the next location.
- Ji Hyo is the first place, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo will pick...
- the card.
- You get to pay.
- Ji Hyo.
- The king of communication.
- It's so funny.
- Ji Hyo, the king of communication?
It's so funny
that Ji Hyo placed first.
- You are the king of communication.
- I think...
the fans misunderstood
and chose the member...
who doesn't communicate.
I won't communicate anymore!
Let's go.
- I will communicate.
- I will work hard.
I will work hard.
You let me know that I am lacking.
(The bottom four go
to Ms. Choi's office.)
- Let's hurry up.
- I feel so uncomfortable.
I feel like I'm suffocating already.
Well, it has been a while...
since I said hello to Ms. Choi.
This is a good opportunity.
I have never had
a proper conversation with her.
I don't know her well.
- Ms. Choi?
- Yes.
Even if you don't know her well,
you will be intimidated.
(She is excited to see the members
for the first time in a long while.)
Which shows did she work on?
"Truth Game."
- "Truth Game?"
- She made that show.
- She also made "Ya Shim Man Man."
- "Ya Shim Man Man."
- Really?
- "Ya Shim Man Man?"
- She made a lot of hit shows.
- She is cool.
- Is this the office?
- You should go in first.
Okay. Me will go in first.
- "Me."
- He is nervous.
- Is this the office?
- Go ahead.
Go ahead.
- Go on in.
- Hello.
(Director of variety shows at SBS,
Choi Young In)
Ms. Choi.
- You know...
- Come on in.
(He enters the office
with a rotten smile.)
Hurry over.
Come on.
They are ridiculous.
What are you doing?
(What are you doing?)
- Come on in.
- Come on.
She wants you guys to come on in.
- Hello.
- You know,
I should have visited sooner.
It has been a while.
We are the kings of communication.
- Give her the flower.
- Thank you.
Have you been well?
- It's a Swiss roll.
- You shouldn't have.
It's nothing.
- You know,
- It's nice to meet you.
- this is upsetting.
- Okay.
While we are very happy
to receive...
a chance to talk with you,
it makes no sense...
- that we are the bottom four.
- It makes no sense.
Do you know what I'm not happy with?
(Do you know what annoys me?)
(What?)
I don't know...
why a talk with me is a penalty.
- No, no.
- It's not a penalty.
It's not a penalty,
but the rest of the members
cheered loudly.
- They were overjoyed.
- Seriously.
- That's upsetting.
- Of course.
Why would they do that?
- We have no complaint.
- We are so happy.
And thank you for the text, sister.
Back then...
Don't pretend to be close to her.
Don't call her "Sister..."
- for no reason.
- She is warmhearted.
- She is totally warmhearted.
- Hey.
Do you know why she is popular?
She is easygoing.
- He is right.
- She is easygoing.
- She is the best.
- Don't call her "Sister."
Thanks for sending me a fruit basket
while I was in the hospital.
- Really?
- Thank you.
It's not a good deed or anything.
- Really?
- Every holiday...
- Every holiday, you send us food.
- I enjoyed the grapes.
Both the dried laver and grapes
were really tasty.
Her comments touched me
more than the gifts.
I really appreciated the text...
- because I was struggling.
- What did she write?
- I was in a slump back then.
- Are the two of you that close?
- She sent me a long text.
- Really?
- It gave me so much energy.
- I still remember...
how you got me a T-shirt
when you went on a trip to Europe.
- Do you remember that?
- Wasn't that years ago?
- 15 years ago.
- Ms. Choi, we want to know...
why Suk Jin got pulled out
of "Same Life, Unlike Dreams."
- Please explain.
- That's right. He got pulled out.
Hold on.
(No one remembers, but Suk Jin was
in "Same Life, Unlike Dreams 1.")
(But he disappeared after 1 episode.
What happened?)
Why did you bring that up?
- We want to know.
- So...
Why did he get pulled out?
He wanted to quit!
- Really?
- I mean...
I even went to his house
three times...
so that he would reconsider.
I went to Siksa-dong, Ilsan.
You did?
Well,
what happened is in the past.
Ms. Choi understands.
It's all in the past.
You must be embarrassed.
- I have a lot to say about it.
- I am sorry.
They only know about it
because Jae Suk brought it up.
He turned down my offer.
I told you that I was sorry.
When I get married...
Star in the show.
(So Min prematurely promises
to star in a couple's show.)
I thought about starring in the show
with Se Chan.
- Really?
- It's a good idea.
- What?
- We can do that if we get married.
- The two of you?
- It might happen someday.
- It might.
- Hey.
Don't be ridiculous.
You startled me.
Doesn't he look happy?
(Teasing)
He is smiling from ear to ear.
- Don't play with love.
- We could make so much money.
- If we make a contract...
- Don't be that way.
- You should be sincere.
Please tell us what you think
about Running Man these days.
- It's really fun these days.
- Right?
- Suk Jin is on fire these days.
- Yes.
It's impressive that such an old man
is on Running Man.
Seriously.
(An old man)
He wants to have
his 60th birthday party on the show.
- He must have it.
- I have that thought every time.
Please talk about people
who are upstairs.
(Thinking)
There are members
you dislike, right?
Jae Suk or Jong Kook.
That's right.
Well, both of them work too hard.
- It's excessive.
- They need to take a breather.
They are too much.
- The production crew struggles.
- They are too much.
Sometimes, we struggle.
When the shoot resumes
after a break,
you could relax and show up
2 or 3 minutes late.
- That's right.
- Jae Suk always acts up...
by getting there ahead of time.
That's not right.
Combine the 2 or 3 minutes.
If 60 staff members
lose 2 or 3 minutes...
Multiply 60 by 2 minutes.
That's 120 minutes.
You should be right on time.
Suk Jin is out. Suk Jin is out.
- Out.
- He is out.
Suk Jin is out.
("Suk Jin is out" sounds strange
at the director's office.)
I like that Ms. Choi is honest.
- She is honest.
- She doesn't mince her words.
I like that she is easygoing.
Why did you bring these?
It's because we love you so much.
There he goes again.
- You are such a suck-up.
- Stop it already.
- You are my woman
He is disgusting.
Is this how you live?
- I like it when he does that.
- Right?
You know,
- she practically raised us...
- That's right.
- ever since we were rookies.
- Yes.
I have a final favor to ask.
- What is it?
- Would you do it?
(Serious)
Sister, just stay healthy.
(Sister, just stay healthy.)
(She gets knocked out.)
- Okay?
- Let's go.
This won't do. For goodness' sake.
Thank you so much.
- Please stay healthy.
- She likes that.
- Bye.
- He told me to stay healthy.
- Be happy.
- Thank you.
- We had a great time.
- Bye.
- Work hard.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- May I drop by sometime?
Drop by anytime.
- Okay.
- "May I drop by sometime?"
(They conclude the meeting well
with their obsequiousness.)
- I should drop by.
- We had a great time.
- Bye.
- All right.
(The 4 kings of communication
arrive to make a payment.)
Ji Hyo, go in first.
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo?
- All right.
- Thank you.
- We are a team.
- All right, Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- We are in a good mood.
- That's right.
This is the current situation.
(The current number of marbles
is revealed first.)
Everyone has one or more
except for Jong Kook.
Jong Kook has a gold card.
It stands out.
(Jong Kook's gold card stands out.)
I think I should give him a marble.
- Here you go.
- I will pay with this card.
(Jong Kook is chosen.)
I chose your card
because your slot was empty.
It looked too lonely.
- It looked too lonely.
- All right.
All right.
(Ji Hyo loses a marble
and Jong Kook gains a marble.)
Now comes the last schedule.
- All right!
- He did it.
("Flaming Youth")
We are the last winners.
I won thanks to you.
- That's right, you punk.
- Let's go.
- You and I have good teamwork.
- That's right.
I didn't get to choose a card once.
Me neither.
So Min is done for.
What? Why do I have a marble?
Hold on. Ji Hyo.
(He spots the marble
Ji Hyo gave him.)
My goodness.
Ji Hyo paid with my card.
I was the last one before her.
It would be best
to give a marble to Ji Hyo.
- That's right.
- I need to remove mine.
- You need to remove yours too.
- That's right.
- All right.
- What are we going to do?
(But only one of them
can take out a marble.)
Se Chan has a marble too.
In that case...
(Whoever removes a marble
will be exempt from the penalty.)
- This put us in a tight spot.
- Seriously.
Things suddenly became awkward
between us.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- I am sorry.
- It's okay.
(He is sad
that he didn't use force.)
Okay. All right.
Whom will you choose?
- Ji Hyo.
- Choose Ji Hyo.
I will make the payment
with Ji Hyo's card.
Okay.
We need to increase the chances.
- Okay.
I will make the payment.
How many people will get
the penalty?
- Five people.
- For goodness' sake.
(The final number of marbles)
I didn't get to choose the card
even once.
You don't have many marbles.
- Really?
- How about me?
- Who has the most number of them?
- One member has a lot.
But too many people
will receive the penalty.
- 5 people.
- 5 people?
- Only 3 people will be spared.
We will count the repeating marbles,
so it could be less than five.
It's bad
if your marbles go in, right?
The last ones to arrive
will determine who gets the penalty.
- So they need to go in.
- Yes.
They need to go in quickly.
All right.
Here's what the penalty will be.
This is the penalty.
Put on a prisoner's wig
and a pillory...
and stay at the TV station's lobby
for five minutes...
to look back upon yourself.
- It isn't too bad.
However, the cameras will be hidden.
You will be alone.
- Alone?
- Yes.
That would be a bit embarrassing.
There should be a camera crew.
- How about the cameras?
- We need the cameras.
- Give us the cameras.
- Just one camera.
- Lend us one.
A camera stand.
We will film from afar.
For five minutes?
- Let's go.
(Who will receive the penalty?)
- Didn't we do this before?
- The track became longer, right?
It became longer, right?
The owner of the last five marbles
will receive the penalty.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Please, please.
Is Se Chan exempt?
I am exempt.
- Hold on.
- Mix them up at random.
Let's mix them up.
- Let's go.
- Please, please.
- Come on.
(The owners of the last 5 marbles
will receive the penalty!)
- One...
- Come on, blue marbles.
Let's go. Please, please.
- I won the last time.
- This is fun.
- Here we go!
- Let's go.
Let's go. Please, please.
(Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, Haha,)
(Jae Suk, Ji Hyo,
So Min, Jong Kook)
- Let's go.
Go!
- Let's go!
- What is that?
- Come on.
- Let's go, yellow!
What is that?
- Come on.
- Let's go, yellow!
- Please, please.
- Let's go.
- Here we go!
Go!
- Let's go!
- What is that?
- Come on.
- Let's go, yellow!
There go my four marbles.
- There they go.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- There they go.
(The owners of the last 5 marbles
become disheartened.)
(You are doing great,
light green marble.)
- The yellow one.
- No way.
- Come on.
- Please.
- The blue ones are fast.
- Let's go.
- Hey, hey.
- Come on, yellow marble!
(Currently,)
(the last 5 marbles belong to
Suk Jin, Haha, and So Min.)
(Kwang Soo's yellow marble is
6th from the last.)
(Suk Jin, So Min,
Haha, Haha, Suk Jin)
- The green one.
- Let's keep going this way.
- The green one. Turn the tables!
- I made it!
Yellow marbles!
(The last struggle)
- Turn the tables!
- Yellow marbles!
(In the end,)
(who will receive...)
(the penalty?)
The fourth place.
Okay.
To whom
do the last five marbles belong?
Red, yellow, blue, white, blue.
(Who are the owners?)
- Who are the owners?
- Suk Jin.
- Two blue marbles.
- So Min.
Haha.
Who owns the yellow marble?
- Yellow.
- Me.
Haha, Suk Jin, So Min,
and Kwang Soo will get the penalty.
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, and Jae Suk
got spared again.)
- Thank goodness.
- Lucky.
This is really fun.
Would you spare one of us?
- Among us.
- Spare one of us.
- Spare 1.
This game is fun.
- Just 1. Okay, okay.
- The 4 of us will play.
- This is the real deal.
- It's so much fun.
- I know.
This game is so much fun.
(Only 1 of them will be spared.)
Only the first one will be spared.
(So Min, Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, Haha)
This is the real deal.
The person whose marble
arrives first will be spared.
- Please, please.
- One,
- two,
- 25 percent chance.
(Suk Jin, Haha, So Min, Kwang Soo)
(So Min, Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, Haha)
- 3.
- Only the 1st place.
- You don't know yet.
- Red.
Why is mine so slow?
Run white marble, run.
- Gosh, mine is last.
- Red.
- It's the last chance.
- It might bounce off.
- I have a bad feeling.
- Here they go.
This is good.
Here they go.
What is wrong
with the yellow marble?
(The yellow marble has no hope.)
- It's so slow.
- What is it doing?
(So Min's red marble is leading.)
Gosh, there is no twist.
- Come on.
- What?
(You don't know what will happen
until the very end.)
(Who will be spared
from the penalty?)
What?
(Haha, Suk Jin, So Min)
It's red.
(So Min wins 1st place.)
(They just helped So Min win.)
- Kwang Soo's marble...
- What was that?
Was that computer graphic or what?
Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, and Haha
will get the penalty.
Let's go.
(Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, and Haha
will get the penalty.)
- This is so funny.
- There's no camera.
Where is the camera?
This is embarrassing.
I'm so embarrassed.
(They are ready to repent
in the center of the lobby.)
I'm so sick of getting penalties
with these two.
This year,
I've gotten a penalty every week
except for just once.
I'm doing this every week.
I can't believe this.
This is really embarrassing.
(The lobby is crowded today.)
(They can't take their eyes
off the spectacle.)
I'm sorry
but place the cameras closer to us.
I hope there won't be any tourists.
I hope not.
(He's afraid
if he'd see someone he knows.)
(Right at that moment...)
Stop Se Chan from filming this.
Go away.
- Go away. Leave.
- Hey.
- Go.
- Go home.
- What are you doing?
- Hey, Se Chan.
- What's wrong with him?
- Hey.
(Se Chan brought someone.)
- Hello.
Hello.
Hey, Se Chan.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- What is he doing?
(Mr. Yang lets people take
the best photo of their lives.)
More people are coming.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- This is like...
Hey, you're attracting people.
Hello.
(Anyone can take the best photo
with the ugly men in front of them.)
Oh, someone's behind us.
Hey, why are you attracting people?
I'm not attracting them.
They asked me to take a photo.
Please come and take a look.
Haha?
Hey, Jae Joon.
I'm ashamed.
Hello.
Hey, I'm embarrassed.
I'm so pissed.
(The 3 sinners became a small gift
for the people in the building.)
Why is time going so slow?
- What are you doing?
- Why is our crew taking pictures?
Why are you doing this?
You don't even care about us.
(They are done being sinners
and everyone's photo attraction.)
What?
Welcome, Running Man.
- What?
- Go into a room you want.
What's all this?
(Empty Head Land)
(The 8 members must be smart
to escape Empty Head Land.)
(The target score is 100 points.)
Communicate by telepathy.
(What's an exclamation?)
(What's giraffe in English?)
What kind of mission is this?
(Empty Head Land shows them
the bottom of their knowledge.)
(Only the smart ones can survive.)
(However...)
(The escape from Empty Head Land
begins now.)
(The level of difficulty
goes up for no reason.)
(The pressure to escape
is closing in on them.)
(But something's standing
in their way.)
(Smart Escape Race,
Empty Head Land)