Hey.
- Here we go again.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- How have you been?
You have a metal allergic reaction
on the back of your neck.
I'm serious. It's all black.
- Those are so out of style.
- Hello.
Hello. Good to see you.
Today... There's a shade here.
It's good to have a shade.
You know what?
On our way here, Suk Jin said...
Se Chan's outfit is out of style.
He said that
even before we started the shoot.
You're the one
who looks old-fashioned.
Are you entering
"Show Me The Money?"
- Why would you say that?
- I'm just...
- "Show Me The Money Season Ten."
- My fashion...
"Grandpa Special."
"Grandpa Special?"
"Show Me The Money Grandpa Special."
(Hip Hop Grandpa)
- "Who looks younger?"
- Anyway,
- I just finished self-quarantine.
- That's right.
How was it?
I heard your phone bill
is like 2,000 dollars.
I did make a lot of calls.
He must've been really bored.
I talked to Jun Ha on the phone,
and he was sick of you.
Really?
He couldn't even work.
- And he wouldn't hang up the phone.
- He didn't let him work.
Hang on. Then did you not
see your children...
- during the quarantine period?
- What?
- He can't.
- He can't see them.
- Of course, I didn't.
- He's not supposed to see them.
I wasn't allowed to see them.
You must've felt at ease.
He must've been excited.
He had no choice.
- You're unbelievable.
- You must've gotten a good rest.
- You're being ridiculous.
- I mean...
- That's not true.
- He just can't say so.
He just keeps it to himself.
You could've finished
the quarantine in a week.
- Right.
- But he did it for another week.
- That's right.
- He had a reason.
He was on a vacation.
Party time!
- We should congratulate Suk Jin.
- What?
- Why?
He got the Pfizer vaccine.
Congratulations.
I'm jealous.
- That's great.
- Pfizer.
I'm really jealous of him.
Congratulations.
It was just the first shot.
Did you get the shot?
- Did you really get it?
- It was the first shot.
- Pfizer Jee.
- Did you get the shot?
- Is it something to celebrate?
- Sure.
It's just the first shot.
He's the first member of Running Man
to get the vaccine shot.
The vaccine man.
- Congratulations.
- Pfizer Jee.
I got the Pfizer vaccine shot.
- Cool.
- Go, Pfizer Jee.
He bragged about it
after getting the shot.
- About the Pfizer shot?
- He called me.
"It's me, Suk Jin.
I just got the Pfizer shot."
And two hours later...
- My dad did the same thing.
- He called me again.
"I'm just fine."
("I'm just fine.")
- "Hey."
- He sounds like my dad.
He's just like my dad.
Why did he tell me such a thing?
Seriously, I was fine.
It felt like I didn't even
get the vaccine shot.
We will book
the vaccination this week.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- You should do it on the 14th.
- The 10-day rotation system.
It's based on your birthday.
The ten-day rotation system.
- Ji Hyo, is it new to you?
- Yes.
You should tell Ji Hyo
what COVID-19 is first.
- That's not true.
- It's not that bad.
I know what the COVID-19 is.
It's not that
influenza is prevalent now.
- I know that.
- And it's not beer.
It's not like masks are in fashion.
So I guess
this isn't about the shade.
They're filming from afar
because of the COVID-19.
- We don't usually do this.
- They are quite far from us.
None of us wouldn't step forward,
which never happened before.
This is just perfect.
We usually take a few steps forward.
We keep stepping
forward while we talk.
- We're not doing that today.
- We just remain behind today.
It's Africa there.
- It's another world.
- Anyway,
I'd like to thank everyone...
for supporting me
and worrying about me.
Thank you so much.
- Welcome back.
- Make sure...
to get the vaccine on time.
Pfizer Jiis proud.
He sounds excited.
- Guys.
- Yes.
We're doing the shoot
after a long time.
So we ordered
some tteokbokki for you.
- I love it.
- Tteokbokki sounds good.
- I like tteokbokki.
- It must be delicious.
- I like it.
- I love tteokbokki.
And anyone can enjoy this brand.
- What is it?
- It has a pleasant flavor.
What's the brand?
- It's just spicy enough.
- It's the product placement.
- So what's the brand?
- It's coming.
Your tteokbokki is here.
It smells great already.
- There's nothing.
- I don't smell anything.
There's no smell.
- Gosh, this is...
- My goodness.
It has butter in it. That's new.
That sounds unique.
The tteokbokki has
fried chicken in it.
It has fried chicken.
I've always wanted to try this.
We all are product placement freaks.
Look at this.
I just dipped this
in the tteokbokki sauce.
This is really good.
(They all show
exaggerated reactions.)
- What do you think?
- This is crazy.
- Why didn't I think of this before?
- Gosh, what is this?
It has butter in it.
It's very unique.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
You've done enough.
They want you to leave.
(You've done enough.
They want you to leave.)
Move over.
- The most important part...
- They want you to leave.
I'm about to say
the most important part.
Suk Jin's got one
and a half minutes, right?
Go.
Go away, Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin shouldn't be on screen
for over one and a half minutes.)
There's a time limit.
This is amazing.
How could they make
something like this?
It tastes like a paradise.
(Tenacious)
The advertiser must be upset.
The young men did a great job.
(He keeps saying useless things
despite the advertiser's concerns.)
"The young men did a great job?"
- Please listen to me while you eat.
- Okay.
Before we start today's race,
I will show you the prizes first.
- Really?
- What?
Can I get this tteokbokki
as a prize?
(I give up.)
Bring in the first prize.
- I guess it's Korean beef.
- Is it meat?
- The first prize is Korean beef.
- Nice.
Nice. I'll try hard today.
And we have the second prize.
The second one is...
called the modern elixir plant
that will help you...
regain your vigor in summer.
Please bring in
the ganoderma lucidum.
That sounds great.
- You can boil it and...
- It's healthy food.
- It's Young Ji.
- Young Ji.
Young Ji.
(They show up
with ganoderma lucidum.)
It's Young Ji.
- World Cup Young Ji.
- We have two Young Jis.
- Jae Suk, what happened to you?
- Two Young Jis.
It's Young Ji versus Young Ji.
They are Young Jis.
Ganoderma lucidum is here
with Young Jis.
I mean, Young Ji's are here.
- It's Young Ji versus Young Ji.
- Hello.
We said that before.
We talked about this.
Young Ji versus Young Ji.
(However...)
- I'm sorry, but...
- Young Ji.
- This is so good I can't greet you.
- I can't see you.
Hello.
(They greet them for a while
and start eating again.)
- This is really good.
- Let's eat.
- I just can't greet you.
- You guys should try too.
- Hello.
- Come on, let's eat.
- You're enjoying tteokbokki.
- Try it.
- You like it so much.
- You seem to enjoy it a lot.
You enjoy it a lot.
- We will put away the table.
- Okay.
(They put away the table hurriedly.)
This is really good.
- Seriously, I want to eat more.
- I really like it.
I want to eat more.
We have guests here, guys.
We're here.
I guess the tteokbokki is the guest.
They are like our family.
Is it right that
they focus on the tteokbokki?
(Now that they're close,
they treat the guests differently.)
That's because you're our family.
All right.
This is finally happening.
It's Young Ji versus Young Ji.
- Hello.
- Young Ji.
(Lee Young Ji and Heo Young Ji)
- They're back.
- They are...
- our favorite guests.
- I love them.
They are Young Ji and Young Ji.
Young Ji and Young Ji have
something in common.
It's not just they have
the same name.
- There's something else.
- Passion.
- It's passion.
- They have a fighting spirit.
- And the tension.
- Passion!
- They are passionate.
- Exactly.
- Passion and tension.
- What's interesting is...
- that we never met before.
- This is our first time meeting.
- Really?
- We just met for the first time.
It feels like I met my doppelganger.
She's right.
- So we let you meet each other.
- Exactly.
- You're the best.
- Thank you.
We will try our best.
After my appearance on this show,
people keep telling me...
that it's okay.
- It was...
- "It's okay?"
"Young Ji, it can happen.
The questions were difficult."
They comforted you
and cheered you up.
(About two months ago)
- Hey.
- Young Ji.
(Young Ji failed to read "liter.")
(Isn't liter abbreviated as L?)
(That's an L.)
(She read "sigma" as mountain.)
(Young Ji showed her Empty Head
side of her last time.)
You didn't know the basic things.
In "Comedy Big League,"
- we have online audiences.
- Right.
When Young Ji shows up,
they call her Empty Head.
They all say that
even when I'm not there.
They said that to Young Ji.
- She beat our Empty Heads.
- Totally.
She's Empty Head recognized by me.
He looks like my home economics
teacher from middle school.
(He's a dressed-up
home economics teacher.)
So I want to be nice to him.
Young Ji, I know what you mean.
They always wear modernized hanbok.
Exactly. Modernized hanbok.
Or a Chinese character teacher.
- Right. In modernized hanbok.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- That was a good one.
- Today,
we will have Young Ji
versus Young Ji Race...
with the two guests who will
revitalize your energy up...
in the sweltering heat.
We will be divided into two teams.
Like Yoo Grand Award
versus Kim Grand Award,
there will be Team Lee Young Ji
and Team Heo Young Ji today.
It's like a tradition.
The rest of you will choose...
a captain they want
before each mission.
And you will perform
a mission as a team member.
Okay.
So you will have different teams
for each mission.
The winning team will
get the point...
which is the number of team members
multiplied by five.
And the captain will distribute
the point as she pleases.
(The point will be distributed
by the captain.)
But when you lose, only
the captain of the losing team...
will lose as many points
as the number of team members.
(Only the captain will lose as many
points as the number of members.)
So the captains should
come up with good plans.
I believe they will
divide the points fairly.
Then I should go to the captain
who will be fair.
And the three members
with the highest points...
will get Korean beef
and ganoderma lucidum as a prize.
That's healthy.
The two members with the lowest
points will get a penalty.
I don't think she will divide it.
(Their fate depends
on the two captains.)
It's good to have more team members.
Now, I want you to choose
your first team.
The two captains should
step forward.
The rest of you will stand
behind the captain you want.
Hang on.
Is it okay
if we all go to one captain?
- Well... Heo Young Ji.
- Yes?
Do you share things with others?
- Me?
- Yes.
- If you win, will you share...
- Of course.
- I can do that.
- Really?
But I once...
fell for Lee Young Ji's trick.
(Kwang Soo and Haha had a hard time
because of Young Ji last year.)
World Cup Young Ji.
Do you like to share?
Jae Suk, we are friends.
Tell us about your strength.
I need to build
more relationships with people.
- I still have a long way to go.
- Right.
We were together back then.
- Me? When?
- Wasn't it you?
But...
Now that Heo Young Ji is here,
I'm sure there will be
a quiz about common knowledge.
I hate it.
- I can't go to Young Ji.
- What do I do?
All right. The two captains
should look straight ahead now.
The rest of you can
choose a captain you want.
They both have
advantages and disadvantages.
I don't think we will answer quizzes
in the first round.
- You're right.
- We don't do that in the beginning.
- It's usually the 2nd or 3rd round.
- It's the 2nd or 3rd round.
Are you ready?
In 1, 2, 3. Go.
(Which captain
will they choose first?)
- This is hard.
- What do I do?
(Studying each other's faces)
- It feels somewhat chilly.
- It feels like...
no one's behind me.
- As I count to three, you will...
- You know what?
The first poll is
all about popularity.
It's...
- It is a popularity vote.
- I agree.
As I count to three,
the captains will turn around...
and check your team members.
One,
two, and three.
(Team Lee Young Ji: 2 members
Team Heo Young Ji: 5 members)
My gosh.
(She's got only 2 members,
but they both are good.)
(Uncrowded, crowded)
I want to get
on the good side of you.
I can't believe this.
(Captain Heo is loved
by the 5 petty members.)
She took only the good ones.
- Hey, you got the good ones.
- Totally.
- You know what?
- It feels...
- Young Ji is...
- It feels strange.
- She's really strong.
- Of course she is.
The first round might require
physical strength.
If that's true,
we can't predict the result.
Young Ji, Haha and I were
the first to come.
- Please know that.
- Okay.
- This is great.
- Hey, we'll bring you the victory.
- I was the first to come.
- Listen, Young Ji.
I'm happy to be on Young Ji's team.
If Lee Young Ji's team wins
in the first game,
she'll have 15 points to share
with her team members...
whereas the other team gets
30 points.
- We just have to win.
- That's enough for us.
I agree.
The first mission
where you can get points...
will be carried out
under the team leaders' leadership.
- It's Morning Dance Battle.
- Morning Dance Battle.
A dance battle? Great! Oh, wait.
Lee Young Ji is a great dancer too.
She's such a great dancer.
Oh, right. So is Heo Young Ji.
- She was a member of KARA.
- Heo Young Ji is amazing.
Five of the staff members will
evaluate your performance.
- Oh, really?
- These five will be the judges.
(They're planning to give
a fair and accurate evaluation.)
- I see. Okay.
- The team with more votes...
from the judges wins.
Then I suppose we should
aim to entertain the audience.
The idol group dance style is
different from street dance.
- It's different.
- Absolutely.
- I have a raw style of dance.
- Exactly.
She used to be
in a school dance club.
- That's true. I was.
- That's right.
We'll play random songs,
- and you step forward and dance.
- Freestyle dancing? Okay.
Should we take turns?
- It's up to you.
- Got it.
- Young Ji, we can do this.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this. Go for it.
- Don't forget you're from KARA.
- Show them what you've got.
- Young Ji.
- We must win this. That's good.
- Let's do some warm-ups.
- Young Ji, you know, right?
- Yes?
- Sure. My joints move smoothly.
- That's good.
- Of course.
- I haven't gotten rusty.
The team leaders can dance
at the same time.
She took off her shoes.
Hey, she took off her shoes.
- Are you going to dance barefoot?
- Yes. I can't dance in heels.
- But will you be okay?
- Yes.
I'll be fine. I won't get
scrub typhus here, right?
All right.
We'll begin the first round now.
Play the music.
Look at Young Ji. My gosh.
(She's moving to the center
without hesitating at all.)
(A center member's bounce dance)
(Both are dancing passionately
like on a stage.)
Nice. Keep going.
They're so energetic
and enthusiastic.
(Energetic)
What is she doing?
Heo Young Ji must've gotten anxious.
(Going down)
(She got anxious
and laid down on the grass.)
(Getting overly energetic)
Oh, my. It's so funny.
The ground is shaking.
Isn't that a martial art move?
Hold on.
Stop the music for a second.
- Stop the music.
- Maybe we should take turns.
- They're both really enthusiastic.
- I like their energy.
- Young Ji, come back.
- They're so energetic.
- They're amazing.
- They're incredibly enthusiastic.
- They overwhelmed the cameras.
- Great job.
They overwhelmed the cameras.
Young Ji, did you learn
a martial art?
No, I've never learned it before.
- You looked like a martial artist.
- Drunken fist.
(Unlike somebody, they're
full of energy without vaccination.)
- You see...
- It looked like a martial art move.
- Do you know what's amazing?
- What is it?
- You don't know that song, right?
- No, I don't.
- She just improvised despite that.
- I've never heard that song before.
- True.
- We can't compete with them, right?
- We're no match for them.
- They're just amazing.
They're on another level.
They performed a freestyle dance
as a warm-up.
- Was it a warm-up?
- Let's let them dance individually.
- Individually.
- Was it a warm-up?
- Yes.
- Take turns this time.
(I know this song.)
(Young Ji walks to the center
of the stage again.)
There she goes!
My, she's amazing.
- Awesome!
- Oh, my.
- She's really awesome.
- Look at her feet.
(She was worried about scrub typhus
but is dancing with light steps.)
(Jumping with bare feet)
Hey, you might hurt your feet.
Hey, be careful
not to hurt your feet.
You might hurt your feet.
I think she already
got some scratches.
Here we go. It's the highlight.
(Young Ji is doing well!)
- She's just incredible.
- Oh, my.
- My, I'm impressed.
- Awesome.
(She's unbelievable.)
(Everyone is watching
her energetic morning dance in awe.)
I must say, she's really amazing.
I know that part.
(Se Chan is enjoying himself
without interrupting her.)
She's incredible.
- Hey, are your feet okay?
- Okay. That was great.
- I'm fine.
- Really?
- Be careful with your feet.
- I don't...
even take my puppy out for a walk
in heat.
Are you sure
you didn't hurt your feet?
I won't get
scrub typhus here, right?
Put your shoes back on
at least when you're not dancing.
- That's okay. I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm okay.
- By the way, Young Ji,
you have large feet.
My foot size is 260mm.
- Her shoes...
- They might grow to 280mm.
- Your feet are so...
- Exactly.
- How?
- Young Ji.
My foot size is 260mm.
- Put them back on for now.
- I think...
- she'll grow to two meters.
- Right.
That'd be great.
I could be a basketball player.
(Don't worry. Then I would become
a basketball player.)
It's a good plan, right?
- It'd be a good thing.
- She can play along with any jokes.
True.
- All right. You're up, Young Ji.
- Young Ji, you've got this.
- Overwhelm the audience.
- Do this move.
(Smiling charmingly)
The one where you walk forward
like this.
(Heo Young Ji from KARA is here.)
(This idol singer still has
her dance skills.)
(Going crazy)
- Awesome!
- Yes!
- You're amazing. Keep going.
- Oh, my.
- She's amazing as always.
- Indeed.
- She's great.
- She's amazing.
- She's exceptional.
- Amazing.
- Good. Keep going.
- She knows the other members' part.
(All girl groups separate parts
for each member.)
Young Ji,
walk toward the camera crane.
- Let's go!
- Get closer to the camera crane.
- Go.
- That's good.
- Great.
(She knows where to see
from her experience.)
- This is fun.
- She's great.
- Okay. That's enough.
- Great job.
(She maintains the cheerful energy
to the end.)
- Good job.
- Impressive.
- Good. You did well.
- Great job.
- How can I defeat an active singer?
- Good job.
- Well done.
- That was amazing.
- How can I defeat an active singer?
- Okay. Thanks.
You looked so cheery.
- We all enjoyed it,
- You were amazing.
but especially Jong Kook got
so excited.
(He smiled from ear to ear.)
(Actually, Jae Suk and Lee Young Ji
were even more excited than him.)
- I wanted to see the highlight.
- Exactly.
But I didn't want her to use up
all her energy already.
- Right.
- Young Ji, are you ready?
- All right. Don't worry.
- You can pick a song.
- It's okay.
- The one you're confident in.
One that I'm confident in?
- Pick something in your style.
- She can dance to any latest songs.
- I know almost all.
- That's right.
- How about aespa's song?
- How does that sound?
- Dance to one of aespa's songs.
- All right.
- "Walk toward the open field."
- Okay. Let's go with aespa.
- Let's go with aespa.
(She's ready to walk
toward the open field.)
- Okay. Let's go.
- Oh, my.
- Here we go.
- "Next Level."
I think I've seen her dance
to this song before.
(Disciplined moves)
(The dance maverick is enjoying
dancing in the open field.)
(Heo Young Ji joined her
in the open field.)
- Heo Young Ji, headbang at least.
- What's that?
(The headbanging show
begins suddenly.)
(Meanwhile, Lee Young Ji didn't
forget the key moves.)
- Look how she moves.
- Oh, my.
It's absolutely amazing.
(The dancers on another level
mesmerizes the cast members.)
Young Ji and Young Ji are amazing.
Let's give them a big hand.
(Impressed)
- They're amazing.
- Indeed.
That was amazing.
And they danced in this heat.
They don't seem to get tired
in this heat.
- Gosh, that's so annoying.
- Why?
- What?
I asked about this song,
and he said it was
Cho Yong Pil's new song.
(The new song in August,
"Next Level" by Cho Yong Pil)
What is this song?
We like this kind of song.
Hey, what's this song?
It's Cho Yong Pil's new song.
(The home economics teacher is
not familiar with the latest songs.)
- Hey, how about S.E.S?
- Yes.
- What was it? "I'm Your Girl?"
- There's no song to dance to.
- Yes, it's "I'm Your Girl."
- Good. Go with that song.
- Play "I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S.
- "I'm Your Girl."
- No. There's no way she knows it.
- S.E.S. Give it a try.
I don't know
the entire choreography, but...
(As the nostalgic melody
comes out...)
- So Min, join her.
- Go on.
(Temporary member number 2)
- You go too. Dance along with them.
- Go on.
Let's go!
(Member 1, the cheerful one)
(Member 2 dancing in her own style
wearing a face mask)
(And Member 3)
Look at Ji Hyo.
Ma'am!
Hey, Ji Hyo.
(She moved in the wrong direction
and almost bumped into Young Ji.)
Where are you going, ma'am?
(The 3rd member goes in a direction
of her own choice.)
Excuse me. Where are you going?
- She's so cute.
- Excuse me.
(It was successful
for an impromptu performance.)
- She moved in the wrong direction.
- Hey...
- Ji Hyo.
- I know.
- I don't know the choreography.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- It was like a mirrored video.
Jong Kook found it so cute.
(Jong Kook found it so cute.)
- Oh, my. How sweet.
- That's ridiculous.
You didn't even look at me!
You didn't even see my face!
- I saw that too.
- Did you see my face?
- I can't believe him.
- He's unbelievable.
- I saw it.
- I was standing behind him.
- You know...
- It must be true. He's flustered.
- Jong Kook...
- This is so unexpected.
Do I look that cute to you?
- My gosh. I can't believe you guys.
- I could see all of your teeth.
You were smiling from ear to ear.
- I saw it.
- I didn't see that coming.
- That's total nonsense.
- He's flustered.
He seemed to be
totally head over heels for Ji Hyo.
I might actually punch you.
Young Ji. Hey.
(Lee Young Ji got herself ready
to dance again even in the ruckus.)
("Alcohol-Free" by TWICE)
- TWICE.
- Great.
- She's great.
- Impressive.
(We're all mesmerized
by Young Ji's dance.)
- She's amazing.
- Great.
(Fascinated)
- She's incredible.
- How amazing.
- I'm amazed.
- Awesome.
- How amazing.
- Yes!
- She's incredible.
- Oh, my.
She's exceptional.
She has such a good groove.
She does look like a girl
who was born in the 2000s.
She's much younger than us, Ji Hyo.
(The ones who were born in the 1970s
are fascinated by her youth.)
She's on another level.
(She makes sure
that everyone knows.)
Great.
(Heo Young Ji stepped forward again
as she got anxious.)
- She got anxious.
- They're amazing.
(Using every joint in her body)
They're awesome.
- Amazing.
- They have an amazing groove.
- Okay. That's it. Come back in.
- That was great.
- That was good enough. Good job.
- Young Ji is such a great dancer.
- Exactly.
- Her moves are amazing.
- She sure was in a dance club.
- She has a great groove.
(She's still full of energy.)
- That was good as well.
- Their signature dance move.
That was great.
The intense competition...
- between the team leaders ended.
- They're amazing.
- They're neck and neck.
- They're just incredible.
I'll announce the result right away.
The five judges will vote.
- There are five judges.
- Yes.
(She's trying to
win the judges over.)
- I have a good feeling.
- Let's find out the result now.
I think it was a good investment.
Both of them did really well.
Raise the name of the person
you think did better.
- One, two,
- It's Young Ji no matter what.
- three.
Three.
Three votes for Team Lee.
Four, actually.
(The staff members were fascinated
by the raw style of dance.)
- It's okay.
- You did well.
It's okay.
- All right.
- Young Ji, you did a wonderful job.
(The team won
only because of Young Ji's dance.)
By the way, Heo Young Ji was also
really amazing.
Thank you. I'm honored.
You're so cool.
- The power of youth was amazing.
- Indeed.
- I was like her when I was her age.
- I know.
I was as energetic as her back then.
But not anymore.
As a result, Heo Young Ji's score is
minus six points.
(The number of the members is
deducted from the leader's score.)
That's so harsh.
- And Lee Young Ji got 15 points.
- Yes!
Please write down the points
you want to give to the members.
Thank you.
She can have all the points
to herself, right?
Correct.
Young Ji, you can take them all.
I know. I'll think about it.
You should have all the points
if you want to draw attention.
- But, I...
- Okay?
- Young Ji has a good heart.
- Indeed. It's okay...
- if you give us a few points.
- She and I go way back.
- Give us just a few points.
- Should I reveal it?
- Should I hide it from them?
- Just a few points would be enough.
- Don't show it to us yet.
- Write down where they can't see.
And then please give it to us.
Young Ji, give zero points
to one of them.
Young Ji, think of it this way.
Giving us no points is too harsh.
Think that we're your uncles,
and you met us...
- at a national holiday.
- Right.
- Like that.
- Exactly.
- We did nothing but cheer.
- That's right.
- Think that we're your uncles.
- Exactly.
Now, the two of you,
please come and check your scores.
- All right. Young Ji.
- Okay.
- Don't worry. We're like a family.
- I trust you.
- You...
- Young Ji, thank you.
We go way back, you know.
Thank you, Young Ji.
You don't have to tell the others.
Look at his face.
I gave them more than enough.
- Seriously.
- Look at his face.
- Jae Suk seems shocked.
- Well, it seems fair.
- It's fair.
- I'm so curious.
He is just surprised
as he got so many points.
- It's fair.
- You're good at this.
Jae Suk, it's better than nothing.
Of course.
I guess they got at least one point.
She did her best to win
for her own sake.
- Right?
- I'm speechless.
She earned it. It's fair.
Young Ji, I'm impressed.
Jae Suk said that the harder I try,
the more airtime I get.
(It was Jae Suk
who taught me this.)
You will choose your team again.
Please step forward.
- The members will be changed?
- Yes.
- This is...
- Right. It changes in every round.
It's obvious
which team we'll choose.
How many points did you get?
You should tell us.
- What?
- Did she give you no points?
- She did give us some points.
- What's your score...
- I won't tell anyone else.
- I can't...
- tell you my score.
- Were you very shocked?
She gave one point to each
because it's the minimum point.
Isn't it obvious?
All right. Let's go now.
- One, two, three.
- It'll be a quiz game.
I'm sure of it. It's a quiz game.
(Jae Suk heard the word "quiz"
and stopped.)
It might not be a quiz game.
- He's hesitating.
- I'm sure it's a quiz game.
You're sure of it?
- Maybe it's not.
- I'm sure of it.
But it might not be...
On three.
Three, two, one.
You can turn around now.
Young Ji, it's me.
(The elders chose her after being
betrayed by their niece.)
- Okay!
- It's the opposite this time.
- It's you.
- Of course, we chose you.
They just switched the teams.
- You shouldn't betray us.
- Of course, not.
- I will never betray you.
- Don't betray us.
- Gosh. Look at Lee Young Ji...
- I promise. No.
- I can't believe her.
- No.
Young Ji, they don't make any effort
to win.
- Don't...
- They won't make any effort.
I gave them points
according to the effort they made.
- Really?
- Just as much effort they made.
- She's the one who worked hard.
- But still...
- She's right about that, but...
- We cheered for you and all.
- We contributed too.
- My gosh. You shouldn't say that.
- I gave you a lot.
- It's not like...
You will change
into your team uniforms.
- I'll tell you about the game.
- Okay.
The second game is...
You shouldn't change the game now.
- I have a feeling that it's a quiz.
- It's a quiz.
(Could it be a quiz
as they predicted?)
It's Random Player Foot Volleyball.
(The 2nd mission is
Random Player Foot Volleyball.)
- It's not bad. We've got this.
- We outnumber them.
- We'll play foot volleyball?
- Wait. Hold on a second.
We're at an advantage
because we outnumber them.
We don't have a chance to win.
We outnumber them.
Maybe it's not so bad
because So Min will be the referee.
Right. She'll be the referee.
Hey, So Min.
- So Min will be the referee.
- That's right.
- Let me...
- How many players are on each team?
- make this one thing clear.
- I'll explain the rules later.
- I'll kick the ball no matter what.
- Okay.
- I'll kick the ball today.
- Come on.
- Stop. I'll kick the ball today.
- No. Listen, So Min.
So Min, that's not a good idea.
I'll play the entire game.
Hey, I told you that the referee is
the most important person.
(They changed
into their team uniforms.)
Oh, my. This is... Why? What is it?
- You really are the referee.
- I mean...
Let me see. Turn around.
It says "Referee."
- You're the referee.
- Just as we said.
So Min will be the referee today.
I was so surprised.
Suk Jin, she's the referee.
She put the name tag on her back.
Leave it, So Min.
You're the referee.
Don't take it off. Just accept it.
So Min, we're not fooling around
with you. It's the best position.
That's the whole point
of playing this game.
Why is it always So Min
who gets to be a referee?
She's actually the referee.
- No, I'm a player.
- So Min is the referee.
No, I said I'm a player.
I'll play the game today.
- You know the game rules, right?
- So Min, since you're the referee,
blow your whistle and say,
"Line up."
If you say that, all of us will
gather around. You'll see.
If they don't,
I won't be the referee.
(Blowing the whistle)
The referee wants us
to gather around.
- Let's go. Left, right.
- Left, right.
- Referee, what should we do?
- So Min is a perfect referee.
I'm glad we'll play foot volleyball.
It's pointless to have many players.
- Who made you so angry?
- It's weird...
- I feel like we'll lose.
- Exactly.
- We're at a disadvantage.
- Somehow I have a bad feeling.
And the letter "Heo" on their shirts
annoys me.
- It sounds like a smirk.
- "Heo."
- I didn't realize that.
- "Lee."
(The intense,
childish war of nerves)
- "Heo."
- "Lee."
The game you'll play this time is...
Random Player Foot Volleyball...
where the team leaders play
a very important role.
- What is it?
- Each team...
The team leaders should play
the entire game.
In the beginning,
the team leaders choose a member
for a 2 on 2 match.
- It's a 2 on 2 match?
- I see.
The female players are allowed
to use their hands.
When the team leader scores a point,
she can either add one more player
to her team...
or eliminate one player
from the opponent team.
Really? Eliminate a player?
But her team has only two players
other than her.
You can eliminate them all
except for the team leader.
Let's make Young Ji play alone.
This is great.
You should win 11 points in 1 set.
The 1st team to win 2 sets wins.
- Exactly.
- Use your hand.
- Like in volleyball.
- I'm so excited.
- Got it.
- You know volleyball, right?
- Yes, I know what volleyball is.
- Hey, that sticker...
- "Spike."
I mean the sport volleyball,
not "Bali."
- Gosh, you.
- I think...
- Okay.
- Really?
- Do you all understand the rules?
- Yes, we do.
Then we'll pick the first players
from each team now.
- Okay.
- I hope Se Chan will be chosen.
- Please. Pick me or Haha.
- Pick Suk Jin.
- Please pick Se Chan.
(To add more players to the team,
the 1st player must do well!)
- Let's go. Pick my name.
- My throat is sore.
Pick Pfizer Jee!
Pick me, Pfizer Jee.
- It's Suk Jin.
- Gosh. We're in trouble.
(The 1st player is Suk Jin.)
(Big Nose has been selected
for an important position.)
(The nerd was picked
instead of the fast, athletic ones.)
- I'll show you.
- Pfizer Jee!
Pfizer Jee!
- We should get a lot of points.
- Okay.
We should get many points
in the first set.
- It's Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- It'd be better...
- if I didn't play.
- Okay.
- We'll definitely lose.
- Gosh.
Okay.
Let's win.
Go, Pfizer Jee! Let's win!
- Let's do this!
- Go, Pfizer Jee!
- I can do it! Go, Pfizer Jee!
- Let's go.
I did lower body exercise yesterday.
(The non-certified referee is
also ready.)
- Get ready.
- That's so cool. I'm so upset.
I'm so nervous.
Suk Jin, serve.
(Suk Jin serves first.)
Young Ji, stand closer to the net.
- Young Ji!
- Okay.
- Out.
- Has it begun?
- Young Ji.
- Okay.
- It's 1 to 0.
- Stay inside this line.
- I see. Here?
- Stand here.
- You're an attacker, okay?
- Understood. I'm an attacker.
- Hit the ball with a fist.
- I'm an attacker.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Go, Pfizer Jee!
- Who should be added to the team?
- Why did I say that?
- She said, "Go, Pfizer Jee."
- Let's go.
- Go.
- Hey.
Okay.
(The ball fell on their side.)
Gosh. What was that?
- Don't worry.
- I thought you passed the ball.
- This is just the beginning.
- I see.
- That was good.
- It's just the beginning.
Bo Pil, you're so cold-hearted.
Suk Jin, it's better to hit it
with your head at the start.
- With my head?
- Yes, hit it with your head.
- Yes, in any case.
- Young Ji, look at the ball.
- Got it.
- Dodge it when it goes out.
- You've got this!
- We can do it!
- I'll receive.
- Okay.
The head.
- Good.
- Use your hands.
- Oh, no.
(Young Ji kicked it high.)
- Young Ji, use your hands.
- Use your hands.
- Hands. Right.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Nice.
- We'll win.
Nice!
- Hit it over the net.
- I'll do that.
- Or you can pass it to me.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- Go ahead.
Just hit it over the net
with your hands.
(I'll hit it with my hands.)
- Out.
- Okay.
Young Ji, don't try to receive
any serves.
- It's out.
- Okay.
Young Ji, it's out.
- Got it.
- It's out.
- Get it together!
- Young Ji, get it together.
I'll get it together.
Here we go.
- That's good.
- Nice.
- It's in.
- Young Ji, don't receive it.
- Receive.
- What is he doing?
- Good. Hit it over the net.
- Hit it over the net.
- No, not that way.
- Okay.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be. It wasn't your fault.
(The human antibody
lowered his head.)
Heo Young Ji, since you,
the leader of her team, scored,
you can add another player
to your team...
- or eliminate Suk Jin.
- This is just the beginning.
(She can add a player to her team
or send one off from the other.)
(Bringing Jae Suk in
or sending Suk Jin off)
- What should we do?
- Add more players to our team.
- You should do that.
Please eliminate Suk Jin.
That'd be better for us.
- Eliminate Suk Jin.
- Add a player to our team.
- That's better.
- Okay. We'll bring him in.
- Suk Jin is no help at all.
- Okay. This is good.
- Good.
- It's Jong Kook's serve.
We'll end it with 11 points.
- Young Ji.
- Yes?
My ball! Darn it.
(He strikes up a conversation.)
(She ends up hugging the ball.)
- Hey!
- Out!
- I mean...
- Don't receive their serve.
- And Young Ji...
- Their serve...
- Don't think about receiving it.
- I won't.
- Bam bam.
- Take the serve instead.
- What if this is how the game ends?
- Don't receive it.
I mean...
They can't kick the ball
over the net.
This is no fun at all.
It's hardly any fun.
Could we please have a rally?
Suk Jin, you've got this, right?
Of course.
(The confident Suk Jin
makes his serve.)
- Young Ji, move.
- Young Ji, kick it.
Young Ji, with your foot!
- That's it.
- My ball.
- Me!
- With your head.
- Here.
- Use your hands instead!
Use your hands instead!
Punch the ball across.
- Here.
- Use your hands instead!
- Good.
- That's it.
- Good one.
- Nicely done.
- Nice.
- We're on a roll.
Use your hand.
- Nice!
- Okay!
Good one. Nice.
(She hit it with too much power.)
(Team Lee Young Ji scores properly
thanks to Heo Young Ji's mistake.)
- In 1, 2, 3.
- We've got this!
- Okay.
- Nice.
That was good.
Think about striking the ball
when it's up in the air.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Since you scored,
we can add another player.
- Then...
- All right.
- Is that how it's done?
- All right!
Let's go!
Me!
- Haha.
- Nice.
(The nimble Haha joins the game.)
- It's Nino Maximus.
- I'll pass the ball to you.
- Got it.
He adds nothing to the team.
(Team Heo Young Ji tenses up.)
There will be no difference.
(Young Ji and Young Ji
aren't backing down.)
There will be no difference.
Okay. We've got this.
We shouldn't fool around anymore.
(Haha enters the game
to save the team.)
We've got this.
- I'll receive the serve.
- Here we go!
Haha, you receive the ball.
Here we go.
I'll receive it this time.
- You'll receive it, right?
- It's mine.
You'll receive it, right?
- Okay.
- Good.
(Haha sends it over
close to the net.)
- Young Ji, move.
- Hey!
- Nice.
- You did well though.
You did well. It's all right.
- Good one.
- Nice!
- Nicely done.
- All I have to do is watch.
Here we go.
- Nice.
- It's long.
- Take it.
- Oh, it wasn't.
- Young Ji, hit it.
- Hit it hard.
(He taps the ball with his head
and serves it to Young Ji.)
- Nice.
- Hit it.
- Hit it hard.
(She spikes the ball
like she was taught.)
- Good one.
- Give it to Young Ji.
- That's it.
- Young Ji, hit it.
Nicely done.
Young Ji, hit it.
(Tapping)
That was good.
- We still intimidated them.
- Take one player out.
- That was very hip-hop of you.
- Swag.
- Young Ji, what...
There's no player
to take out though.
Young Ji!
- What now?
- There's no player to take out.
Haha, you're out.
Oh, we have to lose a player.
(They lose Haha
who was their best player.)
It was Haha who made us catch up.
- This is hilarious.
- Shouldn't Suk Jin...
- take a break?
- I have no energy left.
Okay.
- Already?
- I have no energy left.
(Jae Suk serves.)
- Mine!
- We're good.
"Mine"?
- Seriously?
- What on earth are you doing?
(What?)
(Huh?)
(His depletion of energy
is evident.)
Can he get a Pfizer shot?
A Pfizer shot.
Here. Here's a Yang-izer shot.
Here you go.
There.
The ball doesn't bounce well
on this surface.
What a mess.
- Okay, do it.
- Here we go.
- The Pfizer shot!
(The serve heads to Suk Jin
who got his booster shot.)
Get it!
Nice. Now, an overhead kick.
- We're good.
- Hold on.
Are you playing beach volleyball?
Get it!
(PE on the beach
with her home economics teacher.)
Send it over the net.
Okay, we're good.
(PE on the beach
with her home economics teacher.)
They're playing beach volleyball.
Just leave them be.
We won.
- We won this point.
- I mean,
it was like watching...
a mother and a daughter
play volleyball on the beach.
- Unbelievable.
- Not father, but mother?
Sorry, I should've said "father."
(My bad.)
(Young Ji's mom
wants to take a break.)
Can't someone take my place?
I'd love to take your place.
Me too.
Young Ji, score this time...
- so we can add a player.
- Got it.
This team...
No other player
has been able to join in.
- Why is it just those two?
- Tell me about it.
- Can't I join in?
- I want to play too!
I'll score from this moment on.
Suk Jin's exhausted.
Suk Jin's exhausted,
so get playing already.
Here we go!
Suk Jin's exhausted.
- Send it over.
- Toss the ball high.
Darn it.
- Send it over.
- Toss the ball high.
(They have the worst chemistry.)
(All they have to do
is serve to win.)
(He's frustrated
past his tipping point.)
Get over there with a Moderna shot.
A Moderna shot?
Shoot him up.
The Janssen shot.
Moderna?
Keep your head on straight
and focus on scoring...
- one point at a time.
- We can do this!
- We can do it.
- Just end it.
End the game.
- It's long.
- Nicely done.
- Gosh.
- Get it!
- Nicely done.
Seriously?
Get it!
(They lost their last point
as the ball goes over his head.)
- They'll lose a player.
- No, we don't have to.
(Heo Young Ji wins Round 1
with a score of 11 to 5.)
That was hilarious.
(Team Lee Young Ji
had to bench most of their players.)
Nice.
There you go.
I can't believe this.
The first set is over.
We'll now move on to the second.
- The first set it over?
- Okay.
Heo Young Ji...
and Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- It's not bad.
- If it's Suk Jin again...
- I know.
Can't the player from
the first set be excluded?
It's So Min.
(So Min will play.)
(Only So Min is excited.)
Jeon So Min!
- Jeon So Min!
- But she's the referee.
Can a referee play?
- The two of you...
- Let's do this!
Let's do this!
- You can both use your hands.
- All right.
That's why you have
a good chance of winning.
- Also...
- Don't use your palms.
- Punch the ball instead.
- Got it.
- This is what So Min loves.
- Don't kick the ball.
- I...
- She's not on Jong Kook's team,
and no one can
pull the brakes on her.
- Kick it.
- Stay way behind the net.
- Over here?
- Think that this is volleyball.
How about here?
(She's the eldest daughter
of a former soccer player.)
Try kicking it.
(She's the eldest daughter
of a former soccer player.)
(Korean volleyball
has Kim Yeon Koung.)
(And Korean foot volleyball
has Jeon So Min.)
- Hey.
- Nice one.
Be the referee instead.
(This is how the master serves.)
She can't serve properly.
- Being the referee is the best.
- You can do this.
- Let me try it again.
- Hold on.
Can you let them serve
three steps ahead?
- Just three steps.
- Okay.
Only when they serve, okay?
- Win the gave with only serves.
- Just three steps.
- Yes, right there.
- That's the spot.
- Take it easy.
- No pressure.
- Nice one.
- Nicely done!
(The team leader
found her composure.)
There you go.
Use your hand.
(She boldly kicks the ball.)
- Move back.
- Young Ji!
The ball!
- Nice!
- What on earth was that?
Young Ji!
(Heo Young Ji scores
with a bold kick.)
How is she so good?
- Young Ji!
- Our Young Ji...
isn't on the athletic side.
Will you add a player
or take one out from their team?
- Sorry?
- Add or take out?
Please take her out of the court!
- Please take her out!
- We'll add a player.
Hey!
- Please take her out!
- We'll add a player.
Hey!
(Jong Kook enters the court
and So Min stays.)
Can't you let us play the game too?
We're not cheerleaders, you know.
Se Chan and...
- Ji Hyo...
- We can do this.
They haven't been able
to play at all.
Someone should be in the back
to receive the ball.
- This is like the Olympics.
- Here we go!
(The courageous Leader Heo
serves the ball.)
- We can do this!
- She's really good.
- With your hands.
- Your hands!
(Receive it with your hands!)
The one in the back
should've gotten it!
Why do you want to play?
Why do you want to play
foot volleyball with us?
Did you see them let the ball pass?
This was So Min.
(He teases their comedic moves.)
- That was...
- Hold on.
- You should've called it.
- Whose side are you on?
- Why didn't you call it?
- So Min.
You can either...
take So Min out
or keep playing as is.
Don't take her out.
We shouldn't take her out.
- We'll play as is.
- Sure thing.
- Play as is.
- Got it.
Team Heo Young Ji
won't take So Min out.
- We'll play as is.
- What?
Please take her out.
- No, we're good.
- Adhere to the rules.
- She's better off on her own.
- I know.
- Then...
- So Min, stand here instead.
All right.
I'll stay along this line.
- Go, go!
- Go for it.
- Nice.
- She's good at this.
Mine!
- Okay.
- Now send it over the net.
Wait. Didn't she just hold the ball?
- Send it over.
Didn't she just hold the ball?
- Double contact!
- No way.
- Look.
- Double contact.
- She held the ball.
- Exactly.
- That was double contact.
- Isn't that allowed?
- This...
- That was wrong.
So Min, how could you?
- I...
- How could you be this bad?
That's not it.
The ball can be hit three times.
Yes, but you held the ball.
I didn't.
The one behind should
receive the ball, okay?
Young Ji, So Min,
bounce it on your arms like so.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
Young Ji,
- your serves are superb.
- Take a few steps back.
(She reflects the serve!)
Take a few steps back.
(Oh, dear)
The one in the back
receives the serve!
Darn it!
(The one in the back
receives the serve!)
(Coach Ha has had it.)
Oh, no.
(He speaks for everyone benched.)
I know what should be done,
but I can't do it.
- I want to do better, you know.
- You're killing me.
- I...
- The one in the back.
The one in the back
should receive the serve.
Okay, the one in the back.
- Stay calm.
- We still have a chance.
Young Ji!
Young Ji, calm down.
Let's do this!
- Okay.
- Nice.
Young Ji's doing so well.
- She's the best.
- Get the ball.
Mine.
- Send it over the net.
- Over the net.
(She sends it flying
without looking first.)
Send it over the net!
(Coach Ha is close to tears.)
How can you be so bad at this?
But we did a good job this time.
- We did.
- That was good.
- We had good chemistry.
- We did a good job.
- It was awesome.
- Wait.
Did you hear them just now?
- They complimented each other.
- Good job.
Why don't you receive the serve?
- Okay, I will.
- We've got this!
How is Young Ji so good at this?
- She's the best.
- The absolute best.
- Look at that.
- Receive it.
(The ball drops on the edge
of the court.)
- There you go.
- Hit it, So Min.
- That's good.
Pass it to her.
- She got it.
- It's coming.
- It's coming. There you go.
- Well done.
There you go!
(Team Lee Young Ji
scores for the first time.)
We did it!
(So Min and Young Ji embrace
each other as they're deeply moved.)
(A miracle came to them
when they were about to give up)
We won, right?
So Min, you can do it.
This is how you play.
You could do it because
you pulled yourself together.
- You never know.
- I'm so happy.
(It's okay.)
That was great.
Well done, Young Ji.
I won't yell at you anymore.
- So Min, you did well too.
- Good job.
- You did well.
- So Min, good job.
Take it easy. You can do it.
- Praise breeds willingness.
- Let's go!
- Take it easy.
- Take it easy. Well done.
- There you go!
- There you go.
- She's good.
- That was a good kick.
- That's good.
- Well done.
- Young Ji, toss it over.
- That's it.
- Receive it. Take it easy.
- There you go.
- Good one.
- Young Ji, come! Attack them!
- Pass it. What are you doing?
Why aren't you moving?
- Good one.
- Young Ji, come! Attack them!
(She just stretches herself
without budging her feet.)
(Why aren't you moving?)
- I did move!
- What was that?
- That was...
- I did move!
- Why didn't you move?
Pass me the ball.
So Min, as long as
you're having fun, it's all good.
I'm going to die out of frustration.
It's so funny that you guys
don't get to play.
Ji Hyo and I didn't get to play
at all.
- You can do it.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Young Ji is really good.
- Pass it forward.
- She's really good.
- The court is too big.
Use your hands. Pass it forward.
- Use your hands. Pass it forward.
- That's it.
She did it.
(Stealthily touching the ball
twice in a row)
- That's it. Young Ji touched it.
- We got it.
- Go! Attack them, Young Ji!
- It's over.
- She did it!
- No, that doesn't count.
- Nice. She did it.
- No, it was double contact.
- Just let it slide this time.
- Let it slide.
But she...
I want to let this go for once.
- We'll let it slide.
I want to let it slide.
Will you add a player or remove one?
- We'll add one.
- Let's add one more player.
(Thanks to Captain Lee,
they get to add another player.)
- If Suk Jin joins...
- Please!
Let it be Suk Jin.
(Who will be joining
to play this time?)
- Se Chan.
- All right!
(Se Chan will join the game.)
- Se Chan.
- All right!
Let's go to the finals.
(Se Chan joins the game
when his team is losing.)
We got this now!
He'll defend,
so you two should move up.
You two should move up.
I'll head the ball to you guys.
- I'll head the ball to you guys.
- You should spike the ball.
Even if he...
Even if he receives the serve,
So Min...
- It's either Young Ji or So Min.
- Then Young Ji can receive it.
- We can toss the ball over.
- That's right.
Serve it well.
(After a deep breath,)
(Se Chan takes the serve.)
- That's it.
- Here it comes.
- I got it.
- Young Ji!
- Use your hands, Young Ji!
That was good.
(Young Ji tosses it over short,
avoiding Se Chan.)
(Tapping)
(Young Ji saves it!)
- You should block it!
- Toss it over!
- Young Ji!
- That's it.
(Hitting the ball multiple times)
- You should block it!
- Toss it over!
- That's it.
(She flapped her hands in the air.)
Are you doing a karate chop?
That was a fail.
(Laughing)
It's so funny
that they don't get to play.
They can't even toss the ball over.
(Their play is so clumsy that
their teammate can't join to play.)
Forget it!
(So Min finds it absurd herself.)
Hey.
(Drawing a player
to remove from Team Lee Young Ji)
(Se Chan is out.)
Se Chan will be removed.
But I played only once!
- That's so mean.
- I played only once.
That's so mean.
Let's have Se Chan removed.
- That's so mean.
- I only got to kick once!
(Se Chan is so upset
that he can't close his mouth.)
Remove him. All right.
So Min isn't even disappointed.
I'm having so much fun, but...
What's the score?
Do we not have it yet?
- It's their match point.
- What did you say?
- It's their match point already?
Ji Hyo never even got to play.
And I only got to play once.
We can do it.
I want to play too.
It's okay as long as we don't
give up. Let's show a miracle.
- I'll receive the ball.
- She's really good.
Let's finish this.
(It's Captain Heo's serve.)
- She's really good.
- I got it!
- Receive it!
- Use your hands!
(Young Ji's receive)
- Don't be nervous.
- Get the ball!
(And So Min's toss)
- That's good! Now spike it!
- Spike!
Darn it!
Nice!
- Now spike it!
- Spike!
(She spiked the ball into the net.)
I did spike the ball.
Well begun is half done!
But you were supposed to
toss it over.
(They take the victory
with the minimum effort.)
It was not fun at all!
- What was that?
- It's absurd.
Jong Kook,
what kind of rule is this?
- We didn't get to play at all.
- This is so absurd.
This is absurd.
(Captain Heo
is laughing out of joy.)
The commentating ends here.
- My goodness.
- The winner is...
- Why are your serves so sharp?
- Team Heo Young Ji.
Lee Young Ji will lose six points.
(Captain Lee loses 6 points.)
And Heo Young Ji will distribute
15 points to her teammates.
All right!
Jae Suk and Jong Kook,
get your points.
- My goodness.
- Young Ji.
- Yes?
- You must be different from her.
I don't know if it's okay
to take these points.
I know. This is embarrassing.
- Good work!
- Thanks.
- I don't know if this is okay.
- This is...
(They take the point card
that Young Ji wrote.)
(They got only 1 point each
from Lee Young Ji in Round 1.)
(How many points
did Captain Heo give to them?)
She's such a scum.
- Jae Suk, don't be...
- Young Ji, you are...
I mean... Goodness, this is...
(Stupefied)
You've got to be kidding me.
- Gosh, this is...
- Both Young Ji's are...
How many points did she give out
that she ran away?
That was hilarious.
Let's have fun.
It's time to choose your team
for Round Three.
The two captains
will stay inside the room,
and the rest will take turns
to choose their team.
It looks like...
they're both stingy
in giving out points.
Let's do this! Pfizer!
Wait.
I came to Lee Young Ji when I was
thinking of joining Heo Young Ji.
- Let's do this!
- I bet we'll play a quiz this time.
- What's the capital of Switzerland?
- We'll be playing a quiz.
- Isn't it Geneva?
- Geneva?
- What about the capital of Africa?
- I'll tell you.
Which country from Africa?
- Oh, a country from Africa?
- Africa is a continent.
Right.
- I'm in big trouble.
- Africa is a continent.
(Lee Young Ji doesn't seem
that different from Heo Young Ji.)
- What's the capital of Australia?
- Australia?
It's Australia, right?
- Yes, it is.
- Australia is known for kangaroos.
They have kangaroos.
They also have nice sceneries.
And most of their cuisines
are greasy.
(It looks like Suk Jin
has come across a big obstacle.)
- What about Malaysia?
- Malaysia.
- It begins with "Ku".
- Malaysia. "Ku"?
- "Ku".
- "Ku"? The rice cooker brand?
It's Cuckoo.
- It begins with "Kuala".
- "Kuala"?
Yes, it's Kuala...
Kuala Guskida Dudalmans.
- It's Kuala Lum...
- Kuala Lumbalumba? Kuala Lumpur.
It's Kuala Lumpur.
What? How do you know all this?
- It's Kuala Lumpur.
- Oh, I see.
Suk Jin is here.
All right. We'll win
if we play a quiz.
(Ji Hyo joins
Team Lee Young Ji too.)
- Kuala Lumpur.
- What's she doing here?
- She knows the capital of Malaysia.
- What's the capital of Malaysia?
Manila.
- She doesn't know.
- Malaysia?
She sounds so confident.
Ji Hyo, don't use
your brain already.
- Keyser Soze
- All right, we're all set.
- Sonador and Sparta
The teams are decided.
- It's over?
- Really?
- No one else is coming?
- This is it?
We'll play a simple mission
before lunch.
While we prepare lunch,
we'll play a simple mission.
Then will we switch teams again
after that?
- If it's a simple mission...
- Then it won't be a quiz.
- Because a quiz is the main event.
- That's right.
(What's the mission
they will play next?)
It's our lunch!
(They're having lunch
after selecting their teams.)
There are so many different dishes.
(All kinds of food
are waiting for them.)
They all look so good.
It's dumpling hot pot.
There's chocolate ice cream.
It's my favorite!
I guess we take a dish each
once we win something.
There's a xylophone.
It looks like we'll play a quiz.
- We're playing a quiz.
- It looks like we'll play a quiz.
(The new Empty Head is intimidated.)
I feel like I have
an upset stomach already.
- What's 7 times 4?
- It's 28.
Everyone, here's the next mission.
If you answer
as many questions as you can,
you'll get to have a hearty meal.
- We're in trouble.
- We got this!
It's called Empty Heads' Lunch.
(Empty Heads' Lunch)
- We're in trouble.
- We got this!
We're playing a quiz?
(Team Heo Young Ji
quickly becomes downbeat.)
Didn't you say...
that we'll have lunch
after a simple mission?
Actually, I'm not that hungry.
No, we never know. We can do this.
I'll just trust Jong Kook.
- We can do it, Young Ji. It's okay.
- Let's trust Jong Kook.
- We can do this.
- Let's trust him and play.
- Let's do this.
- The capital of Italy is Paris.
- What did you say?
- We're done for.
(Did I hear her wrong?)
- How is Paris the capital of Italy?
- The capital of Italy is Paris.
- It's Rome.
- Where was it again?
- Lapura Pumpura?
- Kuala Lumpur.
It's not Lapura Pumpura.
It's Kuala Lumpur.
- Kuala Lumpra.
- It's the capital of Malaysia.
- What about Mongolia?
- Kuala Lumpra.
- Mongolia?
- Ulaanbaatar.
- Ulaanbar?
- What's Ulaanbar?
- The food prepared behind you...
is your lunch for today.
I want to eat it so badly.
Each player from each team
will come forward to play.
They'll answer a question
related to each dish.
The one who wins
will earn that dish.
- It's a quiz related to food.
- It could be difficult.
- I've had a lot of dishes.
- It's related to food?
The team that earns more dishes
among the 11 dishes wins.
And you can have your lunch
with the dishes you earned.
We never know though.
It's a quiz related to food.
But I think
we'll be better than them.
(He's already panicking.)
(How do you spell ice cream?)
How do you spell ice cream?
I, C, E...
- I think we'll be able to answer.
- C, I?
How do you spell cream?
Let's study.
What about pasta? P, A...
He's thinking of the spelling
for ice cream.
He went, "I, C, E".
- He's studying spelling.
- I'm studying spelling.
- How do you spell "Yookgaejang"?
- First of all,
decide which player...
will go first from each team.
Okay. But the order
doesn't really matter.
- It doesn't matter.
- Let's just go in this order.
- Let me go up against Ji Hyo.
Okay.
So Min wants to
go up against Ji Hyo.
Me too.
- I want to go up against Ji Hyo.
- I love her so much.
How come no one wants to
go up against Haha?
- He's gotten smarter.
- I'm on another level.
"Another level"?
The first dish is the appetizer
behind you.
- It's a roast chicken salad.
- It looks good.
Oh, it's a chicken salad.
If you know the answer,
shout out, "Answer".
- Young Ji.
- Then you can answer.
- Here we go. I got this.
- Let's go.
It's a question related
to a roast chicken salad.
The president of the US,
President Joe Biden...
said his favorite dish
is roast chicken salad.
Taking that into consideration,
what is the full name of...
the Vice President
of the United States?
- What?
- He mentioned it earlier.
(How is roast chicken salad related
to the Vice President of the US?)
- Didn't you say...
- They don't know the answer.
- this was a food question?
- I know.
I was going to say
balsamic vinaigrette.
- Gosh.
- Why?
The Vice President...
You mentioned it last time.
It came out on Running Man.
- It did!
- Don't look back.
(The Vice President of the US
is a familiar question.)
I know it.
I mentioned it last time.
I know.
(In Episode 533)
(The answer: Kamala Harris)
(Jae Suk said the Vice President's
full name correctly.)
Even though it came out on our show,
I bet these two don't know it.
- I don't remember.
- Isn't it Headbelt?
(Isn't it Headbelt?)
(What's the full name of
the Vice President of the US?)
- Hey!
- It's not?
(They don't seem
to have a clue either.)
Okay. I'll give you a hint.
It's a woman.
Right.
- Emily.
- Hold on.
(Exclaiming)
- Was I close?
- No.
Her first name has 3 syllables,
and her last name has 3 syllables.
Emily Houston.
That was good. Go in that direction.
Emily Pumbaa.
- I'll give you her initials.
- Okay.
(They gave them her initials.)
- It's quite easy.
- Okay.
This is it.
- Do you remember?
- Answer! Kamila Herris.
- It's close.
- Herris.
(She sounds so confident
that we thought she was right.)
- Answer! Kamira Harris.
- That's wrong.
Kamula Harris.
- You're almost there.
- Kamela Harris.
Kamera Harris.
Kamera?
Kamira Harris.
Kamula.
Kamila. Kamala.
Kamal... Hold on!
- She didn't say, "Answer".
- Kamala!
(She took a bunch of wild guesses
and got it right.)
- Kamala.
- Kamala Harris.
- That's right. Kamala Harris.
- Hold on.
- How it's read is different.
I'm struggling to be heard
next to Young Ji.
- She's louder than me.
- You have to be louder.
- I really do.
- You can take the salad with you.
- Okay!
- Yes.
It's Yang Se Chan
versus Yoo Jae Suk now.
Okay. Very good.
- What's important is...
- Who's Se Chan up against?
- Jae Suk.
- Okay. Very good.
- I'll try to win.
- Go for it!
- This is good.
- Try to win.
- Try winning.
- You can win! We're going to eat.
This next dish is japchae.
- Japchae?
We have to win this!
- Japchae is good. Jang Geum!
- This is ours.
- This is a traditional dish.
- It might be a question...
- about Korea.
- We have a chance.
Japchae came to be what it is now
when a glass noodle factory...
was built in Hwanghae Province
in North Korea in the 1920s.
- And?
- Right.
How do you say, "I had ramyeon
and now my sphincter hurts."
"Can I get some medicine?"
in the North Korean dialect?
What? All of a sudden?
How do you say, "I had ramyeon
and now my sphincter hurts."
(What? All of a sudden?)
- This is a good one.
- What kind of question is this?
Hard questions like this...
- Give him a chance.
- He might get it right.
- Answer.
- Okay.
Well, I consumed some ramyeon,
(An unknown dialect and a man
whose legs can't stop shaking)
and my sphincter hurts.
- Say butthole instead of sphincter.
- This is wrong.
(Wrong)
Well, I had some ramyeon,
and my backside hurts.
Can you give me something
to put on it?
There's a separate word for
ramyeon and sphincter.
- There's a word for them.
- Anal control.
The word for ramyeon
is pretty famous.
- Okay. Answer!
- Ramyeon?
- I ate some curly noodles,
- Curly noodles.
and the hole where
my poop comes out...
(The hole where poop comes out)
(He got graphic when asked
to speak in a North Korean dialect.)
Curly noodles must be right.
Good job. That was so exact.
It was good. Very direct.
Ramyeon was close.
- Answer.
- Really?
- Answer. Curly noodles...
I ate some curly noodles,
and my rear hurts.
- Can you give me some medicine?
- This could be right.
Your rear shouldn't hurt.
I had some curly noodles,
and I... Well... I...
- What is the word for sphincter?
- The... Well...
The thing that's in your rear...
It has wrinkles...
Why is the explanation so detailed?
- It's too...
- Right.
They call it an anus in the South...
That part hurts,
so can you give me some medicine?
It starts with a "C",
but it's not "curly".
and it's similar.
- I think it's curled noodles,
- What's sphincter though?
- but I don't know "sphincter".
- "Sphincter" is hard.
Sphincter ends with "skin".
- Skin?
- Anal skin?
- Anus?
- Anus is from Chinese characters.
- Anus... Oh, right.
- Answer!
- Okay.
I ate some curled noodles,
and...
Stop touching your butt!
(His hands go to his rear
instinctually.)
Why do you keep doing that?
Why do you keep
touching your bottom?
You just need to think of a word.
Why do you keep doing that?
I was hoping it would help...
- What is it?
- What's a word for tightening?
(Tightening?)
(Answer!)
Answer!
I had curled noodles,
and my pursing skin hurts.
Can you give me some medicine?
Yes!
- Japchae! Japchae!
- Pursing skin?
(They were hoping for a twist,
but there wasn't one.)
- Japchae! Japchae!
- Japchae.
(Team Lee Young Ji gets the japchae
thanks to Jae Suk's quick wits.)
- Pursing skin.
- Pursing skin?
- Okay. Very good.
- Okay.
- I'm going to win!
- You can do it!
I can do it!
There's a brunch dish, right?
- Yes, there is.
- Yes. Toast.
It looks very filling.
In Western countries,
they have...
bacon, scrambled eggs, sausages,
and potatoes for brunch.
- Right.
- If that's the case,
what is the famous quote that...
the British philosopher,
Francis Bacon said?
(Bacon?)
Cook it slightly.
Bacon tastes best
when it's cooked over low heat.
- Bacon...
- It's best cooked over low heat.
- Bacon's famous quote...
- You see it in bathrooms often.
A famous quote.
Everyone knows this quote.
It's a famous quote.
- Bacon said it?
- Everyone knows this.
Bacon said this in the bathroom?
- It's a quote.
- "Know thyself." That's Socrates.
- Bacon is a philosopher.
- Right. You know this quote.
- We know it? He's a philosopher?
- We all know this quote.
- Answer.
- It's the most famous quote.
Marriage and death
are best done late.
- Hey.
- That's not right.
Isn't that your saying?
("Marriage and death are
best done late." By JiSuk Jin)
(A famous quote by
the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong)
- Is that your philosophy on life?
- That's just something you say.
That's not it.
- That's not it.
That's just something you say.
I wonder what the answer is.
- Bacon.
- Is it related to bacon?
- No.
- No. That's his name.
- The philosopher's name is Bacon.
- A British philosopher.
The three of us
were talking about bacon.
I thought it was an idiom
about bacon.
This is the first quote
that comes to mind...
- when you think philosopher.
- Really?
Answer! "Tears aren't the only
thing that men must not spill."
- That's about using the bathroom!
- What are you saying?
- Why would you say that?
- I just lost my appetite.
Seriously.
This quote is perfect
for this situation.
- That's right.
- It's true.
This suits the empty heads.
- It suits the empty heads?
- Answer!
"Knowledge is power"?
- That's the answer!
- See? I was right.
"Knowledge is power"?
(All he ended up doing was saying
his own quotes.)
It was this easy?
Really?
This wasn't said by someone
from Korea?
("Knowledge is power" wasn't said
by someone from Korea?)
- Suk Jin...
- This was the answer?
- This was Bacon?
- When it was our turns,
- he kept criticizing us.
- What was his name again?
- Francis Bacon.
- I should remember this.
Bacon.
"Knowledge is power".
- Go.
- Ji Hyo, go up.
Let's go, Ji Hyo.
The main event is here.
Let's go.
(Up against Ji Hyo is...)
- Jeon So Min, let's go!
- Ji Hyo.
- Me?
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo. Be confident.
- You can do it!
- Just...
- "Knowledge is power." Bacon.
- say what comes to mind.
- Okay.
"Knowledge is power."
by Francis Bacon.
(The person behind the legendary
Jeoktoma Answer Case, Song Ji Hyo)
I can do this.
(So Min is trying to make up for
Ambrella.)
This is the match of the century.
(The match of the century)
They look down on one another.
(Jeon So Min vs. Song Ji Hyo)
The next dish is pizza.
We can't miss out on this.
- Come on!
- This is the question for pizza.
When you order pizza, they try to
make sure the slices are the same.
Then what do you call a triangle
with two sides that are the same?
(What do you call a triangle
with two sides that are the same?)
This is really easy!
- You can't give her a hint.
- This is so easy!
Do you know the answer?
(This question comes out in math
textbooks for elementary school.)
- Triangle?
- It's a type of triangle...
I know this.
- It's...
- I know this.
It's a triangle where two sides
are the same length.
(A triangle where two sides
are the same length?)
A triangle?
Answer. An equilateral.
(Correct)
(Make some noise for Song Jeoktoma!)
You got it!
(The empty head siblings
didn't know the answer.)
You got it!
(Ji Hyo remembers what she learned
in grade school math.)
- You got it!
- How did you know this?
The pizza is shaped like
an equilateral!
- How did you know this?
- You knew this?
(Song Ji Hyo sets a record
of 2 answers this season.)
Why are you guys so surprised?
- How did you know this?
- You're so cool!
- It just came to mind.
- Take a seat here.
- That was incredible.
- Jeon So Min is done for.
- Seriously.
(After Song Jeoktoma
got the answer right,)
(she turned pale and froze
in her seat.)
- I... I didn't even get to speak.
- Good try.
I didn't know the answer either.
(She gets dragged out while being
comforted by the empty heads.)
We have a lot of people
who have been injured.
Go up there and hit your head twice.
- I didn't get to speak.
- Heory up and do that.
That's right. Good.
This next dish is dumplings.
- Dumplings, dumplings
Lee Young Ji's favorite food
is dumplings.
- Right. Dumplings.
- Me?
- Why?
That's what it said.
Many people like dumplings, and
in Korean, they're called "mandu".
There is a city
with "mandu" in its name.
Please say the name of the city
and the country it's in.
- Don't say the answer.
- What?
The city and the country it's in.
Is it abroad?
Yes. The city that has "mandu"
in its name...
- There is such a place.
- and the country it's in.
- Where is it?
- A city with "mandu" in it?
Is it an English-speaking country?
(Do you know it?)
Kathmandu.
You'll know it once you hear it.
- Right. You've heard of it.
- Really?
- Okay. Yes.
- It has "mandu" in it?
- Answer. It's...
- I keep thinking Deli Mandu.
- Why does that keep coming to mind?
- Answer. Chengdo Mando in China?
(Qingdao dumplings, China?, Wrong!)
- Qingdao dumplings, China.
- He doesn't disappoint.
Qingdao dumplings, China.
(Does he think
it's like a regional specialty?)
- Qingdao dumplings, China.
- He doesn't disappoint.
He is quite the empty head.
I admire his courage.
Dumplings are famous in China.
The name of the city
contains "Mandu", dumplings.
Is it a city in India?
- I will give you a hint.
- Okay.
It has four syllables.
- This quiz is really hard.
- Four syllables?
Are you sure
it isn't "Qingda dumplings"?
Qingdao is famous for dumplings.
I am not talking about
a regional specialty.
It can't be kimchi dumpling.
- It can't be Myungin Dumplings.
- You forget when you don't use it.
- It isn't Myungin Dumplings.
- Indian dumplings.
- No.
(They go over each country.)
China. Japan.
The first letter is K.
Katanmandu.
- Katanmandu.
- Let me answer. Katumandu.
- It's similar.
- Let me answer. Katukmandu.
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer. Katyukmandu.
Incorrect.
- Katermandu.
- Let me answer. Katekmandu.
- Incorrect.
- Katalmandu.
- Let me answer. Katakmandu.
- Incorrect.
- I have never heard of it.
- It starts with K, right?
- Katilmandu.
- You know what it is.
Katumandu.
Let me answer. Katermandu.
The name of the city is Kathmandu.
- Yes.
- In which country is it?
You have heard of Kathmandu.
- The answer has two syllables.
- Kathmandu.
Thailand.
- An Asian country hikers go to.
- An Asian country hikers go to?
Qingdao.
Qingdao. Just say it's correct.
- The country has many mountains.
- That's right.
- Which country is it?
- This hint will end the round.
Here are the first letters
of the syllables.
- He practically gave the answer.
- Let me answer.
- Nepal.
Okay. Nepal.
Nepal.
Good job.
In Korea, Jeonju is famous
for bibimbap.
- Jeonju.
Listen to the intro of the song...
and guess the song title
and the singer.
Let me answer.
"I Believe" by Shin Seung Hun.
- Okay.
- That's right.
Gwanggaeto the Great, King Jangsu.
There you go.
(Ji Hyo gets
another question right.)
Let me answer. Over the top.
There you go.
- Gosh.
- Nice.
I feel hot.
- I feel hot.
- Isn't "Over the Top" a movie?
That was painful.
Before we will give you
the dishes you acquired,
the points will be distributed.
- Team Lee Young Ji won.
- Okay.
- Young Ji.
- Lee Young Ji.
- Young Ji, you have many points.
- How many points do we get?
- You get 25 points.
- We get 25 points.
- Young Ji.
Heo Young Ji, your team gets
minus four points.
- Young Ji.
- I believe in you.
I got all the questions right.
Some people didn't get
any questions right.
Please remember that.
Was that the last game?
- There will be one more game.
- I see.
- Young Ji.
- Come on.
- Why do you even need to think?
- Young Ji.
I doubt she will give me...
more than one point.
- Young Ji.
- I am hoping for two points.
Jae Suk has enough points.
Young Ji, remember that.
(Will she be loyal to the team
in distributing the points?)
If you gave one point per person,
I won't stand still.
I didn't do that.
- I did my best.
- Really?
- Come and check in turns.
- Let's go.
I didn't give one point per person.
I bet I got more points
than the others this time.
- Young Ji...
- Young Ji, hide.
I can't believe her.
For goodness' sake.
- She is unbelievable.
- She ran away.
How could she give me zero points?
Not even Kwang Soo gave zero points.
I was told not to give one point.
- Still...
- I had to be certain.
- Zero points?
- This is what I received...
- for the 1st time today.
- I was told not to give 1 point.
Thank you for your hard work.
- You are amazing. Team play.
- Jae Suk.
- Join this team.
- We are the team.
- I can't believe her.
- She gives points.
- This is just wrong, right?
- Next time,
- I will choose Heo Young Ji.
- She is considerate.
- I thought that was 6.
- You should at least give 1 point.
Enjoy the food.
- It's so tasty.
- It's good.
(They have lunch with food
for each team.)
Captains, go ahead.
(It's time to choose the team.)
Do you know what my dad texted me?
(Young Ji's dad texted her.)
"When you have a quiz
during the shoot of Running Man,"
"don't get scared and stay calm."
"You know the answers
to those questions."
"Good luck."
But I couldn't answer
a single question today.
(She couldn't keep her promise
to her dad.)
Dad, I am sorry.
The last time...
What my dad said has a problem.
Staying calm didn't get me anywhere
the last time.
(Staying calm didn't get me anywhere
the last time.)
He doesn't know his daughter
very well.
How many points do I have right now?
You have 32 points.
(Lee Young Ji has 32 points.)
I have no conscience whatsoever.
I have 32 points.
That's good. I am full.
The team that wins the last game
will be exempt from the penalty.
The captain will give one point
at the very least.
- Lee Young Ji has many points now.
- I know.
- So naturally...
- Lee Young Ji?
She has no reason
to hoard more points.
- Seriously.
- But you never know.
It's not like you can use
those points.
(Will Young Ji make such a decision
as Jong Kook claims?)
I am full. I think
I can distribute the points now.
Welcome.
Welcome
(So Min enters.)
(Jae Suk enters as well.)
Young Ji, I will trust you
once more.
Young Ji.
You and I share blood.
We don't share blood,
but you know what I mean.
What? He came again.
What?
- Haha came here.
- I stayed loyal to you.
Welcome.
There are too many people here.
(5 members came to Captain Lee.)
And...
Ji Hyo came.
- Ji Hyo.
- There are so many people.
Did you come here to avoid changing?
(That's right.)
There isn't a place to sit.
I won't cry
even if no one chooses me.
(She mumbles to herself...)
I will stay strong.
(and fills the room with sound.)
(The crew in the other room
asks for help.)
That room needs more cameras.
Isn't that right?
(Taking off)
Everyone is leaving.
(The cameraman decided
to help the crew in the other room.)
(He escapes the empty room
without looking back.)
This is too much.
(She fills the audio
with the sound of her crying.)
(It's 1 minute before the end
of the team selection.)
(Opening)
For goodness' sake. Is no one here?
Is no one here?
(Jong Kook came.)
How have you lived your life?
- I have wasted my life.
- Sit down, Young Ji.
I guessed correctly.
- I said you will be loyal.
- Really?
That's right.
I am all about loyalty.
- What?
- Who is that?
(At that moment,)
(Se Chan appears.)
- My goodness.
- Se Chan.
Are these all the members?
I guess so.
I didn't feel like changing.
Don't say something so mean.
- I know. You should be nicer.
- Seriously.
I was joking.
Young Ji, here is the thing.
You should treat us properly.
We should win no matter what,
and you should give us
as many points as possible...
so that the 2nd place and 3rd place
can come from this team.
Do you know what I mean?
If we win this time,
keep your word.
- Of course.
- Okay?
- Trust me.
- Let's say we win.
You have more points
than Heo Young Ji.
- That's right. I have many points.
- She has zero points.
- If we get all the points,
- That's right.
- you can distribute all of them.
- That team will lose points.
Even if you do that,
you will take first place.
- I will take first place.
- That's right.
- We will have all the points.
Would you give me two points?
I will give you all the points.
You don't need to worry.
You joined that team.
No one wanted to change.
- It's too much work.
- I had the same thought.
Too many people have zero points.
- Zero points.
- Seriously.
- It's a match for 1 point.
- Yes. It's a match for 1 point.
Now comes the last mission.
- I want to win.
- To have a fierce match...
we chose a game...
- you have played before.
- What is it?
(The last mission will determine
who gets the penalty!)
This mission...
will let you learn about
each other's image.
It's Good Image.
I know what it is.
- You sing, "Good image."
- We have a chance of winning.
(When the offensive team says
the image and number,)
(the defensive team members
who suit the image must answer.)
(You fail to defend
if 2 or more members...)
(or no one answers.)
Hey.
We are at a disadvantage
since there are more members.
We just need to respond
in three beats, right?
Let's start there.
When you get used to it,
- we will reduce it to two beats.
- Okay.
- We will attack first.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Good image.
- Let's go.
- Good...
- Let's begin.
Good...
- Good...
- Tell him not to exhaust himself.
- Don't exhaust yourself!
You are bored, right?
(They live for the intro.)
- Good...
- Good image
Blue T-shirt, four.
Blue T-shirt, blue T-shirt,
blue T-shirt, blue T-shirt.
A 40-year-old, 4.
A 40-year-old, a 40-year-old,
a 40-year-old, a 40-year-old.
(A 40-year-old succeeded in
defending.)
- A 40-year-old, a 40-year-old.
- Good job.
He's not going to make it.
(The muscular man in his 40s
became speechless.)
(Generation MZ defeated
the man in his 40s.)
- Good job.
- Young Ji!
- For goodness' sake.
- Young Ji.
- That was great.
- What was that?
(Team Lee Young Ji won 1 point!)
You have a nice tone
since you are a rapper.
Good job.
This time,
Team Blue will attack first.
- Good...
It gets tiring
when you team up with Haha.
(The intro artists focus more
on the intro than the actual game.)
(DJ Haha's intro is chaotic.)
Boom!
- Good image
My boyfriend, two.
(My boyfriend, two.)
(He stalls as much as he can.)
Boyfriend, boyfriend.
(Boyfriend, boyfriend.)
Pink panties, three.
(Pink panties, three.)
Pink panties, pink panties,
pink panties.
My boyfriend, three.
(My boyfriend, three.)
(It's too cringeworthy for him.)
Boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend.
- That's good.
Hairy ears, three.
That sounded strange.
You missed the beat.
- I did well, right?
- "My boyfriend" was a good one.
- My boyfriend.
I got so annoyed.
Both of them were annoyed
by the attack.
- "Boyfriend, boyfriend..."
- Seriously.
- I fell for it.
- "My boyfriend" was a good one.
It's fascinating
that each one has a girl.
that both of them know it.
They paired up nicely.
- They paired up nicely.
- For goodness' sake.
We can do this
now that Kwang Soo quit.
- Seriously.
- The number is perfect.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Good...
(Generation MZ does
the shoulder dance.)
(Here comes
the circus troupe of intro.)
- Good...
(The intro enthusiast
is back again.)
Good...
- Good...
- Start the game already!
(He uses 50 percent of his energy
before the game begins.)
Good image
- There you go.
- Heory up.
(That's my type.)
- Good image
Long hair, two.
- Long hair, long hair.
- There you go.
Short temper, three.
(Short temper, three.)
Short temper, short temper,
short temper.
(Short temper, short temper,
short temper.)
(The description went
to the rightful owner.)
Married man, two.
- Married man, married man.
- Okay.
(The attack on the married men
was successful!)
Two people responded.
- Okay.
- I signaled that I will respond.
I did this.
For goodness' sake.
Why did you butt in?
I signaled that I will respond.
I thought you were telling me
to do it.
This is driving me crazy.
For goodness' sake.
Only someone who is happily married
should respond.
- I am happily married.
- Someone who is happily married.
I will respond.
- I will respond.
- Okay.
Se Chan, it's your turn to attack.
I will go slowly.
- Good image
- Good
- How good?
- Very good
Who is good?
- Good image
- Good
Even if it's good,
it's just the image
Good
What's good, money or image?
- Good
I will begin now
- Good image
Bald, three.
(Bald, three!)
Bald, bald, bald.
(Bald, bald, bald.)
Middle age, four.
Middle age, middle age,
middle age, middle age.
Mom, three.
(Mom, three.)
Mom, mom, mom.
(She is a member of Generation MZ
who goes along with anything.)
All right.
So Min, four.
What was "All right"?
- What did she do wrong?
- It was just a rejoinder.
- It isn't allowed.
- It isn't allowed in Good Image.
- Seriously.
- It was like a booster.
- It's confusing with a mistake.
- That's right.
- It isn't allowed.
- Good job.
- Come on.
Good job.
- We did well.
- We were close to winning.
I can't think of any descriptions.
- Let's resume.
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, you avoid
all the descriptions.
He didn't respond to "Bald".
You act like
you didn't hear anything.
You avoided it so many times.
- Respond.
- He is Jamwon-dong's loach.
- He slips out.
- Jamwon-dong's loach.
- He doesn't respond.
- Let's take this to the end.
- Take "Bald".
- I will do that.
"Bald" and "Hair fiber"
should go to Suk Jin.
It's not like he is
a world-renowned celebrity.
Why does he care so much
about his image?
Those are nice descriptions.
The name is Good Image, after all.
Anyone can see
that he is 56 years old.
Voluminous.
- Voluminous.
- For goodness' sake.
Very voluminous.
- That's so funny.
- Voluminous.
Jong Kook, it's your turn to start.
Can you give us a ballad version?
- Good
- Good image
Good image
That's nice.
- Good image
- That's a ballad song.
- It's melodious.
- I like it
- Good image
- Oh, image
(He adds the cheap chorus.)
I like it
What?
(The slow-witted and flippant man
gets smacked.)
Who did that?
- Who did that?
- Who hit me while I was absorbed?
- I was adding ad-libs.
- Who did that during the game?
- Who did that?
We can't find the culprit.
I will let you off
since I am in a good mood.
Suk Jin is much older than us.
Who did that?
- I was doing so well.
- I won't stand still.
- We are sorry.
- Don't mess up.
- Don't do it again.
We are sorry.
- Seriously.
- I was absorbed in the feelings.
- Okay.
- Good...
- Good image
Han Min Kwan, three.
(Clenching her teeth)
Han Min Kwan, Han Min Kwan,
Han Min Kwan.
Mama's boy, two.
(Mama's boy, two.)
Mama's boy, mama's boy.
(He barely defends...)
Age spot, three.
(and strikes back with "Age spot".)
Age spot, age spot, age spot.
Shortie, two.
Shortie, shortie.
Bald, three.
(Bald, three.)
Bald, bald, bald.
So Min, four.
(She attacks with "So Min".)
So Min, So Min, So Min, So Min.
A 40-year-old, 2.
A 40-year-old, a 40-year-old,
a 40-year-old, a 40-year-old.
A 40-year-old, 2.
- Really?
- What was that?
- It was 2.
- A 40-year-old, 2.
- You are in your 40s too.
- You couldn't hear him well.
You are in your 40s.
Se Chan, your pronunciation is
so bad.
- A 40-year-old, 2.
- I could hear him clearly.
- Seriously.
- I can't attack them.
- It's hard to come up with one.
- Just do it.
Just say, "Eunuch, three."
- It's a word from a dictionary.
- "Eunuch, three"?
- Just do it. It's okay.
- I will respond.
- Okay.
- Eunuch, eunuch, eunuch.
(Big Nose instructs them
to attack ruthlessly.)
- Go ahead.
- Good...
- Good image
Hair fiber, four.
Hair fiber, hair fiber,
hair fiber, hair fiber.
My dear, two.
(My dear, two.)
My dear, my dear.
- What?
- Nose hair, two.
(Young Ji took the attack.)
Nose hair, nose hair.
Nose hair, three.
(The nose hair rally begins.)
Nose hair, nose hair, nose hair.
Age spot, three.
(Age spot, three.)
- Age spot, age spot...
Why did you butt in?
The attacks were directed at me.
- You didn't respond before.
- Seriously.
- The attacks were directed at me.
- Suk Jin messed up.
You didn't respond before.
(Suk Jin responds erratically.)
- Age spot.
- Why did you butt in?
I was taking all the attacks.
You didn't respond
to "Age spot" before.
That's why Jae Suk did it.
Why did you respond?
(The worst chemistry
leaves both of them flustered.)
All right.
Now, you must respond in two beats.
- You got used to the game.
- Okay.
- Two beats?
His face turned red.
This team has many members,
so we are at a disadvantage.
We should have started
with three points.
Who are you talking to?
Seriously.
All right.
Don't follow that figure.
Grim Reaper, three.
Grim Reaper, Grim Reaper,
Grim Reaper.
(He responds
to "Grim Reaper, three.")
He responded to that one.
Are you going to respond or not?
- Let's go.
- I don't know.
- This is scary.
- Don't do that again.
- Okay.
- Let's go, Jae Suk.
- Let's go.
- Go slowly.
- Slowly.
- Good image
Catfish, three.
Catfish, catfish, catfish.
Actor, three.
(Actor, three.)
Actor, actor, actor.
Short sleeves, two.
Short sleeves, short sleeves.
Nose hair, two.
- Nose hair...
- Okay.
Okay. We are doing well.
Let's do this.
What was that?
"Nose hair" was directed at Haha.
- I was going to respond.
- He has a mustache.
Dirty things like "Nose hair"
and "Mustache" belong to him.
Then anything about Grim Reaper
is yours, right?
- That's mine.
- Anything small is Jae Suk's.
- That's right.
- Anything about hair is Haha's.
- That's mine.
Anything about love.
- That's right.
- Love.
How about Young Ji?
- I...
- Just...
- I will take the remaining ones.
- You can take anything.
- Go ahead.
If you don't like
"Bald" or "Age spot", signal me.
Okay.
Let's begin.
- Good...
- Let's do this.
- Go slowly.
- Good
- Good image
Someone who wants to kiss me, two.
(Someone who wants to kiss me, two!)
(He gives up.)
Someone who wants to kiss her,
someone who wants to kiss her.
(Giggling)
Boring person, four.
Boring person, boring person,
boring person.
- Hey.
- What is your problem?
- Even his mistake was boring.
- Hey.
Can't you get the rhythm right?
- Hey, Mr. Mustache.
Mr. Mustache is boring.
- For goodness' sake.
- That was boring.
- Boring person.
- Even his mistake was boring.
- Okay.
Mr. Boring.
He is boring.
For four, you start here.
For 3, you start here.
For 2, you start here.
It's 8 to 5 now. Once you get
10 points, the game is over.
- Ten points?
- What's their score?
It's 8 to 5.
Haha, go ahead.
Say something intense.
Bring it on.
Good image
Someone who kissed
last night, three.
(Someone who kissed
last night, three.)
- Last kiss, last kiss, last kiss.
- Good.
Foot odor, two.
(Hesitating)
Foot odor, foot odor.
Someone who wants to go home
like crazy, four.
What did you say?
Someone who wants to go home,
someone who wants to go home,
someone who wants to go home.
(He managed to defend
the long attack.)
Constipation, three.
Constipation, constipation.
That's not it.
(He got it long in a loud voice.)
It's three.
- Yes!
- Three.
He said constipation, three.
He's the one
who suffers from constipation.
Why did you do that
when you don't have constipation?
- Why?
- Why is it so hard?
- Three is... Listen.
- Okay.
Four starts here. Three starts here.
Two starts here. And this is one.
I just thought he said two.
- Constipation...
- I thought it was two.
What's with your ears?
Constipation, constipation,
constipation. How simple is that?
constipation. And...
If I say "Eunuch, two",
they can't say it.
- Why are you...
- We should do that.
How would they say
they are a eunuch?
- Hair loss...
- He is...
You didn't say hair loss.
Why do you keep telling me
to say eunuch?
- Hey, the word is...
- I can say that.
in the dictionary.
- Why do I have to say that?
- My gosh.
Why are you telling me to say that?
Gosh, this is really upsetting.
I just thought it was two.
Two and three... Four starts here.
Three starts here. Two starts here.
And this is one.
- Please calm down.
- I know that.
You do?
Constipation, constipation,
constipation, constipation.
This is four.
Constipation, constipation,
constipation.
- This is three.
- I know.
- I know that.
- Two. Constipation, constipation.
- His vein is about to explode.
- One is...
Constipation!
Eunuch, four.
Why do you keep saying eunuch?
Why do you say eunuch?
Why are you so obsessed with eunuch?
- I'm so angry.
- He wants to win.
Why is he...
Are you sure he's not
possessed by a spirit?
Why does he keep saying that?
He wants to win.
He once said eunuch
instead of Nose King before.
(The butterfly effect
of Nose King in episode 549)
- I'm so upset.
- Do we have two points left?
It's 9 to 5. You have
only 1 point left.
We can do this.
- Let's focus.
- We can't lose.
Jae Suk goes first.
I won't make a mistake.
I should say something
that they can't take.
- He's making a winning move.
- It's thrilling until the end.
- Let's go.
Good image
- Good image, good image
So Min's love, four.
(So Min's love, four.)
So Min's love, So Min's love,
So Min's love, So Min's love.
Eunuch, four.
(Eunuch, four.)
Eunuch, eunuch, eunuch, eunuch.
Bad breath, two.
Bad breath, bad breath.
Prostate, three.
Prostate, prostate, prostate.
Ganoderma lucidum, three.
(This round continues
for a long time without a mistake.)
Ganoderma lucidum, Ganoderma
lucidum, Ganoderma lucidum.
Man, four.
(Man, four!)
- Why did you not say it?
- Why are you quiet?
(They failed
because no one took the word.)
Why is it so hard to say
that you're a man?
Why is it so hard? Man, man,
- man, man.
- Man, man,
- Even if I lose, I would say that.
- Man, man, man, man.
We'd do that even if we lose.
- Why did you not take it?
- Why were you quiet?
- You are a man.
- It's okay to lose.
You said eunuch right away.
- For eunuch, you said...
- Eunuch, eunuch, eunuch, eunuch.
But why were you quiet
when she said man?
Why did you not take it?
- Man, man, man, man.
- Why can't you say that?
- You have to say it.
- Man, man, man, man.
I was afraid to lose.
I should've said that.
- I thought we'd lose.
- Eunuch, three.
- Eunuch, eunuch, eunuch, eunuch.
- You guys are cowards.
- My gosh.
- That was fun.
- So...
Team Heo Young Ji wins this round.
- We did it.
- Three members are better.
Captain Heo Young Ji gets 15 points.
- We need just a little.
- Distribute the points here.
- Just give us a little.
- Now...
How many points do they have?
I can't tell you that.
- Young Ji.
- Now we have...
- the final results.
- Okay.
The three members to win
Korean beef and ganoderma lucidum.
- Jae Suk.
- Ganoderma lucidum.
The first place...
got 26 points. It's Lee Young Ji.
(1st place,
Lee Young Ji with 26 points)
- She got a lot of points.
- Right.
That's a lot of points.
The second place is...
Heo Young Ji with 15 points.
(2nd place,
Heo Young Ji with 15 points)
Now you know how stingy you were.
(Young Ji's heydays)
The third place... The last one
to win the prize is...
Kim Jong Kook with four points.
My gosh.
- Four points.
- He's got only four points?
- And he's the third place.
- Thank you.
I didn't expect to win today.
And the members
who got zero points are...
There must be a lot.
JiSuk Jin, Haha,
Song Ji Hyo, and Jeon So Min.
- The four of them.
- Okay.
I got one point.
- Two members will get a penalty.
- Safe.
- It's a 50 percent chance.
It says either an O or an X.
- An O or an X?
- Open it.
- Open it?
- You can't avoid it.
- Okay. I'll open it first.
- Okay.
- Okay. Do you like an O?
- Yes.
- You startled me.
- I don't like an X.
(He will get a penalty
if it has an X on it.)
There's nothing.
- Yes.
- Gosh, he is...
I thought he'd pick an X.
Yes!
(So Min and Ji Hyo
will get a penalty.)
- Married...
- men.
- Cross.
Eunuch, eunuch, eunuch, eunuch.
Eunuch, eunuch, eunuch, go home.
- And sleep.
We will move to another place for
the penalty and acceptance speech.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
The two losers will
have a hot foot bath...
wearing padded jackets while
having hot tea in the open garden.
- Young Ji and Young Ji.
- It's even a black jacket.
My goodness.
(It's a black jacket that absorbs
all the heat from the sun.)
I'm wearing socks.
I'm doing this wearing socks.
(So Min is having
a foot bath already.)
- Are you wearing socks?
- Yes.
Is it lukewarm?
It's hot.
You should drink tea.
(They're forced to enjoy a hot spa
in the hot open garden.)
What do we do?
They look pretty though.
- They look pretty.
- This feels good.
They look amazing.
It's like a photo shoot.
- By the way...
- Let me take a picture of you.
It looks like you two are
on a vacation.
They look amazing.
They are pretty.
It looks like they are doing this
for beauty and health.
So Min is doing all the good things
including foot volleyball today.
- So Min did all sorts of things.
- She did everything.
After Kwang Soo left,
- we all get a penalty in turn.
- I know.
- You're right. Ji Hyo is...
- She got the energy.
She got Kwang Soo's energy.
Oh, no.
(Kwang Soo's bad luck
has moved to lucky Ji Hyo.)
As I announced
the results of the race,
the three winners will get
Korean beef and ganoderma lucidum.
That's amazing.
- Young Ji.
- It looks really good.
We just bought them
at a department store.
You just bought them?
- This looks great.
- My gosh.
This is great.
- Your parents will love this.
- I know.
They must be happy.
(Let's just have some green tea.)
When you take this with you,
you should leave
without looking back.
Okay.
Suk Jin will make a sign
with his eyes.
Then I'll have to give this to him.
- So you have to rush home.
- He's being silent now.
- What?
- I know this is for you.
My feet are hot.
The sun is really hot.
I'd like to thank you
for letting me...
build good memories
with Young Ji today.
I hope I will come here
with Kim Young Ji next time.
- Is there another Young Ji?
- Another Young Ji?
There's another Young Ji.
I did a TV show
with Yeong Ja before.
Young Ji, Young Ji,
Yeong Ja, and Young Ji.
Thank you for having me here
and getting me a great gift.
Please give them a big hand.
- Thank you for today.
- Thank you.
- Good job today.
- Good job.
- I had a great time today.
- Thank you.
Hello. Welcome.
(Kim So Hee's VIP doll exhibition)
(The place is full
of expensive masterpieces.)
(The members have fun
playing with the toys.)
(The artist shows up
right at the moment.)
- Hello.
- She's the artist.
(This doll is...)
(What is it doing here?)
(The star artist...)
(passes out in front of them
all of a sudden.)
(She left her will.)
(The one who gets the most expensive
doll will get my properties.)
(The members are here
to look for Kim So Hee's traces.)
There are a lot of dolls.
(Find the most expensive doll
to inherit her properties!)
(Right at the moment...)
I've been waiting.
(Some bizarre things
happen to them.)
(The most expensive doll
is controlling them from somewhere?)
(Will the members be able to unravel
the mystery of the hidden doll?)
(Find the most expensive doll,
Scary Doll Detective)