(Jong Kook's natural enemy,
Yeon Koung)
(Long Legs killer, Jong Kook)
(The two players have
a childish war of nerves.)
Good service.
- Good.
- Okay. That's good.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
(Tiger Gym: 4, Locust Gym: 4)
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Good.
- Well done.
- Se Chan, watch your mouth.
- Okay. I will.
- We can catch up.
- Be careful.
- Don't use a formal tone.
- Jong Kook.
- We can do this.
Hey. Jong Kook.
Long Legs, serve. Okay.
- Haha.
- All right.
Let's do this.
- Hey!
- What was that?
- Well done.
- It's out.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
- We can do this.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
- It's not!
It's okay.
- It's all right.
- We can do this.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Drop the honorifics.
- Good.
- Hurry and come here.
- Drop the honorifics.
- In 1, 2, and 3.
- Okay.
- Don't talk.
Don't talk.
- Don't say a word.
- Don't use the honorifics.
Stay quiet.
Drop the honorifics.
Good.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
No.
- Done.
- Good, Ji Young.
- Slow down.
(Oh Ji Young's specialty,
a header spike)
- Slow down.
- Good, Yeon Koung.
- All right.
- Yeum Cheater.
- Okay.
- That was good.
(Yeum Cheater's deep offense)
- Good.
- One and two.
- That was two.
- Good.
- Hey.
It touched her head.
(Oh Ji Young's header)
Yeum Cheater. Good.
- That was good.
- Well done.
- Jong Kook.
- Send it over.
- Hurry.
- Nine.
Well done. Send it over.
Good. Well done.
I'll defend.
- Go ahead.
- Send it over.
- Mine.
- Good.
- I'll get it.
- Okay.
- Great.
(Yeon Koung sends it up high.)
Jae Suk.
(Great)
- Send it over.
- Gosh.
(Groaning)
(He poses...)
(and spins.)
Come here.
(The excellent rally
ends with Trainer Yoo's blunder.)
- Come on.
- In 1, 2, and 3.
There you go.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
- Jae Suk.
- What's with him?
That was a close call.
- Yeon Koung did a good job.
How dare he try to look cool?
- How dare he?
- What's wrong with him?
- We did it.
- That was good.
- Why would he do that?
- Don't use the honorifics.
- Drop the honorifics.
- All right.
We're doing a good job.
We can do this.
- Let's keep it up.
- Okay.
- Let's go. Smile.
- Smile.
- Keep smiling.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
- That was nice.
- Good.
- Go ahead.
- Send it over.
- Good. It's out.
- No, it's not.
Jae Suk.
- Send it over!
- It touched his head.
- Ji Young.
- Slow down.
- That was two.
- Use your hands.
- Hands.
- Use your head.
- Chance.
- Send it over.
(Foot Volleyball Comedian Jong Kook)
(He attacks safely.)
- Go ahead.
- Good.
- Gosh, sorry.
- Go ahead.
- Go.
- Gosh.
(Trainer Yoo caused trouble again.)
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
What was that?
What was that? I don't get it.
It was hard to receive.
That was a hard one.
You should've received it.
- What are you saying?
- It was hard to receive.
- Why can't you receive it?
- Hey, you...
You should've done it better.
I'm sorry.
Those who're good
don't make excuses.
- You have to do something.
- All right.
- Here I go.
- It's the clumsy one.
No, he can do this.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Mine.
- Okay.
- What?
- It was out.
Okay!
- Yes!
- It was out.
Pull yourself together.
- It was Yeon Koung.
- What? Yeon Koung did it.
- It was your fault.
- You should've received it.
You should've received it.
Look at you.
Let's do this.
- Can we stop doing cheers?
- That's enough.
- Let's do this.
- Stop it.
- Don't fight.
- We can do this.
- Yeon Koung, you receive it.
- Gosh, Yeum Cheater.
- Yeum Cheater never stops.
- Let's do this in a good mood.
- Let's do this.
- Long Legs is surprised.
- Long Legs, are you surprised?
- She's startled.
Long Legs seems very shocked.
Just go ahead and do it.
Don't use the honorifics.
- Slow down. Good.
- That was a good one.
- Spike.
- Yeum Cheater.
- It touched.
- Okay.
- It did.
- It didn't touch.
- We won.
- Okay.
- We won. Okay!
- Seriously, it touched.
- I'm sure it touched.
- Okay.
- No way.
- Review the video.
Seriously, I touched the ball.
- I'm telling you.
- No way.
(Checking VAR)
(She didn't touch the ball.)
(It touched.)
- Hey.
- I'm serious.
- No.
- It touched.
Referee, nice.
- That's nice.
- Yeum Cheater.
- It didn't touch.
- Referee, nice.
- Review the video.
- It didn't touch.
- Check the sound.
- Hey, Yeum Cheater.
- It didn't touch.
- It didn't.
Hey, Yeum Cheater.
There you go again.
- The referee is nice.
- Stop it, Yeum Cheater.
- Yeum Cheater is unbelievable.
- He's an international referee.
"Seriously, it touched."
- It did touch the ball.
- Yeum Cheater, are you sure?
- I saw it. It touched her toe.
- I'm serious.
Are you serious?
Seriously, I touched the ball.
Let's move on.
She says she touched it.
- Bo Pil.
- It touched her toe.
- Give me the ball.
I'm telling you I touched the ball.
I touched it, but why is no one
on our team taking my side?
(Her colleagues knew she was lying,
so they stayed quiet.)
- We need one point.
- I'll be sure to receive it.
Nice.
- Done.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Well done.
- Do you want me to send it up high?
Okay.
(He sends a spike onto the line.)
- Okay.
- Well done.
- Hands.
- After a bounce.
Hands. Good.
All right. Head.
- Hey.
- Good.
(She gives a header spike again.)
- Don't make it too hard.
- Good.
- It's okay.
- My gosh.
- Okay.
Okay!
(The ball touches the net,
so they score a lucky point.)
- Good.
- Well done.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- It's okay.
- They were lucky.
I think we're losing.
- I'm bleeding.
- Are you all right?
- What's wrong?
- Did you get hit?
No. I was so upset
that I bit my lips.
(No. I was so upset
that I bit my lips.)
(There's bloodshed at the bench.)
- Do it right.
- We will have a chance.
- Let's do this. It's okay.
- Do things right.
- It's okay. We will get a chance.
- Okay. Don't worry.
- It's us. Serve.
- Don't use the honorifics.
- Don't talk.
- Yeon Koung's service is good.
We have to receive
Yeon Koung's service.
Let Long Legs serve.
Let her do it.
- Good.
- Jong Kook.
That's a good one.
- Good.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Let her do it.
- Ji Young.
Okay.
(Serve ace)
(Long Legs
and her friends are roaring.)
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- It's okay.
- Well done.
Good. It was a hard one.
Jong Kook is out of his element.
Let's go.
- Good.
- It's okay.
With all his muscles.
- Let's go.
- We have only a few points left.
Long Legs, bring it on.
Hey, Long Legs.
Can't you do it with your feet?
(The kid provokes her
feeling afraid of her service.)
I guess she can't use her feet.
- Serve now.
- Can't you do it?
- You can't do it, can you?
- Serve now.
(She answers with a strong serve.)
- You can't do it, can you?
- Serve now.
Gosh.
- Ji Young.
- Here you go.
It's out.
- Okay.
- It's out.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Good.
- We have to stay quiet.
Drop the honorifics.
We have to stay quiet.
(They throw a ball
at Se Chan's head.)
That was a mistake.
- We gave you the ball.
- This isn't right.
We just gave you the ball.
- Hey.
- We passed the ball.
- Why would you do that?
- It is bad manners.
It's your fault
that you turned against the next.
- Is it my fault?
- Hey.
Why did you turn against the next?
- It's your fault.
- Who'd turn...
- against the net on the court?
- It's your bad.
- I gave you the ball.
- I was startled.
I just passed the ball.
All right.
It's your fault...
- that you turned against the net.
- Let's move on.
We should continue.
Don't you dare turn around.
- We have to receive this.
- Okay.
We must win.
Here I go.
- You lose one point.
- She lost a point.
- One point.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Why?
She used the honorifics.
Okay!
Did she use the honorifics?
(Thank you for giving us 1 point.)
- Are we winning?
- Okay.
Is it over?
- They lost one point.
- Don't open it.
(Groaning)
Yeon Koung.
(Unfortunately,
the same incident happened again.)
What was that?
- Yeon Koung, it's bad manners.
- What was that?
I just gave you the ball.
- What?
- Isn't she supposed to...
- throw the ball like this?
- It's bad manners.
She should be given a red card.
- Didn't you do it on purpose?
- No.
Hey!
Didn't you do it on purpose?
(He's caught using the honorifics.)
Let's do a cheer.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes! Okay.
Don't talk at all.
- Keep talking to them.
- Jong Kook can't do this.
- Long Legs.
- Hey.
Long Legs. Okay, good.
Yeon Koung, why don't you
use your legs?
Stay focused.
Send it over.
(Yeon Koung's first foot serve)
My gosh.
That's strong.
(Foot Volleyball Comedian
manages to receive it.)
That was strong.
Yeon Koung is good.
- Mine.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Yeum Cheater.
- My gosh.
- Okay.
(Laughing)
(Depressed)
You can score one point.
- You can do this.
- We have to win.
Turn the game around.
- We have good teamwork.
- Good.
- Tiger.
- Yes.
- All right.
- I'm so excited.
Okay. Long Legs, receive this.
- Long Legs.
- Long Legs, come on and receive.
Long Legs, can you do this?
Okay.
Send it over.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Well done. Use your head.
- Done.
Hey, So Young.
- Good.
- So Young is good.
(The ace player is not distracted
by Trainer Yoo at all.)
- Good. Well done.
- Yeum Cheater.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Jong Kook will miss it.
- Good.
- Pass.
- Serve.
- Jong Kook.
- Ji Young.
- Pass.
- Serve.
- Jong Kook.
- Ji Young.
(They score a point
with a diving header.)
Gosh, we did it!
Ji Young.
Ji Young, that was amazing.
- Hey!
- Amazing.
We did it.
(That was something
that we can't see on Running Man.)
- Ji Young.
- Well done.
Ji Young is really good.
Hey, how could you be so good?
I got goosebumps.
- Ji Young is unbelievable.
- I got goosebumps.
- They are so good.
- It couldn't be helped.
- Right.
- There was nothing we could do.
- It's okay.
- Don't worry.
- This is just the beginning.
- Don't talk.
- Stop talking.
- Just smile.
- Are we 9 or 10?
- We're 10.
- This is the last.
- One point.
- Stay focused.
- Set point.
- Let's do this.
- One more point.
- We can turn it around.
- I'll receive it no matter what.
- Okay.
I love you, guys.
I love you.
Set point.
- Done.
- Okay.
- Stay calm.
- Smile.
- I did it.
- Okay. Go.
There it goes.
It's coming. Do it.
It's coming over.
All right.
- What?
- Deduct one point.
(Trainer Kook charges
toward the net.)
- Deduct one point.
- No.
- Hey.
- He damaged the net.
He didn't touch the ball,
so they lose one point anyway.
- Okay!
- Well done.
- Let's do a cheer.
- Okay. We need one point.
We can do this. Se Chan.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- All right.
- Stay focused.
(The pony is excited
by the score of 10 to 9.)
Good.
Only one point.
- You can do this.
- We must win.
- We will win.
- Turn the game around.
- This is the last round.
- One point.
- Stay focused.
- Set point.
- Good luck.
- Let's do this.
Yeon Koung, make a serve.
Okay. Good.
Jong Kook gave us nine points.
Jong Kook, you're the best.
- No. It's Se Chan's turn to serve.
- It's Se Chan's turn.
It's Se Chan's serve.
- It's Se Chan's turn to serve.
- Right.
- Send it over.
- Long Legs.
Go ahead.
Hey, why won't you say anything?
Just score. Don't let him fool you.
- Se Chan, we just need one point.
- I said, speak.
- You should talk on a variety show.
- We need just one point.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- You can do this.
- Hey, don't step on the line.
- Hye Seon, don't step on the line.
- Just go for it.
- Don't step on the line.
- Can you move back a little?
- Hey, don't step on the line.
- I said, don't step on the line.
Jong Kook is so bad at this.
- He keeps stepping on the line.
- Jong Kook is so bad at this.
- It's coming.
Speak casually, everyone.
- Two.
- Send it over.
- This is our chance.
- That's good.
- Just send it over, and we'll win.
- Send it over.
- Okay. Good.
Let's just play it safe.
We can win
if we just keep sending it over.
- We don't have to take a risk.
- Send it over.
(She kicks it lightly.)
Out.
- Out.
- In.
(Where did the ball land?)
- It's out.
- In!
- It was out.
- Yes!
- Oh, yes!
- In!
We won?
- We won!
- Yes!
- Great job.
- We were amazing.
- It was in.
(It's sweeter than a victory
in the Olympic games.)
- We won.
- Go, Korea!
Hey, guys.
- You did well.
- Good job.
- It's okay. We can win next time.
- How about we complain?
- Should we complain? Can't we?
- That won't work.
- It was in for sure.
- Really?
- Let's do better next time.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Great job.
- Yes!
(They cheer even though they lost.)
(Yes!)
- Tiger! Yes!
- Yes!
(Tiger Gym won Round 1.)
- That was good.
- That was amazing.
- We were incredible.
- I'm amazed.
My, we did incredibly well.
Good game.
- Good game.
- Gosh.
- My goodness. That was amazing.
- Why are you upset?
- Be quiet!
- Good game.
- All right.
- We should cheer for them.
The 2nd-string players of each team
will play in the 2nd round,
but 1 of the 1st-string players
can join the team.
Yeon Koung is good at attacking.
- Let's do this.
- Yes. Yeon Koung, join the game.
- Me?
- Let's pick Yeon Koung. Yes.
Then... You're not so good, right?
- Right.
- You go to the front.
- Which one should we choose?
- How about Ji Young?
- Ji Young, Yeon Koung is playing.
- To serve?
- Shall I join the game? I'll serve.
- Attack as much as you want.
- This is your chance.
- To be honest...
Okay. Let's cheer for them.
Go, Team!
(Tiger Gym: Captain Ji Young,
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Hee Jin)
(Locust Gym: Captain So Min,
Yeon Koung, Hye Jin, Eun Jin)
Choose the libero, please.
- Whom should we choose?
- Hey.
We choose So Min as the libero.
- All right. That's good for us.
- That's great.
- Why?
- I like that.
- Thank you.
- Hold on.
- Was I wrong?
- Was that a bad choice?
- You can't change it now.
- Wait. No. Why did you choose her?
- You can't change it.
- Hang on.
- Then can we...
- No. It's over.
- We should choose Suk Jin.
- Right.
- Is it okay?
- We choose Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is the libero.
- Really?
- Okay. It's decided.
- Are we still speaking casually?
- It hurts when I laugh.
- Let's begin.
- That's over now.
- When did it end?
- Hey, go now.
He says we can speak formally now.
Why haven't you gotten used to it?
- Let's keep it that way for now.
- Let's do that.
(They'll continue speaking casually
regardless of the game.)
But I think it's over.
The option for this round is
smiling and not getting upset.
- I see. I like that.
- Okay.
Right. I know how that goes.
- Make sure not to lose your temper.
- I won't.
- Smile when you speak.
- Got it.
Keep filming Yeon Koung's face.
I'll keep my eyes on her
to see if she smiles or not.
- Hey, you made no contribution.
- What? Gosh.
(Ms. Bread bursts out in anger.)
- She just yelled.
- The game hasn't begun yet.
- She's getting upset. Look at her.
- Go ahead. The score is 0 to 0.
- Deduct a point.
- It's 0 to 0.
- See?
- They should lose a point.
- Smile when you speak.
- Speak with a smile, okay?
- It's okay.
- Okay. I'll do that once we begin.
- Don't forget to smile.
Isn't she actually Kwang Soo?
- She's just like Kwang Soo.
- She acts just like he used to.
Hey, you're Kwang Soo, aren't you?
- Aren't you Kwang Soo?
- She's just like Kwang Soo.
- You didn't do anything.
- Let's do this.
- Stop talking like you did well.
- She acts like Kwang Soo used to.
(The assassin on the court is back.)
- You can practice now.
- Okay.
- You can do it!
- I'll receive it.
- You can do it.
- Let's go!
- Suk Jin, go to the front.
- Okay.
- Out.
- It's just practice. It's okay.
- Okay. It's just practice.
It's just practice.
I got the hang of it.
What are you talking about?
Hey, are you frowning?
I think you are.
- It's just practice, you know.
- The game begins now.
- It begins now.
(Smiling)
Yeon Koung, you should smile.
(As soon as she heard
that the game began,)
(Yeon Koung put on a silly smile.)
- Yeon Koung, you should smile.
- Okay.
- Smile, everyone.
- I'll smile from this moment on.
- It begins now. Okay.
- Smile.
Yeon Koung, you should smile.
- She's just like Kwang Soo.
- Exactly.
- Smile.
- Okay.
She behaves just like he used to.
- Let's go.
- Get ready.
I'll receive it.
- What's this? Is it out?
- Out.
- It's out. Yes.
- It's okay.
- What's this? Is it out?
- Out. It's out. Yes.
- Smile.
- It's okay.
(I think she just frowned.)
- I think she just frowned.
- Yeon Koung.
- How did that happen?
- I think she got upset.
- I think she lost her temper.
- I think so too.
- You hit it too hard.
- How did that happen?
- I don't understand.
- I think she lost her temper.
Hey, you fool.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to kill you.
- Get ready.
- You fool.
- She reminds me of Kwang Soo.
- Let's go.
She does, indeed.
- She's amazing.
- Head the ball.
- She's really amazing.
- Head it.
- Spike.
- I'll receive it.
- Will you?
- Yes, I'll receive it.
- Go ahead.
- Here.
- Head it.
- Head the ball.
- Send it over.
- Head it.
Head it.
- It didn't touch her head.
- Nice!
Head it.
(She missed the ball.)
- It didn't touch her head.
- No, it touched her head.
- Okay.
- I sent it over the net.
- It didn't touch your head.
- He's right.
- Did you see it?
- The ball didn't touch your head.
- Wait.
- She got upset.
- Yeon Koung didn't smile.
- I smiled.
- Speak with a smile.
- Smile.
- "The ball didn't touch your head."
- You saw that, didn't you?
- I smiled.
- She didn't smile.
- Did it touch or not?
It didn't touch. Continue.
- Okay. I smiled.
- It didn't touch.
- I smiled like this.
- No, that's okay.
- Sorry?
- She's just like Kwang Soo.
She's just like him.
She's exactly the same as him.
(She's a world-class player
who behaves like Kwang Soo.)
- Are you sure?
- I smiled.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Hey, Shin Min A,
I'll see how well you can do.
- You should smile.
- I'll keep my eyes on you.
- All right. Bring it on.
- Suk Jin, you're blocking my view.
I don't think you can do it.
- Oh, my. Great.
- My goodness.
- Min A.
- Smile.
- Min A, what was that?
Hey, Yeon Koung, isn't this fun?
- Min A, come over here.
- I told you before.
- Are you kidding me?
- Kwang Soo. Hold on.
- I told you I wasn't good at this.
- Hit it inside the lines, okay?
Why do you think I'm wearing this?
- I know.
- That was funny.
- Min A, get it together.
- I'm sorry, everyone.
Blow the whistle.
- Blow the whistle.
- You fool.
- All right. Let's go.
- Can I go now? Okay.
- It's coming.
- Don't worry.
- So Min, receive it. Move.
- Good job.
(So Min was zoning out.)
(And she hit the ball outside.)
(Libero Jeon is useless
even if she's allowed to use her hands.)
- It's okay.
- It's okay, So Min.
- Oh, yes.
- Great.
(She was like this.)
My gosh.
- So Min, it's okay.
- So Min.
- It's okay.
- So Min, you should focus.
(The daughter of a former athlete
causes the trainer grief.)
- So Min.
- Just replace her with a scarecrow.
- So Min, get it together.
- So Min, you've got this.
- Smile.
- Just replace her with a scarecrow.
Let's hit the ball toward So Min
whenever we serve.
Keep your eyes on the ball, okay?
At least the ball would bounce off
the scarecrow.
- So Min, move.
- Let's go.
Yeon Koung just told me
to move aside.
- No. I told you to stand here.
- Let's go.
The ball will fall here,
then hit it with your hands.
- It'll fall in the middle.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- I'm ready.
Here we go.
- What a powerful serve.
- Oh, my.
- Hey, leave it.
- Yes!
- What a powerful serve.
- Oh, my.
(She looked like she was dancing.)
(The world-class Long Legs
is humiliated...)
(after she tells So Min off.)
(Laughing)
(They start teasing her.)
That was so funny.
(Long Legs forces herself to smile
with her hair blown.)
- You did a good job.
- She couldn't receive it.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
- That's good.
- Like this.
She couldn't receive it.
- It's okay.
- Yeon Koung, it's okay.
Right. We can do this.
- Hey, stop it.
- It's okay.
- That was an amazing serve.
- Let's begin.
- What a great serve.
- Nice serve!
Here we go.
- Min A, smile.
- Okay.
- She's good at serving too.
- She's amazing.
- That's good.
- Go.
- Here.
- Oh, gosh.
(Oh, gosh.)
- Here.
- Oh, gosh.
(Flopping down)
Go, Tiger, Tiger is the best
- Good job.
- Go, Tiger
- What was that?
- That was funny.
(Hold on, Min A.)
- Min A.
- Hey.
- Get it together, will you?
- We'll win.
Min A.
- That was great.
- It was hard to receive.
- Min A, you should stay focused.
- Trust me.
(Proving that not every volleyball player
is good at this)
- Min A.
- Oh, my.
- This is so exciting.
- That was so funny.
- Goodness.
Shin Min A.
Guys, Yeon Koung seems upset.
- No, I'm not.
- I think she's upset.
- You're not upset, are you?
- I'm smiling.
- That was hilarious.
- Stay focused.
- I'm sorry.
- We should do better than this.
They sure are second-string players.
Suk Jin hasn't kicked the ball
until now. Not even once.
Hold on. Suk Jin, I'm sorry,
- but you win after doing nothing.
- True.
- Impressive. That's a great skill.
- Of course.
- This is nice.
- Hey.
- Someone else can serve...
- Just do it.
- Hurry up.
- if you ask.
- Do you want me to serve?
- Suk Jin, shut it and do your job.
- That's the plan.
- Go ahead. Just do your job.
(He got criticized
before he even touched the ball.)
- What did you say?
- Just do your job.
What did you say before that?
"Suk Jin, shut it and do your job."
(He practically asked
to be criticized.)
Do you want me to serve or not?
- Okay.
- You can do this.
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
- Jong Kook, you should smile.
- Suk Jin.
- Right. I'll do that. Go, Suk Jin.
- You should smile.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- Good. Now send it over.
- Send it over.
- That's good. Nice.
- That's good.
- Suk Jin.
- You should've received it.
- Send it over. That's good. Nice.
- That's good.
(The ball quickly passed by.)
- Why didn't you receive it?
- Oh, yes!
It came toward you.
He got upset.
Suk Jin lost his temper.
- Okay.
- Oh, it was me.
Tiger Gym will lose another point.
- Oh, yes!
- Why?
- Suk Jin lost his temper.
- I...
- Suk Jin got upset.
- Let's go.
- Let's cheer.
- We can do this.
- Jae Suk, come.
- Oh, right. Yes.
- Let's cheer.
By the way, you'll keep speaking
casually to the end, right?
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- I feel more comfortable this way.
- Right.
- Smile, everyone.
- Beep!
- Head it.
- Okay.
- Hit it toward So Min if you can.
- Got it.
- So Min, you can do it.
- I can do it.
- So Min, use your hands.
- That's good.
(Playing catch)
(So Min, use your hands.)
(Furious)
- So Min, great job.
- What was that?
So Min, you're not
playing dodgeball.
- It's okay.
- My gosh.
Listen, So Min.
You're not playing dodgeball.
(Her body malfunctions
whenever a ball comes near.)
Did I hit it too hard?
- I think...
- That was awesome.
- You hit it so accurately.
- Great job.
- I'm impressed.
- She's amazing.
So Min, are you kidding?
(He said it with a smile.)
So Min, you should stay focused.
- This is not dodgeball.
- I know.
- Okay?
- I was so startled.
- All right. You can use your hands.
- That startled me. Understood.
- Do better this time. Move back.
- I can do it.
Stop. Stand right there. Okay.
Make sure to receive the ball.
Use your hands, okay?
- Spread your legs.
- Got it.
- Spread your legs. That's good.
- Okay.
Yeon Koung talked to So Min
in an annoyed, commanding tone.
- No, I didn't.
- That's not true.
- Okay.
- That didn't make me upset.
- I was smiling.
- She still looks upset.
- She's getting upset.
- She's losing her temper.
- She's just taken aback.
- That's not true.
- She's taken aback, not upset.
- She has a droopy mouth.
- She's not upset.
- I'm not upset.
- Bo Pil.
She was focusing on the game.
- Exactly. She was focusing on it.
- Come on.
- Can we...
- Are you hungry?
- I didn't get upset.
- She didn't.
I'm too scared to continue.
- Look. He's frowning.
- They keep making an angry face.
- Your team will lose a point.
- Good.
- What did I do?
- Smile.
- Please smile.
- You should smile.
- Both teams lost a point.
- Okay.
- Don't forget to smile.
Min A,
you don't have to hit it hard.
Okay.
- That's good.
- Okay.
- Min A, you did a good job.
- Hey, that was awesome.
- Here.
- She's so amazing.
(Ji Young saved the ball.)
- She's really amazing.
- I'm sorry.
- Use your hands.
- Good.
- Oh, gosh. I was startled.
- Okay.
(However!)
(Long Legs made a mistake.)
- That was great.
- We're doing great.
- Okay. Good.
- Darn!
- You should smile.
- We're doing great.
(She got upset again.)
How did I do that?
- Great job.
- Keep going.
- Oh, my...
- It's okay.
- She's hilarious.
- Smile.
- She's so funny.
- Smile happily.
- Don't get upset.
- Yeon Koung, you're so funny.
- She's hilarious.
- She's the best.
- Yeon Koung is so funny.
- She reminds me of Kwang Soo.
- It's okay. Let's do this.
- Oh, gosh.
- She's likable and funny.
- She's so funny.
Let's go! You can do it!
- She's amazing.
- She's so accurate.
- That's good. Move forward.
- Good.
- Toss it.
- Don't rush.
- Nice.
- You should send it over.
- Send it over the net.
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- Okay. You did well.
- Use your hands. Send it over.
- Good.
- Ji Hyo.
- Send it over. Okay.
- Oh, yes!
(Groaning)
(He groans while receiving it.)
(His team loses 1 point.)
- You should let it bounce.
- It's okay.
- Did we win?
- Yes!
- Great job.
- Suk Jin, come up to receive.
- I'll serve.
Stand in the front and wait.
- By the way... Hold on.
- That was close.
Suk Jin,
were you pulling out a sword?
- I'm so upset.
- Hey.
(The swordmaster)
- Come and stand here.
- Wait.
- Here we go.
- Don't rush.
Eun Jin, stay calm. Don't rush.
Hee Jin is bad at using legs too.
- I'm bad at this.
- That's great.
- Okay.
- Hee Jin.
- There's no one behind her.
- Oh, gosh.
- Scored!
- She failed. All right!
- You guys got the hang of it.
- Let's cheer.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- You got the hang of it.
- Do we have four points?
- What's our score?
- No.
Hee Jin is so bad at this.
That was great.
- Suk Jin, use your hands.
- Okay.
Why don't you do anything
when you can use your hands too?
Hey.
Jong Kook just got angry.
(They lost another point
as Jong Kook lost his temper.)
Hey.
- Oh, yes!
- Yes!
- Don't get upset.
- We won!
- Let them have one point.
- This is nice.
- There was no reason to get upset.
- We're going to win.
- So Min, you can serve.
- Okay.
- I'll hit it lightly.
- Go for it.
- Face forward.
- Where...
- But that's nonsense.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin.
- Good job.
- Score just one point.
- Get out of my way.
(Get out of my way.)
(They both miss.)
Get out of my way.
(Suk Jin knocks out two teammates
with his lousy toss.)
It was too far away.
(This is driving me nuts.)
Hey, do you think
he did that on purpose?
- It's okay.
- Suk Jin.
- Calm down.
- They're getting upset.
- That was so funny.
- Did he lose his temper?
- You should've moved aside.
- I had no choice.
- Is that even possible?
- No.
- He got upset.
- You did it on purpose, right?
- Is that even possible?
- Wasn't it intentional?
- No.
- You did it to be funny, right?
- Gosh, no. I'd never do that.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That was funny.
- There's no deuce from now on.
- The 1st team to get 2 points wins.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Just get two points.
- Let's score.
- No deuce.
- Two points.
- Just win two points.
(Determined to redeem himself,
Big Nose will serve.)
- Let's go.
- Please.
- Just send it over the net.
Good.
- That's good.
- Send it over.
- Just send it over.
- I bet she can't do it.
- The lousy player.
- Send it up. Good.
- Use your hands.
- Don't kick it.
- Okay.
- He sent it over.
- That's nice.
- Send it over.
- Use your hands.
- Oh, my.
Send it over.
(Eun Jin made a mistake.)
- Scored.
- I tossed it wrong.
- Oh, no.
- Okay.
- Hey, we scored.
- They scored.
- We scored.
- Why?
- The libero sent it over the net.
- Tiger Gym will lose a point.
- That's right. He's the libero.
(Locust Gym scored as the libero
sent the ball over the net.)
- Am I not allowed to do that?
- You're the libero.
- A libero can't attack.
- But I used my legs...
- Good. Use your hands.
- Don't kick it.
(He sent it over confidently.)
- Great job.
- I'm allowed to kick it.
- Can't he attack using legs either?
- No, he can't.
- Not even with legs?
- No.
A libero should never send the ball
over the net.
- If you serve well, we win.
- Really?
- Okay.
- Yeon Koung.
- Just receive it well.
- Show them what you got.
- We'll win if you score.
- You can receive it.
- We must receive it.
- See if it falls outside the lines.
(Locust Gym overcame obstacles
and turned the game around.)
(Will they be able to create
a miracle at the end?)
- We must receive it.
- I'll leave the back zone to you.
- Send it toward Hee Jin.
- Okay.
See if it falls outside the lines.
Okay.
- That's good.
- Oh, my.
- Which one of you will kick it?
- Okay.
- Stay calm.
- Kick it lightly.
- Good.
- You should send it over.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- No one's there.
Gosh, I shouldn't send it over.
He said that while sending it over.
We won!
- No one's there.
- Gosh, I shouldn't send it over.
(He realized it too late.)
(We won!)
Gosh.
Why did he come up again?
I told him to stay in the back zone.
- Gosh.
- We won!
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
You fool.
He said he shouldn't send it over
while kicking the ball.
- I'm sorry.
- Suk Jin, you did a great job.
- I'm so happy.
- Thank you.
You're a spy, aren't you?
I shouldn't have sent it over.
- I shouldn't have done it.
- I'm so relieved.
He's just... Gosh.
- I'll cut his salary.
- You did a great job.
- The match...
- Good job.
between Tiger Gym and Locust Gym
has come to an end.
It's a shame.
And the score is 1 to 1.
- But as I said earlier,
- We lost the first round.
the first-string team gets
additional points.
Since they get 1.5 times more,
Tiger Gym wins.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Great job.
- It's okay.
- We did well.
- We did a great job.
- We played well.
- They were just amazing.
- We're all happy.
- They were the best.
- Great job.
- You all did great.
- I was impressed.
- Now, it's time...
- for salary negotiations.
- You were amazing.
Trainers,
reselect 3 members to be 1st-string
and get a salary negotiation.
- The first-string players?
- Three of them?
- Second-string can't negotiate.
- Hey.
- You see...
- You did great.
- You did well.
- I'm going to keep...
- Yes.
- the current first-string players.
- Yeon Koung, Hye Seon,
- Of course.
- and Se Chan.
- Yes.
- I'll negotiate your salaries.
- Understood.
- I want that.
- Okay.
Must the second-string players...
stay on the same team
without getting to negotiate?
No. They can switch teams
under mutual agreement.
- I see.
- We have a choice.
- Then...
- I get it.
- I choose the guests.
- Absolutely.
- You are second-strong players.
- Of course you should choose them.
- Well, we don't have to wear it.
- Okay.
The cast members are second-string.
Then we'll see you
at the negotiation site.
- Okay.
(They move to
the salary negotiation site.)
Based on the result
of the first round,
Trainer Kook got 400 dollars.
That's great. Thank you.
And Trainer Yoo got 200 dollars.
- Two hundred dollars?
- Yes.
That's not bad.
- I know. Of course.
- Please offer me a high salary.
- Trainer Yoo, I love you.
- All right.
- Do we have similar amounts now?
- Of course.
We'll begin
the salary negotiation now.
Each trainer must decide the order
of the players to negotiate with,
and the players will take turns
to negotiate the salary.
The trainers can offer any amount
within the money they have,
including the money you gained
from the game.
Okay.
Players, if you're not happy
with the salary offered to you,
you can negotiate with the trainer
of the other team.
- Great.
- However,
if both teams refuse to hire you,
you must stay on the same team
and get half the offered salary.
- I should just accept 10 dollars.
- I see.
- Would I get 50 if he offers 100?
- If both teams refuse to hire you.
Correct. Also,
the second-string players...
can decide to switch teams
under mutual agreement.
- Under agreement?
- Yes, they can switch teams...
- if they both agree to do it.
- Really?
- Won't we be paid?
- Sorry?
- We should get paid.
You will get the minimum salary.
Oh, I see.
(They can go to another team
and get the minimum salary.)
Also, Trainer Kook whose team won...
can trade 1 of his 2nd-string players
without consent.
- Without consent?
- I see.
- Really?
- Yes.
Trainer Kook can trade
1 of his 2nd-string players...
(He can fire a 2nd-string player
from his team.)
I can trade 1 of my 2nd-string players
without consent.
You can make your choice
after the negotiation.
Now, decide the order
of the players to negotiate with.
I'm going to...
start with Se Chan.
That means you won't offer me
much money.
You've got to be kidding me.
(Jae Suk is planning on
giving him a bad deal.)
- Fine, let's do this.
- Out of my first-string players?
I'll go first.
- We'll go by age.
- Then I'll go next.
Can you at least mention me?
(Can you at least mention me?)
(Hush!)
The trainer and first player
will begin negotiating.
How much do I have left again?
The money?
I received more, didn't I?
- All right.
- Hi, there.
(The first athlete to negotiate
with Tiger Gym)
- I hope it goes amicably.
- All right.
Remember that I'm the captain.
You're Oh Ji Young.
My top player.
- Your top player?
- I'm truly grateful.
- You know...
- What did I tell you?
- I said you wouldn't regret it.
- Exactly.
I'm not kidding when I say I agree.
So how much would you like?
I'd like to hear your offer first.
- No, you...
- How much?
Here. Write down a number.
Go ahead.
Hold on a second.
I understand
you're my top player, but...
Hold on a second.
(She asks for 500 dollars.)
- I'm the captain.
- You're my top player.
But asking for this much...
This is my initial offer.
You're asking for
a 500 percent raise.
This is my initial offer,
so please counter it.
I was thinking about 200 dollars.
- Right.
- Hold on a second.
- Is it that absurd?
- Wait.
- Can I cross my legs?
- Hold on.
If that's the amount you want...
I do have the others to think about.
- Right.
- I need to sign the other three.
So how about 200 dollars?
If I pay the others the same amount,
that'll be 600 dollars.
- I'll be left with nothing.
- Of course.
- Right?
- Yes.
So I'd appreciate it
if you agreed to 200 dollars.
I received 400 dollars
after the previous game.
Can you at least mention me?
I received 400 dollars.
(Haha draws a heart
so that she'd remember him.)
- Then, how about this?
- So...
I'll take 200 dollars.
- Just so you know, I'm loyal.
- I see.
- So 200 dollars.
- I'll take 200 dollars...
if Haha is a package deal.
- Haha?
- Yes, Haha.
I want to stay with Haha.
(She suggests 200 dollars
with Haha as a package deal.)
(Haha uses sweet Ji Young
to secure a spot on the team.)
- So you want me to sign Haha too?
- Yes.
- The both of you for 200 dollars.
- Loyalty.
- Yes, loyalty.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Can you sign the contract?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I hope we keep getting along.
We'll do a good job
in the next game as well.
Negotiations should go amicably.
(By promoting loyalty,)
(Trainer Kook signs her at
40 percent of what she suggested.)
I spent a lot on you two.
- Hello, Trainer Yoo.
- It's good to see you.
- Se Chan, come in.
- I did my best today.
What's your current salary?
The initial amount was 15 dollars,
but Yeon Koung...
- added 30 dollars to it.
- She added 30 dollars?
It's only 45 dollars.
(Yang Se Chan:
current salary 45 dollars)
You're probably aware of this,
but if we had won the game...
Not this again.
Are you already making excuses?
No, that's not it.
If we had won,
I'd have been more generous.
That would've been better,
but you still won 200 dollars.
Did you choose
to negotiate with me first...
so that you could offer 10 dollars?
I get what you're saying.
My salary is 45 dollars
at the moment...
and I don't expect a penny more.
(He doesn't expect a penny more?)
You received 200 dollars
after the game...
which should result
in 50 dollars more for us all.
But my conscience won't allow that.
However, 30 dollars...
(Only 30 dollars
when he has 980 dollars?)
- At least 30 dollars...
- So 30 dollars.
That much you should offer.
Asking for 50 dollars
would make me a thief.
(A mere salary of 30 dollars
puts a smile on his face.)
This number would satisfy you.
- Yes, of course.
- Aren't I right?
Please sign the contract. See that?
I'm glad you didn't argue with me
on this.
As men both with protruding teeth.
Don't you worry.
- In the next game...
- Please do well.
- I'll do my best to win!
- All right.
Let's do a good job.
Go, locust!
- Next.
- I should take this with me.
Goodness.
- What was your number?
- He's more than generous.
Did things go well?
I guess it did.
Negotiations went well for him.
- Go, locust! Yes, things went well.
- You...
- Really?
- Yes.
- How much did you receive?
- How much was it?
- I received a lot.
- Really?
- He gladly offered it.
- Let me see.
How much did you get?
(The fool is just happy to have
a salary higher than expected.)
We're a team, remember?
(They request that he tell them
the generous salary he agreed to.)
(He brags about his 30 dollars.)
- How much is it?
- It's a lot, isn't it?
- How much is that in total?
- Show me with your fingers.
- We...
- Is that 80 dollars?
He won 200 dollars, remember?
So 30 dollars per person...
There's the money he has left
from the previous round.
- What?
- He saved some money earlier,
so that has to be added too.
- So 200 dollars and...
- That's right.
Hold on a second.
Isn't he negotiating with
the 200 dollars he won?
That and the money
he saved from earlier.
- What?
- The remaining money.
He wasn't generous at all.
- I need to...
- He has about 1,300 dollars.
(The reason why Jae Suk
was so generous.)
Hold on a second.
- I made a mistake.
- I see.
You have the 200 dollars you won...
and the money
you have left from earlier,
but like a thug,
you quickly agreed
to the 30 dollars.
But you already signed that.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- We'll talk some other time.
You should've told me
that you had more money.
- So it's the total amount?
- I don't have that much.
The money he earned
and the leftover money?
(He can't take it back.)
- He played me.
- He surely did.
I thought he only had
200 dollars to offer.
That's not the case.
- Did he play you?
- How much did you get?
Only 30 dollars.
I'm only worth one cent.
And I'm only worth 0.1 cents.
You're upset when
you're worth 30 dollars?
Can I give them some of my money?
- Of course.
- Really?
I won't accept it.
But I will.
I offer Haha...
- I offer Haha five dollars.
- Thank you.
Can I have at least ten cents?
And five dollars goes to So Min.
- Se Chan, my gosh.
- You still have a chance.
Bend over...
and crawl between my legs.
(Darn you!)
How dare you?
- I won't accept it.
- Suk Jin.
- I'll ask Yeon Koung instead.
- What?
- I'll give you a dollar.
Why? What for?
Bend over and...
(It takes more than expected
to make Suk Jin give up his pride.)
I'm a man of pride, you know.
Suk Jin, 2.5 dollars.
I'm a man of pride.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- With Ji Young...
- Yes?
We came to an agreement
at 200 dollars.
With you...
- Will you cut my salary?
- What?
Of course not.
That's not how I roll.
I'll offer you the same amount.
- What do you say to 200 dollars?
- So 200 dollars.
- Well...
- Then...
- Yes?
(Will she ask for more?)
I'll accept my current salary
of 170 dollars...
if you agree to pay ten dollars each
to the second-string players.
How can you be this generous?
My gosh, I'm touched.
- Give them a raise.
- Really?
- Then I'll stay for 170 dollars.
- Seriously?
- My gosh.
- Yes.
- So Young, how about 170 dollars?
- Sure.
- Yes, I'm happy with that.
- It's 170 dollars.
- Make sure the others get more.
- Sure thing.
They'll only get about
ten dollars more though.
Throw in another five dollars.
- I'd appreciate that.
- Got it.
Hold on. Hee Jin, talk to me.
Hee Jin.
How much is your salary?
I bet she got a lot.
- Can we be open about it?
- Of course.
- But...
- Of course you can tell me.
But you could use
what we're being paid...
to negotiate your salary.
That won't be the case, Ji Young.
Must you be tight?
Truth be told...
- I heard what she was offered.
- I received about...
- She was given 220 dollars.
- Really?
- Just this time around?
- That's right.
- It's 220 dollars.
- Just this time around?
I thought 30 dollars
was on the generous side.
That hurts.
She got 220 dollars
just this time around.
- What?
- For real?
- I've been scammed.
- How's that possible?
- Locust Gym should shut down.
Someone shut down Locust Gym.
- Because...
- Yeon Koung.
- I got 200 dollars.
- The locust...
- You got 200 dollars?
- Just this time around?
- I've been scammed.
- You got 200 dollars?
- Yeon Koung.
- No way.
- He's known to be stingy.
- How much did Hee Jin get?
I once negotiated salaries with
professional baseball players...
and learned that pay cuts
are a touchy subject.
I don't want you
to see it that way though.
Are you telling me
that you'll cut my pay?
Well, you see...
I'm not excited about...
this negotiation
taking a heavy turn.
So how much
are you willing to offer?
Please don't think of this
as a pay cut.
(He offers her 120 dollars,
which is 20 dollars less.)
Sign it, Hye Seon.
(What will be
Yeum Cheater's decision?)
Rather than being a cheater,
- I'll choose to be loyal.
- Sounds good. All right.
So you got another 200 dollars?
- What about you?
- It's 200 for me too.
- But you barely did anything.
- Exactly. He's that generous.
Our trainer is the sweetest.
I got 220 dollars.
(Kim Yeon Koung is sensitive...)
(when it comes to
how players are treated.)
- Is he kidding me?
- You should...
at least ask for 300 dollars.
- Exactly.
- Yes, you should get 300 dollars.
- He'd better agree to it.
- This is why.
We only perform
to the best of our ability...
because our trainer has our backs.
(The world-class rookie
hopes to stop Trainer Yoo's tyranny.)
- Trainer Yoo!
- Goodness, Yeon Koung.
Trainer Yoo, I hope...
- things go smoothly.
- Don't worry and have a seat.
- Did things go well?
- Of course.
Then I hope things go smoothly.
I don't know
what you'll think of this,
but money is tight here at the gym.
You know that, right?
You're starting off
with the excuses.
I would like to...
We did our best,
but it doesn't change that we lost.
- I can't say anything nice.
- But we won the second match.
The second-string players
won it for us though.
- It's not a win for the team.
- So what's my offer?
- Come on.
- You sound slightly aggressive.
- Hardly.
- Your tone...
Trainer Yoo,
- you need to be generous.
- Sorry?
You need to be generous.
Your first offer...
must be generous.
Because...
I heard how the players
on the other team are being treated.
But they won double the prize money.
Don't forget
the initial amount you had.
You started off with more.
(Unlike someone he knows,
she didn't fall for it.)
- Did you think I didn't know?
- Hold on.
So how much?
- Sorry?
- How much do you want?
I'd like 300 dollars.
(I'd like 300 dollars.)
Yeon Koung, don't sign the contract.
(After playing in both games,
she asks for the highest amount.)
Are you kidding me?
- Because...
- That's absurd.
They received 300 dollars.
- That's a lie.
- I saw it for myself.
- You saw the number?
- Yes, I saw the number "300."
- Don't you lie.
- It's the truth!
You...
- Are you Kwang Soo?
- What?
(Her negotiation tactic
seems familiar.)
That's not what this is.
You obviously have more money.
Then, I'll offer you
a ten-dollar raise.
- What does that get me?
- Well,
- it'll be 140 dollars.
- Are you offering 310 dollars?
No, 140 dollars.
- Come on. I'll leave then.
- Let's talk this through.
If Jong Kook
doesn't take you either,
then your salary
will be cut in half.
You think he won't take me?
- That, I'm not sure of.
- He has a lot of money.
(The frugal Trainer Yoo
met his match.)
- Also, Trainer Kook...
- Listen.
doesn't care about money.
- He doesn't care about money?
- He doesn't.
He does for sure.
I'll take 300 dollars and tell them
that you gave me 200 dollars.
- You'll say you took 200 dollars?
- Yes. I'll tell them I got 200.
Save my face, will you?
Why don't you save my face?
I'll play hard in the next game
and bring victory.
I can't afford 300 dollars.
I'm offering you 200 dollars.
I can't give you 300 dollars!
- They're fighting.
- Yeon Koung asked for 300 dollars.
- Is he upset?
- Yeon Koung, move to Tiger Gym.
(No one is willing to yield.)
Ji Young got 320 dollars!
She received that much,
so they'll compare her to me.
Then how am I supposed to work hard?
They'll do as much as they're paid
since they're paid 300, 320 dollars,
so I'll only do enough
for 130 dollars.
How do you think I'll play?
I'll just hang about on the court.
Then I'll just transfer
to the other team, to be blunt.
I can do that, can't I?
You're right, but...
I want to give my best effort.
I want to be fully immersed
in the games.
If you pay me 300 dollars,
- But 300 dollars is...
- I'll pay you back with my passion.
Passion! I'll show you my passion.
- Okay, then.
- Yes?
Here!
I'll pay you back
since you put trust in me.
This is the best I can offer.
(His final offer was 230 dollars,
and she gave in and signed it.)
Great. Don't tell others.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Thank you. I'll work hard.
- All right. Take this.
- I'll lead the team to victory.
- Thank you.
- All right.
My gosh.
How much were you offered?
The second-string players
don't get to negotiate.
You'll all receive ten dollars...
- and move on to the next round.
- Ten dollars?
Trainer Kim, you can trade
one of your second-string players.
Let's settle some things
before that.
Second-string players...
We don't know what you need
to settle with him.
The first-string players are
supposed to pay some of theirs.
It's an internal deal.
- I'll sort it out for you.
- Okay.
We signed a dual contract.
Also... Stop talking about it.
I'm starting to get attached,
so stop.
(I'm starting to get attached,
so stop.)
(He's preparing to detach himself
from his players.)
- Wait a minute.
- I should tell them.
- Well...
- I expected it,
but why won't you meet my eyes?
His tone changed.
- Meet my eyes when you talk.
- His tone changed.
Is there a member you want to keep?
For our team...
Guys, it needs to be fun too.
Are you going to switch them?
You can't send away your players.
- I know. I don't want to.
- You must've gotten close.
They're so warmhearted.
You can't just ditch
players you got attached to.
He's old and sick!
You can ditch me if you want.
Just ditch me.
- I won't.
- What are you saying?
What do you mean by that?
- Make up your mind already.
- Should I take him or not?
- Take him.
- Shall I?
- Of course, you should take him.
- Okay, fine.
I should listen to the opinions
of the first-string players.
- He listens to the players a lot.
- Is he staying on your team?
Yes, he's staying with us.
- That's great.
- That was so cool.
- Thank you.
- They're all so warmhearted.
The players are all so warmhearted.
Let's move to the next building
to have lunch.
- Let's go!
- Should I carry this?
- We should give this back, right?
Just leave them anywhere.
I don't want anyone to see it.
- Gosh, they look so good.
- They look so good.
- They look so good. I'm starving.
- What's happening? They look great.
They prepared so many dishes today.
- Because we have athletes...
How come the dishes are different?
The 1st and 2nd-string players
are having different dishes.
- Oh, really?
- Really?
I guess so.
- I think so.
- Really?
I thought so.
Is there a specific dish you want?
Pay me five dollars.
- No way. I won't eat it.
- Why do you sound so sad?
Then the second-string players
can't have chicken.
The second-string players
Take a seat, guys.
- They served nice dishes today.
- Come sit here.
- Take a seat.
- The second-string players...
are also served well.
Let's try it.
(The Running Man food team prepared
the 8-dish meal themselves.)
- My gosh. Thank you.
- We have nice dishes. Goodness.
- Take a seat.
- Can we eat them?
Everyone, you can enjoy
every dish on your table.
- Take a seat.
- This is...
- This is so mean.
The dishes are so different.
If the second-string players
want to eat...
what the first-string players
are having,
you can ask your trainer.
Also, there are extra menus.
- Really?
- We'll hand you out the menus.
- Buy us more dishes, Trainer Yoo.
- He's right.
Trainer Yoo.
- Let's enjoy the meal together.
- Buy us more dishes.
Let's do that.
Our team isn't doing so well, but...
At least he's treating us
to a nice meal.
Let's treat them to nice meals.
Something like chicken soup.
There are cup noodles.
- Trainer Yoo, we want tteokbokki.
- Wait a minute.
We have to pay this much?
They're way too expensive.
- There's tteokbokki.
- This is...
Oh, we need to pay for them.
I'm sorry, but are we
in Cheongdam-dong?
- Let's serve everyone cup noodles.
- There's japchae.
Everyone needs soup.
- Listen up, everyone.
- And let's have ice cream later.
- What about tteokbokki?
- We should have that too.
- Two tteokbokki.
- Trainer Yoo.
Who wants to have ice cream?
- Me!
- Buy ice cream for everyone.
Who wants to have ice cream?
- Me!
- Buy ice cream for everyone.
- One, two, three, four, five...
- Do you want tteokbokki too?
- Who wants tteokbokki?
- I want tteokbokki!
We'll order two tteokbokki
for each table.
- Sounds good.
- How about cup noodles?
- Order it for them.
- I want cup noodles too.
Wait. Continue your meal.
- What's wrong?
- Please order them now.
- We're starving.
- Are you paying for this?
- I know you're quite loaded.
Since you're loaded,
buy us a nice meal.
Well, then does everyone
want cup noodles?
- Who wants cup noodles?
- Me.
- I want tteokbokki.
- I want cup noodles.
- Tteokbokki?
- Tteokbokki.
Buy cup noodles for each of us
and tteokbokki for each table.
And we'll all have ice cream.
- Okay.
- That sounds good.
Then he's going to spend 400 dollars
on food alone.
Well...
- Buy them for us.
- What?
Hey, Jong Kook.
Wait a minute.
Buy them for us
using the team money.
I could,
but a source told me...
that Jae Suk didn't spend much.
I'll buy you one of these.
Do you want tteokbokki?
- I want tteokbokki.
- I'll get it for you.
All right. You're indeed amazing.
Wait.
Where is bulgogi?
Oh, we have it here.
Wait a minute.
- I get it, but...
- Can I have ice cream too?
- I want ice cream.
- There's ice cream on the menu?
- Yes.
- Are you having it too?
Don't you want to have ice cream?
I know that Ji Young is good
with games, but she eats a lot.
- Wait a minute.
- I can eat more than this.
Hold on.
Then we'll have
a serving of tteokbokki.
And I'll take ice cream as well.
We're always abundant
when it comes to food.
- This is amazing.
- Eat up!
(Meanwhile, Locust Gym decides
to spend 340 dollars on food.)
Trainer Yoo is indeed amazing.
- Trainer Yoo is indeed amazing.
- Indeed.
This is nice.
- Enjoy your food.
- Enjoy.
Enjoy, everyone.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
I guess it's good.
How come the rolled omelet
is so good?
I was starving.
You eat so well, Hye Seon.
(After filling their stomach,
they arrived at Tanhyeon SBS.)
Oh, it's this one.
(The next mission
that makes them exclaim)
It's scary.
This one is scary.
- It's that game.
- I'm not good at this.
It's where we jump off, right?
Isn't it diving?
- What is this?
- What is it?
- It's that game.
- It's where we need to crawl.
- We need to pick the medals.
It's really scary.
Gosh, we haven't played it
for a long time.
(If you move a bit forward,
it'll break.)
(Even the original Long Legs
was scared to death.)
(The styrofoam breaks off completely
at an unexpected timing.)
It's really high from up there.
It's scary.
It's disadvantageous
for those who weigh more, right?
- The ones who weigh more?
- It tests your guts.
It's really scary.
The players who've watched
our show must know this game.
We played Put a Sticker
on the Edge of a Cliff before.
It's really scary.
In an upgraded set,
we're going to test...
if you're maintaining the courage
you built then.
We'll also test the courage
of the new players through this.
- It's called I'm on the Next Cliff.
- I'm on the Next Cliff?
This time, we'll have players from
each team play at the same time.
However, among the seven medals,
you can take one of them.
We'll add the number to the total
length you put the sticker on.
(Each player can acquire a medal.
The length will be added.)
But you can't take two medals.
You can only take one.
So we're taking a medal each.
But we'll multiply the length...
the first-string players
advanced to by 1.5 times.
You got it, right?
We've picked the players
to go first.
Suk Jin and Hye Seon will go first.
Me?
This is good. We won!
- Who is Yeum Hye Seon?
- Me.
"Who is Yeum Hye Seon?"
That's so harsh of him.
The safety gear and stickers
are ready.
- All right.
- Good luck.
If you go on your fours and crawl,
you can reach the end.
Can you feel
when it's going to break?
- It starts to crack from behind.
- Oh, you can feel it?
- It's scary when you go up there.
- It's really scary.
You can't go to the end
because it's scary.
It's higher than I thought.
It's no joke.
It's scarier than you think.
(The experienced player
walks up confidently.)
(But he's scared nonetheless.)
It's so scary.
Gosh, it's higher than I thought.
It must feel different up there.
Right. It must be scary
when you're up there.
You can do it!
(Who will be the winner
of the first match?)
(He's already scared.)
It must be scary
when you're up there.
You can do it!
Should we go one by one
or at the same time?
You'll go at the same time.
It looks like a CEO of some company
is joining the retreat.
CEO Ji, let's go!
- CEO Ji!
- Yes!
- We will...
- You can do it!
Health, blessing, long life!
You can do it, Chairman Ji.
He looks like a chairman.
It looks like a CEO is setting
a good example...
Should I take off my shoes?
- He's setting a good example.
- That's right.
Yeum Cheater.
(CEO Ji's opponent
is a new employee, Yeum Cheater.)
Hye Seon, move confidently.
You must acquire one of the medals
on the way.
They're pro athletes, so...
Be careful!
(She only stepped on it lightly,
but it starts shaking.)
(CEO Ji confidently
takes his place.)
Suk Jin, it's been
quite a while, right?
Gosh, this is incredibly scary.
If you're ready,
- You must acquire the medal too.
- please start.
- Let's go, Hye Seon.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, Yeum Hye Seon!
- Let's go, Locust Gym!
If you fall without sticking
the sticker, it'll be over.
(Yeum Cheater advances
more than Suk Jin.)
Go, Hye Seon!
Grab the medal if you see one.
Get a medal before the board breaks.
- You need to acquire the medal.
- Get the medal.
(Tilting)
Oh, no. Hye Seon's board is bent.
- Hye Seon.
- Hye Seon!
- Get the medal first.
- Get the medal.
Hye Seon, get the medal
that says 20 or 25.
Get the medal!
I want to get the one that says 30.
No, you can't.
You'll end up with zero points.
Hye Seon is going to fall.
It's going to crack.
I can hear the crack!
You must take one.
Take one that says 25.
Let's go, Yeum Cheater.
There you go.
(She grabs a medal that says 25.)
- There you go.
- Take it.
- That's it.
Suk Jin, she already took a medal!
Look at him.
What are you doing?
(While Yeum Cheater
was acquiring a medal,)
(CEO Ji couldn't advance at all.)
This is really scary.
He got the Pfizer shot,
so we shouldn't make him do this.
Mister, if you're not going to play,
then get out!
I'm trying to play here, you punk!
- Get out if you're not playing.
- Who are you calling a punk?
Suk Jin, grab a medal
with a high number.
Hye Seon, stick the sticker
as far as possible.
Take it easy, Hye Seon.
It might crack any minute.
- It might crack any minute.
- Take the medal!
No, that won't do.
Suk Jin, you can't reach
the medal that says 25.
But I should take the one
that says 25.
(Falling)
(She already passed
the halfway point.)
- No, Hye Seon!
- That's it!
- Let's go, Yeum Hye Seon.
- You need to stick the sticker!
(The board is about to break.)
Stick it before the board breaks.
- Hye Seon!
- Stop there, Hye Seon!
- Stick it!
- Hye Seon!
(She slides down to the pool.)
- She stuck the sticker!
- She stuck it.
- She stuck it before she fell.
(Frozen)
- Are you okay?
- She stuck it.
(She succeeded in sticking
the sticker at 3.9m.)
- Well done, Hye Seon.
- Nice one.
- It's 3.9m.
- Well done, Hye Seon.
- Good job, Hye Seon.
- She stuck it before she fell.
- They're so focused.
She stuck the sticker as she fell.
We should do it as she did.
- We should stick it as we fall.
- He took the medal.
(CEO Ji acquires the medal
that says 25.)
- Did you see him? Suk Jin!
- Isn't it scary?
- Suk Jin, slide down!
- Lie down flat on the board.
- Be quiet!
- Slide down with the board.
You saw how Hye Seon did.
(Trainer Kook becomes impatient
as Hye Seon did well.)
- Is it because he's heavier?
- Slide down the board.
That's it. Slide down.
You can go further.
Just slide down and stick it.
- Be quiet.
- Slide down.
His lips are pale.
You don't know how scary
it is up there, do you?
- Your lips are pale!
- Slide down the board!
Give me a round of applause.
- Health, long life...
- Blessing!
That's it. You're almost there.
Stick it at 3m.
Slide down the board.
- Hey.
- Stick it at 3m.
Hey, where did the cheating girl
stick hers?
She's Yeum Cheater.
- "Cheating girl"?
- Hers is at 3.9m.
Just slide down the board.
- I can't do it at my will.
- It's going to break.
(The board is already bent a lot.)
You need to go forward boldly!
- It's going to break.
- You need to go forward!
(Will the oldest 2nd-string player
show us a twist?)
- It's going to break!
- Just stick it!
(He fell helplessly.)
He failed to stick the sticker.
- He failed to stick the sticker.
(He stuck it after he fell.)
(CEO Ji earned no points.)
- All right!
- He failed to stick the sticker.
- He failed.
My lips cracked.
- His lips are bleeding for real.
- His lips cracked.
- Are you okay?
- He's bleeding.
- Gosh.
- Come and take a rest.
Why did his lips crack?
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
- My lips cracked a lot.
- I saw.
He must've bitten on them.
Why did you become so weak
after getting the Pfizer shot?
(The road to become Human Antibody
surely isn't easy.)
I shouldn't be laughing, but I can't
help it. I'm sorry.
Why did you become so weak
after getting the Pfizer shot?
- Give him a wet wipe.
- Why is he...
- He must've gotten weaker.
- Can you give me some tissue?
The next player...
Is anyone willing to go next?
- They're scared.
- I'm scared.
Oh Ji Young.
- Oh Ji Young.
- I'm scared.
Who is going next from your team?
Shin Min A is going next.
- Min A?
- It's Hye Jin.
Min A!
- Good luck.
- Min A.
Shin Min A will go next.
- I think she'll be good at it.
- Hye Jin is going next.
It's fine as long as
I get high points, right?
- That's right.
- I'll go get high points.
Oh, no. What do I do? I'm scared.
She has a fear of heights. We won.
We're in trouble.
Hye Jin has a fear of heights.
- Really?
- She's scared.
You can do it, Hye Jin.
It's higher than I thought.
- Hye Jin, it's scary, right?
- It's higher than I thought.
It feels different
when you're up there.
It's high. It's a lot higher
than I thought.
You need to crawl forward.
You'll never get a chance
to experience something like this.
You can never experience it...
- unless you're on a show.
- You can never experience it.
You can't find it
in an amusement park either.
You can consider it
as a Running Man experience.
Let's go!
- Min A!
You can step on that part.
- It won't break.
- It's safe there.
- You should sit there first.
- Sit there comfortably. That's it.
It might be better
to go on your fours and crawl.
- Min A.
- She should get a medal with 20.
Ji Young, you need to run from there
and stick it at the end.
- I'm speaking from experience.
- Suk Jin, just stay quiet.
(The player who got no points
gives her a tip.)
I'm giving her a tip
because I failed.
Look at him losing his temper.
- That's...
- It must be the side effect...
- of a Pfizer shot.
- What?
He's losing his temper.
- So what I'm saying is...
- It's the side effect.
- He's losing his temper.
- Did he yell at you?
He sounded like my father earlier.
Ji Young, you need to acquire
a medal that says 30.
Suk Jin. Are you okay?
No, I'm not! Go and acquire...
- Let's go!
- Why aren't you moving, Hye Jin?
You need to stick the sticker on it.
You can go forward, Hye Jin.
You shouldn't run.
- Go for it!
- Take a medal above you.
Take a medal that says 15 at least.
- I should take this at least.
- Ji Young might win at this rate.
- Hye Jin, take the ten.
- Hye Jin, you need to take one...
- in front of you.
- Take one in front of you at least.
Ji Young might win fairly easily.
Make sure to go slowly.
Go slowly at all costs.
- She might win fairly easily.
- Wait.
- Take the one that says 20.
- What I'm saying is...
Is it okay to stick the sticker
when the board breaks?
Yes, you can.
(Just stick it before the board
touches the ground.)
Just stick it before the board
touches the ground.
She's going to run.
- I'm going to give it a try.
- Is she going to run?
(Is she going to run?)
- You shouldn't run. It'll break.
- You shouldn't run!
- You shouldn't run.
- Go slowly.
- Just crawl...
- Don't run.
- Ji Young is going to jump, and...
- You should run.
Ji Young, take it slow.
Lie down flat on the board.
- It's better to slide down.
- You want me to slide down?
Ji Young, it won't go
the way you want.
Ji Young, you can't slide down.
Just crawl.
(Then why did you fail?)
- Then why did you fail?
- Crawl like this.
- Why did you fail?
- I realized it after I tried.
I realized it after I tried.
Ji Young,
if you stick it anywhere...
No! Don't stick it there!
Listen. Just...
Trainer Kook, she's...
- Hye Jin!
- Keep your manners.
(The brave player has been
warming up for ten minutes.)
Hye Jin.
- What are you doing, Hye Jin?
- What are you doing?
- Hye Jin.
- Just go!
- It's so scary. What do I do?
- Hurry up.
- Just crawl.
Just crawl.
- Gosh, what is she doing?
- I can only see her feet.
- Hey, Min A.
- Just lie down flat.
(Hey, Min A.
Yeon Koung is upset again.)
Yeon Koung is upset again.
- Get one that says 20!
- Hey!
(The cowardly player finally starts
to move as Yeon Koung is upset.)
- Min A.
- Don't run.
- Min A!
- Get one that says 20!
- Don't run. You're going to fall.
- What about one that says 25?
- Hye Jin, grab the medal first.
- Hye Jin, get one that says 20.
Get the medal that says 20.
- It's okay.
- Get the medal that says 20.
- The medal that says 20.
- No!
- Go forward. Don't take it.
- Don't take that.
That's it. Good job.
(Hye Jin acquired a medal
that says 20.)
- That's it. Good job.
- That was great.
Just lie flat on the board.
- No! No, you can't do that.
- No! Don't do that.
The board will fall,
and you won't be able to stick it.
- Ji Young is moving.
- Ji Young, lie on your stomach.
You need to lie on your stomach.
- Here I go!
- You need to lie on your stomach.
- It's going to break for sure.
- It's going to break.
It'll break
before you can even reach the end.
- Ji Young, jump!
- I'm going to jump!
- Watch your head.
- Hey!
- You need to crawl.
- Don't jump!
- You need to crawl!
- No!
- No! Lie down!
- I'll jump now.
She won't listen.
- What is she going to do?
- Two...
- Hey!
- My gosh.
- Just lie down on the board!
- That's not going to work.
- Watch your head, Ji Young!
- One...
- One,
- What is she going to do?
- two...
- Hey!
Hold on. How am I supposed to stick
the sticker from here?
Min A, don't mind her
and focus on yours.
What is she doing?
Is she swimming up there?
(Next to Min A, the bulldozer
is after one big success.)
- Hey.
- Is she swimming up there?
Oh, no.
(She entered the pool
with her head first.)
- Hey.
- She failed to stick the sticker.
- She failed.
- You should've stuck the sticker!
- She failed to stick the sticker.
(She talked big, but she ended up
earning no points.)
Look at her.
Hey! Can you breathe?
- Is she laughing?
- She's laughing.
She failed to stick the sticker.
- Where is she?
- Are you okay, Ji Young?
- She ended up jumping.
- You fell!
She failed to stick the sticker.
(Oh...)
She says she's embarrassed.
(Oh, she says she's embarrassed.)
(She says she's embarrassed.)
Oh, you must've been embarrassed.
- Ji Young!
- Come out here.
(Miserable end of a bulldozer who
wants to disappear into thin air)
(Ji Young grabbed the medal,
but she couldn't stick the sticker,)
(so she earned no points.)
- Hye Jin! Go slowly.
- Hye Jin.
Just stick it at 3m and come down.
- Just stick it there.
- Hye Jin.
Just stick it there, Hye Jin.
Nice!
(She stuck the sticker.)
- I stuck it!
- She did it.
- All right.
- Well done.
- It's really scary up there.
This team is done for.
Hye Jin stuck the sticker at 3.4m
and gained 20cm.
In total, she gained 360 points.
Well done.
- Good job.
- All right.
- Our ace player will go next.
- Who is it?
- So Min is going next.
- Nice!
Then we should pick someone
who will succeed this time.
- Pick Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. She's brave.
I can't get the medal.
- No, you can.
- I can't take the medal.
- It's gotten even higher.
- That chicken.
I'm serious. It's gotten higher.
Don't be so weak.
Just take a medal that says 40.
(So Min suddenly got scared
at the higher set.)
- Are you ready?
- So Min, I think you can reach 40.
I want to use the bathroom
all of a sudden.
You said the same thing back then.
I really need to use the bathroom.
(When they first played
the same game in Episode 517...)
(Actually,
I think I might pee in my pants.)
(They can't air it
if I pee in my pants, right?)
(She got scared and told everyone
that she might pee in her pants.)
I can't pee in my pants because
I'm wearing gray pants today.
You don't need to fall
even if it breaks.
Get the medal that says 30.
You've done this before.
- Don't get greedy.
- You can do it!
Ji Hyo, it's safe there.
You can even lie there comfortably.
I'm telling you, it's really safe.
It'll never break.
- I'm really scared.
- You can do it, So Min!
Hurry up a little, So Min!
- That's it.
- Slide down.
Hye Jin, do cheers for So Min.
You can do it!
- Let's go!
She can't reach it. Poor her.
- Her arm is too short for it.
- Her arm is too short.
- It's too short!
- That's great, So Min.
- Ji Hyo's arms are too short!
- All right!
Ji Hyo, don't try to get the medal.
You don't have to.
- So Min.
- How about one that says 15?
We don't expect much from you,
so don't overdo it.
- Don't go beyond your capability.
- He's right.
Just grab the medal that says 15
and come back.
- Keep crawling.
- There's one that says 15.
- Stretch as much as you can.
- I'm really scared.
- It's okay.
- We don't expect much from you.
It's okay. Just go forward.
- I can't go forward.
- You can do it.
- Can she do it?
- I won't go forward.
- Just put the sticker.
- Let's go.
Just put the sticker on the floor.
- You can do it.
- Let's go.
You can do it.
(She stretches her arm forward.)
What am I going to do?
- Here it comes.
- Ji Hyo is going to fall.
Ji Hyo is going to fall.
No. It's okay, Ji Hyo.
It's okay. Just go slow.
Ji Hyo, your styrofoam
began to crack.
- That's not true.
- That's not true. Ignore him.
- Ji Hyo.
- Your styrofoam began to crack.
- That's not true.
- Ignore him.
- Not at all.
- Ignore him. It's nonsense.
- You are going to fall soon.
- Gosh.
- So Min, a bit more.
(For So Min,
every moment is a crisis.)
- So Min, a bit more.
- You are going to fall soon.
Gosh, I can't go forward.
- So Min, you need to grab a medal.
- Get 15.
- Can you go further?
You don't need to go further.
Just put the sticker on the floor.
You did it. Come back out.
- Just put the sticker on the floor.
- So Min.
So Min.
So Min, where are you going?
(So Min, where are you going?)
- So Min, get 15.
- Take off 15.
- Grab 15.
- Take off 15. It's right above you.
- Go slow.
- Back off and grab 15.
Okay.
- She put the sticker.
- There you go.
So Min, we don't expect much.
Come back.
(Hurried)
- Nice play.
- Good job.
Gosh, it was so scary.
It was so scary.
Ji Hyo, just put the sticker
on the floor.
- Put the sticker and come back.
- That's right.
No. It will break if you go further.
(She keeps moving forward
without hesitation.)
Put the sticker on the floor.
- Aren't you scared?
- I am surprised it didn't break.
There you go.
How do you have a smile
on your face?
(She charges forward.)
How do you have a smile
on your face?
(Breaking)
- That was insane.
- Good job.
- That's it.
- She is good.
Ji Hyo did much better
than I expected.
Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook is swooning over here.
(Jong Kook is swooning over here.)
I can't believe it.
- I didn't say anything.
- Jong Kook, I did it.
I didn't say anything.
- He is swooning over here.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Jong Kook is swooning over here.
Nice, Ji Hyo.
- Good job.
- Nice shot. You are the ace.
- You did well.
You did well.
- I did my best.
- Eun Jin.
- Let's go.
- You can do this.
- Let's go, Eun Jin.
- It was so scary.
(Eun Jin and Hee Jin are up next.)
When you were down here,
you were like, "It's okay."
"It's just a little bit bent."
When you got up there...
(Screaming)
I usually cry.
You ordered us around
when you were down here.
- This is so scary.
- Hee Jin, is it scary?
Eun Jin, we won't be able to do it.
Are you scared? Get down.
It will be less scary
if you get down.
- Eun Jin, let's go.
- Come on.
Hee Jin, it won't break
when you are there.
- Hee Jin, get 15.
- You are at the safe area.
It's bending too much.
- It's scary, right?
- Get down.
- I think it's bending already.
- It's okay.
- You need to get down first.
- Come on down.
- Get down.
Hye Seon and Hye Jin,
cheer for them.
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Eun Jin, don't be too scared.
- Let's go.
- You are doing well.
- Get down on your knees.
- Try your best to go 3m.
- Get your hands on the floor.
- There you go.
- Push forward.
- Go slowly.
- Get 15.
- Eun Jin, don't be too scared.
- Let's go.
Eun Jin, you are fearless.
You need to get down first.
- Come on down.
- Get down.
- I can't do this.
- Hye Seon and Hye Jin,
- cheer for them.
- Let's go.
- Stay in the lane.
Get down on your knees.
Get your hands on the floor.
- There you go.
- Get your hands on the floor.
Hold on.
- Hee Jin.
- Get 15.
- Eun Jin, are you going to get it?
(Hee Jin can't get the medal
that is right in front of her.)
Don't look at Eun Jin.
- Hold on.
- It's okay.
- How did you get down?
(How did you get down?)
- Eun Jin.
If you go slowly, you will fall.
You should go fast
and put the sticker on the floor.
- It's bent already.
- Eun Jin, it's quite bent.
- Eun Jin.
- Just put the sticker.
- Eun Jin, it's quite bent.
- It's bent already.
- Eun Jin.
- Just put the sticker.
(The styrofoam got bent
while she inched forward.)
- Eun Jin.
- Just put the sticker.
- Eun Jin, it's quite bent.
- Eun Jin.
(She charges forward.)
She did it.
(Eun Jin dived.)
- She put the sticker.
- Eun Jin, it's quite bent.
- Eun Jin.
(She put the sticker
on the 3.4m mark...)
(and fell!)
- She put the sticker.
- It counts.
- Good job.
- She put the sticker.
- Hurrah.
Let's go.
How was it?
- Was it scary?
- Hee Jin, it was so scary.
It was so scary.
(Teddy Bear is having a crisis.)
Hee Jin, hurry up and do something.
Do something.
Put the sticker on the floor.
Hee Jin, take off 15.
- Put it on the 2m mark.
- Take off 15.
First, take off 15.
- It won't come off.
- Hey.
- Hee Jin, are you okay?
- You have to do better than that.
- There you go.
- You saw the others do it.
It won't break
even if you advance halfway.
- It won't break.
- We will tell you.
- Hee Jin, there you go.
- Come on.
- Go forward.
- Go as slow as you can.
Don't do that!
(Don't do that!)
(Why did he say that
when she got down nicely?)
Hold on. What is your problem?
- Mister.
- Why are you angry?
- I want my team to win.
- What is your problem?
- It's the side effect of a vaccine.
- There you go.
It's okay.
Don't put your leg
over the threshold.
(Hee Jin tries to go forward.)
- It's okay.
- It's bending.
It's okay.
- Oh, no.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
(Locust Gym makes a fuss
when it shakes a little bit.)
- Don't go further.
- You shouldn't go further.
No. Just listen to us. It's fine.
- It's fine.
- It's about to break.
- Listen to us,
- It's game over.
- You are going to fall.
- It's really bent.
Hey.
- Put the sticker on the floor.
- Do it now, Hee Jin.
- Put the sticker.
- I am honestly scared.
- It's fine.
- Hee Jin.
I am saying this to you
with seriousness.
- You are in danger.
- That's not true. Not at all.
I spit on you!
- You are in danger.
- That's not true. Not at all.
I spit on you!
Good job.
- What was that?
- Good job.
Have you no manners?
Hee Jin has no manners!
Put the sticker on the floor.
Put the sticker on the floor
and back off.
- Reach further.
- You can go forward.
Hee Jin, you are in danger.
- You are safe.
- Hey, it's going to break.
- Gosh.
- It's not true.
My eardrums almost burst.
- Come on.
- My eardrums almost burst.
- Right now...
- You are in danger.
You are totally safe.
Hee Jin, you are totally safe.
- No way. It's really bent.
- That's not true.
- It isn't bent.
- Hee Jin, it isn't bent.
- You are fine.
Put the sticker on the floor.
- It's okay.
- Put the sticker on the floor.
- Stop there.
- It's okay.
- Put the sticker on the floor.
- Stop there.
Put the sticker.
Hee Jin, put the sticker.
Put the sticker and go back.
- Put the sticker.
- One, two, three.
Put the sticker and go back.
- You are going to fall.
- No, you are fine.
- It's bent.
- It's going to break.
You are fine.
- She didn't put the sticker.
- She did it.
(Hee Jin picks up her courage
for the first time.)
- She didn't put the sticker.
- She did it.
(Did she fail to put the sticker?)
- She didn't put the sticker.
- She did it.
She did it.
- She put it as she fell.
- I put it as I fell.
- Review the video.
Come on.
(She put it right before she fell.)
She put it.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Thank goodness.
- I put it.
Good job, Hee Jin.
- It was so scary.
- Good job.
- What am I going to do?
- Yeon Koung.
- Yeon Koung, let's go.
- Seriously.
- Yeon Koung.
- You need to do this.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. You can do it.
- It's your turn.
- You are cool.
- Yeon Koung.
- Locust Gym.
- Let's go.
(From Tiger Gym,
So Young will go next.)
- It's so scary.
- Good job.
- We got this.
- Get down.
- Yeon Koung, let's go.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Since I am tall,
I feel like I am up higher.
- It's understandable.
- Yeon Koung, hit the 4m mark.
(Yeon Koung suddenly takes off
the medal that says ten.)
All right.
- Yeon Koung, let's go.
- What are you doing?
- Yeon Koung.
- Did she take it off?
Why did you get ten?
Look over here.
- You should have gotten 30.
- Yeon Koung.
Why did you get ten?
- You will go far, right?
- It's so scary.
It's scary.
- Shall I take it off?
- Get ten.
- Just take it off.
Take it off.
- Take it off.
- Shall I take it off?
Take it off.
- You know...
- Go forward.
You know, I am heavier.
- You can do it.
- Slide forward.
- All right.
- Shall I go slowly?
- Yes.
- Go slowly.
It's so scary.
Come on.
(They set off carefully.)
Let's go.
- There you go, So Young.
- You are doing well, Yeon Koung.
- Go slow.
- You are doing well.
- You are doing well, Yeon Koung.
- Yeon Koung.
You are doing well.
- Get down.
- Yeon Koung, reach the 3m mark.
- What?
- She is relaxed.
You need to reach the 3m mark.
(How am I supposed to do that?
Are you insane?)
- Trainer Yoo.
- You got this.
Why don't you come up here
and do it?
- That's good.
- She is relaxed.
(So Young goes forward
with a grin on her face.)
That's a nice facial expression.
- Go further.
- That's a nice facial expression.
Stretch out your arms.
- There you go.
- Then you can put it anytime.
(Laughing)
- So Young.
- That's good.
(The strong-minded woman laughs
even when she's on a steep slope.)
It's going to break.
Oh, no.
So Young.
(The onlookers are
even more nervous.)
It's going to break.
- Oh, no.
- Push forward.
It's going to break.
(So Young goes forward.)
She did it!
It's going to break.
(She put the sticker right away.)
(The moment she began to fall,)
(she put the sticker on the floor
with a smile.)
(It was the perfect dive.)
- Lee So Young!
- That was great.
- It was the best.
- You did an amazing job.
You did it.
She is so athletic.
She is always relaxed.
- Lee So Young!
- That was great.
- Yeon Koung, you can't lose.
- Hurry up.
- Focus.
- Yeon Koung, you can't lose.
I am heavier than her.
- Let's give it a try.
- Yeon Koung.
- Let's give it a try. We can do it.
- Let's give it a try.
Get down.
(Here is why they are saying,
"Let's give it a try.")
- Let's give it a try.
- Yes.
(Let's give it a try.
Let's not leave any regrets.)
- Yeon Koung.
- Let's give it a try.
Go past the 3m mark.
- Yeon Koung.
- Let's give it a try.
- Go past the 3m mark.
- Hey.
(Hold on!)
- That's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo's facial expression.
(Kwang Soo's facial expression)
Let's give it a try.
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, we missed you.
You are nearly done.
- It's shaking a lot.
- Kwang Soo.
That's Kwang Soo's
facial expression.
- Don't put your feet down.
- Hey.
- Kwang Soo.
- Look at the Jimmy Jib.
Kwang Soo.
Yeon Koung.
- Yeon Koung, come on.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yeon Koung.
- Look at the Jimmy Jib.
It's time to look at the Jimmy Jib.
Go faster.
Stretch out your hand.
(The parallel universes
of the lanky people)
Yeon Koung, don't move so much.
Yeon Koung, move forward.
Stretch out your hand.
- You are going to fall.
- Stretch out your hand.
- Let's give it a try.
- Yeon Koung.
Let's give it a try.
- For goodness' sake.
Come on.
You need to move forward.
Hey.
(Wriggling)
- This is fun.
- Her feet are touching.
- You need to move forward.
- Move forward.
- Who knew she was like this?
- Come on. You can move forward.
- This is fun.
(Yeon Koung hasn't even reached
the halfway point.)
- All right. Let's give it a try.
- A bit more.
Yeon Koung.
- Let's give it a try.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Yeon Koung, throw your body.
- Throw your body.
Throw your body.
- Go.
Come on.
- What?
- Throw your body.
- Come on.
- You can't jump.
You can't jump.
You talk big
because this doesn't concern you.
- Hey.
- My goodness.
- You little...
- This concerns all of us.
- I will end you when I go down.
- Cheer for her.
- She is angry.
- Let's go.
- Just reach the halfway point.
- Yeon Koung.
- Yeon Koung, let's go.
Just reach the halfway point.
- Yeon Koung, don't do that.
- Hey.
(Yeon Koung, don't do that.)
Yeon Koung.
- Come on!
- She put the sticker.
(The junior volleyball players
throw sponges at her.)
Now...
- Come on!
- She put the sticker.
- For goodness' sake.
- She took it off.
- Move forward.
Go. Move forward.
Move forward.
Hurry up.
Stretch out your hand.
- Don't do that.
- Move forward.
- Hurry up.
- A bit more.
- Throw your body.
- Push your body forward.
Go a bit further.
- You got this.
- Go.
Throw your body.
Throw your body and put the sticker.
- You got this.
- Throw your body.
Throw your body and put the sticker.
Why do you keep telling me
to throw my body?
I am not a bird that can fly, okay?
- You are spouting nonsense.
- Let's go.
She is exactly like Kwang Soo.
(She is exactly like Kwang Soo
when she is annoyed.)
- No.
- Yeon Koung, put the sticker.
- Okay.
- You are doing well.
- Now is the time.
- Hurry up and put the sticker.
- No.
- Yeon Koung, put the sticker.
- Put the sticker.
- No.
(She needs to put the sticker now.)
Yeon Koung, put the sticker.
- She did it.
(Thankfully, the sticker
stuck to the floor.)
- Did she succeed?
- She fell after she put it.
She put it after she fell.
- She put it after she fell.
Review the video.
- Are you okay?
- She put it after she fell.
Yeon Koung, are you okay?
She is going to swear!
Hey. I put it, you punk.
Review the video.
(Long Legs is angry.)
Hey. It should count.
You did it.
I know how it feels now.
Okay. Good job.
- Good job.
- Seriously.
- You did it.
- I want her on the show.
I want her on the show.
Jae Suk, she is the best.
- I want her on the show.
- I hope she joins the show.
You know, I found a replacement
for Kwang Soo.
Nothing is amiss.
Her height and everything else
are perfect.
She is perfect.
Everyone.
The scores are so far apart...
that the last round
won't make a difference.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- It's over.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Why are you clapping?
- Didn't we win?
- We lost.
- We did it.
We lost.
Please divide the members
into 1st-string and 2nd-string.
- Hold on.
- I will be a second-string player.
Yeon Koung should join
the second-string team.
Why?
- I worked hard.
- Yes you did, but in general...
- Just this once.
- Switch places with Min A.
- Min A.
- Okay.
(Hye Jin and Yeon Koung
switch places.)
- Switch places with Min A.
- I haven't done much either.
Switch places. Hold on.
- Switch places with Eun Jin.
- Really?
- Eun Jin.
- Today...
- Min A did a good job.
- Thank you.
- She did a good job.
- I acknowledge that.
(Meanwhile, Trainer Kook)
One last game remains.
They switched some players.
Everything will be all right...
if the players cut me some slack
during the salary negotiation.
Before the last game, we will have
the last salary negotiation.
Let's resume after we clean up.
- You get to negotiate, right?
- Yes.
I am jealous.
Trainer Yoo and Trainer Kook,
listen up.
The difference
between the trainers' money is...
less than 50 dollars.
The two of us?
(The difference is
about 50 dollars.)
What? Really?
- They need to save up money.
- It's less than 50 dollars.
During the salary negotiation...
They need to save up money.
- Eun Jin, welcome.
- Hello.
- Please sit down.
- Okay.
It's good to have you here.
Eun Jin, how much do you want?
Please write down the number.
(Despite the smiling face,
she isn't easy.)
- How much do you want?
- Please write down the number.
- Let me see the amount first.
- I am thinking about 50 dollars.
(Did you say 50 dollars?)
My first salary was 120 dollars.
You cut it down
by more than 50 percent.
Trainer Kook and I are
only 50 dollars apart.
We spent too much on the meal.
Still, 50 dollars is too much.
- How about 60 dollars?
- How about 70 dollars?
(How about 70 dollars?)
(Sighing)
- Okay. 70 dollars.
- That's good enough for me.
You will pay
the second-string players, right?
I can't do that
unless your salary is 50 dollars.
Give me 60 dollars
and pay the 2nd-string players.
- Okay.
(Eun Jin agreed on 60 dollars.)
Since we have 400 dollars... Okay.
Are you done? That was quick.
How much did you get?
- Half.
- How much?
- Min A, come on in.
- Did you get 60 dollars?
She got 60 dollars.
That's so little.
We agreed upon 70 dollars at 1st,
but he said he wouldn't be able to
pay the second-string players then.
- So I lowered the price.
- That's heartwarming.
- How much did she get?
- He should be able to pay us.
- She got 60 dollars.
- I learned what teamwork is today.
Are the numbers
susceptible to change?
How did you learn what teamwork is?
- No one went to the other team.
- That's right.
- We stayed together.
You are right.
It's the first time
I saw something like that here.
So Min, you can't be sure yet.
- You can't be sure yet.
- He is thinking about ditching me.
That's not true.
It's up to Trainer Yoo.
- Hello.
- Min A, welcome.
Min A, what was your initial salary?
- Me?
- Yes.
- It was 110 dollars.
- It was 110 dollars, right?
Then 20 dollars got added to it.
You won't place last.
- No.
- I am sure of it.
So you want to give me
a small amount.
(The players aren't as easy
as Trainer Yoo would like.)
It's not like that.
Let's make it 70 dollars.
How about 80 dollars?
Seven is my favorite number.
So you should add 10
and make it 80 dollars.
I have no greed.
I just want 80 dollars.
- Okay. Let's make it 80 dollars.
- Okay.
- Let's hurry up with the contract.
- Let's hurry up.
- Okay.
How much do you want?
Please make an offer first.
- You should tell me.
- Please make an offer first.
- Shall I do that?
- Yes.
The team always makes
an offer first.
Hold on. Please whisper it to me.
How much do I have right now?
We are at the bottom.
Why do I need to sacrifice myself
for the team?
We ended up at the bottom
without a chance to do something.
To be honest,
the talk of teamwork is all a ruse.
The trainers take all the money,
but we are forced to struggle
with them.
(He begins to badmouth
the trainers.)
- He just gave us tteokbokki.
- You are right.
(Getting up)
You have a point.
- You worked so hard,
- Seriously.
but the 3 1st-string players took
all the money.
- It's ridiculous.
- If they have a conscience...
They just say that we are a team.
- You are right.
- The trainers are the bad ones.
- There is a feud between them.
- They are the bad ones.
Let's be honest.
How did the gym make money?
We did all the menial work.
You are right.
How did the gym make money?
Ji Hyo crawled
to put the sticker on the floor.
Did you succeed?
- Kwang Soo.
- She didn't succeed,
- but Ji Hyo did.
- All right, Kwang Soo.
- Ji Hyo succeeded.
- But Ji Hyo...
- Kwang Soo.
- Ji Hyo is a second-string player.
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, calm down.
- I mean...
- Feeling! Say, "Intuition!"
- Feeling! Cross!
- Intuition! Cross!
(Feeling! Intuition! Cross!)
My goodness.
It's good to see you again,
Kwang Soo.
Feeling! Intuition! Cross!
- One more time. Feeling! Cross!
- Intuition! Cross!
My goodness.
- I am in tears.
- Kwang Soo came back this way.
That's so funny.
(While they have quality time
with Kwang Soo)
- So that will be the price.
- Yes.
My goodness.
- Good idea.
- As long as I avoid the bottom...
- That's right.
- We can win the next game.
That's right.
- I am running out of money.
- I don't know about that.
I made a sacrifice.
How much are you getting?
You're getting a lot of money.
Hye Seon, listen.
I don't know how much money
they are getting, but...
They all get at least 200 dollars.
(She lies by instinct.)
To be honest, I regretted it before.
You know my nickname
is Yeum Cheater.
I hesitated earlier.
I'll give you 220 dollars. Good?
I want 225.
You want 225 dollars?
(She's the first one
to ask for another 5 dollars.)
- Let's make it 220.
- Make it 225.
- It's 220.
- What about 223?
(Embarrassed)
(He gives up and signs
with her at 223 dollars.)
- Feeling!
- Intuition!
(Salary: 223 dollars)
- My gosh.
- That's nice.
All right. It's over. Since you won,
you can trade
one second-string player.
- But we... Have a seat.
- Okay.
(He can trade one player he wants.)
But...
Earlier, I thought...
it would be nice to keep
our team as it was.
But one of you...
went to Tiger Gym...
and checked her salary there.
- Her salary?
- Really?
- Yes.
- Who?
(Did one of the players go to
Tiger Gym and checked her salary?)
Her salary?
- I mean...
- It will just break...
- our trust.
- Who was that?
So Min.
No.
Why did you ask
about your salary there?
- So Min.
- Did you really do that?
It's not that I asked
about my salary there.
I just checked to see if there was
anyone who wanted to join our team.
(A little earlier)
(Sneaking)
I paid them too much.
Do you want to join? No?
I need to get something from him.
- Really?
- Why?
Do you want to leave your team?
No. I'm just asking.
She's funny.
She had one foot in the team.
When she signed
with you earlier, she said...
we had good teamwork.
She said she realized
what it was like for the first time.
But she was doing that
right before she said that.
- Right. That's what I mean.
- She betrayed us.
- I can't believe this.
- We all are betrayed.
You guys know
what I've been through.
I don't have much money,
but I even bought you...
You bought us food.
I even paid for the ice cream.
But three of the ice cream bars
were left over!
(Trainer Yoo has been
counting everything.)
So Min, come on here.
Don't remove her.
Don't you have loyalty?
You can't do this.
- But...
- He has no sense of loyalty.
Just embrace them all.
Jong Kook, think of this.
This episode will be aired
for two weeks.
And I've had her the whole time.
(And I've had her the whole time.)
He has good reason.
- Don't you understand?
- I see.
He's right.
- You guys are unbelievable.
- Right.
Trainer Kook just said...
- Trainer offered me...
- Don't say that.
- Don't say anything.
- What did he say?
- I understand your point.
- He said he'd take So Min in.
And he wants me to take Suk Jin.
(He wants me to take Suk Jin in.)
(Me?)
- No.
- Hang on.
Come here. Hey.
- If I had to.
- How could you...
If I had to...
- He's right.
- You're so mean.
Did you take that off?
I have a pain relief patch
on my neck.
- All right.
- If I had to...
You used me.
It looks like you're wearing
a turtleneck from the back.
It looks like
you're wearing a turtleneck.
- All right then. Let's do this.
- Do what?
Send Suk Jin to me
and give me 100 dollars.
(Send Suk Jin to me
and give me 100 dollars.)
You jerks!
(You jerks!)
You ungrateful idiots!
My goodness.
- That's funny.
- Why?
My salary is 0.01 dollars,
and you ask for 100 dollars?
(My salary is 0.01 dollars,
and you ask for 100 dollars?)
This is really upsetting.
All right then. I have no choice.
I'll go.
- Yeon Koung, what are you doing?
- Why would you do that?
Kwang Soo, don't be like that.
- Kwang Soo is being weird.
- Hey.
It's taking too long.
Kwang Soo, think.
- Just make up your mind.
- Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo?
- You have to make up your mind.
Kwang Soo, we are on the same page.
- Feeling!
- Intuition!
- Cross!
(Again, feeling, intuition, cross.)
- We're on the same page.
- You two are the same.
- All right then.
- Okay.
I'll trade her with Haha.
- I'll trade her with Haha.
(Locust Gym chose Haha
who is a good second-string player.)
- Haha?
- Join us.
- I have no other choice.
- Without a deal?
It's a choice for my team.
- All right.
- Good.
(Tiger Gym tells Haha something
at the moment.)
Hey, what are you doing?
We will give you the money.
- Make it even.
- Sixty dollars.
Make it even.
- Twenty dollars from each.
- Okay.
- You won't lose.
- You'll get 60 dollars.
We will get you the money.
I'll give him the money.
I'll give you.
Go. All right.
Okay.
- We have to win.
- We must win.
Keep your energy level high.
- What is this?
- Is this possible?
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
Let's do this. No regrets.
(Between victory and penalty,)
(they get the last chance.)
I looked like a fool.
(The trainers will decide
the fate of their 3-week salaries.)
(Who will be the loser
and get the humiliating penalty?)
(And...)
(Firenze, Italy)
(What line of business are you in?)
(I import fashion products
from Italy.)
(How is your diaper business going?)
(It's a meeting of smugglers
who sell fake goods.)
(And they have
fancy Western dishes?)
(But it's too much.)
(Aren't we getting lunch today?)
(No, you'll get a lot of food.)
(They have to taste and experience
everything to be Italian.)
(The hillbilly members with
rustic tastes are knocked out.)
(The rustic ladies and gentlemen
try to become the bourgeoisie.)
(Did you ever date a celebrity
whom you met on a variety show?)
(I don't want to pay my membership
fee to Jong Kook's soccer club.)
(I think Running Man is
a long-run show because of me.)
(He was like that at first.)
(Just say that you made it happen.)
(I must say I made it happen.)
(To Become Italian Ladies and Gentlemen,
Elegant Road of Western Dishes)