- Now we have the final mission.
- Okay.
Here is the second recipe.
- It's a pancake.
- This is nice.
- That's easy to make.
It's delicious. I love it.
- How many eggs do we need?
- You need five eggs.
- Again?
- Then...
- We have 2.
- We have 2, so we need 3.
- How many?
- I'll bring one of mine.
Let's look for it first. If we don't
find anything, I'll give you mine.
- Me too.
- And you give yours.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- This is the last mission.
- Okay.
The last mission
will be an individual game.
Okay.
Three members of each team
will be taggers.
The rest of you are supposed
to hide in this room.
- Really?
- My gosh.
There's no place to hide.
This is what you're going to do.
The remaining 8 members excluding
the 2 taggers from each team,
will choose a spot...
somewhere in this room
and stand there.
Once the eight members
are done hiding,
one of the two taggers
from each team...
will wear an eye mask.
And the other will carry the tagger
on his back to a random spot.
The tagger with an eye mask on...
should tag the rest
of the members for one minute.
The ones who survive
until the end get one point each.
The tagger who finds more than
5 members gets 3 points.
There will be three rounds.
The three members with the highest
points get two eggs each.
We came up with a list of matches.
- Ha Do Kwon versus Haha.
- Okay.
Se Chan versus Chung Hwa.
(Se Chan versus Chung Hwa)
Jong Kook versus Jae Suk.
(Jong Kook versus Jae Suk)
But it's not
a head-to-head match though.
I see.
Right? Are you okay with that?
In Round One...
My goodness.
- Gosh.
- All right.
Round One is Do Kwon versus Haha.
I'll give you one minute.
(The tagger, Haha covers his eyes.)
- You can use anything in this room.
- Okay.
Can I hide in here?
(They try to find a place
where they can't be found.)
Where will you be?
Will you hold onto the wall?
There's no place to hide.
This is...
Here.
There's no place to hide.
You can put him down
anywhere you want.
(The old man hides.)
Do Kwon.
This is
an individual game after all.
- Take me to where they are.
- Okay.
I'll do the same
when it's your turn.
I'll do the same.
(Se Chan finds out
that these two are joining forces.)
I think one minute is too short.
Okay.
(Over there.)
(Yong Gu is planning
to betray Haha.)
You have 20 seconds left.
Once the time is up, you can't move.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Time's up. No one can move now.
Carry him on your back.
One, two, and three.
Haha, give me your hand.
(The tagger wears a flour glove.)
You have one minute
from the moment you're down.
- Take me to where they all are.
- Okay.
(Where should I put him down?)
I'll release a zombie.
(Send him to a place
where there's no one around.)
(Do Kwon's choice...)
(is a corner.)
Where am I?
(The little zombie is
right next to Chung Hwa.)
Do Hwon, put him down.
You have one minute.
(The time limit of 1 minute begins.)
Where am I?
Where is this?
Where am I now? I have no idea.
(I survived.)
(Haha heads to the back room.)
Where is this place?
I hear something.
(Haha steps back towards Se Chan.)
(Will Se Chan be
Haha's first victim?)
(He loses Se Chan within his reach.)
(Now Haha heads to So Min
feeling after the wall.)
(He goes close to So Min
covered in blankets.)
There's someone here.
So Min is out.
Sorry, So Min.
So Min, I'm really sorry.
- You have 15 seconds left.
- I don't want to do this.
(Jeon So Min is out.)
It's here.
I'm so upset.
You have 15 seconds left.
(The two members were relieved
outside the room.)
(The little zombie's
surprise attack)
There must be
someone behind the sofa.
- Here's one.
- Jae Suk is out.
(Jae Suk is out.)
(There is little time left.)
(Will he tag Jong Kook as well?)
There's one more here.
Jong Kook is out.
Time's up.
- Is it over?
- It's over.
- Haha.
- How did you find me?
Haha, you almost got me.
You were right over there.
- It was so close.
- Who was here?
- Haha, you just went past me.
- Where did you put me down?
Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Se Chan,
Chung Hwa, and Young Ji
get one point each.
Okay.
This is really hard.
Now it's Do Kwon's turn.
- All right.
- It was really funny.
You have one minute.
Go ahead and hide.
- Should we hide again?
- I was out in the open.
I'll stay here.
Suk Jin, you can't go out.
Seo Jin, are you going in there?
Stay quiet.
(Suk Jin's location notice service)
Who do you want to find?
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook!)
(Yong Gu cares
only about Jong Kook.)
(His target, Jong Kook is
trying hard not to get tagged.)
(Se Chan pretends he's a cameraman.)
This is tricky.
You have ten seconds left.
This is really hard.
(Se Chan's camera)
Five.
Four.
Three.
- Two.
- This is an individual game.
One.
- Move him now.
- Okay.
All right. One, two, and three.
My gosh.
- Sit here.
- Sit?
One minute starts.
(He starts searching.)
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Jae Suk)
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook)
(Do Kwon crawls toward Ji Hyo.)
(At that moment!)
(He changes his course
toward Jong Kook.)
(The hyena smelled Jong Kook.)
There's something here.
Out.
(Kim Jong Kook is out.)
(Yong Gu is
Jong Kook's natural enemy.)
He found Jong Kook right away.
He's really good at this.
This is really hard.
(He goes past Chung Hwa.)
(He's about to touch Se Chan.)
- What is this?
- I'm a cameraman.
I'm sorry.
(Do Kwon fell for Se Chan's
lame impression.)
(Se Chan survived.)
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
(An unwelcomed guest shows up
right before the ending.)
(Will Jae Suk be out first?)
(Will the time be up first?)
Time's up.
(Checking)
(Shouting)
That was so close.
That's amazing.
He was right in front of me.
I turned around.
How did you survive?
He just went past me.
This is really hard.
- It's difficult.
- It's hard.
Round Two is
Jong Kook versus Jae Suk.
Okay.
Please sit here.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
All right.
Take me to a spot with many members.
Suk Jin and everyone. Okay?
All right. It's my turn.
I hear something.
I hear something on my left.
The back of my left.
(Yoo Zombie pretends
that he's sharp.)
At my seven o'clock.
I can see.
Someone's moving.
(Running)
I know who's running here.
It's Haha.
I can see it.
(Young Ji joins them
in messing with him.)
Yang Se Chan.
I smell his feet. It's Se Chan.
(I smell his feet. It's Se Chan.)
(They found out
something last week.)
(But last time she was here,)
(they were dirty too.)
(Young Ji's soles are always dirty.)
(Another fact is revealed today.)
(Her feet are not just dirty.
They smell too.)
I'm sure.
I'm sure it's him.
I can smell his feet.
(The idol artist is easygoing
when it comes to her feet.)
- Get him on your back.
- Okay.
(All the members are done hiding.)
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
All right.
- You can start moving.
- Jae Suk.
- I'll make things easy for you.
- Okay.
- I'll do the same for you.
(Horse Jong Kook carries
Yoo Zombie on his back.)
- Jong Kook. Oh, gosh.
- Oh, dear. My gosh.
Oh, boy.
(Touching)
(Seok Sam got caught in 1 second.)
I found one.
Suk Jin is out.
Was it Suk Jin?
Hey, seriously.
- Jong Kook.
- Oh, another one is here.
- I think...
- Haha is out.
I can't believe you.
What was that?
Wait. I hear something around here.
- It's me.
- Oh, I see.
Hold on. I'll move to this side.
Be careful. Good.
Wait. What's this?
Someone put the table here.
- Who are you?
- Do Kwon is out.
I found you. All right.
(Do Kwon who tried to cheat is out.)
I think someone else is here.
(He eliminated 3 people
and needs 2 more to get points.)
(But he's moving
in the wrong direction.)
- They're all cameramen.
- Is that so?
Turn around.
There are only cameras here.
He doesn't believe him.
- Those are expensive cameras.
- He doesn't believe it.
He trusts no one.
(He keeps moving as he wants,
ignoring their advice.)
Jae Suk, don't act
like you know where everyone is.
- Hold on.
- You have ten seconds left.
I'll go this way.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
- Time's up.
- Okay.
(Time's up.)
- Gosh.
- Four of them were standing there.
- There were four people there.
- Oh, man.
- What a shame.
- I put you down where they were.
- That's a shame.
- My goodness.
- But I couldn't see at all.
- How could you put him down there?
- Exactly. How could you?
- I slipped.
- You're lying.
- Gosh.
- No. He wouldn't do it on purpose.
- I slipped just as I said.
Why would I have done it?
You know I'm strong enough.
Exactly. That's nonsense.
(Suk Jin pats off the flour
after losing the argument.)
- You're covered with flour.
- Look at Suk Jin.
Look at Suk Jin.
You got so much flour on you.
I got so much on me.
Please put on the blindfold.
- There's no place to hide now.
- Let's hurry up.
Guys, Viper is up next.
- Where should we hide this time?
- Exactly. There's no place to hide.
We've hidden at every place in here.
- They're all standing behind us.
- Okay.
- Are you two allies?
- No.
- You shouldn't do that.
- We're not allies.
I won't tell him.
Five.
(They decided to split up to fool
the 2 Grand Award winners.)
Four.
Three.
(Frog sat on the karaoke machine.)
- Two.
- I can hear you all moving.
One.
Now, please hop on his back.
- Got it.
- Okay. I'll do that.
- Someone's in the middle. Okay.
- Go straight once I put you done.
- Here we go.
- I should mark on them.
- All right.
- You're good to go.
(The allies start moving.)
We're going this way.
Excuse us. Oh, dear.
- Oh, my.
- I'll put you down over there.
Okay.
(Go over there.)
Where do you want us to go?
That way?
Over there?
(Flustered)
All right. Please excuse us.
Sir, I'm sorry.
- I think I just heard something.
- I'm sorry.
I'll put you down here.
Okay.
- All right. Go.
- Okay. Oh, dear.
(Jae Suk put him down
where he can find many people.)
- Oh, here?
- There's one on your right too.
Oh, here?
- Oh, dear. Who are you?
- Ji Hyo is out.
(Ji Hyo got eliminated right away.)
- Oh, my.
- Suk Jin is out.
Hey, Jae Suk.
- Who are you?
- You made it too easy.
- Jae Suk, come on.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I found another one.
- Gosh. What are you two doing?
- It's not like that.
- Oh, gosh. What's this?
- Is this a wall?
- You shouldn't have done it.
- He'd search the corners anyway.
- There must be a camera here.
Right? Oh, was I wrong?
Right? This is where a camera is.
No? No one's hiding here?
Okay. How about here?
This is the television.
(Young Ji barely survived.)
Here. This is the television.
Right. And next to it...
(Hitting)
Who was that?
(Frog is attacking him
with her tongue.)
She hit him with a fly swatter.
(Frog hit him since she was going to
get caught anyway.)
- Watch out for the table.
- Okay. Thanks.
And this is a wall. Okay.
Let's keep going.
I think I just heard someone moving
around here.
- Four people haven't been found.
- Who?
Do Kwon, Haha, Chung Hwa,
and Young Ji.
Okay.
You have ten seconds left.
- Oh, my. Who is this?
- Do Kwon is out.
(Do Kwon got eliminated
with only 10 seconds remaining.)
I thought he was going to
pass by him.
(The 3 of them haven't been caught
by Viper who's good at this.)
Time's up.
You picked a great place to hide.
You hid there twice
and never got caught.
- You went past Young Ji.
- Did I?
He found five people.
Jong Kook, you found five people.
- My gosh. That was fun.
- Five?
We'll begin the final round.
Se Chan versus Chung Hwa.
(Round 3, Chung Hwa versus Se Chan)
- Should I put it on now? Okay.
- Yes, please.
(Chung Hwa will go first.)
You have one minute. Go.
(Haha sits down
right in front of Chung Hwa.)
Playing games like this is
so hard for me.
It's so hard.
(The pranksters are gathering
1 by 1.)
(Even Suk Jin came
right in front of her.)
But I'll get better
at playing games eventually, right?
(This is called
the right-under-her-nose strategy.)
Be quiet and sit down.
(The dirty players are exchanging
signals without letting her know.)
I've never done this before.
It'll be so much fun.
Put it on my hand now.
Five.
Four.
- Three.
- I'll take you to where they are.
Two.
- One. Carry her on your back.
- Stand up now.
Oh, he should carry me on his back?
Ready? One, two, three.
Let's go.
Here we go!
(Chung Hwa seems energetic enough
to catch everyone.)
- Where are you taking me?
- They're all hiding in here.
- Where are they?
- I'll put you down here.
I'll put you down. Be careful.
(Everyone is on the other side.)
(But he took Chung Hwa
to the empty space.)
You can start searching now.
(She started shadow boxing.)
Hang on a second.
Where are you?
Where did my pad go?
Oh, I found it.
(They're enjoying watching
the Cha Chung Hwa Show.)
What's going on?
Is there anyone here?
(Boxer Cha managed to come
to the other side of the room.)
Is no one here?
Oh, this is where I hid before.
(She went past Young Ji and So Min
and is getting close to Ji Hyo.)
Is no one here?
(Will she find Ji Hyo?)
(Grunting)
(I found someone.)
- She's our writer.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry.
(The unfortunate Boxer Cha hit
the audience member.)
I'm sorry.
(The gold mine)
What should I do?
(She went past the gold mine
without finding anyone.)
Oh, gosh. I haven't found anyone.
Where is everyone?
Five.
- Where is everyone?
- Four.
(This is her last chance.)
Three.
Two.
One.
- Time's up.
- No!
- That was hilarious.
- She almost found them.
Chung Hwa.
- Chung Hwa, look here.
- Take off the blindfold.
We all enjoyed your show.
(Plenty of people)
Cha Chung Hwa Show!
- That was very entertaining.
- Chung Hwa.
You went past us.
They're giving you
a standing ovation.
- That was amazing.
- I'm impressed.
- Thank you for your show.
- We really enjoyed it.
I can't believe
that they were all sitting there.
- Hey!
- Why?
- According to the results,
- Yes.
we'll give each of the top 3 players
2 eggs.
They're Young Ji, Chung Hwa,
and Jong Kook.
(Young Ji, Chung Hwa, Jong Kook)
- I'm so excited!
- That's a great benefit.
I can't believe this.
(Jigsaw is very happy that she won.)
Oh, my. She can jump so high.
- Young Ji, you jumped so high.
- That was impressive.
Do it again.
How do you jump so high?
That's amazing.
- Oh, my. She jumped so high.
- I'm impressed.
- She won.
- She's amazing.
We'll hand out the eggs
and reveal the last recipe.
The first team
to finish making pancakes...
- and the last dish we'll reveal...
- Can we start cooking now?
- wins the race.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- The winning team?
The third dish is deep-fried eggs.
You can just deep-fry
boiled eggs with bread crumbs.
- Got it.
- All right.
These are for the winners.
Take two of them.
(Chung Hwa, Young Ji,
and Jong Kook get 2 eggs each.)
- Jong Kook, these are your eggs.
- Thank you. I'm so glad we won.
- Exactly. I'm so happy.
- This is great.
- All my eggs were stolen.
- Really?
- Chung Hwa, hand in 1 egg.
- Jong Kook, give me 1 of them.
- How many eggs do we have?
- We can use them all.
- Are you sure?
- Bring your eggs.
- We can use them all.
- Really?
Young Ji lost a lot of eggs.
Hand in a few if you some left.
- I lost almost all.
- I'll bring mine.
- I didn't lose any of mine.
- Really? That's great.
- I'll bring one more egg.
- Bring your eggs.
- I'll hand in three eggs.
- Where we cooked?
Let's break the eggs we have
for now...
- and count the rest later.
- Okay. Let's do that.
Each of you should bring one egg.
I already handed mine in.
When? You should bring one more
for the new dishes.
- Right.
- Each of us should bring one.
Chung Hwa will pitch in 1 egg,
so each of us should bring 1.
- Okay.
- Bring your egg, okay?
- Let's do that.
- I'll go and find my egg.
- Right.
You have a 20-minute break
starting now.
Let's hurry up
and finish cooking quickly.
- Let's make a Hamburg steak.
- Okay. Good.
(They started making a Hamburg steak
with the 2 eggs they just got.)
- You need this too, right?
- Yes, I do.
Cha Chung Hwa.
Is it fully cooked?
- It's fully cooked.
- Good. Let's go.
- Really?
- Put it on the plate. Hurry.
I see that the other team made
their food halfheartedly.
(So Team Jong Kook made
their 1st dish.)
Okay.
(Currently, the 2 teams are tied.)
- Let's go.
Let's find some eggs together.
- We need all five eggs.
- We can't start cooking yet.
We need to put in the eggs now.
We just need one more egg.
Suk Jin, we can't cook
because we need one more egg.
- Sorry?
- We need one more egg.
- Just one more egg...
- But I don't have any eggs now.
Darn. I have no choice but to bring
this one.
Darn it.
(Flustered)
Gosh. My egg is over there.
I'm in trouble.
(He found Ji Hyo
where he hid his egg.)
I'm sure they hid their eggs
at unimaginable places.
Our members would do that.
She's still searching there.
I think she found it.
Darn it.
(He's expressing his anxiety
with his entire body.)
(Surprised)
What's this?
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
What's wrong with her?
(What Ji Hyo found was...)
(Suk Jin's egg.)
Hey, did you find some eggs?
- I'll break this egg.
- Wait. Hey.
- I'll break it.
- Go ahead.
- Just break it.
- I'll break it.
Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Tell me where the others' are.
- Deal.
I'll tell you. Jae Suk hid
his eggs upstairs.
- Exactly where?
- Right there. Come and see.
Stand up and look over there.
His eggs are right there.
Hey.
(She broke his egg.)
I broke it.
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, Ji Hyo.
Darn. How did she find it?
- Ji Hyo, did you find only that?
- Yes?
Yes, that was the only one I found.
I guess there's more there.
(Suk Jin was so anxious
that he made a mistake.)
There must be more eggs there.
That was all.
I'm sure she won't find it.
(He's leaving awkwardly
while pretending he's okay.)
I can't believe Ji Hyo.
- So Min.
- I'll make pancakes quickly.
We still need one more egg.
I brought an egg.
(He brought an egg?)
- I'll break it.
- Wait.
(When he was trying to negotiate
with Ji Hyo to save his egg,)
(he retrieved 2 of his eggs
while pretending to stop her.)
There's no place to hide this one.
(He left 1 of them
with a cameraman.)
Okay?
(And he came back proudly
with the egg he had left.)
Let's hurry up and make it.
Let's go.
Let's hurry up. Come on.
- It looks good.
- Right?
- What are you making?
- Pancakes.
- You don't make pancakes like this.
- I'm doing it right.
(What? It's too big.)
It'll be hard to flip it.
You should've poured
just one scoop in the middle.
It's okay.
(They must make 5 pieces.)
(Jae Suk is making the 1st piece
too big.)
Gosh. Are you making
green onion jeon?
(Are you making green onion jeon?)
What kind of pancake is that?
(Chef Yoo is making
Western style green onion jeon.)
- I could make five pieces at once.
- Exactly.
That's right, Jae Suk. For now...
Where could they be?
Where did Soek Jin hide them?
I don't think he hid them
at a place like this.
(Surprised)
(She found Suk Jin's egg.)
(She found 2 eggs, not just 1.)
This is like a gold mine.
(She found 3 eggs in total.)
- Okay. I found enough eggs.
- Do we have enough eggs?
- Yes, we do.
- Hurry up and start cooking.
Let's hurry up.
How many pieces must we make?
Pour it.
- We'll win if we finish first.
- Correct.
- We just have to make five pieces.
- True.
Is that enough?
(Team Jae Suk is speeding up
as So Min joins Jae Suk.)
That's good. You're doing great.
- I'll help you.
- Good. Okay.
You can use a spoon.
- Good.
- The eggs we have...
You just have to shape it now.
- Shape it, Se Chan.
- Okay?
You can use the ladle...
They haven't made pancakes yet.
- All right.
- Yes.
(The 2nd dish is done.)
To make deep-fried eggs,
- We should hurry up.
- we need three eggs.
I'll boil the eggs when we have
2 more eggs. We need 2 more.
- Where?
- So Min, start boiling the eggs.
- We need... We should peel them.
- Boil this one first.
Peel the eggs.
- I brought 1 egg too.
- The rest of the 2 eggs...
We have to mix them, right?
I broke them.
- I'm using one of mine.
- Okay.
(They collected 5 eggs.)
- Here.
- I'm relieved we had it. Okay.
- Done.
- Let's go.
- There.
- Okay. We're done.
- It's done. Put it on top of them.
- I'm boiling them.
- I'll put it on top of them.
- Hurry.
- Let's go.
- Go on.
- Okay.
- Cover the eggs with flour,
egg mixture, and bread crumbs.
Then deep-fry them.
(The 1st team to make
the last dish will win.)
Oh, gosh.
I lost all my eggs.
(Team Jong Kook needs 5 eggs
for the last dish.)
I lost mine.
I can't believe
that someone found it.
Oh, no. Wait.
(The other team found their eggs
with even stronger determination.)
- I was wrong.
- I didn't search here.
Oh, boy. Where on earth
did they hide their eggs?
(The place where Do Kwon came
to find an egg is...)
(where Jae Suk hid
all 10 of his eggs.)
No one will search this place.
(Jae Suk hid
all 10 of his eggs here.)
(Do Kwon had a hunch
about this place.)
Wait.
(Yong Gu is moving
straight to the eggs.)
(He's searching where the eggs are.)
(It's a crucial chance for him
to turn the game around and win.)
(But he fails to find them.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk
who almost lost all of his eggs...)
They made pancakes.
We should hurry up.
Guys, we should hurry up.
Oh, gosh.
When will the alarm go off?
How much longer should we wait?
I set the timer for 11 minutes.
- Now?
- It'll go off when 11 minutes pass.
- We have to cover it with flour.
- We need iced water.
- It helps to peel eggs easily.
- Wear gloves.
No, I'll do it. So Min.
- Yes, Suk Jin?
- Here are gloves.
We need to peel
the boiled eggs, right?
Yes, but the water isn't boiling.
- I think it's boiling.
- I set the timer for eight minutes.
You should wait a little longer.
We're running out of time.
No, Suk Jin. We should wait...
- until the alarm goes off.
- Shouldn't we roll the eggs?
No, we don't have to do that.
We just have to close the lid.
- Suk Jin, just be quiet.
- You know nothing about cooking.
Why must you keep nagging me
like this?
- Hey, I'm just...
- He asked a lame question.
- I see some cracks.
- I see them too. Okay.
- I think they're ready.
- They might be broken.
They're cooked well enough.
Don't worry.
(While they're arguing
whether to take the eggs out...)
- They won't be broken.
- Exactly.
- Hey, get out.
- Get out.
- Gosh, it's too hot.
- What are you doing?
Hey, Sesen, get out right now.
- Move, Sesen.
- Sesen.
Be careful.
(The quality of the food
doesn't matter anyway.)
(They can win the race
as long as they finish cooking.)
- It's hot.
- Okay.
- See? It's not cooked well enough.
- Be gentle.
(They're peeling
the eggs carefully.)
Oh, gosh. Darn it.
I knew this would happen.
We should boil them for longer.
Shall we boil them for longer?
We should hurry up.
- We still have a long way to go.
- Oh, no.
(Meanwhile, Team Jong Kook is
patiently boiling eggs.)
We still have a chance.
Okay. I peeled one.
- It's not easy.
- Right?
(She started deep-frying
the 1st egg.)
- Deep-fry it.
- Okay. Good.
- See? It's not cooked.
- No, this one first.
They're peeling the eggs now.
- Really? That's unbelievable.
- Yes.
How do they cook so fast?
- I wonder if they're ready.
- No, not yet.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
The eggs seem to be cooked well.
- Hurry.
- Can we peel them? Be careful.
(Do Kwon took 1 of them out.)
- Okay. It's cooked.
- Good.
Cool them all down.
Each of us should peel one, okay?
Okay. Let's peel them.
But peel it gently.
It's not fully cooked.
- Is it intact? What should I do?
- Yes, it is.
Let's just use it as it is. Hurry.
Look at this. I kept it intact.
- Okay. Good.
- I told you so.
- It wasn't cooked well.
- No, this one first.
- Okay. Let me do it.
- Here.
- Sorry?
- Of course, it's undercooked.
It's about to hatch.
- Don't worry. The eggs were fresh.
- It's okay.
- It's okay. Absolutely.
- It'll taste great.
Why is it so sticky?
I see the yolk dripping.
- Gosh. What's this?
- I see...
(The 3rd egg is crying.)
- It's okay.
- I knew it. We should've...
- boiled them for 11 minutes.
- This is how we eat it.
- Like this.
- He's a troublemaker.
Gosh, it's so messy.
Boil another egg.
- We have no more eggs.
- We don't have any eggs left.
Give it to me.
- That's good.
- Look at this.
- Put it in there. Okay.
- Give me the egg.
- Put it in here, Jong Kook.
- Here? Okay.
- There.
- Let's go.
Good. That's great.
I'm sorry. I'll use my egg.
- Let's boil it quickly.
- In boiling water...
- Oh, we have an electric kettle.
- Boil some water.
Wait. Keep boiling it for now.
- Hold on. Move aside.
- Instead of waiting until it boils,
- we'll put it in cold water.
- So Min, I'm sorry.
- What's your plan?
- I'll explain.
- We'll just...
- We should boil it in this pot.
We'll put it in cold water
and boil it.
We have this one.
Will you use that pot?
(However, Se Chan passed by
right at that moment.)
(On the plate that he's holding,
there are deep-fried eggs.)
Where should we put this?
(So he put it on the table.)
One, two, three.
(Shooting a confetti cracker
to celebrate the victory)
- Put it in cold water...
- It's over.
- They won?
- They shot a confetti cracker.
Gosh.
The other team finished cooking.
Seok Sam ruined everything
once again. Gosh.
- Oh, yes!
- We won.
- Let's take a look.
- I'm relieved.
- Young Ji, did we win?
- I told you we'd win.
Are the eggs cooked well?
Their eggs don't seem
to be fully cooked either. Gosh.
- Gosh. I can't believe...
- What happened to your eggs?
- One was broken.
- You boiled them all earlier.
- One of them was broken.
- Because of Seok Sam...
Oh, no.
Collect your eggs and gather around.
- Gosh.
- What a shame.
Let's go and see
how many of them are still there.
Let's see if they're still there.
I hope no one took my eggs.
I thought that no one had hidden
an egg here. Really?
- Who was it? Do Kwon?
- I hid one here.
My gosh. I came here to search.
(He looks as if he was
digging relics.)
Sir.
Can I have my eggs back now? What?
(Jae Suk looks for his eggs too.)
(His 10 eggs are gone.)
Someone stole my ten eggs.
- Really?
- What's wrong?
- I should check.
- Someone stole mine.
Yours?
Who stole his eggs?
Hold on a second.
None of us found Jae Suk's.
(Who will receive the penalty
in this unpredictable race?)
Here's the final result.
The one who came in last
on the winning team...
could receive the penalty if chosen.
How many do you have left?
The one who came in last
could receive the penalty if chosen.
How many do you have left?
(Who came in last
on the winning team?)
- I have three left.
- No way.
- I have three left too.
- Three.
(The remaining number of eggs)
- I have five left.
- Five.
- Check Do Kwon out.
- I have nine left.
- Nine?
- See what I mean?
I have nine left.
(Do Kwon has 9 eggs left?)
You...
It's only because I found
what the others hid.
- Unbelievable.
- All right.
He's like the neighborhood jerk.
- Watch the show when it airs.
- We don't have any left.
It seems like...
Ji Hyo came in last.
(Did Ji Hyo come in last?)
- She has 1.
- Do you only have 1 left?
- Lucky you.
- Nice!
- Check out her expression.
- Really?
(Here's how she was only
left with one egg.)
(She hid most of them
in a staff member's van.)
- Sir.
- Yes?
- Promise me you won't leave.
- Got it.
(But that staff member
went home first!)
(Going home on time
was more important...)
(than his agreement with Ji Hyo.)
He's gone.
Sir?
(She desperately searched for him.)
I need my eggs back.
- I hid them in a van.
- It's as if she lost her world.
- I have three left.
- But the van is disappeared.
- Really?
- The van is gone!
Why did you hide them in a van?
- The van was gone.
- The driver took off.
The cameramen
get off work before we do.
- My gosh.
- He left.
Those who can receive the penalty...
are Ji Hyo and the five
from the losing team.
A vote will decide
which three will receive it.
- A vote.
- But I don't have any ballots.
You will all participate
in the vote.
Throughout the race,
you obtained ballots.
- Yes.
- How many do you each have?
- I have one.
- One.
- I found Young Ji's egg.
- I have none.
I gave mine to So Min.
- You have no ballots...
- and no eggs.
- I have nothing.
What have you been up to today?
I have two.
- Why do I have two?
- This is from So Min.
- You.
- What?
- Get over here.
- Why?
- You!
- What is this about?
- Why?
- Attention.
- But why?
- Tell me what this is about.
- Attention.
- Why?
- Se Chan.
- What?
- How many do you have?
- I have two,
but hear me out.
- These are from finding Young Ji's.
- Did you find mine?
I swear.
- It's not from finding yours.
- Isn't it odd...
- that he's saying it's mine?
- These are Young Ji's.
We agreed to give back
the eggs that belong to teammates!
- I gave them back.
- I found two of Young Ji's eggs.
I gave all that I found back.
Young Ji, how many do you have?
I have 11.
What? 11?
It was her.
(Young Ji has 11 ballots?)
- It was her.
- She must've found my eggs.
- My eggs!
- She has 11.
(How did she collect
so many ballots?)
I'm off to the restroom.
(During the cooking stage,
she went to the restroom.)
(But she actually went outside.)
I need to find someone else's eggs.
This isn't the time
for me to cook with the rest.
(She searched here and there.)
I think I saw something here.
(No way!)
No way.
(She found 10 of Jae Suk's eggs.)
Sweet.
(And those eggs...)
I'm cashing them all in.
(They were all swapped for ballots.)
Jae Suk, I'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
My stomach was acting up.
(Deceitful)
(Her restroom break
served as the perfect alibi.)
We were talking about
you being a spy.
- Eleven?
- She found my eggs.
But you didn't
give us any to cook with.
- She's a little thief!
- No way.
- How can she...
- My gosh.
- That's stealing.
- I'm impressed, Young Ji.
How did you find them?
(The number of ballots they have
was revealed.)
Anyway, let's begin the vote.
- With what you obtained...
- We get one more each.
(They get a ballot each
on top of what they obtained.)
Whose name should I write?
- Whose name did you write?
- I can't tell you that.
It's hard to choose.
- She has over ten.
- I can't believe it.
- My gosh, Young Ji.
- How can she have so many?
- No way.
- She has over ten.
The guest will decide on
the penalty for the members...
- and vice versa.
- Sure thing.
Getting hit by a wet tissue...
seemed good enough.
- Wet tissues?
- Yes.
- So the guests...
- Getting hit by a wet tissue.
- For the guests, right?
- Right.
We'll go with
getting hit by a wet towel.
Choose a penalty for the members.
The guests can decide.
- Then...
- Is it up to us?
Choose a penalty
for the members who lost.
- You may discuss.
- Let's discuss this.
(It's payback time for the guests.)
Wet tissue is better.
Let's take the annoying path.
They'll be at
the SBS Entertainment Awards,
so let's have them film themselves
getting ready for the event.
They'll be followed...
- from their homes.
- They'll be woken up too.
- Right.
- The staff will enter the house.
- And wake them up.
- They must be woken up too.
A camera will be set up.
- They'll hate it.
- Of course.
- From the day before.
- Must we go that far?
From the moment they go to sleep
the day before.
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
- Have you decided on a penalty?
- Yes, we have.
What kind of penalty
will the losing members receive?
(They carefully announce
the penalty they chose.)
You'll be at
the SBS Entertainment Awards soon.
I'm sure you all have been
nominated for awards.
Here's the penalty you'll receive.
The day before the event,
a camera will be set up
in your home.
- After you wake up...
- Not from the day before.
- No? Why not?
- You'll be followed.
Then start in the morning.
You'll go to the salon, right?
- From your house.
- From the moment you step outside.
- This is the worst.
- You'll leave the house...
and go to the salon.
- Look here.
- You'll get dolled up.
Not being regulars on the show
doesn't mean...
that you can make awful suggestions.
- Why not?
- It's the worst.
- Really?
- Hey.
I can promise you...
that this won't get more than
20 seconds of air time.
Just...
- decide on one we can do today.
- It's the worst.
Okay, fine.
- From the salon then.
- Sure.
- How's that?
- No, please don't.
The camera will
"fellow" you from the salon.
Fellow?
What do you mean by "fellow"?
- What was that?
- Fellow?
It'll be like a fellowship.
- Choose something we can do today.
- No way.
- It's our right to suggest this.
- Okay, fine.
Thank you for the fun idea.
(They will be followed around
on the day of the award ceremony.)
- Unbelievable.
- Here is your prize.
Of course.
- Is there a prize?
- It's my first time receiving one.
Do Kwon's getting a prize.
For a smooth transition
into the new year,
we have prepared body products.
A body wash.
And body lotion.
These will go to Young Ji,
Do Kwon, Jong Kook, and Se Chan.
(Young Ji, Se Chan, Do Kwon,
and Jong Kook receive the gift.)
- Lucky you.
- This is a first for me.
Look at Jong Kook smiling.
If only we took
three more minutes on the eggs.
- Yes, the eggs.
- I have the voting result.
A total of 31 votes were cast.
A total of 31 votes?
Here's the result.
- Being followed is the worst.
- Tell me about it.
Who will greet the fans more
on the day of...
- the award ceremony?
- Oh, no.
The one with 16 votes is...
(Who came in 1st place
with 16 votes...)
(and who came in 2nd and 3rd place?)
Say that it's Jae Suk.
It can't be me.
The one with 16 votes is...
(Who will receive the penalty?)
(A week later)
(December 18, on the day of
the SBS Entertainment Awards)
(The three members
will receive their penalty.)
(Which member
kicks it off at the salon?)
Unbelievable.
(Suk Jin enters.)
I bet you're going to
follow me around all day.
The one with 16 votes is Suk Jin.
I can't believe this is happening.
(That's why the camera
is already in his face.)
As you know,
I'm not one to get my makeup done
at a salon.
It happens rarely.
But since it's
an important day today...
It's why I'm here
to get my makeup done.
- I'll start with skincare products.
- I applied nothing today.
(He's 100 percent bare-faced.)
The last race's penalty...
I'm curious though.
Will the viewers...
be interested in seeing me
get my makeup done?
- I'm sure it will intrigue some.
- Really?
I don't think they'll be interested.
(The staff is taking a huge risk
since it could lower viewership.)
- I doubt it.
- Really?
- Running Man is a beloved show.
- You're not intrigued though.
- Of course I am.
- I'll watch this part of the show.
- Really?
The others receiving
this penalty are...
(The others receiving
this penalty are...)
It's us three.
- Who intrigues you the most?
- In my case...
(You...)
(This is how they became
the number one salon.)
Thank you for saying so.
(This is how they became
the number one salon.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Another makeup artist enters.)
We talked earlier...
about the Running Man camera
following us.
Who would you like to see the most?
(Who would you
like to see the most?)
Duly noted.
(Duly noted.)
I could tell from her silence
that she didn't mean me.
You must not be good at lying.
(The salon where another member is)
How adorable.
You look like a celebrity.
Jeon So Min.
(She received 8 votes out of 31.)
Must the camera be this close?
The director had to come to work
when it's his day off today.
(The cameraman and director
have to work as well.)
This is insane.
I thought it'd be more like a Vlog.
Here I am getting my hair dried.
Don't I look awful?
(The staff insists on filming
while she's getting her hair dried.)
I bet I look awful.
(The vicious production crew
even shoots her drying hair.)
I haven't put on...
There's one over here too.
(She protects her bare face.)
I don't want to show this
to our viewers.
How do I look on camera?
It's not bad.
I don't look ugly at all.
(She finds her bare face
better than she thought.)
Look over here.
(She put up her poster
on the wall of a salon.)
It's like before and after.
Because I couldn't hide
my eggs well...
(She got a penalty because of that.)
I haven't watched this episode.
It'll air tomorrow though.
Do you watch our show every week?
("Unanswered Questions")
(Do Running Man members
watch the premiere of the show?)
To be honest...
I watched it every week
until three years ago.
But now, I watch it through
the online streaming service.
I watch the replay of it.
Running Man is the number one show
on the online streaming service.
Please watch it.
(Trying to make it
sound nice instead)
It's really nice to watch the show
while running on a treadmill.
It helps the time go by quickly.
It's the best.
- Everyone, cardio...
- Then do you laugh...
when you see yourself?
I've laughed a lot
when I saw my parts.
I laugh out loud
watching myself on it.
I also laugh a lot
watching the guys.
I don't laugh because
I find it funny...
but because I'm proud to see myself
performing on the show.
(She laughs because
she's proud of herself.)
I've laughed a couple of times
because I was proud of myself...
and I found myself cute.
Because I was proud of myself.
(The self-loving variety show star
finds herself cute and proud.)
(Meanwhile, her poster
steals everyone's attention.)
I should sign the poster,
but I couldn't.
- I should sign it.
- You should do it today.
Did you know? It's the poster
that the Running Man crew made.
And I stole it.
(She confesses her crime
while smiling brightly.)
You remember, right?
I brought my poster
to put it up on the wall here.
You know the stickers
that the production crew makes?
I love them so much.
They're very useful too.
I take all of them with me.
Remember the scratchcard
you guys made?
I brought a bunch of them,
and people loved it.
Actually, I also took
a couple of mission bags.
There's a staff member
of our drama team...
whose name is Jae Suk.
When I brought him Yoo Jae Suk's
mission bag, he loved it.
I love them so much.
I wonder how you guys
can make them so creatively.
(The last member
to receive the penalty)
(Haha)
He earned five votes.
(The last member to receive
the penalty with 5 votes)
Gosh, this is troublesome.
I need to get changed,
so I'll be right back.
I'm carrying out the penalty
of Running Man.
And today, I'm attending
the 2021 SBS Entertainment Awards...
where Suk Jin will be getting
the Grand Award.
I'm at the salon to get ready.
(There's regrettable news
we must share with the viewers.)
(The Running Man members
sincerely wished...)
(that Suk Jin would win
the Grand Award.)
I'm actually looking forward to it.
I really want Suk Jin
to win the Grand Award.
I personally hope Suk Jin
will win the Grand Award.
Kwang Soo called me.
- Kwang Soo called.
- What did he say?
"I think you'll win
the Grand Award tonight."
And I told him that I don't think
I'll be winning it tonight.
So he asked me
if I prepared an acceptance speech.
I did prepare it though.
And he laughed.
(Even the makeup artist
burst into laughter.)
You laugh a lot.
I did prepare an acceptance speech.
I think you'll really win it.
- Me?
- Yes.
- You can't lie, right?
- I can't.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Then can you foresee things?
- I have a good hunch.
You do? Do you think
I'll win the Grand Award?
Yes.
He's gotten nervous.
I'm so nervous.
- I really have a good hunch.
- You do?
What encourages me...
are the viewers who root for me...
on online forums.
I'd be really grateful to win it,
but I'll be okay even if I don't.
I'm going to look handsome soon.
After the magical touch...
I don't usually put this on,
but they cover the empty spots
when I'm here.
(After applying black hair powder,)
(he's done with the makeup
for the award show.)
Are you going to keep following me?
You'll keep following me?
There's nothing much to it.
I'm just leaving.
Please make my hair look
cute yet sexy.
(Transforming from little Haha...)
(to cute yet sexy celebrity)
What is this, a CCTV?
Why do you keep filming me?
(Meanwhile, Actress Jeon
is getting transformed as well.)
I look pretty now, right?
(Thrusting herself)
It won't focus.
(Super overwhelming)
I've become more confident.
This part is a see-through.
It's an off-shoulder black dress.
I can say it suits me perfectly.
It's a really sexy dress.
I think people will criticize me.
Ever since I started
shooting the drama,
I keep thinking that I'm sexy.
Because of the drama...
I'll get changed.
(The pretentious actress
goes to get changed.)
(She's done transforming.)
I should wrap up.
(Exuding the charisma
of an actress,)
(she's transforming
into a sexy queen.)
(The sexy queen is ready to go.)
Do I look pretty?
I thought it wouldn't be much
of a penalty...
to have the camera follow me around.
But it really is a penalty.
I hear you'll be presenting
a special performance.
Today, I'm performing
with Shin Hyo Bum,
the forever diva. We'll be singing
a duet at the award show.
We'll be singing a duet. My gosh.
(He arrives first
with the pressure of performing.)
Kwang Soo is calling me.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Suk Jin.
- Hey.
You got ready really early.
I'm singing
with an incredible singer today.
Oh, really?
(Laughing)
I'm doing a celebratory performance
with an incredible singer.
I'm so pressured
because I have to sing later.
- Kwang Soo.
- Suk Jin.
- I've been meaning to ask.
- Yes?
Do you think I have a chance
to win the Grand Award?
Didn't you say you'd get it
for sure when we talked earlier?
(You said you'd get it for sure
when we talked earlier.)
Hey.
You told me what you'll say
and asked if it sounded okay.
This guy... He's slandering me.
Anyway, congratulations in advance.
No, I won't be getting it.
Anyway, I miss you.
- Me too.
- Right.
(Entering the waiting room
with excitement after the call)
Hey, you're here.
- Hello.
She's my stylist.
- The one who always...
- We're looking forward to it.
puts me in shocking clothes.
(What will he wear today?)
Is this it?
(It's an ordinary velvet tuxedo.)
- It's pretty. It's velvet.
- Isn't it?
- Is it dark blue?
- Gosh.
- It's pretty.
- It's so cool.
You think? What is this?
I knew it wouldn't be ordinary.
(Suk Jin's suit is extraordinary
even for an award show.)
Goodness, this is...
(He can't continue.)
It'll make me look wealthy.
It looks like gold.
- I attached it myself.
- Oh, you did?
I attached it myself.
Today, I wanted to dress you nicely.
Okay.
Then does that mean you've been
dressing me ridiculously?
She just blurted out the truth.
That means the clothes she brought
so far weren't meant to be nice.
You've been dressing me like that
on purpose.
She said, "You should wear this.
You'll look really cool."
It was all a lie.
(While Suk Jin found out
that his stylist has been lying...)
- Do I go up now?
- Yes.
- Shall I go up now?
Suk Jin is coming down.
(He has a busy schedule ahead.)
- Hello!
- Hello.
(Hyo Bum finishes singing
the 1st verse.)
(Here comes a senior singer.)
(His appearance is supposed to be
a surprise for everyone.)
(He fails to hold back
his laughter.)
(It's his first time singing
on an award show...)
(with a friend of his age.)
(They show perfect chemistry
as they practiced a lot.)
(Suk Jin sings
especially well tonight.)
(Thumbs up)
Give me a kiss.
(The rehearsal was successful.)
Suk Jin, your throat
is okay, right?
- No, it's hoarse.
- Okay.
(It's 2 hours before
Entertainment Awards starts.)
Who is it?
- Goodness.
- Hello, Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin was waiting for the others
after getting changed.)
It's obvious that you'll win
the Grand Award.
You put a lot of effort
into your suit.
That's not it.
I hear you went to the salon at 1 p.m.
- I had other works to do.
- I see.
I'm doing so many things tonight.
- Before I knew it...
- I'm certain.
Of what?
Why do you think they made you do
a lot of things?
(Se Chan makes a fuss
as soon as he arrives.)
That means you'll win for sure.
- That's not true.
- No.
Didn't they mention
that I was at the salon earlier?
They did. They said you came at 1 p.m.
And they said
you were really nervous.
You were restless
while getting your makeup.
(Laughing awkwardly)
That's not true.
- That's not it.
- Is that so?
Didn't your wife say something?
- My wife?
- Yes.
She said I wouldn't win.
Why not? You will.
My wife is really rational.
She doesn't get swayed by others.
She's always right.
- And she doesn't think you'll win?
- She said this a few days ago.
She said it's impossible for them...
to give the Grand Award to our team
for three years in a row.
- That's...
- Doesn't that sound convincing?
That could be one of the reasons.
She's right.
Jae Suk and Jong Kook won before.
Now it's you.
So I'm actually at ease.
But why are your legs shaking?
You said you were at ease,
but your legs were shaking.
They only get a bust shot.
If you didn't mention that...
No, they're getting a full shot too.
- Is that for a full shot?
- Yes.
Push it up.
(Push it up.)
You can see how I feel from my legs.
You're trembling. Gosh, seriously.
I think no one else can beat you.
I'm certain that you'll win.
Because there were so many articles
about it,
I practiced...
(So I practiced...)
saying an acceptance speech at home.
Oh, an acceptance speech
for the Grand Award?
My wife went out to work out,
and I was alone at home.
Where do you practice that?
In the living room?
Or in your bedroom?
I couldn't stand still,
so I practiced it
while walking around.
And I...
You know
the typical acceptance speech.
I mentioned my parents,
parents-in-law, family,
- Your family.
- and the production crew.
The production crew and the members.
Then I mentioned the members.
I mentioned Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
- I'm not kidding when I say this.
- Did you get emotional?
I didn't just get emotional.
I teared up.
- Oh, really?
- I did.
So I couldn't go on.
I was saying it all by myself.
Then I...
saw myself in the mirror...
and thought,
"What on earth am I doing?"
Imagine me saying the speech
all by myself.
I was even wearing something shabby.
- I get what you mean.
- Then I saw myself...
in the mirror.
- Gosh.
- Did you get choked up?
I did.
Because so many things
happened in the past 11 years.
Of course.
I could call them struggles
or hardships,
but I could also say
that I was happy.
We all shared it.
I...
How many of us are there?
Come on, Suk Jin.
What's wrong with you?
- I was just joking.
- I thought so.
- Haha is here.
- Hello!
- Hey.
- You're here.
- We've been talking.
- Suk Jin.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
- It's Jae Suk.
- Gosh, it scared me.
- Jae Suk, you...
- Goodness, Jae Suk.
Gosh, you punk.
He's also one of the nominees
for the Grand Award.
He is. He has always been
a nominee for the Grand Award.
If Jae Suk wins the Grand Award,
then Suk Jin can say his speech
in his place.
You can say it in his place.
And you'll cry for him.
- You can cry for him.
- You'll cry for him.
- I should accept it on his behalf?
- Yes, on behalf of him.
"That's what Jae Suk said."
- I hope you'll do that.
- If I cry,
that'll make me look really lousy.
And a headline will go,
"Suk Jin Cries out of Frustration."
Goodness.
But there's still a chance...
that you can say the speech
you practiced if Jae Suk wins.
The Grand Award isn't a big deal.
It's not a big deal.
Let's show our authentic selves...
in the waiting room.
You can make yourself at home.
I know I'm a celebrity,
- Have this.
- but I'm a human too.
- I change my socks here too.
- Of course.
I cut my toenails here too.
I even pick my nose
with the hand that touched my feet.
I fart a lot as well.
He used to hang out
in the streets of Dongducheon.
How could you say that?
In the streets of Dongducheon?
There are so many people
from Dongducheon who watch this.
He used to hang out in Itaewon
and Mapo. I'm only being frank.
- What about you?
- Where did you use to hang out?
Celebrities are no different.
(Celebrities are no different.)
Suk Jin,
imagine that this is a trophy.
(A stinky sock trophy
that Haha just took off)
Hold it.
Although it may be smelly,
go ahead and rehearse.
(Handing the trophy)
(Bursting into laughter)
This is so funny.
(The spectators find it hilarious.)
He's like a New Yorker.
(The Grand Award nominee
is getting immersed.)
Watching this alone chokes me up.
(The tear-jerking acceptance speech
that he said to himself at home)
I didn't know I'd win.
I came up the stage while eating.
(I didn't know I'd win.
I came up the stage while eating.)
It's American style.
He's like a New Yorker.
Here we go.
You know how people say...
that they don't dwell on awards?
But after I got nominated,
I realized it was all a lie.
You should kiss your trophy.
(You should kiss your trophy.)
Kiss it like this.
It's like a miracle for me.
I've always wanted to do this
when I won an award.
(Getting ready to kiss the trophy)
(Mwah)
(The nominee for the Grand Award
does anything to make us laugh.)
- Thank you so much.
- He's amazing.
I think I was given this award
on behalf of the Running Man team.
Thank you!
- He deserves the award.
- I got choked up.
- Me too.
- My gosh.
- Someone must be coming.
- I think So Min...
will make a splendid entrance.
I talked with her earlier
on the phone,
and she said
she's really pretty today.
She said she's
a cynical and haughty princess.
Wait, she isn't. So Min.
What are you doing?
Why are you acting so haughty?
- Aren't we supposed to do this?
- We haven't even started.
You can just walk normally.
- She is acting cheeky.
- What's wrong with her?
(Waving in the air)
So Min.
So Min, take a seat.
(It looks like she's in love
with herself.)
Should we make her pass out?
- Why is she...
- What's up with you?
Go away!
There aren't many days
where I look this pretty.
It was really traffic, wasn't it?
- No, you look pretty every week.
- That's not true.
You're pretty.
You're always pretty. Take a seat.
You look handsome today, Suk Jin.
You look extraordinary.
- He looks different today, right?
- He does.
- Haha is also...
- I know this is too much.
wearing velvet.
Both are wearing velvet,
but doesn't Suk Jin exude
the vibe of a Grand Award winner?
Can you get grilled chicken skewers
in advance?
- Why?
- Why do you need them?
He'd look weird
if he goes home empty-handed.
(He'd look weird
if he goes home empty-handed.)
(Haha wants Suk Jin to bring home
chicken skewers if he doesn't win.)
- Chicken skewers?
- Or a sausage and rice cake skewer.
That's original.
Instead of a bouquet?
At least get me plenty of skewers.
How many times must I tell you?
When you have
a long career like mine...
No one asked you.
- I heard him say this...
- No one asked you.
so many times already.
"When you have
a long career like mine..."
You're the one who made
the most fuss through texts.
"Suk Jin, you must prepare
an acceptance speech."
"Call me Dong Hoon instead of Haha."
- Hello, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook.
- You're here.
Come on in.
- You went to the salon.
- I did.
I got dressed up at home.
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- Look at her.
- Why are you wearing slippers?
I can't wear heels.
- Take a seat.
We're all here?
It feels empty without Jae Suk.
- He's here.
- It feels empty.
- It does feel empty.
- I know.
I talked with Jae Suk earlier,
and it was his first time
to miss Entertainment Awards.
- Of course it is.
- It's his first time?
It is his first time.
- It really feels empty.
- Right.
At least it's consoling
because we have something...
- to focus on.
- We're looking forward...
- to Suk Jin's win.
- Right. He has a chance.
That's true.
- You look like a star today.
- Doesn't he look cool?
- You're handsome.
- Ji Hyo.
- It'll be funny if Jae Suk wins.
- You should hold it.
(Stealing her mic)
Gosh, seriously...
That's Ji Hyo's mic.
It's not yours.
Everything seems to belong to you,
doesn't it?
The trophy and the mic!
I thought we were sharing it.
Didn't Haha also win...
the Top Excellence Award last year?
- He did.
Haha did a lot of difficult works.
He did.
- For me...
- But this year,
he worked too hard
on "How Do You Play?"
- Right?
- He did.
- Haha, are you really leaving?
- Jong Kook, what's even worse...
is that Haha just posted something
about "How Do You Play?"...
- on his Instagram.
- Oh, no!
My gosh.
- It's the day our album...
- He's seriously...
- gets released.
- He came to Entertainment Awards...
- as a member of Running Man.
- How could you do that?
I told you,
the album is released today.
- The album...
- That's really disappointing.
Mi Joo and Jae Suk...
Gosh, that jerk.
(Gosh, that jerk.)
He's eliminated
from the list of nominees.
We should skip him.
He's not ready with his mindset.
- Shall we try calling Jae Suk?
- He completely secluded himself.
- Like the movie, "Oldboy."
- He's growing a mustache too?
I was going to send him
fried dumplings.
- Hey, Suk Jin.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
- Where are you?
- Hey.
We're all gathered here without you.
- Jae Suk!
You guys...
It feels empty without you.
- Jae Suk, he's lying!
- It feels empty.
He's only thinking about himself.
He's...
- I told this to Haha earlier.
- What did you tell him?
I told him that there won't be...
(There won't be...)
a big twist.
(There won't be a big twist.)
A big twist?
- Actually...
- I'm sure you'll win...
You should join...
"Same Life, Unlike Dreams"
next year with your wife.
Right, you should.
- Then you'll win the Grand Award.
- That'll be amazing.
Then you'll win the Grand Award
for sure.
He definitely will.
Which show did you recommend to him?
- "Same Life, Unlike Dreams."
- With his wife.
But if he joins
"Same Life, Unlike Dreams,"
it'll be very difficult
for him to win the Grand Award.
- Why not?
- Because of his image.
- Because of his image?
- His image.
You'll be lying down the whole time.
His image will be controversial.
- This will guarantee him the award.
- Which one?
You should join
"Invitation from Bachelor-agains."
(Laughing awkwardly)
- Then you'll win for sure.
- To win the Grand Award...
- It'll guarantee you the award.
- That's a bit...
It'll be too complicated.
Joining "Same Life, Unlike Dreams"
is quite simple,
"Invitation from Bachelor-agains"
is too complicated.
It's nice to hear from Jae Suk.
I miss him.
All right, then.
- See you.
- Bye!
Good luck, everyone.
- Thank you!
- Hello.
(Placing Jae Suk's
life-sized cutout in the center)
He's in the center.
Of course, he should be
in the center.
Put Jae Suk in the center.
Here we go. Smile.
In 1, 2, 3.
- That's it.
- Let's take one more.
It's one minute
before the live show.
Those who haven't taken their seats,
please take your seats now.
All right.
Please take your seats.
Look at Jae Suk. They tied him up.
(Jae Suk is wrapped with tape
and forced to take a seat.)
- You should sit here.
- The show is about to start.
Everyone needs to be in their seats.
(Suk Jin isn't at the table.)
Please take a seat.
Suk Jin is in the middle.
Suk Jin must be doing something.
I know. He must be doing something
in the beginning.
(Suk Jin is getting ready
to present the first award.)
So what are we doing?
I am not sure. Earlier, I heard...
Suk Jin.
What is the key point
of your fashion today?
You can see it. It's the brooch.
It looks nice.
Fashion is all about confidence.
I am not embarrassed at all.
Do you want to wear it?
Me?
No, thank you.
Let's go.
(While Suk Jin talks about
his belief in fashion,)
(the opening performance begins.)
(aespa enters.)
(Cheering)
- aespa.
- Who are they?
This dance.
They are cool.
(They did the Digeut Dance often
on Running Man.)
They are cool.
(I know this song well!)
(Perfect angle)
(Last summer,
Young Ji taught them the dance.)
Is this the only dance move?
(Last summer,
Young Ji taught them the dance.)
My arm doesn't twist like that.
(Suk Jin mastered the Digeut Dance
as he lives young.)
That's great.
(The celebratory performance ends.)
First comes the award...
that will make your heart beat fast,
the Best Rookie Award.
The award will be presented
by the rising fashionista,
Ji Suk Jin and the winner
of last year's Best Rookie Award,
- Cha Eun Woo.
- The rising fashionista?
You are a rookie
in the fashion scene.
Cha Eun Woo.
(The rising fashionista,
Ji Suk Jin)
Gosh, he will do it with Eun Woo.
(When Eun Woo waves,)
(he waves as well.)
They look very different.
They look very different, Ji Hyo.
- They look like a father and a son.
- I know.
He looks like a father.
All right.
I was surprised
to hear them introduce me...
as the rising fashionista.
- As you know,
- He looks cool.
Yoo Jae Suk always presented
this award.
Unfortunately,
he couldn't join us this year.
He was quite disappointed as well.
In any case,
I hope he will get better soon.
(After he is done,
he motions Eun Woo to talk.)
Why do they look so awkward?
They have no teamwork whatsoever.
They aren't close at all.
You have been showing off
your fashion sense...
on Running Man lately.
- I can explain.
- Okay.
That's an exaggeration.
But my outfit did become
the talk of the town a few times.
That's right.
(Chuckling)
What was that awkward laugh?
I feel very awkward.
(The Running Man members' applause
saves the moment.)
Let's keep going.
Now,
who will...
Who will win the Rookie Award?
He stuttered.
He stuttered once.
- Jae Suk sent me a text.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk was watching
the award ceremony at home.)
He wrote that Suk Jin isn't good
with ad-libs.
(Suk Jin isn't good with ad-libs.)
(Everyone burst out laughing.)
(His mind must be
on the Grand Award.)
(There is no way he will win
the Grand Award.)
(Jae Suk teases him in real-time.)
That's so funny.
Here comes the emperor of ad-libs.
(The emperor of ad-libs returns.)
Good work, Suk Jin.
So Min.
(Se Chan and So Min are
the next presenters.)
(Despite being presenters,
they practice the dance.)
- Then I go right.
- It has to be done fast.
In any case,
I will go right after you.
You are here
to present an award, right?
No. I plan to use this opportunity
to become a star.
This is our only chance
to get some screen time.
That's why we need to do well.
Isn't that right?
You need to charm everyone.
Se Chan, this is your chance.
This is a live broadcast...
and many producers are watching.
- Se Chan, you need to focus.
- Right now.
- Would you give me a pen?
- Here you go.
(He picks up a pen and works hard.)
It's "Present", right?
It's "Present," not "Pleasant."
I am so nervous.
Se Chan will be on the right...
and So Min will be on the left.
The next award will be presented
by the husband and wife...
of Running Man,
Yang Se Chan and Jeon So Min.
(Now comes the performance
they worked hard on.)
(Se Chan seems to be drunk
on his sexiness.)
(So Min follows.)
(They begin to compete
for screen time.)
(They suddenly scold the camera.)
(They begin to shake their hips.)
What a grand entrance.
They don't disappoint.
- Is that even allowed?
- I guess so.
(The rebels of the award ceremony)
I don't know what's going on.
(For some reason,
this presenter is angry.)
It's like a musical.
(For some reason,
this presenter is angry.)
(The husband goes wild.)
Yang Se Chan is going wild.
(The wife is the same.)
It's nice to meet you.
I am the man
who flirts for his gain,
Yang Se Chan.
Hello, I am the woman
who flirts for her gain,
Jeon So Min.
It's nice to meet you.
We will briefly check
the teamwork of the couples...
who were nominated...
for the Best Couple Award.
Jong Kook is well-known...
- for Absolutely Game.
- It's a fun game.
That was a long time ago.
Would it be okay
if we ask a question?
- Is it for Absolutely Game?
- Yes.
Okay.
You want to win
the Best Couple Award with Ji Hyo...
more than you wanted to win
the Grand Award last year.
Would you hold this?
(He hands over the microphone
and covers her ears.)
(My goodness.)
My answer is the Grand Award.
- That was romantic.
- "My answer is the Grand Award."
He chose to be funny.
(Kim Grand Award
reenacted the famous scene.)
The winners...
(The winners...)
will be revealed soon.
My goodness.
(He succeeded to be flippant
on SBS Entertainment Awards.)
My goodness.
(They finish presenting
the Best Couple Award.)
Good job.
He is so funny.
(The presenters come back.)
You did so well. It was so funny.
It was funny.
(Suk Jin gets called over again.)
- He is busy today.
- I know.
- He really is busy today.
- Good luck.
Seriously.
- Why does he have so many tasks?
- Seriously.
He has so many tasks today.
The next event...
of 2021 SBS Entertainment Awards...
is the celebratory performance.
(Suk Jin showed up to work
earlier than anyone today.)
(Will he be able to perform
without any mistakes?)
("I Knew I Love" by Shin Hyo Bum
and Ji Suk Jin)
(The members are already absorbed
in Hyo Bum's performance.)
It's so cool.
(It's so cool.)
(They wave the flashlight
and wait for Suk Jin to come out.)
I will turn on the flashlight.
(Suk Jin enters.)
(Suk Jin enters relaxedly
like a proper singer.)
(Suk Jin's diehard fans get up.)
(He looks much happier
than he did as a presenter.)
He is doing well.
(It's rare to see him look
so cool and relaxed.)
(This year as well,
Suk Jin didn't hold back.)
(Despite his fragile body...)
(and weak ad-libs,)
(he made people laugh out loud.)
(The production crew wants to work
with him until the end.)
(He is the winner
of the Grand Award in our hearts!)
(And everyone hoped...)
Yang Se Chan.
(that Se Chan would win
the Top Excellence Award.)
- Congratulations.
I have been on Running Man...
for a little over five years now.
(He talked about the past 5 years.)
For over four years...
Well, it's not like
I have gotten a lot better.
But for four years,
I struggled a lot.
It was difficult for me.
The Running Man family
cheered me on until the end...
so that I wouldn't get intimidated.
Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
Haha, Ji Hyo,
So Min, and Jae Suk
who must be watching at home.
I will work harder next year.
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Se Chan, congratulations on winning
the Top Excellence Award.
(They said goodbye to 2021
with a round of applause.)
- This place is pretty.
- Hello.
- Jae Suk...
- Yes.
used a self-test kit.
Since the result was
a bit suspicious...
- He received a proper test now.
- Yes.
- The result isn't out yet.
- He is waiting for the result.
That's why we are here by ourselves.
- That's right.
- Isn't this the first time...
we had an opening without Jae Suk?
- It's the first time.
- That's not true.
- Really?
- He was gone momentarily.
- He was gone momentarily,
so we had an opening
by ourselves at a park.
It was a complete mess.
- Suk Jin.
- I remember that.
(In Episode 97 which aired in 2012,
Jae Suk wasn't in the opening.)
We are in Thailand.
- Suk Jin.
- Running Man in Thailand!
- It's 2012.
- Did you sleep well?
People will think
that this is an old video.
- We are in Thailand.
- Jae Suk, where are you?
Things are getting frustrating.
It was a complete mess.
- Suk Jin, this is your chance.
- I remember that.
- Suk Jin, you are the main host.
- This is Jae Suk's hardship.
- I won't think of it as a chance.
- You are the main host.
We need Jae Suk.
- Go ahead and lead us.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- We are in this together.
- Suk Jin might cry.
This is our Running Man.
- We are in this together.
- That sounds awkward.
I am sorry, but raise your pitch
so that you sound cheerful.
How much do you want me to raise it?
Do you want me to shout?
- Raise your pitch.
- Listen.
- Your gestures are too much.
- Seriously.
Just how much
do you want me to raise it?
- You should raise your pitch.
- My throat will go hoarse.
Viewers watch this show happily
on weekends.
Use a cheerful tone.
There is something we always do
when a new year comes around.
You will have your fortunes read for fun.
- I love it.
- It isn't for fun.
It's shocking
when you hear something bad.
- So Jong Kook wore pink last year.
- That's right.
- That was the reason.
- Which color will it be this year?
Today, we invited a fortune teller.
- Gosh.
- I am excited.
I am nervous.
I heard that he is very talented.
- Seriously.
- He is well-known.
The man who will do
the fortune-telling is...
Oh Wang Geun.
- Hello.
He is handsome.
- He is young.
He is really young.
- Please sit down.
- I am nervous.
- Seriously.
- He is dressed casually.
You know, you look very cute.
- Really?
- He looks like a teddy bear.
Is it okay to say that?
- He is handsome.
- Please sit down.
- It looks like he studied abroad.
Old man, sit down.
- Please sit down.
- It looks like he studied abroad.
He does.
Do fortune tellers
read their own fortunes?
Of course.
- Really?
- How was your fortune?
My three years of misfortune began,
so the result wasn't very good.
When I pray often,
I can see what will happen.
Beware of people.
Beware of accidents.
Shouldn't everyone be aware
of people and accidents?
But there are times
you get attacked for no reason.
- You experienced it.
- You are right.
You got attacked for no reason.
- It was an unprompted attack.
- That's right.
Sometimes, people throw rocks at you
for no reason.
- Seriously.
- That happens due to bad luck.
Seriously.
You are a perfectionist.
So you can't stand it
when people badmouth you.
- I hate it.
- It makes you struggle.
He hates getting criticized
for no reason.
- Did he begin already?
- If there is a reason, it's okay.
Did he begin already?
- Now...
- All right.
- Hello.
I am struggling these days.
- Ji Hyo has strong energy.
- I am excited about her fortune.
- She has strong energy.
- No, I don't.
I don't have strong energy, right?
(How will be Ji Hyo's fortune
in 2022?)
- Her energy isn't that strong.
- Really?
- Her element is wood.
- Are you sure?
- Isn't it strong?
- I don't have strong energy.
You are like a flower that bloomed
in the middle of summer.
- A flower?
- Yes.
You are a beautiful flower,
but there are too many knives
by your side.
- Do they hurt her?
- Thus,
these knives keep hurting the tree.
So that makes you sensitive.
- It's true.
- And...
- you blame yourself a lot.
- It's true.
Instead of blaming the others,
you think, "Why did I do that?"
- She does that.
- "I am pathetic."
You currently have low self-esteem.
In 2020 and 2021,
the tree almost broke.
- Yes.
- You were very unlucky.
So you want
to change everything now.
- Yes.
- You want to move too.
That's why I got a haircut.
- I wanted to change.
- Yes.
But you don't need to worry.
In 2022, good fortune will come.
- Next year?
- Yes. It will begin in 2022.
Next year will be good for you...
because you will get a chance
to challenge yourself.
- What do you mean?
- You will be asked to star in...
a movie or a drama.
I see a Netflix project.
- Really?
- Yes.
It will be a big and global project.
People will applaud you
and acknowledge you.
It will be a fruitful year.
Will she meet a man?
- A wedding?
- That's right.
- A relationship.
- A wedding.
Running Man members
will need to help her.
She has really bad taste in men.
- I think that's the case.
- She has really bad taste in men.
- Yes.
- It's true.
- Seriously.
Thus, she could get used
by a horrible man...
who plays with a woman's heart.
She used to date someone horrible.
A man like that.
(Glaring)
But when you fall for someone,
you get blinded by love.
You give everything to your love.
- You are a romantic.
- Yes.
You can't multi-task.
- It's true.
- You can't do two things at once.
If she has rice and soup,
she can't eat them at the same time.
- She puts the rice in the soup.
- So she eats the soup first.
- I thought, "Why does she do that?"
"Why does she finish one
before the other?"
She can't cross the road...
- while chewing gum.
- She can't do that.
She needs to swallow it first.
- She needs to swallow it first.
- I don't know why she does that.
- My goodness.
- She can only do one thing.
- She can't multi-task.
It's so strange.
When you fall for a man,
you get blinded by love.
Seriously.
It can make your life
very difficult.
So Min is a good judge of character.
- I am a good judge of character.
- Yes.
She is intuitive.
- No way.
- I will judge the man for you.
Her intuition is useless...
when she finds a man for himself.
- It's useless.
- She falls for bad men too.
If So Min likes the man,
she will fall in love with him.
It will be a complete mess.
She shouldn't judge a man
for Ji Hyo.
- It will be a complete mess.
- If that happens...
"Ji Hyo, that man isn't for you."
"Because I love him."
- That won't do.
- She will fall in love with him.
She will fall in love with him.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. That was fun.
- Next.
- That was fun.
- Who will go next?
- So Min.
- This is fun.
- Good luck.
- So Min.
- Hello.
- This is fun.
- Good luck.
- So Min is the type...
- Be careful.
- to become absorbed.
- I like getting my fortune read.
I like getting my fortune read.
It's fun.
You like it, right?
I bet you wanted to sit down
right away.
(He begins to read
So Min's fortune.)
So Min.
(The fortune teller is serious.)
So Min is nervous.
I am nervous.
(I am nervous.)
I had my fortune read for this year,
but not next year.
(What will happen to So Min
in 2022?)
She believes in these things.
- How old are you this year?
- I am 36 years old.
- I see.
- In 2022, I will turn 37.
You have spiritual power.
- Me?
- Yes.
(You have spiritual power.)
- Me?
- Yes.
She does, right?
I see it in your eyes.
You have spiritual power.
If you hadn't become an actor,
you might have become a shaman.
- A shaman?
- Yes.
She might have become a shaman.
I am serious.
But she is so bad
at reading people's minds.
- She is so bad at it.
- She gets things wrong often.
(To the members,
So Min is a clumsy woman.)
- Do you get a sense of it?
- Of course.
I see it in her eyes.
How about me? I don't have it, do I?
Be quiet.
Had you had it,
he would have mentioned it.
He is being selfish again.
- I was curious.
- Everything is about him.
The element
you were born with is gold.
Since it's gold, you shine a lot.
You are like a jewel
that is difficult to own.
- A jewel...
- A jewel that is difficult to own.
Is that the reason why...
I can't have a boyfriend?
That's one reason.
You have many charms.
Sir, you are a good man.
- You are saying many good things.
- You are quite sensitive.
You don't behave that way here,
but you whine a lot
when you have a boyfriend.
It's true.
She is the queen of whining.
You are a bit like a baby.
If your boyfriend
doesn't coddle you, troubles arise.
If he is even a bit neglectful,
you become annoyed.
Hey, he knows you inside out.
- He is right.
- Have you dated her?
Are you her ex-boyfriend?
I got goosebumps.
They might cry
while looking at each other.
- That would be a twist.
- My goodness.
Only a few people would know.
- You get very lonely.
- You are right.
I bet you tell other people,
"I will focus on work.
I don't need a man."
But you think to yourself,
"When will I meet someone?
I want to be loved."
Since you are very feminine,
you keep thinking that.
He must have dated her.
She says that all the time.
Honey.
(She suddenly calls him "Honey.")
Then he goes, "Yes, So Min."
- "Have you been well?"
"How have you been?"
You are a bit distracted.
- That's right.
- It's a serious problem.
You go around asking things
because you are nosy.
Even if it's unrelated to you,
you have to know what's happening.
- You have to know.
- It's true.
Even if it's 12 a.m.,
you call people for information.
You have to know.
You know her so well.
- It's true.
- I can't believe it.
He knows her inside out.
You have to do it to find peace.
- I can't sleep otherwise.
- That's right.
(She can't sleep
when she wants to know something.)
But you don't need to go
to that extent.
This woman has a special ability.
She does? Like how?
- She can attach a spoon.
- On her forehead.
(She has the title
of a human magnet.)
This is quite unique.
You have the ability to curse.
(So Min has the ability to curse.)
(Does So Min have
the ability to curse people?)
That's what she told me.
She says people she hates
always end up with bad luck.
You have the ability to curse.
Let's say there's a man
who betrayed you.
So you curse him
and wish him bad luck.
- That's what she does.
- Then it comes true.
Hey... No, I mean...
- Did you call him hey?
- Hey.
So Min, what are you doing?
- Call him sir.
- He's not your friend.
I'm sorry. There were people...
who betrayed me, and I hated them.
None of them were successful.
- Did they all have hard times?
- They all did.
But the curse might
come back to you someday.
- So you should be careful.
- Stop cursing people.
That's the ability you have.
Did you curse her?
- What's wrong?
- Did you curse So Min?
What's wrong, Ji Hyo?
- He says it's okay.
- It's okay, Ji Hyo.
- She's shocked.
- Hey, it's all right.
- She's startled.
- It's okay.
She's not mad.
Forgive Ji Hyo.
- I won't curse people anymore.
- Good.
That's what you should do, So Min.
So I'll stop cursing people.
- Don't curse me.
- You want to do it even more now.
So Min, don't hate us.
Don't curse us.
This is my ability.
All right.
- Please stop.
- Don't come to me.
- No.
- She will do it even more.
It turns out she's the one
with supernatural powers.
But I'm not a bad person.
- Right. She's nice.
- She's good-hearted.
Will my career go well?
Yes. Things started...
going well for your work this year.
You will keep getting good luck.
- Things will get better over time.
- Congratulations.
Now you should focus
on your work, not dating.
What about dating?
So Min cares more
about her love life.
- Love always comes first.
- Does that mean...
I won't have a boyfriend?
In 2022 and 2023,
you will gain honor.
Your acting ability will be
recognized by many people.
But some flirting might...
- tarnish your reputation.
- Oh, no.
You might end up with someone
who could damage your reputation.
So I'd like you to focus only
on your work for the next two years.
Isn't it okay to flirt with Se Chan?
I'm busy playing soccer.
Forget about it.
I should play soccer.
I can't flirt with you.
- Soccer...
- He can't date anyone now.
- I'm busy.
- He should play soccer.
Actually, that's what upsets me.
It's not like...
I'm not interested in him anyway.
But why doesn't he like me?
- Does everyone have to like you?
- What are you talking about?
The question is weird.
Why would I like you
when you're not interested in me?
You should be careful.
She might curse you.
- Still, I want him to...
- I guess that's what motivates you.
- Right. It motivates me.
- I knew it.
- "Why isn't he falling for me?"
- Why won't he fall in love with me?
I won't date him anyway. But why...
This is about your self-esteem.
- But why do you even care?
- Isn't this strange?
Do I have to fall for her
when she doesn't love me?
But Se Chan...
likes young women.
(But Se Chan likes young women.)
Yes, that's true.
- Jong Kook.
- That's right.
- It's true.
- It is.
My goodness.
- He likes young women.
- You're unbelievable.
- That's true.
- He doesn't like women his age.
- That's right.
- He can't play jokes...
to women he likes.
- He becomes serious.
- He looks very playful now,
but he feels nervous
around someone he likes.
I was shocked
when he said "young women."
So she shouldn't date anyone
this year. She should focus on work.
That's right. You will do
some TV commercials too.
You will have good lucks
with documents.
For celebrities, it means
TV commercials.
You will get to do TV commercials
and dramas you like.
You will get to keep
signing documents.
You'll be very busy.
Good. You should
focus on work this year.
But what I want to do is kiss.
What's wrong with her?
- Instead of signing documents.
- What's with her?
Stop it and come back here.
That was too short for me.
I'm glad that
I'll be busy next year.
All right.
I'm curious about yours, Pouty Mouth.
Okay.
Let's talk about young women first.
Let's start with that.
Young women...
Can you see that I like young women?
Of course. You do like young women.
You don't like women
who're relatively old.
You're not interested in them.
He sees right through you.
Really?
This is crazy.
- My gosh.
- You like women anyway.
In the coming year,
your sexual desire will increase.
That means you're healthy.
- You're healthy.
You should have
your hormone level checked.
It also means
you will have good luck.
Your sexual desire
increases with good luck.
You might start exercising as well.
Don't waste your energy
and exercise with me.
I guess I should play soccer.
Play soccer with me.
Se Chan, you're a comedian.
You're a comedian, but you might get
a chance to do a legitimate drama.
- He's a great actor.
- A legitimate drama?
Yes. You might get a chance...
to do a drama or a movie...
- as an actor.
- You should do a movie.
- You should do it.
- Se Chan, do a movie.
- So you should get ready.
- That sounds good.
- Get ready?
- Yes. You should be ready.
- You should learn acting.
- Practice acting.
- So you can do a good job.
- Try to cry on cue.
Sure.
Try crying.
Then you laugh all of a sudden.
(He suddenly wails
just like a comedian.)
(Now he's told to laugh
all of a sudden.)
- Start laughing now.
- Laugh.
- You're laughing, but you're sad.
(You're laughing, but you're sad.)
Curse someone.
(Curse)
He's good.
Something like this?
You're good.
Who do you live with now?
I used to live with my brother,
but I live alone now.
- I moved out.
- Where do you live?
I moved to Yongsan.
What? Why did you not tell me?
(What? Why did you not tell me?)
- Why did you not tell me?
- Why did you not tell her?
- Is that true?
- It's her neighborhood.
I moved on Wednesday.
- But you...
- Right. He moved on Wednesday.
- Last Wednesday.
- Why did you not tell me.
That's why he couldn't
come to play soccer, right?
Why did you not tell me about it?
- He's not looking at her.
- Hey.
- That's good.
- Is there a possibility that...
- things will work out for them?
- Not at all.
Actually, So Min has
feelings for Se Chan.
- Me?
- Yes.
- I don't.
- She has feelings for him.
I guess she's just pretending.
But Se Chan has...
someone else in his mind.
(But Se Chan has
someone else in his mind.)
Who is that wench?
(Who is that wench?)
- Tell me.
- She will curse the woman.
- Hey, does she live in Yongsan?
- You're scaring me.
- You said you weren't dating.
- Hey, does she live in Yongsan?
You're scaring me.
- Does she live in Yongsan?
- She will curse you.
- I'm not interested in anyone.
- He moved to Yongsan.
- He didn't tell me.
- That's funny.
What about investing in stocks?
That's not good for Se Chan.
What about coins?
- I told you not to do it.
- It's...
minus 70 percent now.
Minus 70 percent?
It's minus 70 percent.
I'm about to be swept away.
I have no money to invest.
I'm better than you.
It's minus 63 percent for me.
(I'm better than you.
It's minus 63 percent for me.)
- Why do you guys invest in stocks?
- Stocks.
- I want to ask about stocks.
- I don't do that.
Today's fortune reading is
different from what I had before.
It's not that he reads what
he prepared. It's spontaneous.
And it's detailed.
He says things right on the spot.
(The detailed fortune-reading...)
(of the members continues.)
Jong Kook,
(When you first met Ji Hyo,
your heart fluttered.)
(The shocking past is revealed.)
(I'm not sure
if it's okay to say this.)
(His secret is revealed as well.)
(How things will go for the members
of Running Man next year?)
(And one day...)
(A man comes to a fortune-teller
after his self-quarantine period.)
(Is this place...)
(Forehead Fortune-teller makes
her debut only for Jae Suk.)
(Top Secret Revealed,
Forehead Fortune-teller)