(December 31, 1999)
The year 2000 is
less than two days away.
The new millennium will
begin in a few hours.
(People felt sad
about the end of the 20th century.)
(And they were excited and worried
about the new 21st century.)
(December 31, 1999)
(The year 2000, D-1)
(7 people of the new generation
are thrown into confusion)
(December 31, 1999)
(What is happening
on the threshold of a new century?)
(The new millennium is coming!
December 31, 1999)
Hello,
(A girl with twin buns
shows up looking shy.)
Hello.
(The rest of the new generation
is coming in as well.)
We have a guest today.
Do we have a guest?
He's visiting Korea.
Michael Jackson, come on!
Michael Jackson.
(Ha Jackson is back.)
Good.
(It's good to see him again
after six months.)
He lost some of his belly fat.
He lost his belly fat.
(Episode 552: The Entering Class
of 1991 Is Back!)
(He looks
just like Michael Jackson.)
(Ha Jackson suddenly
showed up at Euljiro.)
He suddenly starts dancing.
(He became the King of Pop
thanks to his stylist's mistake.)
(He was mocked
for his bulging belly.)
(Now his costume is perfect
for the end of the century.)
He lost his belly fat.
It was funny
with your bulging belly.
- You look cool.
- That's too bad.
His belly is flat now.
This is against the rules.
That's not important.
The biggest issue is...
- Ji Hyo's short hair.
- Right.
I agree.
This is what I thought.
Ji Hyo finally decided...
to win Jong Kook's heart.
- She looks so handsome.
- You know "Coffee Prince".
She looks like Yoon Eun Hye
of "Coffee Prince".
- Really? Is that Yoon Eun Hye?
- Hey.
Well... This is...
- I think So Min has a point.
- I know.
Wasn't that because of Demi Moore?
No. It's Yoon Eun Hye
of "Coffee Prince".
That's nonsense. Stay quiet.
- Nonsense?
- It's definitely "Coffee Prince".
(So Min keeps babbling on,)
(and Ji Hyo loses her temper.)
My goodness. Hey.
You almost got hit.
She sounds really upset.
Now that Ji Hyo got
her hair cut short,
she's the most handsome one
among the members.
Right.
- I'm the best-looking one.
- Number 1, 2, and 3.
- No, that's not it.
- Michael, you stay out of it.
- You didn't make the cut.
- You're out.
- Seriously.
- This is what I said.
For people like Ji Hyo,
the hairstyle doesn't matter.
- Right.
- You know?
- She looks really handsome.
- I won't say who it is,
but the hairstyle is very important
for some of us.
I know who it is.
You definitely need good hair.
(Some of them need a good hairstyle
to look like a decent person.)
It's you.
Who is this guy?
Who on earth is he?
He's just ugly.
Are you an archer?
Who are you? Aren't you an archer?
Are you an alpinist?
They know nothing about fashion.
- So who are you?
- Jae Suk.
- I can't see your face.
- You don't know anything.
- You know nothing about fashion.
- Are you Jang Woo Hyuk or what?
I tried many different things.
Many different things?
Are you from
the movie, "Home Alone"?
"Home Alone"? Are you
talking about the thief?
No. This is fashion.
What? Who are you?
I'm Yangpa.
Yangpa?
I thought you were S.E.S.
- "Heart Beat Away"?
- I always look at you
(I always look at you from behind)
You sound pretentious when you sing.
- S.E.S.
- She's Yangpa.
- And you...
- What?
- Don't I look nice today?
- You look normal today.
- People said I looked nice today.
- You look cool.
- This is...
- You look like an old man.
No. My stylist found this
at a vintage shop.
Suk Jin, that's not important.
This is also vintage.
You started talking.
I'm just answering.
Don't go to the restroom
when we take a group photo.
- Right.
- What?
(The members posted a group photo
without Suk Jin last week.)
Why did you take it without me?
- Where were you, Prince?
- My gosh.
- Where were you?
- You took it without me.
Suk Jin, you know
why you left early.
- That's...
- It's because of So Min.
He was afraid I'd ask him
to drive me home.
He didn't want to drive So Min home.
I didn't even ask him.
Here's the thing.
We had dinner together,
and So Min sent her manager home.
When we got out of the restaurant,
we asked So Min,
"How will you go home?"
"I'll take a taxi."
We said, "Why would you
take a taxi?" And Suk Jin...
- He went straight home.
- He could've given her a ride,
but he just left.
He avoided my eyes.
You thought I went to the restroom,
but I just went home.
I left early. But I could've
taken a photo with you before that.
Why did you leave like that
when So Min needed a ride home?
- She goes your way.
- You and I are the only ones...
who can give her a ride.
Then you give her a ride.
- I did.
- You are a warmhearted person.
- I gave her a ride.
- He took her home.
So it took me two
and a half hours to get home.
Did you go to Daejeon?
I was stuck in traffic.
It rained that day,
so traffic was bad.
It was okay, So Min.
- I had a lot of fun, Jae Suk.
- It can happen.
Who paid that day, by the way?
- Who paid for dinner?
- Suk Jin seemed hesitant.
Jae Suk paid.
"Jae Suk, you go ahead and pay."
You could've paid for that.
We just had sundae soup.
It's not like that. Jae Suk
arranged the meeting that day.
- But still...
- Jae Suk called us together.
- I...
- But you're the oldest one here.
I didn't want
to infringe on his right.
Jae Suk called us together,
but you were the oldest one there.
That doesn't matter. Hey.
When it comes to money,
he's the senior.
I know, but...
He's the richest one here.
We just had sundae soup.
It didn't even cost a lot.
Okay. I understand
that you saved money.
- I didn't save money.
- Why did you not take So Min home?
- About So Min...
- You say first.
I believed that Jae Suk
would give her a ride.
It would've been better
if you took a taxi home.
That's what I was going to do.
That was my plan.
He's the worst.
It was your choice.
It was your choice
that you sent your manager home.
- I was going to take a taxi.
- If you took a taxi,
he would've gone home in an hour.
Take a look
at the banner behind you.
- What?
- What is this?
- "The new millennium is coming."
- "The 21st century."
- The millennium!
- My gosh.
- I remember 1999.
- Me too.
Turbo released
the song, "Cyber Lover".
- Right. "Cyber Lover".
- "Cyber Lover".
Do you remember the time?
It was the end of the 20th century.
- It was like the end of the world.
- We thought we'd die.
- They foretold the end.
- And that wasn't it.
They also believed
that computers wouldn't recognize...
the year 2000.
- Right.
- The millennium bug.
We were told
not to access a computer.
- They said it would be crazy.
- Some people even withdrew money...
- from their bank accounts.
- Right. It was crazy.
Did you make your debut in 1999?
No, I debuted in 1991.
So it was a lot after your debut.
But that's when I started
doing many TV shows.
It was 1995...
- when he hosted my fan meeting.
- Your fan meeting.
But I don't remember him at all.
- Was it 1995?
- Not at all.
Seriously, I was...
- I remember only one thing.
- It was a stadium.
- What?
- In a corner of the waiting room,
you were getting an envelope
from the CEO of my agency.
(Polite)
I remember that we had an MC.
The CEO was like this. "Here."
And he was getting a white
envelope in front of the door.
- I remember the very scene.
- My goodness.
I felt bitter.
I was supposed
to introduce Jong Kook and leave.
"It's Turbo!"
And I was supposed to leave.
Jong Kook showed up.
The fans were roaring.
And outside the hall,
the CEO paid me like this. "Thanks."
(Thank you, sir.)
(Jae Suk's tears plopped down
on the thin white envelope.)
So he went through things like that.
- He did.
- I did.
Jae Suk did.
Today is December 31, 1999.
- My goodness.
- For the year 1999,
we have guests
who were born in 1999.
- Born in 1999?
- People who were born in 1999?
- In 1999?
- I see.
We have guests
who were born in 1999.
Please come on out.
Hello.
(SAN of ATEEZ,
Arin of OH MY GIRL, Jin Ji Hee)
- Ji Hee.
- Bbangkku Ttongkku.
Arin is here. And there's SAN.
(They are excited to see
the guests born in 1999.)
- Hello.
- Come over here.
Welcome.
(The little girl who caused...)
(the Bbangkku Ttongkku craze
12 years ago...)
(has grown
into this pretty actress.)
(The hottest drama of 2021,
"The Penthouse",)
(Jin Ji Hee showed
her professional acting skills.)
(The popular girl group, OH MY GIRL)
(Arin is the youngest member
with her refreshing charm.)
(The 2022 World Tour Concert
of ATEEZ is sold out.)
(ATEEZ's concerts are selling out
around the world.)
(The rising global
K-pop star band, ATEEZ)
(ATEEZ's performer
and lead vocalist, SAN)
(The trio born in 1999)
- Come here.
- Welcome.
- All right.
- Hey.
ATEEZ.
Look at her.
She's grown a lot.
- Ji Hee, you are...
- Hello.
I can't believe this.
I really liked her
when she was little.
- Me too.
- Seriously.
- I saw her on the news.
- I saw you on MBC.
I really liked you.
- This is great. Ji Hee...
- Hello.
This is undone.
- I opened it on purpose.
- You did?
I was surprised to see that.
I thought it was undone.
- This is the point.
- It's fashion.
- That's what we used to do.
- In the 1990s?
- My goodness.
- So we have...
Ji Hee here.
We also have Arin and SAN.
They all were born in 1999.
- Really?
- My gosh.
- I don't want to say...
- She was really cute.
- what happened in 1999.
- And her acting was the best.
It was crazy in 1999.
So Ji Hee is...
- 23 years old now.
- What?
- That's unbelievable.
- But...
I can't believe that.
It's been 19 years since her debut.
She debuted before some of you.
She debuted before me.
- She made her debut before I did.
- It's been 19 years?
She made her debut
in a TV drama in 2003.
- It was "Yellow Handkerchief".
- Right.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
So is this...
your first time
on Running Man, Ji Hee?
- Yes. This is...
- It feels like...
- you were here before.
- Right.
I wanted to join you,
but I wasn't invited.
I see.
I can't believe...
Ji Hee is 23 already.
- It's hard to believe.
- How old were you in the sitcom?
I was 11 back then.
I was 11 and 12.
- Were you 11 back then?
- Yes.
You wanted to join our show...
- when you were an eighth-grader?
- Of course.
It was her wish.
- Right.
- As an eighth-grader.
"Ji Hee's wish
is to join Running Man."
(The 14-year-old Ji Hee's dream:
Joining Running Man)
- That's cute.
- I know.
That was her dream
when she was in middle school.
- And she's 23 now.
- It comes true when you're 23.
- She's a Running Man kid.
- I grew up watching Running Man.
(Her dream from 9 years ago
is finally coming true today.)
So how do you feel to be here?
Gosh, stop it.
(He suddenly asks her
about how she feels.)
- He's being ridiculous.
- Stop it.
It's so old-fashioned.
- Oh, dear.
- Stop it, Mr. Vintage.
What's wrong with him?
He's being condescending again.
- This is amazing.
- Do you find it amazing?
Ji Hee recently finished her drama,
"The Penthouse 3".
How are you doing these days?
I go to school
and prepare for the school play.
- You're a college student.
- Right.
- That sounds nice.
- She's so young.
It sounds really fun.
- It must be fun.
- I'm a college senior.
- Are you a senior?
- Yes.
You know what?
He didn't graduate from college.
He's envious.
- He's a college dropout.
- But I went to college...
for four years.
As a freshman.
I took only the first semester.
I went to college for four years
as a freshman.
And I went
to a college retreat every year.
If that's the case...
He just went to school for fun.
- He deserves an honorary diploma.
- I liked to hang out with friends.
- So I went to every retreat.
- That sounds fun.
So did you drink makgeolli
on the campus lawn?
What?
Hey, that's not
what college students do now.
What are you talking about?
- That was a long time ago.
- That's ridiculous.
He doesn't know
about what young people do.
- Haha.
- That was a long time ago.
Did he go to college?
- Sure.
- Come here.
Did you hear that?
- "Did he go to college?"
- You did?
Hey, Jong Kook.
My goodness.
"Did he go to college?"
Arin says she's a Running Man kid.
Really?
- Is that true?
- Yes.
I really wanted to try
tearing off a name tag.
I said that in many interviews.
- You did?
- Yes. I'm...
just like Jin Hee...
- Jin Hee...
- It's Ji Hee.
(Jin Hee?)
(Embarrassed)
Arin, it can happen.
- Ms. Ji Hee... I mean, Ji Hee...
- It's Ji Hee.
- She's Jin Ji Hee.
- I see.
I know it's confusing.
They are not close.
During the opening,
Arin said the wrong name.
- It's awkward.
- It's like...
- they fell into a pit.
- Right. It's awkward now.
- I'm sorry.
- It's really okay.
SAN can barely hear...
what Arin and Ji Hee are saying.
He's worried
about his own interview.
- He's feeling nervous.
- Right.
- Because he's nervous?
- Yes.
This is the face
of the 21st century.
- He's different.
- He looks sophisticated.
- It's the urban type.
- I know.
Standing next to him,
- Jae Suk looks like a squid.
- He's totally different.
It's like a squid is
standing next to him.
- SAN looks so cool.
- Hey.
- He looks like a baby octopus.
- Seriously,
- This is a mudflat.
- You guys.
Se Chan, Suk Jin, and you...
look like dried white baits.
Dried white baits?
So we have SAN here.
- He's a member of ATEEZ.
- ATEEZ.
He belongs to ATEEZ.
We did an album together.
- Oh, right.
- That's true.
They recently worked with Jong Kook.
- They did a collaboration.
- They did an album together.
(Jong Kook appeared
in the music video...)
(for "The Black Cat Nero" by ATEEZ.)
(They also released
a collaboration album together...)
(with the song,
"Be My Lover" recently.)
(Jong Kook has
a special bond with SAN.)
Look. He's got broad shoulders.
He does have broad shoulders.
I've been taking
your protein supplements.
- He is pleased.
- I told him...
that his face needs a nice build.
I can tell...
- Jong Kook cares for him a lot.
- Sure.
- His eyes...
- Jong Kook can't hide it.
By the way, your outfit is...
You look like a dump truck driver
in an American film.
- I know what you mean.
- You know it.
- A guy who arm-wrestles.
- And beer.
- He always drinks beer.
- He drinks beer.
- I drive a truck.
- He goes to a bar at night.
- And I carry around a rifle.
- Right.
And he's divorced.
He has a son.
His wife died.
- She died?
- That's what he looks like.
That's enough.
You look good
with your boyfriend today.
We're a couple.
(Excited)
They are clapping.
(Clapping)
They are idol artists.
So they give reactions all the time.
They look good together, don't they?
Yes. They look lovely.
They are idol artists,
so they just clap their hands.
They are of the same age,
but they're different from Ji Hee.
They are a little different.
I want to be like them.
- Ji Hee claps when she wants to.
- Right.
But SAN and Arin
just clap no matter what.
- Right.
- Am I right?
All right.
Today, with the 99 kids
who were born in 1999,
we will have the Prophets of
the End of the Century Race.
Today is the last day of 1999
when Nostradamus predicted...
the Earth would come to an end.
If you guys manage to survive today,
you will be able to see
the new millennium safely.
(If they survive today, they will
see the new millennium safely.)
But in here...
(But in here...)
(In here?)
We have two people who
try to stop you from doing so.
I knew it.
- They are two prophets,
- I had this feeling.
Nostra and Damus.
(There are two prophets,
Nostra and Damus.)
A French prophet from the 16th
century, Nostradamus has revived.
He predicted World War I and II,
and even the end of the world.
This is what Nostradamus predicted.
He said the world would come to an
end right before the 21st century.
(Nostradamus predicted the Earth
would come to an end in 1999.)
They are the new prophets...
who foretold the end of the world
and shocked Running Man.
They are named Nostra and Damus.
In here,
we have two prophets,
Nostra and Damus.
My gosh.
Jong Kook is starting it again.
(Jong Kook is starting it again.)
- He's staring at me.
- Do you think it's him?
- Stop it.
- I got him.
We have Nostra and Damus in here.
- You...
- Nostra and Damus?
You are overreacting.
- It's not like that.
- All right.
I know I look strange.
I'm the only one
who looks strange here.
Today, you will
accumulate prize money...
after each mission.
If you manage to single out
Nostra and Damus through a vote,
you will get the prize money
you accumulated during the race.
The two people...
who are picked by the final vote,
whether they are
citizens or prophets,
will get a penalty.
I see.
And the prize money
that the rest of you get...
will vary depending on whether
the prophets are arrested or not.
So two of you will be arrested.
(The rules of Judgment Stand)
If both Nostra
and Damus are arrested,
the rest of the members will get
the prize money they accumulated.
(The citizens get their prize money
if Nostra and Damus are arrested.)
If only one of them is arrested,
you will get only half
of your prize money.
(They get only half of their money
if only one of them is arrested.)
If you fail to arrest both of them,
you won't get your prize money.
(If they fail to arrest them,
only the prophets get the money.)
There will be three teams
in each round.
The teams will be decided randomly
for each mission.
(The teams will be decided randomly
for each mission.)
Before each mission,
the prophets will...
predict the ranking of the teams.
They will predict...
who will be in
1st, 2nd, and 3rd places.
And their team always
has to be the third.
That means they will try...
- They have to be the 3rd.
- to make their team the 3rd.
We will be able to see that.
This is tricky.
- I'm worried about you, Se Chan.
- So one member in a team...
- I'm not. Trust me.
- It sounds so difficult.
- You're done for.
- It'll be too difficult for you.
- That team must be in the last.
- I told you, I'm not the one.
If their predictions turn out right,
they'll get a big prize.
- I guess they know about the games.
- We'll inform them.
But when their predictions
turn out wrong,
the citizens will get a chance
to decide who they are.
He's in trouble.
- That's how you can find...
- It'll be hard for him.
- Nostra and Damus hidden among you.
- Got it.
We'll begin the first mission.
It's a gun shooting game.
- What? A gun shooting game?
- Yes, that's the first mission.
It's a simple game.
We'll draw names to decide the teams
for that game now.
Suk Jin looks quite nervous.
Suk Jin has been acting
a little weird.
- He stuttered too.
- Oh, right.
- He always stutters though.
- Maybe he's Nostra,
- and Se Chan is Damus.
- But Suk Jin got much smoother.
Now, I'll draw the three names...
- on the 1st team for the 1st game.
- Okay.
(The teams for the 1st game
will be decided.)
- Se Chan, Suk Jin, and So Min.
- Oh, okay.
(Team 1: Se chan, Suk Jin, So Min)
- Oh, the 3 of us?
- The 3 of us.
- What does that mean?
- Okay.
- We're on the same team.
- Right.
SAN, Arin, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.
And the rest three of you are
on Team Three.
- Ji Hee is on our team.
- Oh, yes. I'm excited.
- Awesome.
- Ji Hee and "How Do You Play?".
Before I tell you the rules
of the first game,
the prophets will make
their predictions.
They want us to put on a blindfold.
- A blindfold?
- Put on a blindfold.
(So everyone put on a blindfold.)
Keep a distance from one another
so you won't touch one another.
All right. Everyone.
The prophets will predict
the result of the game.
Only Nostra and Damus,
pull down your blindfolds slightly.
First, predict the ranking
of the team of Se Chan, So Min,
and Suk Jin, and show us
by raising your fingers.
(Each of them predicts
the ranking of Team 1.)
Next, show the ranking of the team
of Haha, Jae Suk, and Ji Hee...
that you predict using your fingers.
(And they predict
the ranking of Team 2.)
Now, predict the ranking
of the team...
of Ji Hyo, Arin, SAN, and Jong Kook.
(They predicted the rankings
of all 3 teams.)
It's over.
- You may take off the blindfold.
- Okay.
Well...
I think that Suk Jin is
one of the prophets.
- Why?
- It's because...
- Are you wearing cologne?
- Yes. Why?
- Whenever he moved,
I could smell his cologne.
(Whenever he moved,
I could smell his cologne.)
- Suk Jin, come on.
- He got caught.
- I think he got caught.
- You're not, are you?
- Really?
- Of course not.
- You're not, are you?
- I smelled it whenever he moved.
- We caught one.
- Even that can be suspicious?
- This is so funny.
- Nostra and Damus are so lucky.
- Everyone thinks I'm one of them.
- It's hilarious.
- I could smell it.
- By the way...
- It's too easy.
- They must be happy.
Suk Jin, why do you keep blushing?
You're not one of them, are you?
Now, please move with your team.
- Yes.
- I act suspicious when I'm not.
You know that I act suspicious
when I'm not, right?
All right. We'll begin
the first game now.
- Okay.
- The first mission requires...
a good strategy
for getting a bigger prize.
It's Cyber Balloon Lover.
You'll play a survival game
divided into three teams.
You can find pouches with a badge...
with the number 99 on it
at different places.
Each badge is worth ten dollars.
You can either find
as many badges as you can...
or you can shoot the last balloon
out of five balloons...
on the back of a member
of another team to get one badge.
Also, each team has
its headquarters.
Your team is out if you lose...
all the balloons
at the headquarters.
Even if you lose all the balloons
on your back,
you can refill balloons at your
headquarters to go back to fight.
But your team may be eliminated soon
as fewer balloons will be left.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
Don't forget that Nostra and Damus
will do anything...
- to make their teams lose.
- Oh, right.
- It'll be easy to tell.
- I think it'll be difficult.
Hey, Damus.
- No.
- Hey, Damus.
No, I'm not Damus.
- Were the three of you on Team One?
- Yes.
- This way, please.
- Got it.
That must be our...
Oh, I see balloons.
- Is that our headquarters?
- That's pretty.
It's like someone prepared
a surprise event.
- A surprise event?
- Right? Look at those balloons.
- Right. I see what you mean.
- Se Chan.
When did you prepare all that?
- Yes?
You should tell her
how you feel now.
You've waited long enough.
Okay. I filled the trunk of my car
with balloons.
- That's so pretty.
- Oh, my.
- I guess it's been a long time
- How pretty.
Whose are those red balloons?
- The red balloons belong...
- I see the red balloons.
to the "How Do You Play?" team
and Ji Hee.
- The "How Do You Play?" team?
- Oh, I see.
You mean those two?
- I'm speechless.
- Oh, the "How Do You Play?" team?
- Gosh, seriously.
- The "How Do You Play?" team?
- Exactly.
I can't believe this.
- Gosh.
- Come on.
(They're putting on a balloon vest
at their headquarters.)
- You've never done this, right?
- No, I haven't.
There's nothing special
about this game.
Haven't you played a shooting game
like this with your parents?
Don't you play games like this
with your friends?
- I've tried it on my school trip.
- On your school trip?
You can wear the glasses as well
if you want.
- Sorry?
- The glasses.
That won't be necessary.
- You get scared easily, you know.
- Gosh.
Why that little...
(Protective glasses are prepared
for the scaredy-cats.)
The director of Running Man.
I hate the director of Running Man.
- Where are those glasses?
- Right?
Gosh, I'm worried.
(So all 3 teams settled
at their own headquarters.)
- It won't be easy.
- Who should guard the headquarters?
- I think...
- The strong one should do that.
You think so? I agree...
that since you two are the guests,
you should move around
more than I do.
Suk Jin, I'll guard
our headquarters.
- Will you do that?
- Yes, I'll do it.
Z-KIRI, will you be the guard?
(Z-KIRI, will you be the guard?)
Let's take turns
guarding our headquarters.
Come back when you get tired.
- Good. Let's do that.
- To take a break?
- Got it.
- I'll be the first to guard here.
- Okay. Keep our balloons safe.
- Okay.
The race will begin now.
- Okay. I'll stay here.
- Five.
- You'll be here?
- Four.
- Three.
- So Min, keep all of them safe.
- Two.
- I'm scared.
- This spot here...
- We've got this!
- We'll get going.
- Go!
How shall I teach them a lesson?
Let's find some 99 badges.
What could those pouches look like?
Okay. I found one.
Did you find one? Okay.
(Se Chan found a pouch
with a 99 badge.)
- I did well, right?
- Yes, you did well.
- Oh, there it is.
- Where?
I've become better
at finding hidden things like this.
I'm impressed.
You're really good at finding it.
- You're so good at it.
- It used to be hard before.
But it became easy.
I think there's another one
around here.
(They get 10 dollars
for each 99 badge they find.)
Do you think we should attack
the other teams first?
I like that idea.
(Team Black's attackers are
moving forward boldly.)
Arin, you should find pouches too.
(Ji Hyo luckily found a pouch
while walking.)
(Arin took her advice
and tried hard to find a pouch.)
Where should I put it?
(While she was celebrating
finding her first badge...)
Great. I see two weaklings here.
What? How dare you...
- call us weaklings?
- Don't shoot first. SAN is coming.
- SAN, you look so enthusiastic.
- What? How dare you...
(At that moment,
SAN started running toward them.)
Look at SAN.
Your balloons will pop
once you show your enthusiasm.
(A male idol singer who's trying to
prove himself is always ruthless.)
- SAN, you look enthusiastic.
- Hey, this is...
(The scaredy-cats who were watching
decided to join the fight.)
(He gets excited
every time he holds a toy gun.)
Ji Hee, follow me. Hurry.
(SAN got surrounded by his enemies
in an instant.)
(He's trying to protect his balloons
with big movements.)
(During the brief confrontation...)
(Jae Suk runs with a smirk
on his face.)
(Pop)
(Bull's eye)
- Oh, gosh.
- Nice.
(He never misses the target.)
- Oh, gosh.
- Nice.
SAN has only one balloon left.
(SAN has only one balloon left.)
(Team Black is
pushed over the edge.)
I'm out.
(Team Black is
pushed over the edge.)
Go away!
No.
(Pop)
(Screaming repeatedly)
I can't go near her
because my ears hurt.
I can't get close to her
because she keeps screaming.
Oh, gosh. Help me.
(The new technique of building
a shield by screaming)
My ears hurt so much.
(Screaming)
- She has some balloons left.
- No!
- I didn't shoot. You...
(While they are having
a fierce battle...)
(Haha leaves the headquarters!)
Okay.
Suk Jin, give me time to reload.
I'm out of bullets.
Darn it.
(As Ji Hyo retreats temporarily,)
(Haha runs toward her.)
(He popped all Ji Hyo's balloons.)
(That's when...)
Hey, stop!
(This is my chance.)
(Se Chan is running
into Team Red's headquarters.)
Oh, no. That's our headquarters.
Hey, stop!
(Team Red's headquarters are empty
as Haha left there.)
(Se Chan's Camera)
(Shooting every balloon)
No!
(He popped 9 balloons
at an insane speed.)
Get him!
(He's leaving quickly
after the sudden attack.)
Give us our balloons back.
(Team Red lost 9 balloons
in a flash.)
Give me more bullets.
- Ji Hee.
- Yes?
- Give me more bullets.
- I don't know where they are.
- How did it go?
- I popped a lot of their balloons.
- How many balloons do I have left?
- I have one left.
- What about me?
- You have two left.
Sorry? What did you say?
(While they were checking
each other's remaining balloons...)
What's this?
What? Hey, you have a red balloon
on your back.
Leave it.
(He brought a red balloon
as a trophy unintentionally.)
- How did it get on your back?
- I have no idea.
Jong Kook, I need to refill
my balloons.
Why did you guys... Gosh.
It wasn't like that.
The other teams...
I think you should go there.
- Really? Why?
- It's because...
they call us weaklings
and think we're an easy target.
Oh, gosh. Go and put balloons
on your back. You lost all of them?
- Yes, I lost all of them.
- Gosh. How did that happen?
Oh, dear. I'm drooling.
Shouldn't we attack them?
(Meanwhile, the high frequency
attacker barely survived.)
(She tries to attack Big Nose.)
(They look like a father
and his daughter playing a game.)
(Pop)
You have only one balloon left.
I'll let you go.
(You have only one balloon left.
I'll let you go.)
(I'll let you go.)
- I'll let you go.
- Gosh.
(Suk Jin let Arin go
when she had 1 balloon left.)
- There. The red one.
- Oh, wait.
- Sorry?
- The red one.
(He could've shot her last balloon
as she could refill her balloons.)
(What was Suk Jin's intention?)
- We're in the middle.
- We're sandwiched between them.
- We're at a disadvantage.
- How about we attack them together?
- Are you at a disadvantage?
- Of course.
- Our headquarters is in the middle.
- Did you lose many balloons?
We can be attacked easily
since we're in the middle.
- Please help us.
- Shall we help Ji Hee's team?
Are we all going to attack them?
(Okay.)
Let's go. Haha.
- Yes?
- Stay here to guard our balloons.
We'll go and attack
their headquarters.
Now, we're allies. We certainly are.
This means we're allies.
(While they're walking
toward Team White's headquarters...)
What are you doing?
(They meet the warrior
of the end of the century.)
- Look at So Min.
- Of course we should attack them.
(She started shooting.)
Hey. That hurts.
I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry.
I see So Min over there.
Ji Hee, come over here.
(Ji Hee joins him without hesitating
as the weakest has been spotted.)
(Team Red is getting closer
to Team White's headquarters.)
Suk Jin, when will you come?
(While they are confronting
the cyber warrior...)
(Ha Jackson runs to ambush them.)
Be careful! Guard the headquarters!
(Team White's headquarters seems
too easy to attack.)
Keep the headquarters safe!
(Ha Jackson is trying to sneak in
along the byway.)
Okay. Haha is going up there.
Hey, he's coming.
SAN is running toward us.
(SAN of Team Black spots Haha
and starts running.)
(Hey, he's coming.
SAN is running toward us.)
- Suk Jin, behind you.
- What?
How dare you?
Oh, no. What should we do?
What do we do?
(Jae Suk and Ji Hee join them
to keep the momentum going.)
(While watching them,
Jong Kook gives a hand signal.)
(And Arin starts running
in the opposite direction.)
(She sneaks into
Team Red's headquarters.)
(At the moment,
all members of Red Team...)
(are attacking Team White.)
Come on, Se Chan.
Hey, Se Chan.
Oh, gosh.
(Arin of Team Black uses the moment
to attack their headquarters.)
I must hurry. Let's go.
(Arin of Team Black uses the moment
to attack their headquarters.)
(She has a chance to eliminate
the whole team.)
Stop it!
We lost all our balloons.
This is bad.
(Arin continues attacking
with no one around her.)
(What?)
(However...)
(Giggling)
(She sat down
after popping only 3 balloons.)
(That's not all.
She picks up bullets...)
(and leaves there
without shooting the balloons.)
(Her behavior seems unreasonable
as no one is chasing after her.)
I should hide.
(She suddenly hides herself
when she has a great chance.)
(The 3 members of Team Red
have no idea.)
Okay!
Hey.
(Jae Suk is returning
as if he started worrying.)
Okay.
(Jae Suk is returning
as if he started worrying.)
(But Arin is still hiding.)
(Pop)
What was that?
(Arin's last balloon popped.)
(Arin popped only a few balloons
so Jae Suk wouldn't notice.)
Arin, what are you doing there?
I was just taking a break.
(I was just taking a break.)
You didn't come here
to pop our balloons, did you?
I walked around here.
I was about to leave.
(At that moment...)
(SAN appears with a serious look
on his face.)
(He meets Jae Suk.)
(SAN wants to get back at him
for his attack earlier.)
(If he pops all the balloons here,
Team Red will be out.)
I'm out. Gosh.
(Right then,
Jae Suk ran out of bullets.)
- What? Arin.
- Yes?
You popped too few balloons.
(You popped too few balloons.)
- What happened?
- I did my best.
Hurry up and come.
(Here goes the troubleshooter.)
- Hey.
- What's happening there?
(Ji Hee saw what happened
at her headquarters too.)
No! Oh, my gosh.
Keep shooting.
(Team Red has only 4 balloons left
until they get eliminated.)
- This one won't pop.
- Hey, stop.
That's not fair. You can't do that.
Gosh. I have no bullets. Gosh.
- Hurry up!
- Jae Suk, you're out.
(Things are getting worse.
Jae Suk is out.)
- Hurry!
- Why won't it pop?
- Come on.
- No!
Hurry up.
(This is the last red balloon.)
- Oh, my gosh.
- Hurry up and come.
SAN.
- We agreed not to do this.
- I mean...
I ran out of bullets.
- Team Red is out!
- Darn.
(Team Red is out.)
Gosh. Where did Haha go?
- I ran out of bullets.
- That went well.
Gosh. I had no bullets left.
You guys let your guard down.
Haha went there too.
Exactly. Why would he leave here?
(Team Red lost because they left
the headquarters attended.)
One of us should've stayed
to guard our balloons.
- I had no bullets left.
- Is Haha one of the prophets?
(Is Haha one of the prophets?)
(The man who caused the defeat
is coming back.)
- Isn't Haha suspicious?
- I think so too.
- You asked him to guard here.
- Why did he leave here?
I heard you saying that to him.
(He was asked to guard
the headquarters.)
(Could Haha who left his position
be 1 of the prophets?)
What happened?
(Could Haha who left his position
be one of the prophets?)
- Hey.
- Haha won't even come here.
Come over here.
Why? He just told me,
"Come over here."
- Come over here.
- "Come over here."
Me?
Hey, the cast member
of "How Do You Play?", come here.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
Why?
Why did you leave the headquarters?
You know that I helped you
attack that team.
(He joined the battle
when he wasn't even asked to.)
We're out, Haha.
Darn it.
(Could Haha who left
the headquarters...)
(be 1 of the 2 prophets,
Nostra and Damus?)
Okay. Hang it.
You might lose them all
if you keep them in your pocket.
I can't believe I couldn't pop
a single balloon.
We should pop
Jong Kook's balloons first.
Whose balloons should we pop?
Hey, we... Red ones.
Let's work together.
What do you mean?
We got eliminated, Suk Jin.
We were the weakest.
- The location of our headquarters.
- That's true.
Gosh, I'm so upset. He runs so fast.
I bet he thinks
that he's really cool.
(He runs so fast. I bet he thinks
that he's really cool.)
(I'm so cool.)
(SAN never smiles
as if he were a secret spy.)
- I'm out.
- Are you okay?
(He's proud of himself
after eliminating another person.)
He looked as if he was fighting
on a battlefield.
Look at his face.
He looks so serious.
He looked as if he thought
this was a real war.
- SAN.
- Yes?
You think that you're really cool,
don't you?
I think so.
(I think so.)
- I feel that way sometimes too.
- I know you do.
Sometimes you find yourself so cool
while holding a toy water gun.
- True. I do feel that way.
- I know, right?
Once you feel that way
about yourself, it lasts long.
(The secret spy's movements
became more skillful.)
SAN, you're merciless.
Gosh, he's back.
(Swoosh)
Hey, look how SAN is biting
a bullet.
My goodness. What's that?
I've never seen
anything like that before.
- Is that really necessary?
- I mean...
Why is he biting that bullet?
- Why?
- What is he doing?
- What's with him?
- My gosh. What is he doing?
(When Arin who's on his team
is being attacked,)
(he appears
like the male lead of a movie.)
Oh, my goodness. Did you see
how he just protected Arin?
What a hero.
I wish I could... Why didn't I think
of biting a bullet?
(While everyone is enjoying
watching SAN's actions...)
Hey, go to the headquarters!
(The fitness lover is running
toward Team White's headquarters.)
Go and protect our headquarters.
To the headquarters!
(The weak ones went after him
too late.)
Go!
No!
(No!)
Wait. Where is the balloon?
Darn it.
Where is it?
No!
(No!)
(Team White's headquarters cleared)
Gosh. No.
Our headquarters have been attacked.
That's it. The game is over.
Why?
Good job.
(The game is over.)
What's important is...
that we must find Nostra and Damus.
Who did the worst in the game?
- I think one of them is on my team.
- They probably lost on purpose.
Right. Haha. Oh, gosh.
- Me?
- One of them must be on my team.
Jae Suk, I did my best.
(Who could be Nostra and Damus?)
I didn't find many pouches.
Me neither. I should've found
more pouches.
By the way, Team Red's headquarters
were located in the worst place.
- It was the worst place.
- True.
It's true that you were unlucky
with the location. But also...
Haha's actions made no sense at all.
- They made no sense.
- What do you mean?
I was demolishing
their headquarters.
It was wrong of you.
You can't leave
your headquarters unguarded.
- But they...
- That's enough.
Those who didn't try hard
must be the prophets.
Haha let me aim at his back.
- Me?
- I get it now.
- Haha and Suk Jin both.
- I agree.
Me?
- No, Suk Jin.
- You mean me?
- It's not me.
- But I did my best.
That's just the vibe I got.
- But Se Chan...
- Did I not try hard enough?
- No.
- Se Chan acted weirdly too.
- Se Chan too...
- But I moved around like crazy.
You saying that
makes me doubt you more.
He let me aim at his back for free.
He only moved around like crazy...
because he didn't mind
his balloons getting popped.
You know what I mean, right?
- So on purpose...
- He put himself in danger.
There's no point
in arguing with him.
The team who survived longer...
will receive 50 dollars each.
And the winning team
will get 100 dollars each.
In teams, you will announce
how much you have.
We have 14.
- That's the same for you all.
- That's 140 dollars.
- And the red team?
- We have seven.
Can you let us have ten?
- Seven...
- We were at a disadvantage.
We collected 13...
- and received ten.
- How much is that in total?
- In total, we have 23.
- Right, 23.
- No way.
- That's a huge imbalance.
- We should do better this time.
- Sure.
Nostra and Damus...
predicted how
the first game would go.
If their predictions were correct,
Nostra and Damus would earn...
a total of 460 dollars each.
The double of what
the winning team has.
First, Nostra...
(Nostra's prediction
is revealed first.)
Nostra's prediction...
came true.
(Nostra's prediction came true.)
Then,
it has to be one of them.
- Nostra is a member of our team.
- The team had to come last.
That means Nostra is on that team.
- Nostra is a member of our team.
- It has to be Haha.
The team had to come last.
- Nostra is a member of our team.
- No way.
It really isn't me.
I bet my life on it.
- It's one of them.
- One of them is Nostra.
- My gosh.
- I get it now.
- No wonder we lost.
- Exactly.
Meanwhile, Damus...
This is unbelievable.
(Nostra's prediction came true.
So what about Damus'?)
There are two prophets.
Meanwhile, Damus...
(Damus' prediction...)
- Damus' prediction didn't come true.
- I knew it.
(Damus' prediction
didn't come true!)
- There's one on each team.
- Yes, one on each team.
- Se Chan and...
- There's one on each team.
It has to be Se Chan and HaHa.
- Unbelievable.
- Why do you think it's me though?
You left the headquarters
to attack others.
But I did that to win.
- Hey.
- Look. SAN, don't.
Just leave him be.
It's over for him.
"It's over for him."
That's hilarious.
What do you mean it's over?
Are you kidding me?
- It's okay.
- Jong Kook knows it's you.
- He says it's me and you.
- I know who it is.
- Just know that it's him.
- Got it.
(Detective Kim won't even
let him explain himself.)
Since Damus' prediction
didn't come true,
the citizens will
choose four people...
(The citizens can choose 4 people
to be on the Judgment Stand.)
to be on the Judgment Stand.
I will tell you
if Damus is among them.
Haha should be one of them.
He's Nostra, so not him.
His prediction came true, remember?
You've got to be kidding me.
I tried my best, you know.
- Did you hear him?
- Four is a big number.
He can't even speak properly.
What do you mean?
I'm saying it's not me.
- How is it not you?
- Ji Hee...
What else can I say
when it's not me?
(Only those who have been suspected
by Jong Kook before understand.)
I did my best.
You said that twice already.
(You said "I did my best" twice!)
I did my best!
I know how it feels
to be suspected by him.
I...
was the first one
to guard our headquarters.
I'm sorry that you're here
working this job...
when you should clearly
be at a funeral.
Are you a frozen corpse then?
- We...
- Should I stick a talisman on you?
- Even though he's grieving...
- Unbelievable.
I'm grateful that
he made the time to be here.
- I didn't get any sleep.
- Exactly.
Shouldn't it be one of the four?
- Isn't it Arin?
- Exactly.
- I think it's her.
- I don't think so.
She did try her best.
Besides, she tried
not to get eliminated.
It's proof that...
- she wanted to win.
- Of course.
- She didn't make herself a target.
- Who made you a detective?
Just choose the four
you suspect the most then.
(Just choose the four
you suspect the most then.)
- Why bother...
- The prosecutor...
Is this the Kim Jong Kook Game?
SAN also tried his best.
Look at him sweating.
So it can't be him.
- And Arin tried to stay safe.
- SAN...
was absorbed in how good he looked.
In other words,
he fell in love with himself.
- So on our team...
- He was loving how he looked.
From our team, I suspect Ji Hee.
It's not me.
- It can be her.
- Why are you...
- suspecting me?
- Be honest with me.
- Ji Hee.
- You should always remember...
- that you can be suspected.
- Earlier,
you said you'd guard
the headquarters.
- You weren't there though.
- What?
- Haha said he'd take over!
- Hold on a second.
We can check the recording.
You said you'd guard
the headquarters,
so I went to attack.
(Haha's claim)
(He only ran out because Ji Hee said
she'd guard the headquarters.)
(Ji Hee volunteered to guard
the headquarters like Haha.)
I attacked the other team...
and you followed, right?
I'm being framed, you know.
From what I can tell,
Ji Hee also tried hard
not to be a target.
Se Chan's awfully quiet
which can only mean...
- that he's guilty of something.
- No way.
- I'm sure of it.
- It really isn't me.
Let's have him on the stand.
It can also be you, you know.
- And discuss this with the guests.
- How about this then?
Since we're sure
that Haha is Nostra,
let's put him on the stand
to increase our chances.
- Haha and Se Chan.
- Me too?
Yes, go ahead.
- Seok Sam too.
- Also...
- Ji Hee too.
- Come on.
- Why me?
- But it isn't me.
Who's to say you're not Damus?
- Ji Hee... Wait a second.
- Okay, Ji Hee too.
- Ji Hee too.
- No, that's not the way to go.
- I'll go up there.
- Isn't it you?
- No, that's not necessary.
Only that way
will we increase our chances!
(Only that way
will we increase our chances!)
Please don't argue.
Me going up there...
is how we increase our chances.
But you're one of my suspects.
- Me?
- Of course.
- You never know.
No, don't go up there.
- Just don't.
- Not you.
- How can you go up there?
- You can't.
- But I must go up there to...
- No, don't.
Don't overpower us
with your strength!
- Just don't.
- You're being coercive.
But that's the way.
- There's no need.
- Me going up there...
is how we increase our chances.
Why are you naming suspects
right from the beginning?
It's only making me suspect you too.
- But me going up there...
- Can he do this?
You're only pushing this...
to cover up your crimes.
- Mister.
- You're not making any sense.
- Hey, mister.
- What?
In front of us...
- That hurts.
- Hey, mister.
- Okay, fine. Then...
- Can you...
move your tractor?
Then let's put SAN on the stand.
- No, not SAN.
- Not him.
It won't mean a thing.
- But SAN isn't Damus.
- Just hear me out.
Who we know isn't Damus
should be on the stand...
so that when one of them
is revealed as Damus,
- we'll know by deduction.
- Then let me go up there.
You're a suspect yourself, you know.
I'll go up there, since it isn't me.
You're a suspect yourself.
- Se Chan will go up there.
- It isn't me, but still.
- And SAN.
- This is unbelievable.
This will only increase our chances.
And you as well.
- Why bother...
- I shouldn't go up there.
- We need one more.
- Jong Kook.
Can you please
make this a group decision?
Can't you see
we're deciding as a team?
I call this the Kim Jong Kook Game.
Just do what you want then.
- Are you kidding me.
- If you think about it...
- What about our opinion?
- This sure is fun!
What will it be?
Will you do whatever you want?
Should I step aside?
No, that's not what I meant.
You can choose these four
if you agree with him.
- Sure.
- Let it be these four.
- Suk Jin, come on.
- Me?
Why should I be on the stand?
Mister, you're also a prime suspect.
- But...
- After how hard I tried?
- I suspect you as well.
- What?
(Could it be any more tiring?)
Guys!
(Ji Hee watches them.)
I can tell it's Haha for sure now.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook
is certain that Haha is Nostra.)
- But I tried my best.
- I can tell for sure.
- It has to be one of them.
- Unbelievable.
I will be shocked
if Damus isn't one of them.
- Yes, that would be shocking.
- That could be the case.
Listen up.
Out of the four
on the Judgment Stand...
(Suk Jin and Se Chan
are being suspected as Damus.)
Damus...
It's not one of us.
(SAN was put up there
to increase the odds.)
Damus...
It's not one of us.
(Is Damus among these 4?)
- He is among you.
- See what I mean?
(One of them is Damus.)
- We've got this.
- I was sure of it.
- Hold on a second.
- Jong Kook.
- SAN, step out of the way.
- Jong Kook...
Haha isn't Damus either.
- It's not me.
- But...
It's not me either!
It really isn't me this time around.
Look at him. Isn't he acting weird?
- I mean it.
- Damus!
- Suk Jin's acting strange.
- It really isn't me.
- Shut It Damus.
- Unbelievable.
I'm sure of it.
(Suspects for Nostra:
Haha, Jae Suk, Ji Hee)
(Suspects for Damus,
Suk Jin, Se Chan, Haha, SAN)
- No way.
- It isn't me.
I know that it's not Suk Jin...
because I tried to smell
the cologne off him.
The scent was sour though.
He doesn't have cologne on.
I smelled something sour.
You...
- You...
- You're right.
- He smells sour.
- That's the scent...
- from my vintage clothes.
- There's that sour smell again.
- A sour smell?
- Mr. Sour.
- Mr. Sour is hilarious.
- That's your new nickname.
You'll now head
to the next location.
(With the pool of suspects,
they head to the next location.)
Off we go!
(They board the bus to move out.)
- Are you sure?
- Look at you two conversing.
- I...
- Is there a connection here?
What could you be talking about?
We're supposed to sit
with our teammates.
(While chatting,
they take their seats.)
(They're sitting together.)
Ji Hyo, the hair looks good on you
the more I see it.
Of course, it does. The pretty ones
look good with anything.
- They look good with anything.
- Yes, they do.
Why do you keep making hearts?
Why are you two sitting together?
- Because we're a team.
- We're on the same team.
I'm not kidding when I say this.
- I'm actually very serious.
- About what?
- Okay. Tell us.
- What is it?
I don't approve
of colleagues dating.
What about you?
You married Na Kyung Eun.
That's right. He did.
- Hey!
- How could he say that about her?
- That's right.
How dare you shake up
my family that's doing well?
- How dare you shake up my family?
- I'm really sorry.
- He dated someone at the workplace.
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
- Let's get going.
- Ji Hee.
- Yes?
How many siblings do you have?
- I'm an only child.
- Oh, you are?
- I guessed correctly.
- It's nice to be an only child.
How did you know?
- I had a feeling.
- You speak like you did as a child.
- Oh, really?
- She still has it.
Your blood type is O, right?
- No, it's AB.
- Okay. It's AB, right?
Your blood type is AB? That's nice.
Your blood type is AB too?
Arin, your blood type is B, right?
- No, it's O.
- I see.
- SAN, yours is B, right?
- His is A.
- Mine is B.
- All right.
- Mine is B too.
- Me too.
Your MBTI is ENFP, right?
No, it's INFP.
Oh, yours starts with an I?
- Mine is ENFP.
- Is it?
What does it mean?
What's an I and an E?
- I is introverted,
- Introverts...
- and E is extroverted.
- and extroverts.
Oh, is that so? I is for introverts?
- Yes.
- What's yours, Ji Hee?
- Guess what mine is.
- Ji Hee is...
- Hers is I.
- That's right.
- Hers starts with an I.
- Ji Hee's starts with an I.
Mine starts an I.
What's the difference
between an I and an E?
I is...
- What's the difference?
- I just asked that.
- What does an I stand for?
- Introverts.
- What about an E?
- Extroverts.
- What about an I?
- Introverts!
(Introverts!)
Why did you all snap at him?
How many times
do we have to tell him?
- You didn't test yours, right?
- No.
I don't think so. Did I?
I did mine too,
but I can't remember it.
- Jong Kook, yours is INFJ.
- Maybe mine is the same as yours.
- What?
- Yours is INFJ.
Ji Hyo remembers it.
It's because mine is the same
as yours.
No, Jong Kook's starts with a D.
- What does it stand for?
- Protein man.
(Protein man)
No, it starts with an F.
- Protein man.
- That starts with a P.
- Doesn't it start with a P?
- It's not an F.
(He was too confident when he said
protein starts with an F.)
- Protein man.
- That starts with a P.
(Doesn't protein start with a P?)
My gosh.
- Are you kidding me?
- Hey.
- Are you serious?
- Then is it "frotein"?
My gosh.
How can you be so ignorant?
Protein starts with a P.
How could you say it starts...
- with an F?
- Doesn't protein start with a P?
Don't Koreans start it with an F?
Here he goes again.
Hey, Michael Jackson.
- Hey, Jackson.
- It starts with a P.
- P?
- Aren't you hungry, Michael?
I'm hungry.
- You're hungry?
- Okay.
What is this again?
Oh, no. We'll have to
use our bodies.
- We'll have to use our bodies.
- Oh, no.
We'll now select your teams
for your next mission.
Okay.
The first team
is Se Chan, SAN, and So Min.
The second team is Haha,
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, and Arin.
The third team
is Jong Kook, Jae Suk, and Ji Hee.
(Team Green: Se Chan, So Min, SAN)
(Team Blue: Suk Jin, Ji Hyo,
Haha, Arin)
(Team Yellow: Jae Suk,
Jong Kook, Ji Hee)
Before the final mission,
you'll play a pre-mission
to acquire additional ballots.
- What is it?
- It's recommended by Haha.
It's called Balloon World Cup.
This one is really fun.
Haha recommended it,
- saying it's really fun.
- It's really fun.
How do you play it?
- What's this game?
- You'll see.
(Actual message exchange with Haha)
It's fun.
(They don't even play this
on "How Do You Play?".)
Two players from each team
will play against the other team.
You'll hold each other's hands
as you play the game.
Within the given three minutes,
each team will take turns
to hit the balloon...
and keep it afloat.
And you'll take turns
to hit the balloon.
The team
that drops the balloon loses.
You can't hit the balloon
toward the ground.
- You must...
- Hit it upward.
You must hit it
so that it stays afloat.
- I can lightly tap it, right?
- Yes, you can do that.
You can make it difficult
for the other team to hit it.
This is a pre-mission...
that has additional ballots
at stake,
so it's better for Nostra and Damus
to win as well.
- Is that so?
- Let's go. Let's play this!
- Let's win!
- Please decide who will go first.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook, why don't you...
- Yes?
You should play with Ji Hee.
- Shall we?
- I'll do my best.
Let's do it.
We must win our first round,
so shall I play with SAN?
Wouldn't that be better?
Do you want to play with SAN?
(Staring)
What? I'll let you play with SAN.
Se Chan keeps telling me...
to play with SAN
when he doesn't even mean it.
- Stop it.
- Why are you doing this?
You can play with SAN.
Why don't you
play rock-paper-scissors?
(Why don't you
play rock-paper-scissors?)
All right.
Team Yellow will go first.
Okay. Ji Hee
and Jong Kook, go ahead.
I'll play with Suk Jin.
All right. The rest of you,
- please step out of the ring.
- You must win this time.
If the balloon goes that way,
you should hit it.
I think it'll be over soon.
- You won't play dirty, will you?
- Of course not.
Because that team...
Right. Jong Kook
can even carry Ji Hee and play it.
Oh, my.
All right.
- All right.
- They look relaxed.
- What was that?
- Ji Hee, you shouldn't touch it.
(They touched the balloon twice.)
- What was that?
- Ji Hee, you shouldn't touch it.
- Ji Hee touched it again.
- We came this way.
They touched it twice.
- Come on, Jong Kook.
- Were you startled?
- We won.
- She touched it.
- We won, right?
- It's okay!
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay. Let's play.
It falls faster than you think.
- That's it.
- Hit it!
(Falling)
(The old man jumped a bit too late.)
All right.
Didn't he hit it to the ground?
No, I hit it sideways.
- He hit it horizontally.
- Oh, horizontally?
He listens to the PD well.
(He listens to the PD well.)
- He could've complained more.
- That's right.
- It's okay.
- But he went,
"Oh, horizontally?"
He's amazing.
(In the meantime, the game resumes.)
That's so sly of you.
- That's so sly of you.
- Come on.
- That was great.
- Good save.
- He saved it.
- Run!
(He loses his temper
when he's blocked by Jong Kook.)
What was that?
- Hey!
- "Move."
- What was that?
- Move when I hit you.
I was just standing still.
- Jong Kook...
- You should've moved.
- I even got hit.
- You should've let him hit it.
- Ji Hee.
- Okay, we lost.
- We lost.
- Why aren't you playing?
- I've been working really hard.
- She will hit it.
"Why aren't you playing?"
I was really quick.
- Were you?
- Yes.
- Why don't you start the game?
- Shall I?
Hit it.
That's not Geum Bo Ra, is it?
Is that Geum Bo Ra?
(No wonder
her hairstyle looked familiar.)
- She does look like her.
- I see it.
- I see Geum Bo Ra in her.
- No.
- Just a bit.
- I'm Song Ji Hyo.
- Here we go.
(Team Yellow 2, Team Blue 1)
- There you go.
- That's it.
I'll hit it.
Hey. He hit it toward the ground.
(Throwing)
(He hit it toward the ground.)
- He hit it toward the ground.
- Did I?
- I guess my hand slipped.
- He hit it toward the ground.
I couldn't see.
- Hit it upward.
- Got it.
- Upward.
- I'll throw it.
Okay. Are you throwing it
to the back?
- Got it.
- There you go.
It's okay. I got it.
- That's it.
- That was so cool.
That was so cool.
- Suk Jin!
Move!
(Mr. Move appears again.)
- He pushed Ji Hee.
- "Move."
"Move."
(Mr. Move was blinded by winning.)
(They ended up colliding
with each other.)
Hold on. Are you okay?
- How could you push her?
- Why did you push her?
- What was that?
- How could you push Ji Hee?
You threw her.
How could you do that to her?
- I'm sorry.
- What was that?
- How could you push her?
- I was only playing hard.
- Are you okay?
- I didn't mean it.
- Suk Jin is ruthless.
- I'm okay.
- Are you?
- I'm sorry.
I was playing too hard.
You should take it easy.
How could you push her like that?
I can't take it easy.
I should work hard.
I know that you should, but...
He threw her to the ground.
- Do you want a beating?
- What?
Do you want a beating?
- Do you want a piece of me?
- He's scary.
Gosh, what a Bbangkku Ttongkku.
Suk Jin's team is leading.
- We're winning?
- They're winning?
- Jong Kook, we can't lose.
- Aren't we winning?
Mister, you're too much.
- Let's play.
- I'm sorry.
Okay. Let's play.
I should hit it upward, right?
There. I hit it.
(Surprisingly, he actually hit it.)
I hit it.
- We won!
- Play it like a big guy.
- I hit it.
- That was so sneaky of you.
- Yes!
- I hit it.
- He's so sneaky.
That's so sly of him.
- You have 20 seconds.
- Okay.
Let's play.
Suk Jin is good at this.
He's pretty good.
(Suk Jin finally found a game
he's good at.)
- Good.
- There you go.
- Nice one.
- Hit it!
Hit it!
- Nice one.
- Hit it!
- That was a good one.
(Ji Hyo scores with the last touch.)
It's okay.
Game over.
- Is it over?
- Yes, it's over.
- It's over?
- He's really good.
Good job.
You're really good.
- That was close.
- We're pretty good.
Round 1 is over.
Let's move on to Round 2.
- Are you right-handed?
- It's SAN and So Min.
Who is Jae Suk playing with?
I'll play with Jong Kook.
All right!
- That's too harsh.
- Let's crush them!
- Let's go.
- Good luck!
- That's too harsh.
- Let's finish them.
- Let's destroy them!
- Okay!
Hold on. I think you should
give SAN some bullets to bite.
He should get some bullets.
- Okay?
- I think we have a chance.
(SAN became the star
of a thriller again.)
- All right. Let's go.
- I'll start.
Take it easy.
All right.
That was good.
- You're relaxed.
- We got this.
There you go.
(Sliding)
(A cool guy who doesn't back down
by a sneaky attack)
(It's time for the cool guy
of the old days to receive it.)
- Take it easy.
- Are you okay?
- All right!
- Yes!
- Okay. That was great.
- Okay!
They're so sneaky.
All right. Here we go.
- All right.
- All right. Here we go.
They're so sneaky.
Wait for it.
- They're both good.
- Take it easy.
- Wait until it falls. No.
- Hit it when it falls.
Like him. Hit it when it falls.
- Hit it when it falls. Wait for it.
- Here we go.
No, hit it lightly when it falls.
Gosh, seriously.
(Tap)
- Gosh, seriously.
- That was...
Play it like a big guy.
(They're okay with anything
as long as they win.)
That was...
- All right! That was great.
- All right!
- SAN.
- You're so sneaky!
- Okay!
You're so cool!
- Let's play.
- What's so cool about them?
- This is wrong.
- Seriously.
That's not cool.
Those who play dirty
have an advantage.
It's a battle to see
who plays dirtier.
Here we go.
They can't even use a VAR.
Isn't that too low?
You can't sit from the beginning.
- Wait for it.
- Yes, we should hit it!
Wait for it.
- Go for it. Get your hand ready.
- Touch it.
(Team Green attacks boldly
when the other team is being sly.)
- He saved it.
- So Min, get ready.
So Min, get your hand ready.
So Min, your hand.
That was too high.
Hit it to that side.
- Go for it!
- We got it.
- All right! Nice.
- He hit it toward the ground.
- No, I didn't.
(VAR verifying)
- He hit it toward the ground.
- No, I didn't.
- He didn't hit it to the ground.
- He did.
- He hit it toward the ground.
- The angle was toward the ground.
- It went below their legs.
- Check the angle.
They said he hit it downward.
- He hit it downward.
- Okay.
- It fell to the ground.
- That's right.
What was that?
- All right.
- That was sly.
All right. Let's play.
If they play slyly,
put your hand under the balloon.
- How?
- I was talking to them.
Not you.
- Which team is he on?
- You shouldn't give them tips.
Put your hand under the balloon
when they play slyly.
- Okay.
- Try putting it.
- Here we go.
- I'm sorry,
but you look intimidated.
Wait for it.
(Hitting both their faces)
It was a rebound. All right!
- Hey, you shouldn't have.
- How sneaky of you.
- That was so sneaky.
- Okay!
- All right.
- They're Jiring at you.
- Come on.
- Come on, seriously.
- Is it your turn?
- That was so sneaky.
(Jong Kook finds teasing So Min
most fun.)
You never go easy...
- on So Min.
- I never do.
Of course not.
- Let's go!
- Go!
- Are you that desperate to win?
- That's a good one.
- That's good. It's a no-look...
- What is that?
- It's a no-look throw.
- Wait a minute.
A no-look throw. Good one.
Wait for it. There you go.
- Okay.
- Wait for it.
(Getting dragged)
(Jong Kook drags his teammate
who is out of it.)
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Nice!
(The sly players lose a point.)
You should've followed me!
Why did you just lie there?
- You should've followed me!
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
- I think it's our turn.
- Pull yourself together.
- Follow me!
- Okay. Let's play.
Let's play. Okay, I'll hit it.
- That's it.
- Can I hit it?
Go ahead.
(So Min announces her attack
as though she's determined.)
- What? What is it?
- What?
- Okay.
- Let's play.
You should receive it well
when it rebounds.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
(The tiger moth
is ready on standby.)
Oh, gosh.
- Get ready.
- Oh, gosh.
Hey, that was...
(The tiger moth succeeds
in getting her revenge.)
She hit it toward the ground.
- No, she hit it upward.
- No, it went upward.
- She hit it upward.
But Jae Suk's protruding mouth
hit it.
She hit it upward.
Are you going to keep this up?
- Okay, fine.
- She's going to keep this up.
- So Min, keep playing.
- Fine.
- Go for it.
- Go, So Min.
- You should hit it.
- So Min.
SAN.
- I should stay away from it.
- Keep your face lifted, will you?
- SAN.
- So that it won't fall.
I should stay away from it.
I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- Go for it.
Come closer. You should come closer.
There you go. Come closer.
Hey.
- Okay!
- Hit it.
- Good!
- Nice one!
- They let go of their hands.
(Jae Suk let go
of Jong Kook's hand.)
They let go of their hands.
Jae Suk let go of his hand.
- Team Yellow loses a point.
- Okay!
You should've gotten up
and held my hand.
You let go of my hand!
Game over.
- Is it over?
- Oh, gosh.
- We won.
- I bet we won.
Let's move on to the last round.
Wait for it. You got it.
It's out.
Wait for it. There you go. Nice!
Team Green takes first place
for winning twice in a row.
- Yes!
- They won?
- We're in the first place?
- Yes.
We'll give you additional ballots
to the three of you.
- All right.
- It was fun.
- But you were really cool.
- I can't believe they won.
- Good job.
- That was close.
- You were good.
- We beat Jong Kook.
We beat Jong Kook.
- Jae Suk got hit in the face.
- Good job.
Ms. Geum Bo Ra was really good too.
Ms. Geum Bo Ra?
- Let me see.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- I see it.
- She's really beautiful too.
All right. We'll now play
the final mission.
The final mission is called
Millennium Joys and Sorrows.
A total of 6 players,
2 from each team, will play.
You'll get on top
of the slippery slope behind you.
Then stick your name tag
on the spot on top of the slope.
- It's pretty simple.
- We just have to go up.
The team that sticks
all of their name tags first wins.
The team that comes in second...
will win if they get just one of
their name tags up there.
All right. Decide who will go first.
Two for Round One
and two for Round Two.
Jong Kook and Ji Hee will go first,
then Ji Hee and I will go next.
Okay, let's do that.
- SAN and I will play.
- And then?
Then...
(Studying their faces)
Then So Min and I will go second.
Why would you play twice?
Wouldn't it be better
for SAN to play one more time?
- It's okay.
- What?
- Should we do that?
- Why would you play twice?
- Then SAN will go.
- Yes, let SAN play.
- It'd be better for him to go.
- Damus.
- Is it because you're Damus?
- No, I'm not!
You're Damus.
SAN can go twice.
- That'd be better.
- I'll show you that I'm not Damus.
- You must win.
- I know.
Suk Jin and I will go.
- Why?
- Why not?
- Are you Nostra?
- Are you Damus?
- Does he have to win or lose?
- He has to lose.
- He should lose.
- Oh, is that why?
- No, not at all.
He might push me down
when I try to climb up.
I'm really not Nostra or Damus.
- What's wrong with you?
- Of course.
Let's predict the ranking
one last time.
Thank you, Ji Hee.
(Nostra and Damus will predict
each team's ranking.)
Haha, I'll win first place.
- Sorry?
- I'll win first place.
If I think you'll win first place,
I should put down the blindfold...
- and do this?
- That's right.
He's given up.
- No, one of them is a prophet.
- We're just joking around.
All right. Nostra and Damus,
put down your blindfold.
Predict the ranking.
(Nostra and Damus are predicting
the ranking for the last mission.)
(They're done
with their prediction.)
Let's start Round One.
Take off your blindfold.
(Ji Hyo looks at Suk Jin
as though she finds him suspicious.)
What is it?
I kept hearing you move about
next to me.
- I know.
- I just scratched myself.
I heard someone rustling.
I heard it too.
I scratched myself to be suspected.
- Right.
- I did it to be suspected.
Anyway, Suk Jin
smelled sour earlier.
- He's definitely not it.
- I'm really not it either.
- I scratched to be suspected.
- You are...
- They wrote our names?
- so weak-hearted.
I kept hearing sounds from his side.
I know. Something was rustling.
- I'll do it.
- Isn't it Ji Hee?
Arin.
Why does no one suspect Arin?
Because no one can.
Six players for Round One,
please gather here.
- We won't fall.
- I'm so nervous.
You can do it!
Se Chan, do you want me to go first?
- My gosh.
- Let's go!
Jong Kook, this is slippery.
Of course, it is.
How are we supposed to go up?
- It's so scary.
- Ji Hee.
You should just sprint up there.
- Everyone.
- We can't hold on to these, right?
You can't, but if you find it
too difficult, I'll allow it.
- Do you see towels in the middle?
- How are we supposed to go up?
You can make use of the towel.
- Which one?
- Make use of what?
- The towels.
- Oh, we can wipe as we go up?
You want us to
make use of the towels?
The team that sticks
two name tags first will win.
- Ours or other teams'?
- Your own.
You and I should take
each other's name tags off.
We're supposed to remove ours
and stick it up there, right?
Ji Hyo, Arin.
- Get ready.
- Let's do this.
You can do it!
Get set.
- Okay.
- Go!
- They can't go up.
- We can't go up.
Don't hold on to the rails.
(Exclaiming)
Gosh, this is... Hold on.
- They can't even stand on it.
- This is...
This is impossible.
You can't even do a run-up.
You should run up from there.
(Shouting)
This game is fair for everyone.
- It's impossible.
- It's really fair.
This is...
(Running)
(A gym-goer suddenly
runs on a treadmill.)
- Hold on. We should make a path.
- Hey.
No matter how hard I run,
I can't go up.
- Shall we go up together?
- Sure.
Hold on.
Push her.
- Push her and support her.
- Let's go!
How are we supposed to go up?
Let's start from there.
- Let's run from here.
- Let's run up.
- Over here. Hold on to it.
- One,
- two...
- Ji Hee. There you go.
- Ji Hee...
- Go!
- Look at them.
- Let's go!
- Go!
- It's working.
- He's going up.
This is impossible.
Let's try one more time.
(Right then, Ji Hee hangs on to
the plastic and climbs up.)
- That's great, Ji Hee!
- She's going up.
She's going up.
- It's working.
- There you go!
Good job, Ji Hee! Keep going.
I can't do it!
(Screaming)
Keep going!
(Collecting Ji Hee)
No. Ji Hee, I got it.
Come on. We can do it.
It's so slippery.
(Mr. Gym gives it a try
instead of Ji Hee who failed.)
Ji Hee, let's do this. No.
Hold on to me. Who are you?
Ji Hee.
(Arin is hanging on to
the member of another team.)
You should go up now.
Ji Hee.
(The game is getting dirty.)
Ji Hee!
(Right then)
Look at SAN.
(The cool guy SAN
faces the slope head on.)
(Impressed)
- SAN.
- He made it.
He failed.
SAN is pretty good.
- Ji Hee!
- Hold on.
- Ji Hee, grab me and get up there.
- Ji Hee.
- Hurry up!
You should hang on to me.
- I think we can just run up.
- Ji Hee.
Ji Hee, hold on to him
and climb up the slope.
- Hold on to me.
- There you go.
- That's it!
- Jong Kook!
- Ji Hee.
Someone is pulling me from behind.
You're almost there, Ji Hee.
(It's a mess.)
It's slippery.
(He ends up demonstrating
a feat of super strength.)
What's he doing?
(He's 1st to reach the base camp.)
Get up here.
Try to get up there.
- What is my team doing?
- My goodness.
- We can never get up there.
- Everyone.
You're allowed to hold the bar
on each side.
(They're allowed to hold the bar
on each side.)
We're allowed to hold onto this?
SAN. Why do you hold it like that?
(He didn't get far for showing off.)
We're allowed to hold onto this?
This?
This? Come on.
This is slippery.
This is worse.
- This isn't working.
- Se Chan.
- I can't go up. What do I do?
- I can't do it.
(He's falling.)
Yes!
(My goodness.)
My goodness.
Yes! Get down even more.
That was close.
He did it.
(SAN succeeded in
hanging in the middle.)
He got it.
SAN...
(Jong Kook gets rid of SAN
with a petty gesture.)
Jong Kook!
(Laughing)
SAN.
What am I supposed to do?
This is almost impossible.
This is getting slipperier.
(Ji Hee goes up slowly.)
- He did it.
- There's nothing to hold.
- Push her.
- Hold onto her.
- Grab Ji Hee.
(Everyone from Team Yellow
reaches the 2nd floor.)
- She got it.
- Come on, Ji Hee.
Good job. That was good.
We got it.
- I should've eaten more.
- I'm stuck here.
- This is so hard.
- They keep going up.
- Ji Hyo. Come here for a second.
- We have to stop them.
This is funny.
(Panting)
- Push SAN.
- Keep going up, SAN.
Please.
- He's strong.
- Right?
- He's young.
- He's jumping around...
- all day long.
- SAN. Hold onto me.
By the way, why did you...
only send Arin and Ji Hyo?
- Why?
- I know.
One of you should be there.
I know. It should've been one of us.
Please.
Please!
- Arin made it.
- That's crazy.
Arin made it, Jong Kook.
(Arin and Ji Hyo made it
to the 2nd floor.)
SAN. Come here.
Gosh.
(Jong Kook reaches the peak first.)
Jong Kook made it.
Okay!
It's impossible.
Ms. Geum.
Stop Jin Ji Hee.
Ji Hyo.
How will I get up there?
You're pulling me from both sides.
- Send her down.
- You're still okay.
- Rip her name tag.
- Arin.
(Ji Hee's name tag goes down.)
Oh, that's a good idea. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Do the same on her.
Send Ji Hee down.
Hey!
Jong Kook.
Yes. You got it.
Yes. That's what you need to do.
- He made it in the end.
- SAN.
- What about me?
- He made it.
- SAN.
- He leaps.
- He leaps so much.
- Like a frog.
Throw it. That's right.
It's okay. It's your turn to go up.
Please.
- No. Don't.
- Se Chan. What are you doing?
Se Chan. What are you doing?
He's like Captain Um Hong Gil.
- Captain Um.
(He tries to go up while panting.)
- You must hold onto it.
- Hey.
It's amazing.
Captain Um's partner is SAN.
SAN. Wait for me.
If you don't make it in a minute,
the rank is determined.
Yes. I dare you to come.
- I'll block them.
- Yes.
The team with more people
in the middle place second.
- No.
- SAN. Take this.
Hurry up.
- You have 40 seconds left.
- SAN.
Hold this please.
- No.
- Hold it please.
- Good.
(What will happen to Team Green?)
He got it. My goodness.
(He fails to climb up.)
First place goes
to Jong Kook's team.
Okay. It's over.
Second place goes to Ji Hyo's team.
Third place goes to Se Chan's team.
Well done.
Did Se Chan try hard?
I think he didn't go up on purpose.
Suk Jin. I tried
until the mic broke.
- It's Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
- Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Good luck.
Jong Kook. Let's finish it at once.
Get ready, set, go.
- What was that?
- Hurry.
Hurry up.
- Yes. You got it.
- Hold onto it.
- Oh, that was good.
- Watch carefully.
- It's slippery.
- Now, now.
(Falling)
- So Min.
- What's wrong with you?
What's wrong, So Min?
Gosh.
- Hey.
- How do I get up there?
Hey.
(Many famous dirty players joined
this round.)
- It doesn't work at all.
- So Min.
(A collision occurs.)
- Hey. Be careful.
- So Min.
- Why did you go in there?
- You can't do that, So Min.
- So Min.
So Min.
You're not allowed to do that.
(No one plays fair as expected.)
It's so funny.
How do I do it? Wait.
I can't go up at all.
What should I do?
- I can't hold on to it.
- It's slippery.
- Now.
- Go up at once.
- Do you want me to push you?
- Hey. Look at him.
SAN. Stop Jae Suk.
Stop him.
- Both of them are going up.
- Good job.
You're doing great.
Gosh.
(Jong Kook reaches
the 2nd floor first.)
Jong Kook.
- Help me.
- You got it.
- Jae Suk.
- Help me.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
Hurry up.
It's all thanks to you.
(Jae Suk makes it
thanks to Jong Kook.)
(Grunting)
Wait.
(Jae Suk pushes Suk Jin
who struggled to go up.)
Are you alone?
I almost had it.
- He made it again.
- How did you do it?
- How does he do that?
- My gosh.
(Jong Kook is 1st
to reach the top again.)
I did it.
How do you get up there?
Hey. I can't lose like this.
What is this?
Haha.
You said that was not
how I should play.
Grab my leg.
My team reached the top.
- We got it.
- My goodness.
- We did it.
- We got it.
- It's over.
- We did it.
- How did they do that?
- Get down here.
- Okay!
- How did they do it?
We don't have a second place yet.
- We don't have a second place yet.
- We did it.
- How did you do it?
- How do I do it?
- I can't get any higher.
- It's so hard.
- Suk Jin. You're good.
- My goodness.
- Hold me.
How do you go up?
(Grunting)
(The steep slope makes them grunt.)
How do I get up there?
Are they drunk by any chance?
They look like they're crawling home
after drinking.
Excuse me. You drank too much.
Wait.
- How did they do that?
- Get down here.
How did you do that?
Hey!
How did you get up there?
How did that old man get up there?
(They're amazed
by how hale Suk Jin is.)
I can't do it at all.
Here.
(Then the old hiker sends
a rope down.)
Here. Reach it.
(Then the old hiker sends
a rope down.)
Grab it please.
I'm holding back with my jaw.
(I can reach it.)
- We're in first place anyway.
- Here.
(1st place hikers are watching.)
I'm holding back with my jaw.
(Twitching)
Oh, I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
Oh, I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- I slipped.
- My goodness.
I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk slides
and kicks Suk Jin.)
- I'm sorry. I slipped.
- Suk Jin.
- My goodness.
- I slipped.
- Come back up.
- Hey!
- I slipped.
I slipped. I'm serious.
- I'm sorry.
- Suk Jin.
I slipped.
I slipped. I'm done anyway.
Good job.
It was so hard to get up there.
- No.
- I slipped.
I'm really sorry.
- Gosh.
- Yes. Jae Suk looks sorry.
It was so hard to get up there.
- Yoo Jae Suk. Seriously.
- I mean it.
- It was a mistake.
- I have no energy left.
- I slipped.
He's right.
What are you doing?
Are you a worm or what?
I want to move, but I can't.
- You have a minute.
- It was so hard to get up there.
The person who makes it
to the second floor places second.
You have to get up there first.
Haha. The person who reaches it
places second.
No! Haha!
- Get there first.
- Just a bit more.
- He did it.
- He got it.
We're last.
My.
Go away, you punk.
(Go away, you punk.)
- SAN. Push him.
- It was so hard to get here.
Wait.
- Give it to So Min.
- So Min is doing it.
- So Min's coming.
- She's so cool.
The old man is coming.
Look at the old man.
The old man is coming to catch her.
(The old hiker hasn't given up yet.)
- So Min.
- Look behind you.
There's an old man behind you.
So Min. Look at the old man.
Help her, SAN.
Hold her hand. That's right.
(Everyone from Team Green
makes it to the 2nd floor.)
Yoo Jae Suk. That punk.
I'm going to kill him.
(I'm going to kill him.)
Sorry, Suk Jin.
(The game ends.)
Okay.
Second place goes to SAN,
So Min, and Se Chan.
(Team Green places 2nd.
Team Blue places 3rd.)
You predicted us placing the bottom.
Haha.
(Did Haha not go up on purpose
to place 3rd?)
That's funny.
I'm so tired.
So, all the missions with 99 kids
are over.
- Okay.
- We have to catch them.
The 21st century is about to come.
- First place goes to them.
- Yes.
Second place goes to the team
that sent more people up.
Third place goes to Team Blue.
- Yes.
Nostra and Damus...
(Did Nostra and Damus succeed
to predict the result?)
failed to predict the result.
(They both failed.)
Right. He tried to place second,
but he couldn't.
- They failed.
- He placed third.
You're totally wrong.
Now,
we'll have a vote
to arrest Nostra and Damus.
Each of you...
will tell the producer over there.
- Okay.
They have an extra vote
from earlier.
That means you can pick two people.
And...
you can buy an extra vote...
with your own money if you want.
If we buy it,
we can't take money home.
That's right. You can use
your prize money to buy the vote.
That's up to you.
But you never know...
if Nostra and Damus buy
a lot of votes.
Oh, that's right.
They could buy the votes.
- They might vote for someone else.
- That's right.
You probably know by now.
"Kim Jong Kook Game" begins.
Let's listen to him.
No, I won't say anything today.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm sure you're all thinking
the same, so I won't say anything.
Se Chan.
Why don't you say something?
- Everyone is suspecting you.
- Yes.
I know everyone is suspecting me.
Everyone suspected me
when I was with Suk Jin.
So I have no choice
but to point at Suk Jin.
But Jong Kook is driving it on me.
So I have nothing to say
even though I know the truth.
If it's not me, who else?
How come it's not her or him?
(Ji Hee and SAN)
- I've tried so hard.
- So...
we think it's not them
based on the situation.
It's not me, but I'm thinking
what if it's not him.
- It's not me.
- You've become kind, Suk Jin.
- I think it's Suk Jin.
- It's Ji Hee.
But he did so well.
It's not me.
Ji Hee is suspicious.
Ji Hee and I were on the list.
- Yes.
- You were on the list.
I don't think Ji Hee is Damus.
(Haha and Ji Hee)
Then she's Nostra.
(Then she's Nostra.)
- Me?
- You can't say it's not possible.
There is a possibility.
Why are you driving it on me?
Because it's not me.
- It's between you and me.
- It's not me.
It's really not me.
You kept holding onto it
and didn't go up.
I have no idea.
Please vote.
How much do I have?
- You currently have 410 dollars.
- I see.
You have 1 vote,
and you can buy up to 4 votes.
I'll use it all.
Two on Haha and three on Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Yes.
One for Haha and...
- Ji Hee.
- Okay.
I...
vote for Haha...
- and Haha.
- Okay.
How's the voting going?
(It's Haha's turn to vote.)
You can buy up to five votes.
I can buy up to five votes?
You have 510 dollars.
Can you tell me...
- how the voting is going?
- Haha.
- Really?
- Are you asking him for advice?
(Are you asking him for advice?)
Are you asking him for advice?
(He looks small today.)
- Stop it.
- "Stop it".
(Haha is asking for advice
because...)
You are new prophets...
who will predict the end
and shake Running Man today.
You are Nostra and Damus.
You'll now predict the ranking.
(Then he began predicting
the ranking.)
(Nostra Haha carefully...)
(predicted the ranking.)
Haha, Jae Suk, and Ji Hee.
(Haha predicted
his own team last...)
(and Jong Kook's team 1st.)
(Nostra carries out his plan
to make his prophecy real.)
- I'll protect it at first.
- Okay.
(He said he'd protect
the headquarter,)
(but he went to have fun.)
It's not working.
(So,)
(Nostra's prophecy came true.)
(Nostra took a risk
to make his prophecy come true.)
(He won 460 dollars in secret.)
(He struggled in the last mission.)
(Haha was Nostra.)
(Nostra is bitten by vipers
and asks for advice.)
Nostra.
Hey, Nostra. Stop it.
Nostra
Oh, my love Nostra
(A song for Nostra who went through
a lot today because of Jong Kook)
(Haha never gives up...)
(and votes carefully.)
You have 200 dollars.
I'll buy votes with all I have.
You can buy two.
- Yes. I get four in total.
- Four.
Who do you vote for?
(Everyone votes for the person
they suspect.)
Okay.
(Will they be able to arrest
Nostra and Damus?)
Everyone. I have the result.
You do?
I'll announce two people
who received most votes.
We'll decide the penalty,
then tell you who they are.
I'll first announce the person
who received the most votes.
- He received 13 votes.
- Received 13?
(Did Haha receive the most votes?)
(Or is it Se Chan who Detective Kim
suspected from the beginning?)
(Or could it be Suk Jin or Ji Hee?)
(Who will become
the final candidate?)
- It's Suk Jin.
- What?
(Suk Jin)
What?
Me?
(It was neither of them,)
(but Suk Jin.)
They both voted for him.
I'm telling you it's him.
- I think they both voted for him.
- They must've bought the votes.
The other person is...
(Who else received the most votes?)
It was one vote difference.
- Haha.
- It's Haha.
(Haha received 9 votes.)
- But...
- How many votes did Se Chan get?
He received eight votes.
I'm telling you it's not me.
But he's...
I think he's Damus.
(Nostra Haha is already arrested.)
(Then who's Damus?)
Let's decide the penalty first.
Who receives the penalty?
You two. It's been determined.
It's been determined.
It's over.
- I'm sorry.
- Whether it's you or not.
- Whether it's me or not?
- I'm sorry.
- And you get no prize money.
- For the penalty,
slide down here.
Forward, backward, and sideways.
That's funny.
- My goodness.
- That's hilarious.
Hey. I can't believe you.
You voted me for Nostra and Damus?
- They both voted for me.
- All right.
I'll reveal who Nostra is.
- We did it.
- You're with me.
Nostra is...
(Nostra is...)
- It's Haha.
- I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
I knew he was Nostra.
(Throwing)
(He was caught by Detective Kim
and couldn't avoid suspicion.)
He's obvious.
I can tell by looking at his face.
He's in trouble.
Now, there's Damus left.
- Damus.
- Damus is Suk Jin.
First, Suk Jin...
is...
(Suk Jin became the candidate
at the end.)
(1st prediction time)
(Suk Jin became suspicious
due to his cologne.)
(Suk Jin might forget
that he's Damus.)
(People kept suspecting Suk Jin
even in the car.)
(2nd prediction time)
(People suspected Suk Jin even more
due to the sound he made.)
(Is Suk Jin Damus?)
Is he just a resident of Seocho-gu
or what?
He's a loach of Jamwon-dong.
- Hugh Grant.
- The loach of Jamwon-dong.
(Or is he just a loach
of Jamwon-dong?)
(Is Suk Jin Damus?)
- He is not Damus.
- I knew it.
- Obviously not.
- Damus is...
(Suk Jin is not Damus.)
- Obviously not.
- Damus is...
(Damus is...)
Se Chan.
- See?
- I knew it.
(Se Chan survived dramatically
at the end.)
Shut It Damus.
You are Nostra and Damus.
- Who's Damus? Me?
- Shut It Damus.
I'm Damus obviously.
- I'm Damus.
- Yes.
(Damus Se Chan felt confident.)
(But he got bitten by the viper
in the opening.)
(In the end)
(Shut It Damus focused
on avoiding suspicion.)
(Then...)
(he kept talking
about how hard he tried.)
(He made the innocent guests
believe him like that.)
(Then he accused Suk Jin
of being the prophet.)
(That's how the naive 99 kids...)
(voted for Suk Jin.)
(Shut It Damus spent all his money
to vote for Suk Jin.)
It was Yang Se Chan.
- I knew it.
- See? I told you.
- It was so obvious.
- My gosh.
I told you the answer
from the beginning.
- I said it was Se Chan.
- At the beginning...
- Seriously?
- I had no idea.
- Did you two plan it together?
- It was Se Chan.
- I hate this.
- It was hard at the beginning.
As soon as we began the mission,
Se Chan was like this.
(He acted awkwardly.)
He was like this,
so I caught him right away.
I didn't do anything.
- It was...
- It wasn't usual.
It was like...
he was doing things...
- by instinct.
- He's so good at this.
So the citizens will get
their prize money.
- To be honest...
- This is funny.
If Jong Kook behaves like that
when I'm a spy,
I'll want to go straight home.
- Jae Suk.
- It's torturous.
- I can't even eat.
- Ji Hee gets 95 dollars.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
SAN.
- You get 175 dollars.
- That's a lot.
(150 for Jae Suk, 100 for So Min,
5 dollars for Ji Hyo and Jong Kook)
And Arin gets no money.
- No money?
- She spent all her money.
I just did it because of you.
So we will wire the prize money.
You two should go up then.
(The penalty decided by the members
is going down the soapy slide.)
It's so slippery.
(They chose a penalty that is
more bothersome and humiliating.)
Here comes the soapy water.
(They enjoy the penalty
splashing soapy water.)
Okay.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
(We'd like to thank the 99 kids
for saving the world.)
- Haha is it.
- This is funny.
(Se Chan's birthday party)
(Se Chan is here to be a good son
with a fancy birthday party.)
(And the variety parents are
waiting for Se Chan.)
(Thank you, Mother and Father.)
(A thick bundle of money)
(Here.)
(He treats his variety show parents
with good money.)
(He dreams of a perfect
variety show family like that.)
(I guess I've spoiled him.)
(He hit you as if you were
his parents' enemy.)
(He gave up being a good son.)
He pretends he doesn't like me.
(The parents blinded by money
speak ill of their son...)
(and hit him.)
(Did he get his teeth straightened?)
(He will turn 60 soon.)
(You're not good at soccer.)
(Like father, like son.
The family criticizes each other.)
(Will the son's birthday party
end successfully?)
(The Variety Show Family,
Yang Se Chan the Good Son)