(A wedding hall in Seoul)
Hello.
Hello. Hi.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Why do we have three cushions?
- What are we doing today?
- What is going on?
- Why are there three cushions?
I haven't been on the same team
with So Min for quite a while.
Se Chan is not here.
It feels like I'm a big senior.
Guys, do you think Se Chan
has improved in a variety show...
compared to when
he first joined Running Man?
Se Chan? Of course, he has.
He has improved.
He was daunted at first.
So he couldn't even talk.
I know. He was too nice.
When So Min was playing
an active role, he was just quiet.
I know.
When So Min won
the Best Rookie Award... Of course,
- Se Chan congratulated her.
- Right.
But he got really drunk that day.
I felt really bad for him.
We felt bad watching him.
Right. But now, he throws
a tantrum sometimes.
I know.
I don't even remember how many
times he slapped me in the face.
He is a lot better now.
So Se Chan is not here.
But I don't think he's good
enough to be the protagonist.
He hasn't improved that much.
He's not that good.
So Min and Se Chan
joined our show together.
So Min adapted right away.
But it took Se Chan
about a year to adapt to our show.
He's on fire now.
He's a slow starter.
Se Chan needed more time to adapt...
because he's shy of strangers.
- Exactly.
- He's very shy.
Those who are shy need more time.
- Right.
- So it took me about ten years.
You?
- It took me a long time.
- You don't feel nervous anymore.
- I don't.
- It took him about ten years.
Honestly, he didn't
get adjusted at first.
Everyone needs some time to adjust.
Then I tore down the wall.
(Then I tore down the wall.)
It was like the reunification of
East Germany and West Germany.
I'm a lot older than him, so we
don't usually meet on variety shows.
But I offered my hand first.
Are you showing off
what you've done for him?
It's not like that.
I'm a lot older than him.
I made my debut way before he did.
He must've been afraid of me.
But I broke it down.
I treated him like my friend.
There was this game...
where we hit each other
with a cushion.
I tried to be considerate
playing the game.
I told Se Chan to hit me first.
(He told Se Chan
to hit him first playing the game.)
(He thinks that's how he broke down
the wall between him and Se Chan.)
(He sounds like an old fossil.)
I just told him to hit me harder.
That's how we got the great scene.
(No one remembers the great scene.)
Seriously, this is
what I can never become.
I can never become an old fossil.
So why isn't Se Chan here yet?
December 8,
which is 3 days from now...
is Se Chan's birthday.
We can't celebrate
the members' birthday every time.
So what?
So we prepared this race today.
It's called Filial Son
Yang Se Chan Race.
Filial Son Yang Se Chan Race.
Se Chan was a newborn baby
on a variety show,
and you have raised him with love
like his parents.
That's true.
When Se Chan first
joined our show, I was...
- You gave birth to him.
- Seriously,
I embraced him.
So your son, Se Chan will...
choose the parents
he wants to do his filial duty...
and visit their room.
But he can visit only one couple.
And the parents chosen by Se Chan...
will get some spending money.
It's done. Get ready.
- This is a little...
- Get ready to greet him.
- It's a done deal.
- Sure.
- This is done.
- Get ready.
- He must come to my room.
- Right.
- He knows that too.
- Sure.
I know
everyone has been nice to him.
But...
Jong Kook raised him.
- He even breastfed Se Chan.
- Sure.
- And he made baby food for him.
- I even breastfed him.
- You did.
- I know that.
- Of course.
But now he knows
what's funny on variety shows.
So I'm afraid
he might play some pranks.
- He can't do that this time.
- He can't.
- That's not right.
- This isn't the right time.
You can throw a tantrum
if he doesn't come.
He'd say, "Gosh, Jong Kook."
"Please."
- "I get it."
- "This is a variety show."
- "I know. I get it."
- "I understand."
- "I know what you mean. Okay."
- "It's fun."
- "Good."
- "Go to your dad then."
"Se Chan, you can't do this."
It feels strange today.
- This is strange.
- You're tired, aren't you?
I'm very tired.
(It is tiring just to think
of the parents' nagging.)
It's true that we've raised Se Chan.
You're like his dad.
Of course.
Son!
- I should go get him.
- Hey, stay here.
I've never fathered a punk like him.
Honey.
Hang on a moment.
"Honey?"
- You're my husband.
- Right.
He has a protruding mouth.
He takes after you.
- All right. I get it.
- He's our son.
- I know. Don't push him too hard.
- And, honey...
While raising Se Chan,
I just thought...
I'd send him
to someone else for a while.
(Flustered)
Do we really have to go that far?
Is it necessary?
Actually, there was something
going on between Se Chan and you.
Right. Actually,
I'm his variety show wife.
- What?
- On variety shows...
I'm not like his variety show mom.
I'm more like his variety show wife.
So it might be uncomfortable.
His variety show wife?
(While the variety show parents and
variety show wife are waiting...)
(A fancy banner is greeting
Se Chan downstairs.)
(The Empty Head biography
to praise him)
(Empty)
(With the grand music,)
(the star of the day shows up.)
What is going on?
(His gum has dried up from shyness.)
(There's a drum and fife band.)
Why are you doing this?
(The drum and fife band plays
instruments without touching them.)
(Playing drums in the air)
They are our production crew.
They're not playing for real.
(The fake band consists of writers,
producers, and floor directors.)
(The band is hired without pay.)
What?
Halt!
(Off the beat)
Why is the music still playing?
(The band can play
only when there's music.)
I thought you spent some money
on this, but that's not true.
Thank you anyway. What's all this?
- Blow the candle.
- Thank you.
My goodness.
Thank you.
Gosh, I'm startled.
It hurts.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
(Clashing)
(1986, The day
when Se Chan was born)
You may leave now.
(The fake band leaves.)
They don't seem sincere at all.
- On your birthday,
- Yes.
you're supposed
to thank your parents...
who gave birth to you
and have raised you.
Your variety show parents who gave
birth to you with their hearts...
and have raised you
are waiting upstairs.
My variety show parents?
You should choose one couple
who you want to do filial duty...
and visit them.
- Only one couple?
- Yes.
The first couple is
Jae Suk and So Min.
The second is Jong Kook and Haha.
And the third is
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
There are stories
behind each couple.
Should I pick only one couple?
Why? Can't I choose all of them?
This is a lot of pressure.
And Jong Kook will be mad
if I don't pick him.
(He is going to chew
on Se Chan all day.)
Gosh, I'm in trouble now.
My goodness.
This is driving me crazy.
They will be disappointed.
They feel disappointed for real.
You don't have to be so anxious.
- He'll definitely come.
- I'm not anxious.
I'm fine.
I'm not nervous at all.
You seem nervous.
- Right.
- No, I'm not.
- You might chew your nails soon.
- No.
This isn't fun. I don't know
why we are doing this.
See? You look anxious.
I understand...
that he can hesitate. He's a pro.
I understand.
- But if he doesn't come in here...
- Gosh.
That means he doesn't want
to see Jong Kook again.
It means he wants
to disown Jong Kook.
Good.
- You're good at cornering him.
- I know.
You are forcing him into a corner.
(He's a good decoy.)
I knew it.
Honey.
What's wrong with our son?
He's not even here
to see his parents.
I don't know.
(Ms. Jeon is so into her character.)
My son...
He won't be here.
Honestly, I don't
expect him to come.
He won't come here.
- You still want him to come.
- But he's not a human being...
if he doesn't come.
(The son is heading
to his particular parents groaning.)
(He's visiting his parents
with a lot of worries.)
- Son.
Son.
I'm annoyed
that we're feeling nervous.
I know.
- This is just obvious.
- Son.
Hey, Se Chan.
I'm his warm...
variety show parent.
And I'm sitting right here.
(Which parents does Se Chan
want to do his filial duty to?)
There you go.
- Come on in.
- Gosh.
(Touched)
You've raised me...
(You've raised me...)
- and guided me.
- Right.
- That's why I could come this far.
- Of course.
- You two.
- Okay.
Please blow the candle
to celebrate my birthday.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's celebrate his birthday.
- One, two, three.
Thank you...
- for having raised me.
- My gosh.
Thank you.
- How nice.
- I wasn't even worried.
- Thank you.
- My son.
Dad and Mom.
You are the parents I must visit.
I should do my filial duty.
- Of course.
- I know.
- Now...
- Thank you for having raised me.
(Disappointed)
Oh, Jong Kook...
He worked with Jong Kook.
- What?
- He chose Jong Kook and Haha.
See? I knew it.
What...
- He didn't even show his face here.
- I can't believe this.
He's unbelievable.
The thing is,
he has no understanding
of the overall rules...
and today's theme.
We have everything ready.
I know. So Min and I have
developed the situation.
And he ruined everything.
All he needed to do was
come in and play along.
- He could've at least peeped in.
- I know.
My goodness.
- Gosh.
- He's hopeless.
He hasn't changed at all
for the past five years.
- He's a hopeless case.
- Se Chan hasn't improved.
He's just...
- Jae Suk, he hasn't improved.
- That's true.
He should learn more.
If only he were
half as good as So Min.
- Darn it.
- I don't have a son.
- Let's go.
- I don't need him.
- Let's go, So Min.
- Honey, let's make one.
What?
If you didn't come...
Actually, we kind of imagined...
what it would be like.
It would've been horrible.
It was horrible.
That's what I thought
as I passed by here.
If I chose someone else,
I knew
things would've been terrible.
You've grown up very well.
Actually, you grew up yourself.
That's not true.
I could come this far
thanks to you, Mom and Dad.
Thank you.
- You look great in that hat.
- Thank you.
All right. Go ahead and make a bow.
Okay.
- Stay healthy.
- Okay.
My goodness. My son, Se Chan.
- Se Chan is...
- I'm so proud of you.
Will you cheer me up a little?
Sure. There you go.
That's my boy.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- I'm so proud of him.
- Thank you.
- He's doing well on many TV shows.
- Right.
You turned out so well.
It reminded me of the old days.
What did you think of?
The time when I was struggling.
The time when I felt lonely.
- When you first joined this show?
- Yes.
- Who did I have back then?
- Who did you have?
My gosh.
- I had Jong Kook.
- This is so touching.
- A lot of videos flashed...
- I know.
- before my eyes.
- The time in New Zealand.
(The parents' love flashed
before his eyes.)
You encouraged me and praised me.
Nevis.
- Swing!
(His variety show parents raised him
getting penalties together.)
I remember all that.
Actually, it's us
who received your help.
That's not true, Mom.
We did a lot of things together.
I didn't realize it,
but we did a lot of things together.
- Dad, thank you for everything.
- That's my son.
(Proud)
- My gosh.
- Hello.
Hello.
I mean, our son is...
- Wait.
- My son is...
- It's you.
- Who are they?
- They are our production crew.
- My gosh.
- Really? I didn't know.
- I thought they were...
actual musicians.
Hello.
Get close to each other.
(Taking a picture
to save the memory)
One, two, three.
(Staring)
Hey, are you a tour guide
or something?
(1986, The day
when Se Chan was born)
- It's nice to meet you all.
- I feel like I'm at a theme park.
- Don't you recognize them?
- They're our staff members.
- He didn't recognize them.
- Min Hee and everyone on the team.
- He greeted them like strangers.
- Suk Jin.
- Look.
They're all our staff members.
- You must be disappointed.
- What did he say earlier?
"It's nice to meet you all."
(He said hello politely
as if he had never met them before.)
- He's the worst.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
Oh, my. I thought a band came
from some kind of school.
- My gosh. Really?
- You're the worst.
Now, the star of the day Se Chan...
and his variety show parents will
come out.
- His variety show parents.
- I'm really disappointed.
- Exactly.
- This is ridiculous.
- Let's go.
- Gosh.
- Look how disappointed they are.
- I can't believe this.
- Hey, how could you?
- I had no choice.
- Nonsense.
- It was an obvious choice.
- How could you do that to me?
- Of course, he chose us.
- It was so predictable.
- Suk Jin seems so disappointed.
I had no choice.
- You know that.
- I can't believe you.
- Jae Suk, you know, right?
- But still...
Sir, you know why I did that.
- I didn't even get nervous.
- I mean...
- You all know. Don't be upset.
- When I heard about it,
- I thought it was obvious.
- Suk Jin, you know me.
- You see...
- Why are they your parents?
- Why? Tell us the reason.
- Of course...
- I practically gave birth to him.
- Of course, we're his parents.
- And I raised him too.
- Tell us the reason.
- I raised him until he was seven.
- Why?
- We fed him since he was a baby.
- Yes, we did.
I realized that I had
so many good memories with them.
- We made a lot of good memories.
- Yes.
- I'm so disappointed.
- Suk Jin talked about memories.
- Like what? Tell me.
- What good memories?
- This is what I said.
- What is it?
- "Whenever he had a hard time..."
- Where did we go together?
- Where did you go with him?
- Gosh, you punk.
Are you Charlie Chaplin or what?
Where did you take him
when he had a hard time?
- I'm really disappointed.
- My dear baby.
- My sweet child.
- I'm upset too.
- My baby.
- You grew up so well.
Look at his shoulders.
He's just like me.
- Look at his shoulders.
- You're smart and athletic.
- My teacher taught me well.
- Thank you, sir.
- Anyway...
- He's my teacher.
I'm the one who helped them all
grow as entertainers.
- That's true.
- Hey, he's your grandfather.
- He's your variety show grandpa.
- Grandpa.
- He's my variety show grandfather.
- I raised them all.
- It's true that he's your grandpa.
- True.
- I admit that he's our elder.
- That's right.
- But he's not your parent.
- We're all in the same family.
Today, Se Chan will treat
his six variety show parents...
to celebrate his birthday.
It's Filial Son Yang Se Chan Race.
It's a special episode.
The successful son Se Chan will
receive R money of 1,000 dollars.
(The grown-up son Se Chan will
receive R money of 1,000 dollars.)
(The bills have been specially made
to celebrate Se Chan's birthday.)
Those bills look so tacky.
Se Chan, you can give
any of your parents an allowance...
- whenever you want.
- Really?
The tally of the allowances
and the money the parents get...
from the missions will decide
the parents' rankings.
The top 2 will get a prize,
and the bottom 2 will get a penalty.
Se Chan, give me an allowance
before we begin.
(The allowance that Se Chan gives
will play a big part.)
Please wait a little while, Mom.
Se Chan, you'll be exempt
from a penalty...
- since you're the birthday boy.
- Oh, I won't get a penalty?
- I'm jealous.
- But the money you have left...
at the end will decide
the prize you'll receive.
- The money I have left?
- The more money, the better prize.
- Try to save as much as you can.
- I see.
Se Chan, you can choose the parents
to team up with before each mission.
- Before the mission?
- Yes.
Will I get some information
about the mission?
- Yes.
- Right. Got it.
Also, after each mission,
we'll give you lottery tickets...
with different chances of winning.
You may win 200 dollars
if you win the lottery.
(The odds of winning are different
according to their rankings.)
(If all 3 faces are the same,
they win 200 dollars.)
In brief, you can get money...
- by winning the lottery...
- Yes.
- Or I give you an allowance.
- I see. Okay.
There's one more way
to get more money.
If you get upset at your son...
or if you need more money...
- On the notepad in the mission bag,
- Yes.
you can write five bad things
about your son Se Chan...
(If they hand in a note
with 5 bad things about Se Chan...)
and hand it in to the cameraman,
and you'll get a lottery ticket.
- Oh, okay. Got it.
- What?
- What if I catch them?
- There are no bad things about him.
Will there be a disadvantage?
No, but you probably won't give
that person a lot of money.
I can write
more than five things, right?
- Five will be enough.
- I can think of ten things now.
He already thought of doing it.
- It started already? Okay.
- Why would you talk badly of him?
- Any trivial things would work.
- Okay.
If I get about 50 lottery tickets...
- You'll write 250 bad things?
- I'll win a few times...
if I get 50 lottery tickets.
The parents that Se Chan chose will
receive 50 dollars now.
(Jong Kook and Haha got 50 dollars
as they were chosen by Se Chan.)
Come on. Take the money. It's yours.
- How can I take your money?
- I can't spend this money.
- Gosh. I'm so upset.
- Thank you.
Also, Se Chan will choose
the penalty as the birthday boy.
- I'll choose the penalty?
- That's great.
- I'm worried.
- I'll pick one that's a hassle.
Choose something
that's done at once.
Since you're all here,
we'll begin the first mission.
- Yes.
- Okay.
The first mission is a simple game.
It's a heartwarming game
that Se Chan...
and his parents who are like
his friends can enjoy together.
It's Head Smack Mafia Game.
- What game is it?
- Head Smack Mafia Game?
In this game,
Se Chan will play individually.
- By myself? Okay.
- Yes.
- It's a match between four teams.
- I see.
All seven of you can play the game
at the same time.
The mafia will be chosen randomly.
Next, you will put on a blindfold,
and only the mafia will take it off.
The mafia will hit the back
of the head of one citizen...
except for the one
on his or her team.
(The mafia hits the back
of a citizen's head.)
(The mafia will hit the back
of the head.)
If the citizens find the mafia,
they get a point.
- If they fail, the mafia wins.
- Got it.
The mafia can't hit the person
on his or her team.
And if you're on the mafia's team,
you have to help the mafia...
because it's a team game.
I have a feeling
that I will get hit.
There's only one note
with "Mafia" written on it.
- There's only one mafia?
- Yes.
Check if you're the mafia or not,
and then put on a blindfold.
I want to be the mafia.
Me too.
I'll just hit hard
since anyone will know it's me.
- That doesn't matter.
- I'm sure...
I'll know that it's Jong Kook
if he hits me.
Right. It'll be obvious.
- We'll get a chance to pay back.
- That'd be great.
That's possible
since there will be three rounds.
Here are blindfolds for you.
Now, let's...
Should I take it off?
(Snorting)
You should put it on.
- He said he'd take it off.
- I mean...
(He said he'd take it off
even before he put it on.)
Why...
He said, "Should I take it off?"
- What is wrong with you?
- He's always distracted on set.
Please start walking in place.
(Head Smack Mafia Game begins
as they start walking in place.)
Mafia, take off
your blindfold quietly...
and hit one of the citizens.
- I think that we may...
- I have a good feeling.
- The back of my head.
- I don't hear So Min walking.
- I'm here.
- Mafia, you can move now.
(The mafia is moving quietly
among the blindfolded citizens.)
(And...)
(The mafia stopped behind someone.)
(Hitting hard)
(The mafia chose Jong Kook.)
- I'm 100 percent sure who that was.
- You can take off your blindfold.
I'm 100 percent sure.
- Did the mafia hit someone already?
- I know who it was.
- I heard a loud bang.
- Exactly.
I'm 100 percent sure who it was.
I heard the noise too.
- It was quite loud.
- Indeed. I heard that too.
I'm 100 percent sure.
- The sound... You know who it was?
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- The feeling...
- Someone on this side.
- Could you tell whose hand it was?
- Yes. I could tell.
- On this side?
- Who was it? Who got hit?
- Why do you think so?
- What?
- I got hit.
- Oh, it was you?
- I heard the noise.
- It was so loud.
- It was loud.
- I thought a watermelon was broken.
Now, start guessing
who the mafia is.
- Hey, why on this side?
- Why is that?
- It came from this side.
- Why?
I felt someone approaching me.
I thought, "Someone is coming."
Then I got hit.
- No. Listen to me.
- But...
- the mafia could've come this way.
- That's possible, but...
The mafia could've stopped here
to hit you.
But I started feeling the presence
from a distance.
- I guess it was you.
- Was it Jae Suk?
- I'm sure it was him.
- I felt that person approaching.
- No. It wasn't me, obviously.
- What?
I think that it was him.
- Let me see your hand.
- No, it wasn't me.
- Your palm is red.
- It was really loud.
- No.
- Especially your fingertips.
- You're wrong.
- Look.
I'm sure it felt different
from my hand.
When it hit my head... Wait.
It feels different.
Right?
- See? I told you so.
- Put yours on my head.
Put it on my head.
(Detective Kim began
an investigation.)
- Put your hand on my head.
- Here.
A little higher.
- Oh, that's where you got hit.
- You punk.
You punk.
Me? What makes you think it was me?
Jong Kook, it wasn't me.
- Trust me. I'm a citizen.
- It's you, right?
- Jong Kook, I didn't hit you.
- That's shocking.
- How could you hit your father?
- Hold on a second.
- I could never do that.
- Hang on.
- It should be on the news.
- I can't make my footsteps silent.
How could you hit your own father?
Since I compared how it felt
when their hands touched my head,
- I realized it was this punk.
- No.
- It wasn't me. Trust me.
- What?
- I would never have...
- It was definitely him.
- dared to hit him. No way.
- Hang on.
- I'm not stupid.
- It was him. I'm sure of it.
Jong Kook, listen.
Here's what I think.
Before I heard the smacking noise,
I heard something falling off.
I must've spoiled you.
Enough, you brat!
- I heard glasses falling off.
- How could you?
You said he came from your left.
So it was 1 of these 2.
- It was one of them.
- No.
Well, actually... I don't know.
- Jae Suk is suspicious too.
- Come on.
- He was closest to Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, it must've been him.
- And I heard the rattling sound...
- Jae Suk must be the one.
- from his glasses.
- Really?
- No, I'm not the one.
- I heard him taking it off.
- And Jong Kook.
- I was standing next to you, but...
- I heard him taking it off.
- Wait.
- You sounded suspicious.
- I was...
- Hold on.
- He got caught.
I'm a citizen.
It's possible that it was him.
Do you want to hear what I think?
- I'm a citizen.
- Okay.
- You see, Jae Suk...
- He asked for his permission.
- can't see without his glasses.
- True.
So he probably had no choice
but to hit the one next to him.
- When I got hit, it felt...
- Suk Jin.
- It felt...
- See? Guess who it was.
Guess who it was.
Who hit you?
There's no way
you can figure it out.
I'm sure that it was
1 of the 2 of them.
- It's hard to tell.
- It felt...
I have no idea.
Actually, to be honest...
- Was the hand thick?
- No, it wasn't.
- Then it was 1 of the 2 girls.
- It might've been Ji Hyo.
- Jong Kook.
- It was either Ji Hyo or...
- It felt...
- Let them touch your head too.
- The back of your head.
- Right. Her hand...
Wait. Open your hand.
Put it on my head.
- Ji Hyo can hit hard.
- I think it was her.
- She's quite strong.
Jong Kook, listen to me.
- I only heard the hitting sound.
- Okay.
- And that sound...
- The smacking sound.
It was loud.
(It was a sharp, clear
smacking sound.)
It didn't sound like a big hand.
I know. It was a small hand.
- Do you see what I mean?
- I have big hands.
I put your hands on my head, right?
- Yes.
- Yours were bigger than I thought.
- My hand...
- It didn't sound like a big hand.
- It was smaller than a man's hand.
- I have big hands too.
- Right. This wasn't it.
- You see...
It didn't sound like someone
with big hands hit you.
- Gosh, this punk.
- Why do you keep suspecting me?
- Why only me?
- Let me think.
- Why did you tilt your head?
- Hold on.
- My hands are bigger than average.
- I need to point something out.
Someone on this side came
and hit the left side of my head?
- That'd be too predictable.
- True.
But maybe the mafia wanted me
to think that way.
- He would've stopped on that side.
- I think it was one on this side.
- That's what I said.
- Jong Kook.
- It was a small hand. I'm sure...
- I told you so.
- that it was a small hand.
- I'll be honest with you.
- Ji Hyo has the smallest hands.
- I honestly think it was Ji Hyo.
- What's suspicious is...
- Jong Kook, listen.
- So Min or Ji Hyo.
- Gosh. I'm not...
- She's acting.
- I mean, Ji Hyo or Se Chan.
- Gosh. I told you it wasn't me.
- So Min is suspicious too.
Right. So Min.
- Let me see your hand.
- It's So Min or Se Chan.
I'm absolutely not the one.
Her hand feels similar too.
- Really? I have thin hands.
- Yes.
- But think about this. So Min...
- is wearing perfume.
- Oh, right.
- So if she swung her arm here,
- I guess I should be careful.
- and hit the back of your head...
- I would've smelled it.
But you didn't, did you?
Hear me out, Jong Kook.
I saw something.
When I took off my blindfold,
So Min's face was so red.
So I thought that it was So Min.
What's with that look on her face?
- She's the last to take it off.
- I thought it was So Min.
That's not true.
I took it off right away.
So Min, if you are a citizen,
you must not do anything suspicious.
- He's right.
- Can you prove your innocence?
- You can't fake blushing.
- I'm not the mafia.
- Are you the mafia?
- No, I'm not.
- Then what are you?
- I'm a citizen.
- Did you see the word on the note?
- Yes.
- Show us.
I don't have it now.
I put it back in the box.
Even if you didn't smell it,
I could've smelled it.
True.
- But you didn't smell it.
- No.
Why is he saying this?
- You're the mafia. That's why.
- What?
- Jae Suk smelled So Min's perfume.
- Right.
- Right?
- How?
- He smelled it, but he lied...
- Because she's on his team...
- because she was on his team.
- Exactly.
- That's why he defended her.
- That's right.
- He wouldn't have said it...
- It might not be true.
- if he could smell it.
- True.
I might have smelled her perfume,
you know.
- That's true.
- Would I have smelled it?
So Min, come here
and hit him lightly.
- Come and hit him.
- If she came...
- Where?
- On this side.
See if you can smell her perfume.
- How?
- Just hit me.
- Should I hit him hard?
- The scent is quite strong.
See? You would've smelled it.
Her perfume has a unique scent.
- So it wasn't her.
- I see now. You're right.
It has a unique scent.
You smelled it too, right?
- You can still smell it.
- You're right.
(You can't smell her perfume there.)
- You can still smell it.
- You're right.
- Maybe he's not sensitive to...
- You can't smell it there.
- It would be weird if you can.
- What is he doing?
- What are you doing, Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin.
What are you doing?
- So Min...
- Why would you smell your wrist?
- That's creepy.
- I wondered...
- if my cologne had a strong scent.
- That's so creepy.
- What are you doing?
- I'm just checking.
- But given the situation,
- Yes.
it'd be the funniest
if he was the one that hit me...
- You're right.
- because he chose me as his parent.
- He hit his own father.
- He came up to me and hit me.
- If he was the one...
- I told you it wasn't me.
- Let him hit you again.
- It wasn't me.
Hit him one more time.
See if it was him.
- You want me to hit him?
- Yes. He'll know...
- if he gets hit again.
- How hard did you hit him?
I can't hit him.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Go ahead and hit him.
- Where?
- Here?
- Yes, here.
- Hit there.
- Hit him.
- He'll see if it feels the same.
- Go ahead.
You punk.
It was him. I'm sure of it.
- That's the sound I heard.
- It was him.
- I heard it. It sounded the same.
- I can assure you.
- It was him.
- You can hit me, but it wasn't me.
- I'm sure it was him.
I'm not the mafia.
- That was the same sound.
- The mafia must be excited now.
Because I'm not the mafia.
It's either So Min or Se Chan.
But I didn't hear
Ji Hyo's footsteps.
I could hear my own footsteps.
Why couldn't you hear it?
That sounds suspicious,
don't you think?
- Look at her face. She's not lying.
- I'm really not the mafia.
Gosh. I said it wasn't me!
- Now, let's begin the voting.
- It's Se Chan.
- One.
- Two.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
I'm not the mafia. Trust me.
I think you should go with your gut.
- In 1, 2, 3. Point at the mafia.
- I think it's Se Chan.
- No, it's not me.
- Point at the mafia.
(Everyone voted for Se Chan.)
All right. You chose Se Chan.
- He must be the one.
- I said I wasn't.
- I'm sure he's the one.
- The decision has been made.
- It's not me.
- But Ji Hyo...
- Now,
- I'm really not the mafia.
I'll tell you
if Se Chan is the mafia.
He must be.
Se Chan is...
(Who is the mafia
that hit Jong Kook in the head?)
(Se Chan is...)
- not the mafia.
- I told you so.
(Se Chan turned out
not to be the mafia.)
- Who was it?
- It must be Ji Hyo.
The mafia who scored a point is...
- Could it be Jae Suk?
- No, it's not me.
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- It's not me.
(The mafia is...)
It was So Min.
So Min and Jae Suk won a point.
- See?
- I told you so.
- What did I tell you?
It was So Min.
(She finally smiles.)
I said he was defending her
because she was on his team.
- I was so afraid.
- I knew it was you.
- I was worried.
- I knew it.
I was so afraid I might get caught.
(The scaredy-cat mafia So Min
who successfully survived...)
(She boldly chose Detective Kim
who's good at guessing.)
(Should I really hit him?)
(She was lucky enough
not to get caught by Jong Kook.)
What I said was right.
Jae Suk smelled her perfume...
- I was so afraid.
- It's amazing that he smelled it.
- You see...
- I mean I smelled her perfume.
Listen.
- When she hit me,
- Yes.
- I knew it wasn't a man.
- What a shame.
- See? It wasn't me, right?
- Wait.
I was wrong. Ji Hyo hits
like a man does.
- My gosh. I smelled it...
- Jae Suk saved her.
I saved her.
- We almost got her.
- That was great.
- I saved So Min.
- I want to be the mafia.
Can you play
the marching band music?
- Right. Play some music for us.
- Yes, play it for us.
- Play the marching band music.
- Play some music for us.
- It'll be more difficult though.
- I had to walk so carefully.
- It'll be more difficult.
- Indeed.
- Put on the blindfold.
- Get further away from one another.
If they have good hearing.
(Who could be the mafia
for Round 2?)
- This is better.
- It's hard to guess.
Right. This is good.
Now, Mafia...
Please take off your blindfold
and hit one citizen hard.
(The mafia took off the blindfold
and quietly moved.)
(And then the mafia stopped
behind someone.)
(Hitting hard)
(Grunting)
Can we take the blindfold off?
(The 2nd victim is Mr. Ji
who lives in Seocho-gu.)
(The criminal is hiding
among the citizens.)
You may take off your blindfold now.
(Mr. Ji, the victim, seems
very shocked.)
(It's time to find the criminal.)
- Who got hit?
- Look at him.
- Was it Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin?
He got hit really hard.
I could hear the noise over there.
It was loud.
- What was that? Wait.
- I could hear the noise over there.
I got so surprised.
- Seriously.
- That startled me.
I was so surprised.
- He got hit really hard.
- It was so loud.
It hurt so much that I laughed.
(It hurt so much that I laughed.)
I don't know why, but I laughed.
I got hit so hard...
that it felt like
my eyes would pop out.
Suk Jin, who hit you?
- The arm wasn't swung like this.
- Then how?
- It moved like this.
- Vertically?
Really? Then I guess
it wasn't a man.
- I'm sure it moved vertically.
- I see.
As if the mafia was taking
his or her parents' revenge on me.
(As if the mafia was taking
his or her parents' revenge on me.)
- It was loud. I was taken aback.
- Suk Jin.
- I see what you mean.
- I think it was him.
- Why?
- When he told us to take it off,
- he was walking in place behind us.
- Yes.
He tried to hide his identity.
- Gosh, seriously.
- And based on how hard he hit me,
- he wanted to make it look funny.
- It was a man?
- Are you serious?
- Was it skillful?
- Yes, it felt skillful.
- Besides,
- Jae Suk...
- I'm sure it was him.
When we all took off our blindfolds,
I saw him standing behind us...
- He couldn't help it.
- He tried to hold back laughter.
- I bet he was satisfied.
- He couldn't seem to stop it.
- Hey.
- He's mistaken.
- You tried to make it look funny.
- It was him.
- I'm sure of it.
- That's not true.
- He looked like this.
- He knew it'd look funny.
- He was satisfied.
- It was him.
- Let me explain.
- That's funny.
- I...
- Why did you laugh?
- I heard the noise.
- Yes.
And it was so funny.
- It wasn't the sound.
- It was so funny...
- Is Jae Suk the mafia?
- That can't explain the laughter.
- I'll tell you why I laughed.
- It was the motion that was funny.
- I knew Suk Jin was hit.
- It must be Jae Suk.
I think that it could be Se Chan.
- It might sound suspicious,
- Okay.
- but I'm definitely not the mafia.
- Yes, you're suspicious.
- I think...
- I was too far away from you.
- I was standing here.
- I see.
Guys, I want you
to think about this.
The staff gave the mafia
a longer time in this round.
Suk Jin, that means...
I'm sorry to say this.
Although he's on my team,
Right.
he was quite far away from him.
I'm not saying it was Haha.
But the mafia had to walk slowly
not to get caught.
- He could be the mafia too.
- Absolutely.
- He could be the mafia.
- It took longer this time.
But that's why it could be Se Chan.
- I think it's Se Chan.
- Me again?
- I'm serious.
- He was right next to Suk Jin.
- I'm not the mafia.
- Because he was close to Suk Jin?
- Hey, are you just trying to...
- Then choose me.
- escape the suspicion...
- I'm not the mafia.
- By the way...
- I don't know who it was...
Whoever it was...
Although it was very funny...
You shouldn't have hit Suk Jin
like that!
- He's the mafia.
- It was him.
(It must be him!)
- It's him.
- Jae Suk!
The corners of his lips...
(The corner of Jae Suk's mouth
kept twitching.)
(He is a member of the mafia.)
(He danced around...)
(thrilled at the thought
of smacking someone.)
(He chose Seok Sam
who's the best punching bag.)
(He adjusted his cap to make it seem
like the perfect crime.)
- It's him.
- It has to be him.
- Jae Suk!
- The corners of his lips...
- It isn't me.
- But...
- Don't act suspiciously then.
- Don't act suspiciously.
- I won't.
I would've hit you harder
to make it funnier.
Those who do comedy sketches well
will have hit you hard.
I admit I'd be good at it,
but Jae Suk has done
comedy sketches too.
- He's a master at it.
- Hit me.
- In what way?
- The half of it...
- Do I make it look good?
- Yes.
- It could be him.
- That was off.
- You...
- To make it look good,
- he would've hit you like so.
- Hold on.
- He did the opposite.
- I made it look good.
I said the slap was
in a downward pattern,
but he swung to the side.
- Exactly.
- Should I do it again?
- Go ahead.
- That's what I meant.
- It's Se Chan.
- That's the sound I heard.
- Tasty, wasn't it?
- You next.
- Do you want me to hit you?
- Hit me right here.
- Sure.
- I'll hit you the best I can then.
- Yes, go ahead.
- That wasn't what I heard.
- He wasn't hit that way.
- I...
- Was it similar?
- He made it seem funny.
- Suk Jin.
He's digging into his memory
for a match.
- Suk Jin.
- He's digging into his memory.
- He...
- He's remembering.
- What's the verdict?
- That's what I tasted.
- Really?
- I'm sure of it.
(Jae Suk got caught
by the slap whisperer.)
- Was this it?
- Are you sure?
- It was him.
- How about another try?
Let Se Chan have a go.
Despite the direction being off...
- Let me have a go at it.
- Go ahead.
- This is how I'd do it.
- Right.
- Like this.
- This is what I heard.
- This was it.
- That's what I heard.
- No, this isn't it.
- Right?
- It wasn't him.
I detected the feeling
of the edge of his fingers.
- Suk Jin...
- Let's vote.
- Be more certain about it.
- He's right.
- Yes, that's what I felt.
- Is it?
- His fingers leave an odd feeling.
- Was it on the sweeter side?
But Se Chan made a similar sound.
The snap of the wrist...
- Go ahead.
- Should I smack you with force?
- Yes, with force.
- With full force then.
That's the sound I remember.
- I was actually trying...
- Wasn't this what we heard?
- to make the same sound.
- This was it.
- Suk Jin, dig into your memory.
- I made it look good.
- It wasn't him.
- No?
I used the snap of my wrist.
Jae Suk.
- Smack me like you did before.
- Like you mean it.
- Like I mean it?
- Yes.
- Like you'd actually do it.
- I'll hit you like I mean it.
Yes, with feeling.
This wasn't the sound.
(This is what I felt!)
This is what I felt.
- He...
- It was him.
- You'll now vote.
- All right.
- That wasn't what I heard.
- Just do it.
It was Jae Suk.
I swear it wasn't me.
All right.
In 1, 2, 3.
- It has to be you.
- Se Chan...
(The majority votes for Jae Suk.)
- Do you think it's him?
- He's rushing the vote.
- Is it Se Chan?
- So Min, are you kidding me?
- Do you think it's him?
- He's rushing the vote.
- He's trying to rush it.
- Exactly.
- All right.
- I swear it isn't me.
You really should
think this through.
Se Chan made the exact same sound.
Think carefully, okay?
- The snap of his wrist...
- You're killing me.
- He rushed it.
- Okay, fine.
- I switch to Se Chan.
- What?
- It's not me!
- I choose Se Chan too.
- It's because...
- Really?
- What did I tell you?
- He's being serious right now.
- This is his serious face.
- I mean it.
Really?
- It wasn't me!
- One...
In 1, 2, 3.
- Se Chan.
- It's Jae Suk.
- You chose Se Chan...
- I was chosen both times.
See what I mean?
Allow me to reveal the truth.
- He tried to rush the vote.
- Exactly.
Se Chan...
- is...
- I don't know.
- He isn't the mafia.
- What did I tell you?
- It's him.
- It's Jae Suk.
- The mafia...
- Is it HaHa?
- It was Jae Suk.
- I was right.
- What did I tell you?
- Why did you rush the vote then?
Seriously?
(Darn it!)
I said I felt his hand on my head.
So why would you choose
Se Chan instead?
I agree that it was weird.
- It was weird.
- I know what I felt.
But at the end, Se Chan...
- I can't believe it.
- Se Chan made the same sound.
He stood there looking so innocent.
I said I felt his hand on my head!
- But...
- No way.
- You guys are killing me.
- I get it.
Here's how you did...
in the Head Smack Mafia Game.
In first place are...
Jae Suk and So Min.
- Nice.
- That's too bad.
(Jae Suk and So Min
are in 1st place.)
In second place
are Haha and Jong Kook.
Okay.
The remaining three
are tied in third place.
We'll now hand out scratchcards.
Those in the first place...
will be given two cards
and one will lead to a prize.
One out of three for you
will be the winning card.
And 1 out of the 4 for you
Jae Suk and So Min
will scratch theirs first.
Please choose one.
- Must we only choose one?
- Yes.
Which one should I choose?
Which one will you choose?
(Only one leads
to a prize of 200 dollars.)
- I'll just have to gamble.
- Here.
(You might not win any money
even after winning the game.)
Wait.
What do we get
if we see Se Chan's face?
The winning card
will have three of his faces.
- Nice!
- Did you win?
- Yes, I won.
- Three identical faces.
Three Se Chan.
- You win 200 dollars.
- Nice.
- We need three of his faces.
- Mine's a dud.
You need three of his faces.
Mine's a dud.
So Min's card was a dud.
Can I have some money?
Any would do.
(The variety show wife
begs for money.)
Are you going to give me some?
Thanks. Is this 20 dollars?
Thank you.
Why are you being nice to me though?
I'll do my best...
- if we end up on the same team.
- Sure.
(The runners-up
have a 33-percent chance.)
- Darn it!
- Is yours a dud?
Yes, it's a dud.
- I have Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk.
- Wait.
- Hold on a second.
- You need one more.
- It's his face.
- I can't believe I won.
- Did you win the prize?
- Yes, I did.
Congratulations.
Jong Kook won the prize.
He beat the odds.
I'll just choose whatever I want.
It's not like my chances are great.
All I have is a 25-percent chance.
(Those in third place
have a 25-percent chance.)
- I see Haha's face.
- Mine's a dud.
- Out of the three...
Hey, I won the prize!
- I won the prize.
- Really?
- Yes, I did.
No way. Take a look.
I won the prize.
Congratulations.
Here's your 200 dollars.
Suk Jin deserves it.
I actually won.
I can't believe it.
We'll add the 200 dollars
to your name.
The money from Se Chan
should be received in person.
We'll regroup after you get changed.
(Time to change outfits)
(A space stocked with ingredients)
- What's all this?
- What is this?
What is this place?
Is a chef meeting us here?
So Min, get away from me.
- I'm not giving her any money.
- Why?
I saw her writing down my flaws.
That's absurd!
I saw you just now.
- I did no such thing.
- I'm done being nice to you today.
- You won't get anything from me.
- What happened?
She was writing down my flaws
to gain a scratchcard.
It's not like
she was trying to hide it.
She wrote them down
while I was looking.
- That's not the case.
- I peeked at what she was doing.
- Is that what she was doing?
- Yes.
Were you writing down his flaws?
- You...
- Unbelievable.
- But...
- You could've at least hid it.
- While I was looking?
- Ji Hyo, he got it wrong.
Doesn't he look cute today?
His teeth look bigger than ever.
(Tactless)
- Oddly enough...
- His teeth?
Here you go.
Goodness.
- Here.
- My gosh.
- Hold on.
- While everyone's looking.
You're the sweetest!
Is it time for a meal?
Come and get your pocket money too.
- Goodness, my sweet boy.
- How devoted is this?
- No way.
- Goodness, my sweet boy.
- How devoted is this?
- As if this is of any use.
You...
There.
Wait a second.
I'm going to make you wait.
- He's sweet and generous.
- My sweet boy.
Why did you give us a notepad...
where there are no flaws
to write down?
- Se Chan, my goodness.
- He has no flaws.
Isn't he a devoted son?
I should write down five flaws.
You only need five, right?
Suk Jin, today...
- If you write down my flaws...
- Unhygienic.
You can say goodbye
to the pocket money today.
- What?
- I won't give you any money.
Fine, go ahead.
He's ugly.
While I'm here? Okay, fine.
(He talks smack about his son
just to get another scratchcard.)
Goodness.
Come on in.
Now I know who to thank this week.
(He easily detects
product placement.)
Welcome!
- Giddy-up!
(Giddy-up!)
- Giddy-up.
- Giddy-up!
Their coffee tastes great though.
No one drinks
the S brand these days.
- What?
- I do.
Please edit that out for me.
- Please edit that out.
- It's too big of an enterprise.
He has a weird way
of showing loyalty.
(Seok Sam throws out words without
considering the consequences.)
It can't be a birthday
without a proper birthday meal.
(A birthday needs
a proper birthday meal.)
The variety show parents
will pour their love...
into a birthday meal
for their son...
- and enjoy the food with him.
- A birthday meal?
You will find seaweed
for seaweed soup,
lobster, bulgogi, and many more.
- Nice.
- Also,
- there is hairtail...
- That's my favorite.
Yesterday at a Chinese restaurant,
- Suk Jin had his fill.
- I surely did.
He says he doesn't have an appetite.
- Who? Suk Jin?
- Yes.
It's been a while
since I visited my in-laws,
so I enjoyed a feast.
You should see them often,
not once in a while.
Once in every two years
clearly isn't enough.
isn't enough.
- Has it been a while?
- You should at least...
- visit them...
- Hold on a second.
Of course, I visit them more often.
Just count the holidays
we have in one year.
Why don't you visit
your in-laws often?
I don't appreciate you
spreading lies.
His Dad-in-law and Mom-in-law...
- Daddy-in-law.
- Mommy-in-law.
Dad-in-law.
Anyway, his in-laws
greeted him with love.
And I took them out
for a delicious meal.
They adore their son-in-law.
That's sweet of you.
Along with Husband Ji,
please go ahead
and cook a birthday meal.
Should I cook as well?
That's up to you.
You can share the money you have.
The others can cash in his flaws
for another scratchcard.
- I see.
- What would you like to eat?
- More so than anything,
- Yes?
I would like to talk to
Ms. Geum Bo Ra.
I've been enjoying
the TV show you're on.
I see. Thank you.
Could you perhaps
cook seaweed soup for me?
Is that what you want?
- Seaweed soup.
- Of course.
- Could you cook it?
- Seaweed soup.
Aren't you sick and tired
of eating seaweed soup every year?
Of course.
(Then what should we have?)
- What else should I have?
- What about ramyeon?
- What?
Are you suggesting ramyeon?
- But...
- For all of us?
Yes, let's have ramyeon!
We have seaweed soup every year.
- Aren't you sick of it?
- You want to break the mold?
Yes, we should.
All right, then.
Let's microwave instant rice.
Let's have ramyeon.
- Let's have a cup ramyeon.
- It's because...
- I said I wanted seaweed soup.
- No.
- Why would you want ramyeon?
- Seaweed soup won't take that long.
- What's your favorite dish?
- Grilled hairtail.
I'm good at grilling it.
I like grilled hairtail.
- Grilled hairtail?
- It's too difficult.
That's too troublesome.
It'll smell also.
It's too difficult.
- It's too troublesome to grill it.
- It'll smell.
- It's too troublesome.
(As they're strongly against it...)
- It'll smell.
- It's too difficult.
- You have to debone it too.
I can take ramyeon. It depends on
what you put in the ramyeon.
- All right, then. I will...
- You just need to grill it.
- I think the lobsters...
- I'll cook rice for you.
- It looks like they're alive.
- Do you really want seaweed soup?
- What will you make for me?
- Do you want seaweed soup?
- Release them. They're pitiful.
- I want seaweed soup.
But making japchae is simple.
- Then I want japchae.
- Japchae?
- I like japchae.
- You do?
- I want japchae.
- Okay, got it.
- So Min, can we make japchae?
- We can microwave instant curry.
It'll take too long.
We need to soak the noodles.
- It takes long?
- Yes.
- Wait, Jae Suk.
- It takes long?
- We can't make japchae.
- Japchae takes too long.
- I'll make egg fried rice.
- Hold on, Se Chan.
- I don't want that.
- Se Chan.
- Let's just have beef.
- Let's grill some meat.
- We can do that,
- Let's have beef.
- but please season it.
- Se Chan.
- You can dip it in salt.
Soothe your stomach
with this for now.
Ediya coffee on an empty stomach?
Of course. I should boost my energy.
Let's have Ediya coffee
on an empty stomach!
- Giddy-up!
(Na Eun's dad's way
to calm down a sulky child.)
Let's grill beef.
- You should grill beef.
- You should.
So Min, what will you make?
Since there are many soups,
I'll make egg fried rice
we can have as a side dish.
- I'm making egg fried rice.
- Who is making ramyeon?
I'll make it.
All right. Jae Suk is good at it.
I'm having ramyeon in the end.
(I'm having ramyeon in the end.)
- Must I wear gloves?
- Still, it's my birthday,
so please add something
in the ramyeon.
- They can make green onion oil...
- If you add too many things,
- it'll not be tasty.
- Plain ramyeon is the best.
Doesn't this look more delicious?
How is this a birthday meal?
You know how to make seaweed soup?
Of course. I can make seaweed soup.
This is top-quality beef.
It's of good quality, isn't it?
- Let me try it like a taster.
- It's heartwarming though.
- They're all cooking for you.
- If you add too many things,
it'll not be tasty.
Ji Hyo knows how to cook it.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- You're making seaweed soup.
Once, I didn't soak seaweed
when making seaweed soup,
and it swelled
like a volcano explosion.
- It swells a lot.
- The seaweed opened the lid itself.
I'm sorry, but I'm really curious.
Why are you just walking around
after wearing a mask and gloves?
Because his hands were cold.
(Taking a walk around the kitchen)
- I'm so dumbfounded.
- It's because I have nothing to do.
- What do you mean?
- Everyone is working on something.
What am I supposed to do?
- My fathers... Here.
- Oh, my!
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- You're so nice to us.
- Seriously.
He's so nice. He's such a good son.
- No, put it up there. Thank you.
- I'll put it in here.
- There.
- Excuse me.
- He's such a good son.
- Thank you.
He's a good son.
I can't stand someone
leisurely walking around...
- with gloves on.
- He's such a good son.
Sir, go and wash your face.
Suk Jin. Can you make
zucchini jeon?
- You want zucchini jeon?
- Yes.
(He gives work to the old man
who's walking about.)
Gosh, why would you want jeon?
It's a birthday meal.
There should be some sort of jeon.
- There's no cake...
- This is...
or seaweed soup.
You're just making ramyeon.
There are no pans.
Yes, we do. There's a lot.
We have six pans here.
Make me zucchini jeon.
I should make zucchini jeon
since Se Chan wants to eat it.
I'd love to have zucchini jeon.
(Falling)
My gosh. That old man...
(Falling again)
- That old man...
- Mister!
- You could've used both hands!
- My gosh, seriously.
I can't give you any allowances
at this rate.
- I know. Why did he do that?
- Go and wash these now.
- Okay.
- Wash them.
- My gosh.
- I'll make zucchini jeon for you.
- Are you really making it?
- Se Chan.
Do you know how to make it?
- Are you making egg rice?
- Yes, I'm making egg fried rice.
The mushroom looks great.
Se Chan, come over here and try it.
Se Chan wanted to have
zucchini jeon.
- The seaweed soup looks good.
- Ji Hyo knows how to make it.
Ji Hyo is a good cook.
I've never had so many people...
prepare my birthday meal.
- Is that so?
- I'm so happy.
- Se Chan, you're happy, right?
- Yes.
We're cooking with all our hearts
and with one heart...
- for you.
- What is he saying?
What does he mean
by all your hearts and one heart?
Isn't this nice?
- Happy birthday!
- Se Chan.
- Thank you.
Go take a seat.
- I hope you'll be healthy.
- You can stay seated.
Hey, don't act up
and just stay seated.
- Have the Ediya coffee.
- Se Chan.
Can you do me a favor
before sitting? Get me a dish.
I'm sorry, but I'm too busy.
- A big one?
- Yes.
I'm sorry, but I'm too busy.
- I'm sorry.
- Not at all.
It must be uncomfortable
for you to be seated.
Not at all.
(Meanwhile, Chef So Min was
doing something in the corner...)
(with a plate.)
- It's ramyeon.
- Se Chan!
Happy birthday to you
She actually means it.
- Happy birthday, dear Se Chan
- She...
She's always shooting
"We Got Married" with him.
- She actually means it.
- Happy birthday to you
It's so pressuring.
Look at this.
(She's more excited than him.)
All right. Please take a seat.
Please take a seat.
Okay. Do you need help?
So Min, can you make
soy sauce for me?
- Soy sauce?
- Do you know how to make it?
I hate this the most.
It's ready. Ramyeon is ready.
We must have ramyeon now!
(The birthday dishes are being made
one by one,)
(following the fried rice cake.)
(The special ramyeon
made by the noodle lover himself)
Hurry and sit. We must have it now.
- Happy birthday to you
- Come and sit!
- Okay. I'm done with ramyeon.
- Come and sit down.
Leave Suk Jin,
and come sit here, everyone!
- Suk Jin, what are you doing?
- Happy birthday to you
(The zucchini man
barely finishes making his dish.)
- Hurry up.
- It looks pretty good.
It needs to boil down more.
(The seaweed soup, the highlight,
is almost ready.)
- Happy birthday to you
- So Min, give me a plate.
- Ji Hyo.
- It looks pretty good.
- You're not eating it, right?
- It looks quite good.
- Try one.
- Should I?
- Sit down. We have ramyeon.
- Ramyeon?
The seaweed soup
has been boiling the whole time.
Ji Hyo, sit down. Sit down, So Min.
(A spoonful would've been enough.)
Leave Suk Jin.
The noodles will get soggy!
Come sit down first.
The birthday meal looks quite good.
- So Min, have this.
- It looks so nice. It's the best.
This looks...
- Thank you.
- Try it.
It's your birthday.
(Right then, Chef Jeon runs in.)
What are you doing?
(Putting candles)
(The birthday of Se Chan who grew up
by a lot in the past 4 years)
(Happy birthday, dear Se Chan)
(Happy birthday to you)
Thank you!
- Eat up.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Se Chan.
- Se Chan, happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- We hope you stay healthy.
I haven't had ramyeon for so long.
It's so good.
- This reminds me of that.
- You made it well.
This is how seaweed soup
should taste.
You should cut the cake
with chopsticks.
Is it good?
But how did it...
(Chef Jeon's hidden menu,
egg fried rice)
It's ramyeon with meat.
It's incredibly good.
It's fascinating that we made these.
- How is this fascinating?
- Hey.
- So Min.
- Yes?
What's wrong with this fried rice?
It's good.
- Try it.
- What's wrong?
It has no taste.
Didn't you add salt?
- I added a little.
- It looks so good though.
Actually, you should have it
with something else.
- I'll try it.
- Let's try it.
I've never had such fried rice.
- Try it with mayonnaise.
- This is a bit...
(A bizarre dish
that's from another world)
Does it taste bland?
Although I've never tasted it,
it tastes like a cloud.
It's just... It has no taste.
She must've added
a lot of margarine.
Gosh. Hey.
(A shocking collaboration of
margarine, butter, and mayonnaise)
It's good!
It's a horrible menu
for the middle-aged.
- For the middle-aged?
- Margarine and mayonnaise...
For the middle-aged?
I'll try the seaweed soup...
- Ji Hyo made.
- Se Chan's eating the seaweed soup.
I'm having seaweed soup
earlier than my birthday this year.
It's your first seaweed soup.
It looks good.
- It smells nice.
- She made it well.
- The soup looks thick.
- How is it?
The soup looks thick.
- I like soups...
with many ingredients.
I'll judge it. The seaweed soup
my wife makes is really nice.
- It's nice.
- It needed to be boiled more.
It's really nice.
(Jae Suk tries a bite as well.)
Is it okay?
My goodness.
You saw how she made it.
- What's wrong?
- I shouldn't have added salt.
It's too salty.
Ji Hyo, be honest.
Did you add fish sauce to this?
Why? What's wrong?
It smells like fish sauce.
You added it, didn't you?
It does taste
like fish sauce, right?
- But she made it in a short time.
- Right. If it gets boiled more...
- It has to be...
- I should've boiled more.
It needs to be boiled more.
It'll be delicious
if you boil it more.
You need to boil seaweed soup
for a long time.
Why is no one mentioning
the zucchini jeon?
Sorry?
Have some zucchini jeon.
- It's slightly undercooked.
- I'll try it.
- Try it.
- It's incredible.
- It's crunchy.
- I made it with all my effort.
This is quite fresh.
I mean...
How come it's so fresh
when he fried it?
- Because he just harvested it.
- This zucchini is...
It tastes like
it was just harvested.
Doesn't it have a nice texture?
- My gosh, this is...
- It has a nice texture.
I thought it was radish kimchi
when I first bit it.
(Big Nose was asked to make
zucchini jeon,)
(but he made radish kimchi instead.)
(The more he chews,
the more absurd it feels.)
It's just so fresh!
This is how I do it.
- I see. That's how you make it.
- I like it this way.
Suk Jin! This isn't zucchini jeon.
It's pickled radish.
- It's pickled radish.
- It's because...
- It still got its green color.
- The best zucchini jeon I had...
is from a really famous
Korean restaurant.
This is how they make it.
They make it a little crunchy.
Where is that place?
Sorry?
He's lying.
(He's busted.)
Suk Jin.
- Why do you keep making petty lies?
- Why do you keep telling lies?
- He keeps making petty lies.
- Why do you lie so much?
I wasn't lying.
It wasn't a lie. Would you visit
if I told you the address?
Are you going to verify it or what?
That will be Suk Jin's punishment.
Comparing their zucchini jeon
with his.
He should compare
this zucchini jeon...
with the restaurant near Dosan Park.
- The zucchini jeon.
- He must.
That will be your punishment.
Comparing your jeon with theirs.
Can you leave two pieces?
- Hey, stop it.
- Let's compare this with theirs.
- Darn it.
- What?
- What's wrong?
- It'll take hours.
What? We should compare them.
All right. Happy birthday again,
Se Chan!
Thank you for the meal.
(Thank you for the meal!)
- Hey, let's...
- Let's have coffee.
- We should have desserts.
- That's right.
I'll make a hot cup of coffee
for everyone.
Thank you.
What's this?
Is this supposed to be that?
Please don't touch it.
Let me just look at it!
- You should have this in winter.
- You look like an expert.
- Six and seven.
- You're making it like a barista.
You must have warm coffee in winter.
How many cups are ready?
It's a special gold blend.
This is really good.
I'm not even kidding.
Jae Suk.
She's after a commercial deal again.
Hold on. There's no cup for me.
You can't have it there.
Yes, I can.
No, Ediya will not like it.
No, they'll love it.
Who has coffee in a soup bowl?
No, what matters
is the person who has it.
(No, what matters
is the person who has it.)
It's like an advertising phrase
for an ad.
- It really is like a copy.
- He and his confidence.
Suk Jin, your nose is bleeding.
Your nose is bleeding.
There's a reason
why he's shot so many commercials.
This is so good.
Hey, don't you want to...
mix rice in it?
- Why don't you...
- Can you add some rice?
Add some kimchi as well.
Aren't you having scorched rice?
(The gukbap lover always
thinks of adding rice...)
(when there's product placement.)
He always adds rice to it.
He always says
it'd go well with rice.
It'd go so well with rice.
You must add rice to this.
You must have a spoon.
You must have it like this.
I find that the funniest.
(After lunchtime...)
Can you give me a coin, please?
(Can you give me a coin, please?)
Oh, my. When did you write all that?
Earlier, when I was next to you.
It's because I don't have money.
(Yang Se Chan doesn't seem
to like egg fried rice.)
(Yang Se Chan's smile
isn't that pretty.)
(Almost half of it
is about his looks.)
Ji Hyo, let's sit
and write some down.
- We need to write five. Downsides.
- What should we write?
Things you don't like about him.
(So Min writes more bad things
about Se Chan.)
Se Chan...
doesn't have as many downsides
as I thought.
That's only for you.
(To Se Chan's variety show wife,
10 is the most she can write.)
Gosh, you.
(To Se Chan's variety show wife,
10 is the most she can write.)
What are you up to?
What are you two cooking up?
- Oh, for the lottery ticket?
- You're writing his downsides?
I should write some.
I have to write five of them, right?
(They all join in
and write bad things about Se Chan.)
So Min kept
writing something earlier.
I didn't know. I was sitting next
to her, but I didn't know.
- You need that.
- I should hurry and write some.
Se Chan, look at them.
(Right then, Se Chan comes in.)
(Se Chan, look at them.)
They're all holding papers...
- and writing about you.
- They're all writing about you.
My gosh. No wonder
my ears were burning.
I had to cool them down.
- They're no joke.
- It's frantic here.
Hey! I didn't know
we got a notebook for this.
- I can't believe it.
- I was stopping them.
I'm using this bag...
- You know that I told you first.
- to keep my phone.
Jong Kook, here.
- My goodness.
- I haven't seen you write one.
- Haha, you...
- I almost forgot.
Forget it, Haha.
You're holding a lottery ticket.
- Where?
- It's in your hand.
You gave me a lot.
Mister, are you writing it
in my face?
I'm right behind you.
I'm writing down the ideas
I thought of.
(The secret to becoming a national
MC is writing ideas down.)
- You're writing down ideas?
- He's rice with ideas these days.
- I reported it to you.
- Thank you.
What about me?
- I didn't do anything.
- I didn't do anything either.
I really didn't do anything.
I swear.
- I wrote five.
- Here's your lottery ticket.
Give me a ten-dollar bill.
- What are you, a beggar?
- Yes!
Okay.
Give me some.
I didn't write anything.
He wrote it in my presence.
Isn't he being too much?
You wrote them while looking at me.
I told you. I wrote down my ideas.
- They're reflecting your ideas?
- Of course.
- Then I approve of it. Here.
- Give me one more.
- Come on. Give me one more.
- What is this?
Hold on.
You're extorting money from him.
- What do you mean?
- Why are you extorting from him?
- No, I didn't.
- Please wait.
- Everyone.
Did you enjoy your lunch?
- Yes.
- Yes, I did.
Many of you submitted
slanders on the birthday boy.
I didn't know such a thing existed.
- I'll read a few.
- Okay.
"The look in his eyes is dirty.
He's ugly. He's dumb."
"He's ignorant. His feet stink."
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin, how could you?
- Suk Jin, you submitted them.
- He's the worst.
- What else is there?
- And...
"His teeth
look more protruding today."
- It's So Min.
- "He only gave me 20 dollars."
- Twenty dollars?
- "His cap is too small for him."
"He pretends not to like me."
- It's So Min.
- She mentioned protruding mouth.
- "He pretends not to like me"?
- "He pretends not to like me."
- How is that my downside?
- I'm sure So Min wrote that.
- Hey.
- It's So Min for sure.
- Was that a confession or what?
- "He pretends not to like me."
- It's So Min.
That's hilarious.
"His gums show too much
when he smiles."
"Looks like he thinks he's
the only one with a birthday."
(Looks like he thinks he's
the only one with a birthday.)
"Looks like he thinks he's
the only one with a birthday."
But I didn't plan this.
That was funny.
They wrote down such downsides
about him.
- That's a lot.
- It is.
They're all petty.
They're not so impactful.
All right.
Let's start the next mission.
This mission will use
a low-frequency massager.
Gosh, this is...
The parents and son
will massage each other.
It's called
Low Frequency in My Hand.
I think it'll be nice.
I like this kind of massage.
Each team's representative
will step forward...
wear a blindfold and gloves...
that have
a low-frequency massager attached.
Within the given time,
you need to touch the opponents'
bodies with the gloves.
The one who screams
will have their point deducted.
Okay, got it.
Even when I get physical therapy,
I ask them to make it strongest.
- Then you and I will be the winner.
- You're amazing.
I love that tingling feeling.
Each team will play against
its opponents.
Se Chan, you can
pick a partner this time.
- I can?
- Yes.
- Join us.
- This time, I'll choose...
- Jae Suk and So Min.
- Fine. You can join them.
All right. Let's send him away.
We should send him away
when we need to.
The first round will be between
Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin.
- All right.
Please put on
the low-frequency massagers.
- I hate it.
- I like this feeling.
It's good for our body, right?
When they ask if I'm okay,
I ask them to make it strongest.
It's good for our body, right?
Yes, it is. It's good for your body.
It's fine
when it touches you at first.
- If Jong Kook likes it...
- Good!
Touch me a lot. Here and here.
- They're truly amazing.
- If Jong Kook likes it,
- I won't be able to attack him.
- I can't stand pains like this.
No one can.
- I can't stand it at all.
- No one can stand it.
(Screaming)
- What's the strongest one?
- Gosh!
- How does it work?
- Touch your skin with it.
It'll be fine.
(Happy)
- You like that?
How is it?
- Gosh, it stings!
- No idea.
- I'm okay.
- It's like physical therapy.
(The gym lover
is stimulating his muscles.)
- Does it sting?
- It's like physical therapy.
All right!
Jong Kook is enjoying it.
All right. Get ready.
(The low-frequency trio is ready.)
It's me, Suk Jin.
- It's me!
- Not this way!
- Go straight.
- Not this way.
Se Chan, you need to
come to this side.
- Jong Kook.
- Come here.
Suk Jin is behind us.
- Attack from right there, Se Chan.
- Grab him.
- Attack from right there.
- Who is it?
- It's slightly to your left.
(Se Chan, who made noise,
gets a point deducted.)
Se Chan, minus one point.
(He puts on guard first.)
Go straight.
Go straight. He's on the floor.
Grab him!
(Screaming)
(Suk Jin also grabbed Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook isn't affected at all.)
Se Chan, come this way.
It's right there.
(Screaming)
Se Chan, grab his legs.
Go forward. Go straight.
- Right in front of you.
- Go straight.
(Screaming)
No! Jong Kook!
Jong Kook! Who is it?
He likes it.
(What? I clearly grabbed him.)
- Hey.
- Jong Kook likes it.
(He's strengthening his muscles
with the stimulation.)
Hey.
What's wrong with this? What's this?
Maybe my massager isn't working.
(Screaming)
(Big Nose gets livened up.)
(He looks the liveliest this year.)
- I'm sorry!
- Grab him.
I'm sorry!
(The filial son's low-frequency
massage filled with love)
The two of them are on the floor.
- Go straight.
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin is behind you.
Just go straight.
(A hyena hunting the weakest)
- Go straight.
- Hey, Yang Ssaebssaeb.
(Screaming)
Yang Ssaebssaeb.
(What? It didn't touch him yet.)
(He can't hold his energy
and keeps shouting.)
It's over.
I touched Jong Kook,
but how come it didn't work?
- Hey, what's wrong with you?
- I liked it.
- Look at him.
It reminded me of physical therapy.
He's unbelievable.
(The game between the low-frequency master
and his preys is over.)
It was fun. It's a healthy game.
It helps improve your health too.
Round Two is between
Ji Hyo, Haha, and So Min.
(Round 2, Ji Hyo, Haha, So Min)
I'm done for.
Hey, So Min. Do a good job.
This is fun though. It's funny.
(Screaming)
That startled me.
It wouldn't come that fast.
You need to hold it for a second.
He's making a fuss.
I'm Pikachu.
I surrender!
(He practices saying he surrenders
before the game even begins.)
All right. I'm practicing.
What happens when he surrenders?
Does he just rest?
(Screaming)
- Darn it.
- He's a scaredy-cat.
Get ready.
So Min, don't scream.
- Ji Hyo.
- Just stay still.
Ji Hyo, to your left...
No. Behind you.
- So Min is behind you.
- Go straight.
Ji Hyo, you should
team up with So Min.
- Can you even attack?
- Let's attack Haha together.
- It hurts.
- You two should join hands.
Ji Hyo, go straight
to where Haha is.
- Haha is near me.
- I'm Pikachu.
Haha, it might be better
to attack first.
- To your right.
- Go straight.
- Haha, run away!
- Go.
He's right in front of you.
- Run away.
- To your left.
It's not a game about running away.
- Stop there.
- Go after him.
- So Min, go after him.
- Turn around.
Where should I go to, Suk Jin?
- Ji Hyo, over here.
- Follow the sound of my clap.
- Over here, Ji Hyo.
- Over here.
What are you, a zombie?
- So Min, this way.
- You're so disgraceful.
Gosh, Haha.
(Haha is frivolously walking away
fast in case he gets caught.)
It's me.
(Jae Suk is trying to move So Min
to Haha's side.)
Oh, my.
(Screaming)
Hey!
(Haha is all scared.)
- It's so scary.
- It's not.
- Where is he?
- Gosh, Haha.
- He's just a scaredy-cat.
- Where is he?
- I'm right here.
- Be quiet.
No one has touched anyone so far.
(I'm sorry, but no one has touched
anyone so far.)
Hey, this is...
(That's how it started.)
Who was that?
Hey! Gosh!
- Come here!
- He's gone crazy.
- What a scaredy-cat.
- He's a complete scaredy-cat.
Are you playing
a VR game or something?
(Even when someone brushes
by his clothes,)
(he starts playing a VR game
on his own.)
You touched my heart!
(His frivolousness
makes everyone lose their minds.)
- He's gone crazy.
- He's a scaredy-cat.
- How did I team up with him?
- He's gone crazy.
Oh, gosh.
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
(She made an error
and headed toward the staff.)
(Screaming)
(She massaged her cameraman
before anybody knew.)
You should give us points for that.
The cameraman screamed.
- Give us points.
- You should grab someone too!
You can grab others too, you idiot!
- No!
- Go straight.
- Go straight. Go some more.
- Pika-pika!
- Go some more, you punk!
(In the end, the low frequency
gym goer steps in.)
That's it. Grab her.
- Grab her leg.
- Pikachu!
Pikachu!
(Screaming)
Darn it!
(It looks like his VR game
is pretty dynamic.)
What is he, a monster?
What kind of monster is he?
She's right in front of you.
She's on the floor in front of you.
You're almost there.
Go for it! You have to fight now!
Go for it!
(They finally touch each other
10 seconds before the game ends.)
(Screaming)
(He finally gets possessed
by the low frequency ghost.)
- Hey.
- Is he a zombie?
- What is he, a zombie?
- What is that? A zombie?
- Hey.
Are you playing
a VR game or something?
- Hey.
- Are you playing a VR game?
It was so scary.
What is he, a zombie?
What was that about?
All right. Who do you want to
play against, Jae Suk?
- I want to play against Suk Jin.
- Play with Jong Kook.
I want to play against Suk Jin...
and Haha.
Haha, you'll play one more time.
Haha, don't take it off.
(Round 3, Suk Jin, Jae Suk, Haha)
All right. It's worth the fight.
Jae Suk, I think you'll win
even if you just brush past them.
- Of course.
- It doesn't hurt at all.
I don't want to play.
Hey.
You'd better do a good job.
- Hey. Haha.
- It's worth the fight.
- This isn't strong enough.
- Hang in there a little.
- It's too weak.
- Let me make it stronger for you.
Make it stronger.
- Is it still too weak?
- It is.
Jae Suk, it's on level 12.
It's too weak.
What do you want to do?
I want it to make you go like this.
Jae Suk, try it.
Jae Suk is so solemn right now.
- Get ready.
- Good luck!
(Jae Suk solemnly prepares
for his first match.)
(The game starts.)
I can just wave a white flag.
- Go straight, Jae Suk.
- Hold on.
I'm sorry,
but let's take off our shoes.
(Haha hides behind others
as soon as the game starts.)
Jae Suk, to your left.
To your right.
(The two of them met in the corner.)
You got it.
It's right there.
It's right there. Grab him.
(Screaming)
(Screaming in a high pitch)
Suk Jin, he's in front of you.
He's in front of you!
- To your front!
- To the left.
Go straight, Suk Jin.
(Screaming)
(Suk Jin screams in a sweet voice
as it's his first time feeling it.)
Go straight, Suk Jin.
Haha, just stay still.
Just stay still there.
That's it. Go that way, Jae Suk.
To your left.
To your right.
Go straight from there!
In front of you! To the right.
Behind you!
Behind you! Right there.
(Screaming)
(They scream in a higher octave
as they're scared.)
I'm sorry, but where is Haha?
- To your left!
- To the right!
To the right, Jae Suk.
Come here.
- To your left.
To your left, Jae Suk.
Haha is behind you.
(The high-octave screamers reunite.)
(They meet each other again
while looking for Haha.)
Gosh, my arm!
(They keep losing points.)
Gosh, this stings!
- It's over.
- What's wrong with him?
Gosh, Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin screamed like this.)
That's when he's electrocuted.
(The soprano's scream
was full of vitality.)
It was like an animated film.
It looked like he was electrocuted.
That was hilarious.
- It was really funny.
- Yes!
How much do you have right now?
- Me? I gave out a lot.
- Yes.
I have 600 dollars.
You have a lot.
You have so much money.
- I have so little.
- How much do you have?
I have only 20 dollars.
- I have only 20 dollars for real.
- Don't give him any.
Give me just 30... No, 50 dollars.
Then you should at least
show me a cute act.
(Showing him a cute act right away)
- Thanks.
- He showed a cute act over this.
- Se Chan. Give me some too.
- How much do you have?
- I don't have much.
- You two should face each other...
and do a battle on cute acts.
(Being cute)
(Cute)
I'll give you thirty dollars.
Ten dollars for you.
- I gave you 40 dollars in total.
- I'll announce the result...
of the mission.
The winners of the mission...
(First place is...)
- are Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- Yes!
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo, you can take
the lottery tickets...
with 50-percent chance of winning.
(The winners get a lottery ticket
with 50-percent chance of winning.)
- The one with a 50 percent chance?
- That's right.
- It'll be amazing if I win it.
- Second place...
is Jae Suk, Se Chan, and So Min.
- It's us.
- All right.
Third place gets a lottery ticket
with 25-percent chance of winning.
Okay!
Take one each and scratch it off.
(Who will be the lucky winner
this time?)
Darn it. The first face
I'm seeing is So Min's.
The first face I'm seeing
is yours too.
(Jae Suk's is a dud as well.)
(The team in 2nd place all failed.)
It's a dud! Give it to me.
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo, how did it go?
Suk Jin is scratching off both.
You can't do that.
You got a dud too, right?
Darn it.
I got So Min's face
as soon as I scratched it off.
Darn it. I got So Min too.
(I got So Min too.)
(Surprised)
What?
I got three of So Min's faces!
- You got three of So Min's faces?
- Really?
I thought there was only Se Chan.
I also got three of So Min's faces!
I got three of So Min's faces!
- So Min.
- This is...
- Hey!
- Jong Kook.
- I hated that I got your face.
- Me too!
But I got three of your faces.
This is amazing.
It's not that I hated it.
The ones in last place
won the lottery.
I thought it needed to have...
- Se Chan's faces.
- Me too. I thought the same.
It wasn't like that? You could get
other people's faces?
- So Min.
- Goodness, So Min.
- You lucky charm.
- How did you get it?
So then...
the only winners of the lottery
will get 200 dollars each.
(The 3rd place team
gets 200 dollars each.)
- You both won?
- Yes.
They're so lucky.
I'm so jealous.
- This is the last mission.
- What is it?
It's the last mission...
where parents and their son...
can have a heart-to-heart talk.
It's called
What Happened to My Family.
- What Happened to My Family.
Each team's representative...
will be the eldest
among the team members.
That'll be Suk Jin, Jae Suk,
- and Jong Kook.
- What's this about?
One of you will step forward
and wear headphones...
where music is being played.
The remaining members will
sit in front here side by side...
- and slander them in their face.
- In their face?
(It's a mission where they'll
slander them in their face.)
- Slandering in their face?
- Yes.
But the person...
wearing headphones can't hear.
- He'll just see the mouths moving.
- Oh, no.
So whenever you slander them...
in their face,
even if it's just a word,
we'll give you a point each.
And if the player
with headphones wants to know,
then they can secretly
press the button underneath.
Then we'll stop the music in secret.
(The player with headphones can
listen if they press the button.)
They can hear everything
from that moment on,
but the player on the same team
won't gain any more points.
You need to talk badly of me
so our team can get more points.
You must talk badly
of your team member.
For how many seconds?
In which section?
Once they press the button,
the music will stop for good.
- For good? I see.
- Yes.
Se Chan, you need
to choose your team.
This time,
- I'll join Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- All right.
Please place a cushion in front.
You need to hold out
as much as you can.
(It's already making them excited
to slander Jae Suk in his face.)
I won't press the button.
- You can say whatever you want.
- Really?
- You can even curse at me.
- Let's do that.
Can you turn off
our microphones too?
It'll be censored anyway.
(He confidently
puts on the headphones.)
Look at their eyes.
It looks like they're saying
this is their chance.
(They're looking
the brightest today.)
It's like they've been
waiting for this chance.
(Big Nose is already
itching to talk.)
It has begun.
- Wait.
- It has already begun?
- What is it?
- I'm sorry,
- can you turn on recent songs?
- You can't do that.
- Recent songs.
- Put them back on.
- I have a lot to say.
- Just put them back on.
I want to listen to "Kiss Kiss"
by LABOUM.
- We have a lot to say.
- "Kiss Kiss" by LABOUM.
Why does he keep talking about kissing?
I know.
- He's just...
- Jae Suk...
- is very picky with music.
- It's too old.
I can actually read your mouths.
You're a kiss lover.
- You like kissing.
- He can't live without it.
"Kiss Kiss" by LABOUM.
- You see? He's still on about it.
- This song is too old.
He's especially picky today.
He must like kissing.
- I can read your mouths.
- Really?
- You're ugly.
- Can you hear me?
- "You're ugly."
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- "Yoo Jae Suk."
- You're ugly.
- "You're ugly."
- Yes.
- Yes, I can hear it all.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- He can hear us.
- Can you hear me?
- I read your mouths. Yes.
- Can you hear me? Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes, I can.
- Yes.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Do it.
- Let's start.
- Ready, go.
- He is just to picky.
Why is he so picky?
He's so picky.
It's being played!
(Jae Suk's perspective)
(Will Jae Suk be able
to enjoy the song fully...)
(while they slander in his face?)
- He's so picky about music.
- "Kiss Kiss" is being played.
You should keep quiet.
- Be quiet.
- Let's start.
- Go.
- So we can start.
- His face doesn't call for a kiss.
- Exactly.
Listen. He keeps talking about
"Kiss Kiss" because...
he has never kissed anyone
in his life before.
- I know.
- Suk Jin.
How did Jae Suk act
when he meets a woman?
- What?
- How did he act?
He wasn't popular, was he?
- He flirted with them.
- Really?
He flirted?
Can I talk?
- Be quiet.
- I can talk, right?
- Can I talk?
- You know what?
Don't be ridiculous.
Everything he says is a lie.
He's talking nonsense.
- He used to date an older woman.
- He knows nothing about me.
- Tell me. I want to hear it.
- Really?
- He used to date an older woman.
When the cafe street was popular
in Bangbae-dong,
he told her he'd talk informally
and she slapped him.
It's true.
Did you get slapped?
- Did you get slapped?
- Did you get dumped?
You know Lee Seung Gi's song?
"Because You Are My Woman."
- I will call you you now
- I got slapped?
- He said he'd call her you,
- Did he get slapped?
- and he got slapped.
As far as I'm concerned, he has
never dated anyone officially.
- He deserved it.
- He wasn't popular at all.
I'm getting curious.
Do you know what he was like?
When we all went clubbing,
he was the only one with no work.
He had no work.
"Jae Suk. You have to be there
by 7 p.m. to get a room."
- "Be there on time to get a room."
- Is this "Talk Box?"
- I'm serious.
He used to get a room for us.
He was a room boy?
- Were you a room boy?
- What?
- A room boy?
- Because...
you had to be there two hours
in advance to get a room.
- Do you trust what he says?
- Nowadays...
- at least we have a phone.
- Right.
Back then, we had nothing.
There was nothing to do.
- Because...
- He was excited.
- He was waiting in the room.
- So he doesn't have to pay.
- I see.
- He had to keep it reserved.
"Jae Suk. Go get a room."
- "Yes, sir."
- The room boy.
(Jae Suk listened to music
for a minute.)
(He pressed the button.)
(Now he can hear everything.)
- Now he's become the national MC.
- I know.
Let's give him a round of applause.
He became successful.
- That's amazing.
- He's very confident...
- about what he wears.
- Yes.
- He wears...
- Doesn't he have thin legs?
Doesn't he have thin legs?
They're weak.
- He has no butt.
- They're skinny.
You have no butt.
- What?
- Your butt is too flat.
It's too skinny.
Don't say it clearly.
You're very countrified.
(Suk Jin enjoys badmouthing
Jae Suk in his face.)
- You're very countrified.
- What?
You're very countrified.
I'm very countrified?
- He heard it.
- He pressed the button.
- Did you press the button?
- I didn't. I can't hear anything.
- You did.
Your butt is so flat.
- My butt...
- You have no butt.
- I have no butt?
- Where is your butt?
- He pressed it.
- You pressed it.
- You pressed the button.
- I didn't.
Isn't he the Bangbae-dong slap man?
Yes.
- What are they talking about?
- The slap man.
It was hard for him to go on a date.
- Right.
- Because of his appearance?
He was able to hang out with them
thanks to us.
Were his front teeth uneven
even back then?
- Did he get braces?
- He got so much better now.
Did his teeth become uneven after
getting slapped in Bangbae-dong?
I saw him spitting on the street.
When you spit, you spit forward.
He almost spat on my face.
He spits sideways.
(Believe it or not, Suk Jin shares
a ridiculous story about his teeth.)
I'm not lying. He spits sideways.
I was like, "Is it raining?"
It turns out he spat.
- He got so much better.
- Is that so?
He's laughing too.
Why is he laughing?
I'm laughing
because you're laughing.
How did his teeth get better
without getting braces?
Somehow that happened.
I was surprised.
Do you want to hear why he kneeled
in Bangbae-dong?
(Do you want to hear why he kneeled
in Bangbae-dong?)
He can hear us.
Do you want to hear it?
- Tell me.
- Yes.
He begged a woman not to leave.
- He begged her.
- A woman?
- Who was she?
He begged her not to leave.
Is it okay to tell them?
(Groaning)
(Laughing)
- What's wrong?
- Did you?
- He begged her not to leave.
- It's a painful story...
- that happened in Bangbae-dong.
- He went down on his knees.
- Bangbae-dong knee man.
- Yes.
I don't remember
whether it was him or not.
We asked women...
to have coffee with us
all night long.
- That's what we did at night.
- Yes.
After failing at 5 a.m.,
I couldn't believe myself.
I realized
I shouldn't live this way.
So I went to church and prayed.
- Really?
- With him.
It was you, right?
- It was you and Yong Man.
- It was Yong Man?
That's right.
You and Yong Man went to
a Catholic church.
- It wasn't you? You can hear me?
- I left before that.
Yes. I left before that.
I wasn't going to say this,
but you guys told me to go home.
Did I?
- Because we were uneven.
- Wait.
"Uneven."
Since when did you listen to us?
I think he started listening
from early on.
- No.
- It's over.
Next is Jong Kook.
Right. You should play
the latest music.
- That was hilarious.
- It's always "Ring Ding Dong."
Just play anything.
(The calm before the storm)
It's like the calm before the storm.
I have so much to say
about Jong Kook.
Can you give us like two hours?
You'll be surprised to hear...
- what I'm about to say.
- Just wait!
- I have put it on yet.
- Okay.
But he'll get in trouble
if I say this.
I can't wait to hear it.
Is it what happened
behind the camera?
He's trying to make us curious.
I'll stop after this.
- I wonder what it is.
- Is the music playing?
(The music is on.)
- It's playing.
- He can't hear us.
- Go.
- You may start.
- Hey, you fool. Can you hear me?
- Tell us.
- Can I really say this?
- Yes.
- What?
- Isn't it better to say this later?
- Tell us later.
- Is it about Eun Hye?
- Honestly...
- We...
- Did they date or not?
- I...
- I guess it's about Eun Hye.
- Unless it's about Eun Hye,
- I wouldn't talk so quietly.
- It's about Eun Hye.
You're talking about Eun Hye
from the start?
That's why I said
I'll talk about it later.
I knew it. It's about Eun Hye.
You're talking about Eun Hye
from the start?
(He figured what it's about.)
If we say Eun Hye, he can tell.
Let's call her apple.
- Apple?
- Are you scared?
- How about Hye Eun?
- Hye Eun.
- Change her name.
- I won't make this long.
- Hye Eun?
No.
Eun Hye texted me.
- Really?
(Twitching)
- I'll stop here.
What did she say?
- Will she come here?
- I can't tell the details.
Did she tell you...
- to stop talking about her?
- No.
- "I'll appear in Running Man."
- That's what I thought.
Did she say she'll say the truth?
I thought about it a lot
in case she gets mad at me.
- But she isn't like that.
- No?
I talked to her on the phone.
So what's the truth?
- Is it true?
- I can't tell you.
When things lighten up,
I'll tell you.
He's listening.
- Jae Suk.
- That punk...
Jae Suk.
(Flustered)
(Spiteful)
- Hey.
- Wait.
He was listening the whole time,
wasn't he?
- No. He doesn't know.
- Was he listening?
- I think he's listening.
- He hasn't pressed it yet.
He's guessing
by the shape of your mouth.
- Isn't he listening?
- He's listening.
- Yes. He's listening.
- Try.
- Is he listening?
- He's listening.
- He's listening. Look.
- Haha.
- He's listening.
- You say it.
- What?
Say, "You fool."
He probably can't hear me.
Are you that good at fights?
- He's listening.
- Meet me at the rooftop.
He can hear me. Gosh.
(He can hear me.)
- He can hear me.
- I think he pressed it.
He looked at me
when you said my name.
What are you looking at?
- You can't play soccer.
- Can he hear us?
(You can't play soccer.)
- He can hear us.
- Why do you act like you're good?
He can hear us. Look at his face.
- Can you hear me?
- His expression changed.
Can you hear me, Jong Kook?
(The bad son made a big mistake.)
Can you hear me?
- He can hear us.
- I think he can hear us.
- Can you hear me?
- See? He's listening.
Are you listening to us?
How can you make eye contact
with us?
Jong Kook. Hey.
My.
He can hear us.
- He can hear us.
Do you prefer me or Yoon Eun Hye?
(He laughs
at Ji Hyo's sudden question.)
He can hear us.
(Jong Kook can hear them.)
- Jong Kook. Never mind.
- See?
- Stop this.
- Let's stop.
"Do you prefer me or Yoon Eun Hye?"
He can hear us.
- Really?
- He can hear us.
- Ji Hyo. That was crazy.
- It's over.
- Hey.
- Wait.
I can't play soccer? Hey.
(This was expected.)
Hey. Look.
- You talked to her on the phone?
- He heard everything.
- No.
- He heard the whole thing.
- Did you talk to her on the phone?
- No.
You better watch what you say on TV.
- Okay.
- Will you?
- Hey.
- Yes.
- I'm good at fights.
- My goodness.
Fight is the only thing I'm good at.
- I'm well aware of it.
- Did he press it from the start?
- Yes, sir.
- Jae Suk.
- Did he press it from the start?
- Even if...
place last,
we already got everything.
- I'm sorry.
- Watch what you say.
What if people think it's true?
- I'll delete Eun Hye's number.
- Attention.
- I said, don't.
- I'll delete Eun Hye's number.
- Don't.
I haven't talked to her since.
I said it was nice to talk to her
and hung up.
I didn't talk to her about the show.
Don't. You should know when to stop.
- Yes.
- Know when to stop.
I apologized to Eun Hye,
and she said it was okay.
- Okay. Rest.
- Yes.
Yes, sir.
- Hey.
- You're the best fighter ever.
There's no rooftop here.
You're the best in the country.
From a thug to a grand award winner.
- Okay. Sit down.
- Thank you, sir.
Hey.
You're the Messi and the Ronaldo
of Tiger FC.
The king of soccer!
You never lose the ball.
Don't talk about soccer.
Just say I'm a terrible singer.
The best soccer player.
The best singer.
You're the best of all.
Sit down.
- You like Yoon Eun Hye.
- Hey.
- But...
- Don't do that.
- You too.
- Yes.
- Sit down.
- He heard everything.
- But how?
- He heard it from the start.
From the start?
He pressed it
as soon as he sat down.
- He pressed it right away.
- I heard the whole thing.
- His wife doesn't love him.
- Right.
(Then they started
talking about Suk Jin.)
- He's a beggar.
- Big nose?
- You're a beggar.
- Big nose.
- A better.
He's a beggar with big boogers.
You know Suk Jin is very stingy.
- He's stingy.
- I know.
- He's very narrow-minded.
- Right.
Time's up.
Hey, your facial
expression was great.
(He gets back at them.)
- What was I like?
- A beggar?
(The slander time is over.)
- He pressed it early.
- A beggar?
I'm curious about Jae Suk.
So the winner
of the last mission is...
(The winner
of the last mission is...)
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- Really?
- Am I included?
Suk Jin did it a lot.
And the second place is
Jae Suk and So Min.
Se Chan did a good job.
And the third place is
Jong Kook and Haha.
Okay. It's all right.
I'll give you the last scratchcards.
- We can do this.
- Let's do this.
All right. The mission...
So Min, why do you have so many?
- Hey, you have so many.
- How many cards do you have?
So Min is...
- I bet she wrote a lot about me.
- No.
Let's pick one.
- It's random.
- This time...
- I won't raise them.
- Jae Suk.
(Se Chan has a 50-percent chance.)
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk!
- Me?
- What? It's Haha.
I need Haha. It's Haha.
(Jae Suk won the lottery
with his 33-percent ticket.)
Haha!
That's amazing.
(Ji Hyo has
a 50-percent scratchcard.)
- She won.
- I won.
Now please count the money
you have in your bags.
And we will calculate
the money from scratchcards.
Tell us how much money
you have in total.
- I have 300 dollars.
- I have 330 dollars.
- I have 670 dollars.
- I have 50 dollars.
I have 324 dollars.
I have 534 dollars.
I have 781 dollars.
Guys, before we announce the result,
I'll let you exchange
your slander scratchcards for money.
- Okay.
- I'll let you exchange.
(They can turn the game around
with the slander scratchcards.)
Look.
Only 20 out of 100 tickets win.
But So Min is...
So Min is so mean.
That's not it. I didn't get
a single scratchcard today.
- You do have a lot of money.
- Three, four,
five, six, and seven.
I hope that counts too.
- Take this.
- She has seven cards.
I hope it counts.
(She wrote 8 pages of slanders.)
You're unbelievable.
- Here.
- I have two.
(They get scratchcards based on
the number of slanders they wrote.)
(This is what
Haha wrote about Se Chan.)
Ji Hyo wrote about Se Chan.)
It has a 20-percent chance.
Where should I get it?
(This is what
Jong Kook wrote about Se Chan.)
(If one of the scratchcards wins,
the ranks will change immediately.)
- What?
- Why?
I have two Jong Kook.
Really?
It's Jong Kook.
You won?
He's so lucky.
- I have three.
- I know. I never won.
- I'll take three.
- Give me them all at once.
Let me scratch them.
Darn it. It's a dud.
(So Min bet her everything
on the slander scratchcards.)
Is this worth 200 dollars?
- So Min didn't win.
- How many cards does she have?
(She can turn the game around
with the 8 scratchcards.)
- Are they all duds?
- She can turn the game around.
(Are they all duds?)
- They all are duds.
- I have two Jong Kook.
- Two Jong Kook.
- This is a dud.
You should be a nice person.
So Min has only one card left.
It must be a dud.
(So Min has
only one scratchcard left.)
(The last one of the 8 scratchcards)
(What is the result?)
It's a dud again!
(All the 8 cards are duds.)
(How unlucky)
You should be ready
to get the penalty today.
This is ridiculous.
All eight tickets are duds.
Really? All of them?
The first and second
will get the prize.
The first place is Jae Suk
with 670 dollars.
Am I the winner?
- You picked good cards.
- At the last minute.
The second place is Jong Kook
with 534 dollars.
(No. 1: Jae Suk, No. 2: Jong Kook)
- The prize.
- I was honest.
Those two will bet the prize.
The 5th is Ji Hyo with 300 dollars,
and the 6th is So Min
with 50 dollars.
So Min.
She scratched eight cards.
And Se Chan has 781 dollars.
My gosh.
I spent all my money.
I got 200 dollars...
and spent 500 dollars.
What is today's penalty?
We had the low-frequency
patches earlier today.
They should sing a song
with the patches on.
- The birthday song?
- Yes, the birthday song.
Se Chan has 781 dollars,
so the prize he's getting is...
- the beef set.
- Really?
Thank you.
Jae Suk who took first place
gets the pork set.
And Jong Kook gets the chicken set.
- Thank you.
- That's perfect.
Jong Kook likes chicken better.
- I like the prize.
- He likes it.
- The low-frequency patches.
- Please bring them in.
(The low-frequency patches are in.)
All the tickets
So Min got were duds.
- It's unbelievable.
- I thought one of them would win.
So Min got eight scratchcards.
That means she wrote
40 bad things about Se Chan.
How could she think of 40 things?
She got eight cards,
but they all were duds.
And I took first place twice.
- Really?
- It was a 50-percent chance.
But they were all duds.
Ji Hyo is feeling it.
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
- Ji Hyo is a good dancer.
- Are you happy?
They are feeling it.
This is exciting.
Good.
Start.
(Happy birthday to you)
- Happy birthday to you
- They use some vibrato.
(The low-frequency duo sings
"Happy Birthday" with vibrato.)
(The unlucky sisters' special
performance for Se Chan)
Show us the robot dance.
- The robot dance.
- Okay.
They should be
on "Street Woman Fighter."
(I've controlled Suk Jin
my whole life.)
(No. I'll convince him.)
Which cell am I?
(Top Star Suk Jin has six cells.)
(Suk Jin's Cells)
(Top Star Suk Jin's Day)
This is what G-DRAGON wears.
(The six cells try
to make Suk Jin a top star.)
(The cells recommend funny outfits
to make fun of him.)
(I've always wanted
to wear things like this though.)
(As soon as they encourage him,)
(he accepts it.)
(Top Star Suk Jin's Schedule)
(He starts his life as a celebrity
with the stars.)
(What's your bucket list
for the age of 60?)
(Donation!)
(Graduation of marriage)
(For 31 days...)
(Going to a beach in the nude.)
(Shut his mouth.)
(The six cells have occupied
his weak body.)
(He should pose as he's told.)
(And he should love his wife
as he's told.)
(Will Top Star
Suk Jin's day go well?)
(What's your secret
for your 2nd heyday?)
(Jae Suk.)
(Yoo Jae Suk!)
(Turn a mediocre star
into a top star.)
(Suk Jin's Cells)