(Sangam SBS)
(Bright lights that boast
a big production budget.)
(Welcome to Street Human Fighter.)
(Street Human Fighter)
(Street Humans are coming in.)
(Ordinary men and women in the
neighborhood are all dressed up.)
Make some noise!
(Groaning)
Why does it hurt?
I don't know.
(The little dancer is dressed up
in his dad's outfit.)
So Min, have you started already?
(What?)
(Judging from their moves, it looks
like they've never danced before.)
Gosh. Se Chan is
having a lot of fun.
So Min, did you start it already?
What's with the stage?
What is this stage for?
The stage...
(The do-rag man gets
more enthusiastic.)
Gosh, I hate that.
(The lady picks a fight
with everyone.)
(The stage of confusion)
Who is this guy? Who are you, sir?
Who are you, mister?
(The mysterious man dominates
the stage in disorder.)
Excuse me. Who is this guy?
What are you doing here, sir?
Sir.
- A diaper?
- Sir.
It's not a diaper.
Isn't this a diaper?
This is what people wear
in New York.
Song Yi recently lost hers.
My goodness.
- Sir.
- My gosh.
This is what people wear
in New York.
I guess he started
a diaper business.
He will do a diaper commercial soon.
What does it look
if you do the buttons?
- Suk Jin, I want to button it up.
- It will be embarrassing.
I'm not supposed to button it up.
- Let's just give it a try.
- Don't do that.
- Just once.
- Let's just do it.
- Hold his legs.
- I have to touch his bottoms.
Stop it.
- Let's just see.
- My goodness.
- What's wrong?
- It looks okay. It's hip.
It looks cool.
- This isn't right.
- Let me see.
It's not bad.
This is how it's supposed to look.
- This is better.
- It looks cool.
- This is how it's supposed to look.
- I know.
- You look a lot better now.
- This isn't right.
- Mr. Diaper.
- This looks strange.
- Are you a cactus or what?
- Are you going hiking?
- What are you talking about?
- You look just like last week.
This is all about hip hop.
- No, it's for hiking.
- That's mountain clothes.
Excuse me. Are you Toegye Yi Hwang?
Toegye Yi Hwang?
- Toegye Yi Hwang.
- Grandma.
- I'm not your grandma.
This is hip hop.
He's Woong's grandma.
- It looks like a grandma's wig.
- You think?
I think I saw you before.
- I see.
- I think I saw you...
at Juliana in the 1990s.
She looks like a dancer at Juliana.
She used to perform at Juliana.
- After a long time, So Min...
- I'm all dressed up.
It looks like...
she's wearing a Halloween costume.
No one can beat her.
That's right.
- I can dance better this way.
- So Min is...
We will get to see
a lot of So Min's dance moves today.
What is she doing?
Gosh, I can't watch it.
You know what? So Min
used to be an idol trainee.
She's different.
So she can dance.
- She's got the moves.
- She's not all bad.
She's not all bad.
- We read articles about today.
- Right.
- You know "Street Woman Fighter"?
- "Street Woman Fighter".
- That's amazing.
- Right.
We are going to have
the four leaders here.
They are really busy now.
- They are really busy now.
- Hang on. Ji Hyo...
- Do you know what it is?
- She knew "Squid Game".
Ji Hyo wanted to weigh in
when we talked about it.
- Right.
- But she's being quiet today.
- What?
- Everyone.
- Yes?
- You guys are...
at Street Fighter Club,
the shrine of K-pop dance...
(The born-to-be fighter dancers
who represent the street scene)
as the born-to-be fighter dancers
who represent the street scene.
(The born-to-be fighter dancers
who represent the street scene)
- Come on!
- I can be a street fighter.
- I don't dance.
- Please sit on the benches.
- The benches in the back.
- We will have a lot of fun today.
- Okay.
- It will be cool.
I'd like you to enjoy
the hip street culture today.
- Okay.
- Yes.
All right. We have
four global leaders...
who will guide you guys today.
(The 4 global leaders
who will teach them to dance)
- I'm so excited.
- Here's the first leader.
Please come on out.
(Shouting)
Who is it?
(The first leader is...)
(Honey J of HolyBang)
- Yes!
- All right!
She's here.
All right, Honey J!
- Honey J.
Honey J.
She's really cool, Se Chan.
Honey J!
I love you!
I love you, J!
Honey.
Look at her.
She's unbelievable. This is so cool.
(Carried away)
- Honey J!
Honey J!
She's amazing.
(Honey J is here to dominate
Running Man after winning "SWF".)
Honey J!
She is really cool.
She beat everyone.
- Hello.
- All right.
- I love your costume.
- You are the best.
- You're really cool.
- Honey J.
- She's the winner of "SWF".
She won? Is she the winner?
She's the dancer
of "Mommae" by Jay Park.
Right. "Mommae".
(Ugly twerking moves)
Honey J, this is "Mommae".
I learned "Mommae" from Honey J.
I look just like Honey J.
What's the same?
My goodness.
- Just go hiking.
- Look at my lower body.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I look just like her.
- Just go to Mount Maebong.
- Why would I go to Mount Maebong?
- Mister,
- are you a cactus or what?
- A cactus?
Are you a cactus?
He's a guy at the ticket office.
- All right.
- That was really cool.
Here's the second leader.
Please come on out.
Who is it?
(Who's the second leader
who will heat up the floor?)
Where is it?
- It's Aiki!
- Aiki!
(Aiki of Hook)
- Aiki.
- My goodness.
- She looks amazing.
She's so cute.
She's so bright.
You are so cool.
She's unbelievable.
This is exciting. I'm so thrilled.
Let's go!
Aiki!
(The leader of Hook
with cheerful energy, Aiki)
Hey, my sister. Hi, Aiki.
- Why is she your sister?
- She's my sister.
- Hey, my brother.
- Aiki.
(Mr. Diaper wants to be
friends with Aiki.)
You're so cool.
- Hey.
- Aiki.
I've missed you.
- She's so cute.
- Seriously,
along with Honey J,
she's one of the busiest dancers...
- in Korea now.
- She's the busiest one.
- No one can beat her.
- She's matchless.
She's making a lot of money now.
- It's unbelievable.
- What are you talking about?
Were you with her?
That's all I want.
- It's all about money.
- Were you with her?
You're a money hugger.
Show me the money!
- Show me the money!
- Yes.
Who's next?
Here's the third leader.
- Yes!
- This is so exciting.
Look at Se Chan.
(The third leader who will
make them fall for dance is...)
Who is it?
Lee Jung!
- She looks so charismatic.
- Lee Jung!
- Hey, Lee Jung!
- She's crazy.
Lee Jung!
- Lee Jung!
YGX!
She's fabulous.
She's so cool!
That's amazing.
I want to dance like her.
Me too.
(They can't hold back from dancing.)
She's unbelievable.
I told you.
This is fantastic.
(The youngest leader
of YGX, Lee Jung)
- Lee Jung!
- That was wonderful.
- That was amazing.
- Lee Jung!
- Lee Jung.
- Welcome.
- You're the best.
- Come over here.
(Lee Jung's fan meeting
has started.)
You are so cool.
(The guy from an alpine club
is really excited.)
- This is really...
- She's unbelievable.
- She's snazzy.
- She's fabulous.
It's early in the morning,
but she got her hair done already.
- Did you go to a beauty shop?
- Yes.
- I slept only an hour.
- My goodness.
That's amazing.
(Look at me.)
- Stop being so frivolous.
- What are you doing?
- My gosh.
- He loves them.
He's being so annoying today.
- It's because of them.
- What was that?
- That's enough.
- Do you think you're on their team?
- We're a team.
- You know what?
Haha looks like...
a retired hip-hop musician.
He's a retired hip-hop musician
who runs a store in Hongdae.
What are you talking about
dressed like that?
You're wearing a diaper!
You looked very...
- serious yesterday.
- You looked gentle yesterday.
- What did he do?
- What did you do yesterday?
- The gala show.
- What did you do yesterday.
- He was the MC.
- He hosted the gala show.
- Was he the MC?
- Yes.
I went there because I was paid.
You did it for money.
How much did you get? Chicken feed?
(How much did you get?
Chicken feed?)
He got 300 dollars.
- He got 300 dollars.
- Only 300?
Ms. Juliana is very humorous.
- Juliana.
- Juliana?
We have...
Juliana and her boyfriend here.
- All right!
- He's a grandma.
- Yes!
- I see.
- He's just a grandma.
- It's too shiny.
- All right.
The last leader is
Haha's best friend.
- Right.
- They are very close.
- Yes!
- Really?
- PROWDMON.
- All right.
Here's our last leader.
- Who is it?
- Here's the fourth leader.
Please come on out.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Who is it?
My goodness.
- Hey.
- Who is it?
- She's the oldest leader here.
- The oldest one?
She does look like a captain.
- She's also a professor.
- She's a professor.
My goodness.
It's like...
- What is she doing?
- I wonder how she'd look.
(Monika of PROWDMON)
How is she coming out?
There she is.
- My goodness.
- It's like a play.
She plays with music.
She's a professor.
She's so graceful.
She does play with music.
(She makes eye contact
with each member with her dance.)
Professor.
(She makes eye contact
with each member with her dance.)
She's beautiful.
She's going to Jong Kook.
- She's so cool.
- She really is.
She looks so graceful.
- He dances along.
- He's a retired hip-hop musician.
This is so cool.
This is amazing.
It's elegant.
She is elegant.
(Soft and light)
(I was worn down)
(I've been
hiding away all this time)
(You dance so freely)
(She describes the lyrics
with her dance moves.)
That was beautiful.
All together.
From the right.
- Are we supposed to sing?
- Your hand.
(They enjoy
the performance together.)
Left hand.
(Yi Hwang from Dongducheon
ruins it with the air trumpet.)
Both hands.
(Monika brings them together
into one.)
This is nice.
(Monika brings them together
into one.)
Shall we give a bow together?
(Shall we give a bow together?)
I love it. She's a teacher.
- She's a teacher.
- A teacher.
- Ms. Monika.
- Monika!
- Hello.
- She's Monika.
- You're so cool.
- That was amazing.
Like I said earlier,
they turned
the whole country on its head,
but there are people
who didn't watch their show.
- Right.
- Isn't that right?
- Sure.
- It can happen. So...
I'd like to tell you honestly.
Some of our members...
didn't watch your show.
- I see.
- That's true.
Among the members here?
- Among us?
- You know,
"Squid Game" is very popular now,
but some of us
haven't watched it yet.
- Right.
- That's true.
And some of us text me back
like a week later.
- It happens.
- Right.
Even though...
some of our members
didn't watch your show,
they will definitely...
fall for your charm today.
- You just watched the opening.
- That was crazy.
This is how
I'd like to address them.
In a word, they are
the best dancers in Korea.
Exactly.
And not just in Korea.
- They are global dancers.
- The best dancers in the world.
- They raised our nation's status.
- Some of them won first place...
- at international contests.
- They represent our country.
I watched it.
You won an international contest
with a tall girl.
- That's right.
- You were a duo.
- You won third place, right?
- Right.
- I saw you a lot too.
- Where?
On TikTok.
Oh, right.
- Yes!
- Brother!
Yes, my brother!
His video is always
in the recommended section.
- Right.
- He's TikTok Grandpa.
TikTok Grandpa?
He's famous on TikTok.
First, about Honey J...
Her real name is Jeong Ha Nee.
So she's called Honey J.
- Jeong Han...
- Jeong Ha Nee.
I see. Jeong Ha Nee.
- Jeong Ha Nee...
- What?
- Is it Jeong Ha Nee?
- Yes.
That sounds like a foreign name.
- What?
- Ha Nee.
Which means a west wind.
- It's a pure Korean word.
- Is it a Korean word?
- Is that your real name?
- Yes, it is.
- Your mom is...
- It's Ha Nee.
Your dad got you a nice name.
- My mom gave me the name.
- Your mom...
Excuse me.
This will be broadcast nationally.
Ha Nee. Jeong Ha Nee.
- Will you stop talking?
- Jeong Ha Nee. Honey J.
(The local MC is hosting
his own show.)
Actually,
Honey J coined
a lot of famous quotes...
- in "Street Woman Fighter".
- She did.
Monika too.
They are like quote makers.
- I see.
- My gosh.
- What did they say?
- Those who didn't watch the show...
seem very nervous now.
They are afraid
if you'd ask them about it.
- I think I know who they are.
- They're afraid.
- You know why I'm sitting here.
- A few of us...
(Quiet)
- I'm here to help them.
- have shaky eyes.
- These three.
They look like
they're walking on eggshells.
- I see.
- I know what it is.
- Famous quotes?
- They are learning today.
I bet you've heard of this before.
- What?
- "Watch closely."
"This is a fight
between big sisters."
It was on the previews.
He engages only in real fights.
We fight without talking.
It's better to get a head start.
I'm not supposed to talk.
This is my second time
to meet with Honey J.
When you see her dance,
- she comes across as tough.
- She looks tough.
- But she's not like that.
- I know.
All the dancers
on "Street Woman Fighter"...
- They all are like crybabies.
- are like that.
It looks as if they would fight...
as soon as the cameras
are turned off, but...
I know. They all look really tough.
We're just like them.
It looks like we fight a lot,
- but we are actually close friends.
- But some of us actually fought.
- Isn't that true?
- Some of us.
He never loses a fight.
- We had some conflicts.
- Right.
Just a little conflict.
- It's no big deal.
- We've been together for 11 years.
- It can happen.
- It's inevitable.
- Sure.
- Suk Jin got mad like two times.
It did happen.
I wasn't going to see
Haha ever again.
Oh, right.
Didn't you have a fight, Haha?
Haha, you had a little trouble
with Jong Kook.
- No.
- No?
(Haha, you had a little trouble
with Jong Kook.)
(Actually, something happened
while shooting the last episode.)
- It's not like that.
- We can't call it trouble.
- Why?
- It was a misunderstanding.
It was just a misunderstanding.
(They were mad at each other
for a while for something childish.)
We can't call it trouble.
Haha was scolded by Jong Kook.
You guys are so close now.
- It was a misunderstanding.
- A misunderstanding?
I was surrounded by cameras,
and I had to do this.
(Unfortunately, they had to
clear it up in front of cameras.)
"I'm sorry."
Oh, no.
He got scolded by Jong Kook.
Okay.
All right.
Monika runs a large dance academy.
- Her business is going really well.
- Of course.
- And...
- Oh, she's a mogul?
- Absolutely.
- She rakes in the money in Hongdae.
- She's absolutely a mogul.
- Is she?
And Lee Jung teaches
at the academy too.
- She's an instructor.
- That's right.
- Oh, really?
- Honey J teaches there too.
- We both teach there.
- Honey J too?
- Honey J teaches there too.
- Yes.
I see that she's a mogul.
After "Street Woman Fighter",
some fans formed a club...
called People Seeking to be Scolded
by Monika.
- Yes. It's called PSM as well.
- Right.
- I scolded others on the show.
I know that.
I guess people found it charming.
Indeed. You looked so cool.
So some people said
that if I scolded them,
they could pass
a civil service exam...
- or succeed in losing weight.
- It'd help them get it together.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
- They want her to scold them.
- Yes. Some people said that.
- Rather than being scolded by her,
- How does she scold others?
I recommend you get scolded
by Jong Kook.
- It'd help you stay alert.
- Jong Kook can be scary.
- He'd drive you bonkers.
- True.
He wouldn't stop.
Monika would scold you once,
and that'd be it.
- But Jong Kook wouldn't stop there.
- It'd last for a year.
He would keep scolding you
until you make progress.
- Am I right, Jong Kook?
- Yes. I'd never give up.
- Only if I care about that person.
- Of course.
Anyway, it's the same
for all our guests,
but especially Lee Jung...
choreographed many famous songs.
- Which ones?
- True.
They're like superstars
to us TV celebrities.
- Thank you for saying that.
- It's true.
Did you watch
"Street Woman Fighter"?
Yes, I did.
I watched the show.
He's not talking about "The Smurfs".
- Of course, I watched the show...
- Not "The Smurfs".
like all others in the country.
- Then do you know...
- "The Smurfs"?
the names of their dance teams?
- Their team names?
- Yes.
- YGX.
- Correct. What's Monika's?
Monika X.
- Don't they have an X at the end?
- At least add "Y" instead of "X".
- What's about mine?
- Honey X and Aiki X.
- My goodness.
- This is not "X-Man".
- I apologize on his behalf.
- "X-Man"?
(Suk Jin is seriously brazen.)
Anyway, since we're talking
about it,
Lee Jung, can you show us
a few of the dances you made?
- Sure thing.
- Great.
- Yes, I made that move.
- The dance moves she created.
- Let's give her a big hand.
- Yes!
(The hit song choreographer
Lee Jung's show time)
- Here we go.
- Yes.
She even walks like she's dancing.
- This is an amazing choreography.
- Absolutely.
- Watch her facial expressions.
- It's incredible.
She's amazing.
We should see her face.
I'll watch the show when it's aired.
(After warming up her body
with a powerful dance,)
(she goes straight to the climax.)
She's really good.
- Don't you just love her dance?
- Yes.
(This is how the choreographer
of the songs dances.)
- She moves her body so skillfully.
- Indeed.
- I'm impressed.
- It was amazing.
How does she dance like that?
I really love you guys.
All four of you.
She moves her body so skillfully
and freely.
Ji Hyo keeps saying
that she'll learn to dance.
- Right.
- She wants to go to her academy.
Then I think... Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- Since the teachers are all here,
why don't you try to dance
to ITZY's song that she danced to...
- in your own style?
- Just go with your own flow.
Go with your own flow.
- She's Songzy.
- She's a good dancer.
Her stage name is Songzy.
- Songzy.
- Drop the beat!
- Ji Hyo knows some dance moves.
- That's right.
- She's improved a lot.
- True.
- She's interested in dance.
- She improved gradually.
- Oh, my. Look at her moves.
- She's starting to feel the rhythm.
Her moves are great.
She's about to do
the shoulder dance.
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Dancing)
She's doing it right.
(Exclaiming)
(Wriggling)
(I can't watch this.)
Isn't this right?
That's not bad at all.
(She interpreted the dance
in her own style.)
She's dancing really well so far.
That's great.
Look how she moves her shoulders.
This is crazy.
- Isn't this right?
- You're doing it right.
You're doing great.
- Ji Hyo, I think that's enough.
- I'm out of breath.
- It's okay. You did great.
- Wasn't it for a drinking game?
- It's time for evaluation.
- Let's hear what our guests think.
- Let's do that.
- They'll evaluate her dance.
- First of all... Can I go first?
- Yes. Please go ahead.
I really liked her performance.
As soon as the music was played,
from the first beat,
she danced right on beat.
- From the first beat?
- Yes.
- One, two, three, four. Like this.
- She danced on beat?
She's just trying to
make more money.
- That's not it.
- She's a dance mogul.
- That's not true. Let me finish.
- Hey!
- After the first four beats,
- Show some respect.
I thought she moved to simple beats
as beginners usually do,
but she subdivided the beats.
One and two. Three and four.
You see, that shows...
- that she has...
- Thank you.
such a good sense of rhythm.
- She's such a smooth talker.
- I knew it.
She has a good sense of rhythm.
I bet she listens to music often.
Next up is the leader of YGX...
- Lee Jung.
- She did a good job.
First of all, I'm the one
who made the dance.
It's amazing that she could copy
the dance right away.
My gosh. They're all in on this.
- Come on.
- They want to have it all.
Use some professional lingo.
You have a well-balanced body.
- I see how she signed with them.
- Exactly.
- Your upper and lower body...
- No wonder.
- are very well-proportioned.
- That was funny.
- She's good at doing isolation.
- "Isolation"?
- She's very good at it.
- Yes.
- Indeed.
- She has a good sense of rhythm.
- That's so funny.
- They're hilarious.
- However...
They're all great dancers,
but they have different viewpoints.
- Let's hear what Aiki thinks.
- She's the master...
of short-form content.
What do you think
of her dance, Aiki?
She has a similar dance style
to someone I like.
- Who?
(The dance style of someone
that Aiki likes?)
My mom.
Her mother?
(She saw some of her mother's
moves while Ji Hyo was dancing.)
I like her honesty.
Her dance performance reminded me
of my mom's dance.
I see what you mean.
That's a good one.
- I bet she's good at isolation too.
- She danced like Aiki's mother.
The next person to dance is
quite good at dancing.
- She's almost a pro.
- She learned to dance.
- She's a pro among us.
- Don't say that.
- She used to be a trainee.
- That's not true.
- She's a good dancer.
- I'm excited.
- So...
- That's not true.
- She actually came here to compete.
- No. That's not true.
- She's ready to compete with you.
- She's determined.
- Come on.
- She's determined to win.
- She's ready for a dance battle.
- She's a good dancer.
But her biggest weakness is
the weird dance style of her own.
- Look at her outfit.
- Is that so?
- She can't seem to change it.
- But she's talented in our eyes.
She's so good at dancing.
But I'm really embarrassed
to dance in front of them.
- You know this dance, right?
- I've seen her dance before.
- Just do it as you do before us.
- Please play something upbeat.
Director, please add some lights
for So Min just like the guests.
- Are you ready?
- What?
- Drop the beat.
- Show them what you've got.
- All right.
- Oh, yes.
("Hey Mama", the legendary
performance from SWF)
David Guetta.
(She starts dancing
as if she prepared for this.)
I can't watch this.
I bet she prepared for this.
This is so embarrassing.
(Sudden twerking)
(Toegye Yi Hwang hates
the sight of it.)
(The dancing queen continues
dancing in her own style.)
This is embarrassing.
This is hilarious.
(She's cleaning the stage.)
This is utterly embarrassing.
(She's going too far
as she's out of dance moves.)
That's enough. So Min.
(Stop it, So Min.)
- Drag her out.
- So Min.
- This is driving me nuts.
- "Stop it."
- I sincerely apologize.
- "We're all going to die..."
- "at this rate."
- I'm sorry you had to see that.
- Did you see her legs?
- Yes.
- I can't believe what I just saw.
- You saw that, right?
- That was shocking.
- Oh, my.
Everything else was okay.
But this move was shocking.
(Her twerking dance was shocking.)
I thought she needed to
go number two.
It wasn't like that. My body didn't
move as I wanted it to move.
- That wasn't what I wanted to do.
- She danced like this.
Before we hear your comments,
let's watch her dance
to ITZY's song.
- So Min...
- All right.
- ITZY's song?
- prepared something for today.
- I didn't.
- Dance to ITZY's song.
- Ji Hyo did their signature moves.
- How...
- Okay.
- Don't do twerking again.
Just don't do that.
- Go to the restroom first.
- Just...
- Just don't do that.
- I'll kill you if you do it again.
- I'll trample on you.
- Don't do this, okay?
- Don't do it.
- I'll kick you like this.
- Go back to your seat.
- Don't do it.
- Stay quiet.
- Don't you dare.
- Just move your shoulders.
- They're just joking.
- So Min, be confident.
- So Min, just move your shoulders.
Since I'm dressed like a dancer,
I feel more confident.
- You really are a great dancer.
- So Min, we'll play ITZY's song.
- You're the best, So Min.
- This is great.
- You've got this.
- You can do this.
Are you ready? Drop the beat.
Let's go!
("Wannabe" by ITZY,
choreographed by Jeon So Min)
- Your facial expression matters...
- She'll add her own moves.
- in the beginning.
- She'll do something funny.
She turned around.
- So Min, face the camera.
- Oh, my.
(She's charismatic enough to give up
on getting a close-up shot.)
So Min, move to the front.
- It's time.
- You should go now.
- Do the shoulder dance.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
The shoulder dance.
(She starts doing
the shoulder dance easily.)
(Suddenly, she starts dancing
in her own style.)
Stick to the original dance.
Move your shoulders.
(She barely continues performing
with her own cheesy dance moves.)
(But she begins to repeat
her dance moves again.)
- That's great. Keep going.
- Oh, my.
- I told you she was good.
- No. Stop.
(She's twerking again.)
(The dance control squad
quickly stopped her.)
- Great job, So Min.
- That was so hilarious.
That was great.
- I really liked your performance.
- Let's hear what they think.
- We should do that.
- Yes.
- It was so funny.
- We're going to hear...
what you guys think.
- Okay. Professor, you go first.
- So Min is a great dancer.
As for the technical aspects
of her performance,
her shoulder dance looked great
because of her bone structure.
Her move was smooth and beautiful.
She's such a smooth talker.
She can convince anyone
to enroll in a dance class.
- People would be convinced.
- At least for three months.
- Three months.
- That's a great comment.
- They'd pay in advance.
- That's great.
Next, let's hear
what Lee Jung thinks.
(Lee Jung doesn't seem to know
what to say.)
- She doesn't know what to say.
- Exactly.
First of all, she's so pretty.
She's really pretty and tall.
- She has lean, long arms and legs.
- She has nothing to say.
- Say something about her dance.
- And her outfit is so pretty too.
You talked about "isolation" before.
To be honest, I saw some moves...
- that unexpectedly inspired me.
- Really?
- Her dance inspired you?
- Yes.
She just lied around on the floor.
- Are you sure?
- Really?
Could you please elaborate?
I got inspiration from her dance.
I could tell that she pretended
she was open-minded,
but she was actually
quite conservative.
- Oh, my.
- That's true.
- That's unbelievable.
- She could tell that?
- I can't believe it.
- How did you know?
I figured it out from a single move.
- Which one?
- When she did this move...
The pooping move?
Yes, the pooping move.
- We keep our legs straight.
- I see.
But she crossed her legs like this.
(Shy)
(She crossed her legs
while doing a sexy dance move.)
- How did you notice it? Amazing.
- I didn't even know that.
- Like this.
- I'm impressed.
She saw every detail
of the dance moves.
How did you notice it?
- She's incredible.
- How did she know?
- She crossed her legs like this.
- She's the best.
- I read her mind.
- You read her mind.
How did she read my mind
based on a dance move?
I guess it's something
you can't hide.
- I guess so.
- She expressed herself.
- Your dance shows your personality.
- That's true.
- We can see through you.
- I'm amazed.
May I have your attention, please?
Today,
the four leaders of
the best dance crews in the world...
will join the seven average humans.
It's Street Human Fighter.
(Street Human Fighter)
It's true that we're
average humans, but...
- It's SHF, not SWF.
- Street Human Fighter.
Through fierce
and ruthless competition,
we'll decide
the number one dance crew today.
(The number 1 dance crew will be
decided today.)
All right. Let's go!
(Everyone including Thug Dancer...)
(and Toegye Yi Hwang
will compete with one another.)
- I'm excited.
- I want to win.
- Me too. It's going to be a war.
- Okay.
The four guests will be
the leaders...
of the four dance crews
that you'll form.
After each mission ends,
the crews in 3rd and 4th places
will have a dance battle...
and receive different numbers
of penalty badges.
(They will receive penalty badges
according to the result.)
The winning crew will receive...
the trophy and amazing prizes.
(The winning crew will get
the trophy and prizes.)
The prizes must be amazing.
We prepared expensive prizes.
- Really?
- Oh, my.
Meanwhile, the crew in bottom place
with the most penalty badges...
- will get a penalty at the end.
- Of course.
(The crew in bottom place will
get a penalty.)
There will be only one crew...
to get the trophy
and prizes tonight.
Which crew will obtain...
the title of the number one
street dance crew?
- What?
- Ready. Fight.
- What was that?
- "Ready. Fight."
Did you just imitate Kang Daniel?
- What was that?
- "Ready. Fight."
- Should we call you Choi Daniel?
- I guess you wanted to look cool.
- What was that?
All right.
It's time to form the crews.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- We prepared 7 sets of 4 cards.
- Okay.
Each of you will show the card
of the crew you want to join.
If more than 2 people pick the same
crew, the leader chooses 2 of them.
They will pick one of us,
not the other way around?
- We choose first.
- We need to be chosen.
No. I don't like this.
- I have to wait to be chosen again.
- You see...
- There's a dance style I pursue.
- I like all of them too.
- Oh, no.
- Although I'm close to her,
I'll stick to my preference.
- You have your own style?
- Yes.
You never know.
- Haha.
- Wait. I haven't made my choice.
Lift up one of the cards. One.
- Hold on. I haven't decided yet.
- Two.
If you can't decide, just leave.
- Just give me a second.
- "Just leave."
Time's up. One, two, three.
(Lee Jung's crew)
Lee Jung.
- He's acting like a 20 something.
- Here he goes again.
- My gosh.
- He's acting like a younger man.
That old fossil wants to pretend
to be a younger man.
- I can't believe him.
- I hate it when he acts like that.
I'll choose the crew to join.
One, two, three.
- Oh, my.
- Lee Jung's crew.
(Workout Dancer chose
Lee Jung's crew as well.)
- My goodness.
- Next up is Ji Hyo.
- I choose Aiki's crew.
- Aiki's crew.
- Mom.
- She called me "Mom".
- Aiki will have a hard time.
- Okay.
- She called Ji Hyo "Mom".
I wanted to join Aiki's crew too,
but now that she joined the crew...
Why?
- I want to learn to dance properly.
- Monika's crew!
I grunted unintentionally.
"Oh, gosh."
It'll be a long day for you.
- Probably.
- It's my turn. I choose Honey J.
(Jae Suk chose Honey J's crew.)
- Honey J!
- Her "Mommae" dance is my style.
- Her "Mommae" dance.
- That's cool.
- I like her dance style.
- I love your body
I chose Honey J's crew.
I choose Honey J too.
(So Min chose Honey J's crew too.)
- She'll teach you properly.
- She picked Honey J's crew.
- Now, it's Toegye Yi Hwang's turn.
- It's hard to decide.
"Toegye Yi Hwang"?
Which crew do you punks think
I will choose?
- That's funny.
- Se Chan is a good dancer too.
- He's a good dancer too.
- Indeed.
I mean, he used to perform
on "SBS Inkigayo".
Don't say that.
- Okay. I choose Monika's crew.
- That's true.
(Se Chan chose Monika's crew.)
All right. We'll begin
the first round now.
(So the crews have been formed.
Now, Round 1 will begin.)
Don't we have to change our clothes?
- You have to change your clothes.
- Okay.
Se Chan is getting on my nerves
by dancing.
- Why is that so annoying?
- Come on. Bring it on.
- What is he doing?
- You see, actually...
- Honey J...
- Yes.
I was aware of her condition.
She wasn't feeling well
before we began the shoot.
- And her condition got worse.
- Yes.
- Although she wanted to go on,
- That's right.
but we thought that she should
go home to rest.
- Her health is more important.
- So I hope you can understand her.
- We all do.
- Yes.
- Health must come first.
- Absolutely.
- Of course.
- That's why she left.
It's not that serious though.
So please don't worry too much.
Honey J felt bad about leaving...
- without finishing the shoot.
- That's right.
Don't worry, Honey J.
And we hope you get well soon.
Get well soon.
Then should we join another team?
I was going to replace Honey J
as Honey Jae Suk.
- Honey Jae Suk?
- No way.
- You're not on their level.
- I was going to replace her.
- Aiki's crew has only one member...
- Right. You should join her crew.
Who should join her crew?
- Jae Suk, you join her crew.
- I should, right?
- Then I'll join Aiki's crew.
- That sounds reasonable. Okay.
Aiki, you have
the right to reject him.
- Pardon?
- She can reject you.
- Aiki can reject him.
- That's great.
- Do I have the right to refuse?
- Yes, of course.
You have the right to reject me.
Then let me decide
after So Min chooses her new crew.
Okay.
If she chooses Aiki's crew,
Aiki will have to choose between us.
I don't think So Min was going to
join Aiki's crew.
- Aiki.
- Oh, I see.
One, two, three.
I choose Aiki's crew.
(So Min chose Aiki's crew as well.)
All right. It's up to you.
Aiki, please pick one of them.
Well, I'm personally acquainted
with Hye In, so even if she...
Don't drop the honorifics.
She's our dance teacher.
- Hye In and I call each other.
- Be respectful to her.
- Hye In is Aiki's real name.
- Yes.
- I choose...
- Yes. Go ahead.
I...
- value actions more than words.
- Right.
- Instead of the talkative Jae Suk,
- Yes.
I'll choose So Min.
(She chose So Min.)
We'll show the power of women.
- That's great.
- Women can do it!
- The power of women!
- That's funny.
- That's really funny.
- He got rejected.
He's pretending that he's okay.
- He's upset.
- He's hiding his feeling.
- Nice, Aiki!
- That's funny.
- Hey.
- She hates a man who's all talk.
- That was good.
- Let me just...
- Aiki is really funny.
It's not because of her choice.
I'm just feeling hot.
How about you form a one-person team
as Honey Jae Suk?
- I don't want to.
- What do you say?
- Jae Suk, you said...
- Right?
- that you wanted to join my crew.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- I remember that.
But in her crew...
I mean, I really like Lee Jung,
- Look who are sitting on her sides.
- but on her sides,
those two are...
- We can have four members.
- Exactly.
I really want to join her crew.
- Then...
- Okay.
- I'll join Monika's crew.
- Join our crew.
Monika, will you accept him?
- Well... I will...
- Yes?
- accept him. Join us, you poor man.
- Okay.
- Monika!
- It's better than joining them.
Hellucca, Monika.
(Hellucca, Monika.)
- Before we begin the first round...
- Yes.
As you know, all the contestants
on SWF had unique stage names.
The seven members have to decide
their stage names before we begin.
- Sounds fun.
- Okay.
Come up with your stage names.
We need a stage name as a dancer.
- Names that end with "Jung"?
- Sounds great.
- Like my name Lee Jung...
- I'll go by Velvet Dress Ok Jung.
That's a great name.
I'll go by Gym Jung.
(Lee Jung's crew: Velvet Dress Ok Jung,
Lee Jung, Gym Jung)
I hate his name Honey Jae Suk.
Your name is Get Off Work Yi Hwang.
- I'm Ai-dol.
- Come on.
- It should be Dol-ai as in lunatic.
- Maybe that's her intention.
Let me explain
about the first round...
- of this ruthless competition.
- Okay.
It's No Respect Underdog Quiz.
- I'll show no respect.
- No Respect Underdog Quiz.
The leader of each crew will
take turns competing.
And they'll point out an underdog
on each of the other crews.
The 3 players including the 2
that a leader chose...
- will have a quiz contest.
- A quiz contest?
That is, when it's Monika's turn,
she has to pick one
from each of the other crews.
- Got it.
- Yes.
There will be only three rounds.
I want to compete with Aiki
and Get Off Work Yi Hwang.
- Okay.
- I'm up for competing with anyone.
Listen to the question.
The first one to press the buzzer
gets to answer.
You get five points
if you get the question right.
- Five points?
- Great.
If you don't know
the correct answer,
- pick up the battle sign.
- I see.
If 2 or more out of the 3 players
pick up the sign,
Name Tag Elimination begins
right away.
- Name Tag Elimination?
- I see.
- Not a dance battle?
- If you take off a name tag,
- you get two points.
- Okay.
I'll probably pick up the sign
every time I play.
(They can get points even if they're
not good at quizzes.)
I'll pick up the sign
no matter what.
One more thing. In order to make
Name Tag Elimination fair,
we'll replace the guys' names tags
with larger ones.
- Okay.
- Please replace them now.
Then we'll have a chance.
- But I lost when I had a small one.
- It's really big.
The first leader to play is...
Lee Jung.
- All right!
- Lee Jung!
- She's so cool.
Lee Jung, please choose one person
that you think is an underdog...
from each of the other crews.
Point that person
and say, "I choose you."
The person that I think
is an underdog is...
- Go ahead.
- Come on.
(Come on!)
If she watched Running Man often,
she would know...
who the Empty Heads are.
(There are a few easy choices.)
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang, Empty Head!)
- We're all powerhouses here.
- There are a few empty heads.
I'll first choose
Get Off Work Yi Hwang.
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang
from Monika's crew.)
All right.
Look at him.
- Okay!
- Next,
I'll choose Ai-dol.
All right, bring it on.
Yes, okay. She chose Ai-dol.
Come on!
Get Off Work Yi Hwang, are you good?
- Unbelievable.
- Go, Lee Jung.
The first category...
- is a quiz on people
- Okay, you've got this.
- People!
- You'll see the photos...
of two people...
and guess their names.
- Goodness.
- You can do this.
You'll see one from either side.
Oh, no.
- Round one.
- Give us a foreigner.
Losing against them
means you hit rock bottom.
Must you put it like that?
- Good luck.
- Let's go!
Round one.
Go!
(The photos of round one)
Of course, you know them.
Three, two...
- Audrey Hepburn.
- No!
That's not her.
She...
- Please keep quiet.
- She's about my age.
- I know who they are.
- I don't know who she is.
- You can't give them any clues.
- I only know the movie.
- You don't know her?
- Then the other one...
- I don't know her.
- Yes, but no.
- You know them, but not her?
Isn't she Audrey Hepburn?
- No.
- Of course not.
I have never seen her in my life.
- Really?
- Never.
- It's understandable.
- She's about my age now.
Really?
But I haven't seen her before.
Se Chan and So Min should know her.
Of course, they should.
All I remember is the movie.
Let me answer.
Demi Moore.
And the two on the right.
The Wright brothers.
- Okay!
- Nice!
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang is correct.)
He got this right?
(Roaring)
(He celebrates on
his invisible motorcycle.)
Guys, let's go.
Come on!
(A delighted Honey Jae Suk
gets on behind him.)
(They run wild
only after one round.)
This is great.
- Okay.
- I'm shocked.
I knew the Wright brothers.
It wasn't even hard.
Monika's crew
is in the lead with five points.
I can't believe Empty Head
scored big time.
Show them some trending celebrities.
- Here are the next photos.
- If you don't know...
Them...
Who's that guy?
Isn't he...
- Just shout out names.
- Think Europe.
- Shout out the names you know.
- He's...
You know...
I am sure you know who they are.
Who is that on the left?
Is he Steve Jobs?
- He...
- Just shout out any name.
Isn't he a very famous tailor?
- Who could it be?
- Just shout out names.
Oh, I know.
Here's your clue.
- He's in the film industry.
- That's right.
- Aren't I right?
- Okay.
- Yes, that's right.
Steven Stielberg.
- What?
- Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
- Who's Steven Stielberg?
- Isn't that his name?
Was he wrong?
- Stielberg.
- It's not Stielberg.
- Steven...
Steven Spielberg...
and Shakespeare.
What is Shakespeare's full name?
You need to know that?
He's Shakespeare.
- He...
- Shakespeare.
- How about Wolfgang?
- What is it?
- Give the full name.
- Full name?
Let me answer. Steven...
- Stielberg.
- Incorrect.
Seriously?
Jung will answer.
Steven Spielberg...
and Wolfgang Shakespeare.
She actually said, Wolfgang!
Seriously?
- Is that wrong?
- She heard you earlier.
- I was only kidding.
- Is that wrong?
- That's Mozart's name.
- Come on!
- I was trying to confuse So Min.
Who is Bolbbalgan?
Bolbbalgan?
- Se Chan.
- Did you hear him just now?
Bolbbalgan Shakespeare.
He said Bolbbalgan.
Bolbbalgan?
Didn't you say it was Wolfgang?
- What's his full name?
- I have no idea.
- Do you need a clue?
- Yes.
Give us the first letter.
- It starts with a W.
- W!
- Then I'm right.
- Let me answer.
William Shakespeare.
She heard you.
- She heard you.
- That's too bad.
Unbelievable.
- It's coming to me now.
- W!
I can't believe that
the young Lee Jung...
thought Wolfgang
was the right answer.
She was fooled.
- I had no idea.
- You shouldn't have said it.
- This was a minefield.
- I had no idea.
Isn't Wolfgang
a name of a steakhouse?
I can't believe
she stepped on that mine.
Just so you know,
Ji Hyo and Aiki...
weren't saying a thing.
Why aren't you helping her?
They must be a stickler for rules.
Is this because
you don't know the rules?
- We're not supposed to help.
- That's right.
Go, Ai-dol!
- Ai-dol is in last place.
- You can do this.
- Okay!
- Oh, no.
- So Min is in last place.
- Go, Ai-dol!
The next category is...
Chinese idioms.
Nice. Are we supposed
to say what they mean?
You'll see two Chinese idioms...
- which you'll read.
- Se Chan,
- you've been studying up.
- Here we go.
You studied these.
- You studied these.
Of course, they don't know this.
- I'm clueless right now.
- Don't you know these?
- These...
- This one's easy.
They're both easy.
(Yelling)
That wouldn't be ilseokyijo.
There's no "yi."
I know one of them.
- Go ahead then.
- Ilseokyijo...
and namnambuknyeo.
One of them is wrong.
Ilsacheonri...
and namnambuknyeo.
(Ilsacheonri, Namnambuknyeo)
(Se Chan is correct once again.)
- You...
- I'm seeing you differently.
(The rise of Empty Head)
Monika, help him along.
(They celebrate with a move
from the 90s.)
Receive and send.
Okay.
I made an educated guess.
- That...
- Ilsacheonri.
I can't believe that was it.
How did you know it was ilsacheonri?
I knew "il," so I guessed the rest.
- Of course.
- I knew at least one of them.
Ilsacheonri, ilseokyijo,
or ilpamanpa.
In this next round, Aiki is up.
Please point out an underdog.
- We at least got a lot of points.
- Aiki.
- You were amazing.
- You did it.
But I'm the worst at quizzes.
Aiki, you're up.
Come on.
- Here we go.
- Go, Aiki.
Choose me as your opponent.
The underdog I'll go up against...
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
(Who will she choose
to compete against?)
Se Chan, get out here!
(Even after the first round,
he still seems like the dumbest.)
But why?
- Seriously?
- You're on a roll though.
Haha, come on out!
(She points to Haha
in Lee Jung's crew.)
- Get out there.
- I...
Compared to you two,
I'm as smart as Jae Suk.
- As if.
- Se Chan, you're doing great.
You're like the Quiz Master.
- For now...
- Unbelievable.
Compared to those two,
you're absolutely the smartest.
You're the smartest.
- Now...
- She saw...
- right through Haha.
- But I carried my weight.
- All right.
- Let's do this.
- Here we go.
- You can win again.
- The first category is people.
- Just be cautious.
- I would've liked current affairs.
- People are the hardest to know.
- Current affairs?
- Yes.
Here...
you go.
- You know who they are.
- Him... I know him.
But who's he?
Beethoven!
- No.
- That's not who he is.
Macron.
(Macron)
- Shin...
- Lee Kwang Soo.
(Macron, Lee Kwang Soo)
Doesn't it look like him?
It does.
He does look like Kwang Soo.
He looks like Kwang Soo.
Macron.
I doubt that's Freddie Mercury.
He has short hair!
But they look alike.
- Isn't that Freddie Mercury?
- Your boyfriend is hilarious.
He's witty, isn't he?
- Who could it be?
- You all know these famous people.
- Famous?
- They're famous?
I have no idea.
He got a perm.
- A perm?
- Who could it be?
Can we get a clue?
He's not an artist.
- Not an artist.
- Then a scientist.
Macron.
and Newton.
What's his full name?
- What?
- Hold on.
(Hold on.)
He barely knows Newton, and you...
His name is Illegal, darn it!
As in an illegal U-turn.
(Illegal Newton?)
- What?
- An illegal U-turn?
Why am I supposed
to say the full name?
It got me in the last round.
Newton...
It begins with an I.
- I...
- Let me answer.
- Haha?
- He knows.
- He remembers.
Three, two...
Adams Newton.
Macron and Acne Newton.
- Go with iPhone.
- No, don't.
Arsen Newton and Macron.
- It's iPhone.
- No, it's not.
- Macron.
- Yes?
He said it was iPhone Newton.
(He said it was iPhone Newton.)
- Aiki would've been better.
- Yes, iPhone.
- Okay, I got it.
- Haha?
- Aisep Newton.
- What?
- No, that's not it.
- Macron and Issaac.
- No.
- That's not it.
Macron and Aisop Newton.
- No.
- I got it. It's Ice.
Let me answer. Macron and Eisher.
No, that's not it.
Macron and Icy Newton.
- No.
- Let me answer!
Isaac Newton and Macron.
- Okay!
- Nicely done.
- Yes!
- It was Isaac.
- I said Issaac.
- They sound similar.
- It's Isaac.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- I!
- I should've gone with combat.
Tell me about it.
- I've never heard of that name.
- That was a hard one.
- Isaac was a hard one.
- I have never heard of that name.
It's about time...
you paid the show
for its classes and lessons.
- What I know, I learned here.
- They come here to study.
- That's right.
- Pay at least 50 dollars a month.
Aiki hasn't been receiving...
any help from her teammates.
I'm sorry.
The next category is Things.
Things?
- Get ready.
- They must be in English.
Cue.
What are those?
That...
- We always eat that with raw fish.
- Exactly.
- What's that called?
- An open balloon.
- An open balloon?
- Open?
What is that called?
- What do you call it?
- Radish sprouts...
and an event balloon.
(Incorrect)
She's right about
the radish sprouts.
And those balloons
are used at events.
Okay, this must be a brain teaser.
What balloon?
(What balloon?)
That was clever of you.
- It should be the correct answer.
- Radish sprouts sound like "what."
- What balloon?
- A brain teaser!
This is in English.
- It's an English term.
- English?
- Really?
- I hate English spellings.
Consider dance or dancing.
Giant dancing?
Air dancer.
- Air dancer?
- Air dance.
What on earth is that?
Dancing air.
What?
What on earth is that?
Wave air.
Combat.
What?
A match.
(They're having a match.)
That was funny.
No!
- Stop it.
- Rip it.
- Aiki.
- Be careful.
Let's get rid of him first.
Let's get rid of him first, Aiki.
- Why me?
- This is so messed up.
- Haha.
- You can beat him.
That's great.
- Just lie down.
- That's good.
(Laughing)
- Haha, go easy on her.
- He doesn't go easy on her.
He doesn't go easy on her.
- He's too harsh on her.
- He's not easy on her.
He's never easy on women.
He's too harsh on her.
- He's so...
- Aiki, you can do it!
Aiki!
He's too harsh on her.
Aiki, put your legs around his neck.
Hey!
(She tries to capture Haha alive.)
She got him.
She can do that
because she's flexible.
I really want to beat him.
Please...
- Get up, Aiki!
- She's good.
Get up!
- Why is she so strong?
- You're good!
- You got it.
- You got him!
Let's go, Aiki!
- Aiki!
- Aiki, we hope you win!
- She's very athletic.
- Get up!
Get up, Aiki!
(The match between the little ones
is more dynamic than they thought.)
Hold on.
(Screaming)
(Aiki squeezes Haha's joints.)
- Hey.
- Hey!
- That's an armbar.
- Give up!
- Give up.
- The game is getting dirty.
- She's amazing.
- My gosh, she's...
Hey, I can't breathe!
- Give up.
- Use your feet.
- Use your feet, Aiki.
- She's reaching for it.
- She got it.
- There you go.
That's it.
Use the other hand also.
- Poor Haha.
- Don't go easy on her!
(Haha also grabs Aiki's name tag.)
- Use the other hand!
- Rip her shirt!
(Who is the winner of this tussle?)
- Use the other hand!
(Aiki wins!)
- That was amazing.
- It's okay.
She was amazing.
Gosh, Haha.
You only embarrassed yourself.
(His performance was horrible.)
- She's really strong though.
- What was that?
The only thing I'm good at
is using my strength.
- Well done.
- She's really strong.
- You're the best.
- That was incredible.
- Let's have another one.
- That was a match in good faith.
- Sorry about that.
- You fought well.
Good work.
- Now,
- We have to stick that back, right?
Monika will point out...
two underdogs.
All right. Let's go, Monika!
- She's good.
- Let's go, Director Monika!
- Let's go, Professor Monika!
- Let's go!
I think Aiki is...
The person I can beat...
is Ji Hyo.
All right!
- All right.
- Show it to them.
- You can beat her.
- All right.
- She's been studying recently.
- Let's go.
- She's been studying.
- And...
I heard there was
something going on...
- between these two.
- Oh, really?
No, that's not true.
There's nothing going on.
I'll try to come in...
- between them.
- All right!
The person I can beat...
- is Gym Jung.
- Gym Jung, let's go!
Gym Jung!
I'm Gym Jung!
- Come on, Gym Jung.
- Yes, I'm Gym Jung.
The race is neck and neck.
- Let's go, Director Monika!
- Let's go!
- Don't go easy on her.
- Let's go, big player.
Aiki's crew is in last place.
- All right.
Lee Jung's crew is in
the first place.
- Yes!
- Let's win this, Monika.
I've never beaten Lee Jung
in a battle.
So I'll make sure
to beat her this time.
All right.
Here comes the first question.
(Courtesy of Andplus Mediaworks)
I should get this.
- I recognize her, but...
- She is...
Billie Eilish, Sophie Marceau.
She got it.
- Yes!
That was fast.
- I know.
- Yes!
- All right!
Let's go!
- I only recognized Sophie Marceau.
- Right.
- I didn't know the other one.
- I only recognized Sophie Marceau.
This is so exciting.
- She got it at once.
- Let's go!
Here comes the second question.
That's...
- How are we supposed to guess?
- Tell us their full names.
- Let me answer. That's Trump's...
- The one on the left...
(Surprised)
Trump's wife.
- Let me answer!
- Come on!
You can't do that.
Then you can call the other one
a tennis player.
She is Trump's wife, isn't she?
She is Trump's wife, but...
- Trump's wife?
- Trump's wife? That was funny.
Let me answer. Mrs. Trump.
Mrs. Trump?
You need to say her name.
Jong Kook,
listen to their answers first.
- As long as they don't call for it.
- Ask for a match,
rip Monika's name tag,
and get yours ripped by Ji Hyo.
- And then hug her.
- I'm not sure of her name.
Hug her.
- He's going for it.
- Say whatever comes to your mind.
He asked for a match.
If one of you asks for it,
you'll have a match.
They can have a match
if one more person asks for it.
I have no idea.
Gosh, this is...
It's a match.
- Are you asking for a match?
- She held it up.
- No, I didn't...
- Go for it!
It's a match.
Darn it. What's happening?
Did you ask for it?
- Hold on.
- Just so you know,
Monika is really competitive.
Go for it, Ji Hyo.
Monika, go for it.
(Is Monika, the competitive one,
attacking first?)
He's so scary!
- No...
- He's so scary!
(Every guest dreams of ripping
Jong Kook's name tag.)
This is...
He's so scary!
(Screaming)
- What was that?
- She's got fast footwork.
- She does.
- Just hug him.
- Gym Jung!
Gym Jung!
- Wait, I will...
- Hold on.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
You're not even willing to
rip his name tag.
- That's not true.
- My gosh.
(She attacks him suddenly...)
(while pretending
not to be interested in it.)
She just went for it.
She was really fast.
That was really fast.
- She's really quick.
- While I was talking here...
Monika!
Over here. Rip her name tag.
Right. I need to rip her name tag.
- I'm sorry.
- Ji Hyo is really strong.
It's not that.
- Because our team is losing...
- Exactly.
- Because we're losing...
- You can do it, Ji Hyo!
You're saying
you won't go easy on her, right?
- Let's go, Ai-hyo.
- Please beat Ji Hyo.
Shall we get started?
Rip it! Go!
- Let's go!
- Let's go, Ai-hyo!
- That's it!
- Ai-hyo!
You have a really strong grip.
- Rip it! Rip it, Monika!
- Monika is strong too.
- And she's fast too.
- Monika is fast.
(Monika watches for a chance
with her speed.)
- She's really fast.
- Don't show your back to her.
She's fast.
Everything she does
looks like a dance move.
Monika, you'll lose all your energy
at this rate!
Everything she does
looks like a dance move.
- She's done.
- She's really fast.
You need to rip it
for the game to be over.
(Right then, Monika attacks her
after finding an opening.)
(Will she beat Ji Hyo as well?)
(Ripping)
(Ai-hyo wins!)
(Ai-hyo's power suppresses
Monika's speed.)
She's indeed amazing.
You can't win against her.
You just can't.
Monika was really fast too.
- She was really fast.
- I know.
- She's unrivaled.
- It was really fun though.
- You did really well.
- It feels like we won though.
It feels like
we got the most questions.
All right, then.
I'll announce the results now.
The crew in last place...
has 11 points. It's Aiki's crew.
(Aiki's crew comes in last
with 11 points.)
- All right.
- Who won first place then? Us?
- Did she get many questions right?
- She did, but you didn't.
And the remaining teams
have only a one-point difference.
Hold on.
- They must've won.
- No!
- I must beat Lee Jung.
- Monika did really well.
- She ripped Monika's name tag.
- But she ripped Monika's name tag.
Right.
The crew that came in 1st place
with 25 points...
It's us.
This is nerve-racking.
Congratulations.
- It's Lee Jung's crew.
- Yes!
(Lee Jung's crew wins 1st place.)
I can't believe I lost
on this show as well.
- Yes!
- Well done. Yes!
I should be able to beat her here.
It's because you didn't earn
any points.
I did get some right though.
So the first battle
of two losing teams...
will be between Aiki's crew
and Monika's crew.
- Yes!
- Bring it on!
- Where are we having it?
- We only need to watch them.
All right!
Yes, we're watching it live.
We won't go easy on you.
Everyone. Let me tell you
the rules of the battle.
The two losing crews
of the previous mission,
Aiki's crew and Monika's crew,
will have a dance battle
against each other...
with the number of penalty badges
at stake.
- All right!
The leaders
will go against each other.
- The leaders will go first...
- And there will be a group battle.
The winning crew, Lee Jung's crew,
will be fight judges.
The winner from this battle
will receive one penalty badge.
- The losing crew will get three.
- All right.
So we're the judges.
That's right.
- I'm judging them.
- All right.
Yes!
(Lee Jung's crew is excited
that they get to judge.)
I think we need to be more brazen.
We need to be more confident.
They're very confident.
- That's true.
- So we need to be more confident.
Also, we need to make a routine...
to get the start on them.
- Which way should we go first.
- We will...
go from left to right.
(Practicing the routine dance
that'll be used in the battle)
I'm confident
because I'm a good dancer.
Change your expression
after dancing for a bit.
You can keep repeating it.
Let's go to the judges' seat.
- All right.
- This is the judges' seat?
- BoA sits in the middle.
- Is this the judges' seat?
- Hello, I'm the fight judge.
- All right.
Aiki's crew, bring it on.
(Aiki's crew
enters with confidence.)
What do we do, Aiki?
- Why?
- What?
- They have too many people.
- No.
The number of people doesn't matter.
(Right then,)
(Seok32 provokes them.)
- Why are you hitting me?
- Why else?
- Hey!
(Brazen)
- Don't mess with my sister.
- Yes!
(The fight judges
like the provocation.)
He's very aggressive. I like it.
I'll give him additional points.
- I like it.
- He'll get additional points.
He's very aggressive. I like it.
I'll give him additional points.
- I like it.
- Hey.
(Ai-dol fights back.)
- They'll get additional points.
- I like it.
I like that they're making it tense.
Let me tell you
the judging criteria.
The first criterion is newness.
The second criterion is confidence.
The third criterion is
how entertaining it is.
Then we don't need to
show off our skills?
Exactly.
You don't need to dance well.
When do we show off our skills?
Are you ready?
Ready?
(Judge Velvet Dress Ok Jung)
- Newness, confidence, and...
- Fight.
Hey!
(The battle between the leaders
starts with Aiki's attack.)
All right!
Please...
I really want to win.
I really want to win!
I think this battle alone
will be fun.
Aiki's crew, bring it on.
(Battle between two losing teams,
Aiki attacks first.)
Hey, let's go!
(Here comes Aiki.)
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang's jaw drops.)
We can just show this much
to get the start on them.
She's really good.
- All right.
- Yes!
Yes!
She danced more seriously
than I thought, so I was surprised.
(Startled)
Oh, my.
(Making use of the floor
at her pleasure)
- She's really good.
- This is unbelievable.
She's awesome.
(Provoking Monika
right in front of her)
What is she doing? She's good.
That was awesome!
Hey, Monika.
- Let's pretend we're discussing.
- We need to pretend?
That was cool. Let's pretend
we're discussing how to judge them.
You're doing well.
Am I dancing to the same song?
(Monika goes up against her.)
- It's Monika!
Hey, it's Monika!
- Hey!
- Hey.
(Stealing Jae Suk's hat
on the side)
What are you, an archer?
All right, calm down, everyone.
(Judge Velvet Dress Ok Jung)
You can't make me laugh.
Newness, confidence,
and what was it again?
How entertaining it is?
(Monika, Newness, confidence,
and what was it again?)
How entertaining it is?
- You can do it. Make it fun.
- I need to make it entertaining?
Monika!
(Monika's attack that'll satisfy
the judging criteria)
All right.
I'll make it entertaining.
(Monika's shockingly
entertaining performance)
(Showing off charming dance moves
to attract students for her classes)
Hey! Let's go!
I should dance well.
Well done!
(Next up is Aiki's crew.)
- It's your turn!
- Yes.
- What do I do?
- Get ready!
- In 1, 2, 3, 4.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Are you begging for money or what?
Come on.
That's adorable.
They practiced in advance?
The two of them looked like
Aiki's sidekicks.
Shall we get ready too?
- Yes, let's get ready.
- Here we go.
- Come here.
- Yes.
(The song changes.)
- Here we go. Get ready.
- What's that?
Get ready.
(Here we go. Get ready.)
(They get ready to start
following Monika's lead.)
- They're so cute.
- Here we go.
- All right.
- Go!
Go!
(Going this way and that way)
- Go!
- They can't catch up.
- What are they doing?
- Go!
Go! Yes!
It's all about
teasing your opponent.
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang, It's all
about teasing your opponent.)
(Aiki's crew doesn't back down.)
- Show us your skills! Let's go!
- All right!
(It's Get Off Work Yi Hwang's
turn to show off his skills.)
Let's go! Show it to them!
(Fancy)
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang teases them
all he wants.)
All right!
(Right then)
(Diving between his legs)
(Ai-dol instantly catches
everyone's eyes.)
Go for it!
- There you go!
- She just...
How dare she provoke us?
(Ai-dol's provocation
flusters everyone.)
- How dare she provoke us?
- All right.
(Next up is a mid-aged man
from an alpine club.)
(The 90s vibe
comes naturally to him.)
- All right! Come on, Seok Sam.
- Let's go!
- The look in your eyes.
- Do your dance.
- Be creative.
(Seok32 takes his turn
when the corny part starts to play.)
Do your dance.
Do your dance!
Don't do the ridiculous moves.
(Right when Seok Sam
was showing a ridiculous move...)
Don't do the ridiculous moves.
(Ai-dol dives for the 2nd time.)
Why does she keep diving
between our legs?
What was that?
- Hey, you!
- I was really startled.
Isn't that a foul?
- That was a foul, wasn't it?
- Why does she keep...
- Why do you keep doing that?
- I was really into it.
- Well done.
- She's our rising star.
Well done, Ai-dol.
- It was a total mess.
- It was chaotic.
I told you to do your dance.
- What? I was about to.
- Your dance.
- She kept diving between my legs.
- You should've done your dance.
I should've done this move.
You should've done that.
That was a battle between
two world-class crews.
Let's hear
from the fight judges first.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Well, that was
an amazing performance.
Hey.
When it comes to newness,
I think they dominated it.
Newness?
(Aiki's crew got a favorable review
from Velvet Dress Ok Jung.)
My gosh, he's got to be kidding me.
I loved how you dived between their
legs and how confident you were.
But I think this crew
did really well thanks to Monika.
Se Chan was really entertaining,
- and his moves...
- Entertaining?
were really refined.
But then again,
there were two who fell behind.
(There were two who fell behind.)
- Fall behind?
- How could you say that?
- Why that little...
- What was that?
Well, first of all,
I didn't like how So Min
kept crawling under their legs.
- Right?
- She interrupted them.
It's rude to do that
in a dance battle.
I liked Se Chan's frivolous moves.
Are you saying that
because you're close to him?
Thank you!
Let me talk about Aiki first.
It was really new.
- I agree.
- Aiki proved why she's good.
(Aiki proved why she's good.)
She proved why she's good.
There was nothing new
about this crew.
They were all old.
They were like grim reapers.
- Who are you to say that?
- You're the most boring one.
Who are you to judge?
- Darn you.
Stand in line!
(Stand in line!)
- Attention.
- How did he become such a fossil?
- He thinks he's something.
- He's become such a fossil
- Don't lean on one leg!
He became a fossil
after he turned 40.
It wasn't new at all.
Now, the fight judges...
- will make their decisions.
- All right.
Are you going to keep
speaking in that tone?
What's with your tone?
- This is nerve-racking.
- On the count of three...
Fight judges, card...
- Please!
- Do we reveal it at the same time?
- Which crew should I pick?
- Open the card!
(Depending on the result, they'll
get either 3 or 1 penalty badge.)
Please!
All right!
(Monika's crew, Aiki's crew)
(Aiki's crew 1, Monika's crew 1)
- Seriously.
- Please!
I even lifted my top.
Open the card!
(Monika's crew)
(Monika's crew wins.)
- Hey! Yes!
- Hey!
(Monika crew's petty members
show horrible manners.)
Monika's crew who came in 2nd place
will take 1 penalty badge.
- The losing crew will get three.
- Yes!
- You said they looked like...
- You did really well, Aiki.
grim reapers!
You did really well. Can you
not be so serious about this?
I'm really serious.
- Monika's crew gets one,
- I really want to win!
Aiki's crew gets three.
- Stick it on your chest.
- All right.
Gosh, what a bummer.
We'll move on to the next game.
- Yes!
- Okay!
This time, you'll play Good Image.
- Good image, good image
It'll be played in the beat
of Strawberry Game.
A member of an attacking team...
will attack one of you with an image
and a number from 1 to 4.
A member of the defending team
should respond to it...
if they agree with the given image.
But if the two defending teams
do not respond...
or respond at the same time,
both teams will lose points.
You got the rules, right?
(Their points will be deducted as
many as the members that responded.)
It's a game between three teams.
Aiki is upset for real.
- Because they lost?
- Yes.
We think it's unfair.
- She's really upset.
- Because I'm really competitive.
(Will competitive Aiki
avoid going last this time?)
Let's start.
The attacking team
can attack two teams, right?
Yes, you can attack any team
of your choice.
But if two people answer
at the same time,
their points will be deducted as
many as the people that responded.
What if no one responds?
Then both teams
will get their points deducted.
- That'll be good too.
- I got it.
Then we must come up with a way
to attack two teams at once.
You can't point at your team member
with your chin.
You need to read the room.
Let's start with Honey Jae Suk.
Okay, I'll go first.
Honey
- Image
(They get started.)
- I
- Good image, good image
Hat, three.
(Hat, three.)
- Hat...
Thank goodness.
(Ai-hyo and Aiki
answered at the same time.)
- Well done!
- Yes!
- Yes.
- That was a good one.
(Aiki's crew loses 2 points
from the start.)
Thank goodness I held back.
Both of you were wearing hats.
- That was a practice round, right?
- No.
- We began right away.
- Really?
It was a good round.
Aiki is angry for real.
Why don't we let her off this once?
(I am not angry.)
- Haha, it's your turn.
- Okay.
(Velvet Dress Ok Jung will resume.)
There he goes.
I
(Old Fossil Dancer
loves something like this the most.)
(Other wild animals join in.)
I
(Panting)
- Let's go.
- I
Let's go.
- Good image, good image
- Image
Children, two.
(Children, two.)
Hold on.
- Hey.
- The end.
"Children, two"?
Both teams will lose a point.
- People with two children.
- Two children.
- You said it like a swear word.
It sounded strange.
- It sounded strange.
- Why?
He said it wrong.
- It made no sense.
- His direction was wrong.
- "Children, two"?
- What's wrong with it?
- You could have children.
- He said it wrong.
- It made no sense.
- His direction was wrong.
- Children.
- Hold on.
- People with children.
- Let's do this again.
He said it like a swear word
at me and Suk Jin.
It was fine. This is a game.
- It wasn't fine.
- This is a game.
- No!
- Hey.
- This is a game.
- Don't use your muscles.
- Why are you making a fuss?
- Don't push.
- This is a game.
- I mean...
- Hey.
I like this about him.
- This is a game.
- I mean...
Listen.
- What was that?
- Hold on.
- Aren't you your mother's child?
- I am my mother's child.
- Aren't you your father's child?
- I am.
How does it sound like a swear word?
Aren't you your father's offspring?
- You are, right?
- That's right.
- Anyone could have answered.
- He said it wrong.
- They should lose a point.
- That's right.
- Seriously.
- No way.
- They messed up.
- No.
It isn't a swear word.
- You have the freedom to attack.
- What?
You have the freedom to attack.
That's right. You are
your mother and father's child.
People are
their parent's children, you punk!
- What?
- "You punk"?
- What was that?
- Why did you call us that?
You are your parents' child.
You are, okay?
(He takes care of the three punks.)
You are.
- Don't say that to the older ones.
- I am so annoyed.
We are our parents' children.
That's right.
All of us are.
I am so annoyed.
This time, Seok Sam will go first.
- Okay.
- Seok Sam.
(Seok Sam will attack
after cooling down.)
- Are you ready to attack?
- Yes.
He doesn't have the energy
to stall for a long time.
- Good image, good image
Very good image
Why do you think
you have a good image?
Today
Why do you think
you have a good image?
- Here is the thing
- Why do you think
You have a good image?
I have a wife, I have a son
(He barely manages to strike back.)
You don't get along with your wife
I get along with my wife
If married couples
get along too well
That's a bad thing
(That's a bad thing.)
(Seok Sam gives a life lesson.)
- That's a bad thing
- Good image, good image
(Seok Sam attacks
after the ad-libbing crisis.)
Woman, two.
Woman, woman.
Protruding mouth, two.
Protruding mouth, protruding mouth.
Beggar, two.
- B...
- Beggar, beggar.
- Who else said it?
- No.
(The beggar duo is out.)
- All right.
- I just laughed.
- She just laughed.
- No.
- I just laughed.
- She just laughed.
- She answered.
- No.
She really laughed.
- She laughed.
- She answered.
- I laughed.
- Haha answered to "Beggar".
- I can't believe it.
- I heard it.
- Beggar.
- I have no money, okay?
- Do you want to be a beggar?
- Let me off this once.
- No.
- I really laughed.
- She laughed.
- I heard it myself.
- She really laughed.
That counts as an answer.
- That's right.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- You made it sound like an answer.
- That counts as an answer.
- That's right.
- I want to win!
- Okay.
- Aiki takes on any titles.
- The last game matters the most.
- Okay.
- Everything changes then.
(Lee Jung's crew resumes.)
(They get ready
to sing the Image Song.)
- Gosh.
- Save your energy.
- Good image, good image
Ugly one, three.
(Ugly one, three.)
Ugly one, ugly one, ugly one.
Hip-hop beggar, two.
Hip-hop beggar, hip-hop beggar.
(Aiki takes on "Hip-hop beggar".)
Pants, four.
Why did no one answer?
(Her attack was successful!)
For goodness' sake.
Hip-hop beggar
was meant for Haha, not Aiki.
I am a beggar too.
No!
Hip-hop beggar was meant for Haha.
- I am a beggar too.
- Why did you answer?
Why did you answer?
Hip-hop beggar was meant for Haha.
- I am a reggae beggar.
- It doesn't matter.
- I am a beggar.
- No.
- For goodness' sake.
- Really?
It was meant for Haha.
- Hip-hop beggar.
- Are you a reggae beggar?
He is a reggae beggar.
- Monika should go first.
- Monika.
(It's Monika's turn to attack.)
Shake your body left and right
- Shake your body left and right
- Say ho
- Ho
(Monika leads the dancers.)
- Good
- Ho
- Say ho
- Good
- Image
Hold on.
Mister, stop hitting my thigh.
Mister.
Stop hitting my thigh.
- It hurts.
- We need to keep going.
For goodness' sake.
(Get Off Work Yi Hwang is
in danger of an injury.)
Stop hitting my thigh.
- It hurts.
- We need to keep going.
Stop it. It hurts.
We need to keep going with Monika.
- It hurts.
- For goodness' sake.
That was great.
- That's the horse-riding dance.
- That's right.
Aiki, why don't you go first
this time?
- Me?
- Aiki.
Okay.
(Whispering)
(Laughing)
I swear.
Okay.
It will work.
I
(The intro begins
amidst the confusion.)
- Good image, good image
Good image, let's go
Impotent, three.
(My goodness.)
(They look around
without knowing what to do.)
- Impotent, impotent, impotent.
- Impotent.
(Suk Jin and Se Chan
answer together.)
(Impotent men come forward
at the third turn.)
I am sorry.
(It's an attack that never fails.)
- Hurry up.
- I am sorry.
- For goodness' sake.
- I was going to answer.
- Hey.
- Aren't you going to play?
Since the last time,
"Impotent" has been mine.
Then why didn't you answer
right away?
I was torn.
You confused the younger ones.
Suk Jin.
It's not like that.
(It took him two turns
to accept "Impotent".)
- Why are you laughing?
- Suk Jin...
answers so merrily
whenever "Impotent" comes up.
- Impotent, four.
- What an attack.
Why does our team get
the worst keywords?
- Seriously.
- Why...
- Why is that?
- Hey.
Our team answered...
to "Impotent", "Bad breath",
"Protruding mouth",
and "Ugly one".
Why does our team get
the worst keywords?
- That's so funny.
- Give us an advantage.
Advantage.
Give us an advantage.
- Advantage.
- It's too much.
- Seriously.
- "Impotent" is...
- his favorite keyword.
- Aiki.
I am so annoyed.
Now,
this round will determine
the winning team.
- Yes.
- This time,
Seok32 will go first.
Let's go.
(Seok32's attack will be important.)
Good image
(He suddenly begins to sing.)
- Good image
- That came out of nowhere.
He is showing us his specialty.
(Suk Jin gets ready to attack
with his old-fashioned beat.)
Good.
- Good.
- He is like an old singer.
Good, good
What's good? The image is
- Good
- He is like Hwang Soo Gwan.
- He sounds similar.
- Hwang Soo Gwan.
- La la la
- I feel so peaceful.
(The melodious intro
moves their hearts.)
- Good image
- Image
(He begins to attack
after his ridiculous specialty.)
Sexy guy, three.
Sexy guy, sexy guy, sexy guy.
Impotent, two.
Impotent, impotent.
Sweatshirt, four.
(Sweatshirt, four.)
- Sweatshirt...
- We won.
We won.
You won.
(Monika's crew
becomes the final winner!)
We won.
(6 people who were wearing
a sweatshirt failed to answer.)
(She stomps her feet
because she is so competitive.)
- We won.
Let's go.
(They do the old-fashioned wave
to celebrate their victory.)
- Okay.
- Sweatshirt.
- All right.
- Okay.
(Aiki's crew and Lee Jung's crew
enter the dance battle.)
Let's begin the second dance battle
between the two losing teams.
This is driving me crazy.
(Street Human Fighter)
- Okay.
- This is the last dance battle.
We can do it. I will show you
what a true leader is.
We will win.
We will win the battle.
Let's go.
I, Honey Jae Suk,
- will host...
- Honey Jae Suk.
- the dance battle.
- Let's go.
- Let's choose who will go first.
- Okay.
The team that gets this side
will go first.
- You are a bit excited, right?
- Yes.
That's not how you do it.
(Rolling)
What are you doing?
- What?
What? You spin the bottle.
- You spin it like this.
- Yes.
- Why did he roll it?
- Seriously.
I will spin it.
(He promises
to spin the bottle this time.)
- It's spinning nicely.
- Of course.
I think it will spin forever.
That's how you spin it.
Bam!
Okay.
(Aiki's crew will attack first.)
You need to take the lead.
- Okay.
- You can't make me laugh.
She is simply cute. She is too cute.
The leaders will go first.
(Aiki versus Lee Jung)
- Drop the beat!
(The all-rounder, Aiki goes first.)
Aiki.
You can do it.
Hey.
Dance in a cool way.
It's okay to do that.
You are cool.
Hey.
It's cool.
It's too cool.
(Upon hearing Monika's words,)
(she switches to a silly dance
for variety shows.)
What?
That's funny.
(Swaying)
She looks like a tube man.
(She flaps her arms around
like a tube man.)
She looks cute.
Okay.
Lee Jung.
(Lee Jung's dance comes next.)
This is fun.
How will Lee Jung dance?
Here it comes. Lee Jung.
(She aggravates Aiki.)
It isn't funny.
It isn't funny. It looks cool.
It just looks cool.
I know. That's a bit dangerous.
It looks cool.
(Her dance is perfectly controlled.)
(The tube man reappears.)
She is a talented dancer.
Lee Jung.
It must be so nice
to be able to dance like that.
(Jealous)
(She shows her light steps
to the judges.)
You should go again.
She is so cool.
Aiki, go again.
Aiki, show us a cool dance.
- Five, six, seven, go.
- A cool dance.
That's so cool.
(The leaders' battle ends
with the perfect finale.)
The group battles.
(Lee Jung's crew)
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Okay.
(Lee Jung summons
the 1st-generation dancers.)
(The old steps of the 90s)
I really want to win.
(Here comes a street fighter.)
(The thug wave)
(He is the original K-dancer
who took the 90s by storm.)
He looks a bit broken.
(The thug wave has
the end-of-the-century vibe.)
He looks a bit sick.
What is that?
(Showing a b-boying move)
(Is it my turn?)
Haha, let's go.
I will end them.
(He fails to catch the hat.)
(He does the usual dance
when his plan falls through.)
No.
That won't do.
(He wraps up after doing
a meaningless dance.)
It looks like he is in pain.
It hurts.
Everyone can dance well.
Aiki's crew, you are up.
(Is it Latin music?)
(She suddenly transforms.)
(The confident dancer is
in her element.)
- Look at So Min.
- It's funny.
Lie down.
Roll.
(She gets the conveyor belt going.)
What is that?
(It's a unique dance
for Latin music.)
Let's go.
Good job.
(I don't even know.)
(The confident dancer
gives a water show.)
(The confident dancer's
good cheer explodes.)
(Juliana shakes her body
like there is no tomorrow.)
(Sexy)
- Hey, come on.
- Okay.
Why are you trying so hard?
(She wraps up
as she shakes off the water.)
- You ripped up the stage.
- That was so funny.
Give them a round of applause.
She ripped up the stage.
It was a neck-and-neck match.
It was so satisfying.
- Let's give them a big hand.
- They did so well.
Seriously.
Let's hear a few words
from the fight judges.
All right.
Firstly, I have been
in the dance scene for 20 years.
It was quite shocking.
- He sounds so serious.
- The way she poured water...
Aren't you going to listen?
I am sorry.
Everyone was doing something else.
- We are judging the performances.
- I am sorry.
- Why aren't you listening?
We are judging the performances.
- I am so angry that I can't go on.
- Please go on.
In the dance scene,
an act like pouring water...
is unacceptable.
- Isn't it what you like?
- Well,
- it was funny.
- He loved it the most.
Although it was funny,
I focused solely on the dance.
- Didn't you cheer the loudest?
- You loved it.
You cheered the loudest.
It's a different matter.
When So Min poured water, he went...
(Seok Sam laughed the loudest
since it suited his tastes.)
Cheering is a different matter.
My score will be based on
the dance alone.
- You will see the score soon.
- Okay.
It won't be a high score
because of you.
- I am sorry, but...
- Okay.
(Aiki raises her hand.)
- I am sorry,
- Okay.
but she was...
the sexiest today.
(She was the sexiest today.)
Hey, don't shake your body.
Only those who have watched
the show would understand...
- why Aiki said that.
- That's right.
- Really?
- She did the best today.
- I don't know the background.
- It's a heartwarming saying.
You are cool.
- You are cool.
- You are very cool.
You are cool, Aiki.
I told you
that I would focus on the dance.
Mister, your time is up.
She is a professional.
Both teams did very well.
- Gym Jung danced again.
- Jong Kook.
- Give me bonus points.
- Seriously. He never danced before.
Yes. It was very nice.
We have nothing to say
about the two leaders.
I love their styles of dance.
It was insane when she did this.
I am talking right now.
I am sorry.
They are attacking each other.
Everyone becomes an old fossil
on that chair.
I am talking right now.
You should listen while we fight.
Okay.
How dare you? Listen.
- Go ahead.
- "Listen."
- There should be bribes.
- All right.
We need to judge this
as a variety show segment.
On variety shows,
we like such challenges.
- That's right.
- She poured water on her head.
- I can't accept that.
- Water is for drinking.
- I saw something else.
Do you know what?
Ji Hyo stood there and watched.
Do you know what it means?
She wanted to contribute,
but she couldn't go that far.
I love such moments...
on a variety show.
Gym Jong Kook's performance
was nice,
but we need to talk about Haha.
Haha was so serious about this.
I will give a single comment.
- I will give 2... No, 1 word.
- Give us 1 word.
Moronic.
He tried to look cool.
Moronic! I didn't see that coming.
That's the word I use often.
- It was lousy.
- Lousy.
- It didn't even look cool.
- He should have danced funnily.
- That's all I have to say.
- Okay.
Both teams had a member
who ruined the atmosphere.
Lee Jung's crew had Haha.
He pretended to know
something about hip-hop.
- Hip-hop.
- He was an eyesore.
- That's right.
- He pretended to be young.
- Yes.
- He pretended to know...
all about dancing.
That made me change the score a bit.
And Aiki's crew had Ai-dol.
Despite being an actress,
she gave a water show
like a comedienne at a retreat.
I think highly of it.
That's right.
I already have the winner
in my mind.
Really?
It was a neck-and-neck match,
but I chose a funnier performance.
- Okay.
- Shall we choose now?
Fight judges.
(The losing crew will receive
3 penalty badges.)
Fight judges.
- Open...
- Please.
(What will be their decision?)
- the card.
- Please.
Open the card.
(Aiki's crew won.)
Aiki's crew.
- Aiki's crew.
My friends.
It couldn't be helped.
- Oh, no.
- They were too funny.
- Seriously.
Gosh, was I too cool?
We won.
- We won.
- My goodness.
I will reveal the final result.
This is the order
by the number of penalty badges.
(The order
by the number of penalty badges)
First place...
is Monika's crew
with one penalty badge.
(Monika's crew won.)
- Monika's crew won.
- Thank you so much.
It's nice to place first here.
The prize consists of a trophy...
and the latest action camera
so that you can take...
many good videos.
Will you really give her
an action camera?
It's something Monika really needs.
- I love it.
- It's the best.
Monika.
(The winner of Street Human Fighter
is Monika.)
That's incredible.
Mom, I won on Running Man!
- Thank you. I love you.
- She has the best reactions.
I am jealous of the trophy.
One of the crews
will receive the penalty.
(It's time to decide on the crew
that will receive the penalty.)
The last place is...
(Which crew placed last?)
Aiki's crew
with four penalty badges.
- Okay.
- You placed last.
(Aiki's crew)
We didn't place last.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- We dodged the bullet.
We dodged the bullet.
I had a lot of fun with you guys.
I will reveal
the penalty of the day.
For people who began to star in
variety shows,
this penalty will give
both sweetness and spiciness.
It's the fresh cream cannon.
- What?
- There is a special rule.
- A special rule?
One of the fresh cream cannons...
won't go off.
And we will tell the leader, Aiki...
about one of the two cannons
that will go off.
- Really?
- She can volunteer to take it.
Then Aiki will assign
her team members.
- This one will go off.
- Okay.
- This is one of the two cannons.
One of the other two will go off,
and the rest won't go off.
- She's torn.
- Aiki,
assign your team members
to each cannon.
Which color do you like?
- I like yellow.
- Okay. You stand here.
- What about you?
- I like pink.
- Should we sit?
- We don't know it yet.
Okay.
Monika, Lee Jung, and Aiki.
Tell us how you liked our show
before the cannons go off.
- Should I say it standing here?
- Yes, please.
First, I'm so lucky that I'm not
standing here. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- That's nice.
After joining Running Man
as a guest,
I realized that it was really fun.
You should succeed
and join this show sometime.
(You should succeed
and join this show sometime.)
I agree. This is the most fun
TV show I've ever joined.
I was so comfortable.
Thank you for having me here.
- Lee Jung.
- All right. Aiki.
I had a lot of fun today.
I just feel bad
that this is how it ends.
But I believe this will
also be a fun memory.
I had a great time.
(I had a great time.)
I hope Aiki's cannon won't go off.
- Me too.
- I know.
I'll show you
what a good leader is like.
This looks good.
Just mind the angle.
It will go off as I count to three.
(Aiki assigned her team members
knowing the cannon to go off.)
- One.
- Aiki, that's good.
Two.
(Who is the one to survive?)
Three.
- So Min's cannon didn't go off.
- Mine didn't go off.
(Aiki and Ji Hyo are
covered with fresh cream.)
Mine didn't go off.
Aiki chose number two
knowing that it would go off.
- That's amazing.
- Why?
She's so cool.
(Moved)
- Don't open your eyes.
- She's great.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Here's the question.
(What's the highway that connects
Asia and European countries?)
(Look at him write down the answer.)
(He's really smart.)
(I'm so proud of him.)
Se Chan knows the answer.
He knows it too.
(Darn it. I don't remember.)
(This is what we focused on.)
We kept talking about it.
We talked about it.
Did he memorize that?
You're the top student.
Jae Suk.
What? Hi-pass?
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- It's my fault.
- If Ji Hyo...
(answered another couple
of questions...)
(Why would you say that
when she's here?)
(Noisy)
(Darn Korean schools!)
Turn it up!
(What we want is...)
(What's with
this overheated classroom?)
(A few hours ago)
(What do you think of the penalties
on Running Man?)
(Running Man members
versus the production crew)
(The winner will decide
the penalties for the future.)
(The question is,
do we really need the penalty?)
Hurry.
(They cooperate with each other
for the world without penalties.)
(Running Man members
versus the production crew)
(Is it the beginning
of slapstick comedy?)
(We are the funny ones.)
(Raising voices)
(We need VAR.)
(Running Man, Production Crew)
(The two teams meet
under the giant water cannons.)
(Who will lose the match and
get splashed by the water cannon?)
(2021 Running Man
Penalty Negotiation)