(December 7, 2021)
- Hello.
- Hello, Ji Hyo.
- Hey, So Min.
- The Awards Ceremony preview.
- So Min, what's this?
- With a bouquet...
- What's happening? All right.
Okay. All right.
- Okay.
- Hey.
Good. Okay.
Great.
What do we do with the bouquets?
What?
- Are we getting a bouquet?
- Seok Jin.
- This is like "Incredible Moment."
- My goodness.
I love your outfit.
- I think I'm so out of style.
- An old man who looks young.
- Right.
- This is so tacky.
You had your pants mended.
- His pants...
- I bought a new pair of pants.
Really? I knew it.
- Hello.
- Hi.
But the sneakers...
You're all dressed up, Ji Hyo.
- Jae Seok.
- You look nice, Ji Hyo.
What's wrong with her outfit?
She does look good.
- I mean...
- I was surprised.
You're the one who's poorly dressed.
He does look strange.
He looks like an earl today.
Ji Hyo looks great today.
- I like your suit.
- My goodness.
You look so stylish.
Is something going on
between you two today?
What are you talking about?
Don't be silly.
- You look great anyway.
- Okay.
My gosh.
Are we shooting already?
Yes, we are. Gosh, you look amazing.
- I like your outfit.
- I look so tacky.
- Today, I want...
- My gosh.
- Shall we begin?
- Yes.
Jong Kook looks
just like a physical trainer.
Let's just start the shoot.
I have a lot to say. What can I do?
That's enough.
I just have a lot to say.
Let's just hurry and begin.
- My gosh.
- Let's begin.
Your shoes are shining.
Let's start the award ceremony.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Congratulations.
(They finally stop talking
and start the award ceremony.)
- Congratulations!
- Let's go!
I'm happy for you.
- Congratulations.
- Great.
Well done.
- Okay.
- Good.
Be careful.
(The award ceremony
is over like that.)
(The year-end party
for the members...)
(who have worked hard
for the past year)
- It's party time.
- Cool.
- It's a party.
- Hello.
- Cool.
This is a party.
This doesn't seem
like a penalty for Seok Jin.
- I know.
- I think so. He looks fine.
- He's just dressed up.
- Because we're having a party.
That's because I pull it off well.
- What?
- I look good in this suit.
What are you talking about?
What did you just do?
- He touched your eyeglass frame.
- That's what you pull off.
He pulls off his eyeglass frame?
His eyeglass frame.
Gosh, Seok Jin.
By the way, take a look at Ji Hyo.
- You look great.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
- You look beautiful.
- Right.
You should wear suits
like that more often.
- My goodness.
- You look amazing.
- She looks stunning.
- Seriously...
- This is what my stylist got me.
- I know.
- A perfect suit for today.
- It looks great.
- And it's not like...
you just wear
what your stylist gets you.
- It also reflects your taste.
- Sure.
- Exactly.
- Of course.
It's not like
my stylist is not working.
I know.
That's just your taste.
I'm just like, "Forget about it!"
- Sure.
- And I put on what I want.
I do the same thing.
I have a stylist myself,
- but I often pick my outfit.
- He's stubborn.
- He's very stubborn.
- Right.
- I have my own style.
- Right. He does.
- But I just wear what I get.
- What?
- I wear what I get.
- That's true.
- That's a lie.
- The shirt I wore the other day...
that looked like a diaper.
My friend from school
called me after 30 years...
- and said this.
- What did he say?
"Don't live like that."
Was that Yong Man?
- Yes.
- It was Yong Man.
- My hair will grow back quickly.
- Right.
I like your hair.
- Right. It looks good on you.
- You can try many different things.
Ji Hyo, did you go to the same
salon as Jong Kook?
Your hair looks the same.
Did you go to my barber?
- What?
- His barber?
I went to a barbershop.
Did you do your hair yourself?
- A barbershop?
- I went to a barbershop.
- You went to a barbershop?
- A barbershop.
I thought it was my barber.
I guess Kwang Soo opened a shop.
Kwang Soo opened a barbershop?
A barbershop.
I want to go there.
- About Kwang Soo...
- What about him?
- At the Blue Dragon Film Awards...
- Did he win an award?
He looked like a cat's-paw.
Did you see that?
- I did.
- He had this strange mustache.
(Kwang Soo attended the ceremony
with a strange-looking mustache.)
(Give me 10 seconds.)
(Can I borrow 50 cents?)
- Really?
- Yes.
How did he look?
He looked like a cat's-paw.
- Like this.
- He always looks like that.
With this weird gesture.
He's shy to do this,
so he's always like this.
- With his hair parted...
- It looks like a chicken foot.
He had his hair parted like this.
He enjoyed the ceremony
in a strange way.
He doesn't even know
how to enjoy it.
He hasn't decided his character yet.
Right. He doesn't know what to do.
- It's ambiguous.
- That's a problem.
So Min, you look like a character
from your drama.
- Right. It's "The Queen's House."
- "The Queen's House."
Isn't the dress Haha's mom's?
- Mom. "Get lucky this year."
- It's Haha's Mom's dress.
"Get lucky this year."
I watched So Min's new drama...
because it features So Min.
- I watched it.
- I watched it too.
All my friends...
- I didn't watch it yet.
- You know what?
It's just a drama, but I was like...
"My goodness."
I can't watch it because of my kids.
(This is the scene
that became the talk of the town.)
My gosh.
Hey, are you out of your mind?
(Unlike on Running Man,
So Min sounds tough and terrifying.)
(It receives high viewing rates
with her character of a villain.)
- Gosh, that was...
- Did you watch it?
She doesn't look like
the person we see here.
She's different in the drama.
- I can't watch it.
- Ji Hyo texted me.
- What did she say?
- After watching the drama.
"You vixen."
She flirts a lot.
- I asked her to curse me.
- I guess her acting was good.
And there's...
My goodness.
I can't believe this.
- Right.
- It's unbelievable.
- Seok Jin is...
- It was really cool.
Seok Jin won
the Best Project Music Award.
- What?
- Hang on.
- My goodness.
- Thank you.
It's not for me though.
- Seriously, he should thank me.
- Sure.
He raised you.
You should call him Father.
- I'm like his father.
- Call him Dad.
I mentioned your name
in my acceptance speech.
- You did?
- I said I was grateful to Yu Yaho.
- What about us?
What do you have to do
with this award?
What did you just say?
- You sound so mean.
- Amazing.
- My gosh.
- That's not what I mean.
- Hang on.
- It's not like that.
"What do you have to do
with this award?"
That's not it. Just think about it.
- This is...
- Well...
about another show.
- I was there as a singer.
- It's another show,
- but you could've mentioned us.
- I was really glad anyway.
I was glad that
you turned out so well.
He's proud of you.
- Right.
- I'm really happy.
By the way, Se Chan...
- You're all dressed up, Se Chan.
- You look uncomfortable though.
I'm dressed like a hairtail
from Jeju Island.
- Why are you wearing this jacket?
- Because it's cold.
He's gained a lot of weight.
This is about to burst.
You can have
my Michael Jackson character.
- Well...
- What happened?
It's the end of the year,
so I've been drinking a lot.
It's funny when you're fat.
- I met a lot of people.
- This is cute.
- Your belly looks funny.
- I know.
- Why did you put on weight?
- My belly got fat.
But So Min seems...
to think it's really cute.
She's strange.
Seriously.
Stop it.
She looks even stranger
in this dress.
That's not his arm. It's empty.
The sleeve is empty.
It's empty.
It looks like I have my arm
around her shoulder.
It does.
(She tries to hug him
like a tough girl.)
She's unbelievable. She's so feisty.
The year 2021 is
drawing to a close already.
I appreciate the hard work
that you've shown for the past year.
Right. We've worked hard.
- He agrees.
- That's true.
(January 2021)
(February 2021)
(March 2021, April 2021)
(May 2021)
(June 2021)
(July 2021)
(August 2021)
(September 2021)
(October 2021)
(November 2021)
(December 2021)
We've been through a lot.
- Right.
- Yes, we have.
- Sure.
- It wasn't easy.
I know.
So we prepared a year-end party...
for the members of Running Man.
- I see.
- My gosh.
And we need some guests
to grace the occasion.
- Of course, we do.
- Do we have guests today?
We have three guests...
who brought great honor
to Running Man this year.
It can't be Ha Do Kwon.
Really? Is Do Kwon coming?
- I'm serious.
- I'm sick of him.
- Is it Do Kwon again?
- I'm sick and tired of him.
I bet it's Do Kwon.
You were on Running Man a lot.
I think they call me
when a guest doesn't show up.
I was surprised.
- Look at that.
- It's Do Kwon.
- It's him.
- It's Chung Hwa.
I can't believe this.
Hey, Young Ji.
Hello.
- Hey.
- Jae Seok.
Young Ji.
It's Do Kwon.
Young Ji is here.
Hey, Young Ji.
- Hello.
I just mentioned Do Kwon's name,
- and he's really here.
- Gosh, Do Kwon.
(He joins Running Man
acting pompously,)
(but he always ends up
having a hard time.)
(Whatever he does looks funny.)
(He's like a member of the family.)
(The funniest guest,
Do Kwon is back.)
(The guest who swept the Internet
with her appearance, Cha Chung Hwa)
(Cha Chung Hwa overwhelms people
dancing to "Switch to Me.")
(The video has received
1.27 million views.)
(It was the best opening dance
on Running Man ever.)
(She's perfect for variety shows.)
(She dominated Running Man
with only one song.)
(She's amazing. Have Chung Hwa
on Running Man more often.)
(With so many requests
for her comeback,)
(Chung Hwa's back on Running Man.)
(Hur Young Ji joined the Empty
Head Club on her first appearance.)
(She showed up with her
refreshing charm as an idol artist.)
(But her charm becomes sour
when she answers quizzes.)
(She joined the Empty Head Club
saying some alien words.)
(Doesn't liter start with an L?)
(She's the new Empty Head Princess
who's always confident.)
- Gosh, Young Ji.
- Young Ji.
(Welcome to the year-end party.)
Hello.
Young Ji, this is too much.
- Hello.
What's that?
- Hey, this is...
- Hello.
My goodness.
Young Ji, what's with...
It's not like...
Hey, Young Ji.
Hey. Are you a princess?
- I'm just like you.
- Hey.
Young Ji.
The other guests need
our attention too.
- Young Ji, are you Elsa?
- You look beautiful.
- She's Elsa.
- Gosh, Young Ji.
- It's pretty.
- She's unbelievable.
Young Ji, this is like your place.
- She looks beautiful.
- I bet Young Ji saw this.
Today,
I was going to dress
like Elsa from "Frozen."
But the dress wasn't available.
- You work really hard.
- It wasn't available.
You're amazing, Young Ji.
She's Cinderella.
We've had a lot of guests
on Running Man this year,
but these three were really special.
(The 3 guests were outstanding.)
They showed memorable performances.
That's right.
What do you remember about them?
(He can barely remember
what happened yesterday.)
Tell us.
It was shocking that Do Kwon's
family name wasn't Ha.
It isn't?
- It's not his real name.
- It's not?
- Are you Kim?
- From the Kims of Andong.
What's your real name?
- It's Kim Yong Gu.
- Yong Gu.
(They forgot about
the friendly name for a while.)
- We can call him Dragon Nine.
- Yong Gu.
- Dragon Nine.
- It's Yong Gu.
Yong Gu.
- I like Yong Gu better.
- Yong Gu.
- That's better.
- He looks just like a Yong Gu.
- He has the face of a Yong Gu.
- Yong Gu.
You should be called Yong Gu.
Why do you look so shabby?
- Shabby?
- Did you say "shabby?"
I'm all dressed up today.
I'm in my nicest outfit today.
What are you talking about?
For Jong Kook, this is...
- like a party.
- Sure.
- He's not wearing shorts.
- I'm all dressed up.
I should go
to like five different places.
I'm afraid of Do Kwon...
because he looks fine
only during the opening.
He changes completely later on.
Why do you pretend to be fine...
only during the opening?
We are going to have a year-end
party with the three guests today.
And we need special performances
to celebrate the party.
- Right.
- Performances?
- Now...
- Are there more guests?
- Here's the first performance.
- What?
"When We Disco" by Yang Se Chan
and Jeon So Min.
- Music, please.
- What?
- "When We Disco?"
- I can't remember...
What is he talking about?
(The music plays anyway.)
- All of a sudden?
- Do you remember the moves?
(Stepping)
(The hairtail stepped
on the queen's foot.)
So Min took off her shoes.
(The duo is always available
with no extra charge.)
This isn't it.
So Min.
This is so funny.
They're so good.
You guys are amazing.
(They make the best use
of the dance moves they learned.)
- For So Min...
- My goodness.
This is the happiest moment
for So Min.
- Right.
- I was startled. Are you all right?
- So Min...
- She even took off her shoes.
The happiest moment
for So Min is when she does...
- something with Se Chan.
- Right.
- Is your foot okay?
- That's true.
- It's strange.
- It hurts a lot.
But Se Chan...
- never likes her back.
- I know.
- He's unbelievable.
- Right. He keeps his distance.
- Why do you keep your distance?
- That's not true.
- It is.
- I'm not asking you out.
I know.
Thank you.
First, you didn't watch
her new drama, did you?
You should watch it.
What am I supposed to do then?
She was really sexy. I was shocked.
- Thank you.
- She's amazing.
- I look really sexy.
- Okay. I'll watch it.
(The queen forces him
to watch her drama.)
She does look sexy.
- She's a vixen.
- I should watch it.
- She's a fox.
- And...
we have the next performer.
- Who is it?
- Next up is...
He's back as a singer.
- It's Ha Dong Hoon.
- I said I wouldn't do it.
He will perform his new song.
- Just do it.
- Ha Dong Hoon's new song.
You should do your best here.
- Is this how you promote your song?
- Give it a try.
I said I wouldn't do it.
I'm done promoting my new song.
Hey, you look cool today.
- Are you performing your song?
- You look nice.
Play Dong Hoon's new song.
(Haha is actually performing
his new song for the first time.)
- This is a good chance for you.
- You're the best.
There won't be any difference...
between the MR and AR
for his live performance.
- They were different at first.
- They were?
- Let's do it.
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Let's begin.
What's the title?
- The title is...
- What did he say?
- The new song...
- Hey.
I'm back with a new solo album
after ten years.
- Okay. What is the song title?
- After ten years?
- Ten years?
- Yes, ten years.
- I'll sing "Gap." Let's go.
- All right. "Gap!"
- "Gap?" Is it "Gap" or "Get?"
- Seriously.
- It's "Gap."
- "Gap?" I see.
("Gap," Ha Dong Hoon's new song)
- Oh, my.
- You look so cool.
(Had I had any gaps in my life)
Is this a trot song?
It sounds like one.
- Is this a trot song?
- Are you imitating Lee Moon Sae?
- He's singing like Lee Moon Sae.
- If anyone
- You sound like Lee Moon Sae.
- What is this?
- He sounds like Lee Moon Sae.
- What's this song?
- This is so unexpected.
- I would be so happy
- I'm surprised.
- Is this really his song?
- I don't know.
- What's this song?
- Let's go!
(While Haha is barely focusing
on his performance,)
(the old man from Seocho-gu barges
onto the stage.)
What is Seok Jin doing?
(What's wrong with him?)
(It's his new song,)
(but it makes So Min dance
a traditional dance.)
(Haha doesn't care about it
and focuses on his performance.)
(Shouting)
(However, the old man in red pants
won't leave the stage.)
- I didn't expect this kind of song.
- He's excited.
- He's really excited.
- I love this song.
(He seems to have enjoyed
himself enough to leave the stage.)
Are we celebrating
Seok Jin's 60th birthday or what?
Elderly people will love this song.
- Let's go!
- Nice!
(It's so exciting.)
(Screaming)
(Seok Jin gets all the attention.)
(Now that Yong Gu joined Seok Jin,)
(it turned into a party.)
(Haha's performance ended
with a lot of distraction.)
(The singer who just released
a new song is about to cry.)
- That's an exciting song.
- By the way...
- That was great.
- It was unexpected.
- It was more like an impression.
- It sounded like...
- Is it a trot song?
- He sang like Lee Moon Sae.
- It sounded like a trot song.
- No.
I saw Seok Jin rolling his eyes back
after a long time.
Did he roll his eyes back?
(He got so excited...)
(that he rolled his eyes back.)
- That's funny.
- The song was really exciting.
- I loved the song.
- Young Ji couldn't dance to it.
- True.
- She couldn't dance to it?
- It's difficult for me.
- She couldn't seem to do it.
- It's a difficult song to dance to.
- Oh, my.
What was more shocking was
that Chan Hee smiled.
(The song was perfect
for his preference.)
Great. That's good.
- That's great.
- The song will be a big hit.
It's a perfect song for people
aged between 50 and 89.
- Between 50 and 89?
- They'll love the song.
- Yes, they'll love his new song.
It's a perfect song
for that age group.
(He can be a top star among people
aged between 50 and 89.)
- You little... I'll kill you.
- That's hilarious.
- I'll kill you.
- Seok Jin...
- Seok Jin and Chan Hee liked it.
- Between 50 and 89?
I mean, he released a new song
as a solo artist after ten years.
Exactly.
But only I got so excited
and danced to the song.
(Only I got excited.)
- Seok Jin really liked the song.
- Indeed.
- People aged between 50 and 89?
- Do Kwon danced too.
- I rarely laugh this hard.
- I can't believe it.
- I laugh so hard that I cried.
- Hey.
Hey, I rarely dance on the show.
- Why did you dance?
- But your song...
Why did you dance to my song?
- Your song made me dance.
- It's a song for young people.
Don't be ridiculous. It's not
what young people would like.
It's what people in their 50s to 80s
would like.
Why did you get excited?
Chan Hee, why did you get excited?
- He's upset.
- This is hilarious.
- Chan Hee, why?
- Just like Tae Jin Ah.
This is so funny.
The melody was so catchy
that I memorized it all.
(Singing)
- This is it, right?
- Yes.
- It's exciting though.
- It's a great song.
- It's a really great song.
- It'll top the charts.
That was funny.
- I love your song.
- It was shocking.
I didn't expect to hear that people
in their 50s and 80s would like it.
It was nostalgic.
- "Nostalgic?"
- The episode we'll shoot today...
will be aired for two weeks...
along with the behind-the-scenes
of the Entertainment Awards...
that will be revealed
for the first time in 11 years.
As you know, food
for year-end parties are important.
- True.
- Yes.
Just as we did before,
when we arrive at the location,
you will receive eggs.
Eggs?
The first team to make
three dishes...
- using eggs wins the race.
- I see.
- We'll have to cook.
You will be divided
into 2 teams of 5 members.
- I see.
- Each of you will receive ten eggs.
At the end of each mission,
one of the recipes will be revealed.
You can use your eggs
or someone else's...
to make those dishes.
The first team to finish
making the three dishes wins.
(The 1st to make 3 dishes wins.)
Even the member with the least eggs
on the winning team...
can be one of the people
to get a penalty.
That is, even if your team finishes
cooking more quickly,
if you use or lose many eggs
of yours, you could get a penalty...
despite your team's victory.
And all members of the losing team
will be the candidates as well.
Three out of the six candidates
for a penalty...
will be chosen through voting.
You can get a ballot
by finding someone else's egg.
Turn in the egg you found
to the staff in charge.
Of course, you can turn in an egg
of someone on your team too.
- This is stressful.
- Try not to be betrayed.
The team that wins each mission will
receive extra eggs.
Winning the missions will
play a big part too.
We divided you into two teams.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Haha, So Min,
and Chung Hwa are on the same team.
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Haha,
So Min, Chung Hwa)
Jong Kook, Do Kwon, Se Chan, Ji Hyo,
and Young Ji are on the second team.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- That's great.
- We have younger people.
This is great.
- Yong Gu.
- We're in our 20s to 40s.
- Team 2049!
- Let's do this!
- Let's name our team Team Gap.
- Team Gap!
- Team Gap.
- I'm glad we're on the same team.
- Me too.
The penalty will be decided
at the end of the race.
As soon as we arrive
at the location,
we'll give you time to hide
your eggs at different places.
- The first team to hide...
- It's hard to hide eggs.
their eggs will be
at a disadvantage...
since the members of the other team
could find them while hiding theirs.
Therefore,
the losing team will go first.
(The 1st team to hide their eggs
will be at a disadvantage.)
- Okay.
- Got it?
- Hurry up and come out.
- Jong Kook, you can come out.
You can't put it in there.
- You must put it on.
- We all came out. Hurry up.
- You can just put it on.
- Done!
All right. Team Jae Seok won.
(Team Jong Kook will go
hide their eggs first.)
The members of the losing team,
- you have to go hide your eggs.
- Okay.
Should we go?
We're Team 2049.
Nice. I like
the cheerful atmosphere.
- Jong Kook, we're first to go.
- Yes?
So they have a good chance
to find our eggs.
True. Let us all stay alert...
and hide our eggs so well...
- they'll never find our eggs.
- Of course.
- As Kwang Soo used to do before.
- That's a great idea.
As Kwang Soo did?
- Just as Kwang Soo did.
- That won't be fun at all.
- I'll bury my eggs underground.
- Just as Kwang Soo did.
- Kwang Soo was incredible...
- The nice team...
We just have to watch out
for Do Kwon today.
Do Kwon, make sure not to betray us.
I'll sacrifice myself for our team.
You're lying. You would never
do that. That's not you.
Then will you pitch in
more than we do?
I'm willing to use all of my eggs
to cook.
Then give one egg to each of us now.
We're not allowed to do that.
That's not true.
- What do you mean?
- We're on the same team.
Bo Pil told me that we're not
allowed to do that.
- He always acts like this.
- Exactly. Gosh.
(While Do Kwon is trying
to dodge the bullet slyly...)
- We've been here before.
- You're right.
- This is where we hid eggs.
- Yes.
- We hid rice cakes and eggs.
- Right.
(This is where last year's
Chuseok special was filmed.)
(The members hid eggs
in different places in the town.)
(Dirty fights took place
over the hidden eggs.)
- We've done it here before.
- I see.
We know where the others would hide
their eggs.
- I bet we can find them easily.
- This place is...
There were a few places
we didn't search last time, right?
- You'll hide your eggs now.
- Okay.
You can hide them inside and outside
of any buildings you see here.
(They can hide their eggs
anywhere they want.)
I hid one here last time,
but someone found it.
Here?
Places like that are
unexpectedly easy to find.
(Since they've been here before,
they're more cautious.)
I'll check that place out.
I see an air conditioner.
Shall I hide one on top of that?
(Jong Kook climbed up on the roof.)
(He's determined to hide his eggs
where no one can find.)
I wonder if anyone would
climb up here.
(He put an egg on the edge.)
(While Jong Kook is hiding his eggs
with strong determination...)
Done.
(Another member seems
very determined.)
I bet no one will find this.
(He buried an egg underground.)
- Can I hide one of my eggs here?
- Sure.
Good. I think it's perfect.
I must keep them intact too, right?
(She found a box that's good
to hide some eggs in it.)
I hid five in here.
(Ji Hyo also hid her eggs
in a hard place to find.)
- Sir, please don't go anywhere.
- Yes?
Got it.
No one can find it
if I hide it here. There's no way.
(Se Chan will hide his egg
in the bushes.)
(This is it!)
Oh, no. It fell off. Gosh.
(Cracking)
Gosh. I didn't know
there was a hole in there.
(Ssaebssaeb broke 1 of his eggs
from the beginning.)
I didn't know
there was a hole in there.
Darn it. I'm so upset.
Gosh, seriously.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is looking
for another place to hide his eggs.)
- It'll take a long time.
- I broke one of my eggs.
- What? My gosh.
- I broke one.
- Wait a second.
- Why?
- You broke your egg?
- Yes.
Why?
Trust me. I'm not lying.
I tried to put one in the bushes.
You saw it, right?
I put it in the bushes,
and it fell off.
- I'll show you later.
- Give me your hand.
I didn't break it in my hand.
It fell off while I was placing it.
I'm telling you the truth.
I bet you got a ballot.
- No, I didn't.
- Where did you break it?
- Trust me. It's over there.
- Where?
- And we can't get a ballot yet.
- Show me later, okay?
- I'll show you.
- Promise me.
- You can see it.
- You have three minutes left.
- Oh, no. What do I do?
- You should hurry.
How about I hide one
on top of the air conditioner?
Hey, wait.
My gosh. I'm upset.
(Se Chan is also looking for a place
to hide his eggs hastily.)
Come on.
Where should I hide my eggs?
(Do Kwon saw Se Chan looking
for a place to hide his eggs.)
(Rushing)
(He's approaching
without letting Se Chan know.)
(Quiet down.)
(Se Chan is hiding his egg without
knowing that Do Kwon is coming.)
(But Do Kwon is watching it all.)
(After hiding the egg,)
(he's moving to another place.)
(Surprised)
(Do Kwon is hiding himself hastily.)
(Se Chan who hasn't noticed
Do Kwon...)
(hid all of the eggs he has left
in 1 place.)
Can anyone find them?
That's impossible.
(It's not impossible.)
(He's leaving happily
without knowing anything.)
(Do Kwon appeared after Se Chan left
like a wild cat.)
(He found Se Chan's eggs.)
Gosh.
(Surprised)
(He found 1 of Se Chan's eggs.)
(This is a great team combination
unless Do Kwon gets greedy.)
(The greedy Do Kwon)
(He runs away excitedly
after betraying his team member.)
You have one minute left.
One minute?
Hurry up. We can win this.
(Meanwhile, Team Jae Seok sets off.)
Oh, boy.
(There's not much time left.)
(Parking Lot)
Gosh, no. This isn't a good place.
(She has to hide all of her eggs
before Team Jae Seok arrives.)
(Where will Young Ji hide her eggs?)
Can I hide an egg here too?
Oh, no. I don't remember
where I hid them. I'm in trouble.
- Okay.
- That's what he does.
Oh, I remember this place.
- The holiday special. Am I right?
- This is the place we filmed it.
Yes, we played
Name Tag Elimination here.
- I remember Starlight Party.
- We'll hide...
- our eggs here.
- Starlight Party wasn't here then.
- It was here.
- It was here then, Seok Jin.
This is where we hid eggs.
- I remember that, but...
- Will we hide our eggs right away?
- Yes.
- I see.
You can go whenever you're ready.
Got it. Okay. Can I hide one there?
- All right. Let's go.
- Let's go.
I don't think I can find
my eggs later.
I took photos of the places
I hid my eggs.
- Did you?
- Yes.
They might have hidden an egg
in here.
(Team Jae Seok started searching
for Team Jong Kook's eggs.)
Jong Kook must've hidden his eggs
in unexpected places.
Oh, I found one.
(He found Young Ji's egg.)
(She underestimated the cast members
and hid it in an easy place.)
It's obvious. We all think alike.
When can I use my ballot
if I get one?
At the end of the race.
Is it important to get many ballots?
You'll vote for the person
to get a penalty.
Where should I hide these? Well...
(So Min is also looking
for Team Jong Kook's eggs.)
I hid my egg in here last time
and lost it.
Oh, my. I got so lucky.
Awesome. They belong to Se Chan.
Okay.
I'm going to use his eggs to cook.
I have to hide my eggs.
I'll do an amazing job
at hiding my eggs this time.
(He's disassembling
the air conditioner while mumbling.)
This is amazing. I'm a genius.
No one will open it, right?
(He hid an egg
inside the air conditioner.)
Okay.
May I come in just for a moment?
- I'm sorry. I'll be quick, ma'am.
- It's okay.
You won't use them, right?
No, I won't.
I'll hide one here.
(She found regular eggs
in the kitchen.)
I'll hide my egg among them, ma'am.
This is great. Oh, my.
Thank you for letting me in, ma'am.
I think I found a great place
to hide my egg.
No one will find it.
I did an amazing job. Great.
Hold on. I'm going to search
the place I hid an egg last time.
(Jae Seok approaches
the air conditioner.)
This air conditioner lays eggs.
(Seok Jin hid his egg in the place
where Jae Seok hid his last time.)
I'm glad that the air conditioner
laid an egg.
Oh, my. It belongs to Seok Jin
of all people.
I thought it wasn't Seok Jin's,
but it turned out to be his.
I bet he thinks that he hid it
where no one could find.
It's so funny.
I hid an egg here last time.
(Seok Sam hid it in an obvious place
and bragged about it.)
Seok Jin,
where did you hide your eggs?
I can't tell you that.
You won't tell me? Why?
I can't tell you that
because you'd steal my eggs.
- Gosh. I'd never do that.
- I'm sure of it.
You would definitely steal them.
You and I are on the same team.
- Still, you'd steal my eggs.
- No way.
Did he hide one there?
(They lost team spirit
a long time ago.)
I'll go to the place
I hid an egg last time.
Hello.
I hid an egg in a place like this.
I hid mine in the fridge
in the kitchen.
- Hello.
Has anyone come in here?
- Someone stopped by.
- Right?
Yes.
Where did that person stop?
- I don't know that.
- Pardon?
You can't answer
that question, right?
Someone came in here for sure.
(Haha figured something out.)
(Chuckling)
Oh, my. There's a lot of eggs here.
It's a good place to hide many eggs.
I knew it.
(He found So Min's eggs.)
Oh, dear.
Thank you, So Min.
(He's putting the eggs
in his pockets.)
I feel bad about taking her eggs,
but I have no choice.
I should go and exchange them
for ballots.
Thank you so much.
(Following Jae Seok,
Haha betrayed his team member.)
(Meanwhile,
Jae Seok is hiding his eggs.)
Can you still see it?
I can't see it now.
I haven't found any eggs yet.
I found one.
- Whose egg was it?
- It was Young Ji's.
- Really?
- Just this one.
It's hard to hide eggs.
It's really hard. I've hidden
all of mine. What about you?
Did you hide all of them
in the same place?
Yes, I did.
I knew it.
- I hid all of them...
- You never change.
(Anxious)
- Why?
- Where will you hide yours?
- Sorry?
I'll go around to the back.
(He avoided answering the question.)
(He started searching
as soon as Jae Seok left.)
(I'm sure it was around here.)
Where did he hide them?
We're not allowed to find
the eggs of those on the same team.
You can exchange an egg of your team
member for a ballot as well.
- Really?
- Can we?
That's not right.
- Really?
- Why?
The other members on my team must be
searching for my eggs.
(Haha is exchanging eggs
for ballots there.)
Haha is exchanging eggs
for ballots there.
Hey.
- I'll exchange two eggs.
- Hey.
Wait, no. They can see me
from over there.
- Why?
- What are you doing here?
Why?
What is it?
(Jae Seok is worried
Haha might find his eggs.)
I think I should hide my eggs
somewhere else.
Why? Why would you do that?
- I really should move them.
- Why?
- I should hide them somewhere else.
- Why? We're on the same team.
- I don't trust you.
- What?
Why? We're on the same team.
You can't take mine.
- Got a death wish?
- But...
Jae Seok, wait.
- We're on the same team.
- No.
- We're teammates. Come on.
- Darn.
- No. I can't let it happen.
- Please.
I'm begging you.
- No.
- You hid them well.
- Why? We're teammates.
- Gosh, seriously.
(Jae Seok runs away
after retrieving his eggs.)
(What a shame.)
Gosh, I can't believe that punk.
(Haha lost his chance.)
I'll exchange one egg for now.
(I'll exchange one egg for now.)
(As he lost a chance to team kill,
he decided to get a ballot.)
It's So Min's egg.
(He turned in 1 of So Min's eggs
and got 1 ballot.)
(Jeon So Min)
(So Min saw Haha exchanging
the egg for a ballot.)
(She spotted Haha.)
I'd like to get ballots.
Two ballots, please.
(So Min noticed
something fishy was going on.)
(She exchanged Se Chan's eggs
for 2 ballots.)
I'll exchange this for a ballot now.
Getting many ballots will help me
avoid a penalty, right?
(The team spirit has been
shattered in pieces.)
Will I remember all the places?
Please go in now.
No one will search here.
(Team Jae Seok finished
hiding their eggs.)
I remember this place clearly.
I remember everything.
I was pregnant when we came here.
What?
That's right. You were
in the early stage of pregnancy.
I had morning sickness
when I was here.
(Running Man, Episode 523,
Chuseok last year)
(So Min and Se Chan played
a married couple for 1 day.)
(Retching)
(And the fake marriage couple were
blessed that day.)
(They enjoyed role playing so much.)
(And they're back here
after 1 year.)
- I had morning sickness.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi, my sister-in-law.
- Hi, my brother-in-law.
- You're here.
- Yes.
I gave birth recently.
I haven't recovered fully yet.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes.
I left my baby with someone.
- Did you give birth to your baby?
- Of course.
Where is your baby
with a protruding mouth?
It turned out
that she took after me.
That's a relief.
I'll sign her up for a beauty
contest. She's so pretty.
- It's a girl?
- Yes.
You must be happy.
- Oh, dear.
- Se Chan.
- Sir, can I have a dried squid?
- What's that?
- Dong Hoon.
- If I'd found at least one egg...
- It was so easy.
- We rearranged your song...
- Really?
- during the break.
- Did you?
- Yes, it's completely different.
- We rearranged the song.
- It's perfect for elderlies.
- Absolutely.
- Sing the first few bars.
- Sing it.
- We'll sing the rest.
- We'll sing it for you.
Sing the part that goes,
"Had I had any gaps in my life."
(Had I had any gaps)
(In my life)
(Your days will be sunny again)
(They mixed his song
with Song Dae Kwan's "Sunny Day.")
It sounds so natural, right?
Indeed.
(Shaking his head)
- Look at his face.
- It wasn't me.
- Had I had gaps
(Had I had any gaps)
(Your days will be sunny again)
- It does match my song though.
- It's perfect.
- Isn't it perfect?
- It'll become a hit for sure.
- Definitely. It'll be a big hit.
- Right.
(It'll be popular among people aged
50 years or over like Seok Sam.)
- Your days
(His new song became more addictive
with the additional trot vibe.)
It's perfect.
It fits perfectly.
(Chuckling)
- Do you know what's scary?
- Tell me.
It's the fact that Jong Kook's
finding it funny.
(It's the fact that Jong Kook's
finding it funny.)
He thinks it's hilarious.
(Look at him.)
Look at him.
He's been loving it
since he first figured it out.
He sang it about ten times
on our way here.
Really?
- That easily?
- Jong Kook's having fun.
(Madness)
He...
- Jong Kook...
- That easily?
Jong Kook thinks
that it's hilarious.
- Because it is.
- See?
- It's hilarious.
- This is not good.
- Guys.
- Look at him having fun.
- He won't forget anytime soon.
- It rolls off your tongue.
This is the first game...
- where you can obtain extra eggs.
- Extra eggs.
It's the Crazy Acting Party.
- What will we be doing?
- Acting?
- Each team will compete in turns.
- Yes.
After hearing
what the scene is about,
you will go into the room...
and choose a person
to act out the scene.
The others will practice
their responses.
- Our responses?
Once your two minutes are up,
you will all exit the room...
and act out the scene
that was given to you.
The opposing team will guess...
which one of you
actually went through with it.
- That sounds like fun.
- For instance,
I got it.
one of you had to smell...
Se Chan's socks.
You will enter the room
and decide who'll actually do it.
- Then...
- We're supposed to guess who.
- We're supposed to guess.
- The others will be acting.
The others will pretend
to have smelled it.
They'd either scrunch up their faces
or act like nothing happened.
- That's right.
- You will get three turns each.
You will decide who goes first,
but the one going first
could be at a disadvantage.
- Right.
- That's right.
Then...
- How about a Game of Wits?
- Why not?
- A Game of Wits?
- The losing team...
will instantly head to the room.
- Do we stand up?
- Yes.
I doubt Seok Jin
will get on his feet.
It's why we need to win.
It looks like Jae Seok
won't be standing either.
- I'll go first, guys.
- Hey.
- I'll go one.
- A Game of Wits.
I'll go at one and self-destruct.
Yes, do that.
- I'll go at one as well.
- Ready...
- I'll go first.
- And go.
- One!
The both of you?
- The three of us...
- Are you kidding me?
- I said I'd go first.
- I said it too.
- We're at a disadvantage now.
- Unbelievable.
- Next round.
- Just go instantly with one.
Ready, get set,
- go.
- Leave them be.
- One.
- Two.
Three.
- Get up.
- Four.
- Do Kwon, go on.
- No.
- You have to get up.
- Six.
- Five.
- Do Kwon, go on.
- No.
- You have to get up.
- Six.
- Not yet.
- The game's over.
- Why didn't you get up?
- Six.
- Not yet.
The game's over.
- Why didn't you get up?
- Hey!
You should've gotten up.
- What were you doing?
- Are you kidding me?
You could've gotten up ages ago.
- The game's over.
- What's wrong with you?
- But there are ten of us.
- Is someone a mafia today?
Seriously?
When were you eliminated?
- In the first round.
- Exactly.
He wasn't aware of the rules!
- Unbelievable.
- This time, you'll sit down.
- Right.
- Sure, we'll sit down.
- You're done for.
- You've been eliminated.
What's with him?
- He loses it after the opening.
- Yong Gu, please!
Unbelievable.
- Yong Gu's killing me.
- Go, Yong Gu.
I'm glad to know
you're just as ditzy.
- Ready, get set, go.
- I'm glad.
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
(Seok Jin and Chung Hwa
are both eliminated.)
Nice!
- We can win this.
- We did great.
Wait for Jae Seok
and just self-destruct with him.
You can win this.
- Jong Kook, just...
- I'll give it a shot.
Is Jae Seok the only one left?
See how Jae Seok does it!
- You fools!
- I can be faster.
- Right.
- He will beat all three.
- Just you watch.
- You'll see me winning this.
- Okay.
Just you watch.
- Nice!
- You'll be in awe.
- Triple kill!
- Let's do this.
Just wait for Jae Seok
to say a number.
The Master of Games will show you.
- The MG.
- The Master of Variety Shows,
the Master of PPL,
and the Master of Games.
(Yu Jae Seok,
a master in many fields)
Ready, get set, go.
- One.
- Two.
(Jong Kook says one first
by mistake.)
- One will be out.
- He won this round.
(Did you see that?)
He eliminated two actually.
They could say it at the same time.
But... Three.
- Four.
- No one was eliminated then.
- Okay.
- Now it's down to two.
- I know what I must do now.
- I wasn't expecting that.
- Nicely done.
- The Master of Games.
The Master of Games.
- I get it now.
- The Master of Games.
That was cool, Jae Seok.
Young Ji, don't do anything.
- Just stand there.
- Got it.
Let them two compete.
- Get ready.
- The viper's out to get him.
And go!
- Tensions are high.
- Young Ji, wait for it.
Young Ji, wait for it.
Jae Seok, now.
Jong Kook's going
to say "one" together.
- One.
Okay.
- I said it.
- No way.
She wasn't fast enough.
- She said it.
- But a second later.
- She said "One."
- I heard it.
I heard her say it.
- She didn't make it.
- She wasn't fast enough.
- You didn't sit down though.
- Okay!
(Young Ji didn't sit
which is why it doesn't count.)
- Okay.
- Okay, fine.
- Hear me out though.
- Triple kill!
- Yu Jae Seok!
- Had I had any gaps
- The Master of Games.
- In my life
- She didn't manage to sit.
- Your days will be
- What are you going to do about it?
- I don't know.
- But...
- I'm the Master of Games.
- She didn't manage to do it.
Normally when we play...
the Game of Wits,
- you consider this as a fail.
- She didn't manage to do it.
- That's right.
- You eliminate that person.
- She wasn't fast enough.
- But she didn't sit down.
No, hear me out.
When we normally play this game...
(He chokes the producer
with hard facts.)
You consider this as a failure.
But the situation
is different today.
This is what I want to do today, I guess.
(This is what I want to do today,
I guess.)
(He shuts Jong Kook down
with an unbreakable logic.)
Right, okay.
(For some reason, that answer
puts a smile on everyone's faces...)
(regardless of their teams.)
Fine, I hear you.
- Okay.
- Nice.
Take this!
(He celebrates
with the Russian folk dance.)
(You!)
Okay. The last round will be
rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- If you win...
- If I win...
- It'll go down in history.
Triple kill!
Rock-paper-scissors
(How will it end for the hero?)
- The MG.
- I'm amazed.
Triple kill!
- The MG.
- Rock-paper-scissors
Okay!
(Jae Seok loses.)
(He falls flat on his face
when it really matters.)
- After two great rounds?
- That's what you lose at?
But you were on a roll.
- It was all for nothing!
- My gosh!
My gosh!
- Goodness!
- I bet...
the Russian dance annoyed him.
Is this the real him?
- Okay.
- All right.
Let me tell you your scene then.
- Sure.
- It wasn't easy.
- Your scene...
- We're up first.
Only one will eat
a spicy Cheongyang chili...
while the others will eat a chili
that is not spicy at all.
I have a high tolerance
for spicy food.
- But I don't.
- I have a low tolerance.
They must exit
as soon as they've eaten it.
- Right.
- You must exit right away.
- We'll choose randomly.
- I can't eat spicy food.
(They'll decide who'll eat
the spicy chili inside.)
My gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- These are the non-spicy ones.
- This is the worst.
- This is the spicy one.
- We're doomed.
- Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
Seok Jin and Jae Seok
can't tolerate spicy food.
- Really?
- Yes, and it'll show.
Who's good with spicy food?
- Haha.
- That's right.
It could be a Running Man member,
but they might have Chung Hwa eat it
since she's a guest.
Because Chung Hwa...
- She's the guest.
- They started acting already.
- To get her involved.
- I see.
- It'll be Chung Hwa then.
- That's my guess.
Haha usually lets the guest
have more screen time.
That's because
he wants to slack off.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
Nice. No way!
- He's faking it.
- Right.
- It's nothing to shout about.
- It's a lie.
- It's to throw us off.
Talk about old-fashioned.
So...
Must we eat the whole chili?
- It's spicy.
- I can smell the spiciness.
It's killing me!
(Which one of them
ate the spicy chili?)
- Please take your seats.
- Our seats?
- All right.
- Oh, no.
It's killing me.
My gosh. Oh, no.
- Oh, no.
- Here we go.
It's killing me.
Please sit on the cushions.
Just a second.
- She...
- I'm...
- My gosh.
- It was super spicy.
(They all exit the room in agony.)
- Oh, no.
- Why can't I stop laughing?
Chung Hwa means business today.
You're taking this
way too seriously.
- Just a second.
- Chung Hwa...
- You will get one minute.
- Did you throw up?
I bet you spat it out.
What's that in your mouth?
Chung Hwa looks like she threw up.
- Of course not.
- Like this.
Jae Seok, my gosh.
Jong Kook, check out his eyes.
So Min's in tears.
No, she's acting.
- It's really spicy.
- She's that good of an actor?
She's the worst.
- She's acting right now.
- No, it's really spicy.
The fact that
she seems to be acting...
No, it's the truth.
Could...
- her acting be this awkward?
- I think it's Jae Seok.
- I doubt it.
- Seok Jin can't tolerate it,
- so I doubt he ate the chili.
- Right.
Our guess is Haha or Jae Seok.
We decided by playing
rock-paper-scissors.
- But...
- We played rock-paper-scissors,
- so the person was chosen randomly.
- He's faking it.
Can I have some water?
There's no way
Haha would talk that way.
He's good with spicy food.
(No way!)
(Here's another person
who is being awkward.)
I bet he was just thirsty.
- He suddenly got thirsty.
- Do we have 30 seconds left?
Jae Seok's seems
too peaceful right now.
Look at the tone of his skin.
So Min, can we see your ears?
- My ears?
- Yes, show us.
We can see everyone else's,
but not yours.
- Do you want to see my ears?
- Yes.
Show us your ears.
- It's not her.
- She didn't eat the chili.
She's giggling now.
Check out Seok Jin's gaze.
One might think
he ate jelly instead.
- Something sweet.
- I don't see...
- a drop of sweat on his forehead.
- Right.
Chung Hwa's the one
with a damp forehead.
It's time to make your decision.
I don't think we have a choice.
I can actually smell
the Cheongyang chili.
(Groaning)
I can actually smell
the Cheongyang chili.
(Groaning)
The guest today...
No one's suspecting him.
No one...
- is suspecting him.
- But Jae Seok...
He usually does this
after eating spicy food,
but I didn't see that today.
It's time to make a decision.
I don't think we have a choice.
- She's the guest.
- They'd get her involved.
- The guest?
- Please make a decision.
I bet they let Chung Hwa
take center stage.
If you eat something spicy,
you can't keep your mouth closed
like Seok Jin.
- One...
- You'd want to open your mouth.
- Two...
- He suddenly opened his.
- That's right.
- We choose Chung Hwa.
What do you say?
Look at Jae Seok
trying to stay in character.
- It's not him.
- I think it's Jae Seok.
I think it could be him too.
Should we say it's him instead?
I can smell...
the Cheongyang chili from here...
and it's whenever
he lets out his breath.
Two...
Please make your final decision.
In 1, 2, 3.
- No, it's...
- Shall we just pick the guest?
Please choose one. In 1, 2, 3.
- Cha Chung Hwa.
They picked Chung Hwa.
The one who had
the real spicy chili...
will get up on the count of three.
- In 1, 2...
- I don't think it's her.
- No, it's not him.
- It's not him.
Three!
- It was Jae Seok.
- For real?
(It was Jae Seok.)
(Grunting)
I knew it.
- For real?
- Chung Hwa is such a good actress.
Well done!
It was really spicy, right?
- Good work.
- Good one!
- It was really spicy.
My goodness.
Eat the whole thing.
Let's see.
It's...
(Grunting)
- It's really spicy.
- He's already reacting to it.
- It must be spicy.
Ours is spicy too.
We're in trouble. I got hiccups.
I thought Jae Seok was acting.
(He had to drink water
to ease the spiciness.)
He actually drank water
because it was too spicy.
I can still smell
the Cheongyang chili.
All right. The acting Team Jong Kook
is going to carry out...
Us?
One of you will do
an elephant trunk spin...
and get out right away.
- How can they act that out?
- The one who did the spin?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Let's all leave the same way.
- When we leave...
- Or we could...
- We can all go like this.
We could all walk the same way.
Someone must've hidden their eggs
inside the house.
- What?
- In the bag?
I bet. Someone must've hidden
their eggs in the house.
- Definitely.
- They must've hidden them inside.
(The hyenas look for eggs
while Jong Kook is away.)
I really can't find
a single egg they hid.
They must be spinning inside.
They're so loud.
You should watch them.
They'll jump out of the room
as soon as they're done.
- All right.
- Oh, they'll jump out right away?
(Their first reaction
will be the biggest hint.)
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I was going to sit here,
but Seok Jin...
was afraid his seat would be taken.
The seat where he can
lean his back against the wall.
So he pushed me
to go in front of me.
(A petty man's race)
You noticed that?
- He pushed me like this.
- Everyone.
They're coming out.
(It's time for the elephants
to come out.)
- They're so loud.
- You need to check their eyes.
- He's not it.
- He's making it obvious.
- You need to check their eyes.
- They're so loud.
- He's not it.
- He's definitely not it.
- Hey.
- You fail, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is...
Watch them.
- You fail, Jong Kook.
- It's not him either.
What's with him?
(The elephants
can't control their bodies.)
(The 2021 elephant show)
It's not him.
- It could be Se Chan.
- Hey.
No, it's not him. Hey.
- Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
- It's not him.
Could it be Se Chan?
He's going overboard on purpose.
- She's not it.
- It could be Se Chan.
- No, it's not him.
- Look at him.
- Could it be Se Chan?
- It could be Se Chan.
He's going overboard on purpose.
- It's either Do Kwon or Se Chan.
- It's definitely not Young Ji.
- It's not Young Ji.
I think it's Ji Hyo.
- No, she's acting.
- Hey.
Is she acting?
I think it's Jong Kook.
I think so too.
- Because he's acting so well.
- He's gasping for air.
It's Do Kwon
whose acting was most desperate.
- He's amazing.
- Ji Hyo is doing so well too.
(One of them is acting
like they're dizzy.)
It doesn't look like
Ji Hyo's stomach hurts.
But she's...
It looks like
she wants to take a dump.
(He thinks she has problems
with her digestion.)
- I think it's Jong Kook.
- Me too.
- No way.
- But Young Ji's soles are dirty.
Is that so?
Look at them.
- Young Ji.
- But last time she was here,
- they were dirty too.
- Are they always dirty?
(They think Young Ji's soles
are always dirty.)
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- It's a routine.
- I had only one pair, so...
- You had only one pair?
- It's a routine.
- A routine of a public show.
- Right. It's the routine.
But Young Ji's soles...
Her soles are dirty.
They really are dirty.
- What's wrong with them?
- Look at them.
Do Kwon, you must be feeling okay.
No, mine are black.
Are you feeling okay now?
- All right!
- Yes.
I think it's Se Chan
because he's pale.
- He's pale.
- I've always been pale.
You've always been pale?
You're making excuses.
Hold on.
Can they come this close to us?
- They can't sound us out like this.
- Can I approach him?
- It's too close.
- Look at him moving away.
He can't come this close.
- You can't touch us.
- Right. This isn't allowed.
Look at him. He's being defensive
and coming up with excuses.
No, I think it's Jong Kook.
- His hair is messy.
- Right?
I think it's
either Se Chan or Jong Kook.
I also think
it's either Se Chan or Jong Kook.
- I think it's Se Chan.
- Have you made up your mind?
Yes. The lines around his mouth
look deeper than earlier.
- And he's pale too.
- He's aged a lot.
The color of your face
is different from your neck's.
Look at him.
His mouth is protruding more.
Then let's choose Se Chan.
- All right.
- Okay, let's pick Se Chan.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Yang Se Chan!
Tell everyone who did the spin
on the count of three.
Based on the soles,
it must be Young Ji.
Please get up on the count of three.
- One,
- It must be him.
two,
three!
Is it Do Kwon?
Who is it?
Is it you?
(It's Do Kwon?)
(It was Do Kwon
whom they didn't doubt.)
It didn't even occur to me
that it'd be Do Kwon.
We never even mentioned him.
(Actually, Do Kwon,
who easily made it out...)
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
(He lost, so he had
to do the elephant trunk spin.)
- Ten!
- Let's go!
Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
Just go ahead.
(He leaned on the wall
and tripped the others.)
(He made it obvious
that he was dizzy.)
He looked just fine.
- He acted for real.
- He looked like...
I couldn't let go
because I was afraid I'd fall.
- He was trying to grab onto it.
- I had to.
(It's all thanks to him.)
- I thought he was going overboard.
- That was hilarious.
I was really dizzy.
This is hard.
- It's hard.
- It's Team Jae Seok's mission.
What is it?
One of you has to put on the
low-frequency therapeutic apparatus.
(One of their low-frequency
therapeutic apparatus will be on.)
We can definitely catch one.
I should've done that, right?
- This is difficult.
- It's funny though.
- There are apparatuses.
- You all should pretend.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- Where should we wear them?
- All of us should wear it?
- Yes, and you need to act.
- Oh, I need to act?
Okay, got it.
We need to decide now.
I'll do it since you were the chili.
I mean, you ate the chili.
You scared me.
(I'll do it
since you were the chili.)
(Startled)
Since he is the chili?
(What a coincidental mistake.)
You startled me, Chung Hwa.
What do you mean
by "since you were the chili?"
Come on, Chung Hwa.
- You scared everyone.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(After her shocking
slip of the tongue...)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
It's fun to fool others.
Let's do it.
(It's time to find out
who has it on.)
(The low-frequency
therapeutic apparatus lovers enter.)
This is so funny.
It's not Haha for sure.
This is hilarious.
Chung Hwa is amazing.
- Chung Hwa is amazing.
- Seok Jin is good.
What is this?
She's good.
Is this a joke? Oh, no!
- It's Chung Hwa.
It must be Chung Hwa.
(He's certain that it's Chung Hwa.)
Look at her hands.
That can't be fake.
Gosh, this is...
- What's wrong with this?
- This is...
It's Chung Hwa.
- This is driving me crazy.
- If it's her, she's really good.
- I can't...
- This is...
- I can't act.
Look at this!
No, that's fake.
- I'm sure it's not Chung Hwa.
- It's not Chung Hwa.
- Gosh, what do I do?
She's getting the shocks too late.
She's not even stretching
her hands out.
It's So Min.
So Min has been getting
regular shocks.
It's So Min.
This is no joke.
Please sit down now.
I can't sit, you jerk!
- Please sit down.
- I can't!
- Sit down.
- Seok Jin.
- Can you not cuss?
- I couldn't help it.
It wasn't even the right timing
to cuss.
- I couldn't help it!
- Why would you cuss?
I couldn't help but cuss.
- Please keep going.
- Why would you cuss?
- Keep going.
- Chung Hwa.
Chung Hwa.
We have one more minute.
Let's see each of you
stretching your arms out...
and doing this gesture. In 1, 2, 3.
- No, we won't.
- We can't do it.
I can't.
All right.
So Min, try it. In 1, 2, 3.
Gosh, this is so funny.
- Gosh.
- Chung Hwa.
In 1, 2, 3.
I can't do it!
- In 1, 2, 3.
- It hurts, you know?
- I got it. I can do it now.
- It hurts.
It hurts.
I can't do this.
- Seven, eight.
- Seok Jin, show us.
You see? She's on beat.
- You're right.
- She is.
She's on beat.
Chung Hwa is on beat.
She reacts every eight seconds.
(Do Kwon thinks Chung Hwa trembles
every eight seconds.)
Jong Kook!
I'm certain it's Chung Hwa.
- It's Chung Hwa for sure.
- It's her for sure.
(Exclaiming)
Jong Kook!
I'm certain it's Chung Hwa.
(Staring)
- Ji Hyo, Chung Hwa is...
- I think it's Jae Seok.
- We'll give you ten seconds.
I think it's Jae Seok.
Hey, it's Jae Seok.
- No, it's Chung Hwa.
- No, it's not.
- It's not Jae Seok.
- It's Chung Hwa.
She's laughing.
It's because...
Her muscles aren't responding.
No, it's not him.
Since you can see them in action,
please pick one right away.
(The four candidates who are
giving their best performances)
In 1, 2...
- In 1, 2, 3.
- His muscles are budging a lot.
- It's Chung Hwa!
(Team Jong Kook picks Chung Hwa.)
Please get up.
In 1, 2, 3.
Stop it!
It's Chung Hwa.
- Hey!
- It's not her.
(It's Yu Jae Seok.)
- It was Jae Seok.
I told you I saw it.
I saw him right next to him.
He kept twitching.
- Goodness.
- Look,
- his muscles kept twitching.
- So you can see it.
I can see it now.
Wait, that hurts.
It hurts, right?
I told you.
(His whole body twitched
and made it obvious.)
It really hurts, right?
(His whole body twitched
and made it obvious.)
- It wasn't me.
- His muscles kept twitching.
Chung Hwa is really good.
- You know...
- Wait, Chung Hwa.
How come you're so good at acting?
How could you bend your arms
like this?
It was too intense.
Chung Hwa is really good at acting.
- I really thought she was the one.
- She was incredible.
- Chung Hwa went like this.
- Isn't she incredible?
- She's a great actress.
- She even counted the beats.
Exactly. She did.
This is what Team Jong Kook
will do next.
- That was close.
- Let's get them.
It's the last mission.
- That sounds difficult.
- You need to find the person...
who has real ice in their stomach.
One of you will be holding
an ice pack,
and the rest will be holding
a pack of a similar size.
- Let's go.
- So there's water in it instead.
Where should we put them?
In our stomach?
Maybe they'll pick the same person
as they did before.
Young Ji might roll on the floor.
And Se Chan might act the same.
Se Chan always came out first.
I know. He always did.
It's because he likes to act up.
That's true.
(Vocalizing)
You see?
As soon as I was done saying that.
- He likes getting attention.
- It's hilarious.
(Se Chan is ready to act up
as much as he wants.)
(Who is holding the real ice pack?)
Oh, gosh!
(Screaming)
What did he say?
If it's that bad,
you must go to the bathroom.
(Se Chan's amazing acting
of needing to relieve himself)
Gosh, Se Chan.
- Se Chan has never been it, right?
- Gosh, he's so funny.
(Perhaps Se Chan has
the ice pack for real?)
(One of them is holding
a cold ice pack.)
Is it an ice block?
Or are they ice cubes?
It's not dry ice, is it?
Try drinking water, Se Chan.
Se Chan, try drinking water. Gosh.
(Scowling)
- Se Chan.
- Try drinking water.
Gosh, I hate the sight of him.
Se Chan, can you try
pressing your stomach?
- Sorry?
- Try pressing your stomach.
- It's that bad?
- It's not him.
- It's not Se Chan.
He's out. Please stop. You're out.
Young Ji, can you try
pressing your stomach?
- Try pressing it.
- Me?
Press it harder. Is she the one?
It's not Young Ji.
I think she's pretending.
(He finds her more suspicious.)
- Goodness.
- Do Kwon, can you press yours?
No.
You're crouching.
It must hurt.
Look at Se Chan.
(Screaming)
I think I'll be really upset
if it's really him.
It's not him.
- It's not him.
- It can't be him.
No, I think it's him.
It must be him because the rest
are laughing at him.
They wouldn't have laughed
if he was acting.
They're laughing because they know
it's him.
- They're laughing because he's it.
- It's not the shape...
- of ice.
- It is Se Chan.
- They're laughing because it's him.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Yang Se Chan. It's you, right?
(They decide it's Se Chan
after seeing the rest laugh at him.)
- It's him. I'm sure it is.
- They're laughing because it's him.
Because it's him.
- It is him.
- On the count of three,
- please get up.
- Hurry!
- In 1, 2...
- Is it really him?
Three!
(Who is carrying the ice pack?)
- He's acting.
- It must be him.
- Is it Jong Kook?
- It's Jong Kook.
It's Jong Kook.
It was Young Ji.
(Young Ji was carrying
the ice pack.)
Gosh, it's so upsetting.
It's so annoying.
This is really upsetting.
- I told you.
- It was Young Ji.
I told you.
They might think it's your turn
to be it.
- Comedians get penalties a lot.
- They do.
Let me put it here.
(Young Ji volunteered
to put it in her belly...)
(instead of Se Chan
who was more at risk.)
Goodness.
- Se Chan, you're so annoying.
- Ji Hyo must've planned this.
(Se Chan's acting caused
critical damage to Team Jae Seok.)
Oh, gosh.
He's so annoying
although we're on the same team.
I know. He's so annoying.
Darn him.
I want to hit his mouth.
We'll give two eggs
for Team Jong Kook as they won.
- They're for the whole team?
- They're raw eggs.
- They get only two?
- That's too little.
- They're for our team.
- Our names are on it too.
It's time for lunch and to cook.
- What are we making?
- Among three party dishes,
the first one you'll make...
is a hamburg steak.
- It sounds delicious.
- I like it.
We have
all the basic ingredients ready.
You only need to take simple steps.
You need five eggs for this dish.
(They need to use 5 eggs.)
(Today's party dishes)
(The first dish, hamburg steak)
We only need three more.
You can use your own or others'.
- You can use other team's eggs.
- We need five eggs?
Do whatever it takes
to find five eggs.
We can each contribute an egg each.
(But it's advantageous for them
if they don't use their own eggs.)
Since we need to use 5,
let's contribute 1 each.
- Let's contribute one each.
- We should bring one.
Whether you use your own
or others' eggs.
- Let's each bring one.
- Okay, let's do that.
We should look for their eggs
instead of using ours.
Then I'll look for one too.
- I'll go look for eggs.
- We're not using ours, right?
We can find three at least.
We can find the other team's eggs.
- We can look for them now, right?
- Yes.
(It's time to cook
their first dish.)
I need to find our team's eggs too.
(He hurriedly looks for eggs
here and there.)
(Impressed)
Gosh, this is...
(Se Chan easily found
Young Ji's eggs in the cupboard.)
I found Young Ji's eggs.
(Se Chan easily found
Young Ji's eggs in the cupboard.)
Whom should I vote for?
(Se Chan is holding
Young Ji's eggs.)
I'll get two ballots then.
(He exchanges them
with ballots right away.)
Yes. I'm sorry, Young Ji.
I had no other choice.
(Se Chan earned two ballots
by betraying Young Ji.)
(Exclaiming)
(He found two more eggs
of Young Ji's.)
I'll exchange it with one ballot.
You found them again?
Young Ji is in trouble.
- You're exchanging just one?
- I'll give it back to Young Ji.
(Se Chan acquired 3 ballots.)
Mine must be here.
I should check it.
(Surprised)
They took... They took this?
Right? There were two.
Thank you.
Two of my eggs were stolen.
I put two eggs there,
but they're gone.
(The 168cm tall thief
who stole So Min's eggs)
(It's Haha.)
(He sneaked into the kitchen
while others are outside.)
(He used So Min's egg
he was holding.)
(He used one of her eggs
as a ballot...)
(and one as an ingredient.)
(And soon...)
Jae Seok, the recipe...
Whose egg is that? I got one too.
I got two eggs.
Put them in here.
Mine was stolen.
The process doesn't look good,
but it'll be fine...
as long as it tastes good.
- You were already working on it?
- Chung Hwa.
- We need an egg.
- Did you bring an egg?
It took long
because I had to find mine.
- Crack it in here.
- Give it to them.
You got five eggs.
- We got it?
- I have no more eggs.
We got five already.
We should hurry up and make it.
- We should all work on it.
- Hurry.
- Work on that first.
- What is it?
- Heat up the pan already.
- What's with our team?
- Okay.
- Let's hurry.
- We need to hurry.
- Hurry up and make it!
- We need to heat up the pan.
- The eggs...
(How is Team Jong Kook doing?)
Gosh, they took mine.
They took mine.
(Team Jong Kook
is still collecting eggs.)
Gosh, both of my eggs are gone.
What do I do?
I think all of mine are taken.
(Meanwhile, what is Do Kwon up to?)
(He found Chung Hwa's egg...)
(by the stone wall.)
Let me exchange this with a ballot.
I need an insurance for myself.
(Do Kwon exchanges the egg he found
with a ballot.)
(Just as Jong Kook worried,
Do Kwon gets more greedy.)
I didn't find one.
The more the ballots,
the better, right?
Here. I want to exchange it
with a ballot.
(He exchanges the egg he found
with a ballot again.)
- Guys, look at this.
- It looks good.
- It looks so good.
- It's looking good.
It really feels like a holiday party.
Look at that.
We're done.
- We got it.
- They haven't even started.
- Here it is.
- We finished one dish.
- We're done.
- We won, right?
- We should start cooking.
- I guess I really can't find one.
How did they hide them so well?
(It's time for the second mission.)
If we didn't have kimchi
It's this song.
(Team Jong Kook is in good spirit
although they were late.)
- What was it again?
- Delicious ramyeon
Jae Seok, they have
such great teamwork.
Hey, what's the point
of having good teamwork?
They'll part ways
after today anyway.
(They're now used to
the instant family love.)
What's the point?
He said they'll part ways
after the shoot.
The three of them
are on "How Do You Play?"
- I know, this team...
- That was a bit rude of you.
- What do you mean?
- He's right!
- What was that about?
- I'm not on that show!
- What do you mean?
- I was on the show temporarily.
You were smiling from ear to ear
after getting an award.
It doesn't mean the three of us
only work for "How Do You Play?"
It's a gganbu show.
It's a sister show of Running Man.
If it is, then you should
let us be on it too.
I'm planning it.
- Nice.
- I told them what I wanted.
- You should arrange it.
- I already told Bo Pil too.
- Will you wait?
- That's what I'm saying.
You're also thinking
about it too, right? This is nice.
- Will it air...
- It will be innovative.
- on both channels?
- That will be nice.
Will we gather around...
and film for a day?
- No.
- Will it be like that?
We are still talking.
It will be like a joint shoot.
We need to figure it out.
You should arrange it...
in the middle.
I will take care of it.
Hurry up and do it.
- Okay.
- Do a good job.
Anyang Loser should be on that show.
Can we be mean to the other members?
If it happens, you will be the host.
I will be so stressed out.
- Which side are you on?
- Now that the plan is underway...
You should dress up as a bat.
Come on.
I am a member of Running Man.
Then Haha will be paid twice, right?
- Will he be paid twice?
- Right?
Don't say it like that.
It's the same for us.
If we appear on that show,
we need to receive payment.
Of course.
I will talk to them about it.
To whom will you talk?
Why would you volunteer yourself?
- To whom will you talk?
- I will talk to them.
I will talk to Hye Jeong,
the scriptwriter of the show.
He thinks of her as his mom.
(He thinks of her as his mom.)
Mom.
- He thinks of her as his mom.
- Seriously.
So "How Do You Play?"
is like your mom...
and Running Man is like your dad.
While searching for the eggs,
various emotions must have piled up.
- Yes.
- Of course.
Now,
please write down
five simple punishments...
you want the other team to receive
on a piece of paper...
and turn it in.
- Simple punishments?
- Simple punishments.
They shouldn't be too big.
- They shouldn't be too much work.
- Do we discuss this as a team?
- Do we write them down separately?
- Write them down separately.
Separately?
Just make sure they don't overlap.
- I want to see gourd-breaking.
- Gourd-breaking? Okay.
- Okay.
- I have never seen it.
- Gourd-breaking.
- Gourd-breaking?
- Did you write them down?
- Yes.
Take turns to reveal the penalty.
My penalty is getting slapped
with a wet wipe.
- It's a fun penalty.
- It's fun.
My penalty is the eagle.
- What's that?
- Se Chan will explain.
It's pulling the philtrum.
- That's a good one.
- It's fun.
- It will look funny.
- Do Kwon.
- It's fun.
Getting hit on the sole.
- That's a good one.
- Getting hit on the sole.
- What should be used?
- A cane.
Young Ji.
Drawing rosy cheeks on the face.
That's a cute one.
- Isn't it too cute?
- Okay.
Mine is pulling the sideburns.
- Mine is drawing on the face.
- Drawing on the face.
- Getting slapped with a wet towel.
- A wet towel.
It will hurt.
Getting slapped with water.
That's a good one.
That's a neat and nice penalty.
- So Min.
- Eating your raw eggs.
- Raw eggs?
- It's the worst.
- Raw eggs.
- That's annoying.
- Mine is gourd-breaking.
- It's a fun penalty.
- Gourd-breaking.
- I really wanted to try it.
Let's win.
We will be fine if we win.
- I will give you the rules.
- Okay.
Running Man is well-known
for its penalties.
To celebrate the year-end,
the second mission...
will cover a variety of penalties.
It's the Penalty Party,
Good Penalty.
- Okay.
- Good penalty
You will use the beats
of the strawberry game.
The penalty you pick...
will be your name.
(The penalty you pick
will be your name!)
So we need to say,
"Drawings on the face."
Eating your raw eggs.
So this will be our name.
It will go like that.
(Good Penalty Rules)
(1. The penalty you choose
becomes your name.)
(2. Use the name to play
the Strawberry Game.)
(3. After the round, the losing team
will carry out the penalty.)
Chung Hwa, please pick a penalty.
Okay.
(Everyone picks a penalty.)
- What is it?
- Show us.
Getting rosy cheeks drawn
on the face.
It's the one I wrote.
You can't even say that
to attack her.
We will let you shorten it
to "Getting rosy cheeks drawn."
- Getting rosy cheeks drawn.
Getting rosy cheeks drawn.
It's so hard.
- I got "Eagle."
- It's a good one.
- Eagle.
- Okay.
Let's attack her only.
Getting caned on the sole.
Getting hit by a wet tissue.
It's an easy one.
- Getting the sideburns pulled.
Getting the sideburns pulled.
- Okay.
- Getting the sideburns pulled.
My goodness. Eating your raw eggs.
Eating your raw eggs.
- Getting slapped with water.
- Gourd-breaking.
Getting hit by a wet towel.
Drawings on the face.
- Eating your raw eggs.
- One, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight.
- Eating your raw eggs.
"Getting hit by a wet tissue"
is an easy one.
Getting the sideburns pulled.
- Getting hit by a wet tissue.
- Getting the sideburns pulled.
(Each one of them practices hard.)
Let's do well.
- Let's begin.
- This is so hard.
- Good penalty
Getting hit by a wet tissue, eight.
Getting...
What did you say?
(He babbled
because he was too pressed.)
- What did you say?
Getting what?
How am I supposed to say it
eight times?
- Getting.
- I should have started right away.
Good
- Good
- Good penalty
Getting hit by a wet towel, six.
Getting hit by a wet towel.
- There you go.
- Okay.
Getting rosy cheeks drawn, three.
- Pass.
Rosy.
(Rosy)
Why did you just repeat "Rosy?"
Getting rosy cheeks drawn.
This is hard.
- I am sorry.
- Okay.
- This is hard.
- This is too hard.
- Let's just play jachigi.
- Okay.
You failed.
- Chung Hwa, start over.
- Should I start over?
I don't remember
other people's names.
- Drawings on the face.
- Drawings on the face. Okay.
- Go for "Eagle."
- Okay.
(Telling her whom to attack)
That's me, Seok Jin.
What is wrong with you?
(He asked her to attack
her teammate.)
That's me.
- He told me to attack "Eagle."
- That's me.
- She is our teammate.
- You are "Eagle?"
I thought it was his name.
What's your name? Show me.
Show me. Let's play fair and square.
(He shows the back side.)
What?
- is that it?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Okay.
- Is that it?
- I see.
- Let's go.
One.
- Good penalty.
- Let's go.
- Gourd-breaking, three.
- Hey.
- What was that?
Gourd-breaking, three.
(She ignored the rhythm.)
Hold on. Excuse me.
What was that?
She hasn't partied much.
- You should understand.
- Chung Hwa.
We played the game multiple times.
Gourd-breaking, three.
I couldn't believe it.
- We played the game multiple times.
- Gourd-breaking, three.
- Go easy on her.
- It was just wrong.
- She is out.
- I mean...
- Hey.
- Seriously.
Chung Hwa went through a lot.
- Still...
- She doesn't go out much.
- I am not used to playing games.
- She doesn't watch TV...
- or drink.
- She isn't used to it.
Everyone here is the same.
I haven't partied much either.
You have partied much.
- Come on.
- That's not true.
I just followed the older guys
to the nightclub a few times.
(That's right!)
I took him to places.
I used to take him with me.
You are right.
That's so funny.
A few times.
I told you that
he used to book rooms.
"Jae Seok."
I did that.
- "I did that."
- All right.
Haha, you can start.
- Good penalty
- Let's go.
Eating your raw eggs, three.
Raw... Raw eggs.
What?
- What do you want?
- Say it properly.
- I did it.
- His pronunciation was off.
- No, you didn't.
I did it pretty well.
- His pronunciation was off.
- I heard him clearly.
I did it pretty well.
Eating raw... What was that?
I thought you were talking about
eating jjajangmyeon.
It sounded completely different.
I heard him clearly.
- What?
- My ears hurt...
because he enunciated so well.
Jae Seok became his target. Okay.
- Your pronunciation was off.
- Seriously.
Okay. I got it.
- Okay.
- I got it. Okay.
Okay.
He said "Okay."
- Hold on.
- Let's go.
You were the one
who mispronounced the words.
Let's keep going.
- Okay.
- Let's keep going.
- Hold on.
- Good penalty
- Good penalty.
(The 1st punishment has begun.)
Sideburns, six...
Getting the sideburns, seven.
What was that?
(He babbled.)
- What was that?
What was that?
Mr. Raw Raw Eggs.
Mr. Raw Raw Eggs?
- You wrote this name.
- I became too excited.
- What was that?
- Seriously.
- I became too excited.
You should have understood me earlier.
How are you so bad at this game?
"Raw raw eggs."
- He got worked up.
- You wrote this.
- Start over then.
- What is up with him?
- You wrote this.
- Start over then. I got it.
Let's begin. Good penalty
- This is insane.
- Good penalty
- Don't let them win.
When will you stop?
Getting the sideburns pulled, six.
(Determined)
Getting the sideburns pulled
(Melodious)
(He said it with a nasal voice
without minding the rhythm.)
His hands moved on their own.
Seriously.
How am I supposed to do this?
- Getting the sideburns pulled
- It's a hard one.
How am I supposed to do this?
It's so hard.
It isn't hard.
- Let's not play this game.
- In this game,
there is no such thing as a rally.
We can take anyone out at once.
Seok Jin, everyone is thinking that.
That's why I'm just trying
to cheer you up here, you jerk.
- For goodness' sake.
- Okay?
He is getting hounded by both sides.
If you win a point,
you will win Round One.
Let's go.
Let's shout it out.
- Good
- Good penalty
- Same
Only those
who have received a penalty know
The taste of it
- Jjan jjan jjan
Since I have received
a lot of penalties
I know the taste very well
- Jjan jjan jjan
I love penalties
So much
Me too
I know what it's like
I have received a lot of penalties
If I don't receive a penalty
I feel like something is missing
Let's go
Good penalty
- Good penalty
Drawings on the face, four.
- Drawings on the face.
- There you go.
Getting caned on the sole, seven.
- Getting caned on the sole.
- It's game over.
It's game over.
- Nice.
(Team Jong Kook won Round 1.)
(Your days will be sunny again)
His teeth look
especially annoying today.
Seriously.
- My goodness.
- Look at them.
They look so annoying.
Are you wearing dentures today?
Why do your teeth look
so annoying today?
I messed up the number of times.
Why couldn't you do it right?
All right.
Focus like you are
on "How Do You Play?"
Don't give "How Do You Play?"
a bad rap. You need to do better.
- This is Running Man.
- You need to do better.
- Seriously.
- You need to do well here as well.
- You're not doing well here.
- "Gap," let's go.
Team Jong Kook won Round One.
- Okay.
- We lost points.
So Team Jae Seok
needs to carry out the penalties.
Jae Seok, you will get
your sideburns pulled.
- Okay.
- Why?
You lost a point.
(He lost a point
with a nasal voice.)
So it applies to people
who lost points.
Haha, you will get your sole caned.
Chung Hwa, you will get
rosy cheeks drawn on your face.
- What?
- Pull his sideburns.
I'll do it since
I am sitting right next to him.
What?
I am sitting right next to you.
I don't want to do it,
but I am sitting right next to you.
Take your time.
I want to do it gently,
but it won't be funny then.
I will make sure the talk is funny.
He is sensitive right now.
- Come on.
- Are you negotiating?
- Don't worry about it.
- He will make up by talking.
- How will you make up?
- I can do it with ease.
- How?
- Tell me how.
- What are your needs?
I can meet your needs.
- Really? Are you certain?
- Yes.
How many times
will you make me laugh?
I think 2 or 3 times will suffice.
Of course not. Come here.
For goodness' sake.
- Rip off his sideburns.
- Two or three times isn't...
- very impressive.
- Fine. Go ahead.
(Ouch.)
Don't grimace.
If you grimace,
viewers will feel uncomfortable.
I feel the most uncomfortable.
I mean...
- I feel the most uncomfortable.
- Smile.
All right.
- I will smile.
- Don't grimace.
You will look pitiful
if you do that.
What do you want me to do?
- Just take them off.
- Okay.
All right.
He looks more pitiful
without the glasses.
Just put them back on.
- I will do this.
- Okay.
For goodness' sake.
There isn't much to grab.
(Pinching)
(The venomous snake's touch
really woke him up.)
I used 1-4th of my strength.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Haha needs to get his sole caned.
Since I am sitting close to him,
I will do it.
Come on, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Why do you carry out penalties?
- Seriously.
- Right now...
Why do you carry out
all the penalties?
Because I'm sitting close to him.
I heard that it's healthy
to punch your sole.
That's right.
Put your feet up.
Why do you carry out
all the penalties?
- Se Chan, you should do it.
- Me?
- Se Chan?
- He practiced caning.
- He will hit harder.
- Why does it have to be Se Chan?
- Come here.
- This is worse.
- Oh, my goodness.
- This is how you do it.
He has good wrist snap
since he plays badminton.
I will hold his feet.
- Oh, my goodness.
- This is how you do it.
Right?
- For goodness' sake.
- A mortar.
- Be careful.
- Zoom in on Haha's face.
Hit hard.
(Slapping)
Ouch!
(The caning of love
was super effective.)
It must hurt a lot.
- I can't believe you.
- You hit the soles well.
- I did it well.
- He is so annoying.
- Draw rosy cheeks on her face.
- Chung Hwa.
- This is the best.
- Draw rosy cheeks on her face.
It's my first time
trying something like this.
- They look good on her.
- You look nice.
- Seriously.
- Chung Hwa.
You look like Jigsaw.
- She does look like him.
- Yes.
How am I so bad at this game?
- I need to focus.
- Okay.
For Round Two,
you will pick a new penalty.
Getting rosy cheeks drawn.
This is a hard one.
- Do Kwon, what's yours?
- Show us.
(Getting the sideburns pulled)
- Getting the sideburns pulled.
- Mine is getting caned on the sole.
- Getting caned on the sole.
Our penalties are easy.
- "Gourd-breaking" is easy to say.
- Gourd-breaking.
- Is there "Gourd-breaking?"
- Getting slapped with water.
- That's a good one.
- Getting hit by a wet towel.
- Eating your raw eggs.
- I won't say that.
So Min should get a turn.
- So Min won't get a turn.
- I want to play the game too.
It's too hard to say.
- Who will go first?
- Haha.
- Okay.
Good penalty
- Good penalty
- Penalty
Eagle, seven.
- Eagle.
- That's it.
- Getting slapped with water, two.
- Getting slapped with water?
Getting slapped with water?
Getting slapped with water.
Gourd-breaking, seven.
- Gourd-breaking?
- That's me.
That's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok got gourd-breaking.)
(Seok Jin attacked his teammate.)
That's Jae Seok.
(He attacked his teammate
with a solemn face.)
That's Jae Seok.
- You didn't tell me.
- He attacked his teammate.
I...
You didn't tell me.
- What?
- He told you.
Why did you attack gourd-breaking
instead of me?
Why did you attack me?
If I made a mistake,
you should have just gone along.
- This is so frustrating.
- He could have done that.
He could have gone along, right?
- It wouldn't have been a problem.
Can't you improvise?
What audacity!
I am sitting right next to you.
You asked me a moment ago,
"What's yours?"
I said, "Gourd-breaking."
I told you.
People can forget.
You asked me what mine is,
so I said that it's gourd-breaking.
- So why did you attack me?
- Is that what he whispered earlier?
Does it count?
- Of course.
- Really?
- Of course it does.
- It's too much.
Let's resume.
- Good penalty
Getting slapped with water, eight.
Getting slapped with water.
- Getting slapped with water.
- You are doing well.
Getting rosy cheeks drawn, seven.
Rosy...
- Yes!
- We got him!
- They are very happy.
- We got the big fish!
Jong Kook.
A singer should be better
at getting the rhythm right.
I thought it started with "Rosy."
- Rosy.
- That word stood out to me.
My feet are sweating.
- Jong Kook, you can start.
- Okay.
So Min should get a chance.
- Good penalty
- I keep getting nervous.
- But I haven't played the game.
- Good penalty
- Penalty
Good penalty
- Good penalty
- For goodness' sake.
- Focus, Jae Seok.
- He is so scary.
- Good penalty
- He'll lose a point at this rate.
- Yes.
- Good penalty
- Of course.
- Penalty
Good penalty
Bowl, seven.
(Bowl, seven!)
What?
- Bowl.
- It's "Gourd-breaking."
Gourd-breaking.
Isn't it "Bowl-breaking?"
(Mr. Raw Raw Eggs messed up again.)
Good job.
That was incredible.
Is it "Gourd-breaking?"
- It's "Gourd-breaking."
- I thought it was "Bowl-breaking."
We won.
- Okay.
- Six.
Jong Kook, you will get
rosy cheeks drawn on your face.
- Rosy cheeks.
- Okay.
This is the worst.
Why won't you let me play the game?
- You need to draw rosy cheeks.
- That's what I am doing.
You are doing great.
So Min doesn't hold back.
She is doing great.
This is why Jong Kook
is uncomfortable with So Min.
Jong Kook, why won't you let me
play the game?
She goes overboard sometimes.
Okay.
Jigsaw.
This pen is not working.
Soles. Seok Jin.
How will I cane Ji Hyo's soles?
You can get your soles caned
instead.
- Seriously.
- He wouldn't let that happen.
I don't want to do that.
Ji Hyo is...
Aren't you going to receive
the penalty instead?
Who?
Aren't you going to receive
the penalty instead?
- Who?
- Jong Kook.
- Aren't you going to help her?
- She can grant your wish...
- for your trouble.
- Hurry up and cane her soles.
Do it.
- Hold on.
- If I were you, I would...
Will it look strange
if I receive the penalty instead?
Okay. Give me that.
- Will he receive the penalty?
- Okay.
Okay. Give me that.
(His request has been accepted.)
- All right.
- What?
- You said you will do it.
- When did I say that?
When did I say that?
You just did.
I will get my soles caned.
I... I didn't say that.
- Just get your soles caned.
- When did I say that?
- You did.
- This is so funny.
Ji Hyo, I am doing this
in your stead.
- Hey.
- Cane his soles.
- My goodness.
- It's good for circulation.
- It won't hurt at all.
Watch. Ouch!
(Caning of love
left an electrifying sensation.)
- The pain stays for a while.
- It hurts.
- It doesn't hurt at all.
It doesn't hurt at all.
- It hurts.
- It's good for circulation.
That jerk!
The pain intensifies over time.
- He is in a different team too.
- It doesn't hurt at all.
Why did our team get the penalty?
- You should have kept quiet.
- Why did I get caned?
You ran your mouth.
You helped her when you are
in a different team.
- Is it the last round?
- You will play to three points.
- Okay.
- All right.
Can we have a 1-on-1 match?
Just one match.
- So Min hasn't played at all.
- I want to play.
Let So Min have a 1-on-1 match.
- A 1-on-1 match.
- Let's do this.
A representative from each team
will come out and play three turns.
They can only use
each other's penalty.
- Okay.
- That's a good idea.
- Se Chan.
- You can do it, right?
Put them here.
- My heart is racing now.
- Put them here.
So Min versus Se Chan.
Se Chan, come on out.
So Min, let's do this.
- Se Chan, come on out.
- Se Chan.
If we win this round,
we will be the winning team.
- Should I pick one?
- Yes.
She needs to win.
What is she doing this time?
What is up with her?
She is making him nervous.
- What?
- She is making him nervous.
- Will you be okay, Se Chan?
- My heart is beating fast.
- They are so funny.
- Is your heart beating fast?
- She is like that.
Okay. Eating your raw eggs.
- Suddenly...
- Why are you applying lipstick?
(Se Chan, give me a second.)
What... A kiss.
Does this game involve a kiss?
- It doesn't matter.
- You are right.
She is so funny.
(She is playing dirty already.)
- She is so funny.
- Seriously, Se Chan.
Se Chan became nervous.
- What's yours?
- Look at each other.
It's so hard.
Eating your raw eggs.
- It's so hard.
- Call her honey.
Honey.
Call her honey.
My goodness.
- He is our teammate.
- Oh, right.
But she has to say it, though.
Don't say that
with paint on your cheeks.
- It's so funny.
- Eating your raw eggs.
Jong Kook likes
all kinds of romance,
but I don't like this couple.
I have my own taste.
- I like them though.
- Shall I go first?
- Getting hit by a wet tissue.
- Why can't you look at her eyes?
- This is so funny.
- All right. I should look at this.
Why would you look at it?
(Laughing)
He can't look at her.
- I knew it.
- Look at him.
- So Min is really...
- I know.
- She's really good at this.
- She's so skilled.
Eating your raw eggs.
- Se Chan is so shy.
- You should look at her face.
(Give me your hands.)
You should look at her face.
- Look at her face.
- I'm not supposed to do this.
You don't hold her hands.
(He almost lost his mind
and held her hands.)
- Why would you hold her hands?
- He can hold them if he wants.
This is what I should do.
Good penalty
Getting hit by a wet tissue, seven.
Getting hit by a wet tissue.
- Getting hit by a wet tissue.
- She's good.
Eating your raw eggs, six.
Eating...
- What's with him?
- That was...
(Eating raw eggs, six.)
(Se Chan is knocked out.)
- Wasn't she off the beat?
- She was off the beat.
- Even if she was,
- you should've done it right.
- You should've said your part.
She was off the beat.
Just let it slide this time.
Okay. Just this once.
- You go first then.
- Okay. I'll go first.
I'm sorry,
but try not to sound too sweet.
He was flustered.
- Just say it nonchalantly.
- Or just say "your raw eggs."
I'll change it to "your raw eggs."
- "Your raw eggs?"
- "Your raw eggs."
- My goodness.
What was that?
- "Your raw eggs?"
- Oh, dear.
- Good penalty
Your raw eggs.
(Your raw eggs.)
(He gives up.)
- What?
- What was that?
- Will you stop that?
- "Your raw eggs."
- What did I do?
What was that?
What is going on?
- Why?
- My gosh.
- What about it?
- What's wrong?
- My ear hurts.
- You should just play the game.
- What?
- She whispered into my ear.
- You're not supposed to blow.
- Your raw eggs, five.
Gosh, Jeon So Min.
(Even her team members are
astonished by her pranks.)
Gosh, Jeon So Min.
Your raw eggs.
Getting hit by a wet tissue, sesen.
- "Sesen?"
(Getting hit
by a wet tissue, sesen.)
(Sesen?)
(He shouted the magical number
"sesen" trembling.)
What is "sesen?"
He said "sesen."
My goodness.
What about "eightsen?"
- My goodness.
- "Sesen?"
- You did it.
- What kind of number is that?
- Well done.
- We won.
- You're amazing.
- "Sesen."
You are our lucky charm.
- We won.
- We won?
What on earth is "sesen?"
- You idiot.
- I can't believe this.
- You silly thing.
- I was so nervous. That's why.
- Hey, Mr. Sesen.
- You know what?
- What is "sesen?"
- He was really nervous.
- He was nervous.
- Right.
"Your raw eggs, sesen."
(Team Jae Seok wins the second
mission thanks to the femme fatale.)
Team Jae Seok wins
and gets two eggs.
(Team Jae Seok gets
two eggs as a prize.)
This is great.
(Team Jae Seok is facing a crisis?)
(All the eggs
they've collected are gone?)
- What are you doing?
- Take the eggs.
(They have to finish
the cooking mission no matter what.)
(Who will be the winner
of the crazy year-end party?)
(Their fortune for the new year
will be read.)
- This year...
- I love this.
(This year is the year
of a black tiger.)
(You will have
a strong sexual appetite.)
(To celebrate the year 2022,
they have their fortune read.)
- Me?
- Yes.
(A shocking remark about Seok Jin
gives everyone goosebumps.)
(Why doesn't Se Chan like me?)
(Se Chan likes...)
(young women.)
(Their secrets are revealed.)
Your good luck begins this year.
(There are members
who will be lucky in the New Year.)
(Who are the lucky ones?)
(And...)
(All the celebrities are
gathered together...)
(at the Entertainment Awards,
the finale of the year.)
Yu Jae Seok.
- I'll work harder.
- Song Ji Hyo of Running Man.
- Jee Seok Jin.
- Jeon So Min.
- Yang Se Chan of Running Man.
- Haha. Congratulations.
The Grand Award goes to...
Kim Jong Kook. Congratulations.
(The fun, beautiful festival
that puts an end to the year)
(The behind-the-scenes stories
of the Entertainment Awards)
(Running Man Year-End Special)