(It's fall when you want to walk
listening to a sad ballad song.)
(The members have gathered again
on a breezy fall day.)
- Hello.
Hello.
It's been a while
since we came here.
This is where we shoot
the opening with many guests.
And the guests come down the stairs.
- Right. Back then, Dong Geun...
- Cha Tae Hyun.
- Dong Geun was here.
- And Mi Joo.
- Mi Joo.
- Right. Mi Joo was here.
- And...
- How do you remember all that?
- What?
- How do you remember that?
- Of course, he does.
- I remember.
I guess we're having guests today.
This is unique. It's good
for a vaccine injection.
Right. This is for vaccination.
It's called the vaccination look.
- Is this the vaccination look?
- Yes. I got the second shot.
She got the second shot,
but she's just fine.
I was sick after the first shot.
- Hi, Jong Kook.
- Hey.
Hello.
(Another vaccinated member is here.)
Are you feeling all right
after getting the vaccine?
- I'm fine.
- Are you okay now?
- He's finally survived.
- This is what I thought.
I worked hard
after getting the shot.
- Then I fell sick.
- Right.
I feel like a superhero.
They suffer in pain
after getting a shot.
He thinks he's a superhero.
- Are you a superhero?
- After they overcome it,
they become stronger.
- You're aroused.
- I feel stronger now.
- Hey.
- Even stronger?
Yes. I feel great.
Aren't you just a bodybuilder?
Why are you a superhero?
I overcame the vaccination...
- and became stronger.
- Come closer.
- Today...
- This is nice.
We will have
four refreshing guests...
who will recharge your vitamins.
- This is what we need.
- I knew we'd have guests today.
- Really?
- Refreshing?
So Min is dressed like this.
- I know two of them.
- But she won't stand out.
This is somber.
Please come on out.
Come on out, refreshing guests!
- Refreshing guests?
- Refreshing!
(The first refreshing guest
shows up.)
It's ITZY!
(Yeji of ITZY)
Yeji is here.
(It's ITZY!)
Jeon So Min, go away!
It's Yeji.
This is amazing.
I've never met her before.
- Who is she?
- Yeji.
Yeji of ITZY.
(He pretends to know her.)
You know the song.
Dear moon, deer moon
- Yeji.
- Hello.
How have you been?
I'm different from kids these days
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- She looks sophisticated.
- I didn't know Yeji would come.
She's so sophisticated.
Who would say
such a thing these days?
Look at Yeji's hairstyle.
If you dare to copy it...
- You'll be in trouble.
- You'll be in big trouble.
- It looks good only on Yeji.
- Yes.
- She's not like kids these days.
- It's Moon Hee Joon's style.
I know. Say hello to our viewers.
She's so pretty.
Hello. I'm Yeji of ITZY.
- She looks like a doll.
- I know.
- This is amazing.
- Unbelievable.
Go away.
It hurts. It's been only three days.
Really? I'm sorry.
- The vaccine.
- So Min...
So Min will text you
after the shooting.
- "Haha, I'm sad."
- "I'm sad."
(Jeon So Min: Haha, I'm sad.)
Then I'll block your number.
Let's move on...
- to the second guest.
- Who is it?
- Refreshing and cheerful!
- Please come on out.
The guest I know isn't here yet.
Luda!
(Luda of WJSN)
Hey, Luda.
(Cheerful charm)
(The cute member of WJSN, Luda)
(The vocal of WJSN
with a warm voice)
Hey, Luda.
- WJSN.
- It's WJSN.
Luda!
Go away!
(Giggling)
Hi, Luda.
Wait.
- Luda.
- You know what?
- What?
Luda touched
her hair like this, and...
- What was that?
- It's refreshing.
- That's not it.
- What was that, Luda?
She came down the stairs
like this holding the pillar.
Did you see that?
(She did all the typical moves
of idol artists in a short time.)
- What was that?
- I tried to look cool.
I was told to be refreshing.
Refreshing.
- Refreshing.
- Haha was really funny.
He shouted like this,
turned around, and asked,
"Who is she?"
- That's not true.
- Excuse me.
I know she's WJSN. I asked her name.
(He shouts out loud immediately.)
(Who is she?)
- WJSN.
- It's WJSN.
- Hey, Luda.
- Go away.
This is our first time meeting you.
- This is how we become friends.
- Please be understanding.
You will be famous this way.
He keeps asking me about the guests.
Be honest. Do you know
all the members of WJSN?
- Do you?
- To be honest,
WJSN doesn't really know you.
- They know only a few of us.
- I worked with them a lot.
- WJSN...
- You worked with me a lot, right?
- A radio show.
- We did a radio show. And...
Right.
Even if they know you,
they are not interested in you.
I don't care that they are not.
- I only care about my wife.
- He's upset.
- "I don't care."
- I don't.
- You seem flustered.
- Do I?
- This is new. "What?"
- But...
"I don't care."
He's pretending to be bold.
"So what?"
(This is how the entertainer
with 30 years' experience survives.)
Anyway, we have Luda here.
- Luda.
- Who's next?
- I'm excited.
- I'm so thrilled.
- Who else is refreshing?
Here comes the third guest.
I know who it is.
(Who's the next guest
that Jae Suk knows?)
This song is BIBI.
- Hey, BIBI.
- BIBI.
It's BIBI!
(BIBI)
Hey, BIBI.
(She's a new hip-hop artist...)
(loved by the hip-hop scene
and fans in teens and 20s.)
(In the TV audition show,
"THE FAN",)
(she won second place.)
- Hey, BIBI.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Hello.
This is serious.
As BIBI walks down, Suk Jin said...
To the end of the earth
He thinks it's her.
To the end of the stars
- It's not her.
- It's BB.
Actually,
- You met Yeji on the audition show.
- Right.
- Really? Which show?
- Hello.
- They met on "THE FAN".
- Right.
- We were contestants.
- I see.
I thought it looked
awkward between you two.
Who was in a higher rank
on the show?
She was a lot higher.
- She was in the top two.
- She was the second place.
But in reality,
- I'm no match for her.
- No.
(I'm no match for her.)
No match for her?
That sounds rough.
She sounds friendly.
It will catch the ears of those
in the show business.
"I'm no match for her."
- I'm no match for her.
- I see.
She's really popular.
What did you do before your debut?
I just did my music...
as a hobby.
When Mi Rae heard my song,
she wanted to hire me.
- Hire you?
- So we signed the contract.
I like...
her word choices.
She sounds refreshing.
- Hire her?
- She picked her up.
- We don't usually say that.
- That's new.
The two CEOs of her agency
don't speak Korean.
- "I will hire you."
- Right.
"I will hire you."
- "I hire you."
- "You're hired."
- "I'm going to hire you."
"You're hired, okay?"
So we have three guests here.
- But there's one more.
- All right.
It's really...
I don't understand why he's...
- I don't understand it either.
- here with them.
- Why?
- I heard that yesterday.
- I heard it from Shinji.
- Is he someone refreshing?
Is he refreshing?
Let's meet him then.
Here's our fourth guest.
But he is...
Refreshing!
Gosh, he's too sour.
(The sour silhouette shows up.)
(MC Minzy, Jung Jun Ha)
Gosh, he's too sour.
(MC Minzy lip-syncs outright.)
My gosh.
(What?)
He's just too sour.
I had no idea.
- I knew it.
- But...
I don't understand
why he's here with these three.
This is ridiculous.
(MC Minzy of 0.11 tonnes walks
down the stairs with a sour smell.)
- He's lip-syncing.
- My goodness.
Humming
He's ruining the mood.
I didn't know about this.
(They don't know how to react.)
(MC Minzy comes forward.)
He's being silly again.
- He's being silly.
- My goodness.
There he goes again.
This is too sour.
Look at Ji Hyo. She looks tired.
- Why are you dancing like that?
- His head is so big...
that he ripped the cap open.
He ripped it open.
Be confident and keep going.
- That's enough.
- Stop it.
- Come back here.
- That's enough.
It's too sour.
- Another Saturday guy is here.
- I know.
Jong Kook is sensitive about this.
But he...
works hard even on Sunday.
Unlike someone.
He's all dressed up.
- Look. He's not like him.
- What about me?
He doesn't try hard.
You didn't care
about your outfit today.
- You should get dressed up.
- Think of "How Do You Play?".
- All right.
- By the way...
- About Jun Ha...
- You should talk to me.
Why are you here with them?
I'm just...
- Hang on.
- Generation MZ...
I'm grateful that
you are joining our show,
- but it's strange to be with them.
- He's so shameless.
Why? I'm here with other artists.
I'm MC Minzy.
Are you here as Jung Jun Ha
or MC Minzy?
MC Minzy.
Are you here as MC Minzy?
The artists who represent
Generation MZ.
- MC Minzy.
- Hey.
- You're too sour.
- Yes.
What's with your hand?
- This is what I do when I sing.
- Jun Ha.
- You're feeling awkward, right?
- No.
(- You're feeling awkward, right?
- No.)
You didn't know
we'd be like this, did you?
I had no idea.
Your face shows everything.
You know what?
The three of them are staying still,
but you're doing this alone.
(He's the guest
who seems most nervous.)
The gestures are very old-fashioned.
He looks like the mother
of these three, right?
How is his face so big?
There's no comedian today?
- You recently released a new song.
- Yes. That's my second single.
Is it "Abalone"?
- It's "Gizzard Shad".
- "Gizzard Shad"?
- Did you say "Country Life"?
- What was that?
"I Say Woo"...
sounds like shrimp...
in Korean.
"Gizzard Shad" is just like that.
It means "I feel great."
Gizzard shad
You mean the fish.
- It's "Gizzard Shad".
- I feel great
This is just my opinion,
but it's a bit far-fetched.
- It means you feel great?
- I feel great. What?
They don't sound similar at all.
- That's not like gizzard shad.
- It sounds differently.
- But I...
- That doesn't match.
I think it sounds similar.
(He denies their opinions
with no logic at all.)
Is he upset?
So we have MC Minzy here.
- We have four guests today.
- Welcome.
MC Minzy.
Let me tell you about today's race.
With your choice,
today's race will become...
a golden ratio or a dirty ratio.
It's an unpredictable race,
Golden Ratio Race.
It will be an individual game.
I'll give you the keyword
for the main mission first.
Once you check the keyword,
you will pick a captain.
Then the captain will give you
numbers from 1 to 11.
Then I will draw numbers...
- to divide you into two teams.
- That's...
If I pick number one,
there will be two teams
of number one and the rest.
If I pick number five,
from number 1 to 5 will be a team,
and numbers 6 to 11 will
be another team.
If you want to be on the same team
with a strong member,
it's important to get the number
that's close to the strong one's.
And that's what the captain decides.
- We should think of many things.
- I know.
We should win favor
with the strong members.
After the race, we will draw lots...
and decide who will get the prize
and who will get the penalty.
(Who will be the winner
with the golden ratio?)
I think it's a slipper game.
There are slippers.
Minzy!
(Minzy!)
- Hello.
- Minzy.
Gizzard shad
- MC Minzy, gizzard shard
- How old are you, Minzy?
- Me?
- Am I singing it right?
- He was born in 2002.
- In 2002.
- So you're younger than me.
- Yes.
He's younger than us.
He was born in 2002.
What?
- You're younger than me.
- You're younger than us.
- Gizzard shad
- The mission to decide the captain.
It's called Slippers with Feet.
You will go around the slippers...
outside the square dancing to music.
You should put on a slipper
when the whistle is blown.
MC Minzy must be good at this.
The one who survives
until the end is the winner.
The last survivor
will be the captain.
I guess I'll be the first one
to be eliminated.
(Big Nose looks determined
warming up.)
Suk Jin, are you warming up?
Yes. I should warm up.
I should fight...
- against MC Minzy and Jong Kook.
- MC Minzy is too strong.
He's strong.
- He's too strong.
- I'm strong.
I can pull a truck with my forehead.
- It will be tough.
- All right.
There are nine slippers.
- And there are 11 of you.
- So 2 of us will be eliminated.
- So...
- Two of us will be eliminated.
You should dance to the music
outside the square.
Gosh, this is...
It's over when the whistle is blown.
You will see.
(You will see.)
Haha will spare himself...
- playing this game.
- Why?
So he can focus
on "How Do You Play?".
(So he can focus
on "How Do You Play?".)
He doesn't work hard on Sundays.
- Good luck.
- He works hard only on Saturdays.
Haha, just think
that today is Saturday.
- You'll see.
- Today is Saturday.
- Try your best.
- Let's do this.
- All right. I'm ready.
- Try hard.
All right. This is Round One.
Music please.
Dance around the square.
This is an old song.
(They should dance outside
the square while music is playing.)
- Is this "Take on Me"?
- "Take on Me".
"Take on Me".
I think they chose this song
for you, Suk Jin.
Right. "Take on Me".
I wonder when the music will stop.
- I think...
- When will it be?
Won't we change the direction?
- Let's change the direction.
- Let's move backward.
(They changed the direction
of their own accord.)
It's up to us.
Let's try to understand the lyrics.
This is A-ha's song.
(While the others are having fun,
Sunday Man seems very nervous.)
(Blowing the whistle)
- Oh, gosh.
- Yes! I got one.
(Those who fail to get a slipper
get eliminated right away.)
(Se Chan quickly took a slipper
and got out.)
My hit-and-run strategy worked.
(Jong Kook got one easily.)
(So did Ji Hyo.)
There's only one left.
(Sunday Man is going crazy.)
Move! Go away!
(Falling)
(Sunday Man loses it
to prove his enthusiasm.)
Move!
- Go away, you all!
- My gosh.
What happened?
(He sweeps across the set,
leaving chaos behind.)
- Are you all right?
- Are you guys okay?
- Are you okay?
- How come you all failed?
- You're mistreating your guests.
- Why did you do that?
- I think I pushed someone.
- Hey, did the guests...
- Did they all fail?
- Who was that?
Hey, take it easy, will you?
Someone hit me on the head.
(Haha's twisted passion caused
many people damage.)
- Hey, Luna and...
- By the way...
- You can't do that to the guests.
- Suk Jin.
- Why?
- It's Luda.
- Oh, is it Luda?
- Yes.
- That's her name.
- Oh, Luda.
- I'm sorry, Luda.
- But...
Round One ended,
and two guests got eliminated.
- I'm sorry about that.
- I put it on backwards.
This is a competition, you know.
You understand me, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Haha... Yes, you did your best.
- You saw me, right?
- Okay.
- Indeed.
I won't go easy on you guys.
(Round 2 begins right away.)
- Look at him.
- He came here.
Why would you come here?
This is a good spot.
It's a good spot.
We'll begin the second round now.
(People on the other side are
in a war of nerves too.)
What's with these punks?
Round Two begins. Play the music.
Let's dance.
Oh, yes. This is my song.
Pretty girls
("Dalla Dalla" by ITZY makes
everyone want to dance.)
I'm not like them
- I'm different
(The old men are excited
and start singing together.)
(Who will become the 7 winners
to get slippers?)
- I love the way I am, I'm just me
(Blowing the whistle)
(The slippers disappear
in an instant.)
(The quick ones take slippers
and leave.)
(There's a group of people left
in the corner.)
Gosh, you jerk.
(The 0.1t elephant flopped down.)
(MC Minzy fell down helplessly
with a loud shout.)
(MC Minzy who was born in 2002
was thrown down.)
(Se Chan steals his slipper.)
(The elephant ends up
being captured.)
Gosh, you.
Darn it.
- Hey.
- Look at him.
(The uninvited guest,
Jung Jun Ha shows up.)
- Who are you?
- My gosh.
(Jun Ha arrives
in the middle of the game.)
- Who is that?
- That's Jun Ha.
- Hey, my hair.
- Isn't he Jun Ha?
- Jun Ha, when did you get here?
- Help me take it off.
- Gosh, that hurts.
- When did you come?
- Hello, Mr. Jung.
When did you arrive?
- Oh, that hurts.
- How did this happen?
Got it. Nice.
- Hello, Mr. Jung.
- Hey, hi.
- Jun Ha, when did you get here?
- It's been a while.
I just came...
- Oh, my.
- Hold on.
- What?
- Hey, MC Minzy.
I say woo
- He's doing well.
- Keep going.
I say woo
- Higher
- Oh, my. Jun Ha is so funny.
- How long have you been here?
- It's been a while.
- The game looked so fun.
- Right.
- Excuse me.
- What happened?
Aren't you Ms. Hyun Mee?
The singer of "Night Fog"?
Where did my slipper go?
Since you took it from Jun Ha
after he put it on,
- you must give it back to him.
- Really?
- I put it on, right?
- Okay.
- Exactly.
- I'm sorry.
(After Se Chan and Haha
got eliminated...)
Let's begin the third round.
Play the music.
Jun Ha's feet...
(Only 5 slippers remain.)
MC Minzy!
(While the other players start
dancing excitedly...)
- Lee Hyo Lee
- This is a very old song.
- You shouldn't go in there.
- Come out now.
(A daring dancer crossed
into the square.)
- Hey, come and join me.
- Come out now.
Hey, come out!
(Laughing)
- Hey.
- Come out now.
(The dance style
that only people over 50 like)
Stop flailing around and come out.
Exactly. Stop flailing around.
(The game resumes
once the flailing dancer leaves.)
(Blowing the whistle)
(The players flock around
at an unbelievable speed.)
- I got it.
- Give me that.
- Jae Suk, it's in front of you.
- I got it.
(MC Minzy versus Suk Jin)
Gosh. He's so annoying.
(And So Min tries to use
their brawl as a chance.)
- Jun Ha will lose.
- Gosh.
Come on.
(She took it off his foot.)
It's not over yet.
I put it on already.
(Dropkick)
(Suk Jin got hit with a dropkick
by the 0.1t man.)
Look at that slipper.
- He kicked Suk Jin in the end.
- The slipper got torn.
It's over.
What is this?
It's torn and worn out.
The first one
to put it on his foot wins.
- He's really strong.
- Jun Ha is so strong.
- Gosh.
- You're so persistent.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
(Falling down)
(It suddenly turns
into a wrestling match.)
- Put it on your foot.
- It's over.
(Jun Ha puts his foot
on the slipper first and wins.)
That was amazing.
- Good job.
- You did great.
- See? I knew that he'd win.
- Why am I here?
(MC Minzy aged a lot
during the fight.)
- He's invincible.
- I'm impressed.
He's been getting all the attention
while playing this game.
- I mean...
- My gosh.
Why would you get all the attention?
Where are my glasses?
Are you okay, Suk Jin?
Where are Suk Jin's glasses?
Hey, my glasses...
(Looking around)
Suk Jin, what are you looking for?
My eyes.
- What are you looking for?
- His glasses.
My eyes.
- Where did my eyes go?
- Where did his glasses go?
(His glasses disappeared
in the slipper commotion.)
Hey, help me find them.
- Suk Jin, did you...
- Where did you put his glasses?
- We don't know.
- Help me find them.
- Why did you lose your glasses?
- Hey, you.
- I mean...
- You hid them, didn't you?
- No.
- Where did you put his glasses?
(Jae Suk is wearing
Suk Jin's glasses!)
- Why did you lose your glasses?
- Hey, you.
- I mean...
- You hid them, didn't you?
- No.
- Where did they go?
- Hey, Se Chan. Come over here.
- Hey.
- I don't have them.
- Has anyone seen his glasses?
- Where are my glasses?
- I really don't know.
- Suk Jin's glasses.
- Where did you put his glasses?
- We don't know.
- Help me find them.
(His glasses are here.)
- I mean...
- You hid my glasses, didn't you?
(Suk Jin is grilling
the wrong person.)
Where did they go?
- Where are his glasses?
- I don't have them.
You guys, don't pull a prank on him
whenever you get a chance.
- Suk Jin.
- Seriously.
- Give me back my glasses now.
- Where did you hide his glasses?
- You can't find them?
- Where on earth are they?
- Hey.
- Come on. Give them back to me.
- You should stop pulling a prank...
- You took them, didn't you?
- No. Why would I do that?
- Seeing that you're being loud,
- you're suspicious.
- Oh, my.
(He looks at Jae Suk's face
but goes through his pockets.)
(He's unbelievably slow-witted.)
Give them back to me. Now!
Where did they go?
Suk Jin, keep looking.
(After a kick with no damage,
he gives up right away.)
- You see...
- Where did you put your glasses?
Continue. I'll keep looking.
Go on.
Don't let it drag on because of me.
My goodness.
How can he not notice?
His glasses are expensive.
My gosh.
Where did you put them?
- You took them, didn't you?
- Suk Jin, search Jae Suk.
- Why would I take them?
- What?
(What?)
(Something's strange.)
(After a long search,
he finally recognizes his glasses.)
I can't believe you.
Gosh. How long have you been
wearing them?
(It took Seok Sam 5 minutes
to find his glasses.)
- You didn't know?
- My gosh.
- When did you put them on?
- He didn't recognize them.
Did you just put them on?
That was hilarious.
(He barely found his glasses.)
Gosh.
Why didn't you recognize them?
Oh, please come to me
(They continued the game
to the final round.)
Hey. Gosh.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook won.
- Jong Kook is the captain.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Jae Suk didn't even try.
We'll bring you the board
to decide the order.
So this is how I decide the order?
That's great. I like it.
Before that,
I'll tell you the keyword
for the first mission.
The keyword
for the first mission is...
"Quiz".
(The keyword for the 1st mission is
"Quiz".)
Those empty heads are in trouble.
- "Quiz".
- I'm done for.
"Quiz"?
She can't say anything.
- MC Minzy, are you empty-headed?
- I'm not confident.
- What are you talking about?
- You're empty-headed too, right?
- I'm pretty sure he's smart.
- I'm smart.
- He's totally stupid, right?
- No.
He took the college entrance exam
four times.
- I took the exam four times.
- MC Minzy studied...
- high school subjects properly.
- Is that so?
All right.
(Jong Kook will announce the order.)
The first one is Jae Suk.
- Me?
- It's a quiz game, right?
- Yes, it's a quiz game.
- Okay.
- I choose this number.
Somewhere in the middle.
Next up is Suk Jin.
He said that we should choose
our teammates carefully.
- I'll go next.
- Go ahead.
- You'll pick number eight, right?
- Yes.
- I'll go with number eight.
- My gosh.
It would be funny if the 1st team is
from numbers 1 to 7.
I think that numbers 9 to 11...
- I'm ready.
- Okay. Yeji.
- How she dyed her hair...
- Okay. Yeji, you're up.
There are many idol singers
who are unexpectedly dumb.
If the 1st team is
from numbers 1 to 8,
Yeji, you would have no hope.
If they're on the same team...
Now, I'm going to pick the number
to decide the teams...
as everyone watches.
- Yes.
- I'm worried.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
(What number will be chosen?)
Please.
Please pick a good one.
(Who will be on the brainy team
versus the empty heads team?)
The first team is...
(Se Chan, Haha, BIBI, and MC Minzy
are on the same team.)
- from numbers 1 to 4.
- Okay. Oh, yes.
- All right. This is good.
- Oh, no.
(Luda, Suk Jin, Jae Suk,)
(Jong Kook, Yeji, So Min, and Ji Hyo
are on the same team.)
- So Min.
- We'll definitely win.
(Team Majority, Luda, Suk Jin,
Jae Suk, Jong Kook,)
(Yeji, So Min, Ji Hyo)
We'll definitely win.
MC Minzy.
(Team Minority, Se Chan, Haha,
BIBI, MC Minzy)
(Those who aren't good at quizzes
are on Team Minority.)
- Gosh. BIBI, come over here.
- We'll definitely win.
- Se Chan, Haha, BIBI, and MC Minzy.
- That's great.
- We can't be sure yet.
- We can do it.
- Oh, no. Right.
- We've got this.
- I'm worried because I'm not smart.
- It's okay. We can do it.
- You're not smart?
- Not really.
- We'll surprise them.
- Really?
You can be the star of this episode.
How many are on your team?
The four of you? Oh, no.
The four of them.
We can do it.
Oh, dear. I'm worried.
However, the next game...
is not a normal quiz game.
(It's not a normal quiz game?)
It's not a normal quiz game.
You will move to the study room...
to cram before the game begins.
Oh, no. I'm not good at memorizing.
We'll study?
Okay. I can memorize things quickly
since I have an empty head.
There will be three categories.
- What are they?
- One is general knowledge.
- The second one is Chinese idioms.
- Yes.
The last one is
current affairs and economy.
- Divide the categories...
- You study the Chinese idioms.
within your teams
and cram for a while.
- Then we'll begin the game here.
- That would be better.
We can divide the categories
to study?
- Let's divide the categories.
- It's good we have more members.
But you may be given a question
from a category you didn't study.
- We won't get to choose?
- No. You never know.
- Please move to the study room...
- Can't we tell them the answer?
- Let's go to the study room.
- No, you can't.
Let's go to the study room to cram.
(How will they cram
for the quiz game?)
Will both teams study here?
"'Giving up' is not part
of our vocabulary."
"It's never too late
to start studying."
- It's too late.
- Thank you.
It looks like a real study room.
It's so nice in here.
We have snacks here.
(Snacks for the empty heads)
It looks so good.
Let's do this.
I'll read the newspaper.
Yeji and So Min,
which categories do you want?
- I'll study Chinese idioms.
- Go ahead.
Maybe I'll be called Empty Head too
after this.
- We can't predict the questions.
- I have no idea.
- Gosh, I'm hungry.
- Can you?
It's too difficult for me.
- This is my favorite snack.
- Chinese idioms.
(The empty heads always put
snacks before studying.)
That means "every house".
- "To turn over a new leaf".
- "Every house".
My, it's delicious.
Can anyone spell
the word "delicious"?
- D...
- D, I...
- D, E...
- Correct.
L...
I know about two-thirds of them.
(Jae Suk is studying
Chinese idioms.)
- But it may not come to mind.
- Exactly.
Especially the ones like
gyeontojijaeng.
A fight between a dog
and a rabbit... So it means...
It's used to describe
a trivial argument...
or a pointless argument.
- Gyeonto...
- Jijaeng.
Then what's unbearable bitterness
and resentment?
Gakgoltonghan.
"Each one must figure out
how to survive."
- Gakjadosaeng.
What? I can't believe this.
Why?
I didn't know
it was gyeonggeomangdong.
You didn't know?
- Did you say "go", not "geo"?
- Yes.
It's "geo", not "go".
- "Gyeong" means "light".
- I always said "gyeonggomangdong".
- Gosh.
- It's "geo", not "go".
"Gyeonggeo" means "light steps".
- "Gyeonggeo".
- Hey.
You really don't know that?
Gosh. How should I...
I can't seem to focus.
It's because there's a lot of people
and plenty of snacks in here.
It's hard to focus because there are
too many distractions here.
I just want to know...
I always hated it when I had a lot
to cover for an exam.
But it must be easier for you
as you have more people.
- I know.
- You know hyeongseoljigong, right?
- Yes.
- Let's study.
(Unlike what she said,
So Min is focusing on something.)
What was hyeongseoljigong?
The light of fireflies.
- What about nangjungjichu?
- Using the light of fireflies...
- to study at night...
- An ice pick in a pocket.
I only wrote down the answers.
What should I study?
Should I study Chinese idioms?
You should cover all the categories.
- Okay.
- Hyeongseoljigong.
(The empty heads are always late.)
Mister, your shadow makes it
too dark.
I'll just take this book and leave.
Can you give me this book
on common knowledge?
- This...
- Daegimanseong.
I want to keep it in my car
so I can read it as I move around.
If I memorize all this,
I won't be called
Empty Head anymore, right?
No. That won't happen.
I want to take
one of these books too.
I'll take one too.
Me too.
- And...
- Wait. What is this?
"It means a flame before the wind."
"Jonmang"?
I thought "jonmang" was
a slang word.
- "Jonmang"?
- It's "jon" as in "to exist".
- "Jon" as in "to exist"...
- Come on.
and "mang" as in "to perish".
It means "to exist or to perish".
- It's not what you're thinking of.
- What's wrong with her?
- "Jonmang"?
- But it sounds just like...
- "Jonmang".
- What's wrong with you?
Don't act like this in front of
your junior entertainers.
- Mangyeonjasil.
- Exactly.
- Will you...
- Already?
What should I study now?
- It's so difficult.
- "Bansinbaneui".
"Banpojigyo".
Why do I feel like
time passes so slowly?
It passes so slowly.
I'm done studying.
- Let me read it.
- Sure.
Okay. I put everything in my head.
I'm ready.
I mean, is it even possible
to memorize all this now?
- I give up.
- Me too.
Did you study a lot?
- Yes.
- It wouldn't work.
I studied everything
except for Chinese idioms.
- I'll tell you the rules.
- Okay.
If you look here...
One from each team will be
randomly chosen...
for a 1-on-1 quiz game.
The category will also be chosen
in a draw.
You will only get five questions.
The team that gets
more questions right wins.
That is, some of you won't get to
play the game at all.
(The smart members of each team
may not have a chance to play.)
- The first match is...
- Please.
(The players for the first match
will be chosen.)
- I picked the players.
- So Min, I don't think...
So Min versus MC Minzy.
- Me?
- Okay.
- So Min studied really hard.
- Empty Head.
- That doesn't even matter.
- So Min...
(He's glad that he'll compete
against So Min.)
- But So Min...
- I'll win
(MC Minzy seems excited...)
- So Min studied really hard.
- Please.
- Come on. Don't be like that.
- I'll win
Quiz, don't
- Laugh
The first category is...
I'm worried.
Chinese idioms.
- That's a relief.
- That's what So Min studied.
She studied that.
- She studied a lot.
- She can beat him.
So Min, you studied Chinese idioms.
(She memorized the Chinese idioms
using her entire body.)
I don't remember any of them.
I don't remember any.
If you know the answer,
say, "Let me answer."
- And then say the answer.
- Yes.
We should get the upper hand
in the beginning.
Don't try to remember
what you memorized.
- It'll pop up in your head.
- You can do it.
Concentrate, okay?
Here's your question.
"To complete..."
"the most important part
of a project".
(To complete the most important part
of a project)
I didn't see any idioms
with that meaning.
"To complete the most important part
of a project".
(The meaning isn't enough
to think of the answer.)
"To complete the most important part
of a project"?
Isn't this it?
(Whispering)
Let's just pretend
that we know the correct answer.
(Let's just pretend
that we know the correct answer.)
- Right?
- Yes, that's the answer.
(Cheeky)
That's it.
- It's an easy one.
- Right.
I think that's the answer.
(Looking at her arm)
- What could that be?
- "The most important part"?
Look. She's cheating.
- I wasn't cheating.
- You shouldn't cheat.
Jun Ha, wipe her arm
with your saliva.
You're mistaken.
What? There's nothing on my arm.
Gosh. What is this?
- There's nothing on my arm.
- Gosh. How could you?
It hurts. What are you doing?
I'll give you a hint.
It literally means to draw the eyes
of a dragon in a painting...
- We were right.
- Let me answer.
Oh, boy.
Hwaryongjeomjung.
- Pronounce it clearly.
- Hwaryongjeomjung.
(MC Minzy got it correct.)
- Thank goodness.
- Great.
(The answer is hwaryongjeomjung.)
- I knew the answer too.
- Yes!
- Scream!
- MC Minzy!
MC Minzy
I say
The second match is
Ji Hyo versus MC Minzy.
- Ji Hyo, you can win this.
- Jun Ha, you look awesome now.
The category is general knowledge.
All right. Let's go!
MC Minzy, you're not bad.
- Sorry?
- You're not bad.
MC Minzy is smart.
- He's smart.
- Yes, indeed.
Here's your question.
Who is the female poet, considered
1 of the 3 best things of Songdo,
who wrote "Bakyeon Falls"
and "Memories of Manwoldae"...
and was also a gisaeng?
- Let me answer.
- Good.
- Hwang Jin Yi.
- That's right.
(Hwang Jin Yi is
the correct answer.)
(Ji Hyo takes everyone by surprise!)
Why don't you know this
if you studied for so long?
(While everyone was chatting
and eating snacks,)
(Ji Hyo read the 1st page
of the book on common knowledge.)
Great job.
- Hwang Jin Yi! Yes!
- Great.
Ji Hyo, nice.
- I say woo
- I thought...
The third match is
Jong Kook versus Se Chan.
Jong Kook is quite smart.
Any one of you, bring it on.
Hey, my friend from the soccer club.
How about we choose
current affairs and economy?
- What?
- You don't know much about it.
- Jong Kook.
- Hey.
You can't even pronounce
those words properly.
I studied current affairs
and economy. I'm confident.
Okay. It's a Chinese idiom.
Oh, this will be interesting.
Even if I've never heard of it,
- I can guess it.
- I can't...
- I can't understand the meaning.
- Of course.
I'm sure
that you all have heard this one.
Do you think we've heard of it
many times or not?
- It's important.
- He's so sensitive.
Why don't you give us
a difficult question?
You may not have heard of it
many times.
Not many times?
"Each one must figure out
how to survive."
- What?
- You know this.
- You know this one.
- You're allowed to give them hints.
- You know the answer, right?
- I couldn't hear it.
- Jong Kook.
- "Each one must figure out..."
- "how to survive."
- "Each one..."
("Each one must figure out
how to survive.")
- I'm sure you know this one.
- I know the answer.
- We talked about this.
- You mentioned this.
(They all talked
about gakjadosaeng.)
People often say
they should do this.
- Right? It was among the first few.
- I think I saw it earlier.
- This...
- Let me answer. It's gagahoho.
- That's not it.
- Seriously?
(That one was among
the first few too.)
Nice. It's all right.
I quite liked that.
(No one is as confident as he is
when it comes to quizzes.)
"On our own" is the key phrase.
I'm sure you've at least
said this once in your life.
Let me answer. It's gakyanggaksaek.
No, but it's similar.
- I love this.
- Let me answer. It's gakgidareun.
- Seriously?
- Come on.
Just think.
The answer's in front of you.
Everyone's trying
to save themselves.
Then "saeng" must be
in there somewhere.
Everyone's trying
to save themselves.
Then "saeng" must be
in there somewhere.
This is killing me.
- If it isn't gakyanggaksaek...
- Se Chan has half of it right.
- He said the syllables.
- Really?
- Then...
- I did?
Gakyang... What did I say?
Gakgidareun.
(Jong Kook is just as clueless.)
Gakgae...
(Gakgae...)
Gaesaeng!
- Gakgaegaesaeng.
- I thought you were swearing.
- Gaesaeng!
- Gakgaegaesaeng.
Is it gakgaegaksaeng?
But I said the right syllables.
It's not "gae."
- Then...
- Let me answer.
It's gakjailsaeng.
- You know...
- Let me answer. Gakjagaksaeng.
- That's not it.
- Let me answer.
It's Gakja...
honsaeng.
Gakjagaesaeng!
(Ding!)
Gakjasipsaeng!
(He's expressing
all aspects of life.)
- Let's do this.
- "Gakja" is correct.
- Then...
- Gakja...
Gak, ja, blank, saeng.
- It's not gakjahonsaeng?
- Come on.
Everyone goes their own path.
- They all seek their own path.
- Let me answer.
Is it gakjadosaeng?
Hold on. Who uses that
in ordinary speech?
- Gakjadosaeng.
- While grouping up,
- we use that term?
- Who uses that?
I have never said that
in my entire life.
You have probably heard it
at least once.
- Not me.
- It describes how everyone...
- seeks out their own path.
- Gakjadosaeng?
Haha, you seem disappointed.
- You fought well though.
- Okay.
- You fought well.
- Good job.
Nicely done.
- Yeji, it's okay.
- Nice!
(In the next round,
BIBI ties the score.)
You're at a tie...
and this is the last round.
Kim Jong Kook versus Haha.
(Jong Kook and Haha compete
when they're tied 2 to 2.)
Haha, get out here.
Haha, come on out.
(Winning this round
means a win for the team.)
Gosh.
I'm feeling the pressure,
that's all.
- They are the last players.
- The last?
We win if Jong Kook does.
- Really?
- They win if Haha wins.
Brain teaser, please.
Brain teaser.
A celebrity quiz?
- A celebrity quiz?
- A brain teaser?
(He can't help but laugh
at Haha's request.)
The category will be...
(The category of the final round)
- It'll be general knowledge.
- Okay.
- I didn't study that though.
- Me neither.
In other words,
it is called...
kkangkkangi or kkangkkaengi.
This string instrument...
Let me answer. Is it ajaeng?
(Ding!)
This string instrument...
is always included
in a wind ensemble.
It shows a balance between...
a wind instrument
and a string instrument...
It's not ajaeng.
and is made using
the eight elements...
- of traditional instruments.
- Let me answer.
Is it geomungo?
(Ding!)
Just name every instrument you know.
Let me answer. Gayageum.
(Ding!)
- Do we know what it is?
- I know what it is.
It's similar to an ajaeng.
That's right.
- It's haegeum.
- It is made using...
the eight elements
of traditional instruments.
- You know what it is.
- Right.
Come on.
It's an instrument
that is similar to an ajaeng.
- You know what it is.
- Right.
Two syllables.
Let me answer.
(Haha wants to answer.)
I know what it is. It's a pipe.
(A pipe)
(One would expect the final round
to be on a higher level.)
It's a string instrument, right?
- It's like an ajaeng.
- A pipe isn't a string instrument.
It's a lot like an ajaeng.
- You play it like this.
- I confuse them all the time.
Hold on a second.
- Let's give the first letters.
- It's on the tip of my tongue.
No, not the first letters.
(Instrumental sound)
(They mimic the haegeum
with their voices.)
- One letter will give it all up.
- Exactly.
How about I give them
the first letter?
How about this as a hint?
The sea.
Yes, the sea.
- What?
- The sea.
- The sea?
- Yes, the sea.
The sea.
Will that confuse them even more?
- Let me answer.
- That's it. It finally came to you.
- It's eojaeng.
- Seriously?
(Eojaeng instead of ajaeng)
Eojaeng.
Eojaeng!
Seriously?
Unbelievable.
Not ajaeng but...
- Don't complicate things.
- Think of the Chinese character.
Think of the sea in the easiest way.
- Let me answer.
Haegeum!
(Haha is correct.)
- Nicely done.
- See what I mean?
- Of course.
- It was a close match though.
(After a series of wrong answers,
he stumbled on the right one.)
Nice!
(The smart ones on Team Majority
didn't even get to compete.)
Go, team!
And just like that,
Team Minority wins...
which gives the 4 members
100 points each.
(The 4 of them receive
100 points each.)
(Nobody thought
Team Minority would win.)
- We did it.
- Nice.
- What a relief.
- Then,
let's move on to the next mission.
We could've won though.
The keyword
for the next mission is...
rapid response.
- Sounds good.
- Rapid response?
(In the preliminary round...)
- Okay!
- Suk Jin is the captain.
- This is how it should be.
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
Okay.
(How will the teams be divided?)
I'll draw a number now.
All we need is Jong Kook
on our team.
It'll be hilarious if he pulls out
a 1 or a 10.
We don't know
what the game is though.
Jong Kook might only get
to compete in one round.
- So...
- What's the number?
It's all in the luck of the draw.
- No way.
Just until Suk Jin.
(2, Ji Suk Jin)
We've already won.
No way.
(Oh, dear...)
- No way.
- We've already won.
Jong Kook and me?
We've already won.
- But Suk Jin...
- This is insane.
With Suk Jin?
- How can this be?
- This is hilarious.
- This is bad.
- Oh, no.
- Just Jong Kook and Suk Jin?
- What's the game?
How could this be?
They're polar opposites.
But I need to win.
- I have no points.
- I need to win. I have zero points.
- Let's do this.
- All right.
To succeed in this next game,
you must keep
your eyes and ears open.
This is
Sickly White Glove Blue Glove.
- Sickly White Glove Blue Glove?
- Are we doing the opposite?
One from each team will compete.
While facing each other,
you will put on
a blue glove and white glove...
on each of your hands.
Follow the game host's lead...
and play the regular game
of Blue Flag White Flag.
If you fail to do
what the host says,
you will lose a point.
Losing five points
will get you eliminated.
You must beat
all the opposing players to win.
The game host may shout orders...
such as
"Blue Glove, hit your opponent"...
or "Blue Glove, touch your leg".
Anything goes.
- It's at the host's discretion.
- I see.
The game host...
will be Jae Suk
since this is what he's good at.
- Me?
- Of course.
But he's such a prankster.
In terms of this game...
We're already in the lead.
One of you can enter...
and decide on your opponent.
- Okay!
- Seok Sam, are you going first?
Sure. I'll get rid of you all.
(I'll get rid of you all.)
Life is all about
taking on challenges.
- But...
- Of course.
Life is about taking on challenges.
Your hearing isn't up to par,
so will you be all right?
I hear what I need to hear.
- Then...
- He can choose his opponent.
- I'll choose.
- Is that so?
- It'll probably be someone slow.
- No way.
- It'll be one of you guys.
- Well...
- Luda or...
- He might choose Luda.
I'm sure of it.
Don't pick on the weaker ones.
(The hyena only goes after
the weakest links.)
He's not even looking our way.
Suk Jin's eyes have intensified.
(He isn't even considering the men.)
So Min, come on out.
(He chooses So Min,
one who rivals him in weakness.)
He's going to soar through
this round.
Suk Jin, you don't scare me at all.
So Min, come on out.
I need help with these gloves.
So Min, knock him out, okay?
Is this flour? Blue and white.
Get more on the gloves.
I have.
(A hefty amount)
This game was tailor-made
for Jun Ha.
- How so?
- This is his game.
- Is this the Jung Jun Ha game?
- He'll eat it up.
How will you eat it up?
- Deliciously.
- Deliciously, of course.
- He'll make it look good.
- Deliciously?
- It's like the flag game, right?
- Yes.
So Min is trying her best though.
Here we go.
This will be a practice round...
- since I need to practice as well.
- Sure.
Blue Glove, up.
White Glove, up.
Blue Glove, down.
White Glove, down.
Don't raise White Glove.
Blue Glove, up.
Blue Glove, punch.
That's it.
(They both become Smurfs.)
That's how it will be done.
That's how the game will go.
- Okay.
- That was harsh.
- That's how the game will go.
- Do you see me as a guy?
No, I'm just being fair.
- Let the game begin.
- Sure.
(The real game begins.)
Blue Glove, down.
White Glove, up.
Don't raise Blue Glove.
White Glove, down.
Don't raise White Glove.
Blue Glove, down.
Don't lower Blue Glove.
White Glove, up.
White Glove, down.
White Glove, punch.
(White Glove, punch.)
(Did he punch with the blue one?)
Didn't he punch with the blue one?
- Yes, the blue one.
- Suk Jin got it wrong.
Also, hesitating
will make you lose a point.
- Of course.
- Yes, you can't hesitate.
He's hitting me really hard.
- Your face...
- Are you all right?
- So Min, are you all right?
- Yondu?
- Yondu!
- Oh, no.
What happened to your face?
It's been a while
since we saw Yondu.
- What happened to your face?
- Oh, no.
I'm not kidding...
when I say he's punching me
with all his might.
- I'm only invested in the game.
- Rather than...
Here we go again.
Blue Glove, down.
- Don't raise White Glove.
- Hold on a second.
(Minus 1 point, Minus 1 point)
Hold on a second.
What's the matter with you?
- He lost points.
- Focus, will you?
You lost points just now.
Isn't this a hard game
for someone his age?
How many points do I have left?
- You're at minus four.
- Already?
- What about her?
- Minus two points.
- Here we go again.
- Sure.
He'll be eliminated
if he loses another point.
(Suk Jin can't afford
to make another mistake.)
Blue Glove, down.
Blue Glove, down...
(Whispering)
- What was that?
- That's out of the blue.
- Is that allowed?
- I take requests.
Is that allowed?
- I do what you ask of me.
- She's not cheating, is she?
I can do it for you.
All right, now. Blue Glove, down.
- She got her leg up.
- Blue Glove, down.
- So Min is up to something.
- Blue Glove, up.
Blue Glove, up.
Punch as much as you want.
(Punch as much as you want.)
(So Min attacks first)
Blue Glove, down.
Suk Jin, you're eliminated.
- Why?
- Oh, no.
How come?
We attacked at the same time.
(Big Nose got eliminated
for responding late.)
He lost when he got attacked
like that.
(He gets eliminated humiliatingly.)
We attacked at the same time,
so why was I eliminated?
You're eliminated.
- We attacked at the same time.
- You were slower.
How? Based on what?
- She hit you first.
- She was faster.
There's such a thing
as punching as much as we want?
This is upsetting!
Is Suk Jin done with?
What happened? Am I...
Jong Kook can play next.
What? Gosh, we're in trouble.
Jun Ha is determined to win.
He knows that this game
was made for him.
He knows.
He's running simulations
in his head.
He's thinking,
"How should I make it fun?"
"How should I get hit?"
"I need to make it funny."
Here we go.
White Glove, down.
Blue Glove, down.
White Glove, punch.
(White Glove, punch.)
(Throwing a left hook
with his teeth clenched)
Good job!
- Jong Kook is...
- He's good!
He's showing no mercy.
Blue Glove, punch.
(Blue Glove, punch.)
(So Min gets eliminated
after getting blue braises.)
- So Min, you're eliminated.
- You're done.
It's time...
to teach them a lesson.
You should start warming up.
MC Minzy, you should devour them.
Go devour them.
It's the Jung Jun Ha game.
- He's ready.
- Let's have him play right away.
- MC Minzy!
(Here comes MC Minzy.)
- Enjoy it all you want.
- I can't wait to see you play.
MC Minzy,
play with him all you want!
All right.
"This is to my liking."
I should wash my wig later.
- MC Minzy.
- Here we go.
- You were born in 2002, right?
- Yes.
- Why are you so casual with me?
- Yes, I was.
- I'm older than you.
- Here we go.
Teach him a lesson, Jong Kook.
Blue Glove, punch.
(Blue Glove, punch.)
That's one hilarious punch!
You're taking the punch well!
It's the Jung Jun Ha game.
It's the game made for him!
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yes, I am.
Isn't he knocked out?
Isn't he... Are you okay?
Are you good, MC Minzy?
- He's good as expected.
- He takes the punch well.
Here we go again.
White Glove, punch.
(White Glove, punch.)
Are you okay?
- He's...
- He's getting worked up.
Let's get started.
- All right.
- He's strong because he's so young.
- MC Minzy is...
- He's hungry for it.
- You guys, watch it carefully.
His punches are pretty fast.
You're quite strong.
- He learned boxing.
- I was like...
- You didn't...
give us any other instructions
and told us to punch.
Here we go.
White Glove, punch twice.
(White Glove, punch twice.)
(Getting two punches at once)
- It was two punches, right?
- Right.
- Yes, it was correct.
- Are you okay?
So you were supposed to punch
with White Glove first.
Was it correct?
Since you told them
to punch twice...
Even if I swing my arms randomly,
he gets hit anyway.
- It's fun.
- The area of his face...
- It's very wide.
- We need to go faster.
- He learned boxing, that's why.
- His face is wide.
- MC Minzy game!
- Here we go.
- It's nerve-racking.
Blue Glove, down.
- Blue Glove, down.
- It's nerve-racking.
Don't lower White Glove.
(They lost a point each.)
Don't lower Blue Glove.
Don't lower White Glove.
MC Minzy flinched.
Blue Glove,
down.
Blue Glove, down.
Don't punch with White Glove.
He told you not to punch.
(Grunting)
Don't punch with White Glove.
I told you not to punch.
(The boxer threw a right hook
by instinct.)
I told you not to punch.
Wait a minute. Goodness.
He was all ready to punch.
Are you okay?
I mean...
His punch...
- Your punch is too fast.
- It's because I get trained a lot.
- Hey.
- This is...
But it hurts a little.
(But it hurts a little.)
It hurts.
No, I didn't hit you hard.
I didn't hit you hard.
- It hurts a little.
- Are you okay?
It hurts.
- But...
- His face...
- Wasn't this supposed to be fun?
- His face is too wide.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not. That's not it.
This side of my face...
- He looks like a mammoth from here.
- It's the first time my face...
is hurting ever since I got hit
by my friend in high school.
Didn't my eye just pop out?
- It's okay.
- Is it okay?
(It's okay.)
You didn't get hit in the eye.
- MC Minzy, are you okay?
- Yes, I'm good.
- All right.
- You're quite fast.
I really...
care about the guests' well-being,
so don't worry.
- MC Minzy game!
- Here we go again.
If he loses another point,
he'll be eliminated.
- He has only one point to go.
- It can happen.
- Jun Ha, you're doing well.
- They took away my point instead.
Here we go.
Blue Glove, down.
Blue Glove, up.
Don't raise Blue Glove.
Don't lower White Glove.
(Don't raise Blue Glove.)
(Whistle blowing)
(MC Minzy is eliminated.)
- He didn't get to punch at all.
- Hey.
He didn't get to punch at all.
He was only beaten.
You did it.
Am I eliminated?
That's so cruel.
Well done, MC Minzy.
- MC Minzy.
- You're quite strong.
It looks like you pulled your shirt
up to here.
You should be on variety shows
as you pursue your career in music.
You're very talented.
But it hurts so much.
That was hilarious.
That was great.
- Who is going next?
- Then is Haha...
going next?
Haha, you should go next.
My business partner.
He plays golf too.
Show us your footwork, will you?
You know the one you're good at.
- Show it to us.
- Gosh, it's been so long.
- He's fast.
- He's different.
- Go for it.
- He's so fast.
The punches you do
as you put up a guard.
(His punches aren't threatening
at all.)
That was one great punch.
- Let's do this.
- I can't wait to see this match.
As expected of you.
- Here we go.
- He's fast.
(A match between business partners)
Just beat him up.
- Keep your eyes open until the end.
- Here we go.
Blue Glove, down.
Blue Glove, up.
Blue Glove, punch.
- My goodness.
- Oh, no.
Blue Glove, punch.
(Blue Glove, punch.)
(The cheeky boxer got beaten
in 3 seconds.)
He's no match for Jong Kook.
- It's not fair.
- But this is...
- What's wrong with it?
- I don't think this will work.
Do you want me to
throw in the towel?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
- Darn it.
- What's wrong?
He's a father.
- He's a father of three!
- What's wrong with it?
- That was...
- What?
Wasn't he hit right in the face?
What's wrong?
I thought he shot a fireball.
You look like Dream.
He looks like Dream.
Don't raise Blue Glove.
Don't punch with White Glove.
(Flinching)
(He's daunted after getting shot
by a fireball.)
- Are you doing okay?
- I feel bad for him.
Oh, no.
(Whispering)
- All right. He asked me something.
- What is it?
He demanded something.
All right.
Punch as much as you want.
You jerk!
(To protect the player,
Haha got eliminated.)
He didn't get to attack.
(To protect the player,
Haha got eliminated.)
I'm bleeding.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, no.
- What's wrong?
- Are you okay?
Why are you crying? Don't cry.
Don't cry. What's wrong with you?
It's just a game.
Don't cry.
- Let's deal with Se Chan now.
- Se Chan, come out to play.
You're trying to...
- punish them, aren't you?
- That's not it.
- You are...
- That's what I think too.
You're trying to get rid of those
who get on your nerves.
Come play,
Se Chan who loves golfing.
Se Chan, get back at him for us.
If Se Chan loses,
the female players
will have to step up.
- It's okay.
- You got this!
You got this!
- Se Chan who is good at golf.
- Here we go.
(Se Chan
is Team Majority's last hope)
- White Glove, down.
- Aren't we too close?
They're too close.
It'll hurt more
if you're too close to each other.
Blue Glove, up.
Blue Glove, to the side.
White Glove, to the side.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
It was a mistake. I'm sorry.
I got confused.
Didn't you tell us to punch?
- He didn't tell us to punch?
- I didn't.
- It's okay. It can be confusing.
- It can be confusing.
Wait a minute.
- Wait. It can be confusing.
- You got hit.
- Why would he be mad?
- He got hit.
I was...
I was too focused on it.
- Shall we?
- He let his guard down.
White Glove, down.
I told you to put down White Glove.
(White Glove, punch.)
I'm sorry.
You need to follow the instruction.
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
My nose hurts.
- Here we go.
- Se Chan.
- You can do it.
- Here we go.
Blue Glove, down.
White Glove, down.
Don't lower White Glove.
- Wait for your chance.
- Blue Glove, down.
All right. I lost.
I lost.
(After giving him a good punch,
he quits voluntarily.)
- All right. I lost.
- He lost.
Stop lying.
- That was...
- Se Chan lost!
- I punched him twice!
Fine.
In 1, 2, 3.
Look at your members resenting you.
Seriously.
It feels like we're getting dragged
to a slaughterhouse.
Next is Ji Hyo.
Gosh, that was hilarious.
Let's beat them all!
Yes, I won't lose to them.
Ji Hyo, we only need one more win.
You can do it, Ji Hyo.
- Jong Kook, don't go easy on her.
- Let's do it, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, let's go.
- You're the best.
- Don't go easy on her.
- All right.
Here we go.
(The last redoubt of Team Majority,
Song Ji Hyo)
Blue Glove, down.
Blue Glove, down. Blue Glove, up.
- Blue Glove, down.
- What is he doing?
What aren't you doing it?
White Glove, down.
White Glove, up.
Don't raise White Glove.
Blue Glove, down.
Don't lower Blue Glove.
White Glove, up.
- Excuse me.
- White Glove, up.
(Excuse me.)
Ji Hyo is eliminated.
- Ji Hyo is eliminated.
- You're eliminated.
(Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
Ji Hyo is eliminated.
Why are you so bad at this?
I've been counting,
and she made about six mistakes.
- Ji Hyo.
- That was...
- Pull yourself together.
- She made that many mistakes?
Team Minority wins.
- Yes!
- All right! I'm so relieved.
How did Team Minority win?
The team that has Jong Kook
as its member always wins.
(Jong Kook beats everyone else.
They move on to the next mission.)
I keep losing.
What's this?
That's... My goodness.
What is this?
It's that one.
(A huge set
that looks like a bridge)
This looks exciting.
I guess it has something
to do with using strength.
- What's this supposed to be?
- What could it be?
- What's this?
- It's scary.
(It's 14m long and 3m high.)
It must be something difficult.
I think we need to jump onto it.
- Please go easy on us.
- We're in trouble.
There are so many styrofoams.
It must be a big game.
It's the long-awaited final mission.
The keyword for the last mission...
is intuition.
- Intuition?
We'll go in this order.
Jae Suk, you trusted me to go first
because it uses our intuition.
- What's your number?
- Nice.
Five?
- Until number five?
- We have Jong Kook on our team.
Until number five?
It's BIBI, Jong Kook, Se Chan,
Ji Hyo, and me.
Let me tell you the rules
of this game.
When you go up there...
You know the glass panel bridge
in "Squid Game", right?
- Oh, gosh.
- It's that game?
Just like that game,
You're going to cross 13 panels
with a 50-percent chance.
Goodness.
One is made of styrofoam,
and the other one is wood.
If you step on the styrofoam panel,
you'll fall.
That means you'll be eliminated.
Then the next person
from the same team will go.
The team that makes it
to the furthest wins.
- It sounds fun.
- No way.
You can't test the panel.
Of course not.
It's better to have more people
on your team.
It's better to have more people.
We're at an advantage
because we have more people.
- Let's play.
- All right. Let's play!
Gosh, I can't believe
we're playing this game.
It looks fun though.
I'm actually scared.
I don't want to go first.
I thought both teams were crossing
from the ends.
Some might not even get to try it.
This is difficult.
Right? Not everyone can play.
- Of course.
- It's difficult.
- It's really difficult.
- My gosh.
But it's thrilling.
It's scary.
Gosh, I can't tell them apart.
- I really can't tell them apart.
- Of course not.
- I can't tell them apart from here.
- Jae Suk.
- I can't tell at all.
- I can't tell at all either.
This one looks like styrofoam.
To everyone on the winning team,
we'll give 100 points each.
We'll give additional points
for the number of panels...
you guessed right.
- You're giving us more points?
- Yes.
Which member is going first?
Members from each team
should step forward.
Look how Suk Jin got up
to go first.
- It's...
- You're awesome.
I can't do it.
I didn't volunteer.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- That's not it.
- You're awesome.
Okay, I'll go first.
Will you shout out my name
a few times?
- Ji Suk Jin.
(Studying others)
Since we have fewer members...
- You should go.
- A man should go first.
In terms of the order,
you'll have to go first.
Okay. I'll go first.
Jae Suk was suddenly pushed
to go first.
You should step in the middle.
Which one is a styrofoam panel?
I think this is...
Let's see if we can tell them apart.
- That one looks like styrofoam.
- Let's take a look at it together.
- I think this is styrofoam.
- This looks like styrofoam.
- I can't tell them apart from here.
- I have no idea.
- I have no idea also.
Gosh, one of them is a wooden panel?
You did such a fine job.
I can't tell them apart.
Nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
We have 13 chances?
How are we supposed to make it
within 13 chances?
We have 13 chances?
They have a better chance
of winning.
It's somewhat scary.
The team that advances more
will win.
If this was "Squid Game",
we die if we fall.
You're right.
I'll just think
that my life depends on it.
Here we go then.
(It's scary to jump from there
as the bridge is tall.)
If we make it,
then we'll turn the tables.
- Gosh, they made it so well.
- Maybe that's not the one.
- I can't tell them apart.
- Go.
- Go, Jae Suk.
- He made up his mind.
- No. Don't go.
- You're the lucky one.
Gosh.
- Don't look down.
- Goodness.
I think I'll find you flat
on the ground soon.
(I think I'll find you flat
on the ground soon.)
- I'm going now.
- Okay, go ahead.
- I got this!
- You can do it.
- Here we go.
- I think...
you'll be flat on the ground
like a squid.
Is that why
it's called "Squid Game"?
- You won't fall flat from here.
- Okay.
You'll be less scared...
if you just think you're going to
break through the panel.
- Think that you'll break through.
- Let's go!
- Three...
- You should jump with both feet.
- Jump with both feet.
- Okay!
(Why would you talk to me?)
- Let's go!
- Think that you'll break through.
- In one...
- Three.
(Standing at the starting line)
- In one...
- Three.
- Two, one. Go!
- Two.
Go! Why aren't you leaving?
Hey! If this was in drama,
we'd all die!
- I told you to go.
- Just break through it.
- You're going to break through it.
- Three...
- Two, one.
- I'm going to jump on that one.
(Jae Suk chose the panel
on the right.)
(Will he make it?)
- Zero!
- Go!
- Die!
(He jumped.)
- You're going to break through it.
- Zero!
- Go!
- Die!
- Oh, gosh.
(It was a wooden panel.)
Gosh!
That's it!
(He was really scared.)
- You made it!
- He got the right one.
- You made it.
- Gosh!
(He couldn't help but kneel.)
- Can you tell them apart?
- You did it.
Gosh, you're amazing.
- I thought he'd fall.
- Me too.
Oh, no!
- I nearly died!
- It's a little different.
- It almost killed me.
- I'm going next.
Jae Suk. There must be a twist.
You should go diagonally.
(It's time to move on
to the second panel.)
- There must be a twist.
- No.
In "Squid Game", they chose
the one above it.
No, you shouldn't.
I don't think there's a twist.
- You don't think so?
- I don't know.
I don't think
you should choose that.
Try to think
of the host's intention.
(Should he go straight
or diagonally?)
I don't think it's the one
on the left.
- I think you should go straight.
- Should I choose the other one?
Jae Suk. Don't you think
you should go straight?
I'll go diagonally.
- Go ahead.
- Really? It's too obvious though.
- I'll give it a try.
- Go ahead.
- Go for it.
- I don't care now.
- We'll see where you go,
- and we'll follow next.
- I'm as good as dead.
- You know that, right?
- All right.
- I'm as good as dead.
- We heard you.
- Three.
- Two.
- One!
- One.
- Jump!
- Go!
- Oh, no!
Oh, gosh.
Is it this one or that one?
Oh, no.
- Three, two,
- Which one will you choose?
- one!
- I can't bring myself to do it.
(I can't bring myself to do it.)
Go!
(He falls right through the panel.)
That was styrofoam.
What happened?
(The scaredy-cat
got even more scared...)
(by the bottom that was lifted
for safety.)
(Screaming)
- Oh, gosh.
- Darn it.
- We never know who'll win.
- We never know.
I really can't tell them apart.
You need to go as far as possible.
- Oh, no.
- I want to get eliminated already.
(I want to get eliminated already.)
I shouldn't watch them play.
Why did they prepare this game
when I'm here?
I hate this kind of game the most.
- My feet are sweaty already.
- Suk Jin, I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
It's so scary.
Please continue.
It's impossible to tell them apart
from their appearance.
Let's go, Mr. Ji.
(Suk Jin's choice
became more important...)
(as Jae Suk succeeded
in the first stage.)
I hope Mr. Ji can make it
through halfway.
I know. If he makes it
through halfway...
Il Nam!
"What did I say?"
"Did I say it's on the left?"
Suk Jin, just stick to one side
and go straight.
- He's right.
- Three,
- two, one, go!
- Two, one, go!
- Go!
- No, I can't!
You should go.
Three, two, one.
Let's go.
(He can't bring himself to go
as he's scared.)
- They're so well-crafted.
- Three, two...
- You should just run.
- Three, two,
- one!
- I won't die.
- Go!
(He fell from the first panel.)
Oh, no.
You should think that
they'll break anyway.
That's right.
Gosh, you said...
- You said this was the styrofoam.
- We're in the lead.
- All right.
- We're ahead of them.
It's Team Minority's turn.
- All right!
Ji Hyo is the lucky type,
- You should jump on it hard.
- so she has a chance.
- It doesn't hurt much.
- It's this one, right?
- That's it.
- Jump on it hard.
You can step on the next one.
- Go for it.
- Okay.
- That's it.
- Even when you know...
This is where I need to
choose one, right?
Ji Hyo, I don't think
it's on that side.
Watch carefully. If you do, you
might be able to pick the right one.
- Which one should I pick?
- But Jong Kook,
do you think they put
the wooden panels in a row?
It's plausible.
I think they put them in a row.
- Go for it.
- Right, Ji Hyo?
I think this one is styrofoam.
But I think it's too risky.
If it's three blocks in a row...
- I would go straight.
- Me too.
Then go straight. Okay.
Bo Pil, this game
really draws us in.
- You need to be the judge, Ji Hyo.
- One, two...
Three.
Is she suddenly picking her hose?
- She is suddenly picking her nose.
- It felt itchy.
Okay. You can pick your nose
before you die.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- You should go diagonally.
- No.
- Hold on.
- No. I will go straight.
- Will you go straight?
- Go.
(She decides to go straight
and gets down to jump.)
It's hard.
- It's hard, right?
If it's hard for Ji Hyo,
it will be harder for us.
Go.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
I can't believe
Ji Hyo is that scared.
She is someone who bungee-jumped
from the Macau Tower.
- Three, two,
- I understand.
- one. Go.
- One. Go.
It's impossible to jump like that.
Go. Come on.
(Grunting)
What are you doing?
- This is driving me crazy.
- If Ji Hyo is that scared...
Here I go.
- Just jump.
- Ji Hyo.
- Just imagine that you will fall.
- That's the way to go.
(Trembling)
- You need to be ready.
- Her legs are trembling.
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh, this is nothing.
- She is becoming angry.
- Gosh.
- Go.
You can curse.
- That's good. Go.
- You can curse.
It would have been easier
if there were no floor.
It's okay. Just imagine
that there is no floor.
(She is more scared of the floor.)
One, two,
- three.
- Three.
It's okay.
There you go.
- It's wood.
- She chose correctly.
(It's wood.)
She chose correctly.
- It's wood.
- Ji Hyo, jump again.
It was the block on the right
three times in a row.
Let's keep going.
Hey.
It has to be that one.
Trust yourself.
(Nervous)
- Go.
- Here I go.
Ji Hyo.
(It's wood again!)
That's incredible.
She is moving forward.
- Ji Hyo, I love you.
- She is moving forward.
She has good intuition.
What should we do?
- Here I go.
- Okay. One.
- She will go diagonally.
- Two.
- Two, three.
- She will jump.
- Go.
- Jump to the center.
Come on. Jump.
Jump.
What?
- What?
- That's incredible.
(How is that even possible?)
- We are set.
- No way.
This is scarier.
It's unbelievable.
I forgot the path she took.
- Right, right, right.
- You need to memorize the path.
Shouldn't you go straight?
I don't think
you should go diagonally.
Will you go diagonally?
Don't you think
you should go straight?
No. I will go with my hunch.
- I think you should go straight.
- Me too.
- There she goes.
- One,
two,
- three.
- It will be insane if she succeeds.
Then I will acknowledge her talent.
You can take one step first.
You don't have to jump.
- Do that.
- I want to poop.
(I want to poop.)
- Put your right foot on the block.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- I will jump...
- and land on two feet.
- There you go.
- That's good. Okay.
- Ji Hyo.
It has to be wood.
(What?)
- Is it wood?
- No way!
- She is insane.
- Hey.
(The staff members are talking
among themselves.)
- She is insane.
- Hey.
Ji Hyo.
- She is insane.
- That's insane.
Do you know the answer?
My hands are shaking.
I am so scared.
- My goodness.
- I got goosebumps.
- I am scared.
- What is up with Ji Hyo?
- She is incredible.
- That's amazing.
That's amazing.
You are insane.
(Team Minority reached the middle.)
We look so shabby in comparison.
What should we do?
Ji Hyo got four blocks right.
(But she still has
a long way to go.)
Don't you think
you should go straight?
- Leave her be.
- Shall I leave her be?
She has a good hunch.
It's a gift from the above.
Mom.
I miss my mom.
(What will be Ji Hyo's choice
this time?)
I miss my mom.
(Missing her mom in Mapo-gu,)
(she chooses
to go diagonally again!)
Let's go.
(She chose to go diagonally
4 times in a row!)
My entire body is shaking.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(Please!)
Oh, no.
She startled me.
- Oh, no.
- She startled me.
She startled me.
I was so startled.
Her legs gave out.
Do it like you did before.
Take a step
before you jump with both feet.
I will take a step
before I jump with both feet.
- Don't land hard on one foot.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Do it with both feet.
Three, two, one.
Go.
(She survived 5 consecutive blocks!)
(Their jaws drop.)
She knows the answer.
- Hey.
- Gosh.
She knows the answer.
- Hey.
- You are the doctor, right?
- Maybe she is the mastermind.
- How is this possible?
- She must know the answer.
(The entire group goes
into a frenzy.)
You know the answer, right?
- Do you know the answer?
- What is going on?
- My hands are shaking.
- How is this possible?
Do you know the answer?
What's the mathematical probability?
Forget it. You are doing great.
It has to be really low.
She chose correctly
five times in a row.
Only six blocks remain.
(Only 6 blocks remain.)
- Gosh.
- Since there are six blocks left,
we will be able to succeed.
We got this.
- We are safe.
- We got this.
- We will be able to succeed.
- Are you memorizing the path?
- Of course.
- Zigzag.
- Three and four.
- Did I come from that block?
- Yes.
- I came from that block.
- You moved diagonally.
Will you move diagonally again?
- Suit yourself.
- I think she should go straight.
I don't think you should go zigzag.
Do what you think is right.
For how long
will the zigzag pattern continue?
What will be Ji Hyo's choice?
What will it be?
I think you should go straight.
- Will you go zigzag?
- I feel dizzy.
- If she succeeds again...
- You have done so well already.
Despite being in an opposing team,
I can't help but root for her.
- I don't care about the teams.
- I hope she wins.
Just do it.
Reach the end, Ji Hyo.
I can't watch this.
Your intuition is incredible.
I will take off 1 foot
and land on 2 feet.
This makes no sense.
In terms of probability...
It will be okay even if I fall.
One foot.
(She is extremely nervous.)
- Go, Ji Hyo.
- All right.
- Don't land on the right foot only.
- Go.
- Here...
- She will fall.
- I go.
- Just go.
(She succeeded 6 times in a row!)
- That's amazing!
- No way.
How is this possible?
- That's amazing!
- That's impossible.
- No way.
- How is this possible?
How is this possible?
- No way.
- It feels staged.
- You know the answer, right?
- Unbelievable.
Maybe she is just light.
- This is unbelievable.
- Maybe she is just light.
- How is this possible?
- This is insane.
Gosh.
Even I am getting nervous.
Her intuition is incredible.
Ji Hyo, you would survive
"Squid Game".
Shall we have Team Majority
go first?
- Yes.
- Let's do that.
- Give it a try.
- You can resume afterward.
Okay.
Sit down.
Sit down, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, I respect you.
Now,
- will Yeji go next?
- I will die anyway.
You will survive.
Go to the left.
- I studied the blocks.
- Yeji.
It's Yeji's turn.
- Yeji, you should...
- I think...
it's this block.
- Go with your hunch.
- Hold on.
The blocks don't look different.
You need to go with your hunch.
You can't tell by looking.
This one.
- All right.
- Okay. Go.
- I don't think it's a bad choice.
- Jump gently.
- Shall we do a countdown?
- One.
Three,
two,
one. Go.
(Flapping)
Are you okay?
- That was funny.
- Why can't I jump?
- It's hard, right?
- Is it that scary?
I am okay.
- I understand how it feels.
- Me too.
It's okay.
Yeji.
I am sorry, but are you a spirit?
- You keep...
- He is someone who passed away.
- Can you see me?
- This one.
- I will go.
- Okay.
- Three, two...
- Jump at once.
- Don't hesitate.
- You will get hurt if you do.
- Two, one.
- Jump at once.
Go.
(She got the styrofoam board.)
(Laughing)
- My goodness.
- We have no hope.
- Should I go back?
- Yes.
We have no hope.
I guess I am bad at this.
- MC Minzy.
- Look at that.
The board will completely shatter
if I stand on the top.
- Oh, no.
- It's impossible to tell.
Shall we have another member go?
Have another member go.
- Ji Hyo is incredible.
- Two more members should go.
MC Minzy.
- MC Minzy, let's go.
- MC Minzy.
- Let's go.
- I think I am going to die.
I can't do this.
Come on. Don't be like that.
Do you want Luda to go?
Would that be okay?
- Haha should go.
- Go ahead, Haha.
- I don't think I can do this.
- Hurry up, Haha.
So Min is the next in order.
Gosh, the older members...
- don't act their age.
- Go.
- Gosh.
- Haha is the same.
- Go, So Min.
So Min.
- So Min, you are really cool.
- Let's win. You are cool.
- Hey.
- So Min.
You won't jump
into the hole, will you?
That will be funny.
Good luck.
- You can do it.
- Are you a spirit?
Can you see me?
So Min, go.
- Good luck.
- Was it really scary?
Once you sink,
you think, "This is it."
But the moment...
- The moment you jump.
- The moment you jump,
- your heart sink.
- Really?
But it's okay. It isn't that bad.
You were brave.
- So Min, go.
- We will root for you.
- This is really scary.
- So Min, go.
(So Min is
Team Majority's third player.)
I think...
the dirtier board is wood.
- This one. I will go straight.
- Okay.
You should definitely go straight.
The earlier pattern was zigzag,
so you should go straight.
So Min is incredible.
So Min, shall I count down?
- No. Don't do it.
- Okay.
Let's beat the other team.
- Your form is nice.
- What am I going to do?
I am Super So Min!
- Okay.
- That's good.
Let's fly!
- Get ready for the fall.
- You can do it.
- I am ready.
- Let's go.
One.
I won't get startled.
It's the sound that startles people.
Drum roll.
- I think you chose correctly.
- Really?
- One, two, three.
- Three, two, one.
(Will So Min give
the first success to the team?)
That's it.
(She got the styrofoam board.)
What was up with that face?
She closed her eyes and fell.
What should we do?
The pattern continues to be zigzag.
(Team Majority failed
3 times in a row.)
It was completely fine.
But...
- It was completely fine, right?
- Yes.
- Next.
- How did I fail in one go?
- Team Majority.
- MC Minzy.
- MC Minzy, let's go.
- How did I fail in one go?
I can't do this.
Let's go up to Ji Hyo.
- MC Minzy.
- I feel like...
- I am going to poop.
- It's nothing.
Do you want to go after Luda?
Shall I go next?
- Ji Hyo will go next.
- She can jump right away.
Really? Thank goodness.
- You will go sooner or later.
- My goodness.
Ji Hyo, you have already done
an incredible job.
Seriously.
(She got 6 answers in a row.)
Ji Hyo, you really are
extraordinary.
(The probability of Ji Hyo's path)
She chose correctly.
- It's wood.
- No way.
- How is this possible?
- She must know the answer.
- Here I go.
- Just go.
(Ji Hyo achieved
the probability of 1.5 percent.)
I came from this block, right?
- Yes. You did.
- I came from this block, right?
There have been five blocks
in a zigzag pattern.
Three straight blocks
and five zigzag blocks.
Don't you think
you should go straight this time?
Had there been someone like you
in "Squid Game",
about 20 people would have survived.
- She is so cool.
- I would get confused.
- She won't succeed again.
- That's right.
- Will you go zigzag again?
(She chose the diagonal block
6 times in a row!)
She will do it again. Okay.
- Go.
- Do what you want.
- I will go zigzag.
- Okay.
- We kept getting it wrong.
- That way,
- we will see the pattern.
- That's right.
- We kept getting it wrong.
- Two, three.
One, two, three. Go.
(The probability will be 0.7 percent
if she succeeds again.)
I will take off 1 foot
and land on 2 feet.
That's right. 1, 2...
(She will compete
for the 0.7-percent probability.)
Will she get it right again?
- I think she will.
- She got it right.
She knows what to do.
(What will be the result
of her 7th jump?)
One, two, three. Go.
Just go.
This makes no sense.
(She achieved
the 0.7-percent probability.)
(Unbelievable)
(This makes no sense.)
- Gosh.
- You know the answer, right?
- This is impossible.
- How...
- Hey.
- How is this possible?
- This makes no sense.
- Seriously.
- It's insane.
- This makes no sense.
(The production crew's
point of view)
(Oh!)
(My goodness!)
(For goodness' sake.)
(The production crew
became confused.)
- How...
- I think...
- she is a glass specialist.
- How is this possible?
- This makes no sense.
- Seriously.
- I think she knows the pattern.
- Is she a spy?
- She is just that good at it.
- Ji Hyo, just finish it.
- Is she a spy?
- She is unbelievable.
Will you go zigzag again?
(Will she go zigzag again
for the 8th block?)
(Perhaps it will give her
8 consecutive successes.)
I am going to try it.
- Okay. Try it.
- Go.
Isn't she the second player?
Her team will win.
You never know. MC Minzy
might reach the finish line.
She might make it happen.
- We are riding on her coattails.
- Here I go.
- Go.
- If I fail, it's the other one.
- Can you cross three blocks?
- Okay.
She is so cool.
- "Can you cross three blocks?"
- She is incredible.
- I know.
(Team Minority has
three members left.)
- She is cool.
- She is sexy.
I will take off 1 foot
and land on 2 feet.
- That's right.
- Okay.
She is so cool.
She is incredible.
How did she do that?
(Will Ji Hyo succeed
8 times in a row?)
- Gosh.
- It's okay.
Good job.
Are you okay?
- Ji Hyo.
- She did so well.
- You are amazing.
- It's the other block.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Seriously.
- We are set.
You are incredible.
- You got this, right?
- Okay.
She is cool.
- What should I do?
- Team Minority...
will succeed
unless everyone fails at once.
That's right.
If everyone fails at once,
you won't succeed.
This is hard.
If two people fail,
you need to get the last one right.
- Really?
- Right?
- I need to get one right.
- That's right.
- You are nervous.
You are nervous.
I need to get 1 right.
The 2 of you...
- should do well.
- Someone needs to succeed.
- Our team needs a hero.
- MC Minzy.
- Let's go.
I am going to die.
Here comes the hero of the team.
I want to poop.
I understand.
It's scary.
Which way should I go?
It's that block after this block.
- What?
- You know the 1st 3 blocks.
- That's right.
- Go zigzag three times.
Then you choose a block.
Let's hurry up.
- Although she is an opponent...
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
- You are incredible.
- You are amazing.
- You are so cool.
Ji Hyo, give us a tip
if you have one.
- Sit here.
- Sit comfortably.
Sit comfortably.
What will become of our lives?
She is incredible.
It's so nerve-racking.
- My goodness.
- I know.
Let's go.
- Go.
- Those blocks are safe.
- They are wood.
I want to see
how it would feel when I jump.
They are wood.
You can just walk past them.
They might break
because of my body weight.
It's okay.
Get yourself on the block
and jump on the spot.
The wooden blocks can support
up to two tonnes.
- That's right.
- So this is what it feels like.
- It's okay.
- Jump to the center.
- You won't die.
- That's right.
Why is it scary
to move to that block?
- It's okay. For goodness' sake.
- Gosh.
- I hate games like this.
- It's okay.
You know how scared I get
of such games.
What are you saying?
It's no wonder
they wanted me for this date.
Why are you babbling?
- I can't do this.
- What are you saying?
What are you saying?
They said it would be
the most comfortable and easy.
Who are you talking to?
I would rather take a punch
to the face.
- What do you want us to do?
- We could push you.
I am the most scared of this game.
I want to poop.
MC Minzy, we could push you.
It will be funny if you poop.
That block is safe. Just go.
I just want to know
how it would feel.
I know it's safe. I am not a fool.
MC Minzy, it's time to choose.
Look.
Three blocks made a zigzag pattern.
Will you go zigzag again?
- Go zigzag again.
- Will you go zigzag again?
- Trust me.
- Go.
- For goodness' sake.
- Go zigzag.
- MC Minzy. Go zigzag.
- Go.
- For goodness' sake.
- MC Minzy.
Succeed three times.
- Go diagonally.
- I am bad at things like this.
- MC Minzy, just jump.
- Succeed three times.
- Go diagonally.
- Put your hands together.
Lovely MC Minzy.
- I know.
- Put your hands together.
We are worried about you.
I will put my hands together.
Don't rush me.
We only reminded you
because you didn't do it.
- MC Minzy, just jump.
- Go.
- Jump.
- Will you go straight?
- That's cute.
- Three, two.
- Jump.
- Go.
- Gosh!
The TV ratings will fall!
- I am sorry.
- People will switch the channel.
MC Minzy.
- "I am sorry."
- For goodness' sake.
- Be quiet.
- Jump.
Hold on. Gosh.
Just jump.
- I can't say anything.
- I know.
- Jump.
- Go.
We will push you.
Don't push me!
(MC Minzy is filming a monodrama.)
All right.
Say "I Say Woo!" and jump.
Hurry up and go.
- "I Say Woo!"
- Woo!
(Thanks to the cheer,
he decides to go straight.)
- "I Say Woo!"
- Go diagonally.
No. Go diagonally.
I think I should go straight.
- "I Say Woo!"
(The "I Say Woo!" choir
cheers for him endlessly.)
- "I Say Woo!"
Here I go.
Go, MC Minzy, go.
MC Minzy, go.
You can do it.
(He checks the bottom and jumps.)
(Breaking)
- Gosh.
- I told you...
(The styrofoam board shatters.)
I told you to go diagonally.
I said it was this block.
I told you many times
to go diagonally.
Everyone told you to go diagonally.
I was going to go diagonally.
But Suk Jin stopped me.
- I told you to go diagonally.
- Seriously.
- They are fighting.
- I told you many times.
- What did I tell you?
- He told you to go diagonally.
- He did tell you that.
- I told you that...
- about 13 times.
- All right.
It's over.
- Are you okay?
- Gosh.
- Do you feel relieved?
I feel like I am going to die.
But I do feel relieved.
It's our turn.
BIBI.
- You didn't forget, did you?
- No.
- Be careful!
- That's not the right block!
- You startled me.
Hey.
- Be careful.
(Walking forward)
- Does she know the path?
- Go slowly.
- Gosh, she is...
- She doesn't hesitate.
Youngsters these days.
There you go.
(This youngster
seems to be enjoying herself.)
There you go.
- There you go.
- Go straight.
- Now comes the choice.
(Three blocks remain.)
One member needs to succeed.
We will be safe
once one member succeeds.
- Just succeed once.
- I will go this way.
- If she fails and I fail,
- Okay.
- it will be bad.
- Here I go.
- Will you go diagonally?
- Hold on.
Here I go.
- Will you go diagonally?
- Hold on.
(She jumps without missing a beat.)
Things just got complicated.
- It's scary.
- Things will get complicated.
- This looks bad.
- This is a headache. Is it my turn?
- It's okay.
- You can do this.
Luda, with your good hunch...
- Wish me luck.
- Finish this game...
- and be the star.
- What do I do?
We've lost four members in a row.
(It's interesting that the 4 members
got eliminated in a row.)
- Do you have Luda and Haha?
- Yes.
Luda, you have to finish this.
(All they have after Luda
is Haha who's terrified.)
Luda, you're so cool.
Luda, please finish this for me.
All right. Go.
- We've moved only six spaces.
- My gosh.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(Luda decided to go diagonally.)
- Go.
- This is scary.
Three, two, one. Jump!
(What's Luda's destiny?)
Jump!
(Screaming)
(It's the styrofoam again.)
My goodness.
- Oh no.
- What do we do?
- Team Majority...
- I told Jun Ha to go left.
- I know.
- You have to finish this.
No one on this team
got to move forward.
- We have one member left.
- What do we do now?
I believe Haha will finish it.
- Se Chan, do you know that?
- Se Chan, do you remember?
I will watch you.
- One more.
- That's right.
- Go zigzag. Right.
- And...
- No.
- Go straight.
- Move two spaces straight.
They are almost there.
(If Se Chan gets one space right,
his team will cross the bridge.)
- Go.
- Just give it a try.
Go.
(Sighing)
Watch it carefully, Se Chan.
I'll do it like Jiangshi.
- I'll just leap forward...
- Okay.
- and finish it.
- All right.
I will just keep leaping
without talking.
- Go.
- He's being talkative.
- Please finish it.
- He's talking a lot.
Here I go. This is hard, right?
Go on one more space.
Go.
- Is that right?
- He seems nervous.
Just go. Go!
- My goodness.
- What was that?
(It's supposed to be wood,
but it broke.)
- It broke.
- That's...
What's this? This is safe.
My goodness.
- You should be careful.
- What's going on?
Be careful.
- This is safe.
- If I tried, it would've caved in.
- I think so.
- My goodness.
The styrofoam on top broke.
I almost got killed.
- Be careful.
- If it was me,
- I would've been eliminated.
- I can't do this.
- Watch out.
- I'm scared.
- There's wood, right?
- Yes.
I'm scared now.
He can't do this.
Just go.
Se Chan, don't walk on tiptoe.
- All right.
- Don't jump too hard.
Se Chan might finish it.
Right.
If I fall down here,
you'll be in trouble.
- Right.
- Here I go.
- I'm going.
- You can do this.
One, two, and three.
(Groaning)
(Yang Se Chan is eliminated.)
- He fell.
- Oh no.
Haha, we still have a chance to win.
What is he going to do?
Is it over for us?
Do we have Haha left?
- Jong Kook.
- Should I go first? Not Haha?
(Jong Kook
of Team Minority goes first.)
Go three spaces straight.
- Go diagonally.
- Diagonal.
(The last player to decide
the team's fate is Jong Kook.)
- Go diagonally.
- Go zigzag.
- One more.
- Zigzag.
How did we make it that far?
- If he fails here, is it over?
- Yes.
- Jong Kook, just go.
- I have no idea.
I have no idea.
- You can't tell, right?
- No, I can't.
- Go?
- Go.
- Here I go.
- It's no big deal.
We've come a long way.
- We're going to win.
- We will win anyway, right?
Yes. Don't worry.
Here I go. One, two, and three.
(The last jump
for Team Minority's destiny)
Here I go. One, two...
(Despite the slim chance,)
(will they manage
to cross the bridge?)
Three.
(They succeeded
in crossing the bridge.)
(Nice!)
You did it, Jong Kook!
He survived!
(He survived!)
(Thanks to Ji Hyo's superb play,
Team Minority crossed the bridge.)
(But Team Majority has
the hero of Mapo-gu, Haha.)
Go zigzag and straight.
(But he didn't move
even one space forward.)
(Screaming)
Dream! I jumped!
Dream! Your dad did it.
I died, but I did it.
We didn't move...
- even one space forward.
- Dream, I did it!
None of you moved one space forward.
Not even one space.
So all the members
of Team Majority failed the mission.
Team Minority wins.
(Team Minority's
overwhelming victory)
The winning team
gets 100 points each.
And you got additional points
for the spaces you moved.
If that's the case, Ji Hyo is...
You're right.
Let's check the rankings then.
- Let's check it.
- The rankings?
What? Is my ranking high?
- What? I'm in fourth place.
- Is this the final?
Yes. They are the final rankings.
- Why am I in fourth place?
- I'm in the first place?
Why is that?
BIBI and I are in seventh place.
What?
Am I in third place?
- Jun Ha was...
- Why?
Oh, that one.
- He did well at the beginning.
- That's why I'm in the first place.
- We won the first game.
- Right.
I'm at the bottom.
All right.
The rank I pick and higher
will be winners.
- Okay.
- The rest of them will get a penalty.
I have little chance of winning.
- The rest of us will get a penalty?
- Yes.
I'll be fine.
- Pick 8.
- It'll be funny if he picks 7.
- Pick eight.
- All right.
Is there number one in it?
Pick four.
He picked eight earlier,
so we had lunch...
- Why are you smiling?
- We ate Chinese...
- I'm nervous.
- What?
The number I show you
and above will survive.
- Four?
- One...
What's a common number?
Is it 5 or 4?
- It's 5.
- It's 8.
- It's eight!
- That's amazing.
There's no number eight.
- Numbers 1 to 7 survived.
- From 1 to 7?
Numbers 9 to 11 will get a penalty.
(Yeji, So Min, and Luda
will get a penalty.)
It's So Min again.
- BIBI, we've survived!
- I know.
- Gosh, this is unbelievable.
- My goodness.
I'll reveal the penalty.
You should know that
this is product placement.
What is it?
- Product placement?
- Only top stars can do it.
(The idol artists and So Min are
specialized in product placement.)
You'll dance to our guests' songs
in costumes for one minute.
- Really?
- That's a lot of work.
It's so annoying.
- Costumes?
- That sounds really annoying.
That sounds like a lot of work.
But this is
what Yeji and Luda are good at.
So Min, you're lucky.
And that's what you like.
This is pretty.
(Today's costumes are glittering
jackets and colorful wigs.)
Should we look at the camera?
(It's a new 3-member girl group.)
(There's a member who learns
dance moves from her colleagues.)
(She's got the moves
from the 1980s.)
Let's begin then.
- Okay.
- Music please.
(Today's penalty is dancing
to the guests' songs for 1 minute.)
(Music cue)
(The new 3-member girl group
is busy showing off their charms.)
(The music changes to WJSN's song.)
(The 3-member girl group's cheerful
debut performance is over.)
All right.
"I just like this moment."
And...
and "I like everything."
"Running Man" and "Curly hair".
(They are done posting the video.)
- Thank you.
- Good work.
Thank you.
- Good work today.
- Thank you.
(We thank MC Minzy, Luda, BIBI, and
Yeji for all the fun they gave us.)
(A bleak mansion)
Is it a nouveau riche?
(Kim Joon Ho, 45 years old,
an unfortunate guy)
(Since you're here,
I guess this is about a bet.)
(The icon of misfortune, Joon Ho
wants to be the icon of promise.)
(The debate of the 2022's
variety star candidates)
(I'm about to become a parvenu.)
(I think you'll be embroiled
in a big lawsuit.)
(Is it even possible to cast them?)
(Why are you asking me
about the casting?)
(You should ask them!)
(- This is my speaking time.
- I'm not listening.)
(It's the variety star election
with candidates of all ages.)
(The father of comedians,
Kim Joon Ho is joining the race.)
(But his qualifications are
being questioned during the race.)
It's the worst.
It's like sports.
(The icon of misfortune,
Kim Joon Ho...)
(asks them to change his image.)
(Get rid of his bad luck...)
(and fill him with good luck.)
Green light, red light
You're caught.
You should come up here.
(Will Running Man be able
to start his life anew?)
(The Rehabilitation Project,
Icon of Misfortune)