- Hello.
Hello.
Seriously, we should start
treating Suk Jin like a star.
Totally.
He wouldn't even get off his van.
- Okay.
- Good.
Okay.
- It's cool in here, right?
- He has 1.4 million subscribers.
Will you stop that?
- It's 1.4 million.
- Where's the man with 390,000?
- Jae Suk is coming.
- There's Jae Suk.
- He's ready to make jokes.
- Right.
Hello, Jae Suk.
Hey.
Suk Jin is acting like a big star.
You look nice today.
- You look cool.
- That's cute.
I like your outfit.
- It's perfect for today's weather.
- I like your shoes.
- I like your outfit.
- What's with your knee?
I need to take good care of my knee.
Suk Jin is a big star now.
- Why?
- He wouldn't let me open his car.
- Really?
- And the windows are tinted dark.
- I can't see through them.
- Really?
- That's crazy.
- Did you watch the music show?
He should know that
popularity is like bubbles.
Suk Jin did the ending thing.
The ending pose?
Suk Jin did that too.
(Suk Jin made his debut
on a music show a few days ago.)
(He expressed his feelings
with exaggerated gestures.)
(He even did the ending pose
as other idol artists do.)
He doesn't know
that's the end of his life.
(They've got a lot of things
to make fun of Suk Jin with.)
- The end of his life?
- Why isn't he coming?
- He's coming.
- Oh my goodness.
The groom enters.
What?
(They see a dim shape of him.)
What? Why is he...
(Amazed)
I'm just wearing what I got.
Did you just have it fitted?
What's with your suit?
I guess he just had it fitted.
- What's going on?
- What's that suit?
- That's not right for our show.
- Why are you wearing that suit?
- Why is it not right for our show.
- That's not appropriate for today.
This isn't a music show.
- You should look natural.
- This isn't formal.
Just look at this.
- Why are you wearing it?
- Can't I wear a suit like this?
But why?
Because I'm a celebrity.
He calls himself a celebrity.
It's just that you guys wear
the same thing all the time.
- What's with you?
- I want to wear this.
Suk Jin, what's this curtain?
- What?
- Let me pull the curtain open.
- This is...
He's wearing this again.
What do you mean
he's wearing it again?
He was wearing this last week.
- Isn't this an earphone?
- Right.
- Are you listening to music?
- Is it an earphone?
- An in-ear earphone.
- MSG's songs?
- Is it an in-ear earphone?
- Yes, it is.
- This is crazy.
- It's an in-ear earphone.
He has hair on his ears.
You can't pull it out.
You might die.
- It's for longevity.
- Don't pull it out.
It's for longevity.
By the way, it's not aired yet,
but he cried again.
- Really?
- Is that true?
Seriously?
I'm so sick of this.
- Again?
- It's not like that.
- I'm not sure if it will be on TV.
- He's worried.
- You'll understand when you see it.
- Suk Jin...
- has a new catchphrase.
- What is it?
"What's wrong with me?"
(What's wrong with me?)
"You Quiz on the Block" released
one more scene for Running Man.
"What's wrong with me?"
(A few weeks ago,
on "You Quiz on the Block")
(They didn't even add the background
music for Running Man.)
(It's a gift from "You Quiz
on the Block" to Running Man.)
(So Running Man purchased...)
(the clip from them
to return a favor.)
(I don't even know
why I'm being like this.)
(It's not a waste of money...)
(to purchase the clip
of Suk Jin's catchphrase.)
(Starting this video, he's been
crying every other week on MBC.)
Shall we start now? Okay.
- Suk Jin.
- When did you start that?
- "What's wrong with me?"
- I guess he likes to do that.
- I see.
When is Ji Hyo coming?
For today, Ji Hyo has...
invited three special guests.
Let's find out...
who Ji Hyo's friends are.
Is Ji Hyo bringing three friends?
She has a lot of friends.
- Look at that.
- What?
There's Yong Gu.
It's Do Kwon.
Why did he grow a mustache?
Do Kwon is here.
- Yong Gu.
- It's Do Kwon.
Hey, you're here.
What are the glasses for?
You're here.
Hello.
(The No. 1 romantic comedy queen
with great acting skills)
(Actress Nam Ji Hyun who rose from
a child actress to a mature woman.)
(A super rookie who emerged
as a star with "Stove League".)
(An actor with diverse characters,
Chae Jong Hyeop...)
(who featured in dramas
like "Sisyphus" and "Nevertheless".)
(His only target is Kim Jong Kook.)
(He went through a lot every time
because he chose the wrong target.)
(Running Man's family, Ha Do Kwon)
(They are Ji Hyo's friends.)
- They're here.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Ji Hyun.
What's Ji Hyo doing?
Look at Ji Hyo.
She pretends to be a guest.
Ji Hyo, don't act
like you're a guest.
Where's Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo.
- There's Ji Hyo.
- It's for "The Witch's Diner".
- "The Witch's Diner".
"The Witch's Diner".
(They are the stars
from "The Witch's Diner".)
(It's a popular drama
that was aired only two days ago.)
(It's a soulful, cruel fantasy drama
that features a lot of good actors.)
(Actually, it's not an SBS drama,)
(but this is the benefit
that our members can enjoy.)
The first episode is scheduled
to air on July 16?
- Right.
- Yes.
That's why you're here.
All right.
Do Kwon is joining our show
for the fourth time.
- That's a lot.
- What's important is...
He still holds a grudge
against Jong Kook.
- Still?
- Actually,
I've never beaten Jong Kook yet.
I keep doing dramas
just to be on this show.
- Is that why?
- That's funny.
To beat Jong Kook?
He's doing many dramas
to beat Jong Kook on our show.
That's enough, Do Kwon.
You've had enough.
Ji Hyo, tell us about
your character in the drama.
I'm...
- What's wrong?
- Why?
She's crying. You should say,
"What's wrong with me?"
Say "What's wrong with me?"
I play the witch
in "The Witch's Diner".
- Really?
- I see.
It sounds perfect.
She'll make a good witch.
- She's a witch.
- Do you work some magic?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
- Of course. She says she's a witch.
- I'm a witch,
- so I do magic.
- Can you move things?
- Telekinetically?
- Yes.
I also ride a broom.
Excuse me. I can see that
you're trying to help, but...
- It just doesn't work.
- That doesn't help...
their drama.
I knew it sounded strange.
I'm sorry, Do Kwon.
- Say "What's wrong with me?"
- "What's wrong with me?"
- "With my comment?"
Just stay quiet.
What's wrong with my comment?
And they are doing
a drama with Ji Hyo.
We have Nam Ji Hyun here.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Is this your first time...
in Running Man?
Is it your second time?
- It's my second time.
- She was here before.
- When was it?
- It was about six years ago.
That's right. It was a lot of fun.
You thought it was her first time.
- She was really fun.
- I remember that.
- Do you?
- You ran around.
- Are you sure you remember that?
- Sure.
- You were wearing a skirt.
- That's right.
Gosh, you're right.
I heard Ji Hyun was
a psychology major.
That's true.
- That's amazing.
- That sounds cool.
How do you think
Suk Jin is feeling now?
- Look at him.
- Look at his outfit.
His outfit?
I guess he wants to stand out.
(Correct)
We don't have to study
psychology to know that.
- We all feel the same way.
- She knows how he feels.
- He wants to stand out.
- It really stands out.
I'm wearing this
to take good care of you guys.
I think it will be
perfect for our dramas.
Exactly.
I see.
She's nice.
That's good.
Do you know what
giving a two-thumbs-up means?
It means "shut your mouth."
You must already know the meaning.
(She knows the meaning.)
She knows it. She wants me
to stop talking.
That's what young people do, right?
That's what
our writers do all the time.
- I see.
- Oh, that's right!
- "Stop it."
- How dare you...
- But...
- They did it to me.
But old guys get excited
and keep talking.
- "That's enough."
- But they talk even more.
That's when you should stop talking.
There's something
that's even worse than this.
You give a two-thumbs-up
while walking away.
(The worst one is
a moving two-thumbs up.)
- "I'll be on my way."
"I'll be on my way."
And this is your first time
to be on Running Man.
He's Chae Jong Hyeop.
(Actor Chae Jong Hyeop)
- He's handsome.
- He's good-looking.
- He's cute.
- Is this your first variety show?
Yes, this is my first time.
- He's good-looking.
- You've never done this before?
I did one show
to promote our drama...
- a few days ago.
- Which one?
"Amazing..."
- "Amazing Saturday"?
- I see.
You were on "Amazing Saturday".
Why are you so nervous now?
- Don't worry. We're different.
- You will get...
- used to it in no time.
- We're different.
Suk Jin, do something to help him.
I bet he was just like this.
He's blushing to his ears.
You can do this.
- It's so funny.
- Good.
It's all the same.
What was your name again?
My name is Chae Jong Hyeop.
I'll make you a star today.
Wait for me.
First...
I should let him wear this jacket.
My gosh. It's attached.
I'll make you a star.
Se Chan said...
As you said
"I'll make you a start today,"
he murmured, "How annoying."
Wait for me.
I'll make you a star today.
How are you going
to make him a star?
- Just wait and watch.
- What?
What was your name again?
How many times do you have to ask?
This is how I make him a star.
How could you...
- I'm doing this to make him famous.
- That's ridiculous.
- What's your name?
- It's Cheon Yeop.
- Chae Jong Hyeop.
- Cheon Yeop?
It never ends.
Cheon Yeop?
- He's blushing to his ears.
- It's already...
hanging over the viewers' heads.
The directors are being like this.
They all are doing this.
- You're the worst.
- Cheon Yeop?
- It's Jong Hyeop.
- Jong Hyeop?
There's something surprising
about Jong Hyeop.
- Did you study in South Africa?
- Seriously?
- The Republic of South Africa?
- Where? South Africa?
That's very interesting.
It's very unique.
The Republic of South Africa?
How long did you study there?
It wasn't for long.
I spent a year in Thailand
when I was in middle school.
Then I went
to the Republic of South Africa.
- He studied abroad.
- He's a global talent.
- He's a global star.
- He studied abroad.
- He must speak good English.
- Jong Hyeop.
- You must speak good English.
- Not really.
- No? Not at all?
- No.
He does speak good English.
I bet he's good.
U.M.B.R.E.L.L.A.
(She suddenly spells umbrella.)
Umbrella!
Umbrella.
- You memorized it.
- Well done.
That was good.
- I'm hot.
- So Min is...
I'm doing two shows with So Min now.
My heart sinks
whenever she starts talking.
- It's all right.
- This is what Ji Hyo always does.
Monday, Tuesday...
Wednesday? Thursday?
Ji Hyo tries hard.
That's the wallpaper on her phone.
She studies hard.
That's funny.
So did you do something...
to become an actor?
(He tries to continue
with the talk.)
Well... I did.
Tell us more about it!
- That's too short.
- We are curious.
- We don't want a short answer.
- Make it longer.
Give a long answer.
- Go ahead and talk!
- "You know what?"
- Make things up.
- "When I was young..."
Say that you met Tom Cruise
in South Africa.
Jong Hyeop is talking.
I started working as a model
in South Africa.
- A model?
- A model in South Africa.
- Did you?
- Show us your walking.
A model in South Africa?
How did you manage to
become a model there?
- So Min's eyes are shining.
- A model in South Africa?
(She tosses her hair
when she hears the word "model".)
But things didn't go well.
So I wanted
to give it a try in Korea.
- So you came.
- That's why I came to Korea.
- Show us how you cry.
- That's so cool.
Walking.
Show us how you wail.
"What's wrong with me?"
(Show us how you wail.
"What's wrong with me?")
(The wailing king is proud.)
- "What's wrong with me?"
- That's not what he does.
You're not supposed
to say it like that.
"What's wrong with me?"
("What's wrong with me?")
He's really good.
That was perfect.
He's been making the worst clips...
in many TV shows these days.
He's weeping a lot.
Today, we have four special guests.
The crew members will...
grant your wishes during the race
on behalf of the witch.
- You will?
- Really?
First, I'd like you
to write down one wish each.
But it has to be something
that the crew members can grant.
So the Wish Committee
will review your wishes,
and we will grant the ones
that are approved.
Please bring in the table.
Okay.
(What would they write down
for their wishes?)
(They start
writing down their wishes.)
- This is...
- Those who are done...
can hand in your wishes right away.
(What are their wishes?)
Everyone, we've got
your earnest wishes.
Can I change my wish?
- During the race.
- No, you can't.
- I can never change my wish?
- No.
My wish is too small.
All right.
You always have a small wish.
Now I'd like each one of you
to read your own wish.
I want Seok Sam to be
my younger brother for a day.
- One day is too long.
- That's easy.
I think...
he's already treating
Suk Jin like his younger brother.
- It doesn't have to be his wish.
- That's not true.
It's official.
He should treat me
like his older brother officially.
Like his older brother.
- Even when the cameras are off.
- He should be polite to me.
- This is too small.
- Tell us about yours, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- I was being too nice.
- Why?
- I want all the crew members...
to cheer for me when I get off work.
What a boring wish.
- What's funny then?
- Suk Jin.
What do you think is funny?
You should've come up
with something unique.
Calm down.
What's your wish, Jong Kook?
I want Kwang Soo...
- to join our show as a guest.
- That's similar to mine.
- Really?
- I like that.
- What about you, Haha?
- I want...
Kwang Soo to be
a crew member here for a day.
He could be a writer, or
he could learn how to fly a drone.
But he can't be on TV.
He can't be on TV.
So Kwang Soo will never be
able to get away from us?
- He should be here every week.
- We call him every week.
- He might come here every week.
- Right.
- Next up is Ji Hyo.
- You guys are so clingy.
I want the staff members
to tell me...
the answers to the quizzes
for one day.
Yes. I want the same thing as her.
I want the staff members
to only tell me the answers...
for English
or Chinese character quizzes...
and make it look like I knew
the answers.
But you already revealed your plan.
- I mean... You're right.
- You shouldn't have revealed it.
I see that those who are always
at the bottom want such things.
- Exactly.
- I want it.
- Next up is Se Chan.
- This is what I actually wish for.
I want Haha to buy me...
- the latest model tablet PC.
- Why should I?
- Why Haha?
- I want the latest model.
- Why me?
- I really want to have one.
- Why?
- My wish lately is...
- to use a tablet PC...
- Don't build a fake relationship.
That's not my intention.
I'm serious.
- You want what?
- A tablet PC.
You could've asked the staff for it.
No, I want Haha to buy it for me.
- That would be meaningful.
- It would be meaningful.
Haha, can you do it?
Well... I guess I could.
I mean if he wins the race.
- Next up is Ji Hyun.
- I heard he bought a nice gift...
I want the cast members of this show
to watch the first episode...
of our drama and post about it
on social media.
Thank you in advance.
- Thank you in advance, everyone.
- Jae Suk doesn't use social media.
- I'll post about it on Suk Jin's.
- You don't have to do it...
- if you don't have accounts.
- Of course we'll do that.
- Absolutely.
- He can upload a photo of us.
- We'll have a photo taken together.
- You can do this too, right?
- Next up is Do Kwon.
- Of course we can do it.
That's nice.
Okay. I want to give Jong Kook
a personal training session...
and have him upload it
to his YouTube channel.
- That sounds fun.
- Hey, you wrote it in a rude way.
Has he lost his mind?
I followed the format we were given.
You could've used honorifics.
That would've made the sentence
sound unnatural.
Not if you use a proper preposition.
That's why one of them is
in parentheses.
- You use one or the other.
- Just let it go.
- You should write it down for him.
- Just let it go already.
- Gosh. Why that little...
- Yong Gu.
- I like your small revenge.
- That was nice.
- You won, Do Kwon.
- It was small revenge.
- Do Kwon won.
- He went to SNU for a reason.
- That's hilarious.
- Jong Kook, do you accept?
I should be trained by him?
- Oh, gosh.
- Just give it a try.
This is driving me nuts.
I accept it for now.
- Jong Hyeop, it's your turn.
- Okay.
Actually, I'm a big fan of Haha's.
So I want him to buy me
a high-performance speaker.
Nice.
(Jong Hyeop, "I want Haha to buy me
a high-performance speaker.")
- Me?
- Haha?
- Let's make our wishes come true.
- Okay.
(Many people make a wish to CEO Ha.)
- Did he mean me?
- Let's make him spend money.
- You... Who are you?
- Chae Jong Hyeop.
- Do you know me? Why me?
- This is nice.
- Why me? What's the reason?
- Haha.
- Just do it for him.
- Well...
He says he's your fan.
- I'm grateful for that, but...
- It's because he likes you.
- Just do it for him.
- Gosh, seriously.
This is driving me crazy.
- Haha, do it for him.
- Okay. I'll do it.
- Do it for him.
- How much is it worth?
- He wants a high-performance one.
- How much is it?
- Just buy one for him.
- It probably costs 1,000 dollars.
At least 500 dollars.
- Why would he pick me?
- It should cost that much.
- We've gathered your wishes.
- Can't I change mine?
- Can't I change my wish?
- Just this once.
- To what?
I was going to ask Suk Jin
to buy me a T model.
- What's a T model?
- A T model?
It's a new SUV from K brand.
Gosh.
- It's like an ad.
- Why should I buy it for you?
- Why?
- Suk Jin, you can do it, right?
- Pardon?
- You can do it, right?
- Change your wish too.
- Me?
Fine. Then I'll accept that
and change my wish too.
- I'll do the same.
- Me too.
- I want an apartment in Banpo-dong.
- Hey, write it down.
- I want a T model.
- Write it down.
I want a 195㎡ apartment.
Jong Hyeop, is that okay with you?
I want to change mine too.
It's a realistic wish.
I want Dong Hoon to work
at my grandma's house.
She has a vegetable garden
and needs to move sacks of soil.
Dong Hoon, can you help us
with that work?
- I can't believe this.
- Please?
Why would you pick me as well?
All of your ardent wishes
have been received.
And we'll think that the people
who are involved have agreed.
However, it's only reasonable
that if you want something,
you must pay the price for it.
So today...
Some of us don't know
what "reasonable" means.
- I know what that means.
- Tell her the answer.
That's not necessary. I know.
We prepared a Wish Box
and a Payment Box.
After all the missions end,
we'll pick two from the Wish Box,
and the wishes of those two
will come true.
- You'll pick 2, not just 1?
- Yes.
But the price for their wishes
will be paid by two people...
picked from the Payment Box
through a harsh penalty.
- It's on behalf of the winners.
- Oh, I see.
It's interesting.
It's like the plot of the drama.
In the two boxes,
each of you has one ball
with your name on them.
You'll get into two teams
to play a game,
and the winning team gets to add
a ball for each of the members.
(The losing team members' names
are added to the Payment Box.)
Obviously, the losing team members'
names are added to the Payment Box.
Then how many penalties
will Haha get?
(Only when their team wins
will their wishes come true.)
But...
There's a way to avoid adding
your name when your team loses.
At the end of each game,
we'll make penalty juice...
that's bitter in your mouth
but very good for your health.
- I hate that.
- I can't drink it.
The five members will share it,
and if they finish it,
their names won't be added
to the Payment Box.
- Really?
- It's really bitter.
And we selected Ji Hyo and Ji Hyun
as team leaders...
and divided you into two teams
to maintain the balance.
The members of Team Song Ji Hyo
are Haha,
Se Chan, So Min, and Do Kwon.
(Team Song Ji Hyo,
Haha, Se Chan, So Min, Do Kwon)
Yong Gu!
- Yong Gu.
- Great.
- We have younger members.
- Then we're on the same team.
The members
of Team Nam Ji Hyun are...
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
and Jong Hyeop.
- Okay!
- We can beat them.
I like this combination.
- I like it.
- It's nice.
- I'm glad Ji Hyun is our leader.
- It's great.
Oh, my gosh. I'm the team leader.
All right.
Please change your clothes.
- And we'll begin the first mission.
- Okay!
Nice!
(Which team will take the victory
with the best teamwork?)
There comes our financial supporter.
You're here, Do Kwon.
- Isn't Jong Hyeop on our team?
- Okay!
- No, he isn't.
- I see.
- Hey, So Min is disappointed.
- He's on our team.
Exactly. I thought
Jong Hyeop was on our team.
(Love Frog activated her radar.)
So Min is upset.
Are you interested in Jong Hyeop?
- Gosh, no. Why?
- You're waving your hand...
It's so funny that I mentioned
his name more than ten times,
but he never turned around
when he must've heard me.
- Who? Why?
- I don't have good hearing.
That's how Se Chan would look
if he became much more handsome.
Nonsense.
I mean if he gets
all kinds of plastic surgery.
(It sounds a little bit absurd,
but they do look a bit similar.)
- I would look like him?
- Yes.
- Don't compare him to Se Chan.
- Exactly.
- What's your problem?
- Se Chan looks a little like him.
They have
completely different vibes.
- If you hit Se Chan's face...
- Hey, stop it.
- Stop hitting me.
- And scrape it like this.
And reshape it.
By the way, Ji Hyo...
Are you one of our members
or are you a guest today?
- She's our guest today.
- She's our guest.
- Address her politely as a guest.
- As our guest...
Ji Hyo, you should show
your upper teeth like Ji Hyun does.
That's good. Keep it up.
(She's equipped with a smile
like a guest.)
That's great.
- Show less of your upper lip.
- Show your upper teeth. Good.
- She looks so cute.
- Bite your teeth.
The first mission where you must get
the large wish ball...
to add your name to Wish Box is...
The One Who Gets the Wish Ball.
- You'll have 1-on-1 matches.
- Oh, I see.
The rules are simple.
Both players hold a gym ball
as they begin the match.
The one who takes the gym ball
from the other wins.
(The player who takes the gym ball
from the other wins.)
I guess it requires
physical strength.
- Isn't it too simple?
- Strong ones have an advantage.
The names of the winners
of each round...
and the names of all members
of the team with more winners...
will be added to the Wish Box.
- Then...
- We made the matchup list.
The first round is
Haha versus Suk Jin.
Why?
- He's really strong.
- It'll be easy.
- I won't go easy on you.
- He's been working out at home.
I've been working out at home.
He does 20 push-ups in 1 week.
In one week?
Isn't that too few?
He does 20 push-ups in 1 week?
How many push-ups does he do
in one day?
- He does 20 push-ups in 1 week?
- It's not too few.
- Not 20 push-ups in 1 day?
That means he does 2 or 3 push-ups
per day.
- Exactly.
- Hey, he's still young and healthy.
- Always be healthy.
- I'm surprised that he can do that.
I wish you health and blessings.
The second round is
Ji Hyo versus Ji Hyun.
(Round 2, Ji Hyo versus Ji Hyun)
The third round is
Se Chan versus Jae Suk.
The fourth round is
So Min versus Jong Hyeop.
(Me and Jong Hyeop?)
The fifth round is
Do Kwon versus Jong Kook.
- Look how happy So Min is.
- So Min seems excited.
- It's not like that.
- Look at her.
- She's smiling happily.
- It's not like that.
I don't like it. No.
We'll change players.
But Jong Hyeop and So Min...
- Your team has one more man.
- Is it fair?
Then I'll play against So Min
instead of him.
- No. Why?
- Don't be like that.
- We don't want to see her happy.
- I'll do it.
- Why?
- Or let Suk Jin do it.
- I'll do it.
- It annoys me.
I hate it
when So Min acts like this.
- I mean...
- No. It's unacceptable.
- We'll decide. I'll do it.
- Absolutely no.
You do it no matter what.
This is not acceptable.
- Why not?
- I don't like it.
Hey, it's tough love.
- Guys...
- We won't let that happen.
Jong Hyeop, what do you say?
- Absolutely no. Don't even ask him.
- Let's hear him out.
- Don't say anything.
- Who do you want to play against?
- I...
I wouldn't mind playing
against anyone.
- Then play against Se Chan.
- Play against Se Chan.
Then play against Se Chan.
(They stopped Love Frog
from the get-go.)
All right. Play against me, kid.
- I'll teach you a lesson.
- Great.
They look a little alike.
- Taste the power of South Africa.
- Exactly.
- I'll show him Dongducheon's power.
- Okay.
Then we'll change the players
to Se Chan versus Jong Hyeop...
- and So Min versus Jae Suk.
- Why?
Yes. Sounds great.
- That's neat.
- Look at Jae Suk's face.
The fifth round is
Do Kwon versus Jong Kook.
Nice!
I can't believe
Jong Kook and Jae Suk.
Don't even dream of it.
(Team Ji Hyo versus Team Ji Hyun)
The first round is
Haha versus Suk Jin.
Why is Do Kwon tying his shoelaces?
(The only person
who is too serious to laugh)
- Do Kwon is serious about this.
- He's tying his shoelaces.
- He looks weird.
- Why...
Do Kwon is determined to win today.
I hate it when people like him
come on the show. I hate it so much.
- He said he got sick of it.
- I meant it.
I'm worried. He's really strong.
(Suk Jin versus Haha)
He might lose.
I think it'll end quickly.
Ready.
Suk Jin has been working out
at home.
Get set.
(The game begins.)
He's so strong.
What an amazing speed.
(The match between a strong old man
and a fast kid)
It won't be easy.
- You shouldn't move that way.
- Exactly.
- That was good.
- It's a ground fight.
That's good.
(The little wrestler succeeds
in getting him on the ground.)
Just keep pressing him down, Haha.
- That's good.
- Hey, Haha.
Okay.
Suk Jin is in his 50s.
(Laughing)
That's so funny.
(The elder is being toyed with
by the fast kid.)
Haha, Suk Jin is in his 50s.
(The dirty fight
between a kid and an old man)
This is no joke.
I bet our ratings just hit the roof.
Good. You should do things like that
to win.
Roll it. That's it!
(The kid wins in the end.)
(He had to fight with all his might
to defeat the man in his 50s.)
- Okay!
- Great job!
Hey.
I guess nothing can beat youth.
(The kid in his 40s is
still full of energy and vigor.)
- Haha is quite...
- I went easy on him. That's why.
Haha won the first round.
Haha's name will be added
to the Wish Box.
Now, the next round is...
Ji Hyo versus Ji Hyun.
- Okay!
- Oh, my.
They finally meet.
This is a big event.
Teach her a lesson
with your strength.
Ji Hyo, show us what you can do.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyun, Ji Hyo is strong.
- Oh, no.
- She's practically a man.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm in trouble.
Ji Hyun, you can't beat her.
- Oh, no.
- She's incredibly strong.
- What should I do?
- Good luck.
- Ready.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- It's obvious.
- Ji Hyun, do your best.
- Get set, go.
- Ji Hyo, please.
- Go, Witch Song!
- You can do it, witch!
- Ji Hyo, don't go easy on her.
- Look how relaxed Ji Hyo is.
- Ji Hyo, finish it now.
- Ji Hyun, just pull it away.
- Pull it away now.
- Pull it! That's good.
- Ji Hyo, she might take it away.
- Just pull it away. Pull it.
(Ji Hyun caught Ji Hyo off guard.)
- Ji Hyo, she might take it away.
- Pull it! That's good.
(Song Jeoktoma got startled
by her unexpected strength.)
Seeing how she's playing,
Ji Hyun is not easy to defeat.
She is so strong.
She's not easy to defeat.
(Chuckling)
Look how she's chuckling
while pulling the ball.
- This is so funny.
- Actually,
I guess Ji Hyun is the type who acts
cheeky while playing games.
- True.
- She keeps smiling and laughing.
- That's true.
- Ji Hyo, it's time to finish it.
- Ji Hyo, finish it now.
- It's time.
Jong Kook, can you fix my hair?
- Sure. I'll fix your hair.
- Gosh. I'm exhausted.
(Sure. I'll fix your hair.)
She asked me to do it.
That'll become a boyfriend meme.
But he's on my team.
I'm sure the clip will be
all over the Internet.
- She asked me to do it.
- What's going on?
- She asked me to fix her hair.
- What was that? She's on that team.
- Gosh, seriously.
I said, she asked me a favor!
Should I have ignored it?
Let it go. Don't do it.
Don't say a word.
- Okay.
- Eun Hye, I'm sorry.
(Eun Hye, I'm sorry.)
(He mentioned her again as always.)
- I told you not to talk about her.
- Fine.
(This man has been teasing Jong Kook
by talking about her.)
"Eun Hye, I'm sorry."
Ji Hyun seems quite strong too.
Their endurance will decide
the winner after some time...
(So Min came to straighten
Ji Hyo's clothes.)
Let's see. She's lying on her belly.
That's good.
Okay. That's good.
(She's hitting Ji Hyun afterward.)
(She cheats
before anyone could stop her.)
- Hey, stop it!
- Hey!
What? She just helped Ji Hyo.
- Nice.
- Good job.
- Nice!
- Okay. Great job.
- Good job.
- Wasn't that foul play?
- All right. That was great.
- Let's go!
(They don't care if it was cheating.
They're celebrating the victory.)
You're so cool!
- Good job.
- Good job. That felt so good.
- That felt really good.
- Good job. You did well.
- It's okay. It must've been tough.
- She's so strong.
I won't go easy on her.
I don't care that she's a girl.
So Min versus Jae Suk.
(Round 3, So Min versus Jae Suk)
- It's okay.
- We need to win this round.
Jae Suk, just...
- I'll teach her a lesson.
- Yes, do that.
I really don't want to play
against him.
So she can't think of anything else.
- Jong Hyeop...
- Teach her a lesson.
(Her eyes are fixed on him.)
Why are you looking at Jong Hyeop?
- It's not like that.
- She's looking at him.
I'm allowed to look at Jong Hyeop
while playing against him, right?
Yes, that's okay.
- She'll get motivated by doing so.
- Do as you want.
I'll finish it as soon as it begins.
Look at him or not.
Do whatever you want.
- Ready.
- I'll finish it right away.
- What?
- It didn't go as he planned.
- What's wrong?
- Jae Suk is taken aback.
- It must not be easy.
- Look at her.
My gosh. He can't seem to finish it.
What's wrong with you?
- She's looking at Jong Hyeop.
- Hey!
- I'm impressed.
- My goodness. I can't believe...
- Her eyes are fixed on him.
Look at that.
- The power of love!
- Love!
- She won't look anywhere else.
- I can see...
the determination in her eyes.
Gosh. She's strong.
- Hide behind me.
- Gosh.
(He hid behind Suk Jin
as her affection is too much.)
- It's not easy.
- You should twist it.
- Jong Hyeop, make a finger heart.
- No. Our team might lose.
I won't lose.
That's great. Good.
- That's good!
- Come on.
(The frog provokes him.)
- Pull it away.
- That's good.
(She's pulling his hair.)
- Keep it up!
- You're doing great!
Try everything you can!
- Come on. You shouldn't lose.
- Hey.
It seems that So Min is trying
to get her revenge.
(Because he stopped her
from playing against Jong Hyeop,)
(So Min starts to take revenge.)
- Keep it up!
- Hey.
Hey, you shouldn't lose.
- You should not lose.
- He's going to butt heads with her.
- My, it's not easy at all.
- Normally...
- Come on!
- Oh, no. Gosh.
- Okay!
- I ran out of energy.
- You did well.
- Look at him getting all excited.
- I ran out of energy.
Good job. That was great.
- He seems so excited.
- Okay!
- He looks so happy.
- Good job!
Oh, my. What a tough guy.
He's a real man.
He's excited about defeating So Min.
- By the way...
- That was cool. You beat So Min.
- Good job.
- I mean...
(He's celebrating as if he won
a gold medal in the Olympics.)
He looks exhilarated.
- He got too excited.
- Good job!
Next up are Se Chan and Jong Hyeop.
- South Africa!
- Get out here, South Africa!
- He has a muscular body.
- I think...
- he's been working out.
- He has a muscular body.
- He has hard muscles.
- Indeed. He has a muscular body.
But we can't be sure.
Se Chan has a body like a farmer's.
- Unexpectedly...
- He has the body of a servant.
- He has a strong lower body.
Se Chan has the body of a servant.
Hey, you...
- He lost some weight.
- Jong Hyeop.
- Jong Hyeop, good luck.
- He has such broad shoulders too.
- Indeed. He looks strong.
- He has such broad shoulders.
- Exactly. He has a strong body.
- Se Chan, you can do this.
They both have
unexpectedly strong bodies.
- Good. Keep going.
- Hold on. I'm not ready.
- Se Chan, don't get intimidated.
- You can do this.
- You have to win this, Jong Hyeop.
- You can do this!
(It's so tense already.
Who will win?)
You can do it!
- Ready.
- You can do it!
Hey.
(The game begins.)
Jong Hyeop, he's sly.
Watch out for him.
Oh, really?
(Pinching)
(Jong Hyeop starts attacking
fiercely right away.)
- Pull it away!
- Oh, gosh.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- That's good!
Se Chan, you can win this.
Good. Keep going!
- Hey, Jong Hyeop.
- Hey!
Jong Hyeop!
- Jong Hyeop!
- That's good.
- Good. That's great.
- Jong Hyeop.
Good. You're doing great!
You're a pro!
- Jong Hyeop, hit him back.
- No.
(But then, Jong Hyeop got Se Chan
on the ground.)
- Jong Hyeop, hit him back.
- No.
Oh, my. This is like a UFC match.
- Oh, gosh.
(He lifted Se Chan up!)
(Se Chan is desperately holding
on to the gym ball.)
No!
All right! Take it away from him!
(The servant power is increasing.)
- That's so cool.
- Keep going!
- Lift him up just like he did.
- No.
- Keep it up! You can do it!
- Hey.
Se Chan, you're so cool.
Se Chan, you're way uglier than him.
Just think of that.
Hey, Jong Hyeop.
- Hey, Jong Hyeop.
- Go, Se Chan!
Hey, you won't become a star
if you lose!
Gosh, he's so strong.
Se Chan, you can do this.
You've got this.
Hold on to it!
Okay!
(Jong Hyeop pulled it off.)
Hold on to it!
(South Africa won.)
- That was amazing.
- You're so cool.
- How cool. Take a close-up shot.
- Hey, Se Chan...
Take a close-up shot of him.
Go on and strike a pose.
- Which camera should I look at?
- Okay!
- He's so strong.
- Se Chan...
- didn't look cool at all.
- How much do you weigh?
Jong Hyeop is really strong.
- His body looks strong.
- He's so cool.
- Above all...
- He is incredibly strong.
- He has a good body frame.
- Jong Kook...
(Jong Hyeop's hidden strength
surprised everyone.)
Jong Kook, here.
Work out your lower body.
- Okay!
- Here. Use this.
- All right! You've got this!
- You've got this! Go for it!
- Okay!
- Don't worry. You can win this.
- You've got this.
- This is our last chance.
- Do Kwon, you can do it.
- Strength is not everything.
- You're absolutely right.
Come on!
- He just lifts up chunks of metal.
- Exactly.
Do Kwon, you should beat him
no matter what.
You're ready to create
a legendary meme.
Let's create a meme of
Jong Kook being humiliated.
- Aim at his left knee.
- Okay!
(Jong Kook Hunter
failed three times.)
Crush him!
(But he came back for his 4th try.)
He's here to bring Jong Kook down.
I have a feeling that the universe
is on my side today.
That's right. Today, he will fall.
You will see the end of the YouTuber
with 1.4 million subscribers.
I can tell how serious Do Kwon is
from the look in his eyes.
- All right. You've got this.
- Okay.
- Hold it.
- Go, Jong Kook! You've got this!
I think it'll end quickly.
- Ready.
- He looks so weak suddenly.
- Good! Ground fighting is good.
- That happened so quickly.
- Suddenly...
- Good!
(As soon as the match began,
Do Kwon got on the ground.)
(He wraps his legs
around Jong Kook's waist.)
That's good. Keep going.
- Oh, my. That's impressive.
- Do Kwon, you're doing great.
(He's holding Jong Kook tightly
to hunt him.)
- Jong Kook will be humiliated.
- His face looks so red.
I'll show people the end
of the YouTuber with 1.4 million...
No, don't!
(Do Kwon's mortifying moment)
Nice one!
(Do Kwon fights back.)
- What was that?
- That was great.
Did you see that?
Isn't it like watching UFC?
- Yes, UFC.
- Gosh.
Oh, no.
(The UFC-like intense game
drained both of their energy.)
Do Kwon is tired now.
It's over for Do Kwon.
He used up all his strength.
Do Kwon!
- Yong Gu.
- Yong Gu. Oh, dear.
You're only producing
humiliating scenes.
He's scratching Jong Kook's hand
with his stubble.
Can't you let me win this one time?
It's already my fourth attempt.
Do Kwon, you look like
such a coward right now.
Can't you at least look charismatic?
- Where's the camera?
- Good job.
Look charismatic.
Do Kwon,
it's time to go back to reality.
- Do Kwon...
- Just think that you're...
(But then)
That's the spirit!
- Nice one.
- It's his last bit of energy.
Do Kwon, push him away.
(Do Kwon squeezes out
the energy he has left.)
(Jong Kook stands strong though.)
Do Kwon, push him away.
(He pushes with all his might...)
(and wins!)
Did you push him with your feet?
Let him have the win.
- What just happened?
- Do Kwon!
No way.
- He pushed with his feet.
- Yes, his feet.
- Nicely done.
- He used his feet.
- Hold on.
- It's like he lost though.
Why does it feel like you lost?
It's obvious that
Jong Kook let you win.
(He feels iffy
despite getting payback.)
Win a lot against me today
and stop coming on the show.
And so Team Ji Hyo wins.
Okay!
Nicely done.
The members of Team Ji Hyo...
got to add their names
in the Wish Box.
- It's okay though.
- It's okay.
- Good job, guys.
Ji Hyun can't hide...
her disappointed expression.
It'll be all right.
- I'm fine.
- We let them have that one.
- We'll...
- Just wait until the next round.
(Here's a gift for Ji Hyun
who's clearly disappointed.)
(Just like
how your wish is granted...)
(when you eat at the Witch's Diner)
Here's the first juice.
(To have your wish granted,
you must drink the green juice.)
It will protect your stomach
and skin with antioxidants...
and also lower
your cholesterol levels.
It's cabbage and onion juice.
(The first juice has
cabbage and onions.)
(Nothing else was added
than the vegetables themselves.)
But...
I mean...
It's full of antioxidants...
and will lower
your cholesterol levels.
It smells like kimchi sauce.
(The scent of onions
stings their nostrils too.)
- Hold on.
- This is too much.
It'd be better not to eat things
that elevate your cholesterol level.
Must we drink all of it?
- All of it?
- Then our names won't be added?
The ones that are already in there
will stay there.
Let's do it.
Then...
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Only Jae Suk wins.)
Jae Suk's pleased with himself.
Jae Suk gets to go first!
Let's go ahead with it.
- Let's do it.
- I feel bad about this.
As long as
I don't have to drink it last.
Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Scissors.
- Okay.
- Okay, we're good.
(He has to finish whatever's left.)
- It'll be a nice scene.
- That happened seamlessly.
(They let him take the last spot.)
Welcome to the world
of variety shows!
This looks like fun.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Scissors.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Step aside.
(They don't mind letting the guests
take the short straw.)
In order,
you'll drink as much as you want.
(The order: Jae Suk, Jong Kook,
Suk Jin, Ji Hyun, Jong Hyeop)
- I can drink as much as I want?
- That's right.
Since you're the first one
to drink it,
show an example.
Of course.
I'm ready to drink a lot.
Just send it down your throat.
Open up your throat.
This...
Are you sure this is drinkable?
(Are you sure this is drinkable?)
(A key question)
- Right.
- You know,
I'm curious about that too.
That's a question I have too.
They wouldn't try to kill us,
so just drink it.
Everything in it
is perfectly healthy.
What can be bad
about cabbage and onions?
Yes, exactly.
Why don't we clink our glasses
and drink together?
Okay.
- Let's say cheers.
- All right.
And then we'll...
- You know...
- Cheers.
(He samples the drink.)
What's wrong?
(Happy that his cholesterol level
is going down)
How is it?
- Is it all right?
- I...
I'm sorry to say this,
but I can't drink it.
- Wait.
- We must do this.
- Just do it.
- Jong Hyeop...
Jong Hyeop has to drink
whatever is left.
- Him and Ji Hyun.
- I can't possibly drink this.
Leave them with a reasonable amount.
- Cheers.
- I'll consider this champagne.
- Just drink it.
Let me make a toast.
Say, YIN.
YIN.
- Youth is now.
Cheers!
They're drinking it.
Keep going, guys.
- Check out Jae Suk.
- How admirable.
(He drinks it to save their names
from going in the Payment Box.)
- Look at him.
- You can drink more.
Please put it down
when you've had enough.
Keep going. I know you can.
Jae Suk is drinking it all.
Suk Jin, you weak man.
Suk Jin,
it's drinkable.
It's perfectly drinkable.
It's a group effort,
so the others can finish it off.
Suk Jin, you can quit then.
The next one should drink.
- You can quit.
- Go ahead and quit.
- I'll drink the rest.
- This is crazy.
I have a weak stomach, you know.
Think of it as a protein shake.
Look at Jong Kook.
- It's like he's drinking a shake.
- How admirable.
- That...
- All but one is willing to drink.
(He's embarrassed.)
He finished it.
Open your throat wide.
- That's super cool.
- Nice!
- He added water and drank it all.
- He's a true man.
It'll look weird
if they don't drink this.
They have no choice but to drink it.
(On eggshells)
It'll seem like I'm a coward
if they drink it all.
Exactly. Nicely done.
- She drank it all.
- Nice.
She finished her drink.
- Unbelievable.
- Nice!
Have a little taste.
It's not as bad as you think.
Don't push yourself too hard,
but drink it if it's okay.
- Go, Jong Hyeop.
- Nice!
(Jong Hyeop pours the drink down.)
Just keep drinking.
Suk Jin's feeling embarrassed now.
I'll drink the rest.
No, save it.
Step aside.
Move. Let me drink that for you.
Why are you stopping him?
This isn't how it's supposed to be.
It's making me look weird.
- Okay!
- Nicely done.
Nice!
(They polish off the penalty juice.)
- It's drinkable.
- What did I tell you?
The drink was shared
among the four members.
Unbelievable.
Only the four of them?
I drank some of it too, you know.
The four members
played their part...
which resulted in your names
not being added to the box.
You'll now move on to the next game.
- Nice!
- No way!
- Gosh.
- Jong Hyeop,
you were on the fence, weren't you?
I bet it was hard to drink.
(They're onto the second game.)
It must be a quiz.
You're here for your second game.
You must be quick-witted...
to be able to add your name
to the Wish Box.
This is Speak With Your Actions:
Quartet Edition.
It's the Speak With
Your Actions game.
Each team will take turns...
to describe a word
with their actions.
One member will try to guess
what the other four are describing.
- Only one has to guess?
- The four...
must describe the word...
as a quartet.
- As a quartet?
- In one group?
However,
two members
from the opposing team...
will sit facing the other way...
and try to guess the word
by using a mirror.
(The opposing team
will use a mirror to guess.)
Using the reflection in the mirror.
The mirror isn't that big.
I know.
(It'll be a race against
2 members of the opposing team.)
A cuckoo clock.
Which team will go first?
- Go ahead.
- Losers should go first.
You should go first.
- But you lost.
- That's not a crime.
Then you should've won.
Do Kwon, speak up for us.
(He uses the moment
to provoke Jong Kook.)
- Then you should've won.
- Exactly.
You should've won then.
- You should've won then.
- I see.
- Then you can speak up.
But we're back to square one now.
- That's not how it goes.
- We should start over.
Those minions.
- You guys...
- Did you see their expressions?
You guys stay behind.
- How about another game then?
- Suk Jin.
We'll grab a bite to eat.
- They could easily take you on.
- We'll grab a bite to eat.
He wants us to stay for a meal.
- I'll be the guesser.
- Me too.
Go inside.
Jong Hyeop, you be the guesser.
- Nice.
- All right.
- Pull it closest to you.
- Are you sure you can do this?
- You can do this.
- Let's go!
- Come on.
- I'll try and guess the answer.
- Sure thing.
- Know what to focus on.
Let's guess at least ten of them.
- I think I'll be bad at this.
- It'll be all right.
I'm slow at guessing things.
- Really?
- Yes.
This is bad.
It'll be hilarious though.
I think this will be fun.
(Jong Hyeop says
he can be quite slow.)
This is bad.
Why don't I be the guesser instead?
- I'll do it.
- Sure thing.
(The two offer to change seats,
not realizing So Min's excitement.)
- I lack wit.
- Sure thing.
But Jong Hyeop is adorable.
Jong Hyeop...
- Jong Hyeop...
- Why though?
Jong Hyeop wanted to be the guesser.
He wanted a chance at it.
I'll be sticking close
to So Min today.
But Jong Hyeop
was seated here just now.
I'll be by Jong Hyeop's side today.
A 1-on-1 defense.
Sure thing.
- Jae Suk, do your best.
- Are you ready?
This will be easy.
- Okay, let's go.
- Here we go.
Ji Hyun should be in the front.
- Right.
- We can't get in her way.
It's best
if she stands in front of us.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Guys, be witty about this.
(The word?)
Ji Hyun, sit there...
and just do this.
Just do this.
(The first question)
Like this.
The sun.
(Is Ji Hyun supposed to be the sun?)
Is it hot? Is it sunscreen?
(Chopping)
- Something's being cut.
- Sliced. Hairtail.
Mackerel.
It's something we eat.
- Korean cuisine.
- Squid.
It's something edible. Sushi?
(It must be something
you cut up to eat.)
- Small octopus.
- Octopus.
(Small octopus?)
(Keep going.)
Raw fish?
Sushi?
What kind of octopus?
Long-legged octopus!
- Long-legged octopus!
- What are you doing?
(Suk Jin tried to cheat
but Se Chan caught on first.)
Long-legged octopus!
(They were doing well, but he went
ahead and gave a hint.)
(Thanks to Jong Hyeop,
Team Ji Hyo earns a point.)
They're practically giving us
the answer.
- What kind of octopus was it?
- Long-legged octopus.
Oh, long-legged octopus?
(Team Ji Hyun lost their chance
to get the answer.)
(Here's the next question.)
You're the smoke.
Bird, nest, swallow.
(Is Jong Kook imitating a bird?)
- Seahorse.
- Sparrow.
- Ji Hyun, you should...
- Fly.
Blowfish, eagle.
Jellyfish!
Jong Kook... Mosquito!
No, it's not.
- Something sharp.
- Fly?
Seaweed.
We're rolled up here.
Keep quiet!
- Sea anemone?
- You're rolled up?
What on earth is that?
They're imitating it very well!
Hummingbird!
Venus flytrap?
Bee!
Why is he pointing at himself?
Mosquito... Mosquito net!
- Mosquito!
- Hummingbird!
It's related to a mosquito net.
What's it called?
- Bird!
- It's related to a mosquito net.
Mosquito repellent incense!
(Mosquito repellent incense)
(The answer is
mosquito repellent incense.)
It's mosquito repellent incense.
How does that
look like a bee to you?
(The actor who acted mosquito
loses his temper.)
- I got it.
- We got two. Let's do this, So Min!
Se Chan, we can do this!
We can get them all.
Don't let Jae Suk get any of it.
Gosh, Jae Suk.
- What do we do?
Why did he volunteer to answer?
(Embarrassed)
Wait. I'll get the answer this time.
I will...
I'll get the answer this time.
- Think simply.
- I'll get the answer this time.
I should get ready.
You can start.
- "The Little Mermaid"!
("The Little Mermaid")
Who got the answer?
(They did.)
That was great, Se Chan.
- What is he doing?
- Let's do this!
I can see everyone!
Okay.
What is he doing?
- Get on my back.
- They're flustered.
Okay.
We need to see it
from their perspective.
Motorcycle!
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
(Motorcycle)
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
Motorcycle!
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
Okay!
Why wouldn't you answer?
He can't even open his mouth.
(He can't even open his mouth.)
(This is already the last question
for Jae Suk who's facing a crisis.)
I'll shoot it.
1, 2, 3.
- Curtain.
- Firecracker!
A gun salute!
- Bang!
- Firecracker!
Firecracker!
- A gun salute! Fireworks!
- Fireworks!
All right.
- Firecracker! Fireworks!
- A gun salute!
- Fireworks!
- Fireworks! All right, we got it.
(He copies So Min's answer
a little too late.)
- I got it.
- Come on.
Time is up.
You did really well.
He's so bad at it.
(Team Ji Hyo: 5, Team Ji Hyun: 1)
You missed all the questions.
Come back in
when they play Round Two.
So Min should do it.
So Min is good at this.
- So Min is good at it.
- You should do it, So Min.
Should I sit down?
- All right.
- It was too difficult.
- Last round.
- Ji Hyun, you should answer.
- Can I do it? I want to answer.
- Should the two of us do it?
Should the two of us do it?
Jong Kook, Ji Hyun, please do well.
Jong Kook is good at this though.
Look at Jong Kook.
He's incredible.
- You're incredible.
You look really scary from there.
They can see your eye
from the mirror.
I love it when you're on my team,
but when you're not...
- It's hard when he's our opponent.
- Right.
Get ready.
Let's do it.
(After setting his eye,
Round 2 starts.)
- Let's do the highlighted part.
- I'm so nervous.
(Given word)
- Let's do this.
- Get on my back.
Come behind me.
Behind me.
Horseback riding.
(Horseback riding)
- Slide!
- All right!
- I almost got it.
Slide!
(Thanks to his snake-like eye,
he quickly gets the answer.)
(Jong Kook was faster than So Min,
so he wins a point.)
This is really hard.
Crane!
- Look at Do Kwon's face.
- Claw machine!
Brachiosaurus?
Look at Do Kwon's face.
(Claw machine)
(No, that's not it!)
Snake!
Oh, it's giraffe!
All right!
(Disappointed)
- All right.
- How is that a giraffe?
- It looks like...
- That was great!
Our team is doing so well.
- Giraffe?
- Only one should be standing.
Only one person should be standing.
Now, turn.
What could it be?
(Given word)
- Propeller! Helicopter!
- A ride!
- Who got the answer?
- Jong Kook is getting them all.
- Jong Kook is really good at this.
- He's too good.
- Propeller! Helicopter!
- A ride!
(He gets the answer
with the snake-like eye.)
You look like a venomous snake.
He's incredible. He really is.
Jong Kook is really good at this.
What do we do?
You can start.
- I'll get down.
- A sled.
- We need a sled.
- He's really good.
- A sled.
(They quickly assemble a sled.)
Carriage.
(He must be the Rudolph.)
What is that?
Santa Claus!
- Santa Claus.
- Santa Claus?
Hercules.
- Santa Claus.
- Santa Claus?
- Rudolph.
- Hercules?
(Rudolph)
- Rudolph?
- It's Rudolph!
(Ji Hyun got the answer.)
- Rudolph?
- Good job, Ji Hyun!
That's good!
Ji Hyun is good.
So Min, you didn't get any correct.
She's unbelievable.
So Min! What are you doing?
- Why are you so bad at this?
- This is driving you crazy, right?
Jong Kook is incredible.
(Given word: Diffuser)
Diffuser? Let's stand like this,
and Ji Hyo, put your hands up.
So Min is hilarious.
(Given word: Diffuser)
Wi-Fi!
Antenna!
Pine tree!
The Statue of Liberty?
Phytoncide?
What is she saying?
Diffu...
- What are you saying?
- Diffu...
- Air purifier.
(The faulty diffuser
keeps making a noise.)
- Diffu...
- Air purifier.
(Using their whole body
to tell So Min the answer)
- What is that?
- Diffu...
- What on earth are you saying?
Diffuser!
(Diffuser!)
What was that? A diffuser?
Diffuser!
So Min is hilarious.
It's okay. We can get the answers.
We can get the answers.
- We can get the answers.
- Let's get them.
Let's stand like this.
You should spew out water here.
(Given word: Fountain)
Fountain!
- What?
- That was fast.
Fountain!
(It ended before she could
spew out water.)
- The answer is "fountain".
- Your eye!
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- What are you doing, So Min?
(The snake-like eye
keeps stealing the answer.)
- He is...
- He's immersed in it.
- Jong Kook is incredible.
- Let's go!
Jong Kook is incredible.
Bird!
- Woodpecker!
- What is that?
(Woodpecker!)
Woodpecker!
(Annoyed)
Well done, Jong Kook!
You said
it's your first time playing.
You're not really good at this.
It's so funny.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyun
are really good at this.
- It's the last question.
- Let's show them!
(It's the last question
as they're running out of time.)
- I'll get on the floor.
- Get on the floor.
Get on top of us.
Act like you're eating us.
Get on top of me.
- Sandwich! What is that?
- Jenga.
Sandwich! What is that?
Jenga.
Hamburger!
- That guy...
- Seriously...
- Hey, So Min!
- Darn it!
(She got her answer stolen again.)
(Team Ji Hyo became a hamburger
for Team Ji Hyun's benefit.)
(Hey, So Min!)
For whom are we doing this?
(So Min became helpless
in front of the snake eye.)
- He's so good at this.
- It's over.
(End of the mission)
Hey, what was that, So Min?
I kept meeting Jong Kook's eye.
It was so scary when he looked
at us through the mirror.
I know. It was scary.
Is this how you look at it?
- It's like a side-view mirror.
- How?
All I could see was Jong Kook's eye.
I look at the side-view mirrors well
when I drive.
It was so funny.
Team Ji Hyun won the mission.
(Team Ji Hyun turns the table
and takes the win.)
What a relief.
Bring in the juice, please.
We lost?
- It's not a problem.
- That was incredible.
Let's drink it.
- This is... What is that?
- We're drinking it?
Jong Kook was too good at it.
- What's that red juice?
- It must be beet juice.
- Beets are good for your health.
- It's much better than what we had.
- This is much better.
- Let's drink it.
- This is...
- This is tasty.
The next juice is a mix of
noni, beet, and garlic...
which helps you strengthen
your immune system.
- What? Garlic?
- Garlic?
- They added garlic too.
- Then ours was better.
It has garlic, so it must taste bad.
It must taste bad.
It must be bad.
The order is important.
Let's pour it into five glasses
and finish it at once.
- That's enough.
- Let's all take turns to drink it.
- We've been doing well so far.
- Right.
Ready, go!
Do Kwon is drinking it.
(They start drinking
extremely sour juice...)
(without hesitation.)
I'm done. I finished it.
- Look at Do Kwon.
- I'm done.
Our team... We finished it.
Do Kwon looks like Dracula.
Do Kwon must've come today
with a strong determination.
(He keeps declaring war
against Jong Kook.)
There's some juice left.
- Do Kwon.
- There's a lot of juice left.
- Do Kwon, they didn't drink it.
- What's this?
- Fail!
- I don't think I can drink it.
(Are they giving up?)
(What's this?)
I can't drink it.
- It's...
- It's too sour.
You're giving up, right?
What is it?
I'll drink it.
(Putting on an act)
I can't even take a sip.
You nasty people.
Team Ji Hyo, your names
will be added to the Payment Box.
Okay. We're sorry.
- It's bitter.
- I'm sorry.
Let's move on to the next spot.
(What's the next mission
that'll grant their wishes?)
It was really sour though.
I'm the only one who finished it?
That was incredible.
(The long-awaited final mission)
It's summer, so they prepared
a refreshing mission.
Of course, since it's summer...
Goodness, it's refreshing.
(Two huge buoys
are waiting for them in a big pool.)
It's really cold!
- Is it cool?
- It's summer.
It's too cold.
Can we pour some hot water?
It's too cold in here.
- But they already...
- Suk Jin, try this.
This will help you get warmer.
Try it.
You darn jerk.
He's cussing now.
It's really cold.
Sit with your team, please.
- Let's sit down.
- It's like underground water.
- My goodness.
- This is...
Everyone.
Before you play the final mission,
you'll play a preliminary mission
to earn a chance card...
that'll be helpful
in playing the final mission.
You're going to play Good Image.
- Good Image?
It's a game played to
the beat of Break Up Strawberries.
This one is hard.
- My gosh.
- It's a team match.
The one attacking should say
an image and a number.
You can say...
"Ugly person, two".
Something like this.
The person who thinks the image
fits him or her...
will defend.
If two people defend
at the same time,
the offensive team gets a point.
The defensive team...
could study each other's face
up to three times.
- Among the team members.
- Up to three times?
We can say something like,
"Do it, do it."
Someone must defend
at the third beat.
We need to decide who will go.
For instance, you said an image
and a number.
Then the defensive team
should defend.
There should be only one Empty Head.
Play rock-paper-scissors to decide.
(Play rock-paper-scissors
to decide.)
- Haha.
- That team...
- We...
- has four Empty Heads.
- We should all say it.
- There are too many Empty Heads.
- I'll take that title.
- You can't decide in advance.
"Sexy" is Haha's.
We shouldn't steal it.
- It's his no matter what.
- Okay, you can take that.
"Cute and sexy" is mine.
- "Cute and sexy"?
- "Cute and sexy".
"Cute and sexy".
(He's calling himself
cute and sexy.)
We have two guests, so we can't
tell which one is Empty Head.
I don't think Ji Hyun is.
Jong Hyeop seems like one though.
Right? You're a bit dumb, right?
- He's not witty at all, and...
- You are?
It's good that you're admitting it.
I like it.
- Of course. I admit it.
- Jong Hyeop is...
Who do you want to go against
if you were to play a quiz?
(His gaze is fixed at someone.)
- Of course I'll pick...
- Who?
- How dare you look at me?
Hey! I'm smarter than you think!
- This is insane!
- He chose Se Chan right away.
- He knows his opponent.
- I...
How dare he pick me?
Let's hurry up and play.
By the way, Do Kwon...
looks like a cameraman.
He looks like
a documentary cameraman.
He looks like one.
You're lucky that you became
an actor.
That's true.
- How come you're so quiet now?
- He's lucky.
- He's...
- He's tired now.
- Ever since...
- He's been down since earlier.
Ever since we played
with the bouncy ball...
- You're a bit down, aren't you?
- He's out of energy.
He's less excited now.
Which image should we come up with?
Would you like to start?
Who... Do you want to
go first, Jae Suk?
Okay.
- Good image, good image
Empty Head, two.
- Empty Head, Empty Head.
- Good.
Old fossil, three.
Old fossil, old fossil, old fossil.
- What's with the beat?
- It's a practice round.
- Suk Jin.
You said we can clap
three times before defending, right?
- Okay, got it.
- Let's skip one beat.
- Old fossil.
- Why did I answer that?
It was natural.
Let's start with So Min.
- We're playing it for real.
- Let's do this.
- Good image, good image
Someone who'll go out with me, two.
(Someone who'll
go out with me, two.)
("Someone who'll go out with me"?)
Who will it be?
- Me?
- Ji Hyun, Ji Hyun!
- You could've just said it!
- Why didn't you say it?
(No matter how long she waited,
she couldn't get the answer.)
(You could've just said it!)
- How can I go out with her?
- It was me?
- It's just a game!
- No, that's not it.
He's so slow-witted!
- He's so slow.
- Come on, Jong Hyeop.
You should've said it
even if you hated the idea!
He's right, Jong Hyeop.
Who else would go out with her
among us?
- My gosh.
- Who else would go out with her?
I get it.
If I answered that,
- that'd have been weird.
- Of course.
- You're the only option.
- I'm glad we won,
I'm glad we won,
but it doesn't feel so good.
It doesn't feel so good.
(I'm sorry, but...)
- I'm sorry, but...
- My gosh.
can I go to the bathroom?
Why?
When I'm in water...
- for a long time...
- When you're in water...
Is it number 1 or number 2?
I want to pee.
- He's so weird!
- Goodness!
(He's been grabbing his pants
as though he's anxious.)
- He's so weird.
- But don't you have to be...
in the water this deep to feel that?
Only our feet are in the water.
- It's just my habit.
- Don't you have to be deep in it?
(It's his bad habit.)
Don't you have to be in the water
this deep to feel that?
- Is that part of your routine?
- Yes, it is.
- Then you can go.
- My body reacts to it.
Hurry up then!
- If I'm in the water for too...
- Got it.
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry, Ji Hyun.
- Not at all.
- You should run.
- I'll be right back.
- This is so random.
- He's actually going.
It's not like he was deep
in the water.
We only had our feet in the water.
Why would he want to pee?
Who goes to the bathroom
for getting their feet wet?
Maybe it's because of the sound
the water is making.
- That must be why.
- You feel nature's call...
when you shower.
There must be something wrong
with his prostate gland.
He's susceptible to
the sound of water.
- Right.
- That's how kids are like.
Kids pee when they hear
the sound of water.
No one among the actors teases
someone with this topic, right?
- They don't.
- Of course.
This is so new to me.
- It is, right?
- Yes.
You'd just politely tell the person
to use the bathroom.
He's one of the seniors here,
and he had to apologize.
- And he was harshly criticized.
- Everyone scolded him.
When we attack, we attack
until that person gets knocked out.
- That was a short trip.
- All right now!
- It must've been only a little.
- Did you pee well?
- I did.
Did you pee well?
It was incredible.
It wasn't much,
and you feel refreshed?
(He quickly felt the refreshment.)
Why did you...
Seeing how fast he made it back,
there must've been only three drops.
It was incredible.
- It was incredible.
- It must've been only a few drops.
He said it was incredible.
- He said it was incredible.
- He only went to pee though.
- That was hilarious.
- It was great.
- Whom should we start with?
- So Min.
- It's me again?
Let's play Image Game
- It's "good image".
- Oh, right.
- Good image, good image
Someone who likes me, four.
(Someone who likes me, four.)
Someone who likes me,
Someone who likes me.
(She finally got the answer
she wanted.)
(Looking happy)
You should keep going.
- Empty Head, three.
- You should take it, Se Chan.
Empty Head, Empty Head, Empty Head.
Bedwetter, four.
(Bedwetter, four.)
It's you. Here we go.
Bedwetter, bedwetter, bedwetter,
- bedwetter.
- He defended.
Hairy man, three.
(Hairy man, three.)
- Hairy man, hairy man, hairy man.
- Why would you answer that?
- Darn you!
- Why did you do that?
(A sudden intrusion of So Min
evens the scores.)
- I thought he wouldn't...
- Why did you answer that?
- It looked like he wouldn't...
- It needs to make sense!
I'm hairy too.
Not there! Someplace else.
He's the hairy man.
He was getting ready to answer.
Don't forget to look at
each other's faces, okay?
Let's meet each other's eyes.
When you think that the given image
fits you, yell out, "My!"
- "My!"
- You can't directly claim it.
Let's do this then.
To say that you'll take it.
That's it.
- How? Do it again.
- Like this.
"That's me."
("That's me.")
Then you go,
"Empty Head, Empty Head!"
- "Empty Head, Empty Head!"
- What is that?
- Someone looks like him.
- One actor who looks like him.
- Ugly person, three!
Ugly person, ugly person!
(Obviously, I'm the ugly person.)
Do this to say that it's your turn.
- It's like saying, "My."
- This one?
We should think of the images
we can attack them with.
I can't think of one
after defending.
Let's start. Image
- Image, image
(Getting excited)
- Gosh, those punks.
(Here comes the excited duo.)
(Making so much fuss with the intro)
Image, image
- Image, image
- I want to join.
- Aren't you going to start?
- So Min couldn't hold herself back.
- So Min joined them.
Look at her.
(Thanks to the co-ed trio,
the intro has become splendid.)
- Let's go!
- Aren't you going to start?
- Gosh, my head hurts.
- Haha.
Let's do it.
We need to keep this up.
My head hurts.
This is so fun!
- Are you having fun?
- It's so fun!
- Good image, good image
Old fossil!
How many beats, you punk?
- Oh, right.
- How many beats?
- Nice one.
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Good image, good image
- Good image, good image
Gangnam, three.
Gangnam, Gangnam, Gangnam.
Gangseo, four.
Gangseo, Gangseo, Gangseo, Gangseo.
Glasses, two.
Glasses, glasses.
Sexy guy, two.
Was that on the beat?
- Sexy guy, two.
- Sexy guy, sexy guy.
Sexy guy, three.
(Using the same image one more time)
(They fail to defend.)
- You see...
- We let you take it!
- But...
- I should've taken it instead!
- We let you take it!
(I should've taken
sexy guy instead!)
- Anyone could've taken it.
- What? You're not even sexy!
- I should've taken it!
- Just stay still!
- I should've taken it instead!
- Why would you?
- What was that?
- I was going to take it too.
If you think it's yours,
just take it.
- All right.
- Let's start.
White T-shirt, four.
(Everyone is wearing
a white T-shirt.)
White T-shirt, white T-shirt,
white T-shirt, white T-shirt.
Protein, three.
Protein, protein, protein.
Youngest, two.
Youngest, Youngest.
Cap, three.
(Everyone is wearing a cap)
- Cap, cap...
All right!
(The two of them
defended at the same time.)
- Well done!
- We won!
- That was a good one.
Since everyone is wearing a cap...
Why didn't you go
when you had the chance?
I thought I'd get told off
for not going for it again.
Why did you defend
when you didn't need to?
- My gosh, we were almost there.
- Let's just win the next round.
- We can win the next round.
- Let's come up with a few images.
What? What did you say?
Okay, got it.
That's all we need. Keep it down.
The word you're attacking with
is important.
We need to come up with a word
we can attack the whole team with.
We should shake them up.
(They're going to shake them up?)
This is... You're so mean though.
- I can't say this in advance.
- Let's play.
- That's a game changer.
- They're done now.
Let's attack just one person.
- Who's going first? You?
- I'm going first.
- I'll go first.
- He's nervous.
It's nerve-wracking.
- It's nerve-wracking.
- Image
- Good image, good image
Cap, three.
(Cap, three.)
Cap, cap, cap.
(Do Kwon manages to defend.)
Yoon Eun Hye, four.
(Yoon Eun Hye, four.)
Yoon Eun Hye, Yoon Eun Hye,
Yoon Eun Hye, Yoon Eun Hye.
Is that what you came up with?
(The fans of Absolutely Game
from "X-Man" love it.)
Anyang, two
Anyang, Anyang.
(He shouts "Anyang" cheerfully.)
Workout, four.
Workout, workout, workout, workout.
(He responds to the attack
that was aimed at him.)
That little...
Jong Kook, don't get angry!
(He didn't hide his excitement.)
That little...
Jong Kook, don't get angry!
Don't get angry!
- That little jerk.
- Jong Kook.
I told you not to do that.
(He runs away.)
They are so annoying.
What? Jae Suk could have taken it.
- It suits Jae Suk too.
- Jae Suk could have taken it.
They are so annoying.
It was a nice attack.
We should help each other.
You could have helped me
by taking care of the keyword...
on Round One.
- I couldn't take care of "Eun Hye".
- Why not?
I couldn't take care
of "Eun Hye" either.
I know you couldn't,
but Jae Suk could.
- I couldn't take care of "Eun Hye".
- You should protect the team.
What would have happened
had I taken the keyword?
That attack worked so well.
- Seriously.
- It was hilarious.
- Eun Hye had to come up someday.
- Stop it already.
- Seriously.
Thus, Team Ji Hyo won
the preliminary mission.
(It's time to move on
to the last mission!)
The last mission is...
the Strategic Floating Mat Battle.
It will be about pushing people off.
You start on the two floating mats
in the pool...
and win if you push off
all members of the opposing team.
- We have an advantage.
- The matches...
will be 1-on-1, 2-on-2, 3-on-3,
4-on-4, and 5-on-5.
You will have five rounds in total.
Each member can participate
in three or fewer rounds.
So the teams should come up
with plans for the matches.
- I think Jong Kook will kill me.
- Okay.
However, Team Ji Hyo has
an advantage.
Once Team Ji Hyun is done planning,
we will reveal their lineup
for the 3-on-3 match.
You can take a look
and adjust your plan.
- Then we can...
- Still...
Still, we need to be strategic.
That way, you can choose
which matches to focus on.
We should give up on one round.
Don't say that as you look at me.
- You are the referee.
- Please put down the lineups here.
- Okay.
- We will do that.
- All right.
- How many matches?
We need to choose
the rounds to give up on...
since Jong Kook can only participate
in three rounds.
We could give up
on the first two rounds.
Wouldn't it be best to put me
in the less important rounds?
(Captain Ji Hyun volunteers to take
the 1-on-1 match.)
It's a good idea.
She can take the 1-on-1 match.
We need to win
the 2-on-2 and 3-on-3 matches.
In this round,
all of us will participate.
Jong Kook should take
the 2-on-2 match.
- Jong Kook should participate.
- Yes.
And you should join
the 3-on-3 match.
Here you go.
I will reveal Team Ji Hyun's lineup
for the 3-on-3 match.
Team Ji Hyun's lineup
for the 3-on-3 match is...
Jong Kook, Jong Hyeop, and Suk Jin.
(The ace member,
Jong Kook, will participate!)
- Let's give up on the round.
- Come here.
Let's give up on it.
Here. Give it to me.
(Team Ji Hyo will give up
on the 3-on-3 match.)
- Will you give up on it?
- That's right.
Who wants to participate
in this round?
Add Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon.
- Me?
(What will be their lineups
for the other matches?)
Both teams turned in their lineups.
All right.
Let's begin with the 1-on-1 match.
The 1-on-1 match.
The 1-on-1 matchup is...
(Which member of Team Ji Hyo
will take on Ji Hyun?)
Ji Hyun versus Do Kwon.
(Ji Hyun versus Do Kwon)
We lost.
(Team Ji Hyo expected Jong Kook.)
Ji Hyun.
- That's good.
- We chose well.
- What do I do?
- You need to win.
You need to win no matter what.
We need to win
at least a single round.
You can lose.
You can lose, Ji Hyun.
Still, do your best.
All right. Get ready.
You can't lose.
- Good luck. You need to win.
- Let's go, Ji Hyun.
(Ji Hyun has no pressure
whatsoever.)
(Who will be
the winner of this match?)
- I don't know what to do.
- You know,
- you might just win.
- Do Kwon, show us...
what you can do.
Do Kwon, don't go easy on her.
Your wife will find it strange
if you go easy on her.
- That's right.
- Your wife.
No one asked him to go easy on her.
Ji Hyun can do this.
He doesn't need to go easy on her.
- What?
- Just push her.
What are you doing?
Don't fall for that laugh.
Look at her eyes.
- How am I supposed to push her?
- Come on!
I should have gone.
- Go over to her mat.
- Lift her up...
and put her in the water.
Come on.
(He decides to let his daughter
have fun in the water.)
That's good.
He can't lift her up.
- He can't lift her up.
- Dad.
- He can't do it.
- My goodness.
- Do Kwon, what are you doing?
- It looks strange.
(Do Kwon's legs are weak
after the gym ball game.)
He can't lift her up.
- He can't lift her up.
- No.
(The daughter refuses to
play in the water.)
(They enter the water together.)
- He won.
- Isn't it a tie?
- She entered the water first.
- Ji Hyun, are you okay?
- It should be a tie.
- Do Kwon won.
Okay.
Get ready.
Your face went in first.
The beet juice I drank earlier
is about to come back up.
(He gained victory
by sacrificing his face.)
My goodness.
Ji Hyun, good job.
Next up is the 2-on-2 match.
(What's the lineup
for the 2-on-2 match?)
Jong Kook and Jae Suk...
versus Do Kwon and Se Chan.
Okay.
(Team Ji Hyo put the ace members
in the 2-on-2 match.)
- We have a chance.
- There we go.
- What should we do?
- Listen.
I don't know what will happen.
It's a big match.
I am drowsy.
Make sure
you throw us into the water.
- Of course.
- Let's begin.
Don't get intimidated.
Bring it on. Bring it on, you punks.
Okay. Bring it on.
- Bring it on.
- They look weak.
Don't get intimidated
by a bedwetter.
- Bring it on.
- He might start peeing.
- Come here, you punks.
- Bring it on.
- What?
- Bedwetter, bedwetter.
There you go.
Come on.
What are you two doing?
Are you fencing?
There is tension in the air.
All right.
(Jae Suk versus Se Chan)
Cowards do this.
Come on.
Come here. Come here.
(They fight with their tongues,
not swords.)
(For goodness' sake.)
- That's what the weak ones do.
- Let's put the mats together.
Let's grab them.
Let's grab them first.
Hold on. Jae Suk.
Hold his hand.
Jong Kook, this brings back
memories of "X-Man".
- We were on the show.
- It does bring back memories.
- Okay.
- They are testing the waters.
- Bromance, bromance.
(At that moment,
Do Kwon charges forward.)
What are you doing here?
(He gets on their mat
while they think about the past.)
Do Kwon, don't do that.
Do Kwon.
(He enters the water by himself.)
What was that?
(He had too much faith
in his short legs.)
What was that? For goodness' sake.
- What was that?
- What did you do?
- Come here.
- Hold on.
It's 2-on-1.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Come here.
- Hey.
(Hold on, my foot!)
(The big match ends
in a lackluster way.)
What was that?
That was disappointing.
Hey!
- What?
- Seriously.
The floating mat was too far.
- You should have jumped over.
- What was that?
That was lackluster.
- Okay.
- I am sorry.
- Hey.
- It was good.
- Next up is the 3-on-3 match.
- We should have won.
Jong Kook, Jong Hyeop, and Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- And...
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Haha.
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Haha?
Did you say
They chose the weakest members
for this round.
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Haha?
Charge at them.
Protect me, okay?
- No.
- Haha.
Go!
(Mr. Dirty Mustache tries
to sacrifice the female members.)
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- Good luck.
Let's go.
Go, go.
Come here, you punks.
- Attack!
- Don't push.
Come here.
What? Do you want me to go?
- Come here.
- Move back.
- Come one at a time.
- Firstly,
- Bring it on.
- the one in a green cap.
- Hey.
Come. Come on.
- Come one at a time.
- The "twu" of you should step back.
- Okay.
- He said "Twu".
(What was that?)
I mispronounced it.
(His rival's provocation
got his tongue tied.)
Okay.
(The matchup
between the weakest members)
- Come on. Come on.
- We swear...
we won't help.
- We will sit down.
- No touching.
- Let's have a 1-on-1 match.
- It's neck and neck.
- Come on over.
My goodness.
You are provoking me.
That puts me in a bad mood.
You can't come over, right?
Come over. Come over.
(The provocation and mockery...)
(make him charge forward.)
There you go.
- My goodness.
- So Min, hang in there.
(Glancing over)
Good luck.
(When he sees Haha approach,)
(he makes a sudden retreat.)
(What?)
What was that?
(Suk Jin tried to go back.)
(He fails.)
What was that?
(He jumped when there was a distance
between the floating mats.)
What was that?
(The lack of jumping ability
created slapstick comedy.)
What were you doing?
(Humiliated)
- Suk Jin.
- He can't jump at all.
(He can barely jump over
the doorsill.)
- How embarrassing!
- What was that?
That was so embarrassing.
- That was so funny.
- What was that?
- I am so embarrassed.
- Suk Jin, you looked so cute.
It was exactly what I wanted to see.
We could win.
We could win. We could win.
You!
- No. It will be me.
- No.
You can't go against Jong Hyeop.
You!
Come on.
Either one of you
should come on over.
Go over there and fight!
No.
Go!
Don't just sit around like a fool.
Shall we go on over?
- Shall we go on over?
- Okay.
Be careful when you go on over.
The gap gets quite big.
Finish them off.
- No.
- Let's go.
- Let's go over there.
- Come here.
All right.
You should go to the front
and protect me.
Hold each other.
He came over.
- Come here.
- Hey.
(Did he just come alone?)
Push him. Push him.
Hey.
Come on.
Hey. There you go.
(One day, destruction entered
their floating mat.)
You should be careful.
(Jong Hyeop joins him.)
Hold on.
- Hold on.
Jong Kook.
- Come on.
- Don't do it.
Move out of the way.
(Lu Bu on the floating mat
has no mercy.)
Come here.
Ji Hyo, run away.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- Hey.
- Haha, hang in there.
Come on.
- Hey.
- Haha, hang in there.
(Haha is the only one who remains.)
It's over.
Finish him off without pain.
- Finish him off without pain.
- It's over.
- Haha.
- My goodness.
Gosh, I feel bad.
Gosh, I can't watch this.
I can't watch this.
(Screaming)
(Jong Kook pulls his underwear.)
(Throwing)
(He feels pain
from the deep valley.)
He shouldn't have held out.
You have done enough.
- Okay.
- It was time to give up.
Are you okay?
Are you not okay?
The left ball came off.
The left ball.
- Hey, hey.
- The right ball. The right ball.
Next up is the 4-on-4 match.
Ji Hyo, Haha, Se Chan,
- and So Min.
- Me?
Ji Hyun, Jong Hyeop,
Suk Jin, and Jae Suk.
This match is neck and neck.
Let's go.
- We have a chance.
- Hey, hey.
- I am glad I am on this team.
(He acts flippantly
because he has other members.)
- What is he doing?
- Okay, okay.
- Go.
- No, no, no.
You will fall into the water.
- You will fall into the water.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
Se Chan, now is your chance.
Now is your chance.
Don't huddle close.
- Jong Hyeop.
- Now is your chance.
- Watch closely, Ji Hyun.
- I am going over.
- So Min, get Jae Suk.
(The bedwetter is in a hurry.)
(Faltering)
All right.
(He charges forward
when Se Chan falters.)
He is here. All right.
Finish off Jae Suk.
(Jong Hyeop joins him.)
It's too far.
- Guys!
- Sit down.
I want to go there,
but it's too far.
- It's too far.
- Push it.
- Hurry up and go over there.
- All right.
- Push it.
(It's 2 against 1.)
Jong Hyeop.
(Jong Hyeop is out.)
Hurry up and go over there.
(Ji Hyun and Suk Jin come to help.)
Hold on.
- Go over there.
- Okay, okay.
Hold on.
(He misses his steps.)
My goodness.
He is out.
(Suk Jin is out
while jumping over the mat.)
What was that?
(JI Hyun gets attacked.)
All right. All right.
It's over.
- Let's lift him up.
Let's lift him up. Come here.
Hey! Where is everyone?
What happened?
We are out.
Where is everyone?
Come on.
(It's now 4 people
versus 1 bedwetter.)
Jae Suk, don't tire yourself out.
Just get eliminated.
Take off his shorts.
(They no longer care about
the match.)
Hey.
(Taking off)
We did it.
(The pee-stained shorts
get discarded.)
Get off the mat.
Come here. Slap, slap.
Hey.
Get off the mat.
(It's time to let
the grasshopper go.)
Go.
(In the end, he is out.)
We won thanks to the strategy.
(Team Ji Hyun got destroyed
one at a time.)
What happened to everyone?
I was jumping over...
- when I missed my steps.
- You should go over at once.
These guys ganged up on me.
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk, put on your shorts.
- Here are your shoes.
- No!
I will go around like this.
(An eyesore in a swimming suit
appears.)
What are you doing?
Hey.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Stop it.
- Why?
- Don't jump.
I got beaten up!
Don't jump.
Put on your shorts.
I am wearing a swimming suit.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Why are you making a fuss?
- For goodness' sake.
Hey.
Put on your shorts.
- Hey.
- Hurry up.
I got beaten up so much.
You went over too hastily.
We wanted to follow you,
but the gap was too wide.
You should have told us
ahead of time.
- Gosh.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
He did that on purpose.
Put on your shorts!
I won't put them on.
- He thinks I did it on purpose.
- Put on your shorts.
I didn't do it on purpose.
- You know,
- Are you a seal or what?
the water must be pretty cold.
(Shy)
For goodness' sake.
- Hey, put on your pants.
- It's very cold. It's very cold.
Don't make a fuss.
It must be cold.
It must be as cold as ice.
- Hurry up and put them on.
- The water turned a bit yellow.
- What is your problem?
- The water turned a bit yellow...
around Jae Suk.
I am even more exhausted
because I drank so much water.
I feel like only Jae Suk
is taking an active part.
He is the most exhausted one.
- I guess it was a 1-on-5 match.
- A 1-on-5 match.
Suk Jin, what did you do today?
- What did you do?
- Suk Jin, what did you do?
Let's begin the match.
- Okay.
- Let's go. Let's end this.
Go, go.
We should be careful
about going over.
We should go over at once.
Okay.
(Come here!)
- Okay.
- The mats are coming closer.
(The 2nd match
between the weakest members)
Ouch!
My goodness.
(Stepping)
What?
He stepped on Suk Jin's hand.
- What?
- Does it hurt?
- My team is attacking each other.
My team is attacking each other.
- Hey.
- You should be careful.
- I was here.
- We shouldn't attack each other.
(He is unapologetic.)
I can't believe it.
(The weakest members
resume their match.)
- Come here.
- Hold my hand.
Be brave and come here.
(They hold each other's hands.)
(Shouting)
There you go.
Hold on. I will hold off Jong Kook.
Come here.
We need to work together.
(A human tug-of-war)
Hold still.
- Let go of her.
- No, hold her.
Hold So Min. Hold So Min.
Hold So Min.
(Saving Private So Min)
- Hold So Min.
- Is this an execution?
Don't give up on So Min.
- Save So Min.
- You said you will come back.
- Why are you here?
- Save her no matter what.
All of us will die, you fool!
- Don't worry.
- Let's save her.
So Min, hang in there.
So Min, no.
- Let go of me.
- Don't give up.
Let go of me.
- No.
- Let go of me.
So Min, we will never let go.
We will never let go.
You are our comrade.
Come down. Come down.
- Her joints will get stretched.
- Is So Min made of rubber?
- Let go of me.
- Let her go.
Let So Min go.
- They are letting go of So Min.
- Let go of me.
They are letting go of So Min.
There we go.
Get some rest.
So Min. Medic! Medic!
Medic! Bring an energy drink.
Are you okay?
She needs some rest.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Shall we go?
- Jong Kook will go back and forth.
- All right.
- Grab him now. Grab him now.
He is here.
- Did you grab Jong Kook?
- No, no.
What are they doing?
(Suk Jin charges forward.)
- What?
- I got him.
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin's fall acts as a signal.)
- I got him.
- Grab her.
They are here.
(A close combat)
Come on.
Why are you doing this to me?
(Do Kwon aggravated Protein Monster
all day long.)
(Throwing)
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Se Chan.
Grab him.
Come on.
(He escapes, but Jong Kook's push
eliminates him.)
Ji Hyo, watch out for Suk Jin.
You... You...
(So Min is out as well.)
- Hey.
- All right.
(After holding out for a while,)
(Haha gets eliminated
in a lackluster way.)
Let's get her.
I am sorry.
Do Kwon.
- It's over.
- Do Kwon.
(Do Kwon is the only one left.)
I will take one person with me.
(The hairy man is ferocious.)
Do Kwon is holding out
until the very end.
Gosh, Do Kwon is so annoying.
(Flipping over)
(The hairy man
eliminates one member.)
- There you go.
- Push him off.
Do Kwon, hold out until the end.
Push him off.
Suk Jin should participate.
He should stop watching
and participate.
(The man of 3 losses
stands back and watches.)
Suk Jin should use his strength.
- Go down the mat.
- What is he doing?
Is he there to watch?
(Jae Suk shampoos his hair
after washing his face.)
- Come on.
- He is shampooing his hair.
Let's get your hair shampooed.
(It's refreshing.)
This hair salon is nice.
Suk Jin should go against him.
(Suk Jin jumps in
only after he is out of strength.)
(In the end, Do Kwon is out.)
Okay.
(Team Ji Hyun won the last match.)
It's impossible to beat them.
We can't beat them.
- Do Kwon.
- Good job.
After a fierce match,
Team Ji Hyun won.
(Team Ji Hyun won.)
- Good job.
- Okay.
I did my best.
- We fought well.
- We fell apart...
after one member got eliminated.
The fight started
when Suk Jin came over.
I don't think I can drink this.
(Se Chan openly gives up.)
We will fail.
I think we will fail.
The five members' names
will go into the Payment Box.
It's impossible to drink it.
- The smell is too strong.
- Okay.
- It's impossible.
- Okay, okay.
Everyone, here is the Wish Box.
- It's all set.
- You're at a disadvantage.
If your name is in the capsule,
you'll be the winner.
If we pick the same name,
we will pick again.
Okay.
And the Payment Box
is for a penalty.
Today's penalty is...
random ink buckets.
That's the worst.
It's the worst penalty.
(If they're covered with ink,
they have to wash here.)
So we might avoid the penalty.
Sure. One will pick confetti,
and the other will pick ink.
We have little chance
of getting a penalty.
If we get a penalty after winning
the race, it will be the worst case.
- It's the worst.
- It can happen.
All right. Who will pick a capsule
from the Wish Box then?
Ji Hyun will do that.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyun.
- Please.
- To grant a wish.
I hope Se Chan will get an iPad.
Sure. That's what I want.
I want to see Kwang Soo.
(Haha's wish is that Kwang Soo will
be a crew member for a day.)
In the drama, you make wishes.
- I want an iPad...
- My gosh.
(So Min wants the crew members
to tell the answers only to her.)
(It will be decided by sheer luck.)
I hope she will pick mine.
(Jae Suk wants Seok Sam to be
his younger brother for a day.)
Open it one by one.
- Open it.
- I'll be happy to be picked.
Please. I want to get
a tablet computer.
(The first winner is...)
What?
- It's Jong Hyeop.
- Chae Jong Hyeop.
- Speakers.
- Speakers!
(I want Haha to buy me
a high-performance speaker.)
(A pain in the back of his head)
So Min? What was So Min's wish?
It's So Min.
She gets to hear
the answers to quizzes.
I get to hear the answers.
My wish.
We will grant your wishes.
I've only known Jong Hyeop
for less than eight hours.
You should buy him
a high-performance speaker.
He should buy it.
Okay. Good.
Thank you, Haha.
Thank you.
(Haha granted Jong Hyeop's wish
as he promised.)
- So Min...
- You should tell me the answers.
We will tell her the answers...
and make it look like
she answered them.
Okay. Now, pick capsules
from the Payment Box.
Our team should pick.
All right. Do Kwon.
Let's pick one each.
Do Kwon, please.
If my name is picked...
- It will be the worst.
- If I get picked...
I feel like I'll get picked.
- It will be the worst.
- If I get picked...
This is the worst.
- I don't want to get picked.
- No way.
- I can't watch it.
- Why are you looking at me?
- Is it you?
- Is it me?
- Who is it?
- It's not me.
- Is it me?
Song Ji Hyo!
- It's Ji Hyo. Who is it?
- Song Ji Hyo.
(Me?)
(Who did Ji Hyo pick?)
It will be amazing
if Ji Hyo picks Do Kwon.
(Did Ji Hyo pick Do Kwon?)
- Kim Jong Kook!
- It's Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook is picked.)
Nice!
- I did it!
- It's great.
- It's done. I won.
- Ji Hyo!
- Well done, Ji Hyo.
- I won.
They did it!
Let's just go home right away.
- Hey, too bad.
- Let's just go home...
right away.
Let's go home.
Jong Kook, this is the worst.
I'll just get changed and go home.
When she picked it,
I had a bad feeling about it.
- A bad feeling?
- That's ridiculous.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo...
will pick a bucket now.
You should pick 1 of the 2.
It's a random game.
Pick a number.
I pick number two.
Then number one for Jong Kook.
Then bring in the buckets.
You're not supposed to look yet.
- What's Jong Kook's number?
He's number one.
- Should we do it on our knees?
- Yes, on your knees.
All right. Pour it
as I count to three.
(Jong Kook has a bad feeling
because he met Yong Gu again.)
(Ji Hyo is always lucky
when it comes to a random game.)
One, two, and three.
(Ji Hyo picked the ink.)
Seriously? I can't believe this.
I really didn't want to pour this.
I can't believe you poured
confetti on my head.
Look at the ink.
- It's scary.
- Ji Hyo.
(The dark energy is spreading.)
My goodness.
- She looks like a witch.
- There's a witch!
- It's a witch.
- She looks like a witch.
These days, you're really...
Wipe it with this, Ji Hyo.
You look like a witch. My gosh.
- That's cool.
- My gosh.
It's scary.
Please watch "The Witch's Diner".
(The Unofficial
Comedian Association)
(July 6, 2021, Comedian
Association's Annual Meeting)
(Yoo Jae Suk, President,
Comedian Association Term 1)
(Today's event is more meaningful
with new comedians.)
(Lee Yong Jin, Term 3)
I have an official
announcement to make.
We need some money to do something.
So I will collect membership fees.
(They don't know how
the membership fee is used.)
- I'll pay too.
- You should cover all the expenses.
(When the president
is about to give a speech...)
- The news is on.
- This is news that's just come in.
There was a robbery in the office
of the Comedian Association.
The police say the 2m-tall comedian
Lee Kwang Soo is the suspect.
I can't believe this.
He got us some gifts before.
So that's how
he bought all the gifts?
He's a jerk!
What do we do then?
(The Comedian Association faces
a crisis because of Kwang Soo.)
(Will the comedians be able
to guard their office?)
(Theft of Comedian
Association Membership Fee)