- Let's go.
- Hello.
Let's go.
- Hi.
Hello.
(So Min looks cute today.)
So Min is...
(Cute and lovely)
When someone says you look cute,
you usually feel shy,
but that's not the case for So Min.
I just try to look cuter.
- So Min shows her...
- Hello.
It seems like
you've lost some weight.
- Hello, MC Hammer.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Ji Hyo.
- What were you working on?
- Ji Hyo, we...
- A jumpsuit?
Isn't she wearing our uniform
from the first episode?
- Isn't that it?
- The one from the first episode.
To remember my first intention.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- A man in a white shirt.
- Why are you wearing mint shorts?
- Me? Because it's summer.
- It's not pink.
And he's not wearing slippers.
Gosh, that's...
I didn't wear slippers before.
Slippers?
When did I wear slippers
for the opening?
- Gosh.
- Did I wear slippers or not?
- Jong Kook, you should...
- Wait.
- I mean...
- He's upset in the morning.
He's being ridiculous.
Is it something
you have to be this upset about?
- When did I wear slippers...
- Jong Kook started menopause.
- It's menopause.
- Menopause?
- For the opening...
- I'm so surprised.
He's going through menopause.
For the opening, when did I...
I don't wear slippers
at least for the opening.
I wear them somewhere else.
- I read an article yesterday.
- Is it that upsetting?
One of the menopausal symptoms is...
- flying into a rage.
- Is that so?
- Yes. That's what it is.
- Is it?
- You easily get upset.
- My gosh.
- By the way...
- It looks like we are...
- The thing is...
- What is it?
How could you be alone
with Ji Hyo at your place?
I watched that too.
How could you...
(A great number of people
watched the video of them.)
(It had about 13.54 million views.)
(At Jong Kook's place, not a gym,)
(they worked out together
in a sweet but brutal way.)
- It's not like that.
- Just the two of them?
We just worked together.
We're just confused.
So what's the deal?
Hang on.
Hang on. Suk Jin.
- You... Ji Hyo, hang on.
- In Jong Kook's place...
- Again...
- Wait. You...
Did you promise
to join my channel or not?
- I did.
- What about you?
- What about you, Suk Jin.
I promised.
They all promised to do it.
- As Jae Suk brought it up...
- I...
He just started yelling.
- He's being like this on purpose.
- Let go of me.
He's doing this on purpose.
- Hey.
- She just did it first...
because her new drama
was coming out.
- He's blushing to his ears.
- Hang on.
- Look. He's blushing.
- Don't make things up.
- You stay quiet.
- He's going through menopause.
- He's started menopause.
- Your ears are all red.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
I just meant...
- He becomes calm already.
- For your channel...
- I'm scared.
- Ji Hyo can join your channel.
- Of course.
- But what I found surprising...
was that Ji Hyo
seemed so comfortable.
- Totally.
- I know.
(Ji Hyo seemed so comfortable.)
(She had a bowl of cool soup.)
(Then she lied down on the sofa
as if it was her place.)
You can't do that. Get up.
I want to lie down and watch TV.
- It was like...
- It looked like she lived there.
I didn't feel comfortable.
I was just exhausted.
Hang on. When you came...
to my place with the other members
the other day,
did you feel comfortable or not?
Did you not say
you were comfortable or not?
- Why are you so upset?
- Let go.
- Did you say that or not?
- How would she answer?
- Stop yelling.
- How would she answer the question?
- Did you say that or not?
- Say you were uncomfortable.
- What is it that upsets you?
- You said that.
- Right.
- She said...
She felt really comfortable.
But why are you
saying that to Ji Hyo?
Don't be upset.
Don't make things up.
Did she go home after the shoot
or sleep over?
Of course she went home!
(Of course she went home!)
Of course I went home, you punk!
Of course she did.
- I just asked one question.
- Hey!
Why are you guys so upset?
Hey, you two are dating, aren't you?
- They're dating.
- No.
I know you guys are yelling
like this for a reason.
- That's what it is.
- It's not happening yet...
because Eun Hye
finally started talking.
- Eun Hye finally started talking.
- Will you stop it?
(Eun Hye finally started talking.)
Don't do that.
- Stop it.
- What did Eun Hye say?
- What did she say?
- What did Eun Hye say about him?
- Please join our show sometime.
Eun Hye finally started talking.
- What did she say?
- She didn't say anything.
- She was on "Men on a Mission".
- Really?
She was,
but she didn't say much about me.
(She suffers from "X-Man"
as much as Jong Kook does.)
(Old fans of "X-Man" have been
waiting for her answer.)
(Even their parents fell for
their romance in a variety show.)
(Fans of "X-Man" were
ecstatic at the news.)
She was,
- What I'm saying is...
- but she didn't say much about me.
- This is just strange.
- I'm curious.
(This is just strange.)
Eun Hye is on a lot of TV shows,
but not ours.
(Eun Hye is on a lot of TV shows,
but not ours.)
(Follow me.)
Why are you doing this?
- That's enough.
- I mean...
(The huge fan of "X-Man" is
dragged out of the camera view.)
- Today's opening is so intense.
- It's so intense.
- Okay.
- Enough.
- I get it.
- My gosh.
(The former MC of "X-Man"
is intimidated.)
- That's enough.
- This time,
I thought Jong Kook would hit me.
I haven't seen you getting away
from the camera for a long time.
- Where would he hit me...
- They got out of the camera view.
Enough is enough.
- The whole situation...
- I know.
This is just about work.
Anyway, even if you date Ji Hyo,
don't say that for the time being.
Until Eun Hye joins our show.
You have guts.
- You do have guts.
- You're unbelievable.
You've got a lot of nerve
after you moved to a new agency.
Well done.
It's hard, but I'll give it a try.
(He declares that
he will snipe at Jong Kook.)
Eun Hye.
- Don't do that.
- Set up the antenna.
Okay.
Stop talking about her.
She's just doing fine now.
I want to go home.
Please stand in the middle.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
Why are you here?
You're supposed to be there.
- He seems excited.
- I know.
- He's excited.
- He wants to tease Jong Kook.
- My gosh.
- I'm right next to you.
(His snaggletooth charm
melts Jong Kook's heart.)
I like Jong Kook a lot.
- All right.
- He's so fun.
And we have something to celebrate.
- Really?
- What is it?
With the last week's episode,
our show became...
the longest-lived variety show.
- My gosh.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- It was "Infinite Challenge".
- That's right.
- We broke the record.
- Did we beat "Infinite Challenge"?
- Actually, "Infinite Challenge"...
- was about two years longer.
- That's amazing.
But "Infinite Challenge"
was canceled many times...
when the broadcasting company
was on strike.
- So we have more episodes.
- Running Man has more episodes.
So these two broke
their own records.
That's right.
That's so cool.
- No, not me.
- Why not?
- You did.
- Why would you say that?
- He's...
- I didn't do anything.
He served in the military,
so he wasn't in all the episodes.
- He was on the show anyway.
- Still, he was a member there.
Why would you
belittle his achievements?
- My gosh.
- Don't diminish his career.
Now that you're
on "How Do You Play?"...
(Suk Jin's become confident
after he made his way to MBC.)
It's over.
I'm not on the show anymore.
- He's Kim Tae Ho's son.
- What?
Kim Tae Ho's half son.
Hey, Kim Tae Ho's son.
Suk Jin is loyal to MBC.
- Kim Tae Ho's son?
- He loves Kim Tae Ho.
If that's the case,
count out the time when you were
on Running Man half-heartedly.
That's right. That doesn't count.
You should count out
two and a half years.
- You never know how I feel.
- Three years should be excluded.
- How would you know how I felt?
- It should be excluded.
We should exclude 2 to 3 years
of his time. I know that.
We all know that because
you talked about it all the time.
- Sure.
- You know that.
Today's race is
all about your choices.
You will make your first choice
before we start a race.
- Please bring it in.
- What?
- Did it start already?
- I...
What is this?
What's this machine?
- What is it?
- Do we start it right away?
Today,
if you make a good choice,
you'll get a lot of money.
- I mean real money.
- Really?
You can make money in the race.
You will pick...
one of the two buttons you see
and press it.
If you press the green button,
you get 200 dollars right away.
- My gosh.
- It's either 100 or 50 percent.
But if you press the red button,
you will get
either 500 or 0 dollars.
(If they press the red button,
they get either 500 or 0 dollars.)
(Will you get 200 dollars
or go with a 50-percent chance?)
It's either 100 or 50 percent.
- This is hard.
- I'll go with a 100-percent chance.
My right hand is itchy.
I'll go with
a 50-percent chance for sure.
No, I will go with a safe option.
Those who want to choose
a safe option can try later.
I'll go with the safe one.
- A safe option?
- Let's go with a safe option.
(Suk Jin chooses the button first.)
Here I go.
Let's go.
(He has a 50 percent chance
of winning 500 dollars.)
What?
(Will he succeed in
his first challenge?)
This is it. It goes straight to...
- Yes!
- Nice. He gets nothing.
This is why you should go with
a safe option.
You failed.
Let's go with a safe option.
I can't believe this.
You always fail.
You should give it a try though.
You fail all the time.
All right.
- You know me, right?
- I do.
Obviously... Do you want
to try your luck?
- Of course I do.
- He tries his chance.
(Jae Suk tries
the 50-percent chance.)
- Really?
- It's going that way.
(Will he be able
to win 500 dollars?)
It's going well.
- Okay.
- He gets nothing as well.
(He failed and got 0 dollars.)
I guess we should
go with a safe option.
- Let's go with a safe option.
- We will just...
go with a safe option
to make things easy.
- I'll do that.
- Isn't it that it always fails?
It's a fight between these two.
Two people just failed,
so if you give it a try now,
- you are highly likely to win.
- That's right.
- I'll go next.
- Haha.
- Haha, you can win.
- Do you want to try?
- Will you take your chance?
- I'll give it a try.
- Seriously?
- The safe option...
Should I put it in here?
- Press it yourself.
- You want to press it?
I will press the button myself.
(The prankster couldn't wait,
so he pressed the button.)
(Two people just failed.
Where will Haha's ball go to?)
- I was going to press it.
- It's over for you.
I should press it.
I was going to press it.
I'm supposed to press it.
That doesn't count.
- I should do it myself.
- That doesn't matter.
- Don't be like that.
- It's over.
- Hey.
- I should do it.
- It's over.
- I should press it myself.
- Darn it! I have to press it.
- No, Haha.
I'm the one who makes the choice.
- No.
- It's fun this way, Dong Hoon.
- Get out of the way.
- I'll press it myself.
You should draw your eyebrows.
This doesn't feel right.
No. It's over.
It's hot today.
It's hot, so stay away from me.
- That was really fun.
- Who's next?
Those who want to take a chance
should go first.
Look.
Three people just failed.
Now it's time to succeed.
- I'm highly likely to win.
- You're right.
Why did you push the button?
(Haha really wanted
to press the button.)
- Darn it.
- No way.
(Failing 4 times in a row?
Or will Se Chan win as he expected?)
- Yes!
- We should do it again.
(Se Chan wins 500 dollars.)
Do it again. Haha pressed it.
- Why?
- Haha pressed it.
Jae Suk pressed the button
for you earlier.
- It just stopped.
- That counts.
Yes!
Good. We need winners as well.
- That's what makes it tempting.
- Nice.
We all should take our chances then.
For your information,
it's not for R coins.
- Do we get real money?
- Did I win 500 dollars?
Is it real money?
- So Min.
- That's right.
She's got carried away.
So Min's completely carried away.
(They just had a winner.
Will she win this time as well?)
Good, So Min.
So Min's completely carried away.
- That's right.
- Failed.
This is just right.
Failed.
(The tiger moth failed as expected.)
- I knew it.
- She's just like us.
I'll go with a safe option.
- Jeon So Min.
- Yes.
- It's safe.
- I was going to do that.
Did you choose
the safe option already?
I was going to choose
the safe option.
- Ji Hyo, you're up.
- That's how my life goes.
- I wanted to pick the safe option.
- Go with the red one.
You are quite lucky,
so you should give it a try.
Let's split it in half.
I'll give you 200 dollars.
- Give it a try.
- How would you do that?
With my money.
- You should take your chance.
- Pick what you want.
- Okay.
- You are lucky.
If she wins...
- If she wins...
- It's coming down.
(Will Ji Hyo be able
to win 500 dollars?)
- My gosh.
- It's coming down.
- Failed.
- Ji Hyo is not different.
- What's up with you these days?
- She's not lucky anymore.
(She's being unlucky these days.)
Jong Kook, we got 500 dollars
and 200 dollars. Okay.
- We can't win 500 dollars.
- You made it fail.
We didn't do it.
I don't think so.
Can I try it one more time?
When we tried, we won many times.
Really?
- That's not true.
- It's not working.
You should save money as I do.
- Look at that.
- I won.
- It only works for lucky guys.
- It works for lucky guys.
- I'm lucky.
- It just works for him.
You are meant to win.
This isn't a fake. It works.
What's wrong with me?
This is really strange.
- It's strange.
- Is someone controlling the ball?
It's so strange.
All right. Today,
you can make a lot of money
if you make a good choice.
During the race, you will keep
pressing one of these two buttons.
I should keep choosing 200 dollars.
The green button is
for a safe option.
And the red button is
for a risky option.
I'll go with an easy one.
- No, I'll take my chance.
- All right.
In August,
Jae Suk, Haha,
and Ji Hyo were born.
That's right.
It's the month that has
the most birthdays of our members.
For your parents who gave
birth to you and raised you,
we prepared the first
Protect Money For Your Parents Race.
- Is it for our parents?
- The money you win today...
is for your parents.
You can spend the money
on your parents.
(The money they win during the race
is for their parents.)
Just like you did earlier,
you will make choices...
to win money.
You will select a button
every 30 minutes...
and save your money
according to your choice.
You gain the amount of money
according to your choices.
But not all of you get a chance
to obtain money in every mission.
There will be 2 regular missions
and 2 hiding missions.
Only the person in last place...
will press
a different kind of button.
That is, six of you can get money
just as you did after every mission,
but the person in last place...
will press
a different kind of button.
- I guess we have to hide something.
- I feel at ease this way though.
After you change your clothes,
we'll begin the hiding mission.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
(It's all up to your choice.
Who will get the most money?)
(Se Chan, 500 dollars,
Jong Kook, 200 dollars,)
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Haha,
Ji Hyo, So Min, zero)
What's this?
So I'm supposed to hide this?
It's an 80cm-long piece of chalk
that you have to protect...
in order to get a chance
to choose a button.
What? Is this chalk?
Oh, my. I had no idea.
- Oh, is this chalk?
- Yes, it is.
It's so long. I have to hide this?
Each of you gets a different color.
And you're allowed to hide it.
Even if it breaks,
the length of the chalk you have
at the end decides the rankings.
(Protect your chalk for 30 minutes!
The length decides the rankings!)
(The owner of the shortest chalk
will be in last place,)
(and will be given
different choices of buttons.)
You can do anything you want
in the next 30 minutes...
- to protect your chalk.
- I see.
(Who will be the last place?)
Doesn't it stand out too much?
Why is it pink?
It's pink.
It's so big.
It's too long. It's 80cm long.
How will anyone find it there?
No one can find it.
Okay. I'm going to hide it here.
Behind this.
(While Big Nose hides his chalk
like he hides pocket money...)
I think it's not possible
to keep this intact.
It's better to break it
and hide the pieces.
If I can protect just this much...
Oh, gosh. I'll have a chance to win
if I protect just this much.
- Can I hide it outside?
- Yes.
I'm going to go outside
and hide it in the back.
(Se Chan plans to hide his chalk
far away from the starting point.)
Can you do that?
- Can you detach it?
- You mean the pole?
How do you set this up?
(He's trying to take off
the camera pole.)
Done. Give me a second.
(He successfully takes it off.)
This is awesome.
What a great idea.
If anyone finds this,
I'll be impressed.
I wonder if anyone else
came up with this idea.
I'm sure
no one will be able to find this.
(He became so smart
after 11 years on Running Man.)
(He's proud of himself.)
(While the king of petty tricks
feels proud of himself...)
I don't think anyone can find it
even if they come right now.
Oh, gosh. Jong Kook went outside.
- He's out there walking around.
- Oh, man.
Should I carry this with me
just like this?
(The chalk bandit roams around.)
(He's relaxed since he's at the top
of the food chain of Running Man.)
I think I can hide it
somewhere here.
But if I hide it in the bush...
(He hid his chalk
where anyone could easily find it.)
(He's satisfied with his decision.)
My gosh. He already came out. Hey.
(An annoying voice
reaches his ears.)
My friend who's going through
menopause is out here.
I said that's not true.
I guess
everyone else is staying inside.
We should go and find them.
Oh, we should go and find them.
I thought it wouldn't be fun
if I hid it too well.
So? "Come and find it if you can."
Is that what you're thinking?
No.
Well, I'll go
to the weakest man's place...
- Good.
- and crush his chalk.
- Shall we crush it?
- Yes.
I'm planning to crush it.
How about we break it into tiny bits
like what we used in school?
What? Hey.
Why are you carrying it around?
I'm going to run away
from the others.
(He's holding the large chalk
in his hand.)
- But that's too dangerous.
- It's too risky.
Please pretend you didn't see me.
- You see...
- You said you'd run.
But it's too dangerous.
- I ran out of time while hiding it.
- Hey.
You must think we can't see it...
since it's blue
like a chroma key background,
- but you're wrong.
- This is too dangerous.
You shouldn't just carry it around
like this.
It'll break so easily.
I'll be running away,
so please pretend you didn't see me.
- No, Jae Suk.
- You can't run away.
- You should know...
- This is...
- Please pretend you didn't see me.
- You made the decision.
- Hey, why would you...
- It'll break anyway.
- Exactly.
- I don't think it's a good idea.
- I know. Wait.
- This is a bad idea.
Please pretend... Don't take it...
Wait. Stop.
(Wait. Stop.)
Jong Kook, stop.
(It snapped.)
Hey, you had it coming.
You punk.
- I'll break it into pieces.
- Please stop it.
- You should...
- That's enough. Stop it.
- Write something with these.
- Stop it.
- Use these to write something.
- I said, enough.
You've done enough damage!
Use them to write something.
Why did you...
- I'm not even carrying mine around.
- Hey.
- I even hid mine.
- Why would you carry it around?
- Even I wouldn't do that.
- Why did you do that?
You've got some nerve.
That's exactly my point.
- Don't you know the rules?
- Why would you do that?
We're supposed to go around
with our chalks...
and get into brawls.
That's the point of this game.
- Why would you...
- You should have hidden this.
- Why did you bring it out?
- Even I hid mine.
It could break by accident
just by bumping into someone.
- You can keep only the biggest one.
- Hey.
- What's wrong with you?
- Gosh. I'm done for.
- The longest piece?
- Exactly.
Let me see. This one is the longest.
- Let me see.
- Is this one...
- Oh, I think it's the longest.
- Right.
Come on, guys.
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook
turn into a gangster duo.)
(They crushed his chalk.)
- Gosh, no.
- You shouldn't have...
- I mean why...
- Hey.
- I'm done for.
- Hey, you punk.
I'm going to find yours.
Where is Jae Suk's room?
Where is his room?
- Upstairs in this building?
- Downstairs.
Gosh, that punk. Seriously.
- Okay.
- I'll check upstairs.
I won't hide it here.
I'll hide it somewhere else.
(Meanwhile, So Min who decided to
keep one piece intact...)
Should I go down?
It's too obvious.
Is there any place I can hide it?
I'll measure the depth.
(The kitchen sink drain)
I think it'll be safe here.
Okay. I'm done.
(They won't be able to find it here,
right?)
Perfect.
This is Suk Jin's room, right?
Where did he hide it...
Oh, my. What's this?
(Big Nose's room)
(He's searching Big Nose's room
since he's known to be clumsy.)
I wonder where he hid it.
Is this Suk Jin's room?
Yes, this is Suk Jin's room.
There's so much stuff in his room.
I think someone's in my room.
(Running hastily)
Gosh. Why are there two of you here?
(Big Nose got so anxious
that he rushed in.)
Gosh. You came too?
(He seems suspicious.)
Of course I came.
Come on. I'm not that stupid.
I think you're looking at the place
you hid it unlike what you said.
No way. I would never do that.
(Suk Jin's entire body
exudes anxiety.)
I don't think he hid it
somewhere like this.
Suk Jin, you didn't see
what happened to Se Chan's, right?
(He keeps walking back and forth
with an awkward smile.)
Where did he hide it?
(But it's surprisingly hard
to find Suk Jin's chalk.)
Hey, no.
What's going on?
(Big Nose stopped him suddenly.)
- What's going on? Is it in there?
- Hey.
(The bandit is coming.)
- What's going on? Is it in there?
- Hey.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Don't do that.
- Where?
- It's in there.
- Here?
- Down there.
- You mean here?
- Check down there.
- Where?
- Is it there?
- I'll check.
- No.
- Oh, it's here. I found it.
- Where?
(Jae Suk's camera)
(He found the chalk.)
I found it.
(Actually, when Suk Jin hid it,)
(he was sure
that no one would find it.)
Okay. Good.
(He hid it with confidence.)
There's no way they will find it.
(Big Nose smiled happily,
feeling certain that he would win.)
No one will find this.
There's no way.
(He was so anxious that he ended up
revealing the location.)
(He practically told Jae Suk
just as he was about to give up.)
(He laughed weirdly
because he was embarrassed.)
Stop it.
Please stop.
(They start crushing his chalk.)
- Hey.
- How did you find this?
- Why did you hide it in there?
- I can't believe this.
(Hopeless)
How could you hide it in there
and walk around outside?
- My goodness.
- How did you find it?
Only the biggest piece
will be accepted.
- Oh, boy. Suk Jin.
- Darn.
It'll be hard to find
the biggest piece.
I might not have found it.
- He went in there to check.
- He practically confirmed it.
- All right. Who's next?
- Okay.
Gosh. I didn't know.
He seemed to have no idea
while looking in there.
Why did I do that?
Darn it.
You know, you can say...
that this is the type of game
that Jong Kook likes the most.
- This is so exciting.
- I know.
(Jong Kook's favorite game
where he can break things)
(Jae Suk runs into Ji Hyo
while looking for the next victim.)
Ji Hyo, where is your room?
I wonder where she hid hers.
Come on.
(Ji Hyo goes back into the room
after Jae Suk.)
I see that someone already came here
and searched everywhere.
(Jae Suk starts to search hastily.)
What is it, Ji Hyo?
Come on, Jae Suk.
Why?
(Ji Hyo can't seem to leave him.)
Let's not do this
when none of us has any money.
(Surprised)
It begins now.
I'm going to hide it in the closet.
(Right after the race began...)
Okay.
(Ji Hyo hid her chalk
inside the closet bar.)
Oh, dear.
I will keep you safe.
(She even talked to her chalk
while hiding it.)
You can't find my chalk.
(Frozen)
(Jae Suk gets closer to her chalk.)
(No way.)
(He looks inside the closet
for a long while...)
(but just turns away.)
Where did you hide it?
Do you think I'll tell you that?
You won't tell me, right?
Why are you still here, Ji Hyo?
- She keeps following me in here.
- Right.
- No, I followed you there too.
- Just in this room.
She followed me
only when I came in here.
- I went into that room too.
- Let's divide the areas to check.
- You check that side, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- It must be here. I'm sure of it.
- I bet it's here.
You can tell that
Ji Hyo is getting anxious, right?
I'm sure she didn't hide it
in such an obvious place, right?
Gosh. Where did she hide it?
(They're sure
that it's here, but...)
(Ji Hyo pretends to leave for now.)
Seeing how Ji Hyo followed me
in here...
Those punks.
- Jae Suk!
- What is it?
(Jae Suk!)
Where did you find it?
(Haha was searching
around the closet for a while.)
(He even starts searching
the closet bar.)
(Popping out)
(He's gone mad.)
- Jae Suk!
- What is it?
(He starts crushing the chalk.)
- Where did you find this?
- Stop.
(Ji Hyo's chalk has been crushed
like the others'.)
All right.
My goodness.
I can't believe I found it.
- Where did you find it?
- Amazing.
- Hey.
- Where was it?
She hid it inside the closet bar.
Only the longest piece
will be accepted.
Really?
(Only the longest piece
will be accepted.)
Good.
Fine. I'll go and find yours.
We're done here.
We got one.
Okay.
Let's find another one.
You have five minutes left.
Okay.
Finding their chalks is
the only way.
I have to make theirs
shorter than mine.
Gosh. I'm so angry.
Where did he hide it?
I wonder if mine is intact.
Let's go and see
if it's still there.
The fourth floor.
Was my place in this building?
Oh, I'm at the right place.
I heard you hid yours in the drain.
What?
(What?)
(Why am I hearing this from you?)
- I heard you hid it in the drain.
- Who?
Did someone find it?
- So Min...
- Did someone really find it?
- Did someone find it?
- Was hers crushed?
- Your chalk was crushed.
How did anyone find it?
- Hey.
- How did anyone find it?
- Haha found it.
- Hey.
We're all going crazy now.
- But how...
- I'm so...
It'd be funny
if I crush So Min's too.
(Earlier on, in So Min's room)
(Dream's father went crazy
after finding Ji Hyo's chalk.)
Where did she hide it?
I'm sure she hid it here somewhere.
(Dream's father went crazy
after finding Ji Hyo's chalk.)
(While searching every corner
from the toilet to the sink...)
(Surprised)
Oh, my. I can't believe this.
This is amazing.
(He found it!)
(The member who's been on the show
for 11 years pulled it off.)
(The Little Detective
is exhilarated.)
Oh, dear. That's another one gone.
(So Min's plan is destroyed
along with her chalk.)
So Min, I'm sorry,
but this is a game.
I hope you won't get too upset.
I got most excited
when I found a chalk in here.
Whose chalk did you find?
In the drain.
- Who?
- So Min hid hers in here.
I took it out with chopsticks
right away.
and crushed it into pieces.
How did he find it?
You have one minute left.
- Time's up.
- All right.
The game ended.
Good. It's still intact.
(Now they have to gather around
with their chalks.)
Please gather around
with your chalks.
But I cut it a little shorter.
Isn't it inside that pole?
I thought of checking it.
- I saw the pole when I came here.
- You see...
I give up.
- I can't be on Running Man anymore.
- Oh, dear.
- I mean it.
- My goodness.
- He hid it inside this pole.
- I don't think I can do this.
- Inside this pole?
- Haha.
You must not touch this.
- I saw the pole.
- Haha.
The chalk hiding mission ended.
Haha has the longest chalk, right?
- Yes.
- Haha kept his chalk intact.
- Jae Suk is in second place.
- Yes.
- Jong Kook came in third place.
(Jong Kook who broke his own chalk
while bringing it gets 3rd place.)
So Min is in fourth place.
There are three members left now.
- Who's in fifth place?
- Put your chalks on the table.
Ji Hyo, how long is yours?
- I think I'm in last place.
- Ji Hyo's might be shorter.
- It's obvious.
- Mine is as short as his.
- The two of them...
- Put it on the table.
- I mean...
- Ji Hyo, put yours on the table.
They crushed it.
Ji Hyo, put it here.
It's quite long.
- I think hers is... It's close.
- Oh, gosh.
- Move aside.
- Take a look.
- You have nothing to worry about.
- That's it.
(Seok Sam is in last place.)
(Big Nose's chalk is
exceptionally short.)
- We practically destroyed Suk Jin.
- My gosh.
- Seriously.
- Jong Kook and I found his.
- They found my chalk.
- Out of everyone?
Honestly, I didn't see the chalk,
- but Suk Jin suddenly came said,
- Exactly.
"How did you know it was here?"
- He went like this.
- It was hard to see.
- We couldn't see it.
- It seemed so.
- Besides, it was white.
- It was hard to see.
You thought it was a part
of the drawer, didn't you?
- That's right. We didn't know.
- Exactly.
- So I...
- What a shame.
- I was going to give up.
- It took me a while to find it.
- It took a long time.
- He should've stayed quiet.
Ji Hyo too. Whenever I went
into the room where she hid it...
- She was like, "Why?"
- Exactly.
- It showed their personalities.
- Indeed.
It's the second time
to make a choice.
Before we begin,
Suk Jin came in bottom place.
All of you except for Suk Jin...
will choose between the same buttons
as before.
If Suk Jin chooses the safe choice,
there will be no change.
But if he chooses
the daring choice...
- I bet he'll make a risky choice.
- He'll lose...
He'll either deduct 200 dollars...
- from everyone else's money...
- Go ahead and do that.
- or lose 200 dollars.
- Think about it.
- Do you think he'll play it safe?
- I bet he'll choose that.
- He would never do that.
- Never.
- He'll definitely take a risk.
- I wouldn't do that either.
- Great. He'll be like a tiger moth.
- My gosh.
- Let's do this.
- Should I get 200 dollars?
I'll choose it no matter what.
Should I go with the safe choice?
How much do I get...
- Hey, of course,
- Haha.
- you should choose the other one.
- Haha, you should take a risk.
Everyone, don't forget
that the money is for your parents.
- That's why I want to play safe.
- Haha.
Would your parents be happy...
if their son gives them
the money he got from gambling?
What is he saying?
You should give them
your hard-earned money.
- It says "Win" and "Fail".
- Don't you agree?
- With your hard-earned money...
- He may...
You shouldn't consider this
as gambling.
- You shouldn't.
- It's not gambling.
- Hey.
- Just go with this button.
- Go ahead.
- No.
- Okay.
- I hope he fails.
- I mean it wouldn't hurt.
(There's a 50 percent chance.)
(Will he win money this time
since he failed earlier?)
- Please. Fail.
- It's just an excuse.
- Fail.
- Oh, my. I think he'll get it.
- It wouldn't hurt.
I won!
Mother!
(Mother!)
(Safe, Win, Fail)
Gosh, this is annoying.
I made it!
Other people's success
is always annoying.
I'm annoyed. Gosh.
Father!
(The good son is celebrating alone.)
Haha won 500 dollars.
- Father!
- Next.
I've already made my decision.
Today, I won't even look
at this button.
(Today, I won't even consider
the safe choice.)
(He picked the daring choice.)
- Okay. He'll fail.
- I think he'll win.
(He pressed the button
with confidence.)
(He has a 50 percent chance
to win 500 dollars.)
- I'm sure he'll fail.
- Please fail.
Okay!
- Hold on.
- Okay!
It's weird.
Did you change something?
- It really is a 50 percent chance.
- That's right.
They failed before
and won this time.
- It really is a 50 percent chance.
- Next.
- Who came in third place?
- Jong Kook.
- Me?
- I'm so happy.
Since I picked the safe choice,
I'll have 400 dollars
if I make the same choice.
No way. Jong Kook won't press
the safe button.
Okay.
- He chose "Safe".
- Did he really press that button?
- Yes, I did.
- Next person.
I prefer this.
- So Min will definitely...
- Don't pretend to think about it.
- It's not like that.
We all know what you'll choose.
- I know you, So Min.
- To be honest,
I know that I'll likely fail again
since it's the same game...
and that I should press this button.
So Min. Do as you always do.
- That's right.
- We know you.
- It's coming down.
- Please.
- Fail.
Just as expected.
- I mean...
- It's not like that.
- Okay.
Ji Hyo, you're up.
- You should press the red button.
- Are you sure?
- Of course she chose that.
- Really?
- I think she'll win.
- It's moving toward "Fail".
(Could she restore her honor
as the lucky one?)
(Will she fail
as Suk Jin expected?)
(She won 500 dollars!)
- Did I win?
- I think...
It's broken.
- No, it's just...
- It's broken.
- Hey.
- It really is a 50 percent chance.
It's exactly a 50 percent chance.
Next up is the only person
who won 500 dollars earlier.
I'll get 2,500 dollars in total
if I win every time, right?
- Yes, you'll get 2,500 dollars.
- The thing about Se Chan is...
He gets lucky for trivial things.
- Not for important things.
- He really doesn't.
If you use up your good luck
for things like that,
- Does it bring bad luck?
- you don't get big success.
- That's nonsense.
- It's true.
- You should... Right.
- If you're lucky in trivial things,
- you don't get big success...
- Exactly.
- because you use up your good luck.
- That's right.
All right. Here we go.
(He chose the daring choice.)
Whatever he gets will be good
for him.
He always gets lucky
for trivial things like this.
(Will he get lucky this time too?)
- Please fall into "Fail".
- I think he'll fail.
- What's that?
- Hey, do it again.
Hey, you seemed to push it
toward the right side.
- That's right.
- We can't accept this.
- No. That's ridiculous.
- I'll explain.
- Director, please tell them.
- Let me explain.
The ball stayed on the right side
from the beginning.
- I'll do it for you.
- Right?
- He pushed it to the side.
- Yes.
- You shouldn't do that.
- You should put it in the middle.
Since when were you two so close
to each other?
It's not like that.
Listen, Se Chan.
It stayed on the right side.
- Jong Kook...
- It's not fun at all, you know.
- has been nice to me since Eun Hye.
- Come on.
(Jong Kook has been nice to me
since Eun Hye.)
(They're having a deep conversation
with their eyes.)
- It's true.
- They're talking with their eyes.
No, that's not true.
What are you talking about?
I was a fan of that show.
Why don't you play...
- rock-paper-scissors to decide it?
- Why rock-paper-scissors?
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
- Why must I play that game?
- Listen.
- Se Chan, listen. The ball fell...
- Let's do this.
You won't be allowed to complain
about it again.
- If I win, will you give up?
- Yes.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan won.)
Hey, did you say "Start" or not?
Gosh, you crazy punk.
(The petty guy bursts out in anger.)
(The youngest member finally got mad
as they kept joking around.)
- I won!
- I must say...
- I'm glad you swore at him.
- Right?
- He is...
- He's the most annoying one.
- Good job.
- Why did you act up before them?
By the way, you stopped
before saying swear words, right?
Yes, I did.
I was going to say harsher words.
Children watch this show too.
I'm sorry.
Right.
"I'm sorry."
I felt his true feelings.
Now, it's the bottom place's turn.
- Everyone else loses 200 dollars?
- Yes.
- Please. I don't care about mine.
- He chose the red button.
- I want them to lose 200 dollars.
- But many of us...
already won.
I can deduct 1,200 dollars
from what you guys have.
(The money they barely won is
in Suk Jin's hands.)
- Let's go.
- Press the button. Come on.
- What's wrong?
- You already made a wish...
What do you mean I made a wish?
- You were putting your energy...
- I just...
- into this box...
- Suk Jin, I'll give you a tip.
(They almost forgot the ritual.)
- I would never...
- Suk Jin.
- What is it?
- Do the slurp.
- The slurp.
- How about this?
- Open sesame!
- How about "Come here"?
- Slurp, munch, slurp.
- Not like that, Suk Jin.
- Then how?
- Charge yourself with energy.
- Yes, make it seem fun.
- Take the universe's energy!
- That's it.
- I'm jealous of you, you know.
- Why just me though?
- Let the sky...
- This is an important moment.
The energy from the sky...
and from the ground.
Take energy from here and there.
Yes, let me gather energy.
Give me energy!
Zap!
Did you just say the S word?
(You jerk!)
Did you just swear on camera?
- Why did you swear on camera?
- It was "zap".
You heard him too, right?
- Unbelievable.
- I said, "zap".
Are you kidding me?
- Why did you swear?
- Watch it, will you?
- What's wrong with you?
- It was "zap", everyone.
- Don't swear on camera.
- I'll take the energy from the sky.
- The sky.
- Right here.
- Gather the energy.
- Gather it all.
- Come to me.
- Do it up front.
- Let happiness and luck come to me.
- What now?
- Get the energy from Chan Hee.
- Come on.
- Come to me.
- Go to Chan Hee.
- Chan Hee, zoom in.
Zoom in. That's it.
Let me suck
200 dollars from them all.
- Pull the energy down.
- Pulling...
(He's met with reality.)
- He does everything that's asked.
- Yes, everything.
- Pull from further up.
- It's an automatic response.
Pull it from the sky.
- From up high as well.
- Exactly.
From up high.
- Pulling...
- Pull at a certain rhythm.
Stretch out your lats
and pull from higher up.
- Stretch!
- Stretching.
That's the spirit. Nicely done.
- Do it.
- Here I go!
- Nice.
- This attempt will count.
(If he makes it,
the others will lose 200 dollars.)
This attempt will count.
(If he makes it,
the others will lose 200 dollars.)
(Will luck come to Suk Jin?)
It's moving too much to the left.
(He made it!)
You all lose 200 dollars.
(Aside from Suk Jin,
the others lose 200 dollars.)
You all lose 200 dollars.
- Nice!
- Suk Jin's balance stays the same.
Let all the joy in life come my way.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
If your balance is below zero,
we'll deduct it from your paycheck.
What?
Anyway, this is
your current balance.
It'll be deducted from our paycheck?
- I'm at the top.
- 300 dollars.
Okay. 300 dollars isn't so bad.
- Now...
- Nice.
We'll now move on to the next game.
Which is what?
This next game is called...
Smelly Dodge Ball.
- It's dodge ball.
- Dodge ball?
You'll be playing a version...
where Ji Hyo and So Min
are the queens.
The game will consist
of three rounds...
and the teams will be changed up
after every round.
Those on the winning team
will all earn one point.
The one with
the least amount of points...
will press the loser button.
- It doesn't make sense though.
- Sorry?
Referees aren't allowed to compete.
(Jeon So Min,
expert referee for ball games)
(The whistle is blown instantly
whenever she plays a ball game.)
It'll be a game of 3 versus 3.
So Min's father used to play soccer,
- so her father...
- He's angry at me.
- So I've heard.
- Why?
He can't understand
why she's so bad at ball games.
"How can you be that bad
at foot volleyball?"
(Unlike her father,
she's terrible at ball games.)
But why is it called...
- Smelly Dodge Ball?
- What's the reason?
We have prepared
five smelly objects.
Out of 7 available cards,
5 will have them written on them...
while two will be blank.
The objects you choose...
will hang from your helmets.
- What?
- Really?
But I have a weak stomach!
- This is the worst.
- I have a weak stomach.
We can't hold our breaths
when playing dodge ball.
(Her frustration is at a maximum.)
Check out Ji Hyo's expression.
Ji Hyo wears her emotions
on her face.
(Anyone can tell
she's super annoyed.)
What's with your hair?
Are you entering a beauty pageant?
I thought she was
Dr. Oh Eun Young today.
(I thought she was
Dr. Oh Eun Young today.)
They must go to the same salon.
There's so much volume.
- That person's hairstyle?
- The parenting mentor?
- What's with your hair today?
- I blame my hands.
You'll now choose the teams
for the first round.
Play rock-paper-scissors...
- and choose a teammate.
- Do they get to choose?
The one who wins
at rock-paper-scissors...
will have one more teammate.
That's a good thing.
You'll have more members.
I can already smell something!
I can already smell something.
- What?
- No way.
Hold on. I smell fermented skate.
But I have a weak stomach.
- It's strong.
- Too strong.
It's too strong.
Is it dung?
- I smell the skate too.
- Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min wins.)
Please choose a teammate.
You'll then go in turns.
(So Min chooses first.)
(They avoid her gaze for now.)
To make a ball game look funny,
I need Jong Kook.
- To make it look funny?
- He had his back turned.
Come on, Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo, please choose.
- I choose Jae Suk.
- Okay!
So Min, you're up.
This is where it gets hard.
- Why?
- You're at a crossroad.
Absolutely.
You're all pretty much the same.
Haha, why don't you want
to be on my team?
What do you mean?
- I choose Haha.
- Why?
Okay. Ji Hyo, you're up.
Play rock-paper-scissors again.
- Why?
- It's her turn to choose.
- She gets to choose.
- They're now taking turns.
Ji Hyo, go ahead and choose.
- Don't they need to play it again?
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- I choose Se Chan.
- Okay!
(She chooses Se Chan.)
- Nice!
- Suk Jin will be on So Min's team.
This will be a tough battle then.
But we have one more person.
- You're bad at dodge ball though.
- We have one more person.
- No, I'm good at it.
- It's fine.
We just have to avoid
having the least points.
It's all about
making the right choice.
Gosh, the smell.
My gosh, the smell.
On the 7 cards in front of you,
5 have objects that smell...
while the other two don't.
- Should we just choose?
- Yes, go ahead.
Go ahead.
- All right.
- Good.
Let's reveal it one by one.
- Sure. In 1, 2.
- Jae Suk, you go first.
In 1, 2.
What is it?
- Fermented cheese.
- What?
(Smelly fermented cheese)
- It's not bad.
- Cheese isn't so bad.
It's not so bad.
- It's not so bad.
- Is it one of the nicer ones?
- Why is it that...
- What's with you today?
- I have luck in trivial things?
- His is blank.
But what I need
is one big lucky event.
Ji Hyo?
I have durian.
- Oh, no.
- That's the worst.
So Min, you're next.
- That's not bad.
- Onions and garlic.
- It's not bad.
- That's a nicer one.
- That's a good one.
But they will make my eyes water.
Isn't mine better?
(The next...)
Hers is better compared to mine.
I chose skate.
That's a strong one.
It's the worst.
Nice!
What can be worse than skate?
- What on earth...
- What is it?
I chose Se Chan's sock.
- I chose Se Chan's sock.
(Where did
Se Chan's sock come from?)
(The secret weapon: Se Chan's sock)
His feet stink!
(Why did Se Chan's sock
make the list?)
(Episode 538 of Running Man)
(Someone's stinky feet
invaded the quiz.)
(The head director led the search.)
(Darn it!)
(Se Chan was caught red-handed.)
(They were able
to pinpoint the source.)
(He made many staff members
lose their sense of smell.)
(He became known as Sour Feet.)
His feet stink!
Darn it.
- All right.
- Let me...
I'll let it ripen more.
- Se Chan, over here.
- Yes?
- Jump!
(Sour Feet makes his feet
smell worse for Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin, today's a bad day for you.
- Jump!
- Today's a bad day for you.
- It's the worst.
- Tell me about it.
Se Chan, please let us
have your socks.
They will be better
if they're a little damp.
You should've given me a heads up.
It's starting to smell a little.
I can't believe it.
We're getting his socks
fresh from the source.
Skate is better.
At least it's edible.
All right.
My gosh, the smell!
(And finally...)
That could touch your faces.
Gosh, they stink.
(Se Chan's socks are added
to the already smelly lineup.)
Se Chan's socks
are better than the rest.
(So Min has onions and garlic.)
- Oh, no.
- Go ahead.
- What's this?
- They smell awful.
I didn't expect them
to be this strong.
(Fermented cheese
hangs from Jae Suk's helmet.)
Darn it!
(Darn it!)
Hey.
It'll touch my face!
Darn it.
The skate stinks.
(The scent of ammonia
has him groaning.)
It might touch my face.
Is this how it's supposed to be?
Now...
It touches my face.
(Ji Hyo who has durian
refuses to breathe.)
Please wear your cap backwards.
(There's one person
who has no choice.)
My socks shouldn't be in a net.
Darn it!
This is the worst feeling ever!
- Darn it!
- He has my socks.
(Suk Jin has my socks.)
This is so gross!
(The sour smell stings his nose.)
My socks are nearly touching
Suk Jin's lips.
Darn these socks!
(The sour socks
hit him in the nose.)
Forget the smell.
The socks hit me on the lips.
I'm sorry about this.
You shouldn't have picked my socks.
- Darn it.
- I can't do this either.
My feet are
on the smelly side today.
Let's get this game over quickly.
Yes, let's.
Darn it!
(The fermented cheese
isn't any better.)
Just how bad is it? Let me see.
Check this out.
The cheese is one of the worst ones.
(The staff chose the cheese
to be the worst.)
Smell mine as well.
It's like a smelly belly button.
Smell mine.
Darn it!
- My gosh.
- Hey...
It's the smell of
an elementary school restroom.
I'm sorry, but I can't protect you.
I won't today.
This couldn't be more annoying.
(He's almost in tears.)
Darn it!
One male member from each team...
may play from outside the lines.
I'll stand outside the lines.
- Haha, protect So Min.
- Sure.
Darn it!
(Forget the dodge ball.
They groan from all over the court.)
The male members
can't be eliminated in any way.
The game ends
when the women are eliminated.
I just ate some!
(Because of his protruding teeth,
he's forced to eat a bite.)
- It's in my nose.
- This is too damp.
I keep eating the durian.
This stings my eyes.
(The onions and garlic
sting the eyes.)
Play like this.
I'll end up with a sore neck.
Look.
I keep...
I keep kissing it.
Ready.
Get set.
(Game on!)
(Team So Min attacks first.)
- You punk!
- No!
(Jong Kook misses the ball.)
Oh, right. I need to block his ball.
(He forgot what he was supposed
to do.)
- This is so annoying.
- You should catch the ball.
- Darn it.
- Block the ball.
- Gosh, it stinks!
- Darn it.
(Se Chan's stinky socks
keep touching Suk Jin's lips.)
I'll pass it to you.
All right. Hey.
(The socks are still hanging
in front of his mouth.)
- Stay behind me.
- This is so annoying.
(The ball is back to Team So Min.)
(His face muscles keep flinching.)
Bring it on.
Pass it to me.
- Darn it.
- All right, I blocked it.
All right.
I'm going to kick you if you
come close. Don't come near me.
(The man with fermented skate
became weak because of the stench.)
Get ready to turn, Ji Hyo.
(Right then!)
- All right. She's out.
- She's out.
Get ready to turn, Ji Hyo.
(He succeeds in the sneak attack.)
(The ball precisely hit her leg.)
- She got hit.
- All right! She got hit.
Everyone on this team
got one point each.
Gosh, I should take it off.
We'll proceed to the second round
right away.
Pick the team members
and the button again.
This is really annoying.
(Picking team members for Round 2)
Gosh, it stinks!
Are you going to keep
using my socks?
- The smell is too strong.
- Yes.
All right. So Min and Ji Hyo,
play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
- It's better to win.
I...
I'm pretty good.
You saw me play, right?
I pick Jae Suk.
All right.
I pick Haha.
What?
(So Min only picks Haha.)
Why? What's wrong?
- I pick Se Chan.
- Okay.
Next.
Jong Kook and Suk Jin
are remaining.
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook and Suk Jin
are remaining.
(Big Nose doesn't get picked.)
Suk Jin will join the other team.
This feels so lousy.
Of course I should pick Jong Kook.
- How could you?
- What's wrong?
I kissed Se Chan's socks
about 20 times already.
- Let's do this!
- Let's go!
Put your hands together.
- Let's win this.
- Yes.
- Let's do this!
- Let's go!
- Take one.
Just wait and see.
Take one.
- Let's open on the count of three.
- Take one.
You should all take one
at the same time.
Please... I just hope
it won't be Se Chan's socks.
I'd hate to have Se Chan's socks.
- Wait.
- You're not going to hang anything.
(This time, Jae Suk got lucky.)
- What did you get?
- Look!
(So Min passed.)
- I think it's fermented skate.
- I got durian.
How is durian?
(I got fermented skate.)
I got cured cheese.
I got onions.
It's not bad.
It's better.
(Then the only one remaining,
Ji Hyo...)
(She got Se Chan's socks.)
I got Se Chan's socks!
(Jae Suk smells Se Chan's socks.)
Gosh, this is...
(He only smelled them for a second.)
(He's already shocked.)
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
Is this smell from your socks?
- They smell really weird.
- They ruined your mood, right?
What is it?
The smells are mixed.
- They are, aren't they?
- Wait a minute.
- Yes, they are.
- Goodness!
Hey.
This can't be from your socks.
(The socks are ripened to the point
where they seem rotten.)
No way.
This isn't the smell, right?
You put something on them, right?
Gosh, I think I might throw up.
It's killing me.
Smell it. I'm not kidding.
It's crazy.
Smell it.
Just once.
Try smelling it.
Why would you scream
when you came up with this?
Gosh, this is...
Goodness, this is
too close to my face!
The smell is too strong!
(They can't get used to
the unique smells.)
- Gosh.
- How does the cheese smell?
Jae Suk, this isn't right.
I told you.
(He's about to pass out.)
Guys, look at Ji Hyo. Poor her.
Poor Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, we need to win this time.
- Jae Suk...
- We really need to win this time.
- I'll throw the ball.
- Let's do this.
I'll try hitting her.
Let's start.
- Let's start.
- Gosh, it stinks.
(The game starts.)
(Jae Suk passes the ball
to Se Chan for now.)
(Throwing up)
(The smell of the fungi doesn't
allow him to receive the ball.)
Jae Suk...
It's horrible.
(The man who got cheese
in the 1st round can relate to him.)
The smell gets strong
when it comes close to my face.
Jae Suk, here.
- Hey!
(The fungi boy hands the ball
over to Jong Kook.)
We got this.
- Are you going to throw it?
- Yes.
You should throw it.
Suk Jin, you can't hide behind me!
(Suk Jin forgot
what he's supposed to do again.)
(Jae Suk blocked the ball
with his face.)
Why you...
Suk Jin, you should come
in front of me.
(The onion man
is practically useless.)
(It's Jae Suk's turn to attack.)
(Going here...)
(and there)
(The players with no helmet on
are the only excited ones.)
- Hurry up!
- Stay close to me.
- Hey!
It stinks! Darn it!
(Mischievous Jae Suk is
into playing a nimble player.)
Oh, no! It touched my face! Darn it!
No! Se Chan's socks touched my lips!
(Horrifying)
- Throw the ball!
- Se Chan's socks touched my lips!
I'm dizzy now.
(Mischievous Jae Suk
finally passes the ball.)
- They touched my lips!
- Darn it.
(They besiege Jong Kook
and So Min by passing the ball.)
(On hair-trigger alert)
(Throwing up)
Hurry up and end this round!
Just surrender to them.
- I'm dizzy.
- This is killing me!
(They tease Jong Kook
with quick passes.)
(So Min ends up getting eliminated.)
- All right. She got hit.
- I got hit.
You did?
(Team Ji Hyo wins the 2nd round.)
Everyone on this team
got one point each.
(Ji Hyo, Jae Suk, Se Chan,
and Suk Jin got 1 point each.)
The cheese is...
Here's the result.
(The result after playing 3 rounds)
Se Chan is on the bottom,
and the rest of you
get a chance to make money.
- We're going to get more money.
- Bring in the buttons.
- I'll pick the safe one this time.
- Me too.
Everyone, time to make
your third choice.
The options are the same as before.
Is Suk Jin going first?
Who's going first?
They said anyone can go first.
They said I should go first.
Suk Jin, go ahead.
Suk Jin will take the risk.
He'll take the risk.
- You can pick one now.
- Suk Jin will take the risk.
- Of course.
- He'll take the risk.
(He chose to take his chance.)
- I hope he fails.
- Go!
It's going in the right direction!
(Go! It's going
in the right direction!)
You failed.
(Fail)
(With a sudden twist toward
the end, it went straight to fail.)
He said it was going
in the right direction.
Nice! That was the right direction.
- Next, Jong Kook.
- It's really strange.
It's my turn? You know me.
- Will you take the safe one again?
- Can you give it a try this once?
- I'll pick...
- I'm so sick of him.
- I'm so sick of you.
- This is boring.
He only picks the safe one.
Safety first.
- Next, Haha.
- Haha?
- You failed twice and won once.
- It's me?
- He chose the safe one too.
- All right!
- Let's go!
- That's so sneaky of you.
- He's so annoying. I know.
- He's always like that.
He's just...
He's so annoying. I can't take it.
That's so dirty.
So Min, you can go next.
- Put the ball in.
- You failed twice and won once.
- All right!
(Jae Suk and Ji Hyo
both try their chances.)
Fail! No!
- Thank goodness.
- Yes!
It's Se Chan's turn now.
Since I won some money,
I'll try my luck for sure.
- That's for sure.
- Right.
- Se Chan should...
- No, mine will go negative.
- Please don't do this.
- I have nothing.
If I press this, everyone except me
will lose 200 dollars.
You'll lose 200 dollars alone.
Please...
- I'm...
- You won a lot of times.
I'm lucky with little things.
- Fail.
- I'm lucky with little things.
(The man who's lucky
with little things gives it a go.)
I'm lucky with little things.
(Will Se Chan be the only one
to lose money?)
(Or will everyone else
suffer a loss?)
(The man who's lucky
with little things, Se Chan)
(How will it turn out?)
- I'm lucky with little things!
- He made it!
There you go!
(Se Chan succeeds in his challenge.)
I'm the man
who's lucky with little things!
Everyone will lose 200 dollars.
All right!
Jae Suk has 600 dollars.
Haha has 300 dollars.
Jong Kook has 200 dollars.
Ji Hyo has 100 dollars.
So Min has 100 dollars.
Suk Jin has minus 200 dollars.
All right!
Now let's move to have lunch.
- All right!
- Yes!
Guys, you must be hungry.
- Yes, we are.
- Yes, I'm starving.
Today's lunch menu...
will be decided by your choice.
This time, you'll also choose
one button...
just like you did earlier.
I should go with the safe option
for food.
The safe button...
will provide basic side dishes
and rice.
Two pieces of ham? It's not bad.
I like fried eggs and ham.
Those side dishes are good.
For the red button, if you succeed,
you'll get marinated grilled duck
and chicken and seafood soup.
They sound delicious.
It's too tempting
to have the duck and soup.
If you fail, you'll get rice
and stir-fried gochujang.
I'm so torn.
- I love the duck dish.
- I'm torn by the soup.
It's about time
to consume some protein.
- I must have the soup.
- I'm going to take the chance.
- I'll give it a try.
- I'll give it a try anyway.
That's right.
Let's just give it a try.
The lucky ones will always be lucky.
(Fail: Se Chan, Haha,
Suk Jin, Jae Suk)
Yes!
Let's have some duck.
I think we can eat it.
(High-protein chicken
and seafood soup...)
(and marinated grilled duck
that invigorate you)
We can eat it right away.
Perfect timing. It's about time
to take in some protein.
It's so good.
- You guys are so mean.
- You're not giving us dried laver?
(The four who failed get only rice
and stir-fried gochujang.)
Are you serious?
- You knew the options.
- Give us dried laver, at least.
You should give us dried laver,
at least.
- It was your choice.
- You punk. Dried laver...
You guys, don't be so mean.
Give us the fried egg and ham.
Why didn't you succeed then?
- What?
- Why didn't you succeed then?
"Why didn't you succeed then"?
("Why didn't you succeed then"?)
(He yells at Jong Kook.)
- Wow, Jae Suk.
- Jong Kook.
(He yelled without thinking
of the consequences.)
Don't get on his nerves.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- Jong Kook...
(Flustered)
(Don't get on his nerves.)
He was about to open his mind.
Why did you yell at him?
So Min, I'll give you 20 dollars
for a fried egg and ham.
- If he pays 20 dollars...
- Good idea.
- I'll give you 20 dollars each.
- What do you think?
Let's make him pay 30 dollars
and divide it among us.
She lowered the price for you.
She will give them to you
for 30 dollars.
Okay. I'll give you
ten dollars each.
- You can have it.
- Okay, ten dollars each.
I'll give them ten dollars each.
I'll also give you ten dollars each.
Then Jae Suk will also pay
30 dollars.
- I'll pay 30 dollars for it.
- I got 20 dollars.
- Why did you give it to him?
Me too.
Jae Suk, it's really good.
I know. With these,
we can enjoy our lunch.
Let me try a piece.
- How much?
- Let me have some.
(Haha brazenly tries
to take Jae Suk's ham.)
- You...
- Just let me have a piece.
- You should pay me three dollars.
- That's nonsense.
Give back my 20 dollars.
Did you hear what Jae Suk said?
When I tried to take this,
he told me to pay him three dollars.
- "Pay me three dollars."
- I need to make some money too.
How much is this again?
This is 100 dollars.
Ji Hyo, isn't the duck dish
60 dollars?
It's 60 dollars.
Come on, that's too little.
- We're giving you a lot.
- Here's your 30 dollars.
- Wait.
Haha...
Wait. Haha ate mine.
- How could you?
- What?
Where did my fried egg go?
(Se Chan's fried egg is missing.)
- Don't do this to me.
- What are you talking about?
- You should pay for it.
- This is absurd.
What are you talking about?
You stole my egg.
(The precious egg he paid 30 dollars
for disappeared in an instant.)
- How could you?
- I didn't take it.
Or...
Did you take my fried egg?
No, I didn't. It's mine.
I swear I didn't take it.
Then who took my egg?
Gosh, this is annoying.
How could you steal it?
You stole the side dish
from my poor meal.
(You stole the side dish
from my poor meal.)
(The petty thief who even steals
rice from the poor meal is...)
- Yes! It's ten dollars each.
- How much is that?
(He quickly and skillfully
steals Se Chan's egg.)
(Playing innocent)
(Startled)
Could you give me just one ladle
of soup?
- One ladle?
- Yes.
- Can't you just give us some?
- Here's one ladle of it.
- That's enough.
- Can I try a wrap?
No, that's not allowed.
(He returns happily
after getting some soup.)
- Who took my ham?
- Give me some too.
(This time,
Jae Suk's ham is missing.)
- Hey.
- Hold on.
- This is ten dollars?
- Where did my ham go?
- This is...
- Hey!
- When he takes his eyes off it...
Me? Is he calling me?
- Is he calling me?
- No idea.
Where did my ham go?
- It's five dollars.
- He didn't call me.
Hey!
(Serious)
- Hey.
- Can I join your table?
- Hey, was it you?
- You need to get her permission.
I told you it wasn't me.
- Was it you?
- Why would I steal it...
when I know I'll be busted?
Look at him. Check his pockets.
(The real culprit Jae Suk
is desperately looking for...)
(While Jae Suk went to beg
for some soup...)
(Stealing his ham
at the speed of light)
(He doesn't care for his teammate.
He's an expert on stealing food.)
Gosh, this is frustrating.
You stole it, right?
- You're just...
- Haha is...
Don't you even have
respect for yourself?
No.
Let me tell you something
while you're eating.
You'll hide something
in the next mission.
- But you won't be hiding chalk.
- Then what is it?
It'll be a team game.
You'll be divided into teams of 2,
and 1 will play alone.
Teams of 2 and 1 plays alone?
- Let's pick our partners then.
- Okay.
All right! I got Jong Kook.
- Yes! I got Se Chan!
- This is nice!
What's this? Is it water?
It's water in a bucket?
- What is it?
- The object you'll hide...
in this round...
is slime, also known as
a liquid monster.
How are we supposed to hide this?
- We need to hide this?
- Yes.
- It's a team game?
- This is driving me crazy.
We might spill it.
It looks like sticky rice cake.
How do we get rid of this?
How do we throw this away?
- Other teams'...
- You can hide or destroy...
other teams' slime.
You can steal theirs
and stick them on yours.
- We should take theirs.
- We should.
And we shouldn't let them take ours.
It's more important
to keep ours intact.
What's this? Is this it?
- Yes, this is it.
- This rice cake?
(What's this? Is this it?)
Do we take others' slime?
It's slime. Try touching it.
- Oh, I see.
- Doesn't it feel nice?
It can stretch.
I thought it was rice cake.
So we take other's slime?
Hey, shall we make some noodles?
Do you know how to make
hand-pulled noodles?
This is how you do it.
(This is how you do it.)
So you've seen a few things.
Oh, gosh.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep causing trouble?
- Goodness. Oh, gosh.
- Be careful.
(They should come up with a plan
to guard their slime now.)
Suk Jin.
(They should come up with a plan
to guard their slime now.)
- This is...
- Put it in your cap.
Does it look like a scarf?
Or a liquid monster?
You should put this much
in your cap.
But it's so obvious, right?
(Screaming)
- Can you get this off me?
- Hey.
Hey, you're in trouble.
- What?
- This is... How do I get it off?
I think you should cut your hair.
- Wait. I'll put it in the water.
- You're in trouble.
- My goodness.
- You're seriously...
What are you doing?
You're in trouble. What do we do?
Put this in the water.
- Wait. I'll go wash it off inside.
- It won't work.
- Hold on.
- My goodness.
I didn't know it'd get stuck
like that.
Don't come in.
- This is unbelievable.
- My goodness.
(With a big sigh, he struggles to
get it off inside the restroom.)
How come it doesn't come off?
- My gosh.
- Are you done?
Sorry?
Did it come off?
(He shyly comes back
after washing his hair.)
Let me see.
I knew you were going overboard.
You're so mischievous.
Goodness. Did you see this, kids?
Don't put slime in your hair.
Shall we hide the whole thing?
Shall we hide it
in our cameraman's case?
I did earlier,
and I didn't get caught.
(They're thinking of hiding it
inside the staff's case.)
Goodness, it's huge.
(Approaching the camera case
with their slime)
Oh, no. I'm in trouble.
It's stuck.
(A slime disaster)
(Ji Hyo is packing the slime
in a plastic bag.)
Oh, no. Ji Hyo...
(So Min calls Ji Hyo
in a timid tone.)
- What?
- I didn't mean to...
I didn't know it'd get stuck.
I told you to put it in a bag.
- I...
- Hey.
(She became one with the slime.)
I really didn't know.
Come here.
Goodness,
you're one troublesome girl.
- I can't believe it.
- What do we do?
Okay.
- I don't think they'll open it.
- Suk Jin.
No one would use
that elevator, would they?
Right?
We'll start now.
Hold on.
(Jae Suk found an elevator
right before the start.)
Suk Jin, let's hide it here.
- Let's put it here.
- Like this.
(Concealing their slime
with a bucket and a rag)
Let's make it look like
someone is cleaning it. Hold on.
(Let's make it look like
someone is cleaning it. Hold on.)
I think it's a really good idea.
(Perfectly concealing the slime
with the cleaning supplies)
- Here.
- Like this?
- This is amazing.
- Let's go.
They wouldn't open that.
They wouldn't use the elevator.
(Haha, who's playing it alone,)
(tries to throw the whole thing
out the window.)
I'll pick it up later.
I'll use a stick to pick it up.
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going? I'm going to
hide it in your bag. What's wrong?
I'll leave some here.
(Putting a bit of their slime
in the cameraman's bag)
(She hides
the rest of their slime...)
(behind the staff.)
Please. I beg you.
Please don't make it obvious.
(So Min's strategy is to hide it
using many staff members.)
We'll start the mission now.
(Mission starts.)
- My phone...
- Leave the phone here.
- Are you done hiding yours?
- Gosh, you startled me.
- Are you done?
- What is it?
- I mean...
- Why did you run over here?
- I heard you washed your hair.
Because it got stuck in your hair.
Did the word spread already?
- Yes.
- I heard you washed your hair.
Is that yours? So that's yours.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
Where did you hide it?
Wait a minute. This is...
- What's this on your back?
- What?
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, come over here.
- What?
Suk Jin, your slime is melting.
- What are you doing?
- Show me your back.
- What?
- What is this?
Gosh, you should just take it off.
That was hilarious.
- I can mix it with mine, right?
- Yes, you can.
It's important to have ours intact.
(Ji Hyo plans to guard the spot
where she hid her slime.)
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
(Ji Hyo, what are you doing?)
(Jae Suk came to find Ji Hyo
like a demon.)
What is it?
You're on this team?
You hid it here?
Here? No, I came to find something.
I'm looking for other teams' slime.
Gosh, it's hot.
(The spot where Ji Hyo
walked past...)
(is where So Min hid her slime.)
You just got out of here?
(Jae Suk already knows
Ji Hyo's habit.)
It's hard to find one.
(He thoroughly looks for slime
in nearby objects.)
It's not here.
It's sliding down. Wait.
Hold on.
Did you drop something?
- Wait.
- Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk ends up finding
the slime So Min hid.)
Why did you have to find this?
- It's ours!
- It's sliding down.
(The cameraman runs away.)
What's this? It's running down
from the bag.
(He found plenty of slimes.)
Jae Suk! Give it to me.
Give it back!
(Give it back!)
Give it to me...
(He meticulously collects the slime
the cameraman took off.)
Why did you give it to him?
You should've given it to me!
Darn it! Why did you give it to him?
(The slime owner is sad
to lose even 1g of slime.)
What's going on?
- So Min.
- What's going on?
- Where did it go?
- What happened?
- It slid down.
- Hey! Where did my slime go?
Yours slid down the bag.
I could save only this bit.
You promised to guard it.
You promised... I'm so sorry.
- So Min...
- I'm sorry.
You put him in trouble.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I caused all this mess.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was that hard
to take it off.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I feel so bad.
(Ji Hyo and So Min
lost a lot of their slime.)
Time over.
As a result.
Ji Hyo and So Min
are in the bottom place.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Either one of you
will be in the bottom place.
The cameraman was sitting on it,
and it ran down the chair.
(Jae Suk shares the details
of the story.)
Really?
- You two are at the bottom.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- That's right.
- Ji Hyo is in the bottom place.
- Don't talk to me.
- Bring in the buttons.
So Min, could you move?
(He's bringing another button?)
How come there are two?
What's this?
(What is it?)
- There's "Lucky".
- There is?
What does "Vague" mean?
Everyone, we have another button.
- Yes.
- What's this?
This will put you to the test.
We added another button.
From now, you'll have a blue button
where you can go for "Lucky".
If you choose the blue button,
you'll get 1,000 dollars
if the ball ends up in "Lucky".
We'll get 1,000 dollars?
(Lucky, Vague, and Unlucky)
If you get Vague,
you will get 100 dollars...
and other people will get
200 dollars.
- Vague would be nice for us.
- I know.
- Jae Suk, thank you in advance.
- I hope people get Vague.
- What happens if you get Vague?
- If you get Unlucky,
only you will lose 300 dollars.
My goodness.
You could lose 300 dollars.
If you lose that much...
- Let's see how it goes.
- Shall I go first?
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- I will press the blue button.
- Let's go.
It will be good for you
if I get Vague.
- Let's go.
- For everyone else, 200 dollars.
In 1, 2.
(Lucky, Vague, and Unlucky)
- I hope he gets Vague.
- I hope I get Lucky.
- Vague.
- Go.
Vague.
- Turn.
- Vague.
- Please let him get Vague.
- Turn.
(Se Chan hopes for Lucky
and everyone else hopes for Vague.)
- Turn.
- Vague.
- Gosh.
- Unlucky.
(Se Chan loses 300 dollars.)
- Hold on.
- He should have gotten Vague.
This is driving me crazy.
- I am so annoyed.
- Gosh.
Se Chan went first and got Unlucky.
- I don't want to take chances.
- I can't press the blue button.
Are you scared?
- You won't be at the bottom.
- With Vague, you get 100 dollars.
Do you want to go first?
- Go first.
- Okay. I will go.
- It's an individual match...
- Go.
- anyway.
- I don't like this color.
I will use a red one.
(He chooses the blue button
with hopes for Lucky.)
- I need this.
- With Lucky, you win 1,000 dollars.
- I am at minus 210 dollars.
- I want to see someone get Lucky.
- I need this.
- He is at minus 210 dollars.
I really need this.
- He needs Lucky.
- I am at minus 210 dollars.
- Go.
- I will get it.
Let's go.
No, don't go there.
(Will he turn the tables
with Lucky?)
- I need to start over.
- Okay.
(In reality, he's always unlucky.)
- I need to start over.
- No.
- You are done.
No.
- I need to start over.
- Unlucky.
Unlucky.
- I need to start over.
- All right.
It can't be helped.
So Min.
Let me remind you
that there are other two buttons.
Come on.
Come on. Go with the blue button.
There you go. That's So Min.
So Min, that's good.
- Lucky. Vague.
- Vague.
- Nice.
- Nice. 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars.
(So Min gets 100 dollars
and everyone else gets 200 dollars.)
- Okay.
- 200 dollars.
Do I get 200 dollars as well?
Then it's minus 310 dollars.
I will be set
if people get Vague two times.
Okay.
All right. I will go next.
I think he will get Lucky.
- Vague.
- Let's get Lucky.
- I think he will get Lucky.
- Let's surprise the world.
Go. It's out. He will get Lucky.
- Come on.
- He will get Lucky.
(Is the ball heading towards Lucky?)
- Vague.
Lucky.
(He gets Lucky.)
(He gets 1,000 dollars.)
He got 1,000 dollars.
- He is so lucky.
- He got 1,000 dollars.
(The former unlucky member
got his big break.)
That came out of nowhere.
How much will he get today?
- No way.
- This is driving me crazy.
He got 1,000 dollars.
Is this even possible?
All right. Next.
- You are cool.
- He got Lucky with a yellow ball.
- I used a yellow ball earlier.
- A red ball.
Give it to me.
Let me use a yellow ball.
(This won't do.)
- Use a yellow ball.
- He got Lucky with a yellow ball.
Is no one going to choose
the safe option?
(He erased the safe option
from his brain.)
You should strive to get Lucky.
Press it short and hard.
How did you get Lucky?
- There you go.
- Let's go.
- Vague.
- That's good.
- He did it.
- Lucky.
- Vague.
- That's good.
- For goodness' sake.
(We got 200 dollars.)
- All right.
- Okay.
Let's make money
without doing anything.
I will be set
if one more person gets Vague.
(Haha benefited the others.)
- You haven't gone yet.
- Who hasn't gone yet?
- Me.
- Jong Kook, go ahead.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Hey.
(He chooses the safe option
4 times in a row.)
Come on.
- What?
- Okay.
- I can't believe you pressed it.
Live life like Kim Jong Kook!
- What was that?
- I can't believe you pressed it.
- It wasn't even the red button.
- It makes no sense.
I made a lot of money
without doing anything.
You didn't even agonize over it.
I don't agonize over things.
I am on a smooth sail.
- How much do you have?
- I have 820 dollars.
I have 820 dollars.
- You only chose the safe option.
- Yes.
Okay.
- Ji Hyo, you are last.
- Ji Hyo.
You are at the bottom.
If you get Lucky,
you can steal 300 dollars
from a member of your choice.
If you get Vague,
three members including yourself
must pay 100 dollars.
If you Unlucky,
you must give 300 dollars
to a member of your choice.
(Lucky, Vague, and Unlucky)
Understood?
You either win 300 dollars...
- or lose money.
- Ji Hyo.
Making everyone else lose
200 dollars isn't half bad.
It's 300 dollars versus 200 dollars.
Aren't the chances better
for 200 dollars?
I will go for 200 dollars.
(She chooses the 50-percent chance.)
If you get Failure...
- She will get Success.
- I think she will get Success.
I think she will get Success.
(Who will lose 200 dollars,
everyone else or Ji Hyo?)
- Failure.
- You lose 200 dollars.
You lose 200 dollars.
- My goodness.
- Currently,
Suk Jin has minus 110 dollars.
No pain, no gain.
You should know that.
There is ice water.
(They face the next mission
after learning a life mission.)
I am glad since the day is hot.
This mission will involve...
the mascots of the show...
who come to mind
when you think of English.
The two youngest members.
Are we taking the spotlight?
Se Chan and So Min will give
the questions...
of Speed Quiz.
But you can only explain in English.
(But you can only explain
in English.)
But you can only explain in English.
What?
- What?
- The two of them...
I think So Min would do better.
- So Min would do better.
- But I have...
quick wits.
- Conversational English.
- Okay.
However,
you aren't allowed to use your body
or say a person's name.
- Everything should be in English.
- That's right.
The five of you need to answer
with your feet in the ice water.
The person who does the worst
will be the loser.
So Min.
I am getting goosebumps already.
I have gone abroad with Se Chan.
- How are his English skills?
- Se Chan?
He always gets caught
at Immigration.
- I keep going, "What?"
- It's just him.
- Do you have a drug?
- Yes.
Why?
(He always says "Yes"
when he doesn't understand.)
All right.
- The questions...
- I have a question.
Since when did So Min stoop so low?
What happened to you?
It has always been this way for me.
- What happened to you?
- This is intense.
I am joking when I say this.
- I think I have a fever.
- My heart is beating so fast.
Let's begin.
Let's go. Show her the keyword.
- Go ahead.
- My goodness.
Go ahead.
Oh, my gosh.
- Come on.
- Watch. Oh, my gosh.
- Cow cancel.
- What?
Cow cancel.
- What? Cow cancel?
- Cow cancel?
- Did you say "Castle"?
- Castle.
- Oh, my gosh.
(What is she saying?)
What is "Cow cancel"?
(The answer: Fix the shed
after losing a cow.)
I am seriously in tears.
- This is so embarrassing.
- What is "Cow cancel"?
- Dropping charges?
- Canceling.
- This is so embarrassing.
- Dropping charges?
Cow cancel.
Cow. Cow cancel.
- "Cancel"?
- Oh, my gosh.
Cow house. After-sales service.
(Cow, house, after-sales service?)
Let me answer.
- Fix the shed after losing a cow.
- Jae Suk is correct.
(I was close.)
- You got the meaning across.
- That's right.
- The last part helped.
- Cow cancel.
Why?
Say the last part too.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. Why?
You... You know...
- Is it the next question?
- I don't know. Speaking.
Words travel fast.
- No.
- "Speaking"?
My...
My answer. I answer.
"My answer"?
(Give an irrelevant answer.)
- Hurry up.
- My answer.
- Answer.
- My goodness.
My... My question.
- Nice words for nice words.
- No.
My question.
You. Why?
- Why?
- For goodness' sake.
Why?
(It would be strange
if they answer this correctly.)
- Why?
- Thank you, So Min.
Let me answer.
Give an irrelevant answer.
("Give an irrelevant answer"
is correct.)
How did you get it right?
How are we supposed to get it right?
- Everyone.
- All right.
(Gandhi)
How will they get this right?
(It's a difficult question.)
You should tell us
if it's a proverb or a word.
We need to yell
"Let me answer" first, right?
- Celebrity.
- What?
Celebrity!
Let me answer.
Let me answer. Celebrity.
(Embarrassment hits her again.)
I wouldn't be able
to keep my chin up.
Keep going.
So Min, he is a celebrity.
- Yes.
- Celebrity?
I don't know what to say.
I can't think of the word.
(Gandhi)
No hair.
- No hair.
- Let me answer.
Hong Seok Cheon.
- No. While he is a celebrity...
- Are we guessing right now?
Celebrity?
- Always.
- Sit.
(Does he always sit?)
Gandhi.
(Empty Heads understand each other.)
Is he a celebrity?
- Is he a celebrity?
- A celebrity.
A celebrity with no hair.
A celebrity with no hair
who always sits.
(Ordinary people
wouldn't understand.)
- That was incredible.
- Celebrity.
- Okay.
- Next.
- That was incredible.
(They move on to the next question.)
Let me think...
Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Why does she keep saying that?
- She keeps saying that.
- Okay.
- One.
One.
One. Oh, my gosh.
Nine. One.
- Nine. One.
- Let me answer.
Nine, four, one.
- Nine, four, one.
- Yes. No.
On my birthday...
Did you just speak Korean?
- That's 941.
- Nine.
- What does 941 represent?
- "Nine, four, one"?
- I don't know.
I don't speak English.
Ending.
Let me answer.
Nine,
- four, one. I don't know.
- Let me answer.
- I don't know.
- Let me answer. A narrow escape.
Okay.
(Correct!)
(Okay.)
For goodness' sake.
(She used numbers
that are homonyms.)
"Nine, four, one"?
(So Min got saved
thanks to "9, 4, 1".)
- Nine.
- You are good.
I have a chance.
She is good. You will lose.
No. I have a chance of winning.
(They move on to the next question
in a shocked state.)
I am... Headache.
- Headache.
- You have a headache.
Ge... Geworin.
Not Geworin.
Headache.
Many...
You said "Many" in Korean.
Headache, but...
It's...
(Laughing)
Here is the thing. By implication...
By implication...
(She uses Korean
without holding back.)
- Dog.
Poo-poo.
- Dog poop.
- Let me answer.
- No dog poop for medicine.
No dog poop for medicine.
You need to say
"Let me answer" first.
No dog poop for medicine.
You need to say
"Let me answer" first.
- That's right.
- It's over.
How many questions did they answer?
I can't do this.
- It's so hard.
- It's over.
- Jong Kook is in the first place.
- Okay.
Do you know how frustrating it is?
I couldn't remember the words
that were on the tip of my tongue.
- They just kept circling my mind.
- The next questions.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- I will deliver the key points.
- Go.
Set.
Listen. Let's go.
Set, go.
(The most extraordinary idea)
(My goodness.)
- Gosh.
- This one is hard.
- Celebrity?
- No.
- Four.
- Four words?
Yes. Four words.
The answer has four words.
- Yes.
- Four words.
How am I supposed to explain this?
Explain the first word.
(Haha asks him to explain
each word.)
- I told you. It makes you tear up.
- No.
Yes.
Sky.
- I see.
- Sky?
Let me answer.
Only one under the sky.
No!
- Four words?
- Four words.
Champion.
Power. Sky.
Okay. Let me answer.
Omniscience and omnipotence.
Gosh.
- Only one.
- Let me answer.
Power.
Let me answer.
Walk in someone's shoes.
No.
- You should explain it like this.
- What?
- Power?
- What do you mean by power?
- King.
You can pass by adding 30 seconds.
- Okay. Pass.
- Okay.
(Bolt from the blue)
(It's another idiom.)
How am I supposed to explain this?
- Four.
Four.
Do you know what it means?
No.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Start with the first word.
Start with the first word
and move on from there.
Jean.
- Jean.
- Jean color.
- Jean?
- One.
- Jean color.
- "Jean color"?
- And two.
- Hey, you are worse than So Min.
- Sky.
Jean color. One and two.
- Jean color.
- Come on.
Let me answer.
Speak fluently like a running river.
(Gosh!)
Okay.
- Okay.
- Then...
- Sky.
- Let me answer.
- A student exceeds the master.
- No.
Two. Sky.
- Two. Sky.
- "Sky"?
- You keep saying that.
- Let me answer.
- A student exceeds the master.
- Bolt from the blue.
Okay.
Bolt from the blue.
(Empty Heads
were able to communicate.)
- Hey.
- What?
Why did you say "Jean"?
- Why did you say "Jean"?
- Very easy.
- Haha is really good.
- I know.
Gold.
- Gold.
- Come on.
Let me answer. Icing on the cake.
- Gold.
- Celebrity?
No celebrity.
Four words?
- Yes.
- Four words?
"Gold" must be a homonym.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. Apple of the eye.
Let me answer. Return in full glory.
Please listen to the explanation.
- Gold.
- There is no explanation.
Listen.
- Let me answer. A gold spoon.
- No.
- Gold and...
- Gold.
- O'Clock.
- This is frustrating.
- How are you worse than me?
- Watch.
- Watch?
No.
Let me answer. The unheard news.
Okay.
("The unheard news" is correct.)
Thank you.
- For goodness' sake.
You are the best.
This is too much.
I was better, right?
- Seriously.
- He said, "This is too much."
- I was better, right?
- So Min, you were much better.
(Clean upstream water
makes clean downstream water.)
Four words?
(Four words?)
Celebrity?
- No.
- Proverbs?
- What is it?
- What?
I feel like I became a foreigner.
Come on.
- Sky.
- That's wrong.
(Again?)
- He says "Sky" all the time.
- Why are there so many skies?
Sky water.
- "Sky water"?
- No.
Sky water. Clean.
(Clean upstream water...)
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. Rainbow.
- No.
- Cloud.
No.
Let me answer.
The ground hardens after the rain.
- Clean.
- Let me answer.
Hey! You aren't giving us
an explanation!
- Sky.
- You keep doing this.
- Sky. Clean.
- Wait.
- Sky water.
- "Water"?
- Clean.
- Water.
- High water. High.
High water clean.
- Low water clean.
- Let me answer.
Clean upstream water
makes clean downstream water.
- Okay.
- What was that?
- I can't get these questions right.
- What was "Sky water"?
- How were we supposed to guess?
- "Valley" would have been better.
- I can't get these questions right.
(Yi Sun Sin)
- Hey. Celebrity.
- How will you explain this one?
- Celebrity.
- Hey. Celebrity.
(He is confident when it comes
to questions about celebrities.)
- No hair?
- Yes hair.
- Hair. Long hair.
- Long hair?
- Long hair.
- And a sword.
- Let me answer.
- Long hair.
- And a sword.
- Let me answer.
- Yi Sun Sin.
- Okay.
("Yi Sun Sin" is correct.)
- "A sword"?
- That was unbelievable.
- How was I supposed to know?
- "A sword"?
Gold.
("JiSuk Jin" is
the last question.)
This one is easy.
Celebrity?
No celebrity.
- Middle. Middle celebrity.
- Four words?
- Middle celebrity.
B-lister?
- Yes. C.
- B-lister?
- C-lister?
- C and D.
Let me answer. Yang Se Chan.
No.
A Running Man member.
- Middle.
- Let me answer. Lee Kwang Soo.
- No.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- No.
Let me answer.
C-lister. D-lister.
(Frustrated)
- JiSuk Jin.
- Yes.
(A C-list celebrity, JiSuk Jin)
No. I am not.
- C-lister. D-lister.
- I am not a C-lister or D-lister.
- I am not.
- C-lister. D-lister.
I am not a C-lister or D-lister.
A-lister.
(This C-lister is in denial.)
- Not an A-lister.
- No.
- C-lister. D-lister.
I thought to myself,
- "No way."
- C-lister.
C-lister. D-lister. Okay.
(The game ends.)
- Seriously.
- It was unbelievable.
- I was better.
- So Min, you were much better.
- Seriously.
- I am done.
- All right.
- That was so much fun.
Thanks to the fancy explanations,
the first place is...
Jong Kook.
The last place is...
Suk Jin with zero correct answers.
That was a close match.
A close match, my foot.
- We will have another match later.
- It wasn't a close match.
I taught him "High" and "Low".
I taught him "High water"
and "Low water".
Why did you say "Sky" so many times?
Let's begin the fifth round
of choosing the button.
- Go ahead.
- Who wants to go first?
How much does the first place have?
The first place should go.
- Okay.
- Let's hope for Unlucky.
(He goes with the safe option.)
What?
- Hold on. What was that?
- Listen.
- What?
- What was that?
- He is sneaky.
- What?
Jae Suk got 200 dollars.
Yes!
Who is next?
- Go last.
- Since I don't have enough money,
I have no choice
but to take a chance.
- There you go.
- Yes.
- I don't have enough money.
- I hope she gets Vague.
(Lucky, Vague, and Unlucky)
- We like Vague.
- Get Vague.
(Lucky, Vague, and Unlucky)
- Lucky.
- Vague.
(What will happen to the gambler
who dreams of getting Lucky?)
(Lucky, Vague, and Unlucky)
(Unlucky)
Lucky.
- Unlucky.
Unlucky.
So Min lost 300 dollars.
I hope someone gets Vague.
(Next is Se Chan with 820 dollars.)
It will be incredible
if he gets Lucky again.
(He chooses the blue button.)
I think he will get it.
- My goodness.
- Vague.
(Se Chan made a bet for Lucky.)
- It's Lucky.
- Vague.
(What will be the result?)
Vague.
(Lucky? Vague?)
- It's Lucky.
- Vague.
Lucky!
(It's a jackpot of 1,000 dollars.)
- Lucky!
- He got Lucky.
- Lucky.
- I don't get it.
We did the same thing.
Why did he get Lucky
when I got Unlucky?
The yellow ball is more likely
to go into Lucky.
Next.
- All right.
- Your number isn't in the negative.
I will be happy if he gets Vague.
If he gets Unlucky...
Does he have a bit over 800 dollars?
- He has 820 dollars.
If he goes with the safe option,
he will have 1,000 dollars.
(He will get 200 dollars.)
(He is tempted.)
- That's right.
- Shall I choose the safe option?
Seriously.
- Vague.
- That's good.
- Please.
- You will get Lucky.
- Lucky.
- It's turning.
(What will Haha get?)
- That's good.
- Lucky.
Lucky!
- Hey.
- What will we do?
Bo Pil is flustered.
For Bo Pil,
I will go with the safe option.
(The man who is all about safety
will go next!)
You can choose what you want.
- Here I go.
- Go with this button.
No.
I will go with the safe option.
- Unbelievable.
- Okay.
He is unbelievable.
He went with the safe option
to get 1,000 dollars.
- I will choose this one.
- Okay.
- That's a good choice.
- How much does Ji Hyo have?
- How much does she have?
Ji Hyo has 520 dollars.
- That's good.
- That means...
the combined amount is
1,520 dollars.
Combined with whose money?
Jong Kook's money.
(Jong Kook's money)
- Stop it already.
- Don't you have something to buy?
- For goodness' sake.
- Look at Ji Hyo.
- Shall we combine the money?
- Ji Hyo.
Don't you have something to buy?
Don't be ridiculous.
- Will you buy a laptop?
- For goodness' sake.
- Did everyone else go?
- Yes.
Will you buy a tablet computer?
- Hold on.
- He asked me if I have gone yet.
No cameras are taking
a close-up shot of you.
They are taking 2-people,
3-people, and 4-people shots...
- and a full-cast shot.
- The last place will...
No cameras are taking
a close-up shot of you.
- If I get Lucky...
- The cameraman went home.
- That's right.
- Thank you for your hard work.
If I go with the safe option,
I will be in the last place.
- Zero dollars?
- His number is in the negative.
If I go with the safe option,
I will have zero dollars.
You currently have
minus 110 dollars.
That means
you need Lucky no matter what.
(Lucky: Steal 300 dollars
from a member of your choice.)
(Vague: You and 2 members
of your choice lose 100 dollars.)
(Unlucky: Give 300 dollars
to a member of your choice.)
(The poor man's dilemma
stretches on.)
Suk Jin, I made this
a two-people shot.
You don't have a close-up shot.
A three-people shot with So Min.
- They will zoom in.
- It's a three-people shot.
A four-people shot.
- Let's have a full-cast shot.
- A group shot.
It's a group shot.
You don't have a close-up shot.
Cameras are high-tech these days.
They will edit out people.
They will edit you out.
(His face is fully blocked.)
- Celebrity?
- Don't push the button.
- Don't push it?
- Earlier, yellow...
Yellow brought good luck.
I'll go with this.
(Suk Jin goes with a risky choice
dreaming of landing a jackpot.)
I'm sure he will get a penalty.
Please.
- It's Lucky.
- It's going to Lucky.
(Lucky: Take 300 dollars
from a member of your choice)
It's heading to Lucky.
(It's a 33 percent chance!
Where is Suk Jin's ball going?)
- It's Lucky.
Lucky!
(Lucky)
Who will take 300 dollars from?
- If I knew this would happen...
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Give me the money, you sly punk.
(He takes 300 dollars
from Jae Suk.)
- Now you'll make the final choice.
- What is it?
(Do they have
another choice to make?)
- This is...
- In the final round,
only the member
with the least money will...
make a different choice from others.
So Min is the last with 140 dollars.
- All right.
- It's a series of choices.
If you press the safe choice,
you'll get the money you have.
Or you will get 1.5 or 0.5 times
as much money as you have.
(Safe, Win, Fail)
(That means they can get
1.5 times what they have.)
And if the loser wins,
she can make three members
of her choice donate their money.
Me?
(3 members of her choice will
have to donate all their money.)
You can choose three members.
But if you fail,
you will lose
the two members' money and yours.
(Safe choice: 100 percent,
Daring choice: 50 percent)
(The tiger moth has two choices.)
Now I regret...
that I wasn't being nice to So Min.
- I feel the same way.
- Now I regret it.
I was nice to So Min.
At least four of you
will keep the money though.
I was really nice to So Min today.
That's not true.
You called her a judge.
Shall we begin?
I'm the first. I'll give it a try.
I will get 1.5 times as much money.
(Win: Get 1.5 times what he has,
Fail: Get half of what he has)
(He made the daring choice.)
- He's cool.
- I bet he will win.
(Will he get 1.5 or 0.5 times
the money he has?)
Fail.
- I bet he will win.
- Fail.
He will lose half his money.
(The money has halved!)
All right.
Give it a try.
You should definitely
get 1.5 times your money.
- Please start.
- Go.
(He made the daring choice.)
Will he win?
(Will Se Chan's good luck continue?)
- No.
- It's moving a lot.
- What?
(He won 1.5 times his money.)
What's with him?
- That's 2,700 dollars.
- Lucky.
He won 2,700 dollars.
(Se Chan saved 2,730 dollars
for his parents.)
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
All right.
- What's his choice?
- Oh, no.
- He's unbelievable.
- I'm so sick of him.
I should take 1.5 times the money.
(Haha made a daring choice
hoping to get 1.5 times his money.)
- He will win.
- My gosh.
(He won 1.5 times his money.)
That's cool.
(He's in 2nd place
with 2,380 dollars.)
I'll go with this.
She won!
(Ji Hyo won 780 dollars.)
They all won this round.
The door to success is wide open.
Right. It's on a roll.
Good. It's going well.
(He made the daring choice
to continue the good luck.)
(4 wins in a row or a failure?)
- Seriously...
- Win.
(Fail)
It's turned around. It's over.
Suk Jin gets...
Can you believe this?
Hey, how much do I have now?
Suk Jin got Kwang Soo's bad luck.
He took all his bad luck.
Now it's So Min's turn.
I want So Min to win.
I hope she wins and takes the money
from the top three members.
- It will be great.
- I think so.
- So Min.
- The top three members.
Of course.
Take the top three members' money.
You should pick
the top three members.
- I'm sure So Min will do that.
- Of course I will.
- Otherwise, this is meaningless.
- So Min, why?
- It's just meaningless.
- She's right.
- It's good to donate the money.
- Of course.
It's a good thing.
You don't know
whom So Min will pick.
- We don't know.
- That's right. She gets to pick.
- She will be picking the members.
- Right. So Min!
So Min, why are you being like this.
Hang on. That's right.
So Min, do as you want.
You can pick me.
Good, So Min. This is a good chance.
If you're going to donate it, you
should pick members with big money.
That would be great.
- Let's go.
- Here I go.
(Members with big money
have a lot to lose.)
(She made the daring choice.)
I hope she will win.
- Win.
- Win!
- What?
- Win. She has to win.
(Where is the ball heading
to end today's race?)
- Fail.
- Three of us will lose our money.
(So Min and 2 members of her choice
will lose all their money.)
My goodness.
All right. So Min and...
She will lose her money as well.
She gets zero dollars.
That's terrible.
(They can't even
donate their money.)
So Min, you can pick two members
to get zero dollars with you.
- Two members?
- So Min saves us trouble.
Well... Most of us...
You can just pick anyone you want.
- It's not good to win...
- It's 5,000 dollars put together.
the 1st and 2nd place.
- It's not good.
- So Min.
I'm not talking to her.
- This is...
- The rules of the game...
- tell us not to stand out.
- I know.
It's always like that.
A cornered stone
meets the mason's chisel.
- I was being too frivolous.
- You were annoying.
- What do I do?
- Pick anyone you can.
Just do it.
I'll pick these two.
I mean, they got too much money.
- That's too much.
- They have too much.
I know. It was too much.
Here. I hope you will
have a great time...
- with your parents.
- Thank you. This is a lot.
It's no big deal. There won't be
any prizes for a while.
I'll send this to my mom right away.
You can prepare
some prizes with this money.
Who won 95 dollars? This is for you.
(Suk Jin won 95 dollars
for his parents.)
- All right.
- You won the money anyway.
- Thank you.
It's been a while
since the last shoot.
I spent two weeks
in self-quarantine.
(Jae Suk is back
after the 2-week self-quarantine.)
(And there's something
to celebrate.)
(Suk Jin got the vaccine shot.)
(They prepared ganoderma lucidum
for the members' health.)
(And there are other Young Jis.)
(Lee Young Ji, Hur Young Ji)
(Young Ji versus Young Ji.
Pick a team you want.)
(The members have a choice.)
Do you want me?
(They are treated differently.)
(And that makes the members
hold their heads high.)
(They start the dance party...)
(to attract more members.)
(With their attractive dance moves,)
(they get their team members.)
(And the team battle
finally begins.)
(The Young Jis kneel down...)
(in front of the harsh
team members.)
(Can we have decimal places?)
(That's when the Young Jis
rise in revolt.)
If you come to me now,
I'll give you the whole thing.
(The shoe is on the other foot now.)
(How would the conflict
between them end?)
(Team Selection Race,
Young Ji versus Young Ji)