(The end of fall
when the fall foliage peaks)
- This is nice.
- It's like a film set for fall.
Look at the tinted leaves.
The weather is so nice.
Hello, guys.
- Good to see you again.
- This is nice.
I like the fall weather.
- Hi.
- This is really nice.
- Hello.
- This is like a film set.
A film set
with the background of fall.
- Like "Autumn in My Heart".
- Hello.
- It's a lovely day.
- This is like a film set.
We need to talk about someone first.
What?
- Is this a parachute or what?
- The overall...
- concept of this episode...
- Excuse me.
- Are you a lifeguard or something?
- No.
I think you are mistaken
about today's episode.
- Are you wearing a picnic mat?
- No.
Who would wear mountain clothes
when hiking?
We were told to wear
mountain clothes today.
- Hear me out first.
- You look strange.
A lot of people these days
wear things like this.
- He's flustered.
- He's embarrassed.
He knows he looks strange.
- He can't get his way today.
- What happened?
I just wear
what I get from my stylist.
- Suk Jin.
- Think of what I’ve worn so far.
Do you think
they were what I wanted to wear?
Did you wash your bag in hot water?
- It shrank.
- It shrank a lot.
This is So Wool’s bag.
You’re a thief.
- What happened to your bag?
- Forget about...
- Suk Jin, hang on.
- those miscellaneous things.
Are you getting on a plane?
- No.
- This is a life vest.
- My stylist got me this.
- A life vest.
It’s not like that. That’s not true.
Where should we blow in? Here?
- I'm interested in fashion.
- You should blow in here.
What is this?
Is this a magnet or what?
It's like the N pole and the S pole.
You're wearing a skirt.
- No. These are pants.
- It's a screen.
- To cover his diaper.
- Cover his diaper?
Hey! I'm not wearing a diaper.
Are you playing soccer?
- No, I'm not playing soccer.
- "I'm not playing soccer."
He's answering every question.
Maybe they are soccer shoes.
- I guess they are soccer shoes.
- No, they are not.
Is this soccer?
I think they are soccer shoes.
Why would you play soccer like this?
He's the only one
who's not wearing mountain clothes.
- Why are you playing soccer?
- Forget it.
We have Alpinist Um Hong Gil here.
- I look like him.
- You look just like him.
This is how
real mountain clothes look.
They are mountain clothes.
- This is real.
- This is perfect.
- You should go to the Himalayas.
- I'm wearing hiking pants.
- Jong Kook is...
- This is the standard.
Jong Kook likes exercising,
but he doesn't usually go hiking.
He's going hiking
with his girlfriend.
Because she wants him to.
- Can I wear this for hiking?
- Yes.
- That's how Jong Kook looks.
- This is how it feels.
- You alone...
- And about Ji Hyo.
- I'm...
- It looks like she's campaigning.
She's an old lady.
- She looks like she's campaigning.
- Please vote for me.
- Pick up garbage.
- Thank you.
She's campaigning.
She's not interested
in hiking at all.
She comes to the mountains with
her husband during elections.
You and I love hiking,
but we are not popular at all.
(Jae Suk and I love hiking,
but we are not popular at all.)
I'm all dressed up though.
Right. You're a member of a club.
This isn't just mountain clothes.
I try to look fashionable.
- But you're not fashionable.
- I look somewhat strange.
Isn't she amazing?
- Everyone.
- I was mistaken.
- You'd want to cry.
- Why?
- Is that Red Devils?
- It's Red Devils.
- Yes, it is.
- Where did you get it?
(2002 Red Devils)
Korea
Korea!
(Clapping together)
My goodness.
You're wearing Taegeukgi.
Be the Reds.
I haven't seen this for a long time.
It's been a while, right?
- It's been a really long time.
- By the way,
- I think...
- Doctor Choi.
- today's best dresser is So Min.
- I agree.
- This is detailed.
- I like her outfit.
- Look at her.
- She has her own theme.
- Look at the gold watch.
- I like your pants.
- She looks like a drama character.
- This is like a drama.
- It looks like she's in a drama.
- But...
Honestly, I don't think
I'm wearing mountain clothes.
That's not true.
You're wearing mountain clothes.
Earlier today,
my car was parked next to So Min's.
So we met as we got off.
And So Min said hello to me
dressed like this.
This is how I felt at the moment.
"So Min looks good in that outfit."
(So Min looks good in that outfit.)
- I think so.
- Seriously.
- That's true.
- When she dressed like this before,
it felt like...
she was wearing
a costume for this show.
I was a little surprised
to see her earlier.
To be honest, I was surprised too.
- I was startled.
- Because you looked good?
- Yes.
- She's almost 37 now.
She will soon turn 37.
So Min, you have to accept that.
There's something more surprising.
How old do you think So Min was
when she joined Running Man?
- Was she 35 or 34?
- She was 31.
- Only 31?
- Or 32.
- I was 32 or 33.
- She was 32.
- It's been five years.
- My goodness.
I asked So Min
about it this morning.
- Has it been that long already?
- It's been so long.
Jong Kook, how old were you
when you did "X-Man" with me?
"X-Man"?
I was 28 or 29.
- You were 29.
- I was 29.
Suk Jin, how old were you
when you did "Star Golden Bell"?
Suk Jin was 48.
Even back then?
- Hey.
- Was he 48 back then?
Am I 80 now?
Suk Jin, is it that you've
never been 30 before?
I turned 40 right after my teens.
I've lived in my 40s since then.
As far as I know,
in his 30s, Suk Jin did...
(He was busy seducing women
with his dance.)
"Come here."
"Come in here, guys.
This is the room of freedom."
- Room of freedom?
- Come in here.
- In his 30s?
- That's what he did in his 30s.
We have some news.
- Jong Kook released a new album.
- Right. Jong Kook did.
(Jong Kook released a new song,
"Walking Along With You".)
I just released it in secret.
- What?
- Take a look at this.
- What's that?
- What?
Are they pants or legs?
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you naked?
- What...
- My goodness.
- I'm wearing pants.
- Hey.
- Did you sing in your underpants?
- How could you...
- I can't believe this.
- He sang in his underpants.
- He's wearing a diaper.
Seen from a distance...
I thought he was wearing a diaper.
That's not true.
Kwang Soo uploaded...
this darn photo.
Did Kwang Soo upload it?
I'm not naked. I'm wearing pants.
I'm wearing brown pants.
Was it Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo posted the photo.
Hang on.
Why? Will you call Kwang Soo?
- Do you want to call Kwang Soo?
- Wait.
So did he quit or not?
- Kwang Soo got pink eye.
- He did?
Let me see.
That's disgusting.
He got pink eye.
- Kwang Soo got pink eye.
- That's true.
- And he has a nose problem.
- Why?
His nose.
- I guess he has a sinus cold.
- A sinus cold.
He has rhinitis.
I was worried about him
when I saw this photo.
- What's with that pose?
- What's wrong with him?
- So are we having new members?
- Who?
- New members.
- Are we having new members?
- I heard there would be one.
- Right.
- Are we having a new member?
- There will be a new member.
- Really? I didn't know.
- Yes.
- A new member?
- I heard there would be one.
Is it Jung Jun Ha?
- There he comes.
- Where?
- Who?
- Who is he? Is he Joon Ho?
Why would he go hiking
looking like that?
- I saw him in the restroom earlier.
- Who is he?
Hang on.
- We met in the restroom.
- He's...
- He's your friend.
- Is he my friend?
- He's Jang Hyuk.
"I'm Jang Hyuk."
- Hyuk.
"Hello. I'm Jang Hyuk."
- We really like him.
- I know.
- Why did you not tell me?
- What do you know?
- Hello.
I didn't recognize you, Hyuk.
- You should've told me.
- Hello.
- You are my favorite actor.
- Hello, Hyuk.
- Hello.
"I'm Jang Hyuk."
Hyuk, long time no see.
I didn't recognize you.
You know what?
Let me tell you this right away.
Hyuk is shooting a new movie.
(Hyuk is shooting a new movie.)
- He's here to promote it.
- Tell us.
- Are you releasing a new movie?
- Yes.
- It's "Tomb of the River".
- Right.
- "Tomb of the River".
- Is it "Tomb of the River"?
There are two gangs...
in Gangneung.
- Is it about gangs?
- He likes it.
- It's a film noir.
- Is it a film noir?
You should've called me then.
I was going to,
but you were too busy.
- I see. That sounds exciting.
- So?
It's about the gangs
engaging in a power struggle.
- In Gangneung?
- Yes.
And you're a gangster
in a moneylending business.
That sounds interesting.
I love film noir.
- It sounds fun.
- That's my favorite.
That sounds perfect for him.
- Good.
- That's my favorite.
A movie about gangs is really fun.
I've never seen Jong Kook...
stand so close to a guest before.
He's standing very close.
- Seriously...
- He's my friend.
He came running to greet you.
(When Jang Hyuk
showed up earlier...)
(That's my friend.)
(He comes running to greet Hyuk.)
(He stands close to Hyuk
and checks his body fat.)
They are friends.
I saw him in the restroom earlier.
He was dressed like this with
a mask, so I didn't recognize him.
But, suddenly, "Hello."
He was like this.
(Hello.)
So I said hello.
I didn't know he'd be here.
- "Hello. I'm Jang Hyuk."
- "I'm Jang Hyuk."
The whole nation can do
his impression.
- Everyone can do it.
- Literally everyone can.
Seriously, I don't sound like that.
You do.
Hyuk, it's been a long time.
- Say, "Hello, I'm Jang Hyuk."
- To our viewers.
I just can't copy it.
Just do it for us.
- He copies himself.
- "Hello. I'm Jang Hyuk."
Let's say you are talking
to someone far away.
- Over there.
- Start.
Hello. I'm Jang Hyuk.
(I'm Jang Hyuk.)
- Good.
- You did it.
That was perfect.
- You can do it.
- That was perfect.
He did it well.
"I'm Jang Hyuk."
Last year,
we had a special episode
on Jeju Island.
- And Se Chan...
- I called him.
- Se Chan called him.
- He did.
He spoke his mind.
"What happened to Tae Hyun?"
He told me everything.
(Running Man Episode 528)
(Se Chan called Hyuk
with Jong Kook's phone.)
(Where are you headed?)
(I need to go home first
then I have to go to Gangneung.)
(Jang Hyuk didn't recognize
his best friend's voice.)
(Hey, doesn't Tae Hyun
call you these days?)
(He suddenly brings up a topic.)
(That's what he does these days.)
(He starts chattering
talking about this and that.)
(He opened his heart
without knowing anything.)
What happened?
- Right.
- How could you fall for that?
Seriously,
I thought he called me.
That was hilarious.
Today, with our new
member Jang Hyuk,
we are going on a fall picnic
of Running Alpine Club.
It's called My Money
and My Alpine Club Race.
We are going on a trip to places
where you can appreciate fall.
- Nice.
- We're going on a trip.
The rules are simple.
Once you arrive at your destination,
you will enjoy
various tour courses...
that we prepared.
And you will pay for them
with your own money.
- Really?
- With my own money?
- Did you bring money?
- Yes.
- I did.
- I brought some.
I was told to bring 100 dollars.
But it's not that all of you
will spend your money.
There's a way...
- you can enjoy it for free.
- What is it?
Before you pay
for the tour course you enjoyed,
you will be asked to make a choice.
If what you choose is in a minority,
it's free.
Only those in the majority
will split the money.
- We should use our heads.
- Split the money?
After the race is over,
the two members who spent
the least money will win prizes.
And we will have penalty balls
for the rest by rankings.
- Number 3 gets 1 ball,
- So?
and number 4 gets 2 balls.
And we will select two members.
And they might go home very late.
- We've already come a long way.
- "Very late?"
- We might get stuck in traffic.
- That's the worst.
- On Jayu-ro.
- It will be tiresome.
It's tiresome to get a penalty.
Right.
- They give us annoying penalties.
- I know.
It'd be better to be covered
with fresh cream.
We prefer water slaps.
- I agree.
- If we have to pick acorns...
- We'll go on a fall foliage hike.
- Okay.
This is the activity list
you can enjoy.
- Have a look.
- It sounds fun.
- Shall we have a look?
- Tell us what you want.
The weather is so nice too.
Let's eat something first.
There's a list of activities
and a snack menu here.
I don't want any snacks.
- I want a corn dog.
- Can we get yukgaejang?
- Or something like that?
- They make great corn dogs here.
- Really? Let me have a look.
- It's really good.
Let's have an instant photo taken.
- One photo would be reasonable.
- Absolutely.
- We can afford it.
- "Kang Chan Hee"?
"Once in a lifetime photo taken by
the living legend Kang Chan Hee".
- He took our photo on Jeju Island.
- Right.
- Chan Hee did a lousy job.
- That's not true.
- Our photo was great.
- It was a mess.
- He made us look erotic.
- We looked great in the photo.
- It wasn't erotic.
- He made it look erotic.
- He's bad at taking instant photos.
- He really did it.
(The legendary Chan Hee is not good
at taking instant photos.)
We can have a lotus leaf corn dog?
- Let's all have corn dogs.
- We should.
- We should have this too.
- Who wants a corn dog?
- I want a corn dog.
- Let's order one for each.
Let's order lotus flower bread too.
One lotus leaf ice cream
as well, please.
I'd like lotus flower bread, please.
- Can I have lotus flower bread too?
- Right.
- I'll have lotus flower bread too.
- One for each of you?
- I want lotus flower bread too.
- We all will have it.
- Let's all have the ice cream too.
Then we'll begin
our fall foliage hike.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go for a rickshaw ride.
Let's go!
It's beautiful here.
- It's nice.
- It's really nice.
- I'm excited.
- It's so beautiful over there.
- I see that.
- It's so nice.
- Hey, what is this place?
- It's pretty.
- I'll bring my wife here some time.
- It's magnificent.
President Yang.
Are we going to have baeksuk
together after this?
Of course we will.
Let's drink some makgeolli together.
By the way, President Yang...
Is she your girlfriend?
- Or your wife?
- She's not my wife.
We're just getting to know
each other.
- Is she your wife?
- Hey.
- Come on.
- I didn't mean to pry.
This is my first time
joining you guys.
- Really?
- Yes.
We're just getting to know
each other.
- It's a perfect day for hiking.
- It's nice.
- This is such a beautiful place.
- It's really nice here.
- How nice.
- He seems to be feeling too hot.
- Oh, him?
- No, I'm not.
He must be really hot.
- I must say...
- Not at all.
He looks like
he's actually here to hike.
- That's annoying.
- I didn't mean it like that.
Your tone was offensive.
- Why?
- Gosh, seriously.
- That was funny.
- He's here to hike.
I don't like your tone.
- The king of hiking.
- Since you go hiking often...
- Yes. I'm the king of hiking.
- The hiking king.
He's actually here to hike.
- Oh, my. What's that?
- That's so funny.
- This is so nice.
- I wish I knew this place sooner.
- It's pretty.
- How beautiful.
- Look at those jars.
- It's nice.
- It's a jar fountain.
- It's so pretty.
- It says "Crock Fountain".
- It's so beautiful here.
I didn't know there was a place
like this.
So Min, look. Is that the fountain?
Your snacks are on the way.
- You can enjoy the activities here.
- Got it.
- Hey.
- I want to ride a bicycle.
I want to ride a rickshaw.
I want to ride a rickshaw too.
Let's go on a ride.
How many people can ride in it?
- Two people.
- Two?
- Two people ride in it together.
- I see.
- Hold on. Let me think.
- I want to try it too.
- President Yang and his girlfriend.
- Right.
- You two take a ride together.
- Come on.
- We're getting to know each other.
- All right.
- Please don't get the wrong idea.
- I'll pull the rickshaw for you.
- And these two close friends.
- Yes?
You two take a ride together.
- But I'd feel bad. I mean...
- You two ride in it together.
I want to ride with someone else.
- Gosh. You're so slow-witted.
- Hey...
- Oh, I forgot.
- Right.
- Don't do that. You little...
- I hope you understand.
- Come forward.
- Right. They should...
- Come on.
- What's wrong with you?
- They're also...
- getting to know each other.
- That's right.
- They're in the same phase.
- Yes.
- You know...
- Are you for or against?
Well, if they're just
getting to know each other...
Exactly. They're just
getting to know each other.
You put a secret message
in your new song too.
- What do you mean by that?
- That you want to walk with her.
- That I want to walk with her?
- "I want to walk with you."
It's just a song.
You can use this as a chance
to walk with her.
(I want to walk with you,
I really want to)
- This is your chance.
- "I want to walk with you."
- Don't miss the chance.
- Why else did he release the song?
- Exactly.
- What strange timing.
Seriously.
(The news made the hearts
of the hiking club members flutter.)
- We'll enjoy the ride.
- Let's go.
- A rickshaw ride is a must.
Do you guys mind if we take a video
during the rickshaw ride?
- Do we have to pay for it?
- Go ahead.
Yes. I want to leave a record
of our memories.
- It's up to you.
- Right?
- How nice.
- Like an old-fashioned home video.
It's so nice here.
It's peaceful and relaxing.
I like this place.
- Oh, my. Is this it?
- I like it
- This is it.
- It looks nice.
- Let's take the yellow one.
- Oh, this is it.
- Let's get on.
- There are two of them here.
- The rickshaws are here.
- You two ride together.
- I want to drive it.
- So Min wants this one.
- All right. I'm excited about this.
- Hey, come on up.
- What?
- Let's have fun.
Oh, no. What are you going to do?
I think you have to run along
with us while filming us.
- Is he the one who'll film us?
- Yes.
It's a paid service. How much is it?
I think it's 50 dollars.
- Just talk to me.
- We'll receive the video file.
Don't you need to be on this too?
- That's right. You should.
- Do you think you can keep up?
What's with those sunglasses?
Hey, guys.
Come on, President Yang.
She drives me crazy.
She's being too cheesy.
Hey, Ms. Song...
- and Mr. Kim should...
- No, his friend is here.
- Take a ride with your friend.
- Right.
- No.
- You two ride together.
- We don't want to ride together.
- Come on. Go with your friend.
- Go on and have fun.
- What's the point?
- Take a ride with your friend.
- Have a nice chat.
- Is it uncomfortable?
- What would we do during the ride?
- You can have a nice chat with him.
- Sorry?
You want us to ride this together?
Are you uncomfortable
being alone with each other?
It's not that. It's meaningless
for us to ride this together.
- Just take a ride around here.
- You should take a ride.
- He's right.
- Hyuk, do you want to go with me?
- Sounds great. Let's go together.
- You two together?
- You both will be quiet all along.
- Why?
- Go ahead, Suk Jin.
- He's a little shy, right?
- Yes, he is.
- I'm not shy.
- Okay. Let's try this.
- Right. Go ahead.
- He seems to be feeling shy.
- Sorry?
- You seem shy right now.
- We can tell you're feeling shy.
- You seem...
- Suk Jin, take a ride.
Why would he make me do this?
- Don't be like that.
- I feel awkward.
- Hold on.
- Go on and try it.
- I can be a little shy sometimes.
- For a moment...
It's okay.
It's so awkward.
I feel stifled just watching them.
- Suk Jin, it's okay.
- Hey, let's eat that first.
Let's eat.
- What is it? Oh, good.
- Let's eat.
Let's eat corn dogs.
- Hey, look at you.
- Hyung In, what's with your outfit?
- Hyung In, what are you doing?
- Oh, great.
- It's big.
- Hey.
- Hyung In.
- Why are there only four?
- We'll bring you the rest shortly.
I know you never dress like this.
- It looks good.
- Look at how you're dressed.
(So they purchased corn dogs
and ice cream from the peddler.)
So Min.
(So they purchased corn dogs
and ice cream from the peddler.)
- This is so good.
- Indeed.
It's so tasty.
- It's so good.
- I like this.
- People wait in line for this.
- It's so good.
(The purpose of the club is
to eat and chat more than to hike.)
- It's good, right?
- It's good.
What is Haha holding?
I didn't order ice cream.
We ordered one for each of us.
(The lotus leaf ice cream arrives.)
- It smells so good.
- It has the scent of lotus leaves.
- This ice cream is so tasty.
- Really?
It's really good.
We'll leave when you finish
your food.
Hey, this is the best.
I'm impressed.
It's so good, right?
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- What?
- Show us your dance.
- Me?
- Why so suddenly?
If I suddenly start dancing here...
That's okay. You've got this.
(He suddenly starts dancing.)
- I knew he'd do it.
- Oh, my. Mr. Ji.
- You see, Suk Jin is...
- He's in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood.
Suk Jin is...
I'm so excited. This is nice.
Since I've gotten older,
I'm becoming fond
of watching scenery like this.
- We'll be off now.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Hyuk.
- Oh, dear.
Jae Suk got on it.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin get on
the empty rickshaw.)
- Then I should take a ride.
- Wait.
- Let's go.
- Let Hyuk and Suk Jin go together.
Right. Hyuk, come here.
- That's okay.
- Hyuk, come here.
- I mean... Hyuk.
- Have fun.
We'll be all right, Suk Jin.
- All right. Come on up.
- We'll be all right.
(Chuckling awkwardly)
Suk Jin said
he wasn't a shy person.
We're off now.
- Let's go, Hyuk.
- Bye.
(The relaxing rickshaw ride begins.)
- We've never sat together before.
- True.
- Right?
- No, we once sat together.
When was that?
We sat next to each other
while playing a game.
- While playing a game?
- Yes.
Except for that...
We've never had a chat like this,
just the two of us.
I think this is our first time.
You're right. We should get to know
each other too.
Yes. We're getting to know
each other like them.
(They're getting to know
each other.)
Since we're getting to know
each other, may I ask your name?
- I'm Bong Pal.
- Oh, my.
I'm Bok Ja.
- Oh, your name is Bok Ja?
- Yes.
(Bong Pal and Bok Ja
are growing closer to one another.)
Bok Ja, it's really nice
to take a rickshaw ride.
- We have similar names.
- Indeed.
My full name is Jeon Bok Ja.
- Oh, your family name is Jeon?
- Yes.
My full name is Choi Bong Pal.
- I see, Bong Pal.
- Yes.
Are you married?
I was once.
(Bong Pal is back to being single.)
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- Well...
I'm going to make one.
(Bong Pal is open to all options.)
Those leaves are beautiful.
They just started turning yellow.
Right.
(These 2 are so quiet.)
You two, say something.
I guess you two aren't so close.
We're having a chat.
You guys seem so awkward.
Put your arm around his shoulders.
Why would I put my arm
around his shoulders?
It's an order from the president.
Put your arm around his shoulders.
Why are they being so shy?
That's great. Thank you.
Oh, I see some lotus leaves.
(Laughing with satisfaction)
Look how they're putting their arms
around each other's shoulders.
They look so uncomfortable.
Oh, gosh.
That's so funny.
All those lotus leaves
have withered.
I keep making random remarks.
(He keeps making random remarks
since he feels awkward.)
I can't help it.
- I know.
- I don't feel it though.
- You don't feel it either, right?
- No, I don't.
The air is so fresh.
This is nice.
(While the rickshaw team
shares moments of friendship...)
Why don't you
have an instant photo taken?
Don't force us to do it.
How much is it?
- It's three dollars.
- Let's have one taken.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- Great.
I want to look at it later.
Is that person...
Michael Jackson?
(Drawn in by her artistic style,
they pose freely.)
One, two, three.
I look great in these sunglasses.
This photo is a little bit slanted.
Thank you.
Would you like one more photo?
- No. We don't need any more photos.
- I must say...
(The photographer in dark pink
knows how to sell things.)
- Who gets this? I'll keep it.
- She keeps forcing us.
- She won't stop forcing us.
- Then take one more photo for us.
- Okay then.
- I think we need four photos.
- We don't need that many.
- Whenever you're ready.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- It's because... Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
- Each of us should have one.
- That's not necessary.
- Then let's have three taken.
- Okay.
- You two are always together, so...
- Hey.
Let's have photos taken for now.
Jong Kook, this one is ours.
She said, "This one is ours."
One, two, three.
- I like this one.
- That's nice.
- Okay.
- All right.
- That's great.
- Let's go.
- Come over here.
- Oh, my.
- You see, I think...
- Yes?
I guess it's sort of
an essential activity.
Today is the perfect day
for an outing.
It's perfect.
It got much colder,
but it's sunny and warm today.
- The weather is so nice.
- It's really sunny.
- This doesn't happen that often.
- Absolutely.
The air quality is good today too.
- Oh, my. Look at the sky.
- It's not too hot or too cold.
It reminds me of the sky
in Los Angeles.
Why do you always...
- compare the best things to LA?
- I mean, the sky is...
- You're in Korea right now.
- I know that.
Look at the sky. It's magnificent.
- That's crazy.
- There are no clouds or anything.
It looks so clear.
- This is so tasty.
- We should look up at the sky.
We never know when we get to see
the sky like this again.
Oh, my. It's really nice here.
I should really bring my loving wife
to a place like this.
(Ms. Jeon Bok Ja is excited.)
- This is really nice.
- What's with you?
What's the length of the video
for 50 dollars?
My goodness. I didn't know
I would meet you here.
I can't believe I met you here.
It's so good to see you again.
Have you been well?
Ms. Jeon.
Guys, I just met my friend here.
- Ms. Jeon.
- She's acting like a mom.
How are the kids?
- I heard...
- Ms. Jeon.
that your child went to college.
- Gather round, everyone.
- I see an R flag here.
- Oh, we should go that way.
- Where?
- Please come this way.
- Come here.
There are some crocks
and other things here.
(The prankster is acting up again.)
(The kid with the ice cream
already got on the rickshaw.)
My, this is so good.
- Are you ready?
- The rickshaw driver looks strong.
- That's good. Keep going.
- Right. Okay.
- This is good. He drove too slowly.
- Okay.
- We're going really fast.
We're going so fast.
- Oh, no. Watch out.
- Be careful.
- This is fun.
- That's pretty.
Jong Kook, is this good exercise
for your lower body?
Yes, but I wish you two were
a little heavier.
- Are we too light?
- Yes.
- You two are too light. Girls...
- He says we're light.
I mean you two are too light.
What's that chair?
Jong Kook is doing that as exercise.
- Right? I thought so.
- Not long ago...
Of course he's doing that
as exercise.
- He said he hadn't worked out...
- Mister.
- Move.
- Who are you?
Gosh, seriously.
He can't get on it.
(The hipster member
jumped in again.)
This is nice.
My, it's incredibly tasty.
Wait. One of you should stay.
We're awkward around each other.
Don't leave us alone.
It's still awkward for us.
Jong Kook should take care of Hyuk.
We don't do that for each other.
What is it? Yes, please take
a photo of us together.
With that scenery behind us.
That's good.
(They made an impulse buy.)
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- It's three dollars.
- Pardon?
- That's three dollars?
You're practically a thief.
(You're practically a thief!)
That's a place
where you can make a wish.
- Does anyone have a coin?
- I didn't expect to see that.
- This place is nice.
- The weather is so good.
I'm with the people I love
on such a beautiful day.
- It makes you feel happy.
- Everything is perfect.
"Anyway, that's why I was happy."
- Exactly.
- Anyway, that's why I was happy
Wave at the camera.
Hi. It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
- Oh, my.
- Hello.
Hyung In,
can you take a photo of me?
- Me too.
- Come with me.
- Look at the flowers.
- Don't have a photo taken alone!
- Mister!
- He's having a photo taken alone?
Why would you do that?
Why would he waste our money
like that?
My gosh. You can't spend our money
just as you please.
- Good.
- My gosh.
Why would you waste our money?
(Let's have a photo taken together.)
- Go away. I'll pose with him alone.
- But I want to...
Let me have one taken with him too.
Have a photo taken with him alone
after this.
- One, two, three.
- Gosh.
- That was great.
- Hyuk, can I take one with you too?
- Can you take a photo of us? Yes.
- Would you like a photo?
(Everyone asks the star
for a photo.)
That's great.
- Hyuk, can I take one with you too?
- Yes?
In front of the flowers there.
Excuse me.
- I want to join you guys.
- Hyuk, can you...
- strike this pose with me?
- Sure.
Guys, stop having photos taken.
- One, two, three.
- Ms. Jeon.
- He's a married man.
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
- I look great in this photo.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk was looking at
his photos.)
- Hyung In, I like this photo.
- Thank you, Hyuk.
- I like this one. It's great.
- Do you like it?
- How much is for a photo?
- I like this.
Why would you have it taken alone?
How many photos
did you have taken alone?
My gosh.
Why did you have photos taken alone?
- Am I not allowed to do that?
- Why?
- Come on. You spent...
- It's our common fund.
- That's not true. I spent my money.
- Why would you do that?
- Hey... Photographer.
- Mister, come on.
- What's wrong...
- He called her "Photographer".
- Can we take a group photo?
- You shouldn't do that.
- A group photo, everyone.
- Chan Hee...
- Gather round for a group photo.
- It's ridiculous.
- What's going on?
- We're taking a group photo.
- But...
- Smile.
Gosh, seriously.
(They're taking
a group photo again.)
Ready? One, two, three.
(Their trip expenses are going up
higher and higher.)
- Enough. Stop spending money.
- This is great.
- I'm serious.
- Give me that.
Oh, my. The weather is so nice.
Indeed.
Try to imitate Hyuk.
"I'm Jang Hyuk."
"Hello."
- "I'm Jang Hyuk.
It's so beautiful here
with the mountain in the distance.
- It's a perfect spot for a picnic.
- It's beautiful.
It's pretty over there.
- We have chairs. Look at the view.
- How beautiful.
- Hey... Photographer.
- It's beautiful.
- Stop it!
- Come over here, photographer.
Stop taking photos.
We have to take a photo here.
That's enough.
- This is such a hassle.
- Photographer.
- Why are we...
- Come here, Haha.
- Can you take a photo of us?
- Join us here.
- Gosh. Stop it, guys.
- Here.
- Smile.
- Stop having photos taken.
How many more photos will you buy?
(The pretty middle-aged man's love
for photography explodes.)
- That was nice.
- Who will have this photo?
- It's really nice.
- Look around. It's beautiful.
- It's magnificent.
- Why won't you enjoy the scenery?
- This is like a work of art.
- I'm amazed.
- Coffee or adlay tea?
- I want the one with walnuts.
- Walnuts?
- Is tea free?
Yes, it's free.
- Great. It's free.
- Really?
- Wait. It's free?
- It's nice.
- Pardon?
- Is it free?
- It's free.
- That's great.
You can't take them away.
But you said it was free.
It's free.
Didn't your son get fired for
stealing from the staff lounge?
Gosh. Don't say that.
So Min looks so natural
as if it's not acting.
This tea tastes quite good.
My, this Solomon's seal tea is good.
(Everyone is enjoying tea
while catching their breath.)
This is amazing.
I look great in this photo, Ji Hyo.
- This is amazing, right?
- Indeed.
I got a good one.
This is the best photo of me.
- It's worth every penny.
- Why did you take a photo alone?
- I like it.
- Why would you guys do that?
Don't take a photo alone.
We don't have much money.
But I really wanted to take one
with Hyuk.
You spent so much
from our common fund.
- You shouldn't...
- I really like this photo.
- What did he say?
- Hyung In, I like this photo.
- This is the best photo of me.
- Show me.
Take a look.
Oh, my.
It doesn't look like a Poraroid.
- "A Poraroid"?
- He said "Poraroid".
It looks as if they were abroad.
Isn't it nice?
- We look great, right?
- Why does it taste weird?
It looks as if I met a top star...
at a tourist spot overseas.
- It's amazing indeed.
- Yes.
Hey, did you meet Hyuk?
I met him too.
- You met him too?
- I met Hyuk too.
- Me too.
- Hyuk must've traveled a lot.
- I met Hyuk too.
- Hyuk has great body proportions.
- He met Hyuk too.
- Yes, I did too.
Hyuk must've traveled
to so many places. Suk Jin.
- You shouldn't have...
- You should save memories.
- Have more photos taken.
- You had so many photos...
Why haven't I received my photo?
Maybe you didn't ask for it.
Hyuk, did you receive
the photo of us together?
- Yes, I have it here.
- You have it?
I can't believe this.
I wanted to keep our memories too.
- Gosh. Hey, photographer!
- He startled me.
- I want my money back.
- Calm down.
- Gosh. What is this?
- Where are you going?
- Look. Give me my money back.
- It's not that bad.
- Photographer! Look at this.
- Show me.
- It was shot against the light.
- Look at this.
They should give me my money back.
I'll explain the rules
of the first mission now.
- Okay.
- Forget about the rules.
Let's just have fun.
- We'll just see Hyuk's dance.
- Right.
- Why would I dance here?
- Right, his old dance performance.
- Let's see his dance performance.
- Let's just play a quiz game.
- You'll understand if you hear it.
- Is that so?
Hyuk is famous for his performance
in "The Slave Hunters", right?
- "The Slave Hunters".
- Absolutely.
- "Un Nyun!"
- So are we going to hunt slaves?
The first mission is...
Reminiscent Chattering.
- That's great.
- Reminiscent Chattering?
- That sounds fun.
- I like the title of the mission.
Reminiscent Chattering.
- I love chattering the most.
- When it comes to chattering,
- We can talk about old days.
- Hyuk is really good at that too.
- Hyuk likes chattering too.
- Yes.
- He likes chattering.
- He speaks slowly though.
Here are the rules.
You have 30 minutes...
to just have a chat.
- Oh, yes!
- Okay.
However, if no one speaks
for more than five seconds,
ten dollars will be added
to your trip expense.
- Come on. That's so long.
- We won't even last three seconds.
That's total nonsense.
- That won't ever happen.
- Give us a topic,
and see how we continue
talking about it.
- Of course.
- Also, since this is an outing,
- there's one special rule.
- What is it?
In 30 minutes,
each one of you has...
- your Secret Santa.
- What?
- We'll decide your Secret Santa.
- Okay.
As someone's Secret Santa,
you must react enthusiastically
to whatever he or she says.
(Secret Santa Rule:
React enthusiastically to every comment.)
We do that, no matter who speaks.
You know that.
- We're like robots.
- However,
after it's over,
- We shouldn't get caught?
- if you find out...
who your Secret Santa is,
both you and your Secret Santa
get extra points.
- Then should we be explicit?
- It'll be too obvious.
There's another rule.
Let's say Jong Kook is...
- Jae Suk's Secret Santa.
- Okay.
The others can pretend...
- they're Jae Suk's Secret Santa.
- That could happen.
If you fail to find
your Secret Santa,
you will lose points...
while the other gains points.
- That sounds like fun.
- Do you get the rules?
- Then...
- Did you three...
Did you three hear me?
- Then...
- Lotus leaf bread...
- Can we get more bread?
- Sorry?
The lotus leaf bread is to die for.
It's even better...
- with this beverage.
- I know.
You will come forward...
- All we have to do is talk.
- and find out...
whose Secret Santa you are.
- Sure.
- Got it.
You can tell us while we're here.
You need to hear it one at a time.
- I will be...
- Why?
- Keep it short.
- Respond to this person well...
and make sure that
he or she keeps talking.
Can I refuse?
How funny.
You must respond to others
if you wish to win points.
Okay, I got it.
Hyuk, you're next.
In Hyuk's case...
Respond well
whenever this person talks.
- Got it.
- He's not one to respond well.
Who do I have?
(Oh...)
Okay, I got it.
Really?
- This is easy.
- I'm guaranteed a point.
Just let the other person know that
you're trying to get them to talk.
- Sure.
- Can we tell the other person?
I'll just tell everyone
whose Secret Santa I am.
Go ahead. It might be a lie, right?
- Is that so?
- Jae Suk, are you going to say it?
- Yes.
- Who is it?
You know how I am.
I don't play mind games.
Really?
- You won't tell us?
- No.
- Haha, seriously?
- It's him.
He won't say it.
He won't say
whose Secret Santa he is.
That's nothing to laugh at.
Can you believe it?
- So Min, enjoy.
- What's this?
Hey, it's young pollack.
- It's the real deal.
- No way.
- Look.
- So this is what young pollack is.
- Your 30 minutes start now.
- Okay!
And go.
Hyuk, why do even men
find you attractive?
What makes you so charming?
Suk Jin is Hyuk's Secret Santa.
- What on earth?
- I'm sure of it.
That was out of the blue.
Wasn't that awkward?
- What was that?
- It was too obvious.
- He...
- I agree.
- He's Hyuk's Secret Santa.
- Of course.
Hyuk!
- I'm the reason he's a big star.
- You can say just about anything.
He became a top star
due to the love I had for him.
- What?
- In middle school,
- I was Hyuk's...
- That's right!
- That's true.
- I was a fan since his early days.
I bought magazines
to get photos of him.
- Really?
- He was the first celebrity...
- she ever liked.
- They went up on my wall.
I liked him since he appeared in
god's music video of...
- "To My Mother".
- That's right.
Hold on a second.
This isn't just some
meaningless chatter.
- It was when he was in "Zzang".
- Exactly.
- Do you know that movie?
- What we want
- Yes, that's the one.
- Say what you want
Dong Geun from that movie
is my friend.
- Hyuk.
- Yang Dong Geun?
- Hyuk, I remember "School".
- Cha In Pyo played the teacher.
The KBS series "School".
I enjoyed that a lot.
Don't they look like an old couple?
I almost dropped out of school,
but that movie prevented me
from doing so.
I was a huge fan
of the TV series "School".
(Could Haha be Hyuk's Secret Santa?)
"Zzang" was filmed near my house.
- In Anyang?
- In my neighborhood.
It was filmed
right across the street.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(Is that so?)
- In your neighborhood?
- That's right.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
You were in the TV series "School".
Yes, "School".
I remember.
- So Min, you have a great memory!
- I'm a fan...
- Wait, you're being weird.
- What do you mean?
- Hold on a second.
- Wait.
Is there something you don't know?
(Is there something you don't know?)
It's just hard to accept,
that's all.
Jong Kook has never been...
this enthusiastic about
what I had to say.
- Exactly.
- So Min!
Don't fall for it.
- So Min, don't fall for it.
- Can Jong Kook...
be my Secret Santa all the time?
- So Min!
- This is weird.
- Well, So Min...
- Ji Hyo,
weren't you chosen
as someone's Secret Santa?
(Weren't you chosen
as someone's Secret Santa?)
Were you the only one
who didn't get a partner?
- Actually...
- Yes?
My partner's talking too much,
so I don't know what to do.
- Really?
- Someone's running wild.
- Don't overdo it.
- It must be a dilemma for you.
Hyuk.
Out of the actresses
you worked with,
who was most beautiful?
Out of his projects so far?
That I want to know too.
- You're right.
- I want to know.
- Everyone was beautiful.
- But still...
- What if you had to choose one?
- If you had to choose...
Everyone was beautiful.
- But still.
- If you had to choose one.
Can you ask him? I'm curious too.
Everyone was beautiful.
(Laughing awkwardly)
Everyone was pretty in your eyes!
We all know you're faking it.
Everyone was pretty!
They were all pretty!
Are you all right?
When I first met Hyuk,
he wore glasses like these
all the time.
- Right?
- Yes.
- See?
- Do you know where I first met you?
At the cinema.
- Really?
- The one in Samseong-dong.
You were with Jun Ji Hyun.
Really? I've never
seen her in person before.
"Windstruck", right?
- Yes, that movie.
- Right.
- Your hair was bleached.
- You were there to see it.
- You wore this kind of glasses.
Weren't you signed
by the same agency?
Yes, it's why
we were there together.
- Of course.
- It was an intense moment for me.
Just so you know, Bae Yong Joon...
has this "trauma" about him.
- What was that word again?
- A trauma?
(Bae Yong Joon is traumatized?)
I meant an aura.
- Seriously?
- Unbelievable.
- An aura.
- A trauma?
- There's an aura to him.
- Suk Jin.
- Unbelievable.
- Suk Jin,
- did he try to beat you up?
- That's not it.
- Were you traumatized?
- I mean...
I can't believe that he majored...
- in business administration.
- This is an aura, right?
- They're not even similar.
- A trauma?
- I found it funny though.
- But...
Yong Joon...
- Did he ever beat you up?
- Unbelievable.
Was it the "Autumn Sonata"?
- "Winter Sonata".
After...
- "Autumn in My Heart".
- After he became a star,
we met at someone's wedding.
I saw him...
and his hair was long
and waving in the wind.
He's probably younger than I am.
- He is.
- Isn't he younger than you?
- Isn't he the same age as you?
- Yes, he's the same age.
You said that wrong just now.
Unbelievable.
- It's not even that long, but...
- While talking,
he slipped up about ten times.
It was a joy to see him...
and I felt like
I had seen a celebrity.
I bowed and said hello
while he did this.
"Yes, hello."
I bowed...
while he just shook my hand.
Anyway, the aura he had...
(Yelping)
(To the side)
(He shows off his talent
for slapstick comedy.)
That was hilarious.
It was fun.
- I liked it.
- He's a funny one.
Suk Jin sure is a funny one.
Did you remove my chair?
- No, it wasn't me.
- Was it you?
He must be traumatized.
That was funny.
Did someone pour alcohol
into his cup?
I'm your Secret Santa.
I mean it. I'm your Secret Santa.
(Was it Se Chan's way
of helping Suk Jin?)
From what I hear,
"Princess Hours" is being remade.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You were in the original series!
- Ji Hyo...
- Of course.
- Of course I was in it.
- I had forgotten about it.
- How could you now knot that?
It's ironic, isn't it?
In "Princess Hours"...
With Yoon Eun Hye...
- Did you see that?
- What's so ironic?
- I mean...
- That's enough.
- You've done enough.
- Jong Kook.
Aren't I allowed
to mention "Princess Hours"?
- You can but...
- There's that photo.
A photo of the poster
with Jong Kook's face on it...
- is being circulated.
- That's what I told you.
- Isn't it true?
- So Min...
Unbelievable.
Did you see the photo?
Of course I did, So Min.
- Goodness.
- So actually...
- So Min's on a roll today.
- If you think about it,
- life can take odd turns.
- Exactly.
- Kim Jeong Hoon was in it too.
- Can you explain this?
Rumor has it
that Chaeyeon liked you.
- They met when she was a fan.
- She was a fan.
- What's with this gesture?
- Well...
- As a fan...
- We didn't see each other.
- You met on "Date with the Stars".
- Exactly.
- With Chaeyeon...
- She was Jin Sook back then.
- Yes, Jin Sook.
- Back when she was in high school,
we met through a show
called "Date with the Stars".
It might be hard to understand
if you don't explain it well.
In the 90s, there was a show
that let fans meet their idols.
- Yes, "Date with the Stars".
- There was a show.
- That existed.
- They got about...
- one or two days.
- Yes, two days.
- They got to spend time together.
- Really?
Before Chaeyeon made her debut,
- she went by Jin Sook.
- That's right.
She applied for
a spot on the show...
- and she met with Jong Kook.
- That's right.
Did you date her?
- No, we...
- That's all I'll say.
- Did they date?
- What do you mean?
She accompanied me on my gigs...
- and...
- They went to a ski resort.
- For an overnight trip?
- White snow
- Falls
- Of course not.
She followed me around...
- and rode with me in my van.
- For how many days?
Hold on.
What happened after
the cameras stopped filming?
- Did you get a few drinks?
- No, that's not it.
- She was in high school!
- She was...
- in high school.
- She was in high school.
Goodness.
Do you get it?
She was in high school.
Later on, they met on "X-Man".
And I...
During the Absolutely Game,
she asked if he remembered her.
- The Absolutely Game?
- Through his thin eyes he said,
"Have you been well, Jin Sook?"
(Have you been well, Jin Sook?)
That's how he said it!
- Hey!
- What is it?
That wasn't the case.
I'm the one who asked her first!
(He recognized her first
and said this.)
Jin Sook, it's been a while.
"Jin Sook, it's been a while"?
(With memorable lines,)
(Jong Kook created
many memorable scenes.)
You're all grown up now.
(You're all grown up now.)
Jong Kook was the first to ask
if she had been well.
- That's enough.
- That's so cool.
- You created a lot of drama.
- He...
Were they in a love triangle then?
- Not a love triangle.
- That wasn't it?
It wasn't a love triangle.
He had a thing
with both women though.
- There weren't any feelings.
- He said...
it wasn't a love triangle...
but you had a thing with both women.
There must've been
something going on.
- I bet you don't know him well.
- A friend knows best.
Don't be ridiculous.
Nothing was going on.
Instead, it was...
The fact that he's drinking water...
tells me that it's worth
looking into.
Are you kidding me?
- Is this because he's nervous?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I bet he's nervous.
- He sure is.
Hyuk has been in the industry
for a long time.
- Of course.
I just got the chills.
When we're this far away,
Jong Kook normally chooses
to ignore what I say.
I didn't even speak out loud,
but he heard everything.
Well, you just have
a lot of great things to say today.
- Why don't you dance?
- What?
From what I know, Jong Kook...
(Laughing loudly)
Ji Hyo, why don't you dance too?
So Min...
(Lady Song shimmies as well.)
There you go.
This is fun.
(They're suddenly having
a dance party.)
- What don't I have?
- Wait.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Well...
- What are you doing?
- What is this?
I was just excited.
- Look at this!
- It's so dirty.
Why is his leg so skinny?
What is this?
- Look at his leg.
- This is...
- Why is your leg white and skinny?
- What is this?
- I can't believe it.
- What's wrong with you?
Mister!
- What's wrong with your thigh?
- That's...
You want to open it more?
It's not working.
My goodness.
Your leg...
What's wrong with your leg?
It's so skinny and white.
Why is it so white?
- What happened to you?
- What?
- What about it?
- What happened to your leg?
- What's wrong with it?
- It's really white.
My legs aren't that thick.
- Speaking of which...
- I want to hear more stories.
- I want to hear more from them.
- Hyuk...
So Min was a big fan of Hyuk's.
And you're seeing
each other on a show.
Did you have his poster as well?
- Did you?
- I actually...
Why are you saying such nonsense?
You don't do that...
- on "How Do You Play?".
- Exactly.
"How Do You Play?" is really fun
these days.
Will you pay more attention
to Running Man as well?
Your character
on "How Do You Play?"...
- is a big hit.
- That's right.
Please treat us to drinks.
You should treat them to drinks
from time to time!
You've never asked
to hang out with me.
- Not even once!
- Stop it!
- Haha is in his 40s now!
- This is why...
- "This is why"?
- I didn't want to meet up.
- Haha is in his 40s now!
- Hey!
Take that off, Suk Jin!
I hate the sight of it.
Why? I like it. Why would you
tell me to take it off?
We're not even by the sea!
- That's not it.
- Why are you wearing a life jacket?
I like it!
- I like it.
- He's traumatized.
Anyway, it's all a misunderstanding.
- Okay.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Haha loves us.
- All right.
You guys are the first ones
I give out yellow corvina to.
Right. That's true.
I have a question.
If I'm someone's Secret Santa,
is he or she mine too?
- No.
- Oh, it's different.
- You didn't know that until now?
- Suk Jin.
- He is indeed traumatized.
- That could happen.
I haven't played it for so long.
He is traumatized.
What's with this?
Suk Jin is traumatized.
- He's traumatized.
He's indeed traumatized.
- He's indeed traumatized.
- Of course.
- By the way, Hyuk...
- "Eat up."
Whose Secret Santa is Hyuk?
- Seriously.
- I could roughly tell others'.
- All right. Time is up.
- Oh, really?
Guess who is your Secret Santa...
and write it down.
It's obvious.
I could...
I could clearly tell.
- I have to find my Secret Santa?
- That's right.
- The one...
- Find the person...
- who reacted to you the most.
- Someone who reacted the most.
It's so confusing.
- Someone who reacted for me...
- Look at him.
Only one person reacted for me.
(Some are certain,
and some are confused...)
So Min.
(as they write down the names.)
(Exchanging looks)
It's so clear.
I'm really confused.
- No one reacted for me.
- You're confused?
Haha wasn't one either.
Many people reacted
to what Hyuk said.
They could've made me
their target on purpose.
- I'll announce the results now.
- All right.
- Of course I guessed right.
- Suk Jin...
- picked Se Chan.
- That's right.
Really?
And it is...
(Suk Jin picked Se Chan
as his Secret Santa.)
Se Chan.
- It was really you.
- That's right.
- You're getting a point each.
- I was your Secret Santa.
It was you.
Ji Hyo...
(Ji Hyo picked...)
picked Suk Jin as her Secret Santa.
(Suk Jin as her Secret Santa.)
It is Suk Jin.
- What?
- For real?
- Yes!
- Why did he react so late then?
No, he did react occasionally.
- Did he?
- Really?
Jae Suk...
- wrote So Min's name.
- Yes.
- And it is So Min.
- I knew it was her.
- You all got it.
- Of course it was So Min.
Why would Secret Santas
make it so obvious?
I know who it is now.
Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook picked...)
- wrote Jae Suk's name.
- That's right.
And it is Jae Suk.
It's impossible
for you to guess it wrong.
That's right.
But it's nerve-racking...
- This is somewhat heartwarming.
- although I know who it is.
So Min wrote down Jong Kook's name,
- and it is Jong Kook.
- It was obvious.
- It's so heartwarming.
- I did well, didn't I?
- This is heartwarming and nice.
- Are you done with it now?
- We don't have to be mean.
- Yes.
He's done with it now.
Haha...
(Haha picked...)
wrote down Ji Hyo's name.
It's her.
- It is her.
- We all got it correct?
- We all got it correct.
- Right?
Se Chan...
(Se Chan picked...)
- I think he got the wrong one.
- No, he got it correct.
- wrote down Hyuk's name,
- It's me.
- and it is him.
- Yes!
(Se Chan picked Hyuk
as his Secret Santa.)
Hyuk.
- I thought he got it wrong.
- You reacted for him?
I reacted to everything he said.
It didn't even show.
- Hyuk...
- I got the wrong person.
wrote down So Min's name,
- It was Haha.
- and it's not her.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey.
(His real Secret Santa was Haha.)
- I talked to you a lot!
- That's not it.
How could you have
guessed that wrong?
I didn't have that many questions
about you, to be honest!
I knew it was...
one of you two,
and I was wondering who it was.
- Me too.
- I almost picked Haha at the end,
but So Min's reaction...
- was very aggressive, so...
- So Min kept reacting to...
what Jae Suk said.
- That's right.
- You didn't see that?
- That's how I felt.
- Thank you.
It's because you kept telling him
that you were his fan.
He's the sloppiest person
that I know.
I can tell.
So Min will take another point.
And Hyuk and Haha
got one point taken off.
The winner,
the sole winner, So Min...
will get extra 20 dollars.
Treat us to one, will you?
Let's take a photo.
- Of course. Let's take a photo.
- How many points did she win?
- Let's take a photo.
- Thank you.
She got three points.
- Gosh, So Min.
- I don't have much.
So far, you've spent 183.5 dollars.
- We spent so much.
- What did you say?
We spent so much.
The entrance is beautiful.
(Entrance fee for 8)
(8 lotus leaf corn dogs)
(8 lotus leaf ice cream)
(2 rickshaws)
(Lots of photos)
(Total: 183.5 dollars)
We'll tell you how you'll pay
for it once you're in the car.
- We spent that much?
- Do we have that much money?
- Let's move on to the next spot.
- Shall we?
All right. Let's go!
It's time to decide how you'll pay
for the money you spent lavishly.
You guys took so many
individual photos.
Don't say we spent money lavishly.
Soon, you'll get in the car
one by one.
There are three flags
waiting in front of the car.
They are in red, yellow, and green.
(They need to pick choose
one of the flags.)
You'll each select one
before getting in the car.
The ones who picked
the color that was least picked...
will be exempted.
(The ones that pick the least picked
color will be exempted.)
- No!
- You can...
You can discuss it in advance.
You like green, don't you?
Well...
I'm sorry, but I'm going to
pick red no matter what.
- I pick red too.
- I'm sorry.
- I'll also pick red.
- I can't help but pick red.
I'll also pick red.
- I'll pick red.
- He likes red.
I also like red, but...
What about you, Hyuk?
Well, I like green.
- You like green?
- I like red too.
If you're ready,
let's start with Haha.
(Haha sets off first.)
(It's a psychological battle
that requires quick wit and luck.)
These are the colors of reggae.
(They need to pick the least
chosen color to be exempted.)
I'll pick this.
- I know. He'll pick green.
- Everyone.
- I want to pick yellow though.
- You'll pick green no matter what.
I'll pick yellow.
I think many people
will pick yellow.
- Go for yellow.
- Many will go for yellow.
This is so difficult.
(He's come to the place
to make his decision.)
(He picked the green flag?)
(He said he'd pick yellow,
but he picked the green flag.)
You're here.
I'm here.
Which one did you pick?
Which color did you pick?
- My gosh.
- Did you also pick green?
You don't like green that much.
You picked that thinking no one
would pick it.
(Which color did Haha pick?)
I told you I'd pick green.
- Why did you pick green?
- I told you I'd pick green.
- You should've picked yellow.
- I was going to, but...
Which one should I pick?
My favorite color.
Hey!
Which one did you pick?
(The two of them
already picked green.)
- They told me to take it.
- Right. Let me see.
(She picked the yellow flag.)
Is it different from yours?
I'm glad.
(Green 2, Yellow 1)
Which color should I pick?
(Thinking hard)
I'll just go for it.
He's here.
Which one did you pick?
I think he got the green flag.
- Which one did you pick? Green?
- No way.
You said you'd pick red.
(It's another green flag.)
I told you I'd pick green.
(The three middle-aged men
hit it off.)
But I told everyone
that I'd pick green.
You picked green? Darn it.
I'm done for. Green is the majority.
- Gosh.
- No, there are just three of us.
We'll have to pay for this later.
They said the penalty
was something tedious.
My gosh.
I guess yellow stands a chance.
It does.
No one was interested in it.
Green is done for.
(Yang Hong Gil comes to
pick his flag while humming.)
The three of us
will pick red for sure.
- I'm going for red.
- Shall we push ahead with it?
Which color will you pick, Hyuk?
I'm picking red.
- Are you going for red too?
- Yes, I'm going for red.
I'll pick red for real.
(All four of them told each other
that they'd pick red.)
(Se Chan picked the red flag
for real.)
Where should I hide it?
- I picked red for real.
- No one has chosen red yet.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's why I was going to
pick yellow.
Which one did you pick?
I picked yellow,
and they all picked green.
Really?
(So Min and Se Chan have
high chances. The rest set off.)
What is this?
I think Se Chan picked green...
after making everyone else pick red.
(The minority will be decided
based on their choices.)
I'll pick red.
(Ji Hyo chose red.)
(Jong Kook chose red.)
Hide it inside so they can't see it.
(Even Hyuk picked red.)
Hyuk. Which color did you pick?
- Which one did you pick?
- Which color is it?
- All right!
- He picked red too.
It's decided!
This is fascinating.
Am I an outcast or something?
Why am I the only one
who picked yellow?
This is incredible.
Only one person picked yellow.
The seven of you
will divide the bill...
- All right.
- and pay 26 dollars each.
Give me 30 dollars each.
I'll give you the change.
- Gosh.
- Thirty dollars?
- Thirty dollars.
So Min even earned extra cash.
So Min, you might be
the sole winner today.
- Aren't we getting a prize?
- You are.
We have a prize today.
Let's move to the next spot.
- All right.
- We'll get going now.
Thank you.
Where are we headed to?
We'll have lunch, and you'll be
done for today after one mission.
- What are we having?
- But I'm full!
I'm so full too.
What are we having?
When you're on an outing,
you should have...
- Baeksuk?
- No, not baeksuk.
We had baeksuk recently.
- Is that so?
- Are we having eel?
Yes, we're having eel.
(Revitalizing food for autumn, eel)
- Nice! We're having eel.
- My gosh.
I had eel for breakfast though.
- I should work out a lot today.
- Who has eel for breakfast?
I had eel for breakfast
because we had it at home.
- I love eels.
- That's incredible.
We also prepared many dishes
other than eels.
- Oh, really?
- There's green onion jeon too.
- All right!
- Green onion jeon sounds good.
I guess we'll have to
pay for it too.
- Oh, right. We have to pay for it.
- We're having eel?
- That'll be expensive.
- Let's enjoy it and pay for it.
Let's do that.
Right. Let's not mind it
when we eat.
We'll divide the bill anyway.
- Can you take a photo of me?
- Again?
- Stop. I'm so tired of it.
- I want to take it with you.
Then I'll take it when we arrive.
Let's take a photo
at a good spot when we arrive.
We haven't even driven for an hour
from Seoul,
and the view
is already looking nice.
I didn't get to enjoy
views like this.
(I didn't get to enjoy
views like this.)
What do you mean?
We came here often with Yong Man.
- You mean Yangsu-ri?
- We did?
What do you do
when you three meet up?
- We didn't enjoy the scenery.
- We didn't.
We only looked around to see
if there were any women...
interested in us.
There's a famous spot
where there's a bonfire.
Oh, it's Bonjour.
Right. It was called Bonjour.
So Min knows a lot about this area.
I've come to this area often
for a date.
- You know a lot about this place.
- It's nice out here.
(They've arrived at the next spot
while chatting.)
It's breezy here.
- I can smell ginkgo nuts.
- Is it the smell of ginkgo nuts?
- Gosh, the smell of ginkgo nuts.
We should take a photo
since we're here.
- Don't stand against the sun.
- Let's take a photo.
Stop taking photos already!
Why do they keep taking photos?
Hyung In. Can you
take a photo of me?
Jae Suk took more than I did.
- Stop it, Jae Suk.
- Stop taking photos.
- You're standing in the shade.
- Stop it already.
- I haven't taken one by myself.
- Look at Haha.
And the "How Do You Play?" team
keeps taking photos together.
- Don't get together.
- Take it elsewhere!
Don't they take photos for you
on that show?
It's not that.
- I'm just doing my best.
- You're quite sensitive.
Why would you two take photos here?
- They're taking one too.
- You're so sensitive.
- Can you take a photo of me alone?
- Gosh.
All right. Before we have lunch,
to make our
autumn outing more exciting,
Are we playing games?
we'll have Successful Story
of Bright Relay Race.
- It's a relay race?
- A relay race?
You'll form a team of two.
Then you'll have a race
with obstacles.
Here are the obstacles
you need to overcome.
This is a forward roll zone.
You'll need to roll forward
in this zone.
- All right.
- I see.
- Then you'll see hurdles.
- All right.
It's an all-fours zone.
You can only crawl on all fours
and pass through the hurdles.
On all fours?
Next is jumping ropes.
You can just jump ropes
ten times and move on.
Next is a mini ranger training zone.
You can crawl past it on your back.
(Mini ranger training zone, pass
through the obstacle on your back.)
And the last zone
is an assassin zone.
They'll slam you
with toy hammers ruthlessly.
You'll have to pass through that.
Unlike other relay races,
we'll be using a baton
made of chalk.
It'll break easily.
- A 70cm-long piece of chalk.
- My gosh.
Oh, it's that one? It breaks easily.
Oh, gosh.
- It'll break for sure.
- While trying not to...
break the chalk, you'll race walk...
and pass through the obstacles
to make it to the finish line.
Do we have to hold the chalk
while doing the forward roll?
- Yes, you do.
- Oh, my.
- We have to hold it?
- It won't be easy.
- It'll be a team of two.
You'll complete
four rounds in total.
- A relay race?
- You got it, right?
The chalk will end up this small.
We'll deduct the lap time...
by the length of the chalk
you managed to keep.
- Is that so?
- Let's say you finished the race...
in 3 minutes and 30 seconds.
If your chalk is 30cm-long,
then your record will be 3 minutes.
- You're deducting 30 seconds?
- Yes. You got it, right?
Also, since
it's a bright relay race,
when a trot song starts to play
during the race,
- We have to dance.
- You must dance.
During the time you dance,
you can attack the others' chalks.
(They can attack other teams'
chalks while dancing.)
- That'll be dangerous.
- We got it.
But you need to be dancing
while attacking others.
We must be dancing.
We'll end up cracking the chalks.
We'll tell you your teams.
We grouped you in advance
to make it balanced.
- All right.
- Team One...
is Team "How Do You Play?".
- What? Stop it already.
- I'm so sick of it.
(I'm so sick of it.)
I'm so sick of it.
You're not even
discreet about it anymore.
- What's with him?
- You...
- What made you so upset?
- Hey.
- Team "How Do You Play?"?
- What's wrong...
- This is...
- They're dressed alike too.
- Hey.
- You're dressed alike.
What did you say?
Team "How Do You Play?"?
- What's that?
- You want me to call all of them?
You went hiking on that show
dressed like that.
- Come on.
- They did?
- General Manager Yoo, calm down.
- My gosh, this is...
Listen.
How dare you criticize us?
General Manager Yoo,
please calm down.
He called him General Manager Yoo.
"General Manager Yoo"? Hey.
I'll see you next Saturday.
(The JMT employees
hurriedly leave the place.)
Next is...
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
whom everyone roots for.
Come on. You didn't have to.
- Our number one couple.
- Will I do okay with her?
It's Team "Can We Get Married",
right?
- What?
- Hold on.
I'm sorry,
but don't put flesh on it.
You put flesh on us too.
We're also members of Running Man,
but you kept shunning us.
(Gosh, you.)
He's so ugly.
It looks like he's in a good mood,
so we can invite Eun Hye now.
(He couldn't help
but blurt out her name.)
- Stop it.
- All right.
Next is the meeting
of a star and his fan.
It's Hyuk and So Min.
Wait a minute.
Next are Suk Jin and Se Chan.
- It's worth trying.
- It is.
- All right.
- It's worth trying!
It's worth a try.
With Captain Um Hong Gil...
- A strange man.
- It suits him.
A strange man who likes clothes.
- With Captain Um Hong Gil...
- Let's do this!
and an ocean lifeguard...
- We need to hold the chalk and...
- An ocean lifeguard?
- Let's do this!
- We got this!
The first runner from each team,
please stand here.
- The rest will stand over there.
- Okay.
Do you want to go first or second?
I think it'll break right away
once we do the forward roll.
Gosh, we're in trouble.
The forward roll must be difficult.
Suk Jin, be careful.
Get ready.
(Get ready. Start.)
(Broken)
(The chalk breaks in half
as soon as the race starts.)
- Darn it.
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh, watch out.
- Be careful.
Haha, be careful.
- Oh, no.
- You can leave it there.
We need to speed up.
Hurry up!
My chalk!
(Haha and Jae Suk
are currently in the first place.)
My chalk!
(Suk Jin and Se Chan
move up to second place.)
- Hey.
- Who is that?
(Broken)
It's okay.
You need to roll one more time.
- So Min.
- Wait.
- Can't you do a better job?
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
- Why is she...
- You need to race walk!
(Suddenly making a deep bow)
- So Min.
- You should...
It's all broken.
(Walking fast with the chalk
that broke in half)
What will you do now, Hyuk?
I have no idea.
You're done for.
I think this is
So Min's biggest piece.
It's all broken.
We have to race walk, right?
(Behind Haha
who's leading the race,)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo...)
(are catching up fast.)
(The 3 of them have entered
the 3rd course.)
How many?
Break it!
(Break it!)
(They can break each other's
chalk while dancing.)
(Dancing)
(The mid-aged men are excited.)
(While the onlookers are dancing,)
(the players are busy
trying to break each other's chalk.)
(Guarding his chalk)
Attack So Min instead.
(Dancing)
(Right then, the marine boy
runs toward So Min.)
(The music stopped.)
All right.
(Haha who finished jumping rope
10 times sets off first.)
Darn it!
- He's doing great.
- Race walk!
(Haha relaxedly widened the gap...)
(and arrived at the 4th course.)
Do we have to roll forward
in that course too?
No, you need to crawl.
Darn it. Three. Come on, Suk Jin.
Hey. Darn it.
What's wrong with this thing?
Three, four, five.
Suk Jin is horrible at it.
(The marine boy falls behind.)
- Gosh, I'm so tired.
- What was that?
Gosh, this is exhausting!
What's this?
- It's so exhausting!
- How do we pass through?
Gosh, I'm so tired.
How come she's so good at it?
- Darn it.
- What is this?
(His movement is a bit slow
for Hiking Master.)
(While Hiking Master
is struggling...)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
This is so tiring.
(Grunting)
My clothes...
Suk Jin, hurry up!
(The ocean lifeguard met a disaster
while wearing a life jacket.)
My clothes...
My clothes are killing me!
My gosh. They have to
guard their chalks through that?
- You have to protect it.
- Hurry up.
(Attacking with toy hammers)
(Groaning)
(Getting a full body massage)
They're hitting me for real.
Hurry up.
They're hitting him so hard.
- It's a relay race.
- Hurry up.
- Hurry up, Suk Jin!
- Give it to me.
- Is it there?
- It hurts for real.
- Gosh, they hit me for real.
- Your chalk is really long.
(Haha and Jae Suk
are currently in the first place.)
(Ji Hyo enters the last course
as well.)
(Focusing their hits on the chalk)
Hey!
- Where did it go?
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
Hey!
(I'm sorry, Jong Kook.)
(A handful of chalk)
(Their chalk was crushed
by the assassins.)
We're in the first place.
You need to guard that, at least.
Suk Jin!
Team "How Do You Play?"
is in the first place.
My gosh.
Darn these clothes!
(So Min is at the last course.)
Where do I go? What do I do?
(The marine boy
pompously enters the last course.)
(His chalk breaks into pieces.)
- Hurry up.
- Wait.
The yellow chalk.
What is he doing?
(He wastes his time
by looking for the broken chalk.)
Where did it go?
Here, Hyuk. Look at this.
It's all broken.
(He rolls forward fast.)
He's good.
He's like a ninja.
(The slave hunter Dae Gil is back.)
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Hyuk, Se Chan)
(He enters the 3rd course
in no time.)
Hyuk is so fast.
(He begins to chase after the others
after jump-roping 10 times.)
(The slave hunter catches up.)
- Hurry up.
- That's good. Jae Suk, let's go.
(So Min and Hyuk were in 2nd place.)
Se Chan,
(Dae Gil now chases after Jae Suk,
not Un Nyun.)
Hyuk is fast.
Hurry up.
(He passes through
the obstacle right away.)
(Jae Suk becomes nervous
upon seeing Dae Gil so close.)
Hurry up.
It hurts.
Don't hit me there.
(He passes quickly
as he defends himself.)
They hit so hard.
- Hey.
- We need to dance.
Hurry up. You didn't arrive yet.
(Attacking)
(The weakest member
becomes the target.)
Dance.
(She averts the crisis
with her dance skills.)
Shake your body.
(It looks like Jong Kook is
on a treadmill.)
Mine is short already.
(They dance peacefully.)
(Meanwhile)
(Bok Ja takes the stage.)
Hurry up.
All right.
(Bok Ja plays with the rhythm.)
(Glancing over)
(The music stops.)
It stopped.
Hurry up.
(The relay race resumes.)
Hey.
(She hits her tailbone.)
- What's wrong?
- You need to keep going.
Where does it hurt?
- Are you okay?
- I hit my tailbone.
- You need to be careful.
- It hurts so much.
You need to be careful.
(She suddenly gets kicked.)
It hurts so much.
Chief Ji...
Chief Ji rolled on his side.
Are you letting Chief Ji
roll on his side?
(Chief Ji does everything
with ease.)
We make four laps, right?
(Haha, Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, and So Min)
Chief Ji rolled on his side.
Suk Jin,
you need to come back fast.
The length doesn't matter.
(Stopping)
Suk Jin, hurry up.
Eight.
(Chief Ji's traditional costume,
the skirt is the problem.)
The outfit...
The outfit is too uncomfortable.
(The life vest and skirt make
the worst combination.)
(Panting)
What's wrong with my outfit?
(The life vest drags Suk Jin down.)
Suk Jin's outfit isn't helping.
What is this?
(Bok Ja catches up with him.)
(She catches his ankle.)
Hey.
(She grabs him tightly
as if he ran with her money.)
(The match between the weaklings
takes place during the relay race.)
(Haha leads despite getting hit
with toy hammers.)
Hurry up.
They hit my nose.
(Only the last lap remains!)
Team "How Do You Play?"
is doing too well.
- Jong Kook, go.
- Okay.
You need to go.
(Jong Kook starts the last lap.)
(Suk Jin, So Min, Jae Suk,
and Jong Kook)
- Hey.
- No.
- We are the last ones.
(Music plays at that moment.)
(So Min succeeded
to steal his shoe.)
(Swaying)
Give me my shoe.
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
(When the music comes on,)
(Jae Suk quickly runs away.)
(Director Yoo shakes his body
despite the danger.)
(The music stops.)
Suk Jin's chalk is too short.
(The teams in the bottom ranks
still have one more lap to go.)
Don't hit me too hard.
(They are very behind
due to a dogfight.)
- Here.
- Hyuk.
(My goodness.)
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Hyuk)
(The slave hunter
chases after the others.)
(He enters the 3rd course
in no time.)
(The 1st and 2nd places are
still in the 4th course.)
Ten.
(He passes through
the 3rd course...)
(and enters the 4th course.)
(Dae Gil's instincts
come back to him.)
(Only the last course remains!)
(Jae Suk enters the last course.)
Okay.
(Jong Kook enters
the last course as well.)
I am exhausted.
(Dae Gil is right behind them.)
- Where is Se Chan?
- Are we last?
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook
run like crazy.)
(The slave hunter
chases after them like crazy.)
(Will Dae Gil succeed in
coming from behind?)
(Which team will come in 1st?)
- Where is Se Chan?
- Are we last?
Jae Suk came in first.
- We will come in last.
- Good job.
- Jong Kook, good job.
- Okay.
I am exhausted.
(The slave hunter did his best,
but he came in 3rd.)
Hyuk, turn in the chalk.
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin and Se Chan came in last.)
Se Chan, turn in the chalk.
It's too short.
Our chalk is long, right?
- The yellow one is the shortest.
- Whose is the blue chalk?
I didn't know
Jong Kook's chalk was so long.
- I should have broken it.
- The blue one is really long.
I had it in my sleeve.
- Really?
- So you couldn't see it.
- I held a short one on purpose...
- You held a fake one.
to hide the long one.
- He takes things too far.
- Jong Kook is ridiculous.
- For goodness' sake.
- He uses all sorts of tricks.
He is such an eyesore.
The results are out.
Who is the winner?
Please.
Seriously.
One second determined...
the results of the game.
I will give you the final results
in the order of arrival.
You arrived in
8 minutes and 28 seconds.
(Total time:
8 minutes and 28 seconds)
Your chalk was 16cm long.
Okay.
So the final record is
8 minutes and 12 seconds.
(Final record:
8 minutes and 12 seconds)
You arrived in
8 minutes and 35 seconds.
But your chalk was 24cm long.
With 8 minutes and 11 seconds,
you placed 1st.
With 8 minutes and 12 seconds,
you placed 2nd.
(They should have protected
the chalk.)
Mother. We won.
Good job, my son.
With 8 minutes and 52 seconds,
Hyuk and So Min placed 3rd.
We placed third.
Then Suk Jin and Se Chan...
He couldn't roll forward
because of his outfit.
- I couldn't do anything.
- It dragged him down.
I felt like someone was pulling me.
Thus,
the 1st place
will receive 40 dollars.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
receive 40 dollars.)
The 2nd place
will receive 20 dollars.
(Jae Suk and Haha
receive 20 dollars.)
The 3rd place
will receive 10 dollars.
Thank you.
The fourth place
will receive nothing.
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
We will be fine
as long as we don't place last.
- You placed last.
- We placed last.
We aren't done yet.
Currently, Suk Jin is
at the bottom.
Can we take this off?
- Am I at the bottom?
- It's his flesh.
You got your exercise.
- Let's go and eat some eels.
- Okay.
- Eels.
- Give me the money.
- Seriously.
- Eels.
This side is...
My goodness.
It's hot.
- I am like a middle-aged man.
- You really are.
If he hadn't become a celebrity...
We should drink some makgeolli.
He looks like a youth leader.
- Please bring us all the dishes.
- Look at the colors.
I am like a middle-aged man.
Please give us the menu.
Grilled eels,
stir-fried pork and wraps...
- Eels.
There is pork belly too.
Stir-fried pork is nice too.
All right. Let's take a look.
- Let's take a look.
- How much is the eel?
Mister.
- Mister.
- Mister, who are you?
Your reflection in the mirror
startled you, right?
Do you run a restaurant
by the stream?
What are you talking about?
I could go to Hongdae this way.
People will throw rocks at you.
Why would people throw rocks at me?
What are you talking about?
Hongdae, my foot.
Hold on. Do you want to eat eel?
- Eels.
- I should eat eels...
- since I can't eat them at home.
- Do you have money?
I have money.
We will split the cost anyway.
I will get
stir-fried pork and wraps.
Stir-fried pork and wraps.
How about you, Hyuk?
- I will get stir-fried pork too.
- Stir-fried pork?
Won't you get grilled eels?
Won't you?
I like stir-fried pork.
(I like stir-fried pork.)
Eels.
Won't you get grilled eels?
Why don't we order
acorn jello as a side?
"Acorn jello"?
- "Acorn jello"?
- Youth leader.
- You mean "Acorn jelly"?
Acorn jello.
Se Chan, for goodness' sake.
- Everyone.
- You keep looking in the mirror.
Why do you keep looking
in the mirror while you talk?
You look like a mess right now.
Why do you keep
checking yourself out?
- A mess? I can't believe you.
- Right.
Why do you keep looking
in the mirror?
- You have no sense of style.
- Why do you do that?
You keep looking in the mirror.
Jae Suk, you can't win
against Ji Hyo today.
Ji Hyo is the epitome of style.
(The fashionista, Ji Hyo)
Ji Hyo's style is so luxurious.
(It's the style
they have seen dozens of times.)
- Her style is so luxurious.
- Seriously.
She looks so classy.
- She looks so classy.
- Classy.
I am a classy woman.
Let's just eat grilled eel.
Then let's order 4 grilled eels
and 4 stir-fried pork.
- Four.
- Acorn jelly.
Two acorn jelly.
Two acorn jelly. That's good.
- Let's add two doenjang stew.
- Two doenjang stew.
- Captain Um.
- Yes?
Why don't we drink somaek?
- How about makgeolli?
- Shall we make the cocktail?
- What?
- Okay.
- Let's drink.
- Coca-Cola.
- Camera crew, get out.
Everyone should leave
except for Chan Hee.
- Let's make the cocktail.
- Get out.
- Let's mix beer and Sprite.
- Beer and Sprite.
You can't even drink well.
Beer and Sprite.
Two people.
Let's mix the drinks.
- It's nice.
- Let's mix the drinks.
- It will be tasty.
- Who is good at mixing?
I run a small cheonggukjang place.
Mix the drinks.
She has about 1,000 identities.
Do you keep notes?
- Let's mix Sprite and Coca-Cola.
- Okay.
You aren't good at mixing drinks.
Who mixes drinks like that?
Take a glass.
- All right.
- I want a cocktail from Lady Jeon.
- I saw you on YouTube.
- Really?
You are Aunt Cocktail, right?
(Aunt Bok Ja is a cocktail expert.)
- Here.
- My goodness.
Lady Song should drink first.
- Thank you.
- Shake it up a bit more.
(What?)
Lady Song is fixing her makeup.
My goodness.
She is fixing her makeup
before lunch.
(She is incredibly sophisticated.)
She is good.
Take the glass.
- Let's enjoy the drink.
- Give me one.
Let's drink.
Now, the oldest member...
should say something.
- Make a toast.
We don't have
many years left to live.
What are you talking about?
- Come on.
- You ruined it.
- The drink won't taste good now.
- Life is short.
- Our youth starts now.
I have one!
- What is it?
- Even if it's disgusting,
(Even if it's disgusting)
let's live happily
as we did yesterday.
Cheers!
- He just spewed out words.
- What was that?
What kind of toast was that?
- Suk Jin.
- Which answer do you want?
- What kind of ad-lib was that?
- Tell me.
Which answer do you want?
Your ad-lib was horrible.
Tell me.
- Let's live a beautiful life.
- A beautiful life.
Let's live a beautiful life.
Even if it's disgusting...
(They give up on the toast
and enjoy the drink.)
What is this?
- It tastes like a cocktail.
- My goodness.
(The taste is pretty satisfying.)
- It's tasty.
- It tastes like a cocktail, right?
(Lady Song is satisfied.)
The Coca-Sprite is...
- It's nice.
- Seriously.
It tastes like a cocktail, right?
- It does.
- It tastes like a cocktail.
It tastes like a cocktail.
It's refreshing.
Ji Hyo is driving me crazy today.
She seems real.
Middle-aged women
always lift up their pinky fingers.
Lady Song.
(When a member calls her)
(Yes?)
(She is driving me crazy.)
You are single, right?
Yes, I am.
- You aren't married.
- No.
I see.
What do you do?
I look at properties.
- I see.
- She is rich.
She looks at properties.
I am into different things.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why? Are you interested in me?
- He is interested in her.
- Aren't you married?
- Mister.
- I mean...
Don't be like that.
- It has been a while...
- Ji Hyo's character seems real.
since I became single.
What?
(He suddenly moves on with a skit.)
- What?
- Single?
What is wrong with you?
Your wife is alive and well
in Jamwon-dong.
What are you saying?
It's a skit.
Why did you kill off your wife?
Your wife is alive and well.
Why did you kill her off?
- She lives in Jamwon-dong.
- That's reality.
- I will make a toast.
- A toast.
- Ryu Su Jung.
Ryu Su Jung.
(Running Alpine Club
finally got a meaningful toast.)
My goodness.
- You liked that.
- The dishes are here.
- President Yang.
All right. Stir-fried pork.
Acorn jelly.
This is grilled eel.
Grilled eel.
Stir-fried pork.
- It looks delicious.
- Thank you for the food.
- Acorn jelly.
- It's nice.
Thank you for the food.
(The members have a nice meal.)
- Employee Ha.
- General Manager Yoo.
Come on.
You are seeing us on Sunday
as well as Saturday.
This is a continuous story.
- It's nice to have things overlap.
- It's nice, right?
It won't be bad
to keep the same setting.
- Part One, "How Do You Play?".
- You know...
Part Two, Running Man.
I am trying it
since no one else has done it.
Your total is 206 dollars.
Why is the total so high?
- Did we order that much?
- There are only a few dishes.
(They fill their stomachs...)
(with a hearty meal.)
Are the dishes that expensive?
- We ate a lot.
- That was insane.
This will decide on the results.
- We will move to the last location.
- Okay.
Like I told you earlier,
the penalty will be very tedious.
The meal cost 206 dollars.
- That's a lot.
- We ate a lot.
Let's play Choose a Flag
to decide who pays.
The rules will be the same.
- Hyuk will choose red.
- Hyuk, please go.
I don't know what he will choose.
(Red, yellow, green)
Which color should I choose?
I can't choose.
Okay.
(Red, yellow, green)
Yellow.
I don't know what to choose.
(Red, yellow, green)
(Director Yoo goes last.)
They chose yellow.
Yellow.
I didn't know what to choose.
Did only one person choose green?
Is green the minority?
- Who chose green?
- Haha.
All right. Who chose green?
Me!
Everyone except for Haha
will pay 1-7th...
of the total.
How much is that?
Pay 30 dollars each.
Okay. I have no money now.
- Here.
- Thirty dollars.
- Okay.
Okay.
The last course
for Running Alpine Club...
is the shooting location of BTS,
the world stars.
- I see.
- Really?
I really wanted to visit the place.
Check out the forest trail and
the world stars' shooting location.
BTS.
You can enjoy it for ten minutes.
This place is pretty.
I didn't know about this place.
Now that I am old,
I enjoy visiting such places
with my wife.
It's nice.
You know, this place is pretty.
Where do you sell the merchandise?
- I will shop for some items.
- Me too.
Hyuk, this is a good photo of you.
- This is a good photo of you.
- Seriously.
It's a nice photo.
Does anyone want
to buy my cushion? Isn't it cute?
- I won't buy it.
- The mouth looks disgusting.
I will buy this one.
I'll take this one.
How pretty!
What do you think of this woman?
It's a nice photo.
- I will buy it.
- I will buy my merchandise.
I will buy it.
It's my favorite snack,
a fish-shaped bun.
- Fish-shaped buns and steamed buns.
- Fish-shaped buns are nice.
- Steamed bun.
I will eat a steamed bun.
It's so tasty.
It's really tasty and hot.
- I bought six fish-shaped buns.
- It's so tasty.
(They fill their stomachs
with various snacks.)
Are you eating again?
BTS.
I bought six fish-shaped buns.
Didn't you buy too many?
This is really nice.
We will round up the total
before we end the race.
- Okay.
- We bought so many items.
- The total will be high.
I bought 40 fish-shaped buns.
The total is 335.40 dollars.
- This is insane.
- What exactly did we buy?
People will go bankrupt.
- This is insane.
- I should be the minority.
(They will choose a flag
to decide who pays.)
You will receive the flags.
Do we raise one?
I will choose a random flag.
Me too.
- I will put the flags behind me.
- I will choose without looking.
- We shouldn't think.
- Should I use the same method?
That's right.
- Leave it up to luck.
- I should do that.
- Raise a random flag.
I will raise a red one.
Let me tell you that in advance.
- I don't know.
- I will raise a red one.
- No.
- I will raise a random one.
- Me too.
- I will raise it.
- I don't know what it will be.
- One.
- Raise a random one.
- Two.
- Three.
- Okay.
(The flags are raised.)
- This one.
- Why are there so many?
(Se Chan is the only one
who chose a green flag.)
- Why are there so many?
- It's me! I chose a green one!
(It's me! I chose a green one!)
- What?
- Three.
- Red.
- Why are there so many yellow ones?
Seven members except for Se Chan
will split up the total.
I can't believe I picked a red one.
I picked a red one too.
- Green.
- How did I raise a green one?
I should have picked a green one.
You paid 48 dollars each.
- Did you say 48 dollars each?
- That's a lot.
You paid 48 dollars each.
I don't have that much left.
The rankings of the day
will be announced now.
Before that,
I will reveal the penalty.
Please.
I told you many times
that the penalty would be tedious.
- That's right.
- This is bad.
You might hate us for this.
"Tomb of the River"
was filmed in Gangneung.
(Hyuk's movie, "Tomb of the River"
was filmed in Gangneung.)
Take a photo of a road sign
that reads "Gangneung".
- That's the worst.
- For goodness' sake.
(Take a photo of a road sign
that reads "Gangneung".)
- That's the worst.
- For goodness' sake.
(They must find a road sign
that reads "Gangneung"!)
- That will be so annoying.
- Hey!
That's the worst.
You will see it if you drive
toward Gangwon Province.
(There are dozens of ways
to reach Gangneung.)
(They must decide on a route
themselves.)
(They might end up at Gangneung
if things go south.)
- That will be so annoying.
- Hey!
It won't be on our way to Seoul.
Take a photo of any road signs
that read "Gangneung".
- That's the worst.
- Must we get out of the car?
Of course.
We don't know
how long it would take.
I really don't want to get
this penalty.
Seriously.
Wouldn't we find one
on our way to Seoul?
- Right?
- If we don't find it...
Wouldn't we find one
on our way to Seoul?
If we don't find it,
we will be in trouble.
Oh, my goodness.
You are in a good mood, right?
My goodness.
- This is for Hyuk.
- That's right.
- You know,
we might find one
at an intersection.
You just need to find a road sign.
The money we have left.
Please. I want to win.
I just spent 45 dollars.
Number 1 and 2 are excluded.
Number 3 gets 1 ball.
- Number 4 gets 2 balls.
- I see.
- So number 8 gets 6 balls.
- The number of balls matters.
Six balls?
- Six balls...
- You'll definitely get a penalty.
- Jae Suk is right.
- Even if you have many balls,
you might not get the penalty.
- All right.
- We don't know it yet.
- Number one...
- It's So Min.
will win a prize
and get exempted from the penalty.
- That sounds cool.
- I want a prize.
It's So Min.
That's amazing.
- So Min is good these days.
- She's amazing.
So Min is on fire.
All right. Number two.
Se Chan.
- Haha.
- What?
- Me?
Why? When did you save the money?
What's going on?
All right. Number three
is Jong Kook.
Number four is Se Chan.
- Why are you number 4?
- Number 5 is Ji Hyo.
Number 6 is Jae Suk, number 7 is
Suk Jin, and number 8 is Hyuk.
- Jang Hyuk?
- Hyuk, what did you do?
You're number eight.
- Hyuk.
- He was the eighth the whole time.
I bet you'll get a penalty.
- You and I are not going.
- Right.
The prize is
Gangneung's local specialties.
This looks nice.
- I'm so nervous.
- You'll pick two members, right?
Yes. I'll pick one first.
- We don't know it yet.
- It can't be me.
- Two friends should go together.
- Please. I hope it's not me.
I have only two balls.
It can't be me.
Number 1 and 2 are exempted.
The two friends should go together.
- Please.
- No. That can't happen.
- Jong Kook and Hyuk.
- It should never happen.
(Will the two best friends
get picked together?)
(Everyone wants to avoid
today's penalty.)
Here we go.
- Why are you looking at me?
- He's looking and Hyuk.
- All right.
- It's me.
The first member
to get the penalty is...
(They must find a sign that says
Gangneung and take a picture.)
- All right.
- It's me.
The first member
to get the penalty is...
(The member who might
end up going to Gangneung is...)
- It's either you or me.
- The camera is looking at me.
Congratulations.
- It's Suk Jin.
- Oh no.
- How many balls did you have?
- It's Suk Jin.
(Chief Ji is getting the penalty.)
How many balls did Suk Jin have?
It's possible that I might
get away with this.
- How many balls?
- I'm safe anyway.
I might still get picked,
but I'm safe for now.
- It was either you or me.
- How many balls did you have?
- I had 4.
- You had 4 balls?
This is so thrilling.
- All right.
- Please. Not me.
- We have one person left.
- Please. Don't pick me.
Only one person.
Ma'am, please help me.
"I'm Jang Hyuk."
I shouldn't be with him.
Ma'am, please help me.
(Please...)
All right. I picked a ball.
(He picked a ball.)
It's me.
- I'll get the penalty.
- I'll announce the name.
- Not me.
- It must be me.
The one who will go to find
the road sign with Suk Jin.
The member
of the Gangneung expedition is...
- Congratulations.
- Hyuk?
- Yang Se Chan.
- What?
I can't believe this.
(Yang Se Chan is
getting the penalty.)
(What?)
- Seriously?
- This is unbelievable.
(Se Chan got picked
even though he had only 2 balls.)
- He had only two balls.
- My goodness.
I had only two balls.
He had only two balls.
(I had only 2 balls.)
- We made it.
- Hyuk.
This is unbelievable.
- He has only two balls.
- How is this possible?
- He's the most unfortunate one.
- I didn't even imagine it...
- because I had two balls.
- Listen.
Let me just get soaking wet
with water and go home.
I'll just get slapped by Jong Kook.
He'd go to Gangneung
looking like this today.
Should you take the national highway
to find a sign?
I'm sorry, but this isn't an outfit
for taking a photo.
Alpinist Um Hong Gil...
- and...
- Chief Ji.
Chief Ji Suk Jin.
- Please take good photos.
- This is the worst.
I don't know.
- Thank you for today.
- Thank you.
- I couldn't even imagine this.
- It's unbelievable.
- I thought I'd be picked.
(Laughing)
- This is the worst.
- This is crazy.
I'm so upset.
Where would we find the sign?
Sir, where do you think we can find
a sign that says Gangneung?
- Can we find one on our way home?
- Would it be far from here?
I guess we should go...
to Hoengseong.
- Hoengseong?
Wait.
We won't find one near here.
We won't? How long would it take?
It's about 50 to 60km
away from here.
- Is it 50 to 60km away?
All right. First...
(All right. First...)
We might find one in 20 or 30km.
I think so. It should say Gangneung.
Please head to Gangneung.
We should look at the signs
on our way to Gangneung.
I'm so doomed.
I hope we will find one soon.
Me too.
We might find the sign
and say, "What's that?"
We'll see. We might get lucky.
Yangpyeong and Gapyeong.
We need something like this.
So we just keep going
looking for Gangneung?
(So we just keep going
looking for Gangneung?)
- What else can we do? I think...
- Okay.
This penalty is so cruel.
- This is the worst.
- It's ridiculous.
I just feel at a loss.
- My goodness.
- We just need to go to Gangneung.
And we can't even rest on our way.
We should look for a sign.
Gosh, this is...
Why was the movie
filmed in Gangneung?
- I know.
- It should've been filmed in Seoul.
- I wish it was filmed in Songpa.
- Songpa or Shinsa sound good.
- Banpo would've been nice.
- It would've been entertaining.
Gosh, why does it
have to be Gangneung?
So what exactly should we do?
Do we need to take a photo
of a sign that says Gangneung?
Should it say Gangneung?
(They must find a sign that says
Gangneung and take a photo.)
What kind of signs are there?
Would there be one
on the way to Incheon?
Airplane!
Gimpo airport...
No, it wouldn't work.
- It's too far.
- Let's think the other way round.
Is there a KTX station in Gangneung?
(Is there a KTX station
in Gangneung?)
- Is there?
- Gangneung...
Do you know if there's
a KTX station in Gangneung?
- Yes.
- Suk Jin.
- There is.
- Really?
The Gangneung Line starts
at Yangpyeong Station.
- Then...
- But there should be a sign.
There has to be a sign.
Then how long does it take
to Yangpyeong Station?
If there's no sign, we should...
- It takes 40 minutes.
- Pardon?
- It's 40 minutes.
- It's 30km away.
- Is it 30km away?
- Darn it.
(Even Yangpyeong Station
is 30km away.)
Is the station on the way to Seoul?
- Is it on the way to Seoul?
- Yes.
Fortunately, is Yangpyeong Station
on the way to Seoul?
- Really?
- I thought it was the other way.
I don't think so.
I think it's the opposite direction.
Oh, it's the other way.
(The driver sounds bright.)
- Gosh, sir.
- Please.
- "Oh, it's the other way."
- Oh, no.
(They head to Yangpyeong Station
with the innocent driver.)
You know what, Suk Jin?
We're even making a detour.
- We're getting...
- The opposite direction?
- farther away from Seoul.
- We're going backward.
My goodness.
(They are driving 40 minutes
toward Yangpyeong Station.)
If we don't find the sign
at Yangpyeong Station...
- We're here.
- Is this it?
I see the sign
that says Yangpyeong Station.
There's a train station. Please.
- Should we get off here?
- Please.
Please. The sign has to be there.
My gosh. My outfit is too much.
We have to find the word Gangneung.
We must find the word Gangneung.
Please. I hope we will find it.
Wondeok and Yongmun.
- It's not here.
- Gangneung... KTX.
Darn it.
If we don't find the word...
Cheongryangri.
- Gangneung!
- Gosh, you startled me.
Cheongryangri.
(Gangneung, Donghae,
Andong, Jechoen)
(They found Gangneung.)
- That was too loud.
- Please excuse us.
(They let out a shout
and cover their mouths.)
- I'm sorry.
- I was too excited.
I'm sorry. Take a picture.
In 1, 2, and 3.
Done? This is great.
It'd be better to take the KTX here.
You should take the train here.
(Running Nightclub)
(The 7 ordinary humans are showing
off their lame dance moves.)
Sir.
Drag him out.
(Four street women are here
to meet them.)
(Honey J of HolyBang)
She's here.
I love you, Honey J.
(Aiki of HOOK)
(Monika of PROWDMON)
She's so cool.
(Lee Jung of YGX)
Ready?
Fight.
(The weak one I think is...)
(The most popular...)
(Street dancers)
Nice!
(And those below the average)
There you go!
So Min!
(The story about the humans)
(She's an idol. She was
the sexiest one I saw today.)
(You are so cool.)
(Street Human Fighter)