(When someone's leaving,)
(you get together at a certain place
to say goodbye.)
(It's called a send-off.)
(June 13, 2021)
(Lee Kwang Soo's last day
on Running Man)
(A day)
(A month)
(A year)
(10 years)
(He's been with us
for 10 years and 338 days.)
(Even without Kwang Soo,
Running Man's time,)
(Running Man's betrayal,)
(Running Man's jokes,)
(Running Man's laughter...)
(will continue endlessly.)
(And the joy of each episode
will keep piling up.)
(But we hope
it will always be pleasant...)
(to reminisce about the time
that we spent with Kwang Soo...)
(and how bright those days were.)
(Today, we send him off with joy,)
Let's begin.
All right. Thank you.
(but Kwang Soo...)
(will also have to say goodbye
to Lee Kwang Soo of Running Man.)
- So the last shoot is finally over.
- Right.
So this will be
your last pre-recording.
Since this is your last shoot,
we prepared this for you.
Thank you.
(On his last day, he gets dessert
without any mission to accomplish.)
This is really good.
This isn't product placement.
- No?
- No, it's not.
(He tries hard to advertise things
until the last moment.)
We are going to do some races
where you can build...
good memories with the members.
We'd like you to think about...
things you want
to do with the members,
things you want to eat,
or places you want to visit...
on your last day on Running Man.
I want to go to the place
where we shot the first episode.
It's the SBS building.
We don't usually get to go there.
- You mean the roof garden?
- Yes.
Actually, it's not like...
I can go there whenever I want now.
And we went to the Han River
many times.
We crossed the river in winter.
And...
We shot a lot of episodes
at the Han River.
(They rowed across the river
on a paper boat.)
(And they swam across the river.)
I want to go to the Han River...
(They also greeted
two new members at the Han River.)
whatever we do there.
The weather is nice these days.
Things I want to eat?
There was a day...
(Things I want to eat?)
when we shot an episode at my place.
I had chicken soup...
with the members.
(They went to Kwang Soo's place
and ate chicken kalguksu there.)
(They shared the hot soup...)
(and laughed together
on a winter day.)
I think that's my happy memory
about food.
And we recently went
to a pork belly restaurant.
That day,
I saw the members
enjoy the food a lot.
We've been to many good restaurants,
but that day...
I really enjoyed it too.
(He felt happy to see
the members enjoy the food.)
If it's possible,
(He has warm memories about
chicken kalguksu and pork belly.)
I want to eat pork belly too.
In the same episode,
we also went to the LP bar.
If we go there one more time,
they will like it.
(Kwang Soo only chooses the foods
and places that the members like.)
Personally, I just want...
things to be normal as always.
Just like an ordinary day.
Honestly, that's how...
I'm feeling now.
What?
Since this is Kwang Soo's last day,
we're at the place
where we shot the first episode.
(So today's race is prepared
according to Kwang Soo's wishes.)
- Am I right?
- It looks just the same.
- Hello.
- This is where we shot the opening.
We're doing this
for Kwang Soo's last day.
- Hello.
(July 11, 2010,
Running Man's first episode)
(The members look somewhat young.)
(They introduced themselves
in the pouring rain.)
(I'm...)
(a sprout.)
- It rained a lot that day.
- Right.
- It suddenly poured down.
- It rained when Kwang Soo talked.
I think so.
- That's when it started.
- As I said, "I'm a sprout."
(He still remembers
the moment vividly.)
Hey!
- Why are you...
- This is your last day,
but why did you not shave your face?
I didn't see that earlier
because of his mask.
- Hey!
- You can't do this.
- I looked like this last week.
- You should look neat.
I guess it's connected.
He had a beard in the first episode.
- It's not like that.
- You're right.
- You're so meticulous.
- No, it's just for my movie.
- Today...
- He's not usually like this.
I guess even the crew is sad
that this is his last day.
Let's talk about Kwang Soo.
This is his last day.
No.
He didn't say a word
when the cameras were off.
Once the camera was turned on,
he said,
"This is Kwang Soo's last day,"
"so we're at the place
where we shot the first episode."
Say "Feeling! Intuition! Cross!"
- He didn't even look into my eyes.
- Suk Jin.
- Why would he do that?
- Suk Jin, come over here.
- Why?
- Don't stand next to him.
- Why do you suddenly care for him?
- It's not like that.
It's not sudden.
- Kwang Soo, you know how I feel.
- Of course I do.
All right.
Kwang Soo is about to end
his 11 years on Running Man now.
So we should send him out
into the world.
Send him out to where?
- It's not like...
- Into the world?
- I'm getting out of prison.
- The thing is,
For the past 11 years
on Running Man,
Kwang Soo has committed
lots of sins and mischievous acts.
And we should reform him
before he goes out into the world.
So we prepared the Goodbye,
My Special Brother Race.
"My Special Brother?"
They referenced your movie title.
You played Dong Gu, right?
So we analyzed...
what Kwang Soo has done
over the past 11 years...
- to give him a verdict.
- I see.
And we had a former judge...
who is now a deputy director general
of legal counsel review it.
- He will never be released.
- Wouldn't he get a life sentence?
- Do we have to go that far?
- He will never be released.
Kwang Soo can't get out of prison.
- Please play the video.
- He will be there for life.
First, please introduce yourself.
Hello. I worked as a judge
for about ten years.
My name is Jung Jae Min.
- He's a real judge.
- He's a judge.
Why are you being so serious?
- Is he a real judge?
- He's Judge Jung Jae Min.
- Is this serious?
- Is he seriously...
He's a deputy director general
of legal counsel and a writer now.
We've collected
all the mischievous acts...
that Kwang Soo has committed
over the 559 episodes...
- and classified it.
- Okay.
- Property damage.
- Right.
He committed it 58 times.
58 times?
- That's a lot.
- He destroyed stuff.
(Kwang Soo got carried away
and destroyed a lot of props.)
58 times?
(He even kicked away
the members' belongings.)
Look at what he's doing.
Who do you think I learned it from?
That's really...
And he committed assault 353 times.
I got hit as well.
(He beat the members, crew members,)
(and even citizens.)
He beat everyone.
(He kicked, bit, and hit.)
- He hit Jong Kook a lot.
- I got beaten a lot.
(He used every conceivable means
to get his own way.)
And there's public indecency.
- He committed it 37 times.
- Public indecency?
Oh, right.
- That's right.
- That's what he did.
(He didn't take good care
of his pants during the shoots.)
- That was the best.
- And there's fraud.
- He committed it 1,812 times.
- I see.
Actually, we just stopped counting
because there were too many cases.
Aren't you Lee Kwang Soo?
No. I saw him up there.
(He kept lying and bluffing
with no shame.)
He committed 1,812 frauds
in about 500 episodes?
Kwang Soo is the one
who started forgery.
(He even went through
the crew's bags to forge hints.)
Obstruction of justice,
verbal abuse,
blackmail,
- public disturbance...
- Is this how we send him away?
He's just a criminal.
There are 3,353 cases.
(There have been 3,353 cases
of his mischief.)
Gosh, this is terrifying.
- He looks serious now.
- I know.
So...
he used force...
to take someone down.
When he loses something,
he'd grab something.
If he runs away... That's assault.
It makes him a robber.
It's a serious robbery.
The nature of the crime is
quite serious.
"The nature of the crime is
quite serious."
We were doing a TV show
with a criminal.
If that's the case,
we are all criminals.
In the view of variety shows,
what would be the sentence...
for the crimes he's committed?
Kwang Soo,
you can't leave our show like this.
(He decides the sentence
for Kwang Soo's crimes.)
Considering the nature of crimes
and the degree of illegality...
- And he's done it so many times.
- I see.
Considering all that,
the defendant, Lee Kwang Soo,
is sentenced
to 1,050 years in prison.
(The defendant is sentenced
to 1,050 years in prison.)
- What?
- What? 1,050 years?
- Seriously?
- Take him.
Arrest him.
We can't let him go. Catch him.
- In about 500 episodes...
- In the 559 episodes...
Hey, Kwang Soo.
You're done for. You're doomed.
- 1,000 years?
- Catch him.
How would he serve 1,000 years?
According to the consultation
with the former judge,
Kwang Soo is sentenced
to 1,050 years in prison.
In order to get
Kwang Soo out of prison,
the members will perform missions
to reform and train Kwang Soo.
Before the three reform sessions
come to an end at 6:30 p.m.,
the members have to reduce
his sentence.
- Over 1,000...
- You have to get rid of...
all 1,050 years.
- It will be tough.
- If you fail to do so,
you all will get a penalty.
Since this is Kwang Soo's last day,
we prepared various gifts
for Kwang Soo as well.
Really?
Every time you get rid of 150 years,
Kwang Soo will get a chance
to draw lots to pick his gift.
And there will be three venues
for his reformation.
We had a pre-interview
with Kwang Soo...
and decided three places
that he wants to visit...
with the members before his release.
And in order to commemorate
your happy memories today,
a professional photographer
will take photos of you.
There he is.
You will get the photos
at the end of the show.
- We all get the photos?
- Yes.
(The members start posing
for the photos immediately.)
(Actually, the members are keeping
a secret today.)
- Hello.
Hello.
Is Kwang Soo coming late
since he's the main character today?
Today is our last day
with Kwang Soo.
- Right.
- Kwang Soo doesn't know about this.
He thinks we will start at noon.
- Really?
- So he's getting ready now.
And the crew members...
prepared special gifts...
for Kwang Soo
with the members' sincere hearts.
During the missions,
Kwang Soo will get the gifts...
by drawing lots with your help.
- Really?
- Here are the gifts.
The premium champagne, Dom Perignon.
- My gosh.
- We know that.
And a brand-name hoodie.
- Bal-something?
- Yes. Bal-something.
- That's amazing.
- It starts with Bal.
And a brand-name bag,
pants, a decorative picture frame,
a sound bar, and a bedding set.
This is what we prepared.
But he can only receive them
if he succeeds.
You will help Kwang Soo get...
as many gifts as possible
through the missions.
- We'll help him?
- I see.
You will also have a chance to get
the same gifts as Kwang Soo...
- through hidden missions.
- Really?
- I can get gifts too?
- Then we have a reason to help him.
- I can get a hoodie from B brand?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I always wanted a designer hoodie.
Throughout today's shoot,
a professional photographer
that we hired...
will take photos of you
using a film camera.
Kwang Soo likes photos
taken with a film camera.
You will be ranked in the order
of the number of photos...
taken with Kwang Soo.
The person in the first place...
will get the same gifts
as Kwang Soo.
That's awesome.
But the person in the bottom place
will get a terrible penalty.
Why would any of us get a penalty
on a day like this?
The penalty can be a hassle
and scary at the same time.
It's crossing the sky bridge
that is 541m high,
the highest in the world,
where you can enjoy
the whole view of Seoul.
Hey, Suk Jin will cry.
- He'll cry again?
- Yes, he will.
Suk Jin, come over here.
(So they started fighting
to stand next to Kwang Soo.)
Why do you suddenly act all friendly
standing next to Kwang Soo?
- You know how I feel, right?
- Of course, Suk Jin.
Hey, So Min, you stand here.
Right, Ji Hyo. Come stand here.
(They all tried to have more photos
taken with Kwang Soo.)
(Likewise, the 7 members' rankings
kept changing.)
A professional photographer will
take photos of you today.
- There. He's taking photos of us.
- I see him.
We'll give you the photos as a gift.
- Will all of us get photos? Nice.
- Yes.
We'll do the first mission
to reduce the sentence right here.
From the beginning?
I'm worried.
- All right.
- Go on.
You've done a lot.
The first mission is...
(While the rankings are changing,
the 1st mission begins.)
Kwang Soo Knows.
(The 1st mission, Kwang Soo Knows)
In 1 of the 2 boxes in front of you,
there are keywords
that indicate a certain time...
such as "this morning."
In the other box,
- there are numbers from 1 to 7.
- I see.
Kwang Soo,
pick one out of each box...
and ask a question
to which the same number...
of the member as the number
you picked can say yes.
You must include the keyword
in your question.
That is, you succeed if the number
of the members...
who say yes to the question equals
the number that you picked.
- Gosh, you punk.
- He's taking a photo of us.
- Gosh.
1, 2.
Goodbye, Kwang Soo.
(In the end, they got 1 photo
where all 8 of them appear.)
- Please listen to me.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo will ask a question.
- Yes.
And those of you
that the question applies to...
will stand up.
You succeed if the same number
of you as he picked stand up.
- I see.
- Okay. I get it.
50 years will be deducted
for each question you succeed.
- 50 years?
- Okay, okay.
- Kwang Soo, you know us well.
- We can just succeed three times.
Since you know us well,
just go for it.
- Be confident.
- Right.
Kwang Soo, please choose
the keyword first.
(Kwang Soo will choose
the keyword for the question.)
Please show us the keyword
you picked.
Thank you. Now choose the number.
(Keyword, Last Night)
(Number, 1)
Now make a question that starts
with the keyword...
and would apply to that number
of members.
This is difficult.
(The question has to begin
with "last night...")
(and apply to only 1 member.)
Come on! Hurry up!
- Last night,
- Last night...
which of you went to the gym?
Which of you went to
the gym last night?
1, 2, 3.
(He aimed to make Jong Kook get up
as he goes to the gym every day.)
(If no one but Jong Kook stands up,
50 years will be deducted.)
- You failed.
- Jong Kook, wasn't it you?
- Didn't you go last night?
- I went to the gym early yesterday.
I'm not lying, Kwang Soo.
Believe me.
- I went to the gym early.
- He didn't go there at night.
- You should've said "yesterday."
- Right.
- But the keyword is "last night."
- He went to the gym in the morning.
- Kwang Soo.
- Why don't you know that about him?
- Why don't you know that?
- He goes there on Sunday evening.
- Drop it and turn around.
- He often goes to the gym at night.
- Hey, you made him a little upset.
- That was disappointing.
It was disappointing.
Is it something
that could make you upset?
Kwang Soo failed this time.
Please move on.
- Try to focus, okay?
- Right. Focus.
- Okay.
- Try to be more cheerful.
Make it look funny when you pick
balls out of the boxes.
Smile a little while doing that.
- Do something like this.
- Exactly.
Make it funny. That's good.
- Yes. That's good.
- Good job. That's better.
- This is your last time here.
- Get as much air time as you can.
Pour out all you have!
(They told him off harshly
for making it boring.)
- Okay.
- Let's go. What's the keyword?
(Keyword, Last Night, Number, 2)
- Last night...
- Last night!
(Last night...)
- They might switch the channels!
- Wait. Give me a second.
They'll switch the channels!
- Just a moment.
- This is a weekend variety show.
What's with this silence?
- They'll see "Boss in the Mirror."
- No, no, no.
- No! Stay tuned!
- They'll watch another show.
- Don't watch that show!
- Right.
- Last night,
- Last night.
(He started saying the question
hastily not to lose viewers.)
which of you skipped dinner?
Which of you skipped dinner
last night?
1, 2, 3.
- You know we would never do that.
- Dinner?
Turn around.
- What's wrong with you?
- All of you had dinner?
- Isn't it obvious?
- Why would any of us skip dinner?
- Hey.
- I didn't get to eat dinner.
- Why?
- How could you skip dinner?
- What's the number?
- Two.
Did you think we were too sad
because of you to eat dinner?
No, I didn't think that.
- I can't believe...
- Let's just drop it.
- It was an easy one.
- I'm sorry. I'll do better.
Okay. Move on to the third question.
Next, choose the number.
(Keyword, Last Year)
(Number, 1)
Let's do this.
Let's reduce the sentence.
(He's thinking hard and carefully.)
Hey, Kwang Soo, it's getting boring.
Hurry up.
Got it.
- This is difficult.
- Hurry up!
- This is a weekend show!
- I'm sorry.
Just give up if it's so difficult,
you punk.
- Pardon?
- I said, just give up.
"It's getting boring."
That was funny.
- Last year,
- Last year?
- Okay.
- which of you bought a new car?
Which of you bought a new car
last year?
1, 2, 3.
- What? Last year?
- I bought a new car.
(Expected number of members, 1)
- Success.
- Okay!
(Finally, he got 50 years deducted
from his sentence.)
- How did he pull it off?
- Did you think of me?
Yes, I did.
- The SUV?
- Give him a hug!
I'm impressed.
Give him a hug.
I'm so touched.
He knew it. He picked number one.
And he knew Haha was the only one
who bought a new car.
I had another child. That's why.
- He knew it.
- Hey, come back.
- Stop it.
- Go back to your seat, Haha!
- Hey, hey.
- Why are you trying to make...
- people cry already?
- Don't make us cry already.
- Don't look up at the sky.
- Don't do that.
Don't make us cry.
I pulled it off.
- Don't make it unnatural.
- I pulled it off.
By the way,
Kwang Soo did a great job.
You could be released
from prison alive.
You can eat tofu to celebrate it.
Get more years deducted, Kwang Soo.
Please.
(Keyword, This Year, Number, 2)
(Sighing)
I'm sorry to say this, but I can't
watch Running Man this week.
Gosh, it's not that bad.
Are you trying to ruin the show
because you're leaving?
I'm not trying to ruin the show.
(We might get the lowest ratings
on his last day on the show.)
- Why is it taking so long?
- I can...
- I can do this...
- He looks like a donkey.
Could he plan to join
"Boss in the Mirror?"
- Oh, right.
- Could he join the show?
- Why would they accuse me of that?
- Are you leaving our show...
- to join another show?
- I bet it's "Boss in the Mirror..."
seeing that you look like a donkey.
- What's this?
- I'm upset.
- I'll do better this time.
- Try to pick a large number.
- I'll do it faster from now on.
- Use your sense of humor.
- This year,
- This year.
which of you haven't won
any awards yet?
- Not like a toy?
- A real award given at a ceremony.
- A real award?
- Like a prize?
No awards ceremonies have been held
as it's the beginning of the year.
Now turn around.
- Okay!
- Five of us stood up.
- A real award?
- Yes, a real award.
This year, has anyone driven?
- Okay!
- Six of us got up.
(He continued the momentum
and succeeded again.)
- I do but I don't have a car.
- Kwang Soo.
- That one was heart-warming.
- Because you don't have a car?
It was heart-warming. Good job.
I admit it was a good one.
- It was heart-warming.
- Indeed.
Kwang Soo, it was heart-warming.
- As a result,
- Yes.
he got exactly 150 years deducted,
he's going to choose gifts
at random.
(He gets a chance every time he gets
150 years deducted.)
- Right now?
- Yes, we'll begin now.
The first gift is a designer bag.
1 of the 2 eggs is raw,
and the other is boiled.
You'll receive the gift
if you pick the hard-boiled egg.
You will get nothing
if you pick the raw egg.
- It's hard to figure out.
- Kwang Soo, go for it.
- Kwang Soo.
- Go ahead.
Kwang Soo, pick one.
- I choose this one.
- Good. I would choose that one too.
- Break it on your forehead.
- I picked the same one.
- Me too.
- I'm worried since I picked it too.
Let's stay away from him.
- I picked it too, Kwang Soo.
- Come on.
- I picked the same one.
- If that's a hard-boiled egg...
If it's a hard-boiled egg, he'll get
the designer bag right away.
- Right away?
- Yes.
- I had a good feeling about it.
- Let's go.
(Breaking the egg)
- That's amazing.
- Oh, my.
- This can't be right.
- He's already reformed.
- It's hard to believe.
- Hey, you're leaving the show.
- You should've failed.
- People will switch the channel.
You got the designer bag.
Okay!
- Hey, this is not right.
- Hey.
- You should've chosen to be funny.
- People will switch the channel.
- I was just...
- What's wrong with you?
Kwang Soo told us about the food...
he wanted to eat with you guys
before going back to society.
We'll move to the location
to eat it.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
Kwang Soo, please change
into a prison uniform.
A prison uniform?
I didn't know that there was food
that he wanted to eat with us.
(A prison uniform has been prepared
for him.)
Jae Suk, can you drive?
Of course. I'll drive.
Jae Suk, why would you hop
on my back?
(He'll drive Kwang Soo
instead of a car.)
- Why?
- When will I get to do this again?
- Jae Suk.
- Right?
Please take me to the driver's seat.
Who will give me a piggyback ride
after you leave?
Are you giving him a piggyback ride
for the last time?
I got on his back.
I know. I was talking to him.
Thank you, Kwang Soo.
That's okay, Jae Suk.
(Kwang Soo feels happy
after his last ride for Jae Suk.)
Did everyone put on their seatbelts?
- Yes!
- Yes, I did.
I drive aggressively at times.
(They're leaving while chatting
as always.)
- Don't cause us trouble.
- I do that when making turns.
(And Jae Suk is driving as always.)
- By the way,
- Why me?
I realized that So Min...
Did you guys notice it too?
Have you ever seen
a secret royal emissary?
(For the past 11 years,
they felt natural in a crowded car.)
You saw her for the 1st time,
and this is your 2nd time, right?
- Do you have a crush on me?
- No.
(It felt natural
that Jae Suk drove all the time.)
I would even lend you money.
Good boy, good boy.
(Kwang Soo is sitting in the back
because he's a prisoner.)
Don't you think Kwang Soo should be
tied up like a prisoner?
- He should be tied up.
- I'm not an actual prisoner.
How many years do you have left?
- A little more than 900 years.
- We should tie him up.
(900 years to be released
from Running Man Prison)
By the way, Kwang Soo,
do you really have to...
Think again. You see, this is...
- It's not too late.
- Exactly.
Apologize to the viewers
at the end of the show.
Then he goes back on his word?
- You would be okay.
- That would be funny.
The viewers would understand you.
- They'd just laugh it off.
- Exactly.
"Gosh, that brat."
They'd just think he's playful.
- They'd get mad and just laugh.
- Say it was a camera prank.
Say, "I can't find any better jobs
than this."
"I had so much fun
shooting the special episode."
(It's possible to say it was all
a prank because it's Kwang Soo.)
That would be hilarious.
What are you going to do
on Mondays from now on?
- You'll be bored on Mondays.
- It's obvious.
He'll lie in his bed all day long.
- Come to work as a cameraman.
- Exactly.
- Every Monday,
- He'll be at home on Mondays.
you'll think of us a lot.
(Every Monday,
you'll think of us a lot.)
I know.
(I know.)
I remember our trip to New Zealand.
There's a lot of reruns
of the episodes...
- where we traveled to Hong Kong...
- Right.
Watching it made me miss those days.
Recently, I watched the one
where Ji Hyo, So Min, Suk Jin,
- and I went on a trip to Mongolia.
- I remember that.
When you went to Mongolia,
did Kwang Soo and I go to Russia?
- Yes, you guys went to Russia.
- That's right.
We ate snow crab.
I miss those times.
I miss you already.
I miss traveling freely.
I miss you already, Kwang Soo.
Do you remember
when we went to Russia?
- He was right about that.
- It was good.
Are we going to have
a buffet outside?
- I don't know.
- This is Han River Park.
It must be a good place.
- Where are we?
- We're at Han River Park.
Are we going to eat...
on a cruise ship?
- Could that be the case?
- Will we eat on a cruise ship?
- I guess that's the case.
- Really?
- That's it.
- Oh, really?
I always wanted to eat there.
- Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- I've never eaten there either.
We came here for a shoot many times.
We made a lot of good memories here.
(The Han River with good memories
they made while shooting the show)
Shall we walk hand in hand?
(Shall we walk hand in hand?)
(Since it's his last day, they're
trying things they never did.)
"Shall we walk hand in hand?"
- My gosh.
- Are our hands warm?
(Are our hands warm?)
Yes, they're warm.
(Suk Jin was walking
behind Kwang Soo.)
- Oh, my.
- Suk Jin wants to hold your hand.
This will be a lovely but sad scene.
He's acting like that
because the camera is rolling.
- He didn't see it.
- He just saw the camera.
- Who?
- Suk Jin. It makes me upset.
- What did you say?
- I mean, in the elevator,
he didn't even look at me.
- I'm going to take a photo.
- He said it all of a sudden.
- He's the worst.
- I'll take a photo of them.
- What's wrong with him?
Even now, look at what he's doing.
He's taking a photo of us.
(The photographer already took
a photo of them.)
- He's the worst.
- He always does that.
They look so lovely.
(The last feast with Kwang Soo)
What's this?
Something smells good.
I think we're going to eat
pork belly.
- We'll have a barbecue?
- Oh, we'll eat outside.
We'll have a barbecue.
- What's that?
- We'll have a barbecue.
(Kwang Soo chose the most convenient
and familiar menus.)
- Let's sit here together.
- We'll actually eat pork belly.
- Sit here.
- Kwang Soo, sit in the center.
- Come over here.
Kwang Soo, why did you take us here?
Why didn't you choose simple food?
- It's not like that.
- Kwang Soo, what is this?
- I didn't ask for this.
- Why must we eat out here?
I didn't ask for a meal outside.
- You see, Kwang Soo,
- Gosh, seriously.
- you should've kept it simple.
- What is this?
- Having a barbecue?
- Why would you make a fuss?
- A bowl of noodles would be nice.
- I mean...
- A bowl of gukbap would be enough.
- Exactly. This is ridiculous.
Why didn't you order some lunchboxes
so we could have a quick lunch?
They all seemed excited
before the camera was rolling.
- What is this?
- You told the staff, right?
Kwang Soo, you should go home now.
- We'll see you next week.
- I should finish it today.
- Just one more week.
The first menu
that Kwang Soo chose is...
- pork belly with a lot of memories.
- Okay.
The second menu is chicken kalguksu.
- Oh, chicken kalguksu?
- That's good.
- Right. Whenever we visited him...
- Whenever we went to his house...
That's why I chose it.
When Suk Jin and I visited
Kwang Soo's house,
we often ate chicken kalguksu.
It was the first time
Kwang Soo treated us.
You didn't have to point that out.
- My gosh.
- It's true. I won't deny it.
Do you know what the number
on Kwang Soo's chest means?
- What is it?
- 3991.
3,991 days?
- Correct.
- Oh, my.
- My, Se Chan is so smart.
- It's been 3,991 days.
Today is the 3,991st day.
- Since he joined Running Man?
- Then it's been 3,991 days...
- since we joined the show too.
- Since we all joined the show.
- It's the same for us.
- What about us?
- It's been such a long time.
- It'll be 4,000 days after 9 days.
The flame is too weak.
- It's time for you to leave.
- I hope we last long.
- My gosh.
- Why?
I guess he can't stand
any moment of warmth.
Why? What did he say?
He said, "It's been 4,000 days?
It's time for you to leave."
Did you want to do this that much?
(Did you want to do this that much?)
You wanted to have a barbecue
at the Han River?
- Are you happy?
- Why didn't you tell us?
- We could've done it for you.
- You don't even answer my calls.
(You don't even answer my calls.)
- It'll be better than frozen meat.
- Of course.
- Kwang Soo.
- The meat is quite thick.
Look at the fresh meat.
It looks so good.
- It looks delicious.
- It looks good.
You see, chicken kalguksu is
meaningful to us.
(It's time to enjoy the food
that Kwang Soo chose.)
It's cooked now. Let's eat.
Is the meat there cooked?
Is it good?
(Eating a thick piece of pork belly)
Try the soup first
and see if it's good.
It's good.
It was cooked
before it was delivered.
- Is it good?
- It's so tasty.
(He's starting
to get emotional again.)
It's good to eat outside.
Kwang Soo, be quiet.
We're eating here.
But Jae Suk...
(Jae Suk cut him off successfully
to the end.)
He's too chatty.
We don't have time
to laugh and chat.
Then why did you...
We don't have time...
(He laughed and chatted
most loudly.)
Think before you talk.
- Gosh.
- It's good.
This is so nice.
We'll start the second mission now.
It's a simple game.
You have to pull the cloth out
without the bucket falling.
Since you got 150 years deducted,
- you'll choose a gift again.
- Right now?
- The second gift is...
- That again?
a designer hoodie.
This is the best.
- From B brand.
- Go, Kwang Soo!
- Ready.
- I have a good feeling about this.
- This one?
- Yes.
- Me too.
- I'd choose the other one.
Everyone else chose this one.
- Suk Jin, you've been...
- Why?
encouraging Kwang Soo
by his side unlike you.
I've never seen you like this.
Honestly, I'm most disappointed
by him.
When there was no camera around us,
he walked far behind me.
But he ran to me
when he saw the helicam.
(He's upset.)
Come on. The viewers might think
that's true.
I hope you succeed.
Okay. Kwang Soo, that's the one.
Go.
- Kwang Soo seems quite lucky today.
- Indeed.
I'm sure it's a hard-boiled egg.
It must not be a raw egg.
(Could he be lucky for the 1st time
in 3,991 days?)
- Oh, no.
- That's Kwang Soo.
Finally, he's back to his true self.
- What was that?
- I told you to pick this one.
Right. You should've picked
the same number.
You won't get a designer hoodie
since you failed.
What a shame.
Hey, remove snot from his nose too.
That's so heart-warming.
He's washing Kwang Soo's face.
This is beautiful.
Are you happy
that Jae Suk is washing your face?
Blow your nose.
Oh, my.
(Squeezing his nose)
- Jae Suk, you're skillful.
- Of course. I've done this a lot.
We'll ride a ferry
to move to the next location.
- Are we leaving now?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- You can go up there.
- How many photos of me are there?
How many photos?
(He's checking the number of photos
of him with Kwang Soo.)
(1st, Haha, 2nd, Suk Jin,
3rd, So Min,)
(4th, Ji Hyo, 5th Jong Kook,
6th, Jae Suk and Se Chan)
Okay.
Would you like some coffee?
Is that coffee?
(They moved to an improvised
campsite on the ferry.)
This is what I like the most.
I'm sitting on a camping chair
under a parasol.
Thanks to Kwang Soo,
- we're enjoying a relaxing time.
- We got to ride a ferry too.
Exactly. We don't get to ride
a ferry many times.
Oh, gosh.
Kwang Soo... My gosh.
Suk Jin is starting it.
Suk Jin, stop gazing at him
like that.
- Why are you starting it?
- Don't do that.
- It's not like that.
- You're trying to make us cry.
Did you ever make good memories
with him on a private occasion?
- Of course, he did.
- Really? When?
I think he played
a card game with him.
(It sounds too tasteless
to call a good memory.)
- Did we?
- Yes.
- I spent a lot of time with him.
- I bet...
you never let him win
and tried to win more money.
You played cards with him.
I remember that now.
- Right.
- I remember I got double points.
Right. You do share memories
with him.
(Looking around)
Hey, Bo Pil, why are you crying?
I'm not. I had something in my eye.
(Bo Pil suddenly wiped his eyes
while they were talking.)
- Is he crying? Oh, no.
- Why are you crying already?
Why are you crying?
- Come on. Why?
- Why are you crying?
- What's with him?
Bo Pil always cared about you,
unlike the way he talked to you.
Why are tears coming
from only one eye?
- That's an unusual skill.
- What are you doing?
- How do you do that?
- Why are you crying?
- Only one of his eyes is red.
- Everybody cries these days.
Gosh. What's wrong with all of you?
(Imitating a drama scene)
Stop it.
(He's swallowing his tears
by flexing his nostrils.)
Why are you crying? Why?
- They're leaving.
- It blew its horn.
- They're waving at us.
- Bye.
Where is Chan Hee going?
Where is he going alone?
Now he's shooting scenes
without the director's directions.
- Chan Hee is here with us.
- He's here.
(Surprised)
- Chan Hee, I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry, Chan Hee.
- How could you say such a thing?.
Just because you thought
Chan Hee wasn't here...
- You cut him off at the right time.
- Chan Hee, I'm sorry.
You must never leave us.
You complimented him so much
when he was in front of you.
Please stay here with us.
- Don't go anywhere.
- Right.
- Once you leave, this will happen.
- He's so funny.
- The ferry is leaving now.
- Oh, my.
- This is exciting.
- It's moving.
We haven't done things like this
in a while.
You spent a lot of money
on this episode.
We came outside thanks to Kwang Soo.
(The donkey is happy
as the other members are satisfied.)
Suk Jin is getting direct sunlight.
(Only he is under direct sunlight.)
Look at him.
It's as if he's at a tanning salon.
Nice. I picked the right seat.
- He needs to cover his eyes.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I didn't know he liked tanning.
- How can this be?
- Gosh.
- I see seagulls flying around too.
- Seagulls are flying toward us.
- I see them too.
There's a drone up there too. Look.
Oh, those punks. Right. Thank you.
- Their eyes look scary.
- Look at that.
It has the R logo on the side.
- That's nonsense.
- It has the logo on its body.
I think you should catch it.
- Why would a seagull have the logo?
- One of those seagulls...
I think the mission is to catch
the seagull.
Look. It has the logo on its side.
- Kwang Soo, hurry up and catch it.
- Nonsense.
Only then you can finish this.
It has the logo right here.
Hurry up and catch it.
- That doesn't make sense.
- You might get 1,000 years...
- Hurry up and jump.
You might get 1,000 years deducted.
You can finish it right away.
It has the logo on its body.
- Hurry up and go.
- No way.
We're passing the bridge.
I've never seen the bridge
from below.
There might be the monster
from "The Host" hanging there.
- Since we passed the second bridge,
- Yes.
- we'll begin the third mission.
- Kwang Soo, come back to your seat.
Well... As we continue missions...
(Well... As we continue missions...)
- How many are there left?
- It feels...
I hope there will be a lot of them.
It feels like we're counting down
the hours before saying goodbye.
(The mission will be revealed
while everyone's sad.)
All of you will work together
on this mission.
You will take turns to look at...
an elementary-level
Chinese character...
which you must guess
in three seconds.
If all eight of you guess correctly,
Kwang Soo will get to shed
300 years off his sentence.
- 300 years?
If all eight of you guess correctly.
- That's a lot of years.
This is bad. I don't know
many Chinese characters.
- Meanwhile, he knows a lot.
- Him...
Haha, you don't know
what "left" even is.
- I don't know many.
- I don't know any.
- Left.
- The Chinese character for "left."
Doesn't "woo" mean "right?"
- Do you know what "woo" is?
- Left and right.
"Woo" is the character for "right."
Not "woo" and "jwa."
Woo means right.
Woo means right and jwa means left.
- I know that.
- We use it when driving.
(Croaking)
Are you laughing at us?
- Are you laughing at us?
- Seriously?
(Even the seagulls
laugh at the empty heads.)
That one's definitely
laughing at you.
It's so annoying!
I've never heard seagulls
make that sound before.
It was laughing at you like crazy.
That one standing over there.
Why are the seagulls
gathering over here?
Isn't that the one with the R mark?
- There are too many.
- What?
- Hold on.
- We don't need an audience!
- That's super annoying.
- We have an audience.
Let's start over on this side then.
Here we go.
- Starting with Kwang Soo.
- Right.
And go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- "Month."
That's right. Good.
- That one I knew.
- I didn't know.
- Don't you belittle us!
- I knew that.
- I didn't know.
- Don't you belittle us!
I knew it'd be on this level.
- 1, 2, 3.
- "Mouth."
Nicely done!
That one I knew.
Those are the only two I know.
Guys,
I got it right!
Did you know that?
What do I do? That's all I know.
Did you see that though?
He didn't seem sure.
- That one I knew.
- Here's the third one.
- "Mouth."
- Haha, you're up.
1, 2, 3.
"Wol."
- "Eye."
- That's "eye."
(Unbelievable)
- What?
- "Wol?"
What on earth is "wol?"
It means "Thursday."
- It looks like an eye.
- That is incorrect.
- Isn't it "wind?"
- He didn't know.
It's too hard.
Did I look cool
when I got "mouth" right?
I knew "mouth" as well.
He changed seats and got caught
with a character he didn't know.
Mr. Empty Head!
- Let's start over there.
- On that side.
- Oh, no.
- The first one must be the easiest.
- Of course.
- We can do this, guys.
Again, it's elementary level.
- And...
- Don't say things like that.
And go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- "Wol."
- Wrong.
- What?
- "Wol."
- Wrong.
(Wol?)
I meant that it's "eight."
- The syllable is "pal."
- It's "pal," not "wol."
Where did "wol" come from?
It catches you off guard.
It catches you off guard!
- So Min, this is bad.
- Shouldn't we protect her?
- Sit over here.
- It catches you off guard.
- Sit over there.
- Then I'd get a harder one.
Let's go with those
who haven't played yet.
- We three have.
- I'll get a harder one.
I got mine right.
All this after getting
"mouth" right?
- Sit over here if you get it right.
- We got it right.
- You should sit over there.
- Right.
Leader of the Empty Head Clan,
sit over there.
We'll start with Haha then.
Haha will go first.
1, 2, 3.
I know this one.
- "Da."
- It's "da."
"Da!"
- "Da!"
- What does it mean?
Why must I say it?
It's just "da."
- It's not correct.
- "Wol" is just "wol."
He at least got "da" right.
- He got "da" right.
- Haha's clueless.
The character means "many."
- Isn't it better to give up?
- Is it "garlic?"
But So Min knew that one.
- Se Chan...
- Hey, come back here.
- No, don't.
- Take this seat again.
- Unbelievable.
- Please don't.
- I've had it with him.
- Don't.
He asked if the character
meant "garlic."
- Wait...
- "Many."
- He's the worst!
- Don't do this on your last day.
"Does that mean garlic?"
Stop it, okay?
- It's not garlic.
- It means "many."
- Many.
- You thought it was "garlic?"
- No, Se Chan did.
- Se Chan?
I thought it was "garlic."
Like in "many" people.
I get it now. It means "many."
Can you give us the one
for "sun" again?
And go.
- 1, 2, 3.
- "Baek."
1, 2, 3.
It's "Baek."
"Baek."
(He heard Se Chan.)
What does it mean?
It's 1 versus 100.
Seriously? It means "100."
Is it "100?"
(You can't help but drop your head.)
- Did he say "1 versus 100?"
- Does it not mean "white?"
It means "100."
(He was confident enough
to fight 100 men though.)
- Does it not mean "white?"
- It means "100."
"100?"
- Seriously, 1 versus 100?
- Gosh, 1 versus 100.
- That was hilarious.
- It wasn't a bad answer though.
You know,
you need to protect our dignity...
so that we can stay on this show.
Viewers will get sick of us.
- Let them be adequately hard.
- This will backfire on us.
What if the viewers
don't want to see us?
Even those who love us...
will be appalled
by how stupid we seem.
They will be like,
- "How can they not know that?"
- Like this.
- "Seriously?"
- I don't know any of them though.
Ready, set, go.
1, 2, 3.
- You know this, right?
- 4, 5.
- Seriously?
- It means "four!"
- Did you not know that?
- Even I knew that.
I thought about saying "Saturday."
- Seriously...
- How is that "Saturday?"
"Saturday" is this.
Because there are two sticks
inside the mouth?
Don't say things like that.
Kwang Soo, don't show
that you're alarmed.
You should know this one!
Seriously?
Yes, that's "four."
- He gave you an easy one.
- This is bad.
How about 5 correct answers
for 200 years?
- Okay.
- I'll sit this out then.
- Let's do this.
- Just five?
(They replay the game
with an easier objective.)
"North!"
Nicely done.
- "Blood."
- That is correct.
- Of course.
- Seriously?
"Door."
(Kwang Soo answers correctly
followed by Jong Kook and Suk Jin.)
And go. 1, 2, 3...
- "Fire."
- Nice!
- That's right.
- Good job.
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
- Let's end this.
- I can't believe it.
- She got it right.
There's no need to even doubt it.
Jae Suk will get it right for sure.
- Still...
- Let's shed 200 years.
"Flavor."
- That is correct.
- All right!
- "Flavor?"
- That's 200 years.
- "Flavor."
- Yes, "flavor."
- It's used in the word "tasty."
- Nicely done.
That's 200 years off his sentence.
Good job.
So 200 years
have been cut from your sentence,
and now you have 550 years left.
- Good.
- It's not bad.
It's currently 4:30 p.m...
and you have two hours left.
You'll be playing
for a high-end soundbar.
- Okay, I've chosen one.
- All right!
(He chooses egg number one.)
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
1, 2...
- I bet it's a boiled egg.
- Three!
- All right.
- Nice!
Good one.
- You get a soundbar.
- A soundbar?
A soundbar?
- Do I really get one?
- Yes.
(The cruise resulted in
years off his sentence and a gift.)
Good job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Gosh, check out this beautiful path.
- It's stunning.
- It really is.
- This is amazing.
- It is.
- It's so pretty.
- Right, Ji Hyo?
- This is stunning.
- I feel like I'm on a picnic.
Let's take a photo, guys.
(They take a photo
between the flowers.)
- Thank you.
(Kwang Soo,
let your path always be colorful.)
- I feel less queasy now.
- I was a little queasy too.
It's hot today.
- It's hot for me too.
- Please close the door.
- The cruise made me queasy.
- Same here.
I don't feel that good either.
Just because
Kwang Soo's dropping out...
If it weren't for him,
- we'd be doing something else.
- Exactly.
- You just had to quit the show.
- Tell me about it.
Take it back and say
you'll stick around a little longer.
Say this near the end of the show.
"I'll choose one..."
"to drop out instead of me."
That'd be fun.
- It's very Running Man.
- It'll be like a challenge.
Wouldn't it be fun?
"Ji Suk Jin out."
(Ji Suk Jin out)
"I'll be dropping out of the show
against my will."
"We'll be back
after a refreshment period..."
A refreshment period?
The time is 5:18 p.m.,
which means you have
an hour and 12 minutes left.
In this next round,
more years will be shed off...
if you're able
to mimic Kwang Soo better.
This is Hello, It's Me.
The one with the phone call, right?
You will call
Kwang Soo's acquaintance...
pretending to be him.
The more you...
(Call Kwang Soo's acquaintance
pretending to be him.)
(To win the round,
they must fool the receiver.)
(They'll lose the round
if the receiver figures it out.)
This won't be easy at all.
Can you say "Hello?"
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
Hello.
- Who will go first?
- Se Chan.
Hello.
- Right.
- Hello.
- Sure.
Suk Jin, are you willing to play?
I should.
No, there's no need for that.
- I should give it a try.
- Pick someone...
who isn't home.
- Someone who's outside.
- That's right.
Someone who's out and about.
To mask the sound?
It'll seem less obvious
if other sounds get mixed in.
Wait. How about...
I've never talked to Ahn Bo Hyun
on the phone,
- but he texted me.
- Really?
- Ahn Bo Hyun?
- Yes, he texted me.
That's perfect.
He won't know my voice
since we haven't talked before.
If you call him...
Yes, he might not realize it.
What did the text say?
- He said I did a good job.
- We should know.
- Perfect.
- He told me...
to have a good last day.
- This will work for sure.
- I bet it'll work.
Even Suk Jin could make it work.
- Do you want to give it a go?
- Would it work?
Your voice has been
exposed a lot lately.
- Who is he though?
- He's an actor.
(He gives it a go without
even knowing who the receiver is.)
- Wait.
- Hello?
(Will Suk Jin be able
to fool Bo Hyun?)
- Hello?
- I see that you texted.
Yes?
(Who is he trying to sound like?)
You did a good job on the show.
Has filming ended?
Yes, just a minute ago.
I congratulate you on a good job.
Thank you for texting me.
Please don't mention it.
It was nothing.
- It was an emotional day today.
- Right.
- So I'm grateful.
- He's emotionless.
Please don't mention it.
Then...
We should work out together
sometime.
Sounds good. Anytime, Kwang Soo.
Where exactly do you live again?
Seongsu-dong.
I live close to your place.
That's right next to where I live.
Isn't this him just
talking to Suk Jin?
We're only five minutes away.
Five minutes?
We should meet up then.
I haven't been
in the best mood these days.
- His mood?
- Call me when you want to work out.
Sure thing. Anyway,
thank you for the text.
I'll treat you to dinner sometime.
Sure thing. Please give me a call.
Once again, good job.
Sure.
Bo Hyun!
- Hello?
- Anyway, Suk Jin succeeded?
Right.
That was Suk Jin
on the phone just now.
How could he not know?
It sounded completely different.
- Gosh, well...
- It sounded completely different.
Just hang up.
Bo Hyun, that was Suk Jin.
How could you not know?
- Anyone could tell.
- I thought he cried.
What?
I knew it didn't sound like him.
I thought he sounded different,
so I thought he cried.
No.
Even if he cried,
- his voice was very different.
- Right.
I know. That's why...
I was going to ask,
- Right.
- but I thought he sounded upset.
You thought he sounded sad,
so you couldn't ask?
(Bo Hyun let it go
in case Kwang Soo was upset.)
- Okay.
- Thank you, Bo Hyun.
- Thank you.
- He fell for this?
I started to feel guilty
while I was doing it.
You fulfilled the maximum time,
so you reduced 300 years.
300 years.
That's incredible.
That's really incredible.
(Thanks to Big Nose,
Kwang Soo's release gets closer.)
This is so funny. How did it work?
How interesting.
The quiet that comes after laughing.
Right. We're really going
to Kwang Soo's place.
- There's a lingering feeling.
- Right.
(They started at SBS in Mok-dong,)
(and they are getting closer
to Kwang Soo's home.)
Suk Jin's sleeping.
He's sleeping.
(He was talking about
lingering feelings,)
(but he fell asleep
as soon as they stopped filming.)
- Kwang Soo! Congratulations!
- Thank you!
Kwang Soo! Congratulations!
(Really surprised)
(Why are you congratulating him?)
But seriously...
I think it's right to do that.
- Right. It's right to do that.
- Right.
- It's the right thing to do.
- It was too cruel.
But still...
That's the right thing to do.
- Even if you consider the time...
- Right.
- So you all agree, right?
- We do.
- Suk Jin...
How could you decide
like this though?
- About this, I...
- You have to do it like that.
I didn't expect such a twist.
Do you agree?
Suk Jin, what should we do?
Should we do it like that?
- Right.
- Then Suk Jin will leave the show.
(He agreed to leave the show
without realizing.)
Gosh, Bo Pil, you're really...
(The members and the staff
are sincere about teasing Suk Jin.)
- He's so mean.
- For the past 11 years...
This will be another moment of
Ji Suk Jin's light sleep.
A moment of
- Suk Jin was really surprised.
- Gosh, I was so surprised.
We're arriving at
the final reformation venue.
For the next mission,
Kwang Soo will decide the order
everyone will get off in.
Send Suk Jin first.
It's not a bad idea to go
in that order.
- Shall we start from the front?
- 1, 2, 3, 4,
- 5, 6, 7.
- Right.
What is it? I'm so curious.
I'll put down the foundations.
Yes?
- In this mission,
- Yes?
you can reduce Kwang Soo's sentence
according to how well you know him.
It's the Lee Kwang Soo
Aptitude Test.
Right.
All seven members will answer
a question about Lee Kwang Soo,
and for each member
who gets it right,
Kwang Soo's sentence
will be reduced by 40 years.
They're questions about Kwang Soo?
As of this moment,
the remaining sentence is 250 years.
If all seven members
answer correctly,
the mission will end right away.
Okay.
(Meanwhile, the other members
wait for their turns.)
(Looking)
Do I have to divide everything
I did with Kwang Soo?
(Now that they arrive
at the final destination...)
I don't know anymore.
"I don't know."
You just have to do it.
The next person can go out now.
- Haha.
- It's Haha.
I can do it!
You can do it!
Haha is on his way.
- Ji Hyo. You can do it!
- I'll see you in a bit!
You can do it!
- Song Ji Hyo. You can do it!
- You can do it!
(As each member leaves,)
Okay.
(the inside of the bus
is filled with silence.)
This is the final destination!
(It's the final destination!)
Gosh, Jong Kook.
Don't look at him like that!
Let's go. Okay.
(They spent the day laughing,
but as the end draws near...)
They say
it's better to get it over with...
(The word "last"
feels more real to them.)
(They take a photo while they wait
for their turn.)
(They spent the past
11 years together,)
(and in the future,
today will become a distant memory.)
(We will now start the final trip
down memory lane with Kwang Soo.)
- Was it hard?
- Mine was hard.
What was your question?
What?
- Were all the questions different?
- I think they're all different.
There he is.
Hold on.
Why do you keep playing this song?
We can't hear this song anymore.
(Kwang Soo's theme song
is played for this special day.)
- Come in.
This song is very sad.
Gosh, it's Kwang Soo's last day.
My gosh, it's so sad.
- As you all know,
- Yes?
you all received a question about
Kwang Soo as you got off the bus.
- Right.
The first person to get off the bus
was Suk Jin.
(The 1st runner is Suk Jin.)
His question asked
what Kwang Soo's debut project was.
(What was
Kwang Soo's debut project?)
I don't think I got it right.
Kwang Soo,
what project did you debut with?
"Here He Comes."
- "Here He Comes?"
- "Here He Comes."
- That one was hard.
- That's hard.
The first question was hard.
I don't think he got it right.
He didn't get it right.
He couldn't have gotten it right.
- Right.
- I was in...
"High Kick Through The Roof."
Was it "High Kick Through The Roof?"
- The first...
- How do you really feel?
- 191cm.
- Right.
- 300mm.
- 290mm.
(What's Lee Kwang Soo's height
and shoe size?)
(Height 191cm, Shoe size 290mm,
Height 192cm, Shoe size 300mm)
- He got it wrong.
- He was off by 1cm.
1cm and 10mm.
- You wear 300mm.
- He was wrong.
There's a toe that's more rotten.
The main one.
- Right. That's why...
- The right toe.
- What is the answer?
- My right toe.
- That's right.
- It's his right toe.
- He used to paint it.
- Back in the day.
- I changed it.
- It's his right toe.
We used to color it
with a permanent marker.
Nobody got a single question right.
Next up is Yoo Jae Suk.
What's Kwang Soo's father's name?
I had a hard time remembering.
Did you remember?
If you get this right,
it would be unbelievable.
It was a long time ago.
- Can you tell us his name first?
- I believe that this is his name.
(What is
Lee Kwang Soo's father's name?)
- "Lee Jong Ho?"
- What is his name?
His name is Lee Jong Ho.
- Did I get it right?
- You got it right!
(He's surprised too.)
How do you remember the names
of celebrities' fathers?
- It's like "TV Brings Love."
- Am I right?
Doesn't it seem like
"TV Brings Love?"
- That's incredible.
- That's right.
That's his name!
- Right.
- Am I right? Is this his name?
- I think you're right.
- It's like "TV Brings Love."
How did you know?
- Are you crying?
Kwang Soo...
- All of a sudden?
Why are you crying?
- Why are you crying so suddenly?
- This isn't the right timing.
- Why are you crying?
- He said your father's name.
- His father was mentioned.
- His father.
He thought of his father.
- He was a part of Running Man too.
- That's right.
- His father was on the show too.
- Right.
Hello, sir.
He hits me
even when there aren't any cameras.
(He is a special guest who joined us
a few times with his kind smile.)
I saw that you got hit
3 or 4 times yesterday too.
- Really?
- He was improvising.
- How did you...
- But this...
(Jae Suk remembered his name.)
If this is the case,
I know Suk Jin's father's name...
as well as Kwang Soo's father.
- Right.
- I must memorize everyone's names.
- Next was Jong Kook.
- Right.
He wrote the answer down
the fastest.
Really?
- I wrote it as soon as I heard it.
- He really did.
What's the design
of Kwang Soo's bike?
Zebra.
- That's correct.
- Right.
- The answer is?
- Zebra.
- Of course.
- He's seen it.
I know what it looks like.
It's hard for me not to know.
I've seen it before.
We went cycling together...
and rode around the Han River
for four hours.
His sofa has a zebra print too.
- Right. It's zebra.
- Right.
- His underwear is zebra print too.
- His underwear too.
What's the title of the movie
that Kwang Soo is filming right now?
- "Happy New Year."
Please show us what you wrote.
- How did you know?
- It's because she's an actress.
- She got it right.
- That's right.
- Thank you. I'm touched.
This is the last question.
It was "What is
Lee Kwang Soo's phone number?"
- What?
- This is hard.
- This is really hard.
- Nobody memorizes numbers anymore.
- Right.
If he gets
four consecutive numbers right,
we will count that as correct.
- Let's look at your answer.
- Okay.
Out of the eight numbers?
010-2753-8...
I've never even heard
of this number before.
(I've never heard of this number.)
Seriously.
(The touching moment is ruined.)
I seriously... Gosh, this is...
My tears just dried up.
He didn't get
a single number correct.
- I thought it was right.
- Me too.
He sounded so confident.
Why were you so confident?
It's not even close.
I'm sorry.
I always look up your name.
- My tears dried up too.
- Isn't this too hard?
As a result,
you got three questions right.
For each question, you got 40 years,
so it will be reduced by 120 years.
- How many years do we have left?
- How much is left?
You guys have 130 years left,
and the current time is...
It just turned 5:59 p.m.
- That means Kwang Soo...
- Then Kwang Soo...
will be imprisoned.
- He can just go in right now.
- Right.
If you combine what you got
on the bus,
you get a total of three chances
to choose gifts at random.
What is it this time?
This time, it is a pair
of trendy and expensive pants.
- What's trendy and expensive?
- What is trendy?
I think these pants
might be from a popular brand.
I hope you win today.
- I hope you win.
- Seriously. We're being serious.
- The right one?
- Yes. Go ahead.
This might be a splash.
(If it's a hard-boiled egg,
he gets a pair of expensive pants.)
You have to hit it on your forehead.
(Hard-boiled egg)
(Kwang Soo is doing well today.
He gets a pair of nice pants.)
- An expensive bedding set.
- Go ahead.
(Another hard-boiled egg?)
Did you see that?
Why is he doing so good today?
(He exceeds everyone's expectations
and gets the bedding too.)
Hey. It's your favorite, champagne.
- You'll get a lot of gifts today.
- You can do it.
(He gets another hard-boiled egg.)
- What's with him today?
- I can't believe it.
- Gosh, this is...
Aren't they both hard-boiled eggs?
I can't believe this.
- You can tell when you spin it.
- What's with you both?
- See?
- You're right.
Raw eggs don't spin.
Right. These are raw eggs.
- You're right.
- Hard-boiled eggs spin.
- Raw eggs don't.
- This one doesn't.
Now that it's time
for Kwang Soo to leave,
his luck is going back to normal.
Hey, Bo Pil,
why are you putting your head down?
As a result you were successful
all three times.
- See?
- No way.
- He got it all.
- You're incredibly lucky today.
As a result,
you have about 20 minutes left.
The time you have left is 130 years.
I'll give you the mission
to take care of the 130 years.
In this mission,
Unlucky Kwang Soo's soulmate,
the pirate, must come out
to get rid of the remaining years.
My Last Pirate Roulette.
- It has to come out?
- My Last Pirate Roulette.
When you stab the pirate
with the knife,
you will get 150 years reduced
if you get it on the 1st try,
140 years reduced if you get it
on the 2nd try,
130 years on the 3rd try,
and 120 years on the 4th try.
We will continue
until the 8th player like this.
Once the 8th player has gone,
the pirate gets reset,
and you can try again.
- However, that much time will pass,
- Right.
and if that's the case,
you may not get rid of it all
within 20 minutes.
It will be best for you to hurry.
Let's hurry.
I'll give it to you.
It's 150 years
if I get it on my 1st try?
It's impossible to do that.
- You've done it before.
- You have.
It would be cool if you do it
at the last moment and leave.
- Right.
- Did the spirit of variety shows...
come at the end?
- Don't be burdened.
- I don't know.
- I'll just...
- Right. It's impossible.
(It popped out!)
It popped out!
(He succeeded on the first try.)
- Kwang Soo... You...
- Hey.
- Does this make sense?
- You're insane.
This isn't a lie.
Really?
- Did you mark it?
- You can't mark it.
You don't know where it would be.
Every time...
I don't think they'll believe this.
Because it's random...
No, there's nothing here.
Don't go!
Does this make sense?
Just don't go!
Why are you leaving
when you're like this?
There really is
a spirit of variety shows!
Seriously.
The person behind us
must be surprised too.
- Weren't you surprised?
- He looks really surprised.
- You saw everything, right?
- We didn't plan this, right?
- Does this make sense?
- How does this make sense?
It doesn't make sense,
but with 12 minutes left, at 6:18 p.m.,
Lee Kwang Soo is released
after serving his full sentence.
- Does this make sense?
- The expression sounds a bit...
- He's being released.
There must be ghosts.
- Seriously.
- I'm at a loss for words.
It's so scary.
Are we just letting him go?
Or are we clinging onto him?
- We're being cool.
- We're being cool, right?
- This is your last gift.
- I have chills.
When will you get to do this again?
- At this timing,
- You should go.
it's time to let things explode.
You got everything but the hoodie.
Okay.
- It's the trendy decorative frame.
- A frame.
- Okay.
it will look really pretty
in your home.
- Look at that.
- In the end, this happened.
(Raw egg)
(The spirit of variety shows made
the perfect timing for this song.)
So this is how
the spirit of variety shows...
sends Kwang Soo off in the end.
He did this for you.
(Cracking)
(The last hard-boiled egg
doesn't get chosen by Kwang Soo.)
- That's right.
- As a result,
the gifts
that Kwang Soo received are...
a bag, sound bar, pants, bedding,
and champagne.
(A bag, sound bar, pants, bedding,
and champagne)
You weren't unlucky today.
- This...
- You were blessed.
In any case, you got rid of
all 1,050 years of the sentence.
- Right.
The photos we took today
have been printed...
- and are on their way. Yes.
- Are they?
In the meanwhile,
since we're at an LP bar,
each of you can write a message,
and we can listen to some songs.
Since one song per person
is too many,
the four older guys
will request one song,
and Ji Hyo
and the two youngest members...
will request a song.
- Let's make it light.
- Of course.
We need to make it light.
- We'll make it light, okay?
- Right.
(The older guys hate things
that make them cringe.)
(While they all start
to write carefully,)
- It's already...
- 30?
(the LP bar owner
begins choosing the song.)
(It's a rare sight
to see the members...)
(be so serious and sentimental
on Running Man.)
(Every word that they write down,)
(they remember
bits of their memories.)
I feel sad
as I'm thinking about what to write.
It's starting to hit me
now that I'm writing this.
Me too. This is...
A little bit.
(What does Kwang Soo want to say
to the members as he leaves?)
When we read our messages,
the music...
Okay.
Do you want to start
with the older members first?
I should draw a nice picture
of Kwang Soo.
- We'll start with Suk Jin.
- Me?
- Suk Jin is starting.
- Seok Sam...
- I wrote it calmly. I just...
- Okay.
- You can start.
- Should I start?
Don't cry.
- Don't cry.
- I don't even know.
(He tries to hold back his tears,
but his eyes well up.)
I don't even know.
(He tries to hold back his tears,
but his eyes well up.)
Whose is it?
- I'll read it.
- It's Suk Jin's.
Don't cry.
This one is from Suk Jin.
"It has already been 11 years
since I first met you."
"You were just Long Legs
Lee Kwang Soo whom I met at work,"
"but now you're my little brother
whom I'll be with forever."
"Kwang Soo."
"I was happy when I shouted..."
"'Feeling! Intuition! Cross!'
with you."
"I was happy when I shouted..."
(He skipped the development and went
straight to saying he's happy.)
(The touching moment was broken
into pieces.)
- He ruined the moment so suddenly.
- So suddenly.
- My gosh.
- Gosh, Suk Jin is...
"'Feeling! Intuition! Cross!'
might've been nothing to others,"
"but I was sincerely grateful
for each moment of it."
"Kwang Soo, you are kind and cool.
One day..."
Easy, or Lee Ji,
like Lee Kwang Soo and Ji Suk Jin.
You guys are incredible.
(The Lee Ji Brothers were famous
for being weaklings,)
(but whenever they were together,
they were quite reliable.)
(They have good feelings
and good intuition.)
"Kwang Soo,
let's see each other forever."
"Let's be friends forever.
Even if you're not on Running Man,"
we're family.
I love you, Kwang Soo."
That's what he wrote.
Why did your handwriting
get so big as it progressed?
- Right.
- Well...
I experienced my tears
drying up again.
(As it went beyond five lines,
he began to scribble it down.)
- This time it's my turn.
- Okay.
(They continue
with Jae Suk's message.)
"To my beloved brother Kwang Soo."
"It has already been 11 years
since we started Running Man."
"It's hard to put into words
how much effort you put in."
"You did so well."
"I don't know who to interrupt..."
"and who to ask
for piggyback rides anymore,"
"but I think it will end up
being Se Chan or Suk Jin."
(Me?)
He's telling him not to be worried.
My tears are drying up.
I'm going to suffer more
because of you.
My tears don't go beyond this point.
(He only thinks
about joking around.)
- Don't worry.
- He's saying he has alternatives.
Right. I have alternatives.
It could be Se Chan or Suk Jin.
"It will feel empty and be hard
without you around,"
"but don't worry about us."
"Do everything
that you've wanted to do."
"Let's see each other often."
"Call me if you ever need anything.
Thank you, Kwang Soo."
"It wasn't boring because of you."
Gosh, I...
Whenever we had a shoot,
Kwang Soo kept me
from feeling bored.
Se Chan and Suk Jin
should play that role from now on.
- We will work hard.
- You aren't transferring duties.
- Kwang Soo.
- Look at him.
You are giving him no chance to cry.
Since Suk Jin has a bad back,
I will give you piggyback rides.
- Give me piggyback rides.
- I will strengthen my legs.
Jong Kook can do it too.
Kwang Soo really kept us
from getting bored.
Let's read Jong Kook's letter.
(Jong Kook's letter)
- Is it mine?
- Read Jong Kook's letter.
"I don't know why it was so fun."
"We used to laugh
every time our eyes met."
"I thought
we would stay this way..."
"Stay this way forever."
"And I thought..."
"you would be there until the end,"
"which is why I think
I feel even sadder."
"We won't be together
on Running Man anymore,"
"but let's be together
for the rest of our lives."
"Be healthy always, you punk."
- This is a song for you.
- Here you go.
- Seriously.
- Take the drawing too.
- My goodness.
- He drew Kwang Soo nicely.
Thank you.
(Jong Kook shyly hands over
a sketch of Kwang Soo that he drew.)
- Seriously.
- Take the drawing too.
(I love you!)
- He drew Kwang Soo so nicely.
- Thank you.
How many talents does he have?
About three.
Singing, variety shows, and drawing.
- I see.
- Yes.
If we include exercising,
that makes four.
"To my younger brother, Kwang Soo.
To my lovely Kwang Soo."
"Hello, Kwang Soo. It's me, Haha."
"Since I saw you every week
for the past 11 years,"
"I feel like I will see you
next week..."
"as well."
"It's because you did your best..."
"and showed
an incredible amount of effort..."
"that so many viewers are upset..."
"and as sad as we are."
"You worked hard."
"Kwang Soo, who will I tease now?"
"Who will I con now?"
"With whom
will I stay up all night talking?"
"I love you."
"I will pray
that you stay dazzling and cool..."
"and realize your dreams
no matter where you are."
"I love you, Kwang Soo!"
"Stay healthy and happy."
"This is a passionate goodbye.
From Haha."
- Toy's song.
- "Passionate Goodbye."
- "Passionate Goodbye" is nice.
- All right.
"Passionate Goodbye."
- "Passionate Goodbye" is nice.
- All right.
"Passionate Goodbye" is nice.
(This is a passionate goodbye.
From Haha.)
- It's a very nice song.
- It's really nice.
- I think it's perfect.
It's a cheerful goodbye.
Yoo Hui Yeol has only one talent.
(Kwang Soo, it's a happy, cheerful,
and passionate goodbye!)
Only one talent.
(As friends and colleagues,
they stayed by Kwang Soo's side.)
(Suk Jin, Jae Suk,)
(Jong Kook, and Haha)
(In his mid-20s, Kwang Soo was
the immature youngest member.)
(He truly liked and cherished
Kwang Soo.)
- What? What is it?
- It's like a party.
(The man who's the best
at teasing Kwang Soo, Jae Suk)
(Despite being scared of him,)
(Kwang Soo turned to him first
in times of need.)
(Kwang Soo's moral support,
Jong Kook)
(Kwang Soo's forever ally, Suk Jin)
(Kwang Soo's forever older brother,
Haha)
(They are precious men
who filled Kwang Soo's 11 years...)
(with happiness.)
(And as Kwang Soo once was
to the older members,)
(younger brother Se Chan
became Kwang Soo's happiness.)
Se Chan.
Se Chan, come on.
(The youngest members
burst out in tears.)
(Kwang Soo was Se Chan
and So Min's biggest support.)
Don't cry.
Why are you crying?
(Their hearts are full of sadness,)
(but they will say
a passionate goodbye.)
All right.
- My goodness.
- That was nice.
The next ones are...
Se Chan, So Min, and Ji Hyo.
(It's Ji Hyo
and the youngest members' turn.)
"During the mean,
happy, exhausting,"
"stressful, touching moments..."
"and when we went
to unfamiliar places, and saw..."
What is this letter?
(What is this letter?)
"And saw fascinating things."
"And saw fascinating things,"
"thank you..."
- "Thank you..."
- Seriously.
"Thank you for staying with me
through thick and thin..."
(Ji Hyo's hand-written letter
is harder to crack than a code.)
"for the past 11 years."
"Thank you. You worked hard."
"Kwang Soo,
you are my younger brother."
"I love you, Kwang Soo."
That's simple.
- That suits Ji Hyo.
- Is that all?
- That's simple.
- That's all.
- Is that all?
- That's healthy.
"Kwang Soo,
you are my younger brother."
(Ji Hyo stayed the most composed.)
(Two hours later,)
(she stayed behind
after the shoot...)
(to write the words...)
"Kwang Soo, it's me."
(that she was too shy to deliver
in another letter.)
"Like I said earlier,"
"it still doesn't feel real to me."
"I think deep sadness will hit me
and make me crumble..."
"when it hits me
that you are no longer here."
"Visit whenever you miss us."
"I love you, Kwang Soo."
- So Min's letter.
(So Min's letter)
"Kwang Soo."
"I am really thankful
that I got to know you..."
"during the time
that is either short or long."
"I am really thankful
for the unforgettable memories."
"I will pray for you
each step of the way,"
"and I will keep the show going."
"Visit Running Man anytime.
We will be waiting."
All right.
Okay.
Yangsebari.
(Se Chan's letter comes next.)
"Kwang Soo, you worked hard
for the past 11 years."
"I was happy to spend four years
with you."
"We used to call each other
after every shoot..."
"and have long conversations.
I guess that won't happen now."
"I will miss you a lot."
"I will always miss you,
think of you, and feel empty."
"Now, do everything you want to do
in the world without penalties."
- That's right.
- The world without penalties.
- He is right.
- He is good.
- It is the world without penalties.
Se Chan doesn't disappoint.
Which song did they request?
(The song Ji Hyo, So Min,
and Se Chan requested is...)
It's "Goodbye."
- "Goodbye?"
- It's a song by Jung Jae Wook.
- Goodbye, my precious one
- Thank you
Jung Jae Wook.
- I love this song.
- It's a good song.
(Kwang Soo, goodbye.)
(Don't be sorry)
Spit it out.
- You told me to eat it!
- You punk!
I told you to unwrap it, not eat it.
(They fought without feeling sorry
for the past 11 years.)
(Since she was
so close and precious to him,)
(Kwang Soo wanted
to fall into her arms first.)
You have a long torso.
(From the moment
they visited the show as guests,)
(So Min and Se Chan bonded
with Kwang Soo.)
- Really?
- Young blood!
(They formed
the young members' clique.)
(They were happy
when they were together.)
We did it!
(I was happy)
(The younger members are special
to Kwang Soo...)
(and he will never forget them.)
(Goodbye, my precious one.)
Now...
- Kwang Soo's letter remains.
- Kwang Soo's letter.
All right.
(Kwang Soo will deliver...)
(his last story.)
"Members,"
"you helped me become
the person I am today..."
"and gave me another family."
"Thank you so much."
"I am sorry."
"Again, I am sorry."
"I didn't do well
over the past 11 years,"
"but I think I did my best."
"Every week, the Running Man members
do their absolute best."
"Please continue to give the show
a lot of love and attention."
"Thank you."
(I didn't do well
over the past 11 years,)
(but I think I did my best.)
(Every week, the Running Man members
do their absolute best.)
(Please continue to give the show
a lot of love and attention.)
(Kwang Soo left an empty spot
in Running Man...)
He always sits there.
(and Running Man left an empty spot
in Kwang Soo.)
- That means he is confident.
- Yes.
(We hope
pretty flowers will grow...)
- Come on.
- How pretty!
(in those empty spots.)
Seriously.
Will we listen to a song
Kwang Soo requested?
Which song
would you like to listen to?
I was going to pick "Goodbye Now."
- Which song?
- I was going to pick "Goodbye Now."
- "Goodbye Now."
- Yes.
We listened to the song many times.
(The song Kwang Soo requested
will be played soon.)
It's played the most often.
The album that contains
the day with Kwang Soo is here.
- Did it arrive?
- Really?
- Already?
- Before I hand over the album,
I will announce a few results.
- That's right.
That's right.
Today, the seven members
except for Kwang Soo...
had the hidden mission
of getting photos taken with him.
(Get as many photos taken
with Kwang Soo as possible.)
The first place with the most number
of photos with Kwang Soo...
will acquire the same presents
as Kwang Soo.
The last place will receive
the penalty.
I don't think I am in last place.
- I will announce the results.
- Okay.
(They had a fierce competition
to stand next to Kwang Soo.)
(They made memories
as they got the photos taken.)
(Who will place 1st
and receive the present?)
Jae Suk,
27 photos.
27 photos?
Suk Jin,
27 photos.
What?
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk, 27 photos)
Jong Kook, 27 photos.
Haha, 27 photos.
Ji Hyo, 27 photos.
So Min, 27 photos.
- No way.
- Se Chan, 27 photos.
Everyone was
in the same number of photos.
- What?
- What is going on?
(The hidden mission
was competitive.)
(How did they get the same result?)
Since everyone won,
Kwang Soo succeeded
in his last hidden mission.
(Kwang Soo's last hidden mission
is a success.)
- Did you have a hidden mission?
- I see.
- Kwang Soo succeeded?
- Did you have a hidden mission?
(Did Kwang Soo have
a hidden mission?)
Kwang Soo had a hidden mission.
Today, Kwang Soo carried out...
a hidden mission
behind the members' backs.
What was it?
The seven presents that were shown,
a premium champagne,
a brand-name hoodie,
a decorative picture frame,
a sound bar,
a bedding set,
and the others are ready.
Last week and the week before that,
Kwang Soo actually bought these
for the members.
- What?
- Really?
(Kwang Soo bought the presents
over the past 2 weeks.)
Why did you buy such nice items?
I didn't know he would reveal it.
(They were his presents
for the members.)
Kwang Soo had to complete
his hidden mission...
to deliver the presents on the show.
(It's the last surprise
Kwang Soo prepared.)
Are they really for us?
In any case...
(10 days before the shoot)
I want to give presents
to the members.
I won't do that on the show, but...
Are you preparing presents?
I don't know
if I will be able to deliver them.
- They get a bit...
- They think it's cringe-worthy.
They don't even like receiving
birthday presents.
They get embarrassed.
The presents are for the members...
as well as myself.
- My heart will be lighter.
- If you give the presents?
That's right.
(For Kwang Soo,
who feels sorry to the members)
- You prepared presents.
- Yes.
We received the presents
from your manager.
We plan to use them
for the race today.
The members think
those presents are for you,
but it's actually your chance...
to deliver them to the members.
You must pick a boiled egg
to give each member a present.
(Kwang Soo picked the eggs carefully
for the members.)
It will be hard to pick a boiled egg
seven times in a row,
so you will have
a special hidden rule.
The members think
that the person who has...
the most number of photos
with you...
receives the same presents,
while the person in last place
gets a penalty.
If you help all of them
tie for first place,
they will receive the presents...
and be exempt from the penalty.
So they need to be
in the same number of photos.
That's right.
(Make sure everyone is
in the same number of photos.)
The real-time rankings
will be shown to you secretly...
through the dice
in front of the production crew.
It will be in the order of age
starting from the left.
Each die's number shows
the member's ranking.
The moment you enter
the last venue, the LP bar,
the hidden mission will end.
What?
(Thus started
Kwang Soo's game of wits.)
Let me see the rankings.
(He checked with the producer
from time to time.)
Is Se Chan in last place?
(Kwang Soo learned
that Se Chan is in last place...)
(and stayed close to Se Chan.)
(He followed Se Chan around.)
That's a lot.
(When he pulled Se Chan up
in the rankings,)
(he saw that Jae Suk was
in last place.)
Come on.
(Kwang Soo was busy all day long.)
The last place.
Ji Hyo is in last place.
(Then he targeted Se Chan,
Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.)
(While everyone looked
at the scenery,)
(Kwang Soo looked at the members.)
(Even the moments
that seemed like coincidence...)
(contained Kwang Soo's love.)
Hyung Gu, what are the rankings?
Really?
(Kwang Soo's busy day...)
(had a happy ending.)
He completed the mission.
That's how we got the same number.
Since all of you are first place,
you can take your present.
I can't believe
they are from Kwang Soo.
Why did you buy
such expensive presents?
Did you control the numbers?
(The last presents from Kwang Soo,)
You knew about it.
(the man who wanted to give,
not receive)
Thanks to Kwang Soo,
everyone is exempt from the penalty.
I will reveal the presents
Kwang Soo prepared.
- We didn't prepare any presents.
- I know.
We didn't prepare any presents.
What?
- What is that?
- It's a present.
- There is a present for everyone.
There are names.
Kwang Soo bought a present
that suits each member.
Really?
This is for Haha.
Suk Jin.
- What?
- It's yours.
Is that Suk Jin's?
- I didn't prepare anything.
- It's Suk Jin's.
What is this?
Why did you get
such an expensive present?
(Jae Suk often wears hoodies.)
Why is mine small?
You will like it.
What's So Min's present?
Oh, the champagne.
- I love it.
- Right. That's what she likes.
- Gosh, this is...
- What's this, So Min?
The bedding set is for Ji Hyo.
That's because she sleeps a lot.
What's for me?
Why does it always
have to be so big for me?
It's a sound bar.
- It's a sound bar.
- I don't even know what it is.
- It's like a TV speaker.
- Really?
- So you can watch Netflix.
- I've never had this before.
This is really nice.
Why are you giving this to me?
Se Chan, this is a picture frame.
Gosh, what do I do?
We once went to buy
a painting together.
- He didn't buy it that day.
- I can't believe this.
I guess Jong Kook will have to move.
- This is really nice.
- It's so good.
In the living room...
I felt a little shy
about giving this to you,
so I met Bo Pil
and talked about this.
Gosh, this is really...
- It's a commemorative plaque.
- It says Lee Kwang Soo.
- What's that?
- It's pure gold.
(It's a golden name tag,
the symbol of Running Man.)
It's a name tag.
I really want one.
"You can stop running and walk now."
"Our special brother, Lee Kwang Soo.
From the Running Man crew."
- That's really cool.
- It's gold.
- It's pure gold.
- Thank you.
- That's very rare.
- Sure.
And here's our second gift.
All the 112 crew members
wrote messages to him.
- Really?
- It's like a Rolling Paper.
- My gosh.
- This will make you cry.
(The 112 crew members
left him messages.)
There's one from Kang Chan Hee.
- Thank you.
- It looks very sincere.
- He wrote with his sincere heart.
- I can see that.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- There's even a drawing.
- This is a great gift.
- It's really nice.
- This is the best gift.
- Thank you so much.
There are so many things.
This is our third gift, a speaker.
(They got Kwang Soo a speaker
as he was thinking of getting one.)
- He loves music.
- Thank you.
- Is this product placement?
- I bet it is.
- He will use it every day.
- This is really...
- He'll use it with his girlfriend.
- Enjoy it with your girlfriend.
It's perfect for a date.
There's a photo album.
- The next gift is...
- There's a photo album.
It's amazing that
we got it done so soon.
These are the photos we took today.
- They are from today.
- This is really good.
Gosh, when did you take this photo?
- Did they take photos?
- When did you take this?
I saw him make a V with his fingers.
- Kwang Soo did?
- We did.
- What a great world.
- We get it right away.
- Can we get the files as well?
- I bet we can get the files.
- Yes. We will give you the files.
I want the files as well.
He always talks about coffee trucks,
so we got him a coupon.
- A free pass to Running Man?
- Good.
You can come anytime
without making a call.
- Thank you.
- All right.
This is really precious.
Lastly, tell us how you feel.
All right, Kwang Soo.
Say something to our viewers.
(Kwang Soo's last song request,
"Goodbye Now")
- Say goodbye.
- Okay.
All right.
Thank you...
for everything.
I was happy.
(Kwang Soo joined Running Man as
the youngest member 11 years ago.)
(He loved laughter
more than anyone.)
(He was more serious
about Running Man than anyone.)
- Film this.
- This isn't about me.
(Behind the glittering glamour
of Running Man...)
(he always shouted his head off
to cheer for his members...)
(and shared joy with them.)
(He was always
very considerate and thoughtful.)
(To some people, Kwang Soo
is their childhood memory...)
(and the pillar of hope
that got them through hard times.)
(Now he says goodbye to you.)
Thank you for everything. Thank you.
All right.
Well done, Kwang Soo.
- You've worked so hard, Kwang Soo.
- Good job.
You've done a great job
for 11 years.
We will see you again.
Like we said before,
this is...
our last episode with Kwang Soo.
I don't know
how to express our feelings.
I believe our viewers
would feel the same way.
But the thing is,
life doesn't always go
as we planned.
Even after Kwang Soo leaves,
like we said before,
- we will keep working hard...
- Sure. We'll try our best.
to make our viewers happy.
I'd like to thank Kwang Soo again...
for the time he's spent with us.
Thanks to him,
we were really merry and happy.
Kwang Soo won't be there,
but please keep watching our show.
I'll buy this there.
All right.
- Do you have the receipt for this?
- Yes.
- I want one.
- Can you give me one?
No?
1, 2, 3.
This is the last photo.
- Thank you.
Well done.
- Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- You punk.
Look at you.
- Kwang Soo.
- Thank you so much.
- Oh, gosh.
- Good work today.
Thank you.
You were very lucky
on your last day here.
It was amazing.
Kwang Soo, clap your hands once.
- Okay.
- It's the last time.
All right. That's your last slate
on Running Man.
- Stop saying that.
- Here I go.
- 1, 2...
- Are you coming back next week?
I hope so.
- He can do one more week.
- Like a prank.
1, 2, 3. Thank you.
- Thank you.
(Just like that, Kwang Soo
stops running after 3,991 days.)
- Thank you.
Our oldest member, Suk Jin.
Jae Suk, who helped me...
come this far.
My moral support, Jong Kook.
Haha, who is always like
my family and friend.
Ji Hyo who's like my real sister.
So Min and Se Chan...
who are like my sister and brother.
With my gratitude to all of them,
I'll try my best...
for the rest of my life.
I love you.
(Our special brother, Lee Kwang Soo,
thank you for the past 11 years.)
(The 1st get-together
of the Board Game Club)
- Let's meet in person.
- Who is Pink Princess?
They want to beat me.
(All the weird members
are getting together.)
Strong guys use nicknames like this.
(They try to look strong...)
(with their nicknames.)
(The 7 members
enjoy the get-together...)
(with every fiber of their bodies.)
(Then they find a box.)
Do we teleport by jumping?
(The members get into a board game.)
(I'm the protagonist of the game.)
(They ally with each other...)
(and betray each other to win.)
(Who will be the strongest player?)
(The 1st Game Lover Get-together)