(A brisk fall day
when the heat has subsided)
(Jae Suk is the first one
to show up at the studio.)
What's this?
Good morning.
(Good morning.)
It's been a while, right?
(So Min is back
after 5 days of self-quarantine.)
I'm back.
Hello.
Why did you tell me
to come to the underground parking?
When we film the opening
separately like this,
we always get to choose something
and betray each other.
- Hello.
- What are we doing?
Hello. What do we do today?
Director?
This is...
(At the moment...)
What's going on?
(What's going on?)
Gosh, I'm startled.
(A mysterious agent...)
(shows up suddenly.)
Gosh, he scared me.
My goodness.
What do we do?
(Agents in a familiar mask
are showing up.)
What are you doing? You startled me.
What's this? Is it "Squid Game"?
What's going on? This is terrifying.
This is...
Seriously?
Gosh, this is
what we're doing today.
Really? Are we really
playing "Squid Game"?
It's squid.
(It's squid.)
(She greets
the familiar agent politely.)
Hello.
Gosh, hang on.
(The agents from the screen
are standing in front of them.)
Is this...
"Squid Game"?
It's a square.
(They've suddenly
come into reality.)
A square means a high-ranking post.
(What is it they want?)
Isn't this "Squid Game"?
(He keeps a safe distance anyway.)
Who is that?
Is a squid in there?
Are you a squid?
(But the agents remain silent
about their identity.)
What's going on?
Sir, would you like
to play a game with me?
What?
What game?
I know what this is.
Am I going to die?
This is...
Let's do it. What game?
What game?
Sir, have you played
a game of slap-match before?
Actually, I'm good at it.
You'll play a game
of slap-match with me.
Every time you win,
you get my ttakji and ten dollars.
Your ttakji and ten dollars?
(They are offered ten dollars
for winning a game of slap-match.)
Gosh, this is fun.
And if I win,
I will take your ttakji.
Okay.
What? Seriously?
Once one of us runs out of ttakji,
the game is over.
When I watched the drama,
I thought...
I would...
win at least 1,000 dollars.
You don't want to mess
with the members of Running Man.
You can be the first to play.
Okay. I get two?
(Each member gets
two pieces of blue ttakji.)
Okay. Let me warm up first.
(The first player
warms up his shoulders.)
Do you want me to go first?
I excel at this.
What are you going to do?
I'm really good at this.
I was the king
of the game of slap-match.
I won't go easy on you.
Are you okay with that?
(The king fails to flip over
the agent's ttakji.)
You're bad at this.
(Fortunately,
he gets one more chance.)
Gosh, this is...
Do you know advantageous for me
when it's upside down?
Okay.
(Okay.)
(He flips over the agent's ttakji.)
- Okay.
- You flipped over my ttakji.
- Yes.
- You get ten dollars...
- and a piece of ttakji.
- All right.
My goodness.
This is the last one.
If I win again, the game is over.
I'm not like Lee Jung Jae.
I'm good at this.
I'm the king of this game.
Go easy on me, mister.
Mr. Squid.
I'll go first.
(Groaning)
(The agent flips over
Se Chan's ttakji right away.)
What? Why?
What?
(Thump)
(The agent suddenly hits Se Chan
on top of his head.)
What was that?
You didn't say you'd hit me.
Every time you lose your ttakji,
you'll get hit with a toy hammer.
Then I will take one of your ttakji.
Why did you not tell me that?
(They get ten dollars if they win,
and they get hit when they lose.)
I'm in trouble.
What if he flips it over?
(Thump)
(The player gets hit
on top of his head.)
You're wearing Crocs.
Okay. I get it.
This is what I'm good at.
(Jae Suk is playing
what he's good at.)
All right.
Gosh, I did it wrong.
It was a mistake.
(It didn't even touch the ttakji.)
I...
That's because it was so sudden.
Gosh, this is crazy.
(Jae Suk's blue ttakji
is flipped over right away.)
Every time you lose your ttakji,
you'll get hit with a toy hammer.
Place it again.
(Flattening)
Hey. Excuse me.
(The game of slap-match
is getting more serious.)
Gosh, I missed it again.
(Flattening)
(But Jae Suk's ttakji
gets flipped over again.)
(Squeaking)
(While Jae Suk gets hit...)
You're not good at this.
You're bad.
Why are you so bad
at the game of slap-match?
Hang on.
(The wiry player strikes
a strange pose.)
Yes! I get ten dollars.
(She flips it over.)
Mr. Squid isn't good at this game.
I mean...
(Flustered)
You're terrible at this.
Okay!
This is amazing.
I didn't know I was good at this.
(So Min wins 2 games in a row
and gets 20 dollars.)
All right. Thank you.
He's surprised that I'm good.
Actually, I'm not good at this.
(While So Min puts on air
after winning the game,)
(Ji Hyo is getting hit pretty hard.)
Let's play one more time.
Just one more round.
I wasn't warmed up enough.
(As the game continues,)
Hey.
(the self-proclaimed kings
start to mess things up.)
(The agents never go easy
on the members.)
That was really hard.
Go.
(They thought they'd be good at this
since they have some experience.)
That was offensive. Okay.
(Distracting)
(Except So Min,
all the members lost their ttakji.)
Let me play one more round.
Can you give me one more chance?
Let's play one more round.
I'll give you ten dollars.
Will you play one more time?
(The members forget about the pain
and ask for one more chance.)
Is it over?
I didn't get much money.
(They are disappointed
that they didn't make much money.)
Sir.
There's a place where you can
make easy money like this.
(The original soundtrack
of "Squid Game")
(They get a mysterious card
from the agents.)
"Will you join the game
with big prize money to change your life?"
Webfoot Octopus Game?
(Will you join the game
with big prize money to change your life?)
It's a webfoot octopus, not squid.
It's Webfoot Octopus Game.
Webfoot Octopus...
(The 7 members are
invited to the game.)
Webfoot Octopus Game?
"Will you join the game?"
What? Are you inviting me?
Hey, Squid.
Webfoot Octopus Game.
I'll join.
I'll join the game.
Webfoot Octopus Game?
(Webfoot Octopus Game)
(This is Webfoot Octopus Game
which is cheaper than squid.)
(Squid: 7.5 dollars,
Webfoot octopus: 3 dollars)
(This was filmed
with the consent of "Squid Game".)
(The sound of bed wheels sliding)
(The sound of number 2 snoring)
(The 7 members have decided to
take part in Webfoot Octopus Game.)
(Agent 1 stomping)
(The agents leave quickly
after bringing in the members.)
(Upbeat music plays.)
- Can I take off the sleep shade?
- What?
- What's all this?
- My gosh.
- Gosh.
- What is this?
What is this?
- This is...
- What is this?
This is huge.
What?
What's all this?
It's so intense.
Il Nam.
I'm not Il Nam.
I'm scared.
- I didn't know this was so huge.
- What is this?
- This is...
- It's a large scale.
- You're the representative squid.
- Gosh, this is huge.
They all are in pink.
They are pink men.
- Even the cameramen.
- What's going on?
What's all this?
What's going on?
- What's going on?
- Suk Jin.
This is like an indoor playground.
No. This is Webfoot Octopus Game.
- It's an indoor playground.
- This is Webfoot Octopus Game.
It's lovely.
It looks like a dog cafe.
We should take a lot of photos here.
I guess we will be stars.
- You look good here.
- What?
- Okay?
- What do you mean?
- You're perfect for "Squid Game".
- Why?
You're a squid.
Suk Jin.
You should be good today. Because...
this might go viral
around the world.
You should be...
Why is Suk Jin number two?
- It's not about age.
- He's Il Nam.
(Oh Il Nam)
You're Il Nam.
- You're Il Nam.
- No, I'm...
He's Il Nam.
You're Il Nam.
- You're Il Nam,
- No, I'm Jung Jae.
Il Nam and I Nam.
- Why are you Jung Jae?
- I'm Jung Jae.
Who else would be Jung Jae then?
You can't always be the protagonist.
- It's okay.
- It could be Se Chan.
- In this game...
- And he is Hae Soo.
This is Park Hae Soo.
Right.
- And she's Mi Nyeo.
- Mi Nyeo.
- Right.
- She's her.
Who's the captain here?
- She's good.
- She looks just like Mi Nyeo.
She's good at things like this.
And he's the guy from abroad.
- Am I the foreigner?
- Ali.
- It's Ali.
- You're Ali.
- He's Ali.
- You're Ali, okay?
- I'm Kang Sae Byeok.
- He's Ali.
- What did you say?
- I'm Kang Sae Byeok.
- No.
- Sae Byeok?
- You're the gangster.
- Heo Sung Tae?
- Heo Sung Tae.
Deok Su.
- Move over.
- Are you the captain here?
I'm the doctor.
Don't call me that.
- Ji Hyo watched it.
- What?
- I did.
- "Squid Game".
- Really?
- That's unbelievable.
Are you a subscriber?
Yes, I'm a subscriber.
- Don't you use one with knobs?
- She keeps up with trends.
- I watch YouTube videos now too.
- Really?
- Impressive.
- She's a trendy person now.
But Ji Hyo, why are you...
- trying to come out of your cave?
- Exactly. What's the reason?
Are you trying to change your image
or what?
Why did you come out of your cave?
Well, I thought it was about time.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo began looking into
what the world pays attention to.)
What's going on?
- Even the music is the same.
- They're playing the same music.
Wasn't this music played
in this scene?
People start to die
when this music is played.
- It means the game will begin.
- The game will begin now.
- Welcome...
- It's the same voice.
- to Webfoot Octopus Game.
- Oh, my.
- I think he's the same voice actor.
- Is he the same voice actor?
- Today, you will play the games...
- He sounds the same as the drama.
- that we prepared,
- Gosh, I'm scared.
trying to survive
until the last game ends.
(Try to survive
until the last game ends.)
The participant who survives
to the end...
will receive a big cash prize.
(The final survivor will receive
a big cash prize.)
Each participant...
- will be given five lives.
- Five lives?
And every time you lose one life,
one part of your body
will be severed.
- A body part?
- This is a brutal game.
- If you lose all five lives,
- You should've told us sooner...
- you won't be able to...
- join the game again.
- so I could call my mom.
- Are you serious?
- Hey.
- Our body parts will be cut off?
- This is ridiculous.
The cash you earned
through the game of slap-match...
can be used to purchase 5 marbles
for 10 dollars.
Oh, man. I only won ten dollars.
- Darn.
- Hey, hold on a second.
If you turn in ten marbles,
you can eliminate 1 life
of 1 person of your choice.
- Oh, we can eliminate a life?
- Someone else's life?
You will receive three extra marbles
once every hour.
You can also earn more marbles
at the betting room...
- any time you want.
- Got it.
I have no marbles.
But...
Now, we'll reveal
the amount of the cash prize.
- How much is it?
- Hey, guys.
- Look up there.
- It's coming out.
(At that moment...)
- Oh, my.
- They even made that too.
(Everyone is impressed.)
Did they make that too?
(A giant, glowing sphere
came down from the ceiling.)
- Oh, my. That's huge.
- What's that?
- They did a good job making this.
It looks just like the one
in the drama.
(It looks similar to the one
in "Squid Game".)
- They made the same one.
- What is it?
- They did a good job making it.
- I'm impressed.
(A golden light
brightens the inside of the sphere.)
Will cash fall into it?
(A golden light
brightens the inside of the sphere.)
Will cash fall into it?
- What's happening?
- Oh, I remember the scene.
(Cash bundles start falling
into the sphere.)
(Cheers and applause)
- That's a lot.
- How much is that? It's real money.
They prepared all those bills.
I see a bill with Jae Suk's photo
on it.
- It has my face on it.
- That's Jae Suk's face.
How much is that?
- That's Jae Suk.
- Why does it have my face on it?
(The bills are falling
and piling up in the sphere.)
- Oh, my.
- That's a lot.
(The bills are falling
and piling up in the sphere.)
- They keep coming.
- That's a lot.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
- How much is it?
The prize money that
the final survivor will receive...
is 3,000 dollars.
(Number of Players: 7,
Cash Prize: 3,000 dollars)
(The prize money is 3,000 dollars.)
- It says 3,000 dollars.
- We can win 3,000 dollars?
Three thousand dollars?
- Three thousand dollars?
- It's a big prize.
Then we will begin...
the first game shortly.
Oh, my. This is amazing.
Jong Kook, let's be kkanbu later.
I'd love that.
- Hey.
- Be kkanbu with me too.
- Make kkanbu with me too.
- Come on.
- Let's make kkanbu.
- You'll need that.
Then until the first game begins,
enjoy your free time.
(Betting Room)
(They can exchange the cash they won
for marbles at the betting room.)
(They can also
earn more marbles here.)
- any time you want.
- Hold on a second.
My stylist has the money I won.
I mean...
- I changed my clothes.
- Your stylist can't help you now.
- You don't have a chance.
- Il Nam.
- You're looking for your stylist?
- That's so funny.
- I mean...
- I can't believe him.
- My stylist...
- He doesn't understand the rules.
- I put it in my back pocket.
- Does he think this is a joke?
I earned 20 dollars.
We should exchange the money
for marbles now.
(So Min came to the betting room
to exchange her money for marbles.)
Shouldn't we exchange all our money
for marbles?
Should we?
- I spent all I had.
- How much did you have?
How much did you win?
- How many do we get for 10 dollars?
- You get 5 marbles.
- Okay.
- That's cool.
- What should I do without marbles?
- My gosh. These marbles...
I should earn some later.
- Fifteen marbles, right?
- "Would you like to..."
- "play a game with me?"
- Twenty dollars...
"Do you want to make kkanbu
with me?"
You see, to survive in this game,
- we need to eliminate the others.
- That's right.
We should eliminate the others.
- Exactly.
- If we pair up as kkanbu,
- we'll be invincible.
- At least we have five lives.
I have ten marbles.
Don't forget that.
- I have ten marbles too.
- Okay.
Well, I'm just going to
take a selfie.
(Posing behind him)
Hey, move aside.
They're being lovey-dovey again.
- They're taking a couple's selfie.
- That's just crazy.
- Gosh. Why are they doing it here?
- I'm taking selfies.
- You two are posing together.
- That's just crazy.
I didn't ask her to pose behind me.
Why are you taking
a couple's selfie here?
It wasn't like that.
I was taking selfies alone!
But she was in that photo too.
- She was just passing by.
- Jae Suk.
- They're a couple, you know.
- Right.
Gosh, seriously.
(After sending away
the disruptive people,)
(he takes a selfie
from a different angle.)
Stop it.
- I'm going to play a game.
- Me too.
Really?
(Haha and So Min came
to earn more marbles.)
- Do we play odd or even?
- Welcome to the betting room.
Please choose...
one of the three games
that we have prepared.
The first game is Odd or Even.
You have to guess...
whether I have an odd or even number
of marbles in my hand.
If you guess it right,
you win twice your bet.
The second game is Roulette.
There are four colors on the wheel
which are red, blue,
yellow, and green.
If the wheel stops
on the color you bet on,
you will receive four times
as many as the marbles you bet.
- Let's play Odd or Even. It's...
- Odd or Even?
- They played it in the drama.
- Okay.
- Odd or Even it is.
- It's the signature game.
- Should we bet separately or not?
- Let's bet on the same thing.
- That'd be cool.
- Of course.
- We are kkanbu.
- Okay. We're kkanbu.
Han Mi Nyeo and I are kkanbu.
(They formed kkanbu on the spot
to make themselves look cool.)
First,
decide on the number of marbles
you want to bet.
The number of marbles to bet?
(While the 2 of them
are thinking...)
We can play a game between us.
- Hey, play a game with me.
- Me?
If we play a game there,
we may lose some marbles.
But if we play here,
our marbles will move among us.
- By the way,
- But we need to earn more.
- violence is allowed here.
- Correct.
Gosh.
- Violence is allowed here.
- Hang on.
Can't we kill each other
when the lights are off?
- That's true.
- Let's count our marbles first.
Two, four, six, eight.
I haven't played this game
in such a long time.
(Oh Il Nam's Do-it-yourself version
of the odd or even game)
- Odd or even.
- Here.
- I've never played this game.
- I bet two on the odd number.
(- Here!
- I bet 2 on the odd number.)
- I bet two on the odd number.
- Wrong. Give them to me.
Give me those.
Okay.
- I'll give you one.
- Really?
- Yes. In return, help me out...
- I won't forget...
- Help me out once later.
- Of course, I'll do that.
- Okay. Make it count.
- Thank you.
(One marble feels very valuable
to Jong Kook who had none.)
- I gave you one. Don't forget.
- Yes, thanks.
But how should I earn more
with just one?
- Figure something out.
- It's always an odd number.
Right, Suk Jin?
- You should give me at least two.
- I won his marbles.
I bet four on "odd".
- Four on "odd"?
- Yes.
(I bet 4 on "odd".)
"Even". Those are mine.
- Wait.
- It's "even". Give me those now.
- Il Nam is so good at this game.
- Must I give him my marbles?
- Of course, you must.
- It's up to you.
- Oh, I don't have to?
- Then I won't give them to him.
- Jong Kook, take four from him,
- and I'll give you one.
- Ali, come back here.
- Give me those marbles.
- Ali, come here.
- Jong Kook, we're kkanbu.
- Hey, play fair.
- I'll give you two if you help me.
- How many will you give me?
- Two.
- Deal.
- Thanks.
- I'll give you three.
- Hey. Darn it.
- I kept my marbles.
(Number 3 and Number 7 made
an agreement at once.)
Good job.
Hey, I was just trying to...
(The weak players are trying to
make kkanbu with the strong ones.)
Okay.
Come on. I lost some marbles.
I can play the odd or even game now.
Gosh.
I won four marbles in the game,
but I only got 1 of them
whereas Jong Kook got 2.
That's so strange.
Why did you let that happen?
He wouldn't give me the marbles.
(Haha is playing the official game.)
- I only got one.
- I'll bet two.
- Will you bet all of them?
- Yes.
- I bet 8 marbles.
- You bet 8 marbles?
Guys, So Min just bet eight marbles.
(So Min bet 8 marbles.)
Really?
- It's a big game.
- I guess...
- What game is she playing?
- Odd or Even.
I don't know about this game.
How many did you bet?
Jong Kook,
I can't get myself to leave.
- It's addictive.
- Really?
- Even.
- I couldn't see it.
- It's "even". Trust me.
- How many?
- Isn't it "odd"?
- It's definitely "even".
(Haha is sure that it's "even".)
- Are you sure?
- Trust your game partner.
- Even.
- I'm sure of it.
- The correct answer is...
- "even".
- Yes!
See? I was right, wasn't I?
(The correct answer is "even".)
(So Min earned twice her bet.)
You should give me one marble.
Give me one marble.
- How many did you bet?
- I bet eight marbles.
- Give me just one. You know...
- Gosh.
- that I saved you. Okay.
- Okay. Here.
- Let me play a game.
- That was awesome.
(Big Nose quits the unofficial game
and joins the betting room.)
That was amazing.
(But then...)
- What's going on?
- I guess the break time is over.
(Player number 2 is surprised
and joins the others.)
- I guess the break time is over.
- Suk Jin just sat down.
I didn't even start the game.
- He didn't get to play a game.
- Han Mi Nyeo.
- Someone came in.
- What's going on?
(An agent suddenly approaches
the players.)
- Who is this?
- What is it?
What? He must've been eliminated.
- What are you doing?
- His body part will be cut off.
- Suk Jin, you've been eliminated.
(Number 2 Ji Suk Jin is out.)
- Someone must've eliminated you.
- Wait for now.
- Let go of me.
- Someone must've eliminated you.
- Wait for now.
- Did someone...
- What is going on?
- What is it?
His body part will be cut off.
- Someone must've eliminated you.
- Wait for now.
Why is this happening already?
(Suk Jin who lost 1 life
loses 1 body part.)
Who eliminated me?
- We don't know.
- Who did it?
- I was playing a game.
- Me too. It wasn't me.
(Earlier on)
- How many marbles do you have?
- I have five.
How about I give you 5
so we can eliminate 1 person?
- Let's eliminate one of Suk Jin's.
- How many?
- Shall we?
- Let's do that. We're kkanbu.
- What do you say? Here.
- "Even".
(Se Chan plotted with Jae Suk
after losing marbles to Suk Jin.)
Go ahead.
Put your marbles in here.
I want to eliminate Suk Jin.
I mean, Il Nam.
Player number two.
(He collected 10 marbles
and took 1 of Suk Jin's lives.)
You know that I don't have
enough marbles to do that.
- Who killed me?
- My gosh. Who did that?
But why would anyone want to
kill Il Nam already?
- Why me...
- "Who was it..."
- "Who was it that killed me?"
- "that killed me?"
You do look pitiful, Suk Jin.
- That's the worst.
- My gosh.
"Who was it..."
- It wasn't me. I don't have enough.
- What?
But...
- You need ten marbles to do that.
- That's true.
(Suk Jin has only 4 lives now.)
(An elegant song is played.)
This is the theme song
of "Janghak Quiz".
The first game will begin shortly.
- I'm getting a little nervous.
- Right.
Please gather around.
- Got it. We're all here.
- It's scary.
(What will be the 1st game
to decide the final survivor?)
Tell us about the first game.
(What will be the 1st game
to decide the final survivor?)
Isn't it scary? I'm scared.
I guess
we're going to eat dalgona too.
Right. We'll eat dalgona too.
- Will we play the dalgona game too?
- I think we will.
(What is the 1st game
that awaits the players?)
The music slowed down.
Welcome to the first game.
Thanks.
The first game is...
Losing Yootnori.
- What?
- We're going to play yutnori?
As the name of the game implies,
you lose your life if you complete
the race before the others do.
- Oh, so we need to lose.
- We should avoid winning.
- Each player has one piece.
- We should lose.
The 1st 3 players to complete
the race will lose a body part.
- My gosh.
- Oh, no.
(The 1st 3 players to complete
the race will lose their lives.)
- Three players?
- I'm worried.
We need to lose in this game.
- You know, I'm a little scared.
- Me too.
- Honestly, I...
- It feels so realistic.
I'm scared too.
I'm starting to get immersed in it.
- What if it's actually cut off?
- I hope I'll get lucky.
The basic rules are the same
as the regular game.
If you catch the player
ahead of you,
that player goes back
to the starting point.
The player who caught someone else
will be hit with a toy hammer...
and should roll the yut once again.
There is back gae
as well as back do.
- Back gae?
- If you roll back gae,
you can move your piece
two steps back.
It's a good thing, right?
But if you roll back gae
on the starting point...
When your piece lands on a fork,
you can choose the direction
to move your piece in.
And you're not out even when
the yut falls outside the lines.
- There's no rule of being out.
- I see.
- It causes fights in many cases.
- Indeed.
- Can I throw again if I catch one?
- Yes.
- Catching them is a bad thing.
- The first player has an advantage.
- The first player to start.
- Catching others isn't good.
That's right.
That increases your chance to win.
- If I get caught...
- You would keep moving forward.
- Oh, right. I understand.
- This won't be easy.
- It'll be difficult.
- It makes sense.
It's not easy to lose.
Being ranked in the middle
is the best.
The later you start, the better.
Losing Yootnori. My gosh.
Whether you go first or later.
Once you go in, you can't get out.
I will never die.
Let me be in first place
for a change.
Right, So Min.
I have a feeling that you'll win.
I'll win 3,000 dollars.
This is even crueler
than "Squid Game".
My goodness. I'm worried.
Now, Number Two,
the player with the least lives,
please decide the order
for throwing the yut sticks.
- All right.
- Gosh.
- I don't like this.
- You can finish up at once.
Those punks. Being the first to go
is a good thing, right?
- The last one... No. You're right.
- You know...
(Unhappy)
You go first,
and let me go after you.
- Kkanbu?
- Yes, we're kkanbu.
It's kkanbu, not kkanbo.
It's too soon to make kkanbu.
- All right.
- What?
- It's too soon?
- You should make kkanbu later.
It's too soon?
- It's a mere order of players.
- What?
- And he's acting like a king.
- Go ahead.
- Go ahead and pick me.
- That was rude.
- Pick me. I don't care.
- Hey.
- What did you say?
- What was your plan for me?
You go last.
Okay. I'll go last.
That's not a problem.
You'll likely lose...
Did you just laugh?
- Yes, I laughed.
- You go right before him.
(He gives the ones who annoyed him
bad positions.)
You're the sixth player to go.
- What position do you want?
- I want to be the second to go.
- Then I'll go first.
- Sure.
- I'll go first, then you go.
- Okay.
- If we could avoid...
- And then...
Hey, are you the toughest one here?
- No, he's the weakest.
- If you give me one marble...
- She's Jeon Mi Nyeo.
- If you give me one marble,
- I'll put you...
- He'll go first anyway.
Give me one marble. Then I'll...
- No. That's okay.
- I'll put you...
- Really? That's annoying.
- Yes.
What? Why?
- This is not that important.
- You're the fifth one to go.
- Okay.
- The 5th, 6th, and 7th.
- Don't point your finger at me!
Are you two twins or something?
Don't do that.
- Hey, Mister.
- I meant no disrespect.
- Don't point your finger at me.
- I'm just deciding the order.
- Don't point your finger at us.
- How dare you?
You guys are the 5th, 6th, and 7th.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You're the 5th, 6th, and 7th.
- We're the 1st and 2nd.
- Right.
You two decide on your own.
- They're the 3rd and 4th.
- You decide on your own.
I'll let you two decide. My gosh.
- Gosh. He's acting so arrogant.
- Exactly.
Now, we're going to begin...
the first game, Losing Yootnori.
The fewer steps I get, the better.
(Suk Jin goes first
feeling at ease.)
I hope you roll a mo.
I hope it's a yut.
- It's back gae.
- Then what should I do?
- You can't start yet.
- I can't start yet?
- That's really great.
I wish his piece had been
on the board.
- I wish he'd won.
- Gosh.
If I get a do and then a back gae,
I complete the race.
Then it's over.
- That's the worst-case scenario.
- Gosh.
There are "X" marks
on two of the yut sticks.
- That's a back gae.
- One with those marks is a back do.
- It's geol.
- It's easy to get caught there.
Move forward.
- Do, gae, geol.
- I'll stay here and do it for you.
- Mi Nyeo, it's your turn.
- Ms. Jeon Mi Nyeo.
- I hope she gets a geol.
- What? It's mo.
- No, it's do.
- It's do.
If you roll a back gae next time,
it's over.
- Then you'll be the winner.
- That'd be nice.
- If you roll a back gae.
- Did you say it'd be nice?
If you roll a back gae,
you'll lose your life.
- That'd be the end.
- Oh, right.
Three of us will be eliminated.
You'll be eliminated, ma'am.
- I hope you get a gae.
- Sir, here we go.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Yes. Go ahead. Of course.
- You're sure about this, right?
(Ali Se Chan)
- It's gae.
- Yes, it's gae.
- We're in the 1st 3 places.
- That's dangerous.
- It's like a minefield.
- Do, gae, geol.
- They'll likely get caught.
- Getting caught is a good thing.
- I'll give it a try.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn.
If she gets a mo,
she'll be finished.
- It's yut.
- What?
- You should throw them again.
(As expected of the lucky one,
she rolls a yut from the start.)
- It's yut.
- This is exciting.
- Being lucky is not an advantage.
- One more time.
- She's so lucky.
- It's funny.
- Should she throw them again?
- It doesn't help in this game.
- One more time.
- Keep moving forward.
To avoid catching them... Oh, gosh.
- She got another yut... Oh, no.
- It's geol. Catch that one.
- It's geol.
- She can catch that one.
I need to roll a yut.
All right. Not moving at all is
the best-case scenario.
Please roll a gae.
- Gae?
- You'll most likely catch one.
- Roll do, gae, or geol.
- I don't want to catch any of them.
- It's your turn. Come and sit here.
- I shouldn't catch any of them.
I'm sure you'll catch one of them.
- I have to avoid catching them.
- I hope you catch one.
- All right.
- Catch 1 of them.
- You'll definitely catch 1 of them.
- Okay.
- It's geol.
- It's geol. He caught me.
(He caught Haha.)
- That was great.
- I can hit him, right?
- Oh, my. That was great.
- Gosh, seriously.
Hit him as hard as you can.
- Oh, boy.
- Good job.
Catch one more!
(He should throw them again
since he caught someone.)
- This is driving me nuts.
- Roll a back gae this time.
- Back gae.
- A back gae will be better.
- Or back do. He'll catch one more.
- Back do.
That'd be better
since I can move back.
I can get another back do
after catching someone.
Just go for it. That's life.
- It's do.
- It's do. Catch him.
- Okay. That's good. Nice.
- Oh, right.
That's nice.
You shouldn't try to calculate
the odds when you play this game.
- Just go for it.
- All right.
- If you are to die, you die.
- We heard you.
- I mean, we have five lives.
- Where is your piece?
- Okay.
- Sir.
- I wonder what he'll get?
- Here.
- It's back do. My gosh.
- It's back do.
- See? You must clear your mind.
- It's rare to get a back do.
Okay. I'll clear my mind too.
I hope you roll a yut and catch me.
- It's not easy to roll a yut.
- I want him to get a yut.
That won't happen.
It's yut.
- It's gae.
- Oh, it's gae.
- He caught one piece with a gae.
- He caught me.
(Suk Jin caught Se Chan's piece.)
- Darn it.
- He didn't realize it.
- One more time.
- Shouldn't he get hit?
- Okay.
- What? Why did he hit me?
- Did he punch him with a fist?
- You caught him.
- Oh, right. I did the same.
You'll get another gae.
(If he rolls another gae,
he'll catch Jae Suk's piece.)
- Another gae.
- That won't happen.
- You'll roll another gae
- Gae
- It's gae!
- It's gae.
- You'll roll another gae
- It's gae!
(He caught my piece too!)
You'll roll another gae
(Seok Sam keeps moving forward.)
- My gosh.
- Another gae
- Get a gae again.
Avoid getting a geol.
Here we go. I'm so happy
- Swing it like a golf club, sir.
- Sir.
- Nice shot!
- Nice shot, sir.
(Grumbling)
(Jae Suk hit him in the head
as if it was a golf ball.)
- You little...
- Why?
- Why did you hit me like that?
- There's no rule about that.
- Fine. Wait until you catch me.
- He's right.
- That's not against the rules.
- It'd be funny if he gets a geol.
- That'd be hilarious.
- You'll roll a geol.
Geol.
- Geol.
- You will roll a geol
- I hope he rolls a geol.
- Back gae or back do, please.
- You will roll a geol
- I won't roll a geol.
- Geol.
(Will he be able to finish his turn
this time?)
- It's geol.
(He caught another piece!)
(Seok Sam caught 3 pieces in a row
in only 1 turn.)
- He caught three pieces.
- He was acting so arrogant
- And he caught another piece
- He won't stop moving
- It's still his turn.
One more time.
- My goodness.
- One more time.
I hope he gets a yut this time.
- I'm dumbfounded.
- It'll be yut this time.
- I hope he gets a mo
- He's unlucky today
- What are the odds?
- I mean...
- Yootnori Master
(He beat the odds.)
- Yes!
- He's the Yootnori Master
- I mean how could this happen?
What are the chances...
- Yootnori Master!
- I threw them three times.
- He caught three pieces.
- He's Yootnori Master
- My gosh.
- You're unnecessarily lucky.
What's important is that the one
behind you can't catch you
He's gone too far
- He's gone too far
- You can get a back do.
But I can get a back do
- A hundred times
- No, you can't
- It's mo.
- Back do.
- It's gae.
- It's gae. My gosh.
- He rolled gae.
One, two, he rolled gae
- He rolled gae
- I caught three pieces.
- You're so good at yutnori.
- I caught them with gae and geol.
- He's so good at yutnori.
- If this were a regular game,
- I can't believe this.
- he would never have done so well.
- It would never have happened.
- Exactly.
He's the Yoot King.
- Gosh. Darn it. Catch me, please.
- Suk Jin is so funny.
I hope she gets a mo.
(After a few rounds,
it's Ji Hyo's turn now.)
- It's geol.
- Catch up with me.
- It'd be funny if he gets caught.
- That'd be great.
- Nice. There's no piece...
- on the 1st five steps.
- It's empty.
- It's empty now.
- Nice.
- It's empty
- How exciting
Now, here we go
- I hope he gets a yut.
- Two yuts.
- Yoot.
- Two yuts. If you roll a yut now...
- Two yuts?
That would make you a genius
- Let it be yut!
- A genius rolling yut.
- It's geol.
- It was almost yut.
- That's too bad.
- It's geol.
- Go, Gym Jong Kook
- Geol or yut.
- Gym Jong Kook, here I go
- How about geol?
- Geol or...
- It has to be geol.
It's geol, what a day
What a day
Eat your way along the board
It's geol
You'll be hit with the hammer
A single hit with the hammer
- How refreshing
- There you go
- Just a second
- How refreshing
Talk about discrimination
You whipped Suk Jin's head
But tapped Jong Kook's
(A full swing)
(A gentle tap)
- I...
- Are you scared of him?
- He's not stupid.
- No, hear me out.
I could take a swing at Suk Jin
because I'm right-handed.
I can't do it from this side.
- You can stand on the other side
- Why not stand on the other side?
- Then the camera
- I'll be blocking the camera
- Don't you agree?
- We have this camera up here
I wouldn't be that stupid
You could take a swing from here
- And still be on "camara"
- Did he say "camara"?
(Being on camera alone
put Seok Sam's tongue in a knot.)
- Right here.
- Where would I...
Then you could take a swing like so
It's doable
I could accidentally
hit his ear though
My ear is what you struck earlier
(He finally tells Jae Suk
that he was hit in the ear.)
- In the ear?
- Sorry about that
I'll keep that in mind
- Please be careful in the future
- I won't do that again
- I bet it's yut.
- It'll be nothing
- It's gae.
- Gae is what I rolled
- He has to take the shortcut.
- No, I don't.
- He can go the other way.
- I get to choose
If he goes this way,
he might catch the others.
But this way
shortens the overall journey.
I bet Suk Jin will roll a big one.
Seok Sam, roll mo for us
- Mo is something I never roll.
- Mo!
Mo!
- It's mo
- Mo!
- He rolled mo
- Seriously?
(He rolled a mo!)
He rolled a mo
- He rolled mo
- A mo
- Mo!
- He rolled a mo.
- Are you kidding me?
- A mo.
It's a mo!
He rolled a mo
- It's a mo
- How is this possible?
- A mo.
- As always
Suk Jin will be the first to die
This time around
A yut is what you'll roll
- A yut...
- You.
Shut it, will you?
I keep rolling what you want.
Back gae!
- A yut!
- A yut.
Back do.
(After rounds
of catching each other,)
(Se Chan takes the lead.)
- It's a yut.
- A yut.
It's a yut
Back gae is what he rolled
- A back gae
- It was a back gae
- Even do would be nice
- Back gae
- Do would be nice
- No, end it with back gae.
- Back do
- No, back gae.
- It'll be gae.
- Back gae.
- Not back gae, but gae.
- Give me a gae!
- No, a back gae.
- Back gae.
- That would be hilarious.
- It's a yut.
- A yut!
- A yut.
- You've caught one.
- No, I haven't.
- It was a yut.
- You roll again.
- Gae!
- Roll again.
- Please roll a gae.
- I'm seeing hope again.
- Please give me a back do.
- He's giving me hope.
- I need a back do.
- A back do.
- Let it be gae!
- It's a mo.
- Give me a back do!
- Do!
- He caught someone.
(He rolls a do
and catches Jong Kook.)
A do.
I can't believe he rolled a do.
No way!
He rolled a do.
(Jong Kook expressed his joy
by running.)
Gosh, he's fast.
Look at him run.
He rolled a do.
(If he rolls a yut,
he'll catch Suk Jin.)
- Roll a yut.
- Let's see.
- Nice.
- A yut!
- It's a geol.
- He's at my tail.
- Nice.
- Do, gae, geol.
You know, Suk Jin...
- might roll a back do.
- I'm in a dangerous position.
It's me again.
I have to start from
the beginning again.
- Haha could catch me.
- Please roll a do.
It'll be a back do or back gae.
- Back do or back gae.
- Let it be a do.
- A yut.
- It's a yut.
- Is it yut?
- Yes, a yut.
- Nice!
- A yut.
Roll again.
- Roll again.
- Roll again!
It'll be a back do or back gae.
- Please let it be either.
- Another yut would be nice.
- Another yut.
- A second yut.
- A back do or back gae.
- Let it be a yut.
- It's a geol.
- I thought I'd get lucky.
Do, gae, geol.
- You're back where you were.
- Darn it!
That's where you were earlier.
- That's actually impressive.
- Why did I even bother?
Why did I bother throwing the yut?
- He's good at this.
- You make a fast recovery.
- Mr. Gae.
- Back do!
- Back gae.
- No, back do.
- Back do.
- Give me a back gae!
(He'll catch Se Chan
if he rolls a gae.)
Gae!
(He catches Se Chan
who was in front of him.)
He caught me.
- No way.
- Gosh.
- Why am I so good at this?
- Thank you so much.
- I'm always terrible at games.
- Please have a seat
Please have a seat
Let him take a swing at your head
Thank you so much
Who knew Suk Jin
was this good at yutnori?
He's like the Yootnori Master.
- Unbelievable.
- The Yootnori Master.
- How about a mo?
- A mo.
- It'll be a mo.
- A yut.
- Yes, it's a yut!
- Rejoice!
- It's a yut.
- A yut.
Let's rejoice!
He rolled a yut.
(Suk Jin brings joy to everyone
by dominating the game.)
- Suk Jin...
- Unbelievable.
All you need is a geol.
If he rolls a geol, it'll be over.
- A geol and it's over.
- How is this possible?
If he rolls a geol, it'll be over.
How is this possible?
It's still warm,
so cut another sleeve off.
Roll a geol or a yut.
- Please give me a back gae.
- Just roll a yut.
- Back gae.
- No, a yut.
- Yoot.
- It's a geol.
(He manages to stop
at the edge of the cliff.)
- So Min...
- Get him with a back do.
You'll be shattered
if you catch him with a back do.
That'll be hilarious.
- That's my only hope.
- If you roll a back do...
- No way.
- But what if...
- Haha.
- Oh, it's my turn.
- Haha, roll a back do.
- Haha.
- Come on.
- Roll a gae.
- It'll be a gae.
- Do or gae.
- Unbelievable.
- Roll a gae.
- Why am I good at this game?
- No, roll a back do.
A gae!
It's me who he caught
- He caught you
- Why wasn't it a back do?
I'm glad to have
a distance between us.
- Right?
- Okay.
Haha, channel the Yootnori Master
and roll a yut or a mo
- At least a geol
- How about a mo?
- A yut!
- He rolled a yut
- Gosh.
- It's a yut
- Seriously?
- He rolled a yut
(Haha's road to death
is just getting started.)
- It's a yut
- Let's see for now.
(Suk Jin and Haha's gameplay has
the Grand Award buddies dancing.)
What a joy this is.
I couldn't be happier.
Kkanbu.
I can't believe
you're in the mud too.
This is hilarious.
Count me out.
(Haha follows Suk Jin
who's in the lead.)
- Roll a mo.
- There's no point in trying hard.
- Let it be a mo.
- It's a gae.
- He rolled a gae.
Good. That's a relief.
Things are looking great.
Hold on a second.
Will three lose a life in this game?
- Will we lose a life?
- Unbelievable.
- But...
- Seriously?
Why am I so good at this?
- I shouldn't be this good.
- Here.
- Right. Here comes the fun part.
- Good.
He's close to dying.
He's in the best position.
- He's headed to death.
- Get going already.
- Goodbye, Suk Jin.
- Will he live to see another day?
A back do or a back gae.
Suk Jin, that's disgusting.
How is it disgusting?
I should be the one
grossed out instead.
Did you hear his tone just now?
- "How is it disgusting?"
- Right.
- Give me some space.
- "How is it disgusting?"
Give me some space
since this is an important moment.
- Bye!
- Bye, Suk Jin.
- Goodbye.
- So long.
Suk Jin, throw them up high.
- Bye.
- You did well today.
(Will he miraculously roll
a back do or back gae?)
- Goodbye.
- Hey!
(Jae Suk touched one of the yuts.)
Back do!
Is it a back do?
What's the last one?
- Back do!
- Hold on a second.
- A second ago...
- I touched one of them.
- Back do!
- Hold on a second.
I touched one of them.
Jae Suk grabbed it,
so you must roll again.
- Right.
- No way.
- It's true.
- No, it's as is.
- But Jae Suk grabbed one.
- Here we go.
- We're sorry.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
He'll roll that one again.
- Why?
- You'll roll this one again.
- Of course.
- Why should I?
- You said there were no outs.
- Suk Jin.
- I'm really sorry.
- Why must I roll it again?
Even if it rolled that way,
it still counts.
He said he's sorry,
and this is supposed to be fun.
- You should accept it.
- He bowed down to you.
Suk Jin, that's enough.
(He agrees to roll just one again.)
- All right.
- This will be it.
- You can get the back do.
Please let it be on its back.
If he rolls a back do...
(He fails to roll a back do!)
Bye, Suk Jin.
(He arrives in the afterlife.)
- Bye!
- You're out.
Goodbye.
(In the end,
Il Nam managed to win the race.)
- Oh, no.
- Bye.
I'm sorry.
- Use scissors.
- Cut it out here...
so that it's enjoyable.
- Darn.
- There you go.
They completely got rid of
his left side.
- This is annoying, you know.
- You have five lives.
I like how you look wilder.
- Suk Jin, you seem stronger.
- You look different.
You're like Bruce Banner
before he transforms into Hulk.
- Suk Jin.
- Check out his thin leg.
That's hilarious.
You're wearing a cute leg warmer.
It's a cute leg warmer.
- He looks so fragile.
- It's like a bird's leg.
But this...
- Bye.
- You did good, Haha.
(Haha follows Suk Jin
and goes to the land beyond.)
He loves doing that, doesn't he?
It's either Se Chan...
- No, it could be Jae Suk.
- Se Chan's closer.
Jae Suk and Ji Hyo...
- could roll a back do or back gae.
- That's right.
You never know.
- Se Chan.
- I'll roll a gae first.
- Just roll a mo.
- Roll mo and end the game.
- Yes, a mo.
- Let it be a back gae.
- Geol.
- It's a geol.
Okay, you rolled a geol.
You're right at the end.
I have Jae Suk
and Ji Hyo to lean on.
- Ji Hyo, you're up.
- If she rolls a back gae...
If she does,
she'll be right at the end.
Ji Hyo, roll a do.
(She's fine as long as
she doesn't roll a back do.)
- No way.
- It's a mo.
- She rolled a mo.
- That's out of the blue.
- But this...
- It's meaningless.
It'll be the worst
if I roll a back gae.
You never know what he'll roll.
- You never know.
- All right.
Please let it be a back gae.
- What if I roll a back gae?
- Jong Kook...
- could come and catch me.
- It'll be a jackpot for me.
I mean it. If I roll a back gae,
all cameras will be on me.
The Deity of Variety Shows!
What we want is a back gae.
Your rolling back gae
is something I want to see as well.
- Jae Suk...
- If I roll a back gae,
- Suk Jin will...
- Then you can roll a mo.
Yes, it'll be a blast.
- It'll give me huge joy.
- Exactly.
- I wonder how it'll feel.
- Roll a back gae.
- Please.
- Let it be a back gae.
- All right!
(Jae Suk is safe unless
he rolls a back do or gae.)
(Let it be a back gae.)
- All right!
- Let it be a back gae.
Let it be a back gae.
- Back do.
- It's a back do.
(A back do?)
- What on earth?
- A back do.
(A back do?)
- Wait.
- Then at this round...
- Back do...
- If we survive this round...
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk will be eliminated.
- A back do?
- Jae Suk will be eliminated next.
I can't believe he rolled a back do.
If he gets another one,
he'll end up losing.
(Jae Suk instantly became
the first one to be eliminated.)
- He got back do.
- I wish I could get that too.
You need to get back do.
- You must get back do.
- I must get back do?
- Yes, you must.
- Either back do or back gae?
- Yes, because...
- You have no hope otherwise.
Please.
Once Se Chan is done,
it'll be over, right?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
How did I get back do?
I need to get either back do
or back gae.
- Right. You need to get either one.
- Se Chan should be eliminated.
Otherwise, I'll be eliminated.
- Se Chan.
- Please.
- Please, Se Chan.
- Please end it here.
- No, don't go for that.
- Please.
- How did I get back do?
- Let's do this, Se Chan.
- Right?
- Go for it, Se Chan.
You should get their energy.
Take a lap.
Touch them with your nose.
Kwang Soo!
- No, you shouldn't ask Kwang Soo.
- Why not?
- I need his energy for this.
- Kwang Soo's energy is needed.
You should ask Yeon Koung.
- Yeong Koung?
- Please.
Please. Just catch me
and advance on.
(Will Se Chan get
the two Long Legs' unlucky energy?)
Please. Just catch me
and advance on.
(Who will be the last victim?)
(Yang, Yoo)
Please. Just catch me
and advance on.
- It's mo.
- It's mo?
- What was that?
(He's the last person
to be eliminated.)
- What was that?
- What...
- was that?
- What was that?
- That was very neat.
What was that?
(It wasn't even close.
He immediately got eliminated.)
You got more than enough.
- What was that?
- I'm so relieved.
You got more than enough.
Why did I get mo?
It's my first time surviving
in a game like this.
The four players who survived...
will be given three marbles each.
The winners get three marbles each?
(The 4 survivors will be given
3 marbles each.)
He worked so hard to survive,
but he got mo.
I'm going to kill you all.
- Go ahead.
- I'll kill you all.
- If you don't like them...
- Those who passed the first game,
- congratulations.
- Thank you!
I don't get why I died
in the first round.
Enjoy your free time...
until the next game.
- Thank you.
- Three for me, please.
- I'll do the betting.
- Thank you.
- You can go ahead.
- Let's do it.
You can play in groups of two.
- He said we could play together.
- Okay. Take a seat.
He said we could play together.
- Let's bet 3.
- I'm betting 3.
(He bets all the marbles
he just earned on Odd or Even.)
We, the Pouty Mouth duo,
will show you.
Let's do this.
You can just guess
based on the sound.
There are only so many
that he can grab.
Is the number of marbles I'm holding
odd or even?
- Let's go for even. Even.
- Even.
The answer is odd.
(The answer is odd.)
I knew it.
(He was on a high horse, but his
marbles disappeared in a second.)
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Jae Suk. Wait a second.
- Se Chan.
- I'm sorry.
Gosh, that was all for nothing.
Let's play Odd or Even.
- With you?
- Yes.
- Bring it on.
- In "Squid Game", they...
- Okay. Bring it on.
- All right. Let's play.
Let's play.
I used to play this a lot...
near an alley entrance.
You're betting only one, right?
(Right then, Jeon Mi Nyeo
provokes Suk Jin.)
All right. Are we playing now?
Odd. It's odd.
- You got it.
- Give them to me. Three marbles.
- All right.
- I lost.
(Big Nose won 3 marbles.)
So Min, did you lose?
(Jeon Mi Nyeo hopelessly
lost her marbles on a side game.)
You're totally caught up
in his game.
- You lost?
- Let me play with you.
Let me give it a try.
The old man...
- Sir, let me play with you.
- That was hilarious.
I should play the game.
I should play it now.
I should place a bet
to double the marbles I have.
(A siren goes off all of a sudden.)
Number two, Ji Suk Jin, out.
- How come?
- Why is he out?
- He lost...
He lost another life.
(Il Nam who only played Odd or Even
lost his life again?)
What did you say?
- Suk Jin.
- At least tell me the reason.
Maybe it's because you played
a game here.
- What did I do?
- You shouldn't act up.
I only played a game.
So Min, you're a kkanbu, right?
Who should I kill?
- I'll kill them for you.
- Okay.
Suk Jin.
How many lives does he have?
He lost his arm and leg.
Let's cut off his other arm.
This is for Suk Jin.
(Resenting Suk Jin for taking
her marbles,)
(So Min took away his life.)
What's the reason?
Why did they take my life?
- Because you kept playing...
- Why did you act up?
You kept playing a game
to win marbles.
It's because you acted up
and played a game to win marbles.
Hey, at least tell me the reason.
(The agent steps in.)
I get what you're trying to do,
but why did they take my life?
Who did this?
- Was it you, Jae Suk?
- I don't even have any marbles.
- Was it you, Jong Kook?
- I don't have marbles.
- I don't have any marbles.
- Was it you, Jeon Mi Nyeo?
- No, I have all of my marbles here.
- I don't have any marbles.
- Ji Hyo, was it...
- I don't have any.
Who did this to me?
I'm really curious, that's what.
Why are you so sloppy at this?
- Wait a minute.
- Why can't you cut it at once?
- Why would you snap at him?
- Why are you mad at him?
- Just deal with it at once.
- Why would you snap at him?
- It's painful.
- You are...
Just finish it at once.
- You have a nasty temper.
- If you're going to be like this,
- give out two marbles each.
- Why should I?
Otherwise, they'll collect
marbles again and attack you.
- That's right.
- You don't have that many...
So you collected the marbles.
- So give us two marbles each.
- Don't snap at people.
- I'd rather kill someone...
- Be nice, and...
than give out marbles.
This won't do.
Is that so?
I can't die alone.
And he's coming down.
(Il Nam's creative way
of using the stairs.)
Here's 7. You need 3 more, right?
Why did he...
Why did he go up only to come down?
Why did you go that way?
You should come back the same way.
- He didn't need to go up.
- Come back, Suk Jin.
Come back.
He's making full use
of the props on set.
He's so cool.
(After submitting 10 marbles...)
I'll eliminate Jae Suk.
- I'll eliminate Jae Suk.
- But it wasn't me.
He's coming back the same way.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
I can't die alone.
Get rid of Jae Suk's life.
- Get rid of his life.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Jae Suk lost his life
because of Suk Jin.)
He vented on an innocent person.
(A siren goes off.)
- This is infuriating.
- Number one.
- Yoo Jae Suk, out.
- But it wasn't me.
Why did you attack me?
Because it was so upsetting.
- All right.
- My gosh.
This won't do.
I'm going to kill them all.
Are you out too?
That's can't be
what I think it is, right?
My gosh.
(Right then, a familiar set enters.)
- Is it dalgona?
- Dalgona?
Gosh, this is...
- I want to choose the umbrella.
- Me too.
- I'll choose the circle.
- I'll choose the triangle.
Soon,
you'll have to select
1 of the 4 shapes in front of you.
- I shouldn't pick the umbrella.
- You shouldn't. It'll be over.
But I bet there's a twist.
All right. Mi Nyeo, go ahead.
Which one should I pick?
(What do these shapes stand for?)
I like stars.
I think it'll be the opposite
of "Squid Game".
I'll choose the circle.
The umbrella must have
a twist, don't you think?
But I can't help but feel anxious.
How come so many people chose
the triangle?
I think he'll go for the umbrella.
I'll choose the umbrella.
I like rain.
Please enter the room one by one.
- Is that so?
- We should enter in order?
- Should I just go in?
- We're going in one by one?
What's this?
(There's an actual dalgona case
in the room?)
It's the same as the one
from the drama.
Is this dalgona? For real?
What's this?
I think it's really dalgona.
This must be dalgona.
- No, you never know.
- I'm not very good at this.
Now, open the case
and check what's inside.
- What's this?
What's this?
"The lunch menu you earned
by choosing the circle..."
"is rice and fried egg."
- What did you get?
- It's our lunch.
- Right?
- What did you get?
I got udon
and bibimbap with wild vegetables.
- I got the product placement.
- You got udon and bibimbap?
It was to choose your lunch menu.
I got the product placement.
The player who chose the triangle...
will get a triangle gimbap.
I'm getting triangle gimbap.
The player who chose the circle...
- will get rice and fried egg.
- Oh, I'm getting rice too.
I had triangle gimbap for breakfast.
The player who chose the star...
will get the product placement
that only stars get to eat,
and you'll get braised chicken.
- You're getting braised chicken.
- That makes sense.
The player who chose the umbrella...
will get udon and bibimbap
with wild vegetables...
whose initials start with
"U" and "B".
- Everyone, I hope...
- What did you get?
- you'll have a nice lunch.
- Suk Jin's is the best one.
I know. I was the last to pick.
- There was a twist.
- It was for our lunch.
Darn it.
It's braised chicken.
- You got product placement, So Min.
- But I'm not good at it.
Suk Jin got the best one.
Gosh, this looks good.
Udon and bibimbap.
- That's the best menu.
- Mine is the worst.
- But it's tuna flavored.
- There's only egg and rice.
This looks delicious.
I wanted to pick the umbrella
for some reason.
- You should've picked it.
- Right?
They gave me
plenty of braised chicken,
so anyone who pays up three marbles
can join me.
- You can put it on credit too.
- Okay, So Min.
I'm in.
You're in? You're putting them
on credit. Eat with me.
- You can't put them on credit.
- Of course, I can.
It's because...
we have a special connection.
- What?
- What is she talking about?
We have a special connection.
- What?
- What is she talking about?
When she said that,
I almost threw up.
- She was so immersed in it.
- I almost got choked.
I almost threw up.
- I'm supposed to be Ali.
- She came over, and...
- I almost threw up.
- I was really surprised.
Gosh, what's wrong with her?
I'm supposed to be Ali.
(The only star,
Jeon Mi Nyeo's lunch is here.)
It looks so good.
Gosh, look at that.
Goodness, it smells so nice.
(Spicy braised chicken
and creamy braised chicken)
I can smell truffle oil.
- This has truffle oil.
- Gosh, this is...
Goodness.
- What's this?
- Let's go look at it.
This is the best menu so far.
(The hungry webfoot octopuses
gather around So Min.)
Goodness, it smells so nice.
(Se Chan promises to pay 3 marbles
and joins So Min.)
Mi Nyeo, can I have this?
- You need to pay three marbles.
- Sorry?
- If we pay three marbles,
- Okay.
can we join you?
Of course.
You need to pay me
three marbles later.
There's too much
for her to eat on her own.
(Ali's eyes go wide.)
I can still smell the truffle oil.
I can smell the truffle oil
for real.
- The truffle oil smells so good.
- This is delicious.
It's good.
Players, please gather.
We must be playing that.
(After filling their stomachs,
they play the second game.)
What's that?
The second mission...
is a game where your decision
determines your fate.
It's called War of Kkanbu.
- We need to become kkanbu.
- War of Kkanbu...
consists of four games.
You get to pick new teammates...
in each game.
The games won't be revealed.
Without knowing the type of game,
you'll choose
either square or triangle.
The players who choose
the same shape will become a team.
In each game,
the members of the winning team
will earn a point.
After playing all the games,
the players with the lowest scores
will lose their lives.
My gosh.
It's a majority versus minority.
But being a part of a majority
must be better most of the time.
Before the first game starts,
I'll give you a minute
for you to look for your teammate.
You'll gather after a minute.
- After a minute?
- Yes.
Then I should drop by
the betting room.
- Me too.
- Hold on. I'll go to...
- the betting room.
- Wait. Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- Try the Roulette.
- Come here.
- Okay.
The Roulette has higher chances.
- Let me play a round too.
- No, we won't be playing that.
You had the braised chicken earlier.
- We're playing together.
- Let me have it a go.
We need to play it.
- No.
- I'll play the Roulette this time.
You should play the Roulette.
That way you can earn more marbles.
Why don't you bet four each?
- Bet on the red one.
- Now,
- bet on the color of your choice.
- The Roulette has higher chances.
Are you betting everything you have?
I should.
I'll bet everything on red.
- On red?
- No one's gotten red so far though.
Should I go for red too?
- Go for it.
- Just go for red.
- Let's do this, Se Chan.
- Now,
I'll spin the Roulette.
- Go for red.
- I think they'll get yellow.
- Red.
- I don't think you'll get it.
Red.
Please.
(What's the fate
of the pushover brothers?)
Red.
It's red.
It's red!
(They finally hit the jackpot!)
Did you win?
(The pushover brothers
finally hit the jackpot.)
They hit the jackpot.
- They got 16 in total.
- We'll get 4 each.
I'll give you the marbles.
- I can't believe this happened!
- Yes!
I've been betting on red too.
- We're getting 16.
- What's this?
- The lights are off.
- We're getting 16.
(A sudden blackout)
- What's going on?
- Darn it.
What's happening?
(Player number 3 waited
for the blackout more than anyone.)
(The lights went off
just as he wished.)
What's going on?
(A surprise attack)
- Hey!
- Hey, are you serious?
- Let go of me!
- Let go!
- Hey! Song Ji Hyo, that punk.
- Hey!
This isn't right!
(Laughing)
Wait, Jong Kook!
(A nightmare where everything
is allowed in the darkness)
He took everything.
Jong Kook! You can't take them all!
No! You can't take them all!
- Jong Kook.
- Come here.
(The lights are back on.)
Come here.
(Il Nam was being bullied
in the corner.)
- Why are you so...
- You can't take everything.
- Jong Kook.
- Come here.
- You can't take everything.
- Okay. Come here.
- Why did you turn off the lights?
- Gosh.
- My gosh.
- Wait a minute.
- Now...
- He took everything.
This isn't right.
The marbles in the betting room
are gone too.
My gosh. Song Ji Hyo, you little...
- Did she steal yours?
- She put her hand...
You didn't get stolen, did you?
I didn't have many, that's why.
Everyone became savage
when the lights went off.
Just give me enough to make a bet.
The marbles in the betting room
are gone too.
Haha, he took everything I had.
- I can't get back on my feet.
- Hold on.
- He took everything.
- You...
He threatened to punch me
and took away everything.
(Right then, Haha and So Min
gather marbles and submit them.)
What are they doing?
What are they up to?
(Feigning innocence)
- Did they pay five each?
- Who are you trying to kill?
I don't think that's how it works.
I don't think they went that far.
(Wailing)
- Gosh, that scared me.
- That startled me.
(With the siren,
the agent appeared.)
- Who is out this time?
- Who is it?
- No way.
- It's Jae Suk.
- Number one, Yoo Jae Suk, out.
- Gosh. Sir.
(Number 1, Yoo Jae Suk, out)
- Hey.
- It wasn't me.
A while ago, So Min and Haha...
Gosh, these punks.
That scared me.
(A cold-blooded world of
Webfoot Octopus Game)
- That scared me.
- Let's go for it again now.
Come with me.
But I don't have any.
- How many do you have?
- I don't have that many.
- I don't have any.
- Give me five marbles.
- You should give him some.
Give me five marbles.
- Give me five marbles.
- So Min and Haha...
- I only need five.
- When I saw the light...
- in the darkness, I was so scared.
- Who do you want to kill?
Should I give you one?
- Go ahead.
- I'll give you one.
Make it balanced.
You mean So Min, right?
She hasn't been killed, right?
It wasn't me.
You're going to kill me?
I'll give you one too.
I gave you a lot.
- How many do you have?
- Wait. You'll have extra.
It's not that.
I'm the one who's paying the most.
Are you sure? I paid the most.
- I gave you five marbles.
- I lost a life already.
(Whom will Haha kill?)
You lost just one life, right?
(Wailing)
I'm eliminating Jae Suk.
Jae Suk has many lives.
- Haha.
- Number three.
- Kim Jong Kook, out.
- Darn it.
- Did you eliminate me?
- No, it was her.
(Jong Kook is eliminated
all of a sudden?)
(Did you eliminate me?)
Wait. He's a complete lunatic.
Hold on.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Haha got the marbles from Jong Kook,
but he eliminated him.
That jerk!
He took five marbles from me.
That's crazy.
No, I eliminated Jae Suk.
- It was Jae Suk.
- You...
You'd better watch out
when the lights go off next time.
(You'd better watch out
when the lights go off next time.)
I'll eliminate Haha.
(In the meantime,
Jae Suk retaliates immediately.)
- You know me, right?
- Of course.
You know me, right?
- Is it me again?
- It's Jae Suk.
- It's Haha.
- It's me?
Number four, Haha, out.
Give me three marbles.
Haha has only one life left.
- Just three marbles.
- Why?
- Hurry. I can eliminate one.
- Who are you trying to eliminate?
- Hurry! I just need 3 more.
- He's holding 7 marbles.
- All players, please gather.
- Gosh, I was about to give you.
No. I have only two lives now.
- Now, you will select your team...
- I'm going to destroy Haha.
for the first game.
- All right. Let's do this.
- Choose either square...
- or triangle.
- In one,
- two, three.
- Two, three.
All right! This is great.
- This is great. It's not bad.
- Four people on Team Square...
- Come here.
- and three on Team Triangle.
- I told you to choose square.
- What?
I told So Min to choose square.
The first game...
is a tug of war,
which requires a lot of strength.
(It's a tug of war.)
- We have four people.
- We can beat them.
No. This is...
- They have more people.
- We're in trouble.
Jong Kook, it's okay.
I'll pull it like crazy.
You know the rule, right? You need
to hold out for ten seconds first.
Shall we use the method
from "Squid Game"?
- Let's do it exactly the same.
- Let's use the same method.
- Let's try that.
- We'll hang on the rope first?
- Shall we try that?
- That's how it should be played.
- It was in "Squid Game".
- Don't pull. We should hold out.
We shouldn't pull but hold out.
The ones that weigh more
should hold out.
- We should pull?
- You should pull.
We must win this
because our lives are at stake.
Our lives are at stake.
We must win this.
- All right.
- We must...
Put it under your armpit.
(The players on Team Triangle
are desperate as well.)
- I'm going to destroy them.
- Let it go.
- Let's do this!
- Can you pull it a little?
- I learned it from the drama.
- Ready.
- Wait.
- Get set.
- Lean backward.
(If you lose, you'll die.)
Lean backward.
(As soon as the game starts, both
teams put in their best efforts.)
(Although they have lesser people,)
(the two men
show superhuman strength.)
(However...)
(Jeon Mi Nyeo
gets dragged helplessly.)
(Team Square wins in the end.)
- Yes!
- It was impossible.
We won!
We have lesser people,
so it was impossible.
It was too slippery.
(Even the two strong men
couldn't save their team.)
- It was impossible.
- It went okay at the beginning.
We'll give the four of you
a point each.
- Yes!
You'll choose your team
for the next game after a minute.
- All right.
It's important
to be on the right team.
It's so nerve-racking.
Imagine if your life depended on it.
- That's what I was thinking too.
- It'd drive you crazy.
I have only two lives.
Don't you have any marbles?
- I have five.
- We pulled them instantly.
I have one.
I'll destroy Haha.
- How many do you need?
- Can you give me three marbles?
- What?
- Three marbles.
We need to take down Jong Kook.
Why don't we pitch in
one marble each?
- He gathered enough marbles.
- No.
He's going to eliminate Haha.
He's going to eliminate me?
- I have only 1 life.
- You have only 1.
- Is it two?
- Are you going to attack him?
- Here.
- Jae Suk, pitch in more.
- I don't have any!
- I saw you winning them earlier.
- I got them stolen.
- Who stole them?
Why you...
They're coming after you.
Is it me? It can't be.
Hurry up. Give me two more.
- You need 2?
- Number 4, Haha, out.
What's this? Two...
Hold on. Two, four...
(He collected enough marbles.)
Hold on. Why don't you
cut it off up there?
Now I have a reason...
(Now I have a reason
to collect marbles.)
to collect marbles.
I'll eliminate Jong Kook.
- I need to collect more.
- He's cutting it strangely.
Number three, Kim Jong Kook, out.
All right. Bring it on.
- They're on fire!
- All right.
- Give me one more.
- Things are heated.
- I have one.
- Give me just one marble.
I'll give you mine.
I don't need yours. Be quiet.
- Forget it.
- I'll give you one.
I'll be done
if you eliminate me again.
All right. I'll eliminate you
in the next round then.
Let's kill him.
- Jong Kook.
- Do your best to get screen time.
It's best to stay quiet.
It's best to stay in the back.
You are done for.
- He has one life left.
- Talk a lot this time.
(Haha has one life left.)
All right.
(The current survival status)
Let's begin
the second selection of teams.
I will choose randomly.
I will choose without looking.
Me too.
- I will flip it and catch it.
- One, two,
- three.
- This is my choice.
- All right.
- My goodness.
- It's Team Men versus Team Women.
- We are set.
- Okay.
- We will beat them.
- I can't believe it happened.
- My goodness.
- I apologize.
- How did this happen?
- Don't apologize.
- Do your best. You are done for.
- Let's do this.
- You are done for.
- Okay.
- I apologize.
- It's over.
In the second game,
(What will the second game be?)
- a big team has a disadvantage.
- They are so annoying.
Game of Wits. One.
- Two.
- Three.
- He said one.
- Four.
- Five.
- Six.
- Seven.
- Eight.
(He was in a daze.)
- Seven.
- Eight.
(He is out.)
We survived!
(Against all odds,
Team Women survived.)
- Hey.
- Did we lose?
You should have gone faster.
Why didn't you focus?
- Did we lose?
- You have no wits.
Did we lose?
- We lost.
- I mean...
They are so annoying.
For goodness' sake.
It would have been better
to overlap.
For goodness' sake.
- Okay.
- Had people overlapped...
(He sets off with "Okay"
right after the game.)
- I am sorry, Jong Kook.
- Don't be.
- Please don't eliminate me now.
- Forget it.
- Please let me play another game.
- You have played enough games.
Jong Kook,
let him play another game.
I will do my best.
Play another game then.
I see that he will be eliminated
if he loses another life.
- Make sure you enjoy it.
- I will give you ten marbles.
Forget it. Be quiet.
- No. I will take you out.
I wouldn't have minded
if he had simply eliminated my life.
But he eliminated my life
when I had given him five marbles.
I can't let that pass.
- I am sorry.
- Don't be.
- Please. I have three children.
- Forget it.
- Forget it. Be quiet.
- Jong Kook.
Where did you get so many marbles?
He took marbles from me.
He took 20 marbles from me.
He is Park Hae Soo.
- He is totally Park Hae Soo.
- Seriously.
- That's so funny.
- All right.
Let's begin
the third selection of teams.
(It's time
for the third selection of teams.)
Three.
I got square again.
The three of us are a team.
- I will work hard.
- It's okay. It doesn't matter.
- I will give you ten marbles.
- It doesn't matter.
(It could be Haha's last match.)
It's over.
Move out of the way.
How did we become a team?
How did this happen?
(Team Square has
the weakest members.)
- I don't know about this.
- Why are you smiling?
- We can do it. It's okay.
- I don't know about this.
- The third game...
- What is it?
requires a burst of strength
and accuracy.
- It's the Cap Flicking Game.
- Okay.
The team wins if it has the cap
that is closest to the finish line.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
Having four members gives us
an advantage.
- I like games like this one.
- It's unrelated to strength.
Imagine that your life is
on the line.
You would go insane.
- Jong Kook.
- No.
Do you have three marbles?
Give them to me.
- You are going to die anyway.
- Share them before you die.
You are going to die anyway,
so give them to me.
Give them to me.
Give me three marbles, okay?
I won't die just yet.
- I won't die just yet. I can do it.
- Haha.
You are done for.
Who will go first?
(The team wins if one of its caps is
closest to the finish line!)
We just need one winner.
- We just need 1 winner.
- I will go 1st.
- Okay.
- It's because...
Flick it hard.
(The first cap will block the path.)
(What will happen
to Jeon Mi Nyeo's cap?)
- Out.
(It goes out.)
Put your heart into the game!
- Suk Jin.
- Your life depends on it!
- Jeon Mi Nyeo!
- So Min, each failure...
will cost a life!
Why are you playing games
so half-heartedly?
- I did my best.
- I am scared.
- Go.
I did my best.
I did as I practiced earlier.
Why did it slip?
Had this been "Squid Game",
- you would have died.
- Seriously.
She would have died a while ago.
- It's past the line.
- Hey.
- Put it behind the line.
- Listen.
- Do something.
- If this were "Squid Game",
- Hurry up and do something,
you would die
halfway through the show.
Really?
- You are that kind of character.
- I would have died a while ago.
You would have died
when the light went out.
I got all of my marbles robbed
Why don't I flick it this hard?
- That looks bad.
- Good.
- Good. Zero your aimpoint.
- It will go out.
See? It isn't easy.
- Why did you do it half-heartedly?
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
- I will go next.
- Ali.
- Ji Hyo.
- I flicked it too hard.
- I think...
- Don't be too ambitious.
If you flick the bottom...
- Flick it.
- You know,
you need to flick it hard.
Flick it hard.
(Flicking)
- A meaningless shot.
- I am sorry.
(Laughing)
A meaningless shot.
Do it right!
We glared at you too much.
She deserves to be glared at.
- Our lives are on the line.
- Stop it.
Suk Jin, I might end up winning.
Just you wait.
- That won't happen.
- Here I go.
If everyone's cap goes out...
Nice.
(It doesn't go far.)
Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- Jong Kook, it's okay.
- Suk Jin.
- Be quiet.
- Suk Jin, you need to do this.
- You can do it. Relax your fingers.
(Will Il Nam be able
to seize this opportunity?)
- Suk Jin, you need to do this.
- Relax your fingers.
- Gosh.
- Why did you do it half-heartedly?
(After all that talk about lives,
he sent the cap flying.)
- Gosh.
- Our lives are on the line.
- Are you out of your mind?
- You should understand.
- Suk Jin.
- They don't have many lives left.
Only one person remains per team.
- I should have hit more gently.
- Aim for my cap.
Aim for my cap.
Then your cap will go that far.
You know what I mean, right?
Jae Suk, you are our only hope.
This is driving me crazy.
It will be interesting
if Haha hits one of the caps.
Hit my cap and send it forward.
- Practice.
- You can't practice.
- That flick would be too strong.
- Let's go.
Do it gently.
That flick would be too strong.
- All right.
- Do it gently.
- Aim for my cap.
- That flick would be too strong.
- Okay. You just need to go past it.
- Jae Suk.
(The cap didn't go far.)
- Okay. You just need to go past it.
- Jae Suk.
- You...
- What was that?
(Team Square received
a golden opportunity.)
- You will win if his cap goes out.
- Just get it this far.
- His cap will go out.
- It doesn't need to go far.
- Just get it this far.
- Jae Suk.
- You can do it.
- Our lives are on the line.
- Relax your fingers.
- Our lives are on the line, okay?
- Flick it gently.
- Hey.
It just needs to go past this cap.
If you fail, you won't be able...
to see Ji Ho and your daughter.
I am sorry. I forgot her name.
And your daughter.
(He forgot his daughter's name.)
- I am sorry.
- Na Eun.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Na Yeon?
- Who is Na Yeon?
- All right.
You won't be able
to see Ji Ho and Na Yeon.
- It's Na Eun.
- Na Eun.
I am sorry. I forgot for a second.
- It's a matter of life and death.
- I know your family members' names.
- How would you know that?
- Your father is Mr. Ji Chang Gyun.
You don't need to know that.
That's not what's important.
Just get it past this cap, okay?
- Think of Ji Ho and...
- Don't be nervous. Get it this far.
- Jae Suk will win.
- Get it this far.
- Your life is on the line.
- No.
- It's hard. It isn't easy.
(Everyone's life
depends on Jae Suk's shot!)
- Jae Suk will win.
- Your life is on the line.
No.
- Okay.
- Yes!
(He turned the tables.)
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, that was incredible.
We did it.
- We did it.
- There goes Jong Kook.
- He will take Haha out.
- Please let me play another game.
Please. I will be loyal.
- Jong Kook.
- Move out of the way.
- I will be loyal.
- Your moves are too erratic.
- Move out of the way.
- Please let me off this once.
- Please.
- Haha.
- Just one more game.
- No.
- Your moves are too erratic.
- Is Haha out?
- No.
- Is he out?
Your moves are too erratic.
(The siren blares.)
I can't believe Jong Kook.
- He took Haha out.
- Of course.
Of course.
Number four, Haha is out.
- Today,
- Haha.
- he really motivated me.
Which body part will be cut off now?
Oh, no.
(He runs away.)
They will show us.
Ouch! Gosh.
(The guard fires off
the webfoot octopus bullets.)
That hurts.
He shot at Haha since he ran away.
(A firm action is used
for those who try to run.)
That was cute.
He shot at Haha.
(Haha gets dragged away
with a gunshot wound on his arm.)
- What will happen to him?
- Bye.
The guard actually shot him.
Bye. We will take care
of your three siblings.
(Number of players: 6)
Let's now begin
the last selection of teams.
- Good.
- It will be six.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan versus
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, So Min)
Two.
- Come on.
- She is strong.
One.
- Three.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan win
a point each.)
- Thank goodness.
- Okay.
- All right.
- We needed a smaller number.
- Hold on.
Who is that man?
- What is going on?
- Triangle.
- He really is a squid.
He looks cute.
- A fresh squid.
- He came back as a squid.
Your final points will be revealed
in the sketchbook.
(Jong Kook, Se Chan, So Min,
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk)
(Se Chan is at the bottom.)
(The squid will get to work soon.)
- Haha.
- Squid.
- That was so funny.
- Seriously.
- I feel dizzy.
- He looks cut.
- Don't cut haphazardly.
Where are you trying to cut?
Don't cut my hair. It's here.
Cut the bottom.
(He unleashes his remaining anger.)
(He wordlessly fires off
the webfoot octopus bullets.)
He won't talk.
I guess he can't talk.
- Guards aren't supposed to talk.
- That's right.
- Are you making hot pants?
- Why are you making it so short?
Why are you making it so short?
It looks like
you are slicing a fruit.
I can't see the seamline.
- Hey.
- It's not an apple.
Stop it.
Hey.
Be careful.
Gosh, it keeps going up.
- Enjoy some free time...
- It looks nice.
before the next game begins.
It's free time.
This won't do.
- I am too nervous.
- Seriously.
All participants, gather around.
It's time for the third mission.
Many participants
could be eliminated...
as a result of this mission.
It's the Hide-and-Seek of Despair.
(Hide-and-Seek of Despair)
In a given time,
correctly guess the number
of the items in order to pass.
- What?
- Hide-and-Seek?
- What are the rules?
- Do we play in the open?
- But we will allow...
the error range that corresponds
with the number...
you get on the dice
before the game begins.
My goodness.
If your answer is wrong,
your body part
will be severed immediately.
- Gosh.
- Immediately.
Many people will get eliminated.
People will get weeded out.
What is that?
(A big object enters.)
As you heard, you will see things
that are hard to count.
- There will be three stages.
- Okay.
- Will the penalty come right away?
- Can three body parts be severed?
- No matter what...
- Gosh.
No matter what, I have to do well.
I have one life left.
This could take people out at once.
- Just...
- I don't know. Let's see.
Don't worry about winning.
Ji Hyo or So Min will win.
You will have 30 seconds
to count the 1st object.
One, two, three.
- What?
- My goodness.
- What are those?
- This is Webfoot Octopus Game.
(Count long-legged octopuses.)
(Count them in 30 seconds
to save your life.)
One, two, three.
- Do we count them?
- What?
- My goodness.
- What are those?
- This is Webfoot Octopus Game.
- Do we count them?
Now?
(They will lose a life
if they fail.)
- Do we count them now?
- How am I supposed to...
How am I supposed to count them?
- Gosh.
- One, two...
- Hold on.
- They are moving. What should I do?
How am I supposed to count them?
(They move and huddle close.)
(Long-legged octopuses
even have eight legs.)
Hold on. This one keeps moving.
Where does it end?
(They count long-legged octopuses
to save their lives.)
Hold on. This one keeps moving.
Where does it end?
Ten seconds remain.
Ten.
I have no idea.
How am I supposed to count them?
How many are there?
I will need to take a wild guess.
I can't count them.
Our lives are on the line.
They keep moving. One, two, three...
Cover the sink.
I don't know how many are inside.
How am I supposed to know?
You can set the error range.
- The error range.
- Is it chosen at random?
- Bigger numbers give an advantage.
- That's right.
(Roll a die
that has numbers from 1 to 3.)
(Bigger numbers will increase
their chances of success.)
- Is three the biggest number?
- Yes.
(Suk Jin, the man with 2 lives,
goes 1st.)
- Two. That's not too bad.
- Your error range is two.
- Okay.
- That's not half bad.
It's my turn.
Everyone will lose a body part. One.
- He will lose a body part.
- Give me three.
I will lose a body part.
- Two.
- It bounced.
That's too bad.
- One.
Everyone will lose a body part.
It's bound to happen.
- One.
- Gosh.
It was three
before the dice bounced.
- Three.
- I am jealous.
Take turns and guess
the number of long-legged octopuses.
I don't know the answer.
- Can our answers overlap?
- Yes.
My answer is 45.
Your answer is 45.
- I think 50 would be too big.
- My answer is 39.
- Your answer is 39.
- There are more than that.
I know.
Don't say that.
(Jae Suk)
- My answer is 49.
- Your answer is 49.
That's a good one.
My answer is 47.
Your answer is 47. Suk Jin.
My answer is 51.
Are there that many?
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook)
My answer is 46.
(Jong Kook: 45 to 47)
- My answer is 46.
- I should have gotten 3.
(Se Chan, So Min, Jae Suk,
Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Jong Kook)
The answer will be revealed.
(Se Chan, So Min, Jae Suk,
Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Jong Kook)
- Three people survived.
- What?
Three people? I must be wrong.
The answer...
(Se Chan, So Min, Jae Suk,
Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Jong Kook)
is 50.
Gosh.
Jae Suk, Suk Jin,
and Ji Hyo survived.
I survived.
I knew 50 would be the answer.
- Were there that many?
- We lose a body part, right?
- I had a feeling...
that there were 50.
- It's okay to lose a body part.
- Number three,
Jong Kook is out.
- It's okay.
- I am out. I have one life left.
- Are you out?
- I am out.
Number seven, Se Chan is out.
Gosh, I survived somehow.
- Number 6, So Min is out.
- I knew it would be 50.
I felt like 50 would be
the right answer.
Were there 50 long-legged octopuses?
I was going to say 50.
(Hide-and-Seek of Despair
took out 3 people.)
What is that?
(The next object enters.)
Maybe it's a mountain of doughnuts.
The cloth will be removed
on the count of three.
One, two, three.
(Screaming)
Gosh, there are too many.
How will we count them?
Can we touch them?
You can't touch them.
We can't touch them.
Roughly...
- My rough guess is 30.
- My rough guess is 40.
Somewhere between 30 and 40.
My guess is 40.
(Completely focused)
(How many are there?)
- It's impossible to count them.
- I am so annoyed.
They keep moving. Hold on.
(The little webfoot octopus
acts out.)
How many are there?
- Count with them.
- Hey, get lost.
Get lost.
- This is really hard.
- This is driving me crazy.
Counting 30, 40...
- Counting 40...
- I can't count them.
It's impossible to count them.
There are about 30.
- Gosh.
- I will go with 30.
I think 40 would be too big.
I will go with 30 or 35.
Right now...
All right. Cover the sink.
- I don't know.
- Seriously.
- I can't count loaches.
- Let's decide on the error range.
- Okay.
I will throw it first.
Okay. I did it.
- Let's get three.
- That's not too bad.
I am dead.
- My answer is 40.
- My answer is 37.
My answer is 38.
(Jae Suk: 36 to 40)
My answer is 37.
(Ji Hyo: 35 to 39)
My answer is 35.
(Jong Kook: 34 to 36)
- I will lose a body part.
- I will die if it isn't 35.
- All right. This is interesting.
- Did anyone survive?
Why? Did anyone survive?
Half of the members survived.
This is driving me crazy.
- I guess I am not one of them.
- It must be them again.
I think I survived.
The answer...
(Jong Kook, Se Chan, and Suk Jin
are out if their answers are wrong.)
(So Min, Se Chan, Jae Suk,
Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Jong Kook)
is 40.
- I survived.
- You jerk!
I said that there were 40.
- I survived.
- I survived, right?
I survived.
(Jae Suk, Se Chan,
and So Min survived.)
- I survived.
- I survived, right?
I survived. My answer was 38.
I should have picked 39.
I said that there were 40.
For goodness' sake.
- Are you out?
- I am done for.
Me too.
- Number two, Suk Jin is out.
- Okay.
Number three, Jong Kook is out.
- I said that there were 40.
- I will follow you. I am done for.
If you survive this round,
only the final remains.
Hurry up and change.
- Does that mean I have a chance?
- Yes.
(Ali has survived for a long time
despite having one life left.)
Hurry up.
I will join you soon.
All right.
Here comes the last question.
(Will they become webfoot octopuses
or move on to the final?)
Remove...
(It's the last round
of Hide-and-Seek of Despair.)
the cloth.
- Gosh.
What?
(Gosh.)
You have 30 seconds.
Isn't it a painting?
(The last stage involves carps.)
- What should I do?
- I thought it was a painting.
(Jae Suk counts them as a group.)
- They are moving too much.
- Ten seconds remain.
In 10, 9, 8, 7,
- six, five,
- What should I do?
four, three, two, one.
Time's up. Come on.
- All right.
- I mean...
No way.
Go away.
(The little one is absorbed
in his role.)
I am dead.
All right. Let's roll the dice.
Roll the dice.
Rolling the dice is important.
My answer is 35.
- Your answer is 35.
- The number is smaller than that.
My error range is two, right?
My answer is 32.
- I am safe if it's 30, right?
- Yes.
Okay. My answer is 32.
- My answer...
- It won't be a round number.
is 30. No, 31.
- Your answer is 31.
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo: 29 to 33)
There must be more than 25.
- There must be more than 25.
- Hurry over here.
- I think so.
- My answer is 30.
- Okay.
- There can't be 30.
- Our answers are about the same.
- If the answers...
are 50, 40, and 30,
I would be disappointed.
You never know.
Maybe they used it against them.
The answer...
(So Min, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk)
is 34.
(So Min, Se Chan)
- I survived.
- I was off by one, right?
- Me too.
(Se Chan and So Min survived.)
(This one passed all 3 questions
with a single life.)
- Let's move on to the final!
- Number one, Jae Suk is out.
Number five, Ji Hyo is out.
- Who is out?
- I survived.
Come here, Ji Hyo.
(Only the last stage remains.)
I will use the money well.
I will buy presents.
Let's go racing with the money.
Yes.
Final survivors, gather around.
All right.
I am moving on
To the final
With one life left
He dodged.
- He dodged my bullets.
- I am moving on
To the final
With one life left
(The siren blares.)
(Why is the siren blaring
at this point?)
(Who died?)
Who died?
Se Chan is out.
Number seven, Se Chan is out.
Hold on.
- Why did you behave flippantly?
- Hey.
- Hold on.
- Why did you behave flippantly?
- Hey.
- I am moving on
- You behaved flippantly.
- To the final
- Hey. This is too much.
- I am moving on
- Why did you behave flippantly?
- Please take him out.
(Why did Se Chan get eliminated?)
- I survived.
- Me too.
(It was the work of the member
who sent through a lot with him.)
- Let's move on to the final!
- We need to take Se Chan out.
We need to take Se Chan out.
I am moving on
- To the final
- Se Chan.
(His song became a funeral march.)
Please take him out.
(They feel refreshed
after taking him out.)
- Go and change.
- Gosh.
- It ended so fruitlessly.
- Listen.
- One of the three will win.
- Hey.
We can't go all together.
Okay? Don't even think about it.
Number seven, Se Chan is out.
(Number of Players: 4
Cash Prize: 3,000 dollars)
(Number of Players: 3
(The final game)
My heartiest congratulations
to the final survivors.
The final game is
Jackstones on the Cliff.
(The final game,
Jackstones on the Cliff)
- Jackstones?
- You will place...
five jackstones on the back
of your hand.
If you catch all five stones,
you will win the prize money.
- I'm really bad at this.
- But if you fail,
you will lose your life.
I'm good at playing jackstones.
If you have lives left,
you can try it again.
Those who succeed
will be co-champions.
We catch the jackstones?
I'm really good at this.
No, you're not.
- I really am.
- What are you talking about?
We just catch the five jackstones?
- Yes.
- That's it?
- That's it.
- It's so easy.
They just need to catch the stones.
Gosh, I can catch only four stones.
- Gosh.
- This is...
You should spread
your fingers like this.
- This is crazy. I can't do this.
- My hand is too small.
So Min, you might become
the single winner.
So Min.
(Catching all the stones)
So Min is good.
Look at her.
So Min will definitely win.
All right.
- This is a death match.
- For 3,000 dollars.
You'll do it in turn.
It's a death match
for 3,000 dollars.
So Min, you do it.
All right.
(Each member has two chances.)
This is fun.
Then you're out.
Let's begin. Okay. Let's go.
This is the final game
for the prize money.
It begins now.
(It begins now.)
All right. So Min goes first,
and Ji Hyo goes next.
- Start.
- Do I get to practice it?
- No, you don't.
- I'll try then.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
(She puts all the 5 stones
on her hand and throws them.)
Oh no.
- Cut it off.
- Jeon So Min is out.
- Oh no.
- She's out.
(Jeon Mi Nyeo's first attempt
ends up in failure.)
- Let me take care of it.
- I have only one life left.
Cut it.
Who's next?
I just can't catch them.
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, are you ready?
- I had them on my hand.
- Yes.
- Let me try.
- I bet she will drop them.
She has small hands.
- Gosh.
- That was too high.
(Dropping the stones)
- All right.
- Ji Hyo...
What did you play
when you were little?
- That's because my hands are small.
- Song Ji Hyo is out.
You all have only one life left.
- Please cut it.
- Should I cut it?
Cut it.
What if Jae Suk wins?
Hang on.
- This is driving me crazy.
- So Min is more likely to win.
Jae Suk must feel nervous.
- I'm feeling nervous.
- That's what always happens.
Just take it easy.
- I will...
- He'll be overwhelmed by tension.
I did mess up
the game of slap-match.
When he feels nervous...
- I even failed to touch the ttakji.
- Seriously?
- I knew it.
- Because I was nervous.
- That's what he does.
- Because everyone was watching.
You don't have to throw them high.
- He's really...
- Can I try it now?
- Yes.
- Take it easy.
(He placed the stones on his hand.)
I don't think he can do it.
He did it.
It's done. Take your time.
(Groaning)
Take your time.
(He threw the stones away.)
It was so close.
- Number one, Jae Suk is out.
- Why is it so hard?
- Go ahead and cut it.
- Where?
Now you all have only one life left.
Let me cut it for you.
If they fail, will they be out?
If you succeed, you'll survive.
If you fail, you'll be out.
My heart is pounding so fast.
I'm in trouble.
This is driving me crazy.
If all of you fail,
no one will win the prize money.
My goodness.
No one will get the money
after we go through all this?
I hope all three of you will fail.
- All right.
- That's better.
- I like that.
- Then it's only fair.
Will So Min become
the single winner...
for the first time?
- It will be my first time.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Try your best.
- You should win.
But I'm feeling so nervous.
What do I do?
You were good earlier.
She's good. So Min,
pull yourself together.
I can't focus.
This is all about mental strength.
You were doing just fine.
(Will she catch the stones
as she did while practicing?)
- This is all about mental strength.
- You were doing just fine.
(Rolling)
(Sighing)
She failed.
Oh dear.
Bye.
So Min was...
- She did a good job earlier.
- She was good.
Hey.
Number six, So Min is out.
- I was nervous.
- You should catch it right away.
- I was too nervous.
- The thing is,
they feel nervous
because it's for 3,000 dollars.
You should just catch it right away.
There's no way Ji Hyo can do this.
- I can't do this.
- Give it a try.
I'll try anyway.
Don't spread your fingers like that.
You throw them too hard.
- She doesn't seem good.
- I have small hands.
That's not why. It's just
that you throw them too high.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Just leave her be.
- This is for 3,000 dollars.
- So she feels nervous.
- I hope she will make it.
- Make it low?
- Yes.
- It should be kept low.
- This is for 3,000 dollars.
Good luck.
(Dropping)
Can she really do this?
- Gosh.
- I knew it.
(Song Ji Hyo failed.)
All right.
Number five, Ji Hyo is out.
Jae Suk, you should win.
Let's not say anything.
Go, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, you should do this.
- Jae Suk, take the money.
- If no one wins,
- all our efforts will end in vain.
- You should take it.
You can't make it this way.
It's too high.
You should keep it
as low as possible.
- If Jae Suk fails, is it over?
- It's too high.
Jae Suk, don't try to throw them.
Try to keep the stones as they are
while you flip your hand.
It's still too high.
I just can't do things right
at a time like this.
(I just can't do things right
at a time like this.)
- Because you feel nervous.
- Because I'm under pressure.
You're a dad.
Just give it a go.
- Why are you shaking your hands?
- Just do it.
Don't get carried away.
- It's a close-up shot syndrome.
- Why is it so hard?
This is about 3,000 dollars.
But why are you shaking so hard?
- I'll give it a try.
- Okay.
He's doing it.
He did it. Catch them.
It's done. All you need to do
is catch them.
(He managed to place
the stones on his hand.)
- Put them together.
- Do it gently.
- It's almost done.
- It's 3,000 dollars.
It's done.
(He threw them!)
(They've played Webfoot Octopus Game
all day since early morning.)
(This is the finish
of the long game.)
- It's almost done.
- It's 3,000 dollars.
It's done.
(He caught them.)
(Unbelievable)
He did it?
- Did he nail it?
- He did.
- He did it.
- Number one is the final winner.
- He looked like Lee Jung Jae.
- My gosh.
- Share the money with us.
- Congratulations.
- He won?
Congratulations.
I made it to the finals
for the first time.
Was it your first time?
I think you did it before.
All the games are over.
Gosh, you did it.
My heartiest congratulations...
to the final survivor.
(My heartiest congratulations
to the final survivor.)
The money is coming down.
(Surprised)
It is a total of 3,000 dollars.
- Really?
- Are you serious?
- Congratulations.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- No one knew I'd be the winner.
- Right.
But I survived to the end.
That's me!
(That's me!)
All right!
(Number of Players: 2
Cash Prize: 3,000 dollars)
(Number of Players: 1
(We will die if we fall.)
- Il Nam.
- Three, two, one.
(MC Minzy: This is
the last thing I want to do.)
(Yeji: I'm horrible
at making a guess.)
(Luda: This is so scary.)
Here's the hero of our team.
- Gosh, be careful.
- Watch out.
(BIBI: She's fearless.)
He disappeared.
(A few hours ago,
they decided who would go first.)
(They have to pick larger numbers
no matter what.)
(He gives up his big face
to get a larger number.)
(I'll go.)
(But they are acting mean.)
(We don't know it yet.)
(I might be your future wife.)
(They give up their future
out of fear.)
(How will their attempt to get
a larger number end up?)
- Who was that?
- I say woo
(The Choice of Destiny,
Golden Ratio Race)