(Last week)
Today, we have Trainer Kook...
(Trainer Kook decided to foster good
athletes to revive Tiger Gym.)
(So he accepted new members
and trained them harshly.)
Do you think
that loyalty is important or not?
(The members went through
harsh training...)
(for the revival of Tiger Gym.)
- I feel bad for him.
- You two, please stand up.
- Is this a prison camp?
- Tell us what we did wrong.
It's over the net.
(Thanks to the trainer, the members
have become good athletes.)
Good job. That's the power
of a middle-aged man.
(During the hard training,
they got something.)
(The members
who just finished their training...)
(got an invitation out of the blue.)
(What is the invitation for?)
(Surprised)
(What is the invitation about?)
(The 2021 New Female Player Draft,
Trainer Recruitment)
(Kim Yeon Koung)
(Kim Hee Jin, Oh Ji Young)
(Yeum Hye Seon,
Lee So Young, Ahn Hye Jin)
(Park Eun Jin)
(Coming soon)
(The national volleyball players
are participating in the draft.)
(Trainer Kook smiles broadly
looking at the amazing rookies.)
(However)
(The uncontrollable rookies
dominate the gym.)
(Jae Suk!)
(Okay, Kwang Soo.)
Okay, Kwang Soo.
- One more time. Feeling!
- Intuition!
(The draft with the best rookies
will begin soon.)
We are recruiting new trainers...
to bring in promising rookies, so we
look forward to your participation.
So, this team...
- To lead this team?
- Today's winner...
will be a new trainer
to train the promising rookies.
- Really?
- What?
I mean, next week.
- There's no chance I can win.
- Me neither.
- There will be Kim Yeon Koung...
and many other players.
- Hang on.
- I want to be a trainer.
Will Sang Jun be
here again next week?
We don't know yet.
It depends on the results.
Really? Then I'll try hard
from now on.
- I didn't know.
- It's too late.
- I'll come back next week.
- All right.
Can I become a trainer too?
You can.
- My gosh.
- Is there a chance of an upset?
This is thrilling.
A trainer to lead this team?
(This is how they set up a new gym.)
(A week later)
(The day of the draft)
Hello. I'm Caster Jung Woo Young...
who will host
the 2022 Running League Draft.
Just like last year, we have
a lot of promising rookies...
in the Korean sporting world.
A lot of gymnasiums who got
the invitation from the league...
competed fiercely for the draft.
And only two trainers won
the draft rights to the rookies.
(Trainer Kook from Tiger Gym)
(And Trainer Yoo Jae Suk?)
(Last week, they had the last match
for the huge prize money.)
(They struggled
to win the prize money.)
(A snailfish shows up.)
I'll announce the final results.
(The winner was announced
after the match.)
The trainer who will get a new gym
and 800 dollars is...
(Captain Yoo became a new trainer...)
(after pocketing
the membership fee.)
(I want to get away
from Trainer Kook,)
(so I kept pocketing the money.)
(I will bring shame to you.)
(I have my own gym now,
so keep your mouth shut!)
(Trainer Kook of Tiger Gym)
(Trainer Yoo of Locust Gym)
The trainers who are here
to unearth the promising rookies...
will enter now.
"Pain is a gift from up above."
Trainer Kim Jong Kook of Tiger Gym.
(Trainer Kook of Tiger Gym.)
"A student of today
is a rival of tomorrow."
Trainer Yoo Jae Suk of Locust Gym.
All right.
- Chan Hee is back.
- He's back.
(Both trainers are talkative.)
(Trainer Yoo trained by Trainer Kim
is seeking to bring in rookies.)
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- All right.
(They take a seat
making idle remarks.)
Trainer Yoo won the last race.
- That's right.
- He was just lucky.
So I'm the owner of my team.
I made it happen.
So you became independent
from Trainer Kook.
Right. Like I always say,
I don't like to work for someone.
I should let him go when it's time.
- Right.
- I see.
I do admire Trainer Kook's
athletic ability...
- and experience. But...
- I see.
he still lives in the past.
It's like an apprentice system.
- Do I live in the past?
- He's too strict.
- I'm rather strategic.
- Really?
- I utilize AI.
- You think you use your brain.
- That's right.
- I'm not like that.
Training brings about good results.
- I see.
- It's all about training.
I don't know
who will join my team yet,
but I'll make sure
to filter out the players...
who are not good enough...
- to participate in the draft.
- We have to.
- That's what we have to do.
- Right.
- Now the first players will enter.
- Who is it?
Do we have to see the players
coming from that way?
"I will show you the power
of a father with three children."
He's an old rookie, Haha.
He doesn't look that way,
but he used to be a student athlete.
An old rookie, Yang Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan used to be
in an athletic club.)
They're making a fuss already.
I can't pay them
more than five cents.
Do we really have to pay them?
(Their lame performance
doesn't even deserve 5 cents.)
I can't pay them
more than five cents.
- We're here.
- I don't like stuff like this.
I don't like it either.
- Sport is no joke.
- Sure.
- When you exercise...
- I know.
The father of three children
is so pretentious.
He's so annoying.
All right. I'll introduce
the next players.
"I'm on the next 60-level."
"But I have a heart
of the MZ Generation."
An old rookie, Ji Suk Jin.
A good face.
Good power.
And good dating skills.
Song Ji Hyo.
A touching story of a forever judge.
An old rookie, Jeon So Min.
- They are...
- They are all of a sort.
Are they traffic lights or what?
I'm watching...
- their movements carefully.
- Turn around.
But I haven't seen anything useful.
There's nothing worth
saving from them.
Gosh, it's hot.
Why is it so hot in here?
- Look at the guy in the blue suit.
- Okay.
That guy is...
- What about me?
- He's a troublemaker.
- Right.
- What?
- We're better off without him.
Did you hear the rumor already?
Let's hurry and...
- We should move on.
- Right.
Let's move on to the main round.
All right then.
I'm excited.
- You've waited so long.
- We have to do this.
- The promising rookies will...
- All right.
- enter now.
- Promising rookies.
- Enter now.
- Who are they?
Christian has the Bible.
Buddhism has Buddhist scriptures.
And volleyball...
has Kim Yeon Koung.
Rookie Kim Yeon Koung.
(All-time number one
volleyball player, Kim Yeon Koung)
She's a rookie.
The Olympic top four good-looker,
Rookie Kim Hee Jin.
(The byword for good looks,
Kim Hee Jin)
This is unbelievable.
- They look so cool.
- They are perfectly proportioned.
They look amazing.
They are like models.
(The two pillars
of the national volleyball team)
(The living legend recognized
around the world, Kim Yeon Koung)
(Powerful spike
that nothing can block)
(An all-around player
with an impenetrable defense)
(Captain Yeon Koung's leadership
brings her team together.)
(We live in the time
of Kim Yeon Koung.)
(The powerful main armament
of the national team, Kim Hee Jin)
(She sends a ball
only to empty spots like GPS.)
(Her destructive offense
from the 3-meter-high point)
(High-level defense)
(Showing the impenetrable blocking,)
(the magical teddy bear
captivated people's hearts.)
(The rookies who live up
their names show up.)
They're really tall.
Kwang Soo!
- Isn't this what you do?
- In 1, 2, and 3.
(They ignore
what other members say.)
They look amazing.
(A heart serve)
They show good performances.
(The old rookies' lame toss)
(She responds to it
with a sweet spike.)
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
It's so nice to see you here.
Thank you.
- Hello.
- You're the best.
- By the way...
- Hello.
- You guys look...
- like models.
- Hello.
- You look amazing.
- Unbelievable.
(They have the charisma
that comes from their height.)
They're so tall.
As Yeon Koung walked in,
- she looked like Kwang Soo.
- I thought she was Kwang Soo.
- She was like Kwang Soo.
- I get that a lot.
- I know.
- Her long hair.
- They say we have similar images.
- This is unbelievable.
Seriously, you look
just like Kwang Soo.
You look just like him.
I will try to replace
Kwang Soo today.
- Because I look like him.
- Okay.
And we have Hee Jin here.
- She's really handsome.
- I know.
- All right. Go up there.
- Why?
You guys are standing up now.
You didn't stand up when we came in.
Just go back to your seats.
- My goodness.
- All right then.
- Let's sit.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- I got the vaccine yesterday.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
Turn on the AC.
Suk Jin is feeling hot.
He got the vaccine yesterday,
so he's running a fever.
He had the second Pfizer shot,
so he's feeling hot.
I got the second Pfizer shot.
I'm feeling really hot.
Today...
Since you got the second shot,
- you may go home early.
- Right. You should go home.
No, I'm fine.
- They're so cool. Their shoes.
- They are amazing.
We have five more players.
(There are more players to meet.)
Number one in the dig ranking
of the Tokyo Olympics.
She's the best libero,
Rookie Oh Ji Young.
- Libero!
- Oh Ji Young.
She's the nation's beloved setter
with volleyball DNA,
Rookie Yeum Hye Seon.
- Yeum Hye Seon!
(After Ji Young's defense,
Hye Seon scores.)
Welcome!
Hello.
(The official scoring duo,
Yeum Hye Seon and Oh Ji Young)
(Yeum Hye Seon: Setter)
(She's the master
of a spin-free serve.)
(Her dancing serve emasculates
the opposition defense.)
(But she also shows good defense.)
(Nation's beloved setter,
Yeum Hye Seon)
(Oh Ji Young: Libero)
(Perfect defense ranked first
in the digs of the Tokyo Olympics)
(Oh Ji Young receives the ball...)
(and Yeum Hye Seon finishes it.)
(All scores start with her defense.)
(Forever libero, Oh Ji Young)
(The keepers of the national team
show up.)
Throw the ball.
(The libero's spike performance)
(Excited)
They're the best.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
(Since they are volleyball players,
they slap high-fives.)
- That was amazing.
- This is what they do.
I saw them do this.
Please come here.
- You guys do this when you score.
- Right.
That's so cool.
- Please say hello.
- We have Ji Young and Hye Seon.
When they were with other players,
- they didn't look so cool.
- Right.
- But in the flesh...
- In the flesh,
Hye Seon and Ji Young are very tall.
- We have to look up at them.
- I know.
It's not like that.
Before I came here...
They all are very tall.
I didn't want to look short,
so I put on high heels.
- I didn't want to look short.
- I understand.
Please have a seat.
All right. Please have a seat.
This is really...
My goodness.
- The place is full.
- Trainer Kook and I will...
My goodness.
I'm not sure if it's okay
to pick players I want.
We have three players left.
I'll introduce them all together.
She's an all-around player who's
good at attacking and defending.
She's called Air So Young.
Rookie Lee So Young.
- Lee So Young.
- So Young.
She's called Jangchung Shin Min A
with perfect serves.
Rookie Ahn Hye Jin.
Jangchung Shin Min A!
- The new cute giant at the center!
- Who looks like Shin Min A?
- The rookie player, Park Eun Jin?
- Shin Min A?
(The new cute giant Park Eun Jin
who blocks the center area)
(The Generation MZ who dominated
the Tokyo Olympics are here.)
(The youngest players
with skills and passion...)
(who are the future
of Korean volleyball)
(Lee So Young, left-side hitter)
She scored a point at the right time
whenever she joined the game.
(She scored a point whenever needed
with her jump skill and agility.)
She's hitting the ball.
And it worked.
(She destroys blocks
with her unique bowstring spikes.)
(Air So Young)
I agree.
(Ahn Hye Jin,
setter and right-side hitter)
Ahn Hye Jin is
serving the ball again.
Ahn Hye Jin is serving the ball.
(The master of tricky serves
that are hard to receive)
Player substitution.
Park Eun Jin is going in.
(Park Eun Jin, middle blocker)
Park Eun Jin hit the ball.
She hit it long. But it's blocked.
Kim Yeon Koung scored.
(She turns the tide
whenever her team faces a crisis.)
Park Eun Jin hit the ball.
She hit it long. But it's blocked.
(The team scores
whenever Eun Jin serves.)
- Eun Jin served the ball very well.
- Exactly.
(Park Eun Jin is the starting point
of all attacks.)
- Juggle, everyone!
- Oh, my.
(The Youngest Avengers are here.)
My goodness.
(The members are welcoming them
with an air juggling performance.)
Welcome!
- They're all so tall.
- I know, right?
- They're so tall.
- Indeed.
(The cuties are here.)
They planned it together.
It's nice to see you all.
- It's nice to see you.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- The cuties are here.
- Hey, why are you standing there?
- Hello.
- Welcome.
(They bumped into each other.)
- Hi.
- This is so exciting.
(But the passionate youngest players
didn't care.)
- I'm exhilarated.
- Let's go!
This is so exciting.
(It feels like a festival.)
- So Min is 170cm tall. She's tall.
- Right. I'm not small.
- But she looks so cute.
- Stand right next to her.
- I'm surprised.
- I know.
They're all so tall.
Hey, kids, go back to your seats.
- They look like babies now.
- I'm so excited.
Come on. Stop joking around
and go to your seats, kids.
Today,
- Jong Kook is excited.
- Trainer Kook and I...
(Jong Kook likes it
when athletes come on the show.)
- He's excited.
- Sorry?
You look so cute
standing next to Yeon Koung.
- You look like a baby.
- Can you pinch his cheeks?
- Please do that for us.
- Pinch his cheeks.
- Pinch his cheeks just once.
- I can't stand next to her.
Can you just pat him on the head?
- Put your arm around my shoulders.
- Right.
- My, he looks so cute.
- How cute.
- Whenever you get bored...
- Kwang Soo.
She looks like Kwang Soo.
- How cute.
- We haven't met anyone...
- She did it like Kwang Soo used to.
- as tall as Kwang Soo in a while.
- They all look fabulous.
- Now we'll begin the interview...
- to learn more about the rookies.
- That's important.
Before that, let's give the national
volleyball team players...
- a round of applause.
- All right.
Welcome.
(The national volleyball team
players, welcome.)
They're so cool.
Their games moved my heart.
- They were incredible.
- I was touched too.
- No words can describe it.
- Exactly.
- It was amazing.
- I was filming the game at the end.
- Really?
- Yes, the moment of the victory.
He's excited.
- He must be happy to meet them.
- He seems so happy.
- He's a big fan of athletes.
- He gets so excited.
- He's exhilarated now.
- I was recording that moment.
- You filmed as you're watching it?
- His left foot is out.
I was sure that they would win.
As a workout enthusiast,
it was so amazing.
(He got choked with emotion
and couldn't go on.)
- I see.
- He looks like an athlete.
- He's just a gym lover.
- I'm just a gym lover.
- Yes.
- He just loves to work out.
- I'm a gym lover.
I'm like an expert
when it comes to that.
He's like a town gym lover
who can be seen in any town.
(Laughing)
(The gym lover is excited to meet
the international sports stars.)
- He likes to train others too.
- True. I like that too.
We'll interview each of you briefly.
- First up is Yeon Koung.
- Yes.
How have you been
since the Olympics?
- I've been doing great.
- Yes.
I got a lot of offers
for advertisements.
- You deserve it.
- Maybe I shouldn't have said that.
You all worked hard.
If I were close to her,
I would've asked her to treat me.
Hey, be quiet.
Come on. Be quiet!
(The original steps up.)
- How dare you make a noise?
- What did you say?
I'm here as a rookie too.
By the way, Suk Jin,
are you not feeling well?
- I think he is. He's sweating.
- He's sweating.
Why would I be feeling unwell?
- I mean it's such a special day.
- Are you all right?
- Don't mind me and go on.
- We need a stretcher.
He really is sweating here.
- His lips are so pale.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I'm worried about him.
- Shouldn't he lie down?
- Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- His lips are so pale.
Anyway, Yeon Koung, you've been
the team captain for a long time.
Have you ever thought
that you're bossy?
- I'm sure she has.
- Right.
I think... Have I ever been bossy?
Pardon?
- You just acted bossy.
- Did I?
- Yes, you did.
- That's what bossy people say.
- "Have I ever been bossy?"
- Right?
- Oh, I didn't realize that.
- She didn't know.
- To be honest, I'm not sure.
- I see.
- But sometimes...
- You didn't realize it, right?
- No, I didn't.
- That proves you're bossy.
- Gosh. I'm bossy?
- You're bossy if you don't know.
- If you do, you're not bossy.
- That's right.
Hey, have I ever been bossy to you?
- Answer me.
- It's good to see you, Yeon Koung.
(The bossy Haha jumps in.)
I am bossy too.
Don't talk while I'm talking!
(In terms of that, he's on the same
level as Queen Yeon Koung.)
Hey, listen.
Don't talk while I'm talking.
We have so many bossy people here.
There are three of them.
- She's definitely bossy.
- They love being bossy.
What did he say?
- What was the question?
- You didn't realize it, right?
Suk Jin just whispered to me...
asking what we were talking about.
- He wasn't even listening.
- We're talking about being bossy.
- He didn't hear you.
- I see.
- He never listens to others. Bossy.
- That's true.
- Then let's ask her teammates.
- Let's do that.
Has any of you ever thought...
- that Yeon Koung was bossy?
- Tell us.
- That never happened, but...
- I see.
We once said we wanted to cover her
with a blanket...
- and beat her up at least once.
- That's right.
- Covering her with a blanket?
- Yes.
(Covering her with a blanket
and hitting her?)
Covering her with a blanket?
What does that mean?
- After all the matches ended...
- You wanted to hit Yeon Koung?
we all had a beef with her
after several months.
- So on the last day...
- Like slapping her on the back?
- No, we'd kick her too.
- Just like a game penalty.
It would never be
just slapping me on the back.
- Well, she said that.
- They'd beat me up...
without letting me know who hit me.
That's what a blanket is for.
- That's right.
- Oh, I see.
Then how about we give you
a chance to do so at the end?
Sure. If you prepare a blanket,
I would...
- Why don't you make a promise?
- It will be a good chance.
- We'd appreciate it.
- What's with you?
- Really? They all like the idea.
- Do you have a blanket?
- A blanket.
- We'd appreciate it very much.
We don't even need a blanket.
Just cover her face.
- We just need to cover her face.
- Just her face.
Oh, my. You all seem so excited.
- Considering their reactions...
- We should do it today.
- Pardon me?
Are you saying you want to try it?
Please step forward.
(He approves of it unintentionally
with a pale face.)
Let's cover him with the carpet.
- I didn't mean it.
- Help him.
- That's not what I meant.
- We'll cover his face with this.
(Since the vaccination, Pfizer Ji
volunteers to get anything.)
- He volunteered to be hit.
- Right.
In the pre-interview,
she was asked...
which cast members she thought
she looks better than...
- and to rate us on our looks.
- On our looks.
And she said, "Se Chan is
no match for me."
(She answered,
"Se Chan is no match for me.")
(By her standards,
Se Chan is the ugliest.)
That was her answer.
- Also...
- How could you tell them?
- There's one more thing.
- I only told that to the writer.
That means she thinks
Jae Suk is ugly too.
- Yes, she said that too.
- Right?
She said, "Jae Suk sure is popular,
but he's not handsome."
- That was between you and me.
- I like that comment.
- That's a good comment.
- She picked the two of us.
- You see...
- Se Chan and me.
One of the good things
about her is...
- that she always speaks her mind.
- True.
- She gave an honest answer.
- Yes.
When you were invited to this show,
you said you wanted to be here
with your junior players.
- What was the reason?
- I wonder why.
- I'm too embarrassed to say it.
- I see.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Actually, I got invited
to many other TV shows as well.
- But this is the most popular show.
- Yes.
It's one of the best variety shows.
- I'm honored to hear that.
- Thank you for saying that.
And they all are huge fans
of this show.
- Really?
- They love this show.
So I divided them into two groups.
One group would be on another show
with me.
- And the other would be here.
- Oh, I see.
- You divided them into two groups?
- As far as I heard...
Actually, I met Yang Hyo Jin
and Kim Su Ji.
- Yes.
- And Su Ji told me the same thing.
"We wanted to be on 'Running Man'
too, but Yeon Koung divided us."
- They weren't chosen.
- Did you randomly divide them?
No, that's not true.
- I let them choose the show.
- I see.
The players who didn't play long
in the games...
- wouldn't get many chances...
- You're right.
- to appear on a TV show.
- You did the right thing.
So I suggested we should give them
a chance too...
and divide the team.
It's always the same person who gets
to be on a TV show. It's Hee Jin.
It's always the same person,
and it's Hee Jin.
- That's true.
- Hee Jin appeared on many shows.
- I mean, she didn't play that well.
- Okay.
But she's the only one
who gets invited to those shows.
- She appeared on many shows.
- She's so funny.
- She's hilarious.
- That's not fair.
- They have so much to talk about.
- Right.
I saw her on "The Manager"
not long ago.
You're right. She appeared
on a lot of shows.
- She's done all sorts of stuff.
- I can see that.
- That's true.
- She filmed a TV commercial too.
Are the others scheduled
to be on another show?
- No.
- No, they're not.
- They didn't get invited.
- That will change after this.
- Give it your all.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- We can do this.
- Things will work out well for you.
- Let's do this.
- We'll kill it.
- Pour everything you have in this.
First of all, Hee Jin was chosen
as a national team player...
- when she was in 12th grade.
- She was in 12th grade?
(She joined the national team
at the age of 19.)
It's hard for a high school student
to be chosen.
- She has short hair now,
- Yes.
- but her photo with long hair...
- drew a lot of attention.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- They'll reveal that photo.
- She had twin tails back then.
- Oh, no.
- It's viral.
- I want to see it.
- They'll show us the photo.
- Do we have her photo?
Really? She had twin tails?
(The comedians are pretending
they saw the photo.)
She really had
that hairstyle before?
(Laughing)
(Staring)
- I'm scared.
- She's so scary.
- We comedians are good at this.
- We can make it funnier.
Hee Jin, you said
that you're quite tenderhearted,
and that you get timid
whenever you make a mistake.
That's understandable.
- I could see that about you.
- True.
- I always want to do well.
- Yes.
And I should score points
as an offensive player.
So I get downcast
when I can't score enough points.
Is it just how you feel?
- Or are you worried about someone?
- Does someone put pressure on you?
(Glancing)
(She glanced at Yeon Koung
instead of answering.)
- She just looked at...
- Is someone over there?
- Was there someone there?
- Is anyone there?
Is there anyone over there?
- I think she looked over there.
- She looked...
- Is someone going to come out?
- I think she looked over there.
But I saw her eyes...
- I have a slight squint.
- Okay.
I'm pretty sure she looked...
I see.
If I had to talk about our teams...
I won't say their names.
But some of the cast members won't
be happy to join...
- Trainer Kook's team.
- Absolutely.
- They won't be happy about it.
- I mean...
- we didn't even say anything.
- Exactly.
But those punks tiptoe around us
for no reason.
- "Those punks?"
- That's why we can't seem to...
- He said, "those punks."
- perform at our very best.
- That's exactly my point.
- Yes.
- So Min, anything you want to say?
- Yes?
- Do you have anything to say?
- No.
(She cautiously says no.)
- Is there anything you want to say?
- No, sir.
You've dressed like a referee again.
Look at the color.
Right.
I guess she has no intention
of playing in any games.
- Next up is Yeum Hye Seon.
- All right.
The three generations of your family
have played volleyball.
- Is that true?
- Really?
- Really? That's cool.
- I didn't know that.
Your grandmother and your parents
used to play volleyball.
- Really?
- Yes, that's true.
- I see.
- But...
- they were not so famous.
- Even so.
- But they used to play volleyball.
- Oh, I see.
- Your grandmother too?
- Yes.
- So I...
- That should be a long time ago.
Oh, my. That's impressive.
So whenever she has a game...
- Since it's a volleyball family,
- That's right.
- your parents and grandmother...
- True.
often nag you about how you play.
- I'm sure they do.
- They did so in the early years.
- Did your grandmother do that too?
- When I was a freshman in college,
my grandma called me
after every game I played in.
- What did she say?
At first, she said,
"What was that?
You call that a game?"
- That's so funny.
- But I couldn't yell at her.
- I think I know how it feels.
- That's so funny.
She imitated her grandmother.
- She must've told you her stories.
- That was hilarious.
"Goodness. What was that?"
- "Do you call that volleyball?"
- "Do you call that a game?"
"You're there to play volleyball.
What have you been doing?"
- She said things like that.
- She sounds like a granny.
But I hated to hear her nagging.
Didn't your grandmother say anything
after the Olympics?
After the Olympics,
she was busy playing gateball.
Can she let Suk Jin join her?
Why don't you...
- She was busy playing gateball?
- Suk Jin could join her...
- She's funny.
- Indeed. She's so funny.
- She's really funny.
- Yes, she is.
- I like her story. Hye Seon,
- Right?
I'll give you an extra point
for your story.
- You get points for funny stories.
- Yes.
- That was a good one.
- He evaluates their sense of humor.
Exactly.
- I see her nickname here.
- Right.
She has a nickname? Oh, my.
What is this?
- What does Yeum Cheater mean?
- What does it mean?
(Yeum Cheater?)
- She's a crook.
- Yeum Cheater?
"Yeum" as in "salt?"
- No, her family name.
- Like "The Boy Who Cried Wolf."
- There are a few entertainers...
- Oh, I see.
who have the image of a crook.
- That's true.
- Today's show will be fun.
- Is she a crook?
- Watch out for her.
For example, when I block
during a game,
and it's obvious
that the ball hits my hand,
I'd lie that it didn't touch my hand
without a guilty look.
- Oh, I get it.
- I see.
- They all need that kind of skill.
- That's why I got that nickname.
- That's a good thing for the team.
- It's embarrassing.
- Su Ji talked about it too.
No player would admit it
if the ball touches their hands.
- Really?
- Yes.
But in her case, it's unreasonable
because if it's obvious...
- True.
- that it touched her hand,
- she should admit it.
- She should admit it?
- But she denies even in that case.
- Let me explain.
- The other team would request VAR.
- I mean...
- I'd deny until they ask for it.
- They would make this signal.
- Everyone saw that.
- I wouldn't admit it until then.
- But she would deny.
- She keeps denying until then?
- Yes, she would keep denying.
- Really?
- What's funny is...
that she even lies
to her teammates too.
- Really? What does she say?
- Even her teammates.
- "It didn't touch my hand."
- That she didn't touch it.
- When we ask her...
- Then they'd use VAR.
if she touched the ball,
she would say she didn't.
- It's not like that.
- Right?
- Let me explain.
- What happens when it's confirmed?
- I just apologize.
- She apologizes.
But she knew it all along.
- I'd say sorry.
- By the way, Yeum Cheater.
If your hands moved,
you can't deny it.
But it works once in a while.
- Really?
- Because she denies?
It works sometimes
since I have short arms.
- If it works 1 out of 10 times...
- Even when I tell the truth,
- they don't believe me now.
- We don't believe her.
Then I would say
that I'm really telling the truth,
- but they don't believe me.
- She's just like us.
- I see why you got that nickname.
- Like "The Boy Who Cried Wolf?"
Is that why your nickname is
Yeum Cheater?
- Next, we'll interview Ji Young.
- Okay.
- It's Ji Young's turn.
- As for Ji Young,
- I met her on another show.
- Did you?
You look more sophisticated
than you did last time.
- His pronunciation is funny.
- I was wearing my uniform then.
- Oh, that's why.
- Yes.
Are you saying
that she looked tacky before?
- Right? He subtly criticized...
- Exactly.
- Don't make a comment like that.
- Wait.
He thinks that the national team
uniform looked tacky.
- I agree.
- Right?
He just said that our uniform
looked tacky.
When did I say that?
- Right?
- How dare you say such a thing?
- She's good.
- Keep going.
That's great.
- Oh Ji Young!
- Let's do this!
Let's make it hard for him
to say anything.
This is great!
- She should be an offensive player.
- Hey.
You must know that I never used
the word "tacky."
- You never use that word.
- I just said that she became...
- even more sophisticated.
- That's right.
- Anyway, Ji Young, that's it.
- We should be careful.
- When we hire players...
- Oh, right.
- Wait. No.
- You see,
- I consider everything.
- I mean she didn't stop...
- Let's not hire her.
- When I interviewed her before,
- she bad-mouthed the coach too.
- Really?
- She backbit him.
- Did she really do that?
- Yes, she did.
- Stop saying that.
- Oh Ji Young, checked.
- Which page is she on?
- She's on Page Ten.
- I see.
- Hey, don't join his team.
- Okay.
- I'll never join his team.
- Good.
Oh Ji Young should be our trainer!
- Even if my team loses,
- Yes.
I won't hire Ji Young.
Trainer Yoo got upset.
- My goodness.
- He's upset.
- He's holding a grudge.
- I'll never join his team.
And I'll make him beg me
to join his team. You'll see.
She's right.
We don't have to impress them.
- That's true.
- Of course.
- What did you say?
- We didn't need to impress you.
You don't need to impress us.
We never wanted to hire you.
- Hiring you is like a penalty.
- Exactly.
You'll have to hire me eventually.
- That's so funny.
- We won't hire you.
We should talk about
your relationship with Yeon Koung.
Yeon Koung is one year older
than you.
You've known her since when you two
were on the youth team, right?
- Oh, my.
- Yes.
- What does she mean to you?
- I wonder that too.
Well... She's like my senior player
by many years.
Although people point out
that we both were born in 1988...
- What? Hold on.
- We both were born in 1988.
- Then you two are the same age.
- But I was born...
- in the early month of the year.
- Oh, I see.
- So I started school a year early.
- That's right.
That's why I'm her senior.
They're like me and Park Jin Young.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
It seems that athletes have
a strict seniority system.
Do you use honorifics
when talking to Jin Young?
- Pardon?
- Do you...
- Can you speak more loudly?
- Speak up.
Do you speak formally or casually
to him?
I'm sorry, but if you text me,
- I'll reply right away.
- Please text us.
- Can't you hear me?
- No.
- We'll read it for everyone.
- Please text me instead.
- We'll do that.
There's something wrong
with their ears.
My goodness.
Hey, do you have mold in your ears?
- Do you have mold in your ears?
- Listen.
- Text me.
- Can't you hear me?
- He said "mold in the ears".
Why would I text you
when we can talk to each other?
- I can't hear you clearly.
- We can't hear you.
You can't hear me again?
- Gosh, those jerks.
- Now...
(He blurts out a swear word
that's inappropriate for a TV show.)
We make jokes like this
to make our guests laugh.
- Did that feel good?
- Yes!
Why?
We have an MC here too.
- Go on.
- He's an MC too.
- Stop chatting there.
- It's quite fun.
- Why would you interfere us?
- This is like a YouTube channel.
- It's so much fun.
- Let us do our own show.
- It's just like small talk.
- You just keep going.
We'll just have a little chat here.
We have the best MC
for small talks, so let us do this.
It's being broadcast simultaneously.
- Next up is So Young.
- All right.
Finally! Yes!
- It's her turn.
It's finally her turn.
How have you been, So Young?
I played in another team
before the Olympics.
As I transferred to a new team...
- That's a good thing.
- Right.
- It's a good thing.
- Changing your look.
- It was to create a new mindset.
- Upgrading yourself.
- She wants to show that.
- That's what it symbolizes.
She's determined to devote herself
to her new team.
We need a mindset like this too.
Absolutely. We all need it.
- I signed with a new agency.
- You did?
Do you think I should shave my head?
- I'm not afraid of doing it, but...
- I see.
- I'm not sure how this might sound.
- Okay.
People like me look very different
depending on our hairstyles.
- True. His look would change a lot.
- I know.
- You see...
- It's old-fashioned style.
His hairstyle doesn't make him
look handsome.
(He must think that he looks good
because of his hairstyle.)
He's delusional.
- He says your hair doesn't matter.
- It doesn't make you look handsome.
- Absolutely not.
- He says you don't look handsome.
- Why would he think that way?
- What makes you look better is...
- your glasses.
- I was so puzzled.
By the way...
- You saw who said that, right?
- Hold on.
- I understand Se Chan and Haha.
- Exactly.
- But why did Hye Seon say that?
- She argued strongly.
I couldn't help but hear
them talking.
Yeum Cheater, why did you jump in?
I told you to watch out.
- Yeum Cheater heard us.
- Yeum Cheater.
Yeum Cheater, I gave you
an extra point earlier.
- I'm disappointed.
- Me too.
He's writing down something again.
By the way...
So Young said that she was
a big fan of our show.
- Is she? I'm grateful.
- Yes.
(How do I control my mind?)
(The answer is
watching Running Man.)
(Running Man!)
(As a fan, So Young dreamed of
coming on the show.)
(So did Hye Jin.)
- Yes, this is my favorite TV show.
- Really?
I watch the show every single week.
- Which episode is your favorite?
- That's great.
The one about stock investment.
- Oh, the stock investment?
- You must know well.
- That was good. You liked it too.
- That was the best.
She must know how things work
on the show.
I'm sure she does.
Then you must understand
why I always yell at Suk Jin.
- Of course. I fully understand.
- Great.
- I'm relieved.
- You can understand him?
That's a relief.
By the way,
she has played against Yeon Koung's
team as the team captain.
- Oh, right.
- Really?
- When was that?
- In that game,
I was determined
to block all her attacks.
- Were you?
- Yes.
- You must've done your best.
- How did it turn out?
How did the game go?
- My team won.
- Really?
You lost?
When did you win?
I mean, in general,
not just one game.
- Oh, in general?
- Yes.
I see. Okay.
(Oh, in general? I see. Okay.)
(I see. Okay.)
- So Young seems agitated.
- Wait.
- Yeon Koung seems upset.
- Indeed.
- I got taken aback.
- But...
I won the MVP
in the national league.
- I see.
- As an individual player...
And she won the MVP
in the championship league.
Both of us win the MVP.
- So Young, I have a question.
- Go ahead.
Is there something that Yeon Koung
says often when she nags at you?
- Right. I want to ask everyone.
- No, right?
- She rarely nags at us.
- If you had to pick something.
She often says, "Hey, smile."
"Smile."
Isn't that what a bully would say
when taking money?
That's exactly how it sounds.
While training, she says,
"Let's liven up the mood.
Cheer the others up."
There were times when we all got
a little downcast.
So I told her to smile to spread
positive energy in the team.
So Young was on the mid-level.
- Between senior and junior players.
- Oh, I see.
- So she played an important role.
- That's the most important role.
So I told her to smile and talk
to the others to liven up the mood.
- I often told her that.
- Couldn't you smile first?
- I always do, you know.
- Really?
If she doesn't smile when I do,
- those younger won't smile either.
- Can't you...
- say that with a smile?
- Please say that with a smile.
- But I'm smiling.
- Smile, everyone.
I guess we should smile too.
- Aren't I smiling?
- She's like Kwang Soo.
It's the same smile Kwang Soo has.
She's hilarious.
Next up is Ahn Hye Jin.
(Ahn Hye Jin:
Born February 16, 1998)
(Position:
Setter, right side hitter)
I have no idea
what kind of serves she hits,
but due to its erratic behavior,
her serves are known among teammates
as a dirty serve.
(She displayed her dirty serve
in the Olympic games too.)
(The receiver faltered.)
What on earth is that?
- A dirty serve?
- How can a ball be erratic?
It must drop suddenly.
It'd soar but then suddenly drop.
- How fascinating.
- The drop is steep.
Those who have
received them before...
say that they're the dirtiest.
So they're like Suk Jin's ad-libs.
- They're dirty.
- They're hard to respond to.
- So dirty.
- It's not a compliment though.
I'd love to try and
receive her ball.
(Due to the vaccine aftereffect,
he lets out a dirty response.)
- I'd like that.
- Hold on.
He needs to rest,
so please don't ask him anything.
- I'd love to receive it.
- Suk Jin...
- Pfizer Ji.
- I think it's better for him to...
- Go, Pfizer Ji.
Anyway,
Loony Kid is one of your nicknames
while the other one is...
- Shin Min A.
- Right, Shin Min A.
- What?
- What on earth?
- How did that happen?
- Who calls her that?
- Are you calling yourself that?
- Haven't you heard it before?
- I only found out just now.
- Me too.
- Did you see their reaction?
- I had no idea.
How can you not know this?
- They were all just as shocked.
- It's...
- She's pretty but...
- No one came to her defense.
I know she's pretty,
- but Shin Min A is a first.
- Still...
Shin Min A on the volleyball court,
say your piece.
Is it a nickname you came up with?
No, of course not.
The fans call me that out of love.
- What do you think of it?
- Sorry?
Don't you find it to be wrong?
I do look like her in some ways.
- What the...
- She's angry.
- Do you need a blanket?
- At the end...
- At the end?
- I'll let the anger build up more.
Hye Jin's also not one...
to be intimidated
by Yeon Koung either.
You have no idea
how vicious they can be.
They're even worse than I am.
They're the ones to look out for.
They've built
a sweet image for themselves...
which is why
it looks like I'm scolding them.
- Hye Jin...
- I'm the victim, you know.
- So Hye Jin...
- That I agree.
You're saying
you do look like Shin Min A.
I guess I do.
(I guess I do.)
She's no pushover.
- You have no idea.
- I love it.
- She's gutsy.
- Nice.
I give her points for being gutsy.
(Points for being gutsy)
- Nice.
- Points for being gutsy.
- We need that, you know.
- Of course.
She's Shin Min A
of the volleyball court.
That's how I like my people.
I would've thought twice
if you had cowered.
That showed us
what kind of a person she is.
- Also...
- She thinks they look alike.
- She didn't say it herself.
- Others did.
Others gave her the nickname.
- What can she do about it?
- Exactly.
That can only be translated
to being gutsy.
It's rare for an athlete...
to ask a team owner
to call her as Cutie.
You seem to have a lot of requests.
- I...
- She does it all the time.
- That's my first request.
- Is that so?
Why do you want
to be called that way?
Because I look cute.
Gutsy!
I'm loving the confidence.
Ms. Gutsy!
- Another spoonful of gutsiness.
- She's adorable.
Take my gutsiness!
I give you
the top grade in being gutsy.
Nice.
It's been a while since we had
someone like her on the show.
Now that it's been mentioned,
I see the resemblance.
What?
Why is it...
that I don't see the resemblance?
- Take a look.
- You can see it.
- I see the resemblance.
- You do?
- It's subtle, but...
- How?
Shin Min A...
(She boldly twirls around
for the others to see.)
- Shin Min A?
- In what way?
Just how?
- Shin Min A?
- Hey!
- It's just that...
- As if you know anything.
I don't see the resemblance!
As if you know anything.
- Is it an illusion?
- As if you know anything.
Must one stare to see it?
- Like this?
- Hey!
Quiet, everyone!
- Hey, sit back down.
- Sit down.
Sit back down.
- Quiet.
- I see the resemblance.
It can only be seen
by those with kind hearts.
Kind hearts?
Quiet. You'll see it
if you have a kind heart.
- I'll try all day to spot it.
- Anyway,
- don't...
- Yes?
- Don't look for the resemblance.
- Just don't.
- Gosh.
- We're not saying that...
- she's Shin Min A.
- Exactly.
- So don't look for a resemblance.
- Just don't.
She has the same eyes.
- Just consider it as an opinion.
- Exactly.
All right. So at...
- the Dokko Olympics...
- Dokko?
(He suddenly chokes on his words.)
- What's that?
- What was that?
- The Dokko Olympics?
- He is flustered.
- Is it for the elderly?
The trainers are flustered!
(The Shin Min A debate
threw the trainers off balance.)
- The Dokko Olympics?
- We help each other out, right?
- So that's why.
- As you know,
helping each other out
is the Olympic spirit.
That's why.
Anyway,
so you see...
- The day before the games...
- You must've been traumatized.
You're too traumatized
to speak properly.
(The veteran show host of 30 years
hits his first slump.)
You stuttered just now.
Hye Jin, I apologize.
The Shin Min A debacle...
Why can't anybody tell me
why she looks like Shin Min A?
I want to know.
Why are you obsessed with this?
- Is she a mystery woman?
- Why do you want to know?
Why do you keep asking?
Why do you want to know?
So far, I've found five reasons
why she resembles Shin Min A.
- Really?
- Five reasons.
- Already?
- Yes.
That was fast.
Next up is Park Eun Jin.
Her nickname is...
Ms. Positive
on the volleyball court.
I like people
with positive attitudes.
She has a lot of bright energy.
The moment she steps onto the court,
the whole team is energized.
- "Go, team!"
- She's the only one...
- that Yeon Koung complimented.
- The only one.
She exudes positive energy.
- Is that so?
- I stick to the technical stuff.
Just so you know,
she was excited when
Hye Jin mentioned the blanket.
Is that so?
(Glancing)
Eun Jin's the youngest member
of the team.
- Yes.
- She was born in 1999.
I'm sorry to ask,
but when was your father born?
My dad was born in 1969.
(Her father was born in 1969.)
Suk Jin was born in 1966.
(Pfizer Ji was born in 1966.)
- What did you just say?
- Well...
Well, Eun Jin was born in 1999.
- So of course.
- What are they talking about?
- They're complimenting you.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
What did Suk Jin say just now?
I couldn't hear a thing
because your voices overlapped.
(The simultaneous broadcast
is a mess.)
Just know that Suk Jin is in pain.
He's sick.
- He's at his weakest.
- Is he?
I'm not in any pain.
- This was fun.
- Right.
I love listening
to the players' stories.
For some reason, I'm now starving.
That was a long introduction.
- And now...
- Finally!
Is it time?
Finally!
The draft begins.
Were you able to check
the status of their mentality?
- Of course.
- Same here.
It was a lot of help.
We will now begin...
the 2022 Running League
Rookie Draft.
- That's right.
- Unlike actual drafting events,
the players will choose gyms...
after participating...
in a salary negotiation
with the trainers.
The trainers may
draft their players...
with the money
they earned in the previous race...
and an additional amount
of 500 dollars.
- We're given 500 dollars each.
- The amounts they have are like so.
Trainer Kook has 990 dollars.
- That's a lot.
- Did he say 990 dollars?
Meanwhile, Trainer Yoo
has 1,300 dollars.
That's a lot!
It's all thanks to me.
I have more room to splurge.
The trainers
will choose three players...
and write down their names
along with the desired salary.
The players will check
how much was offered...
and choose the gym
they'd like to join.
If you're not satisfied
with the salary,
you may negotiate.
All right.
You may also choose
the gym you desire...
regardless of the salary
that was offered.
Really?
Each gym may only draft six players.
- Only 6?
- Just 6.
- We can only have six players.
- Right.
Once one gym recruits
all of its members,
the remaining trainer and players...
will automatically become a team.
The remaining recruits.
- Right.
- Before salary negotiations,
players will try...
and hit uncooked eggs
that are at a distance...
- by spiking a volleyball.
- I'm doomed.
(Ball control: Hitting uncooked eggs
by spiking a volleyball)
(Speed: Ball's speed
will be measured with a speed gun.)
Ball control.
Yes, this we must see.
Or speed.
You may choose one category...
to show off your talents
to the trainers.
You will be divided
into four groups.
In Group One are Oh Ji Young,
Jeon So Min, and Ji Suk Jin.
In Group Two are Kim Yeon Koung,
Yang Se Chan, and Park Eun Jin.
In Group Three are Song Ji Hyo,
Lee So Young, and Ahn Hye Jin.
In Group Four are Haha,
Yeum Hye Seon, and Kim Hee Jin.
- Group One will go first.
- All right!
- Group One.
- Oh Ji Young, Jeon So Min,
and Ji Suk Jin,
please step forward.
- Do we go down there?
- Yes, please step down.
Okay.
I'll be watching you
even when you step down the stage.
(Their every movement
will be reflected in their salary.)
So Min, good going.
Go, So Min.
What?
(What?)
(For some reason,
her serve travels behind her.)
- Nicely done.
- Are you sure they aren't rocks?
Suk Jin will go first.
Out of speed and ball control,
which one will you choose?
- Me?
- Go ahead and choose.
I'll go with ball control.
- You chose ball control.
- I will hit...
- the one in the middle.
- Suk Jin,
which gym would you like to join?
Truth be told,
neither of them speaks to me.
So I'll go with the one
that values my talent.
The one that offers me
the most money.
- Got it.
- If that's the case,
you won't be drafted into any team.
Just so you know,
chump change won't cut it.
But chump change is all we have.
(They only intend to offer him
chump change.)
You...
- Please know that.
- That's minus five points for you.
You just lost five points.
Can you show us your jump?
Let's do the vertical jump test.
- Is it possible?
- Jump on the spot.
(Whee!)
(The miraculous jump
that burns 0 calories)
- That's not much of a jump.
- I'm sorry but,
are you taking a photo?
Here I go.
Suk Jin chose to focus
on the ball control.
The ball control?
- Please show us.
- I won't hit with this one.
- Health, long life, blessing!
- Long life, blessing!
(The first step
of the oldest rookie player)
(Will he be able to hit the egg
in 10m?)
That was amazing.
(Hurling it down)
- That's enough. Thank you.
- He got to hit the ball.
Should I even pay him?
I choose ball control.
- Ball control?
- Yes.
Which team do you want to join?
- Well...
- You can just hit the egg.
- Oh, really?
- Does anyone of you want me?
They're avoiding her eyes.
- They're avoiding her eyes.
- Excuse me. Can't you hear her?
- She's talking.
- Look at Jong Kook.
- She's talking to you.
- What did you say?
- Could you say it again?
- It was a communication error.
- I can clean, cook, and...
- We hired a service for that.
- It's fine.
Then I can just ace in this, right?
- I'll try it now.
- Wait. Ms. Jeon.
Could you show us
your jump in place?
- As expected.
- She's so cute.
- She's cute.
- She doesn't know how to jump.
I jumped really high though.
(The player
both teams want to avoid the most)
(Player Jeon's ball control test)
As expected.
(As expected,
she hurls the ball down.)
She's good.
- Can you give me one more chance?
- No, it's okay.
- I'd pick So Min no matter what.
- That's enough.
- She's a bit better than Suk Jin.
- The two of you...
But I want to give her more points
than Suk Jin.
- Oh, really?
- She's a bit better.
- She did better than you.
- Right. She's way better.
You jeered at me when I spiked,
but why are you...
- approving her spike?
- Health
(The filial song
shuts the old man's mouth instantly)
- Next is Oh Ji Young.
- Health
Which one are you going to choose?
Speed or ball control?
I'm going to choose both.
- Both?
- Yes.
- Then Ji Young...
- Can they choose both?
- Ji Young.
- Is there a team you prefer?
I want to join your team!
Jong Kook's team? Got it.
(Jong Kook's team? Got it.)
- He likes it.
- Jae Suk is sullen.
- But Ji Young...
- All right!
- Ji Young...
- You got this, Trainer Yoo!
- In any case...
- Kim Jong Kook!
All right.
- Ji Young chose both.
- He wrote something down.
(Stepping on the line)
- You're stepping on the line.
- The line.
- Ji Young, you're stepping on it.
- You're stepping on the line.
- It needs to be shown.
- Oh, does it?
You guys are really strict.
- They really are.
- Here I go!
- Okay.
- You can let that slide.
- I should hit it like this.
(She was the best digger
in the Tokyo Olympics.)
(How good is her spike?)
(She missed the target,
but it was sharp.)
- She didn't hit the target either.
- She's good.
She got 0 points,
and it was 67km per hour.
- Got it. It was 67km per hour.
- I should've hit it.
She missed it.
Now, you should offer the players
of this group their salary.
How much should we offer?
- For now...
- You should consider their skills.
(Exclaiming)
(The master of slapstick)
He just showed slapstick.
- He got hit in the face.
- Are you okay?
- That was...
- Long life
(They start singing the filial song
as Suk Jin is healthy enough...)
(to show slapstick.)
Why does it bounce so much?
(Darn it.)
(Player Ji is at the risk
of being forced to retire.)
- This is dumbfounding.
- Stay healthy, Suk Jin.
He's showing his character well.
- Darn it.
- I hope you live long.
Wait a minute.
Since I have 1,300 dollars...
Do we have to use up all the money?
There will be a competition
between you two,
so it'd be better if you leave
as much money as you can.
- Right?
- Yes.
- So the less you spend...
- So we should spend little...
- to scout the players.
- That's right.
That'd be advantageous for you.
Then how much
should I offer Ji Young? Hold on.
I need to plan it well.
What if they offer me ten cents?
They'll offer you a lot.
(Even the libero
on the national team is nervous.)
- Did you write it down?
- I'm ready.
- Hold on.
- Lift the board at the same time.
Since it's our first round,
we need to study how it goes.
He told me to write it big.
Please reveal their salary.
In 1, 2, 3.
Here you go.
- Fifty dollars?
- Two cents?
One cent?
- What? One cent?
- He offered one and two cents.
- He offered me fifty dollars.
- One cent? Come on.
He's offering me a lot, isn't he?
(Trainer Yoo: Ji Young 50 dollars,
Suk Jin 1 cent, So Min 2 cents)
- What on earth?
- What? You're offering 0.1 cents?
(Trainer Kook:
Ji Young 100 dollars,)
(Suk Jin 0.1 cents,
So Min 0.1 cents)
How can you offer 0.1 cents
as a salary?
- I couldn't help it.
- We can only offer this much.
- This is driving me crazy.
- You need to be understanding.
- It's too little.
- There's not much money I can use.
- But...
- What do you do in this situation?
- You must thank them at all costs.
- This hurts my pride.
- Can you add a zero to mine?
- Sorry?
- Make it 20 cents.
- Twenty cents?
- Twenty cents.
- Hey.
She's negotiating.
Why would you beg them?
Just get what they're offering?
I'm going to negotiate.
Make it 20 cents.
- He's adding a zero.
- For me...
I'm in a good mood
after a long time.
- I'll offer her two dollars.
- All right! I'll join your team.
- Really? You're offering so much?
- Yes. I'm offering her two dollars.
- Can I make my decision now?
- Excuse me.
- Why are you offering her so much?
- Isn't one cent too little?
Salute!
You're selling your soul
just over two dollars?
Of course!
- Whatever. I don't care now.
- He's paying me two dollars.
How much are you offering?
- I'll offer you ten cents.
- Ten cents?
Yes.
Add another 0, will you?
You're offering So Min 2 dollars.
Then I'm worth only 1-20th
of what she's worth?
- Why are you yelling at me?
- Why are you yelling?
Of course I'm upset.
Look at this yourself!
Why are you being so rude?
- Why would you talk like that?
- We're team owners.
The next group is waiting.
Seal the deal already.
- What's wrong with you?
- He blocked it.
- Hurry up and be done with it!
- Wait a minute.
- Mister.
- I'm trying to negotiate here.
Both teams will hold off
the recruitment of Suk Jin.
- Hold off?
- Please remove him as a candidate.
Ji Young,
you chose Trainer Kook, right?
Of course she should join
that team. He offered 100 dollars.
- He's offering 50 more dollars.
- I'm joining his team for sure,
but you're not going to offer me
a higher salary, are you?
- She must be considering his team.
- She's trying to negotiate.
- Wait a minute.
- She wants to negotiate with him.
- Ji Young...
- I'll be negotiating later?
Why don't you raise it a little?
I'm much more athletic
than the rest of them.
Since we'll be playing many games...
Watch how they
spike the balls later.
I bet I was the best one
out of them.
You should offer her more.
Gosh, you're only raising that much?
Of course.
You're offering her
just ten more dollars.
- Ji Young is being offered...
- All right now.
- I'll offer her ten more dollars.
- What use is that?
- Ten more dollars?
- Yes.
Why don't you all sit down?
- I'll offer you 110 dollars.
- Then I'll offer you 10 more.
- My gosh.
- They're offering 110 dollars?
- You're raising it to 110 dollars?
- Of course.
You should've increased more.
- I should offer the same at least.
- He's so stingy.
- I'll join this team.
- All right.
(She chooses Tiger Gym.)
- All right! This is great.
- Yes!
That was amazing.
Group Two, please step forward.
Let's go, Group Two.
Yeon Koung, Eun Jin, and Se Chan.
This group is...
- I don't think I'll hit it.
- We're in trouble.
(They set off
with resolute determination.)
They're so cool.
(They check the ball first
as they're pro players.)
- They're so cool.
- It won't hit the target.
It's quite far too.
- They're practicing a lot.
- This isn't an official ball.
You weren't considerate
of us with the balls.
This is a ball for foot volleyball.
She's...
She's quite aggressive.
Let me just say this to you guys.
You need to take me so that
it'll be advantageous during games.
- Right. Good thinking.
- Yes.
I hope you'll offer me a lot.
- Okay.
- Offer me at least ten dollars.
If you offer me below that,
I won't join your team.
- He's...
- Both of you.
You must've intimidated him
so much...
that he's asking
for ten dollars only.
- How can he...
- Offer me at least ten dollars.
- Don't go below ten dollars.
- My goodness.
You need me
so that you get a chance to win.
- All right.
- Wasn't he in "Shaolin Soccer"?
- Good luck.
- I think I've seen him in it too.
- You got this.
- Let's do it.
(High-five)
I've never raised my arm so high
for a high-five.
- You got this!
- Here we go.
(After the high-five,
he gets ready for the test.)
- Go.
- Don't go over the line.
(He hit it!)
Speed?
(Se Chan's ball
was faster than expected.)
- He's good.
It was 52km per hour.
- It was really fast.
- That was incredible.
I hit as hard as I could,
but it was only 52km per hour.
(Even the pro players are surprised
by Ssaebssaeb's speed.)
You're generous with compliments.
- How did you...
- I hit as hard as I could, but...
She's asking for a high-five.
You're really good.
(Jumping)
That was so cute.
He jumped for the high-five.
It feels like I'm hanging out
with women older than me.
Eun Jin, which one will you choose?
Ball control or speed?
- Speed.
- Speed?
- Yes.
- Everyone will go for speed.
- You chose speed?
- Yes.
(The youngest middle blocker,
Eun Jin's spike)
Let's go.
(It was light,
but the ball hit the target hard.)
- That was fast.
- It was really fast.
It was 64km per hour.
That was really fast.
All right, we got it.
- Yeon Koung, which one...
- Ball control or speed?
- Tell them you'll go for speed.
- I'll go for both.
- Both?
I'll give it a try.
Which team do you want to join?
- I'll see first.
- Okay.
- She's so cool.
- She's good at negotiating.
She's very relaxed.
She needs to take the upper hand.
- You're offering her a lot.
- Yes, I am.
- You must offer her a lot.
- Of course.
- Can I hit it now?
- Yes.
The decision will be important
for our team.
She's awesome.
Yeon Koung ripped up the court!
She scores.
Yeon Koung scores again!
Kim Yeon Koung!
- She roars!
- Let's go.
I should hit it though.
(She'll show her spike
in front of the two trainers.)
- Can I hit it now?
- Yes.
(She'll show her spike
in front of the two trainers.)
That was close!
(Powerful spike)
- I should've hit it.
- It wasn't close.
- Not close at all.
It was 60km per hour.
- Wait a minute. Yeon Koung...
- That was pretty fast.
Trainer Yoo!
This ball isn't good enough.
You should get better balls.
The three of you
are done with the test.
Please decide their salary now.
I don't think they'll get
more than what I got.
- What do I do?
- I dare say...
that we're the aces.
You did really well though.
You were really good.
- You'll need to pay us a lot.
- You were really good.
He's the ace. I mean it.
You did really well.
We can always negotiate later, so...
You can just offer a lot
from the beginning.
It's better for us to accept a deal
than to negotiate.
So that we'll all be happy.
Please reveal their salary.
- Reveal the salary for Group Two.
- Hold on.
- Goodness.
- Wait a minute.
- It's really difficult.
- It's difficult.
- Goodness.
- Wait a minute.
You need to spend a lot
for this group.
- You can trust us.
- Is that so?
It's hard for us too.
Here we go. In 1, 2, 3.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Here.
- She's offered 150 dollars?
- How much did you offer?
(Trainer Yoo: Yeon Koung 120 dollars,
Se Chan 15, Eun Jin 110)
(Trainer Kook: Yeon Koung 150,
Se Chan 10, Eun Jin 110)
This won't do. Yeon Koung!
- You offered her 150 dollars?
- What's with you?
- Yours is so much higher than mine.
- Come on.
Se Chan is offered 15 dollars?
- That's too low.
- They offered me 110 dollars?
He did better than the two of them.
- He did really well, right?
- He did.
- You can negotiate with us.
- Okay.
Did you offer only that much,
so you can negotiate with us?
(Striding toward the trainers)
She's too...
- She's too aggressive.
- She's so scary.
- Trainer Yoo.
- First of all...
Are you testing us?
- What do you mean?
- I don't like people testing me.
That's not what I'm doing.
- Are you sure?
- You're testing her.
I don't like it when the salary
ends with two.
- It should be fivefold.
- What was that?
- It should be fivefold, right?
- He was trying to test me...
and wrote 2. He was thinking
of raising it to 5.
- Exactly. He wanted to negotiate.
- He wanted to negotiate.
That's what negotiating
is all about.
Are you willing to raise my salary?
I can pay as much
as Trainer Kook is offering.
- I can also...
- That was too low.
I'm willing to pay more
for Yeon Koung.
- You should negotiate too.
- They're offering the same amount.
- You can ask us comfortably.
- Could you raise it by ten dollars?
Is that so? Let me see.
- They're both fixing the amount.
- Since she asked...
How much did you add?
- They're both fixing the amount.
- Listen.
Can't you ask them
to give some of yours to me?
What? Why would I do that? No.
He asked me to offer my salary
to him.
- He's so cunning. No way.
- What are you, a beggar?
- If you're willing to raise it,
- How much do I have?
- then raise it now.
- Wait a minute.
I'm sorry, but can't you see me?
Can't you see me?
- We'll talk later.
- Wait there.
- Just stay still.
- Since you're an amazing player...
Of course, I'm willing to raise it.
If you're willing,
then just offer the final price
without negotiating.
- She's a bit...
- Offer me the highest salary.
I know that she's good,
but she's making me uncomfortable.
- Wait a minute.
- I'm having a bad feeling.
- I think...
- Right?
- It's a bit...
- Seeing her behave...
- Don't regret it later.
- Wait a minute.
- They both find her difficult.
- We should...
They find Yeon Koung difficult.
Wait a minute.
I'm offering the highest salary
that I can offer.
- Wait.
- Okay.
(They fix the offering salary
after accepting to negotiate.)
- You offered 130 dollars?
- How much is it?
- He offered ten more dollars.
- What?
(It'd be weird
if you lower the offering salary.)
It'd be weird
if you lower the offering salary.
- What?
- He lowered the offering salary?
I got scared of her.
- She's too scary.
- It's weird that you lowered it.
Look at her.
(Trainer Kook lowered her salary
by 20 dollars because she's scary.)
- You lowered her salary?
- Look at her.
- This won't do.
- Wait.
(The deal is about to go off.)
- Thank you.
- Wait.
- Yes, Eun Jin.
I will...
give 30 dollars from my salary
to Se Chan...
and take him with me.
- We're all joining his team?
- Great.
- You want to take him?
- Yes.
I'll give up my salary for you.
She's indeed amazing.
She's the goddess!
I'll give you my 30 dollars.
- Great. She's giving it to me.
- I'll give you my 30 dollars.
I'll be with her.
- Then...
- Thank you.
- Let's go!
- Yes! We're joining your team.
- This is great.
- All right.
- Fine.
- Fine!
- How dare you lower my salary?
(How dare you lower my salary?)
You dared to lower my salary?
- You lowered my salary. No way.
- Locust Gym has four players now.
- So Min, Yeon Koung,
- She's so scary.
- Se Chan,
- She's scary.
- and Eun Jin.
- This is great.
Let's check out Group Three now.
Ji Hyo, So Young, and Hye Jin.
- Good luck!
- Excuse me, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is pretty strong.
Could you show us
your jump in place?
- What was that?
- She's funny.
Ji Hyo.
(She shows how unathletic she is
with weak jumps.)
What was that?
- What was that?
- She's funny.
- We should...
- make her do slapstick.
- She is...
She's funny these days.
She is indeed.
Which team do you want to join?
I...
I want to join a team
that appreciates my capabilities.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
She's after love? Got it.
(She's after love? Got it.)
You're saying
you're after love, right?
What are some of your capabilities?
You know.
- "You know."
- A couple...
- volleyball team!
- Volleyball team.
- Is it okay to date in secret?
- That little...
Here we go.
(Player Song will appeal herself
with speed.)
- She'll slap it down.
- Ji Hyo chose speed.
- Let's go!
- Off you go.
That's enough.
(That's enough!)
- We've seen enough.
- Next, please.
- That was hilarious.
- It's okay. It was funny.
- That's enough.
She couldn't catch up with the ball.
Her slapstick
is hilarious these days.
- You blew your chance.
- I'll give it a go.
- It's over for you.
- Please give me another chance.
- It's okay.
- It needs to be fair.
- Every player gets only one chance.
- It's over for you.
- I'm sorry, but it's over.
- Ji Hyo.
- That was hilarious.
You didn't hit the ball,
so you can give it another go.
It's okay.
You can give it another go.
(Exclaiming)
Love...
- Power!
Thank you!
- Kim Jong Kook!
- It's because...
- She should hit it too.
- Kim Jong Kook!
- She didn't get to hit it.
For this draft,
I'm going to withdraw
my draft rights to Ji Hyo.
Why would you withdraw it?
- We should see how good she is.
- She can go ahead.
Let's see.
All right.
(A super-fast ground ball)
- All right.
- That was...
It was 28km per hour.
- Listen.
- What is it?
Trainer Kook is head over heels
for Ji Hyo.
I know.
Look at the way he's smiling.
- He can't stop smiling.
- Trainer Kook.
- When the ball hit the ground,
- That's not it.
- you were smiling so much.
- She tried her best.
- You find her adorable.
- You're head over heels for her.
- He can't help but smile.
- That's not it.
She's giving him finger hearts.
Who wants to go first?
- Hye Jin is going first?
- Shin Min A!
- What?
Will you choose ball control
You're choosing both?
- Yes, I'll choose both.
- All right.
(Amidst the players' cheer, she goes
for both ball control and speed.)
She has chosen both.
(She's famous for her dirty serves
which bounce off sharply.)
Ahn Hye Jin is serving.
(The dirty and strong serve
that flusters the opponents)
(Shin Min A on the volleyball court
will show her dirty serve.)
That was so fast.
(Hye Jin's serve
sharply hits the target)
- Well done.
- She did really well.
(The trainers are amazed
by the dirty serve.)
It was really sharp.
- It was 66km per hour.
- Good job.
- She's really good.
- It was 66km per hour?
- That was incredible.
- She's amazing.
She's known for her serves?
Which one will you choose, So Young?
- I'll go for both.
- Will you go for both?
- Go ahead.
- She needs to come closer.
Here we go.
(The ball flew off the target.)
- She slightly missed the ball.
- It was great. Good one.
She gets only one chance regardless.
It was 60km per hour.
(So Young records 60km per hour.)
But it wasn't accurate.
It was powerful though.
Since she hit the target...
(How much will Ji Hyo, Hye Jin,
and So Young be offered?)
- Their salary...
- They're taking quite long.
I hope we'll meet with good results.
All right now.
We'll reveal the salary.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- I don't think he'd offer a lot.
- He offered 110 dollars.
(The players burst into laughter
after seeing the amount.)
(Song Ji Hyo will join
her boyfriend's team.)
She's going to join her boyfriend?
Ji Hyo will be joining
her boyfriend's team.
- What is this?
- What?
Don't corner us like that.
You need to offer her a salary.
I'm offering Ji Hyo the highest
among the players...
- in the minor league.
- How much are you offering?
But...
But So Min was offered
only two dollars.
- I was offered only two dollars.
- I know.
I offered So Min 0.1 cents.
But we don't have many positions...
to recruit more players.
You must have
some money left though.
We know that your team
has more money than his.
Can't you increase it a little more?
- I showed a good performance.
- He has a lot of money.
That's true, but...
But this team is saving up too much.
- You're saving up more than him.
- He's not spending a lot.
You have more money than him.
Why aren't you spending more?
That's not true, Min A.
He has about 1,200 dollars,
and I have only 990 dollars.
That's not true, Min A.
You're saving up too much.
- You're not spending a lot either.
- He should use it if he has money.
You should spend more.
There are two more spots.
- I...
- No, listen.
- Here.
- Okay. Then we will...
All right. That's great.
I'd like to set a standard
among players...
when deciding your salary.
This is the salary I'm offering.
I'm willing to offer you more,
but I don't know what will happen
with the other players.
But I offered them 110 dollars.
Which team will you choose,
Hye Jin, So Young, and Ji Hyo?
I'll join Trainer Kook.
- Yes. That's the way it should go.
- Fine. Go ahead.
- The amount...
- Go ahead.
- What about So Young and Hye Jin?
- They'll choose Jong Kook for sure.
- I'll join Jong Kook too.
- Okay.
- Come join my team.
- I'll join Jae Suk.
- For real?
- You're joining my team?
(I'm joining Jae Suk's team.)
(Hye Jin chose Trainer Yoo when he
offered less than Trainer Kook?)
- How much did you offer?
- This is...
You're joining his team
for 110 dollars?
- But I increased your salary.
- It's lower than what he offered.
It's okay with me. If I show...
- Fine.
- a good performance later,
- you can raise my salary.
- Of course.
- Fine.
- Sit down.
Fine.
- Okay.
- How could you...
I'm on your team!
Hello!
Look at them.
We've been close friends
since we were young.
I can join any team
if you offer me 30 dollars.
- How much?
- That's too high.
How much?
It's because we're a package deal.
- You must stick with each other?
- Yes.
- With whom?
- The three of us.
Wait. The three of you?
The only team you can join...
- is Tiger Gym.
- You need to ditch one.
- I know.
- Only two can go together.
(They need to split up
to negotiate their salary.)
Really? In that case...
(They desert Haha.)
They decided to go separate ways.
- That's good.
- That's the way to go.
(Hee Jin shows a spike.)
(She hit it!)
(Even at a glance,
it's the fastest!)
My goodness.
(Even at a glance,
it's the fastest!)
It was 70km per hour.
(Kim Hee Jin, 70km per hour)
It was so fast.
I could barely see the ball.
They should select her
no matter what.
(The trainers' hands move busily.)
- Hold on.
- You need to use money.
You need to use a lot of money.
Hye Seon, what will you choose
between speed and ball control?
Both.
- Both?
- Yes.
Which team do you want to join?
I will have to consider the salary.
I am sure both of them know about...
the synergy I will create
in the team.
- Is that so?
- I will see the offers first.
Okay.
The only thing you have shown is
your nickname, Yeum Cheater.
- Let's go, Yeum Cheater.
- That's the talent you need...
on this show.
She doesn't disappoint.
- She is bragging about herself.
- She learned well.
(Hye Seon knows the importance
of being a cheater on the show.)
That was fast.
(That was fast!)
- That was fast.
- Didn't she hit with her fist?
- She hit with her fist.
- Is that allowed?
(She hit with her fast.)
- She is a trickster.
- Really?
One, two, three.
I see 0.1 cents.
Did he write 140 dollars?
I will join this team.
Hye Seon.
We got Hye Seon.
- We got Hye Seon.
- I will do my best in the team.
- That's good.
- Hye Seon didn't disappoint.
Hye Seon, congratulations on
joining the team.
Welcome. Okay.
- All right.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Congratulations.
Are you joining my team?
As for Suk Jin...
His salary will be ten cents.
Ten cents.
(Thanks to Woo Young's draw,
Suk Jin's salary became ten cents.)
(Suk Jin's salary is ten cents.)
Which team is Suk Jin joining?
- Your team.
- What?
He automatically joined...
Tiger Gym.
Isn't that a penalty?
(Suk Jin automatically joined
Tiger Gym.)
It's okay. We don't know
which game we will be playing.
Okay.
- Locust Gym will go first.
- Locust Gym.
- Shouldn't you look like a locust?
- Come this way.
Let's say, "Let's go."
One, two, three.
- Let's go.
Gosh.
That's too normal.
- Let's do this.
- That's too cliched.
- The coach should be in the center.
- That's right.
- Really?
- Come to the center.
Okay.
Put your hands on me.
You love things like this.
He loves being
the center of attention.
- He wants to take the spotlight.
- What an old fart.
The team owner
is stealing the spotlight.
Seriously.
- That's just wrong.
- That's great.
Locust!
What an old fart.
The team owner stole the spotlight.
Since we are Tiger Gym,
we should pose like tigers.
Tigers.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Pose.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Suk Jin.
- Hold on.
You called our pose childish,
but you couldn't come up
with anything other than a roar.
One, two, three.
This is embarrassing.
That's great. We have the spirit.
They got 3 photos,
but we only got 1 photo.
- It's okay.
- We posed more neatly.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
(It's time for a real competition.)
I will look forward
to a passionate race.
- Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
(The first match)
- It must be foot volleyball.
- Foot volleyball.
- The net is too low, right?
- It must be foot volleyball.
- Are we playing foot volleyball?
- It seems that way.
- The players have entered.
- All right.
Foot volleyball isn't half bad.
- Okay. Let's go.
- I thought she was Kwang Soo.
- Seriously.
Let's go.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk, let's go.
- We got this.
- All right.
We will win.
Come on out.
We don't have time to sit down.
- We don't have time to sit down.
- Let's go, Locust Gym.
We got this.
Is it foot volleyball?
We are set.
- It's foot volleyball. We are set.
- Jae Suk.
- Yeon Koung high fives too much.
- Seriously.
- It's foot volleyball. We will win.
- She hits too hard.
- She high fives too much.
- Hey.
- She hits too hard.
- She is too strong.
She pushes down from the above.
My hands keep getting twisted.
All right, everyone. Today,
you will have
the Fierce Transfer Race.
After each round,
the trainers will receive money...
in accordance with the result.
Use that money to negotiate salary
with the players in your team...
and make payment.
The remaining money
will go to the trainers.
So today,
the trainer who has more money...
will win and receive the prize.
The trainer who has less money
will receive the penalty.
Three players
with the most amount of money...
will receive the special prize...
and two players
with the least amount of money...
will receive the penalty.
They will pick
two additional people.
- That won't do.
- Do they get to pick?
- Don't pick your teammates.
If you don't give me money,
I will pick you.
They shouldn't get to pick.
Today, there will be
a special system.
Each gym will have
1st-string and 2nd-string players.
The first-string teams
will go against each other...
and the second-string teams
will go against each other.
- Trainers can join any team.
- Okay.
It's more advantageous
to have the first-string team win...
for the overall result.
(Additional points come
with the first-string match.)
And only the first-string players
will have a salary negotiation.
Really?
The second-string players
will get the minimum salary.
- Minimum salary?
- Minimum?
So Min, you are
totally a first-string player.
- A first-string player.
- Worry about your own team.
- What are you saying?
We won't lose.
All right.
(The rules of the day
got delivered!)
Yeum Cheater thinks
we should do a cheer.
- Let's go.
We did that many times already.
Let's do it one more time.
What are you doing?
- Yes!
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Tiger!
- Roar!
- Go!
- Gosh.
- That was great.
That was great.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
They high five too many times.
I mean...
They high five...
- if you stretch out your hands.
- They do this endlessly.
It's a habit.
That wasn't what I had in mind.
Jae Suk.
Yeum Cheater
wants us to do another cheer.
- Didn't we do that already?
- Let's do another cheer.
This is the last one.
- We did that already.
- Let's do another cheer.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Let's do this.
- Gosh.
I am so happy.
I feel like I became
a professional volleyball player.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
(So Min is happy to join
the national team members.)
- Let's do it again.
- Tiger! Roar!
One, two, three.
- Tiger!
- Roar!
Didn't someone say "Water deer"?
- Water deer!
- Didn't someone say "Water deer"?
- I heard "Water deer".
- You are ridiculous.
It's "Tiger".
- Water deer! Ah!
- Ah!
Trainers, divide the players...
into 1st-string and 2nd-string...
and appoint the captain.
The captain will receive
ten more dollars.
- Ten more dollars?
- Really?
All right.
- The captain.
- It should be Ji Young.
- No way.
- That sounds good.
- She was the one on my mind.
- That's right.
- The position comes with a perk.
- Really?
- You get ten more dollars.
- All right then.
- You told me before...
- You are a first-string player.
that you aren't confident
with foot volleyball.
- Hang on a second.
- Okay.
- How about you?
- I am pretty good.
To be honest, I have no confidence.
You have no confidence?
You need someone in the back...
- who will receive the ball.
- You should do that.
- Isn't it for the 2nd-string team?
- It's for the 2nd-string team.
Come on.
- Trainer Yoo, come on.
- All right.
- Firstly,
- I am on the first-string team.
So Min should be...
I know that you are good.
- Put it on.
- So Min, take a break.
- Put it on for now.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- I don't know.
- As for the captain,
A player with a low salary
should be the captain.
(So Min's salary is 2 dollars.)
- Isn't it a good idea?
- It is.
- You are the captain.
- Thank you.
Captain.
- Captain.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Jae Suk, you let me earn money.
- Our captain.
- Let's go.
Captain Jeon.
(Both teams get ready
with the 7th cheer.)
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
(Tiger Gym: Trainer, Jong Kook)
(1st-string, Haha,
Ji Young, and So Young)
Captain Jeon.
(2nd-string, Hee Jin,
Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo)
We can do this. Let's go.
All right.
We let the ball bounce
on the floor once, right?
Everyone.
- There is an additional rule.
- What is it?
(An additional rule?)
In Round 1, the 1st-string team
and the trainer will have...
a 4-on-4 match.
The opposite team
will choose a libero.
That player can use hands.
(Can the opposite team choose
a libero?)
Ji Young is a libero
who represents Korea.
- She saved it.
- My goodness.
She can take strong attacks.
The libero can use the hands,
but he or she can't attack.
I want to attack.
She is determined to attack today.
We get to choose, right?
- The opposite team chooses.
- That's right.
- Whom should we choose?
- Let me attack.
Jong Kook can't use his feet.
- We should frustrate them.
- That's right.
It won't do
to make Jong Kook use his hands.
He can't use his feet anyway.
- Haha would be a better choice.
- Let's make him use his hands.
Haha can use his feet,
but Jong Kook can't.
- Feet.
- We will make Haha use his hands.
- Haha.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook can't use his feet.
- Okay. You are provoking us.
- Okay. We are provoking you.
We will choose Yeon Koung.
- Yeon Koung.
- Will you make me the libero?
- Hold on.
- Isn't that bad for them?
- Yeon Koung?
- I will get to use my hands.
- That's good for us.
- Will you let her receive the ball?
- Yeon Koung?
- Okay.
(Was it a mistake?)
- Shall we choose Se Chan?
- We will choose Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- You can't change it.
- No.
Gosh, they are ready
for a bench-clearing brawl.
- Right away,
- You can't change it.
- they came forward.
- Did you see that?
- You can't change it.
- What are you doing?
- Let's go.
Are we doing another cheer?
One, two, three. Yes!
They do so many cheers.
Everyone.
As you did
during the last week's game,
you will have an option.
- An option.
- Why are there so many things?
It's the last one. The option...
- for Round One is...
- It's complicated.
not using the formal tone.
- Right now...
- Use a casual tone.
- Are we on a first-name basis?
- That's right.
Jae Suk.
- Yeon Koung.
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- We are set.
We can't use a formal tone.
I love it!
(The youngest member
who was born in 1999)
- We are friends.
- No formal tone.
- Really?
- Use a casual tone.
Let's do well.
Ji Hyo, do well.
You had better do this right.
Jae Suk, you are the one
who needs to get a grip.
Jae Suk, get a grip.
Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- My goodness.
- Jae Suk!
- Se Chan,
- let's go.
- My goodness.
They are excited.
Yeon Koung, be quiet!
Kim Yeon Koung!
- Be quiet!
- What is up with her?
They are no joke.
(Yeon Koung gets intimidated
for the first time.)
- You lose a point if you mess up.
- All right.
Yeon Koung, serve.
What?
Yeon Koung.
(Her face hardens at times.)
She is glaring at me.
- Say something.
- She is glaring at me.
Tell her to be quiet.
Say, "Long Legs, be quiet."
- Long Legs!
- Say, "Long Legs, be quiet."
Long Legs, be quiet.
- Okay.
- Let's go, our team!
- Let's go.
- All right.
- Roar!
(We refuse to lose.)
Let's begin.
Here.
- Receive it.
- Okay.
- Send it up. Come on.
- That's good.
- Send it over.
(So Young makes a good toss.)
- Head the ball.
- The head.
- What?
- It's 1 to 0.
- Why?
Didn't it touch her head?
It didn't touch her head, did it?
- It touched my head!
- She says it touched her head.
- It didn't touch her head.
- It touched my head!
(I can't believe her.)
- She says it touched her head.
- No, it didn't.
- It did.
- She says it did.
- No, it didn't.
- Hey.
- She says it did.
- No, it didn't.
- Don't lie.
- It touched my head.
- What are you saying?
- No, it didn't.
- It didn't.
- It did.
- Hey.
It didn't.
- It touched my head.
- No, it didn't.
I even heard a sound.
It really touched my head.
- It didn't touch.
- It's better for us if it did.
- We win if it did.
- What is your problem?
It touched.
- It didn't touch.
- We win if it didn't touch.
- Do we need to say it didn't touch?
- I told you.
- We win if it didn't touch.
It touched. Review the video.
Shouldn't you review the video?
- That's good. Head the ball.
- Send it over.
(It didn't touch her head at all.)
- She says it touched her head.
- It really did.
It touched.
Move up after you serve.
- Okay.
- We hit it after a bounce, right?
Yes. Okay.
- Hey.
- Okay.
Hye Seon.
- Hye Seon.
Let's do a cheer.
- Why are we doing a cheer?
- Seriously.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Hey.
Yeum Cheater.
Why do you want to do a cheer
after messing up?
- Good job.
- Yes.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Yes.
A single point makes you
high five endlessly in volleyball.
- Let's cheer up.
- Let's go.
Here I go.
We will receive it.
- Mine.
- Okay.
- All right.
- I got it.
Yeum Cheater.
People in the back, get ready.
That's good.
(He drove the ball to the ground.)
- Jae Suk.
- What was that?
- Jae Suk, what was that?
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you. We won a point.
- Okay.
Okay.
- All right.
- Jae Suk.
- I am sorry.
- Do you want to switch?
- All right.
- No.
- All right, Hye Jin.
- We run whenever we score.
- This is driving me crazy.
We will save up a lot of energy...
- if we don't do that.
- Save up the energy.
Whenever I do something,
five people gang up on me.
I am sweating after running
two rounds.
Jae Suk, let's do well.
Here I go.
Yeon Koung, take this.
- Mine.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Mine.
Yeum Cheater.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk.
- I will send it over.
- There you go.
- Receive it.
- Head.
- Okay.
- Receive it.
Head.
That was great.
- Okay.
- Head.
- That was great.
- Good job.
- Yeum Cheater.
- Head it, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk sent it over the net!)
Take it. Here.
They are doing well.
They are too good.
Here.
- Here it comes.
- They are too good.
- Gosh.
- They are good.
- Good.
- How are they so good?
- Send it over.
- They are good.
Yeum Cheater. There you go.
Okay. Is it me again?
It's okay. You are doing well.
- Oh, no.
- It's okay.
(The ball goes into the net.)
- Oh, no.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- Good job.
- There we go.
(Locust Gym succeeded
to score a point.)
(Gathering around)
- What?
- Let's do a cheer.
Let's do a cheer.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Jae Suk.
- Hold on.
You know, ceremonies are
more exhausting.
Can the libero serve with hands?
- She can serve with hands, right?
- Yes, she can.
Okay.
Kim Yeon Koung.
Kim Yeon Koung scored 30 points
in a match against Japan.
She scored with a serve.
That's good.
(She is known for a strong serve
that resembles a spike.)
Use a casual tone.
- Let's go.
- Yeon Koung, send it to Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, let's go.
- Okay.
Long Legs, serve all you want.
- Jong Kook, let's go.
- Okay.
Long Legs, serve all you want.
- Jong Kook, let's go.
- Okay.
(Gosh.)
(He talked big.)
(But he failed to defend.)
(He made the ball fly off
with a cry.)
It's okay.
Don't be disheartened.
(Queen Yeon Koung scored
with a serve.)
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
Jong Kook!
- It's okay.
- Jong Kook is bad at this.
Jong Kook,
you should stop exercising.
He is like a tiger without teeth.
That was cute.
- Jong Kook,
- Hey.
- you need to do better.
- Okay.
It's okay.
- Just score.
- There we go.
Use a casual tone.
Come on.
- Head it.
- Okay.
- Send it over.
- Let it bounce.
So Young.
(The national team shows
a game of high quality.)
- Okay.
- Head it.
- That's good.
- Good.
- Hey.
- Send it over the net.
- There you go.
- It will go out.
No.
- Okay. I got it.
- It's okay.
- Spike.
- Okay.
(Trainer Yoo's sudden spike)
- There you go.
That's it.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
Sir, it's out
if your body part goes over the net.
- No.
- It's okay on Running Man.
(Jong Kook said "Sir".)
- All right.
- The ball went over.
Jong Kook used a formal tone,
so Tiger Gym will lose a point.
- Okay.
- It was directed at you.
The last time, you said
we can use it with you.
- You don't need to come.
- Okay.
You said we can use it with you.
Hey.
Jong Kook might not be able
to negotiate the players' salaries.
Long Legs, show me what you got.
- The team is losing because of him.
- Long Legs.
- Shouldn't they get a new trainer?
- Hey.
- You need a good team.
- Good job.
Make sure you use a casual tone.
- Use a casual tone.
- Long Legs, bring it on.
- Let's go.
- We just need to win the game.
- Suk Jin, move out of the way.
- Stop being flippant and sit down.
- What?
- Stop being flippant.
The 2nd-string players have no say.
Let's go, dear 1st-string team.
(Oops)
- You lose a point.
- Se Chan.
Don't use a formal tone.
- Okay.
(Tiger Gym becomes happy again.)
We scored a point.
Se Chan.
I will tone it down. I am sorry.
- Tone it down.
- I am sorry. I won't do it.
- Okay.
- Here I go, punks.
- Get a grip.
- Don't call us punks.
Send it up.
- So Young is good.
- They are good.
- All right.
- In.
It was out.
(After Ji Young's attack,
Yeon Koung received the ball.)
- No.
- You didn't have to receive it.
- Okay.
- Kick it.
- Gosh.
(Gosh.)
What was that?
- Okay.
- Kick it.
(Collapsing)
- What was that?
- Hey!
- You should have kicked it.
- Don't send the ball like that.
Good job.
We did it.
- We did it.
- Let's tease them.
Good job.
- "Gosh."
- Good job.
- You should have kicked it.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
You should have kept your body down.
- Good job.
- You sent it backward.
- You should have kept it down.
- You didn't need to do that.
- It's okay.
- Good job.
- Tiger! Roar!
- It's okay.
- Tiger!
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
(Locust Gym does a cheer.)
Jong Kook can't use his feet.
- Good.
- Jong Kook can't use his feet.
- Jong Kook.
- It's so funny to see...
that Jong Kook can't use his feet.
- We are doing well.
- It's okay.
- It's still 3 to 1.
- Bring it on. I got the hang of it.
I got the hang of it.
Hey.
- That's good.
- Good job.
That's good. You are doing well.
Mine.
There you go.
- Out.
- It was in.
- It really was in.
- It was out.
- Out.
- It was in.
- It hit the line.
- Out.
- It was out.
- Bo Pil!
- No.
- It was in.
- It hit the line.
Let's review the video.
- Bo Pil!
- It was out.
- Yeum Cheater.
- I mean...
- It was out.
(Even the audio director
gave up for a short while.)
(They are saying things like
"It was in" and "It was out.")
No.
It hit the line, sir.
She used a formal tone.
- Hey! It was out!
- A formal tone.
She used a formal tone.
- It was out.
- It went out.
- I'm telling you.
- Hang on.
- All right.
According to the assistant judge...
It was out,
and she used the honorifics.
(It was out,
and she used the honorifics.)
(Locust Gym lost 2 points
in an instant.)
No.
It touched the line.
How is it out?
The ball was right here.
- It was out.
- It touched right here.
No. It was deflected.
Right here.
- It was out.
- It was deflected here.
Great. It's out.
(It's obviously out.)
- Hey, Long Legs.
- It was out.
Let's move on.
Long Legs committed a foul.
Long Legs, just move on.
- Let's move on.
- I can't believe this.
I'm sure it was deflected.
- They don't know the rules.
- It was obviously in.
- Stay focused.
- You're being unbelievable.
It's out.
- You think it's in?
- Let's continue.
Gosh, this is really upsetting.
Kill them.
Don't use the honorifics.
Yeon Koung, you can use your hands.
It's okay.
That was good.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Send it over.
- Good.
That's good.
- Well done.
- It's good.
- They're good.
- So good.
- That was good.
- They are really good.
(So Young is the master
of foot volleyball.)
- How could they be so good?
- Your head.
(The original libero Ji Young
has a chance to make an attack.)
Mine.
(Heading spike)
Gosh, Hye Seon.
(They follow the ball,
but it's too late.)
(The original libero finally
won a score.)
Well done!
Yes!
- She's really good.
- She's amazing.
- I mean...
- They are really good.
Yeon Koung, they are so good.
What's with them?
(Hilarious)
My goodness.
Hey.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- Let's do this.
- We can do it.
- This is fun.
- Here you go, Yeon Koung.
- Mine
- It's Yeon Koung.
Good.
- Jae Suk.
- Good.
- Head, Jae Suk.
- Gosh.
- Hey. You fool.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk.
- Should we switch players?
Jae Suk, you should send it over.
(The serial laugher twins
make fun of them.)
Put this on.
Jae Suk, put this on.
- Hey.
- You don't belong here.
- Yeon Koung...
- Put this on.
- You can't do this. Put this on.
- Hey.
Hye Jin, give me
one more chance. Okay?
- This is your last chance.
- Just one more chance.
Gosh, Yeon Koung is...
- Yeon Koung was like...
- I'll give you one last chance.
Right.
(She wanted
to switch players right away.)
Don't you think you should switch?
I know.
I'll just wait a little more.
He wants to have one more chance.
This is your last chance.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Why aren't you talking?
- What?
- Hey, just go on.
- Hurry and go on.
- Won't you continue?
- Hurry.
What?
- Hey. Shin Min A.
- What?
- Are you Shin Min A?
She says she's Shin Min A.
- Hey, just stay still.
- Calm down.
- Don't mind him.
- Talk down to him.
- Don't fight.
- My gosh.
(The little libero
keeps teasing her.)
I'm so happy.
- My gosh.
- Hey. This is no joke.
Dong Hoon, move back.
- Step back.
- There you go.
- What is he doing?
- What?
- Good.
- Mine.
Send it over.
Here.
- Receive it.
- Ji Young.
(The ball goes back to Ji Young.)
Hey!
- Here.
- Our team is so good.
- We're really good.
- Jae Suk, send it over.
- Again? An attack.
- Nice.
- Jong Kook.
- Receive this.
(Ji Young, receive this.)
Good.
(What?)
- Hey.
- Receive this.
(Why is she happy
when the ball touched the net?)
I touched it.
- I touched it.
- What?
Why are you happy?
What's so good?
- Why are you happy?
- Ji Young, why are you excited?
- My head touched it.
- Ji Young, I'm sorry,
- It didn't.
- but you need to be punished.
- It didn't go over the net.
- Why are you so excited?
- It didn't go over the next.
- My head touched the ball.
- It went over the net.
- No, it didn't.
- It didn't?
- It's okay. We're winning.
- No.
- They're the best female players...
- I've ever seen.
- We lost.
Jae Suk, they are
professional players.
Good.
(Oh, dear.)
Guys, Se Chan used the honorifics.
(Se Chan used the honorifics.)
Se Chan used the honorifics.
Hey!
I can't believe this.
- Why?
- Why did you use the honorifics?
Why did you do that?
I'm going to...
- Why did you use the honorifics?
- Why?
- Jae Suk made me say it.
- Why would you do that?
It was because of Jae Suk.
I won't talk from now on.
- Don't talk.
- Okay.
- I won't.
- Why does he keep doing that?
Guys, let's smile.
Why is the ignorant brat
being so polite?
I know. He's just ignorant.
An ignorant brat?
- Let's do this.
- Here we go.
- All right.
- Mine.
- Good.
- Jae Suk.
- Again?
- Okay.
- You guys are so good.
- It's coming over.
(Groaning)
- Gosh.
Jae Suk!
(Rib blocking)
(Jae Suk...)
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- Why are you here.
- Ji Young...
- Why were you standing still?
- Move back.
- Go back. You can't do this.
- Hey.
(Se Chan and Jae Suk
are ruining the game.)
- It's going so well.
- They are horrible.
They are really bad.
It's not like that.
It's not my fault. Gosh.
Why did you turn your back on them?
- You should look at the ball.
- He's horrible.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
Now I know what you meant
about Yeon Koung.
It's suffocating, isn't it?
Gosh, Yeon Koung is unbelievable.
Her face says everything.
Why are you coming forward again?
Go backward.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Okay. I'll do it right.
- Let's do this.
- We can do this.
It's going well.
- Okay.
- I should've used my foot.
- Back.
- Good. Slow down.
- Use your leg.
- Good.
- Yeum Cheater.
- Send it over.
- Good, Yeum Cheater.
- Good.
- Use your leg.
Jong Kook.
- Okay!
- Yes!
(You should come and take the ball.)
In 1, 2, and 3.
- Good.
- Well done.
- Se Chan, watch your mouth.
- Okay. I will.
- We can catch up.
- Be careful.
Jong Kook.
- We can do this.
- Jong Kook.
Hey.
It's okay.
(Your turn to serve.)
My gosh.
It only touched my lips.
- How is that possible?
- It touched my lips.
If it was someone else,
it would've been fine.
It just touched my lips.
It happened because it was you.
The ball would've passed by
if it was someone else.
It can only happen to you and me.
It only touched my lips.
That's funny. It grazed his lips.
Long Legs. Okay, bring it on.
Hey, Long Legs!
Can't you do it with your legs?
(What?)
- Can't you do it with your legs?
- You can't, can you?
You can't, can you?
(How would Team Yeon Koung react
to the little libero's provocation?)
(The option of this round is...)
(not to lose your temper.)
(Smiling)
(They cannot help
but lose their temper...)
(playing the games.)
- It's not here.
- It's not.
(They even glare at their trainers.)
- The score is 0 to 0.
- Yeon Koung should...
(You should go
to the second-string team.)
(The Long Legs are
in danger of relegation.)
(Overcoming the crisis)
(Let's do this!)
It will break.
(The rookies seem confident,)
(but they aren't good enough.)
(You're
the highest-paid player here.)
(- How about 220 dollars?
- I want 230.)
(Because of their dishonesty,)
(the negotiation falters.)
I'll go.
(What will happen to the Long Legs
after the negotiation?)
(Kwang Soo!)
(Chil Deuk!)
(Fierce Transfer Race 2:
Negotiation of Long Legs)