It's fall now.
Your outfit is perfect for fall.
- Hello.
Hello.
This is a wedding hall, isn't it?
- Is this a wedding hall?
- This place is a wedding hall.
This is lovely.
There was a controversy...
- over Suk Jin again.
- What?
- Controversy?
- Really?
At a press conference, he said
he doesn't want to work for long.
He's worked for a long time.
- I know.
- He doesn't want to?
- I mean...
- "I don't want to work for long."
"I just try many different things
like YouTube and TikTok."
"I like to try new things."
- It's not about trying new things.
- At the press conference...
You started all of them for money.
- That's not true.
- It isn't?
No. It's a new challenge.
"You know I majored
in business administration."
(Ji Suk Jin: You know I majored
in business administration.)
So I have some friends
who run their own businesses.
So I can get...
- Why did he say such a thing?
- advice from them.
The friends
who make Suk Jin go broke.
Why did you talk about friends
who run their own businesses?
- Suk Jin.
- Did he want to brag about them?
Hey, you didn't have to
write down the details.
He wants to say that he will have
work to do after his retirement.
He lost the money he'd saved
because of them.
Why does Suk Jin try to look bold
when he's with others?
- What's with him?
- Hey.
This is how I've lived.
Don't yell at us.
Smile.
I'm just expressing
my opinion emphatically.
- This is just the opening.
- I know.
I'm just stating my opinion.
And in an interview, Ji Hyo said...
There were many interviews.
- What interview?
- There were many interviews.
- What did she say?
- What is it now?
- When did you say that?
- "Recently..."
Ji Hyo said a lot of useless things.
Is that a recent interview?
"I'm playing along with my romance
with Jong Kook for good chemistry."
- Lock your fingers together.
- "Playing along?"
That's not what she really wants,
but she plays along with it."
- It's not like that.
- Ji Hyo.
You just passed Ji Hyo's audition.
- That's...
- He passed.
After ten years.
She didn't seem to care when there
was a rumor about our relationship.
And now she plays along with it?
- Ji Hyo, what does that mean?
- I'm just playing along with it.
I guess there was
some misunderstanding.
- Misunderstanding?
- I see.
People really liked it though.
- Sure.
- It's fun.
So I thought it would be fun
to play along with it.
What we really want is...
Ji Hyo with Jong Kook
and So Min with Se Chan.
Me and So Min?
- The two of us?
- Me and Se Chan?
- Do you want us to be a couple?
- This couple?
Good. I guess a lot of things
happened in the past week.
- That's right.
- I see.
Today, we have three guests
who are trying to defeat...
the members of Running Man.
- Really?
- We will have to trample on them.
Why would they want to defeat us?
I saw today's guests roam around.
- I know.
- So Min was...
We will talk about it
with the guests later.
I heard So Min made
today's guests uncomfortable...
with her words.
- Really? Why?
- What happened?
They tried to leave after seeing me.
They waved their hands like this.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
So Min surprised them.
- We will talk about it later.
- Okay.
Hey, Hani.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hey, Si Yoon.
- Ki Woong.
Ki Woong looks like Kim Won Jun.
Is he the guy
from "2 Days and 1 Night 4"?
- Yoon Si Yoon.
- It's Yoon Si Yoon.
- His name is Yoon Si Yoon.
- He's Yoon Si Yoon.
Hello.
- Hello.
(Park Ki Woong,
Hani of EXID, Yoon Si Yoon)
- Stand here.
- Hello.
- Come over here.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's the millstone guy.
- Right.
- He's Ki Woong.
- Ki Woong.
Ki Woong, you looked like Won Jun...
- coming down the stairs.
- I know.
- He looks just like Won Jun.
- He also looks like Yang Joon Il.
- Yang Joon Il.
- I mean Yang Joon Il.
- Will you move over a little?
Okay.
Why are you talking casually to him?
- Hey.
- Why are you being mean to him?
- My gosh.
- I can't believe this.
I already met them
in front of the van.
But you can't talk
to them like that.
Why did you say this
when you already met them?
"Hey, who are they?"
I met him on a TV show before.
I know. That's what he does.
That's right. We met before.
- On "Star Golden Bell".
- Right. It was "Star Golden Bell".
Really?
- You have long hair now.
- That's right.
Is that what you say to catch up?
"You have long hair now."
(The former show host's
lame comments)
Isn't that the worst thing
to comment on?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Ki Woong, I'm sorry.
- You look really cool.
- Thank you.
- You look like a European.
- Anyway,
the three of them started
a new drama, "You Raise Me Up".
- Is that right?
- "You Raise Me Up".
You raise me up
- It sounds perfect for this place.
- It does.
Let's talk briefly about...
- their new drama first.
- Okay.
- You two are doctors, right?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Doctors.
- And I'm a patient.
- Tell us about it.
I'm in my early 30s.
But for psychological reasons,
I can't get it up.
- Oh no.
- Oh dear.
In your early 30s?
I can't get it up.
(They all sigh.)
- That's...
- In your early 30s?
- Seriously?
- Suk Jin should be there.
That's really sad.
It will get better
if you work out the lower body.
- In your early 30s?
- For psychological reasons.
- Psychological reasons.
- It's about psychology.
- For psychological reasons...
- Still, a workout will help.
- I hang low.
- You do?
So you go to a doctor.
- I go see a doctor.
- I'm the doctor.
And you two are friends from school?
- Right.
- The urologist was my first love.
- His urologist?
- Yes.
- I find the setting interesting.
- That's intense.
I'll watch the drama for sure.
I like the story.
We did the reading before.
Men of your age
really liked the story.
- I see.
- Men in their 50s?
- Men in their 50s.
- Jae Suk...
doesn't have psychological reasons.
(Jae Suk doesn't have
psychological reasons.)
- Is this what you want to do?
- But he hangs low.
- You should be careful.
- No psychological reasons?
You said the phone bill
of 2,000 dollars before.
So people think
I actually spent 2,000 dollars.
Please don't get the wrong idea.
- Isn't that too provocative?
- That's why...
it's titled "You Raise Me Up".
Is that why it's called
"You Raise Me Up"?
- So it's titled "You Raise Me Up".
- Is that why?
It sounds interesting.
Anyway,
I talked about this before.
So Min scared them away with a word.
- What did she say?
- I mean, one of the guests.
She embarrassed one of them.
- What did you say?
- Well...
It was Ki Woong.
- What?
- Well...
Our guests usually don't
get out of their cars.
But I ran into him here.
So I was excited to see him.
"You remember me, don't you?"
- And he remembered me.
- Ki Woong was like...
"Well, yes."
"Sure. Of course I do."
(Was he flustered
because they met a long time ago?)
How do you know each other?
It was 2005.
- I was a college freshman.
- Where?
This feels good.
She's from
Dongduk Women's University.
- That's right.
- I am.
- Did they meet on a blind date?
- No.
My ex-girlfriend was
from the same university.
So I set my friend up with So Min.
You did?
He set his friend up with her.
So Min, you're unbelievable.
Should we go back to 2005?
We should.
We should travel back in time.
- Things were good in 2005.
- Ki Woong...
set me up with a really nice guy.
So we hung out
with Ki Woong's couple.
- It was a double date.
- Yes, it was a double date.
So how did it go?
- It didn't work out.
- I see.
- Did you drink or not? Tell me.
- What?
Did you drink or not on the date?
I don't think we drank.
We just had some coffee.
(Come on!)
- Did you play Truth or Dare?
- Stop it.
- Did you not play games?
- That's enough.
Just stay quiet.
You're like that all the time.
Actually, I still remember
what she was wearing.
What was she wearing?
She was wearing boot-cut jeans.
That was in fashion in 2005.
- It was popular in 2005.
- Boot-cut jeans were in fashion.
Was she wearing True Religion?
And she was wearing Von Dutch.
Were you wearing Von Dutch?
- Von Dutch?
- Von Dutch.
Von Dutch.
I remember that.
- And I was wearing heels.
- Von Dutch.
- And big hoop earrings.
- That's right.
We had Mini Homepage back them.
So Min is so funny.
Today,
we will have
You Raise a Man Up Race.
And "You" means...
Yoo Jae Suk.
What?
That's enough.
I know this is
Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man.
But enough is enough.
So Jae Suk will be the "You"
in the You Raise a Man Up Race.
Today, Ji Hyo, So Min, and Hani...
will be the captains of each team.
And they will pick one
male member they want in each round.
- And the rest will be my team?
- Exactly.
The unchosen members will join...
Team Jae Suk.
Captain Yoo Jae Suk will help you
improve your self-esteem...
- Self-esteem?
- and rebuild your mentality...
- as Dr. Yoo.
- Rebuild their mentality?
How could he do that
when he has no self-esteem?
Rebuild our mentality?
- He's a doctor?
- Me?
This is what I'm good at.
Okay.
(Okay!)
That's not what he can do.
I like stuff like this.
The gown doesn't suit him.
Dr. Yoo.
- I'm confident in this area.
- Dr. Yoo.
Like I said before,
the three women...
will pick a man they want
and become a couple.
And the other four men
will be a team.
After each mission,
the 1st place wins 40 points,
the 2nd place wins 30 points,
the 3rd place wins 20 points,
and the rest will win 10 points.
And the captains will
distribute the points.
(The captains distribute the points
after each mission.)
The two members with the lowest
points will get a penalty.
And the two losers can...
pick one member
to get a penalty with them.
So there will be three people
to get a penalty.
Three members will get a penalty,
so the captains shouldn't...
- get on their bad side.
- They can't be all bossy.
- They should behave themselves.
- They can't get on our bad side.
After each mission,
the captains will get a chance...
- to switch their partners.
- Switch my partner?
If you're ranked high,
you can pick a partner you want.
And Dr. Yoo...
will get two replacement cards.
- And?
- If you're done...
rebuilding a member's mentality...
He's there already.
- Why are you trying so hard?
- Jong Kook, you're good.
- I don't want to be on his team.
- My gosh.
I feel uncomfortable around them.
- I feel suffocated already.
- I don't want to be on their team.
- They make me uncomfortable.
- This is horrible.
Pick me so I won't be
on the same team as them.
- Please pick me.
- I'm tired.
He's rebuilding
my mentality already.
You can use the cards
to switch your team members anytime.
You should pick your first team now.
The captains will play
rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
Ahn Hee Yeon goes first.
- Pick a partner you want.
- Hee Yeon goes first.
Hee Yeon runs a lot.
I can't be her partner.
I pick Si Yoon.
- Si Yoon.
- Okay.
I bet they are dating.
They are doing a drama together.
- Why would you pick him again?
- They are dating.
My gosh.
It's smoke and mirrors.
- Who's second?
- It's me.
- I guess So Min already has one.
- She has her partner.
- It's obvious.
- We all know that.
But I can't pick one right away.
I pick Ki Woong.
(But I can't pick one right away.
I pick Ki Woong.)
(It took her 3 seconds.)
You don't need to hesitate.
(She picked the man she met
in 2005 with no hesitation.)
- So now...
- He seems glad though.
Ji Hyo said she'd play along
with the romance.
Will the romance continue?
- You should.
- Go ahead.
Should I start it today?
(Should I start it today?)
The Metallica shirt.
She's saying that
in the Metallica shirt.
- "Should I start it today?"
- She sounds scary.
Should I start it today?
All right. Come here.
(Should I start it today?
All right. Come here.)
All right, Metallica.
- Okay.
- Go to her.
- It's your fate.
- Go to Metallica.
The rest of you, come over here!
One, two.
(The rest of them join Team Dr. Yoo.)
You're with me now.
- Okay.
- We're going to train them, right?
- What?
It's not like we're being trained.
You're being trained.
- You will train us?
- Yes, I will.
- He doesn't understand it.
- Is that true?
He will help you improve
your self-esteem.
I don't have a problem though.
So the doctor will rebuild
his mentality too, right?
- Exactly.
- The doctor will be trained too.
Now we have teams for Round One.
Please get changed before we start.
Okay.
(Team Dr. Yoo, Team Song Ji Hyo,
Team Jeon So Min, Team Ahn Hee Yeon)
- This is...
- It's a ring.
It's a ring.
Should I knock them down today?
Suk Jin, you should fight me.
What's this?
(The lovey-dovey couples
are coming into the place.)
Suk Jin, come over here.
I'm getting my microphone set.
You won't talk a lot anyway.
- I still need the microphone.
- We have the boom microphone.
- It's done.
- Okay.
- Stand in the middle.
- Why?
- I'm taking care of my members.
- Thank you.
- Come here.
- Stand at the end.
Thank you, Jae Suk.
Do you like your first team?
- Yes.
- Yes. I'm satisfied.
Here's the first mission...
that requires
your courage and hearing.
- It's called Cry in Zombies.
- What?
Two members of each team will play.
Two humans will...
play Cry in Silence
avoiding zombies.
The team that gets the most
correct answers will win the race.
It will be over once you get caught.
- We shouldn't get caught.
- One human...
will give quizzes outside the ring.
But the other human should
stay in the ring...
and give answers wearing earphones.
Two members of the other three teams
will be zombies in the ring.
Wearing eye masks,
they will catch
the human in the ring...
and induce the person's surrender.
The human's surrender.
If you surrender to the zombies...
or exceed the time limit of five
minutes, the game is over.
Okay. Good.
Can zombies touch humans?
You can press them
or pinch them if you want.
Don't say that.
We can tickle them.
- We should just tickle them.
- We can tickle them.
Why would we hit or pinch them?
You can do anything but biting.
- I see.
- All right.
- We're at a disadvantage.
- In Round One,
So Min and Ki Woong are the humans.
Okay. Let's go.
Please put on the earphones.
And the other teams should put on
eye masks and get on the ring.
Okay.
All right.
Put on the earphones.
I'll catch them,
twist their arms...
What?
Hit them.
Then I'll tickle them.
I'll put my fingers into the ribs.
(Then I'll tickle them.
I'll put my fingers into the ribs.)
Why do we have a first-aid box here?
- What does this mean?
- What is this?
Why do we have this here?
- Are we going to get hurt?
- What?
- Will someone get seriously hurt?
- That means I'll get hurt.
(Ki Woong will give answers,
so he put on the earphones.)
He can't hear us.
Ki Woong looks so weak.
All right.
It's worth a shot. Let's do this.
The second zombies are
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
And the third zombies are
Se Chan and Haha.
Ready.
Start.
(Urology)
Your new drama is about this.
- Hee Yeon, behind your back.
- In your drama.
- Here.
- The doctor.
The doctor in your drama.
(The zombies have no idea
where Ki Woong is.)
- Over here.
- The doctor in your drama.
- The opposite direction.
- The other way.
The doctor...
- The kind of doctor in the drama.
- That way.
- Behind you.
- The opposite direction.
- Si Yoon, in front of you.
- Run. Run that way.
- Run. Run forward!
- Go straight!
You got him!
- No.
- Hey, Hani.
- Hani!
Hani, that's not him!
That's not him.
- Right. Go forward!
- Go forward.
To the left!
- A job!
- Over here!
- Forward.
- A job? Actor.
- No.
- Right there. You got him!
No. The character.
What's the character's job?
- A doctor. A psychiatrist.
- Behind you.
- Corner him.
- No. What specialty?
That's not him!
(Ki Woong passes them, and 3 seconds
later the zombies begin fighting.)
My gosh, Yoon Si Yoon!
It's not this way.
Si Yoon, that way.
- Hani, behind you!
- A specialty for men.
- Comedians.
- No.
- Move forward!
- Forward!
No. That's not him!
The second team will go in now.
- That's us.
- Ki Woong, it's for men!
- Listen to my voice.
- I got it.
- I'm going to listen to Jae Suk.
- Where should I go?
To the left. Straight.
- Go straight!
- Just listen to me.
- Speak one at a time.
- To the left.
- Haha, to the left.
Urologist.
- This way.
- Over here.
Beer... You have peanuts...
- You eat it with beer and peanuts.
- It's me, Haha.
- Zombies stick out your arms.
- Beer, peanuts, and...
Go all the way to the right.
(Right?)
You got him.
- Beer, peanuts, and...
- You got him!
- Go to the right!
- Ki Woong!
- Si Yoon. To the right.
- No.
- To your right.
- Squid.
Behind you.
- Haha!
You got it!
- Where is he?
- It's me.
- You got it. Haha.
- Hold hands and move forward.
- Like this.
- It's me. Se Chan.
- Go in a line!
- Let's hold hands!
- Where are you?
- In a line.
- Over here.
- Let's hold hands. Don't move.
Okay. He's standing behind you.
- Who is this?
- He's behind us.
- He's standing behind you.
- Who is this?
(They're playing
ring-around-the-rosie.)
It's me. Si Yoon.
- Turn around.
- Okay.
The third zombie team is going in.
- Behind you!
- Do we go in?
It's a bird that can repeat words.
A puppet boss?
- It's a bird that can repeat words.
- Behind you!
- Behind us!
- You got him!
In front of you...
Hold hands like that.
Haha! Behind you!
A bird. A colorful bird.
- Who is this?
- It's me, Haha.
Go forward towards your left.
A colorful bird.
An alcoholic?
- A bird that can repeat words.
- He's standing to your left.
- My right.
- Your left!
- A bird that can repeat words.
- He's standing to your left!
- To your left!
I got him!
- Where?
- Oh, no!
I got him!
Where? How did you get him?
- Who was it?
- How did you get him?
I give up!
- I give up!
- Oh, gosh.
He was right here?
You got two right.
I don't know.
- Nice.
- This is really hard.
You guys got two questions right.
- How could you only get two right?
- What was the last one?
Parrot.
This time it's Ahn Hee Yeon
and Yoon Si Yoon.
(It's Team Ahn Hee Yeon's turn
to be humans.)
He stayed close to the person giving
the hints because he couldn't hear.
- Right.
- Get close to...
the person giving hints.
Someone should stay by
the person giving the hints. Right?
I'll give you the questions.
I'll stay by Hani.
- I'll follow Hani around.
- Ready.
Start.
Hani is right here!
(Hani's fan appears.)
- Hani is right here!
- To the left. Right. That way!
Hani is right here!
- Chicken.
- Hani is right here!
Fingers.
- Hani! Hani is right here!
- Fingers...
- No!
- Hani is right here!
- Over there.
- Chicken.
- Hani is right here!
- Ostrich.
- What is it?
- Feet!
- Hani is right here!
Chicken leg. Chicken.
My gosh!
- Hani is right here!
- What is that?
What is this?
Hani!
Chicken. Chicken feet!
- Chicken feet!
- Hani is right here!
(They finally get 1 question right.)
- Second team.
- Okay.
- Second team, go in.
- Go in.
- Where are you, Haha?
- I can see you.
Hani is right here!
(While everyone's busy, the protein zombie
focuses on the sounds.)
- Over here!
- Hani is right here!
Jong Kook, stick out your arm!
Behind you!
You got him!
Behind you! You got him!
(He falls to the ground after
being grabbed by the venomous snake.)
He got him.
- He got him.
- It's over.
- Did he get him?
- He did.
He's not giving up!
- Archery.
- Hurry!
You can do it!
Team Korea, you can do it!
- Who is this?
- It's...
- Where is he?
- Who is this?
- A little bit more!
- It's Jong Kook!
- Where are you?
It's me!
- That's me, and he's here.
- I'm holding onto him!
- Where?
Give up!
(Grasshopper zombie is doing
martial arts on his own.)
- It's me!
- Where are you?
That's me, and he's here.
- I give up!
- Don't.
- Stop!
- I give up!
He gives up!
Who is that? Who kept hitting me?
- Was I hitting you?
- Hey.
(He kept punching someone
without knowing who it was.)
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry about that.
No wonder I kept hearing
sounds from in front of me.
- I hit you really hard.
- Really?
(Ssaebssaeb was blinded
by the eye mask.)
Yoon Si Yoon got one question right.
(Team Ahn Hee Yeon got
1 question right.)
Si Yoon. What happened?
Right.
I hit him in his pressure points.
Se Chan and Haha will go first.
- "Love letter" in Korean.
- Zombies!
Zombies, clap!
Love letter.
(The zombies created
their own signal.)
Then we won't attack other zombies.
- Where is he?
- Four syllables.
- What is it?
- That's me.
- It's me.
- We have to talk.
It's over.
They got five questions right.
That was okay.
Yoo Jae Suk's nickname.
- This.
- Grasshopper.
The hair that grows
in Suk Jin's ears.
- Old man hair.
- Right.
The shot that Suk Jin got.
- Pfizer? Vaccine?
- What did you just do?
(That hurt.)
(Thanks to the weak zombies...)
It's over.
They got nine questions right.
Suk Jin will go in for our team.
- Okay.
- Right.
Really? Shouldn't you go in?
What are you saying?
- He's a doctor.
- Oh, right. Dr. Yoo.
That's right.
This team got 5 right, so if they
get 4 more, they'll be tied for 1st.
(If they get 4 right,
they'll be tied for 1st.)
If they get five...
- We can get 4 right.
- Let's get 4 right.
- Just get 4 questions right.
- We need 4 questions.
Four questions.
I'm going to catch him.
- Ready.
- I'm going to catch him.
Start.
We need to catch him.
(Answer: Giraffe)
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo's nickname.
- Kwang Soo.
- I can't hear you.
- He can't get that close.
- Kwang Soo.
- I can't hear you.
(Is he over here?)
What's Kwang Soo's nickname?
- Kwang Soo.
- I can't hear you.
(I hear him. I can hear him.)
- That close?
- Kwang Soo's nickname.
- It has a long neck...
- Giraffe!
- He's coming this way.
- That's right. Giraffe.
(He focuses his hearing
on Suk Jin's voice.)
- Right.
- You got him.
- Giraffe!
- That's right. Giraffe.
- Giraffe.
- He's coming this way.
(Big Nose shows off his agility
as he avoids him.)
Se Chan.
Se Chan's feet.
Move forward.
(They begin cornering Big Nose
thanks to Si Yoon's coaching.)
Keep going forward.
To the left. That's right.
- Se Chan's feet!
- Sit down!
Keep going forward.
To the left. That's right.
(Laying down?)
We got him!
(Big Nose cornered himself
by lying down.)
- You can torture him now.
- That's too bad.
- Keep torturing him.
- Let's keep going.
- Se Chan's feet!
- There you go.
Se Chan's feet!
- Darn.
- It's over.
(A move that gets rid of
his teammate's enthusiasm.)
- Just endure it!
- Okay.
(They try to get him to endure it,)
(but he's already pretending like
it hurts a lot.)
- Enough. I give up.
- The...
- I give up.
- How annoying.
- He's...
He's surprised.
- Suk Jin...
- How boring.
Ki Woong twisted his arm.
- He was surprised.
- It really hurt!
- Wait.
- You got one question right.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- Was it stinky feet?
Stinky feet.
- How could you get caught so fast?
- You should've rolled.
- Wait.
- I should've gone in.
Why did you lay down?
(Nobody can understand that.)
It's easy to avoid two people.
Why did you do that?
Gosh. I know.
He was shocked
when his arm got twisted.
Suk Jin!
It hurts!
- Suk Jin!
- Right, my arm! Where is he?
Ki Woong.
Hey! How could you put me
in an armbar for real?
- I'm sorry.
- Stop pretending.
Let me go again. Hey.
I'll go again when it's your turn.
- It's over.
- What do you mean you'll go again?
- It's over?
Okay. As a result, Ji Hyo
and Jong Kook are in first place.
Okay.
In second place is Jae Suk's team.
- That's not bad.
- Okay.
In third place is Jeon So Min
and Park Ki Woong,
and in fourth place is Yoon Si Yoon
and Ahn Hee Yeon.
- We're not in last place.
- Team leaders, divide the points.
- Okay.
- Do whatever you want. It's okay.
- I did my best, Jae Suk.
- So Min, 20 points.
- Don't abuse your power.
- It's the first game, so be fair.
- Of course.
- Who's giving out the points?
- The team leader.
- Hey.
Mr. Yoo.
I don't think Suk Jin
will get anything.
Jae Suk, we get to appoint someone
at the end, so...
- That's right.
- We get to appoint someone,
but you should still think about
what's best.
We shouldn't get to appoint people,
but we can.
Just do whatever you want.
- I think you should be first place.
- Me too.
You could get first place
and avoid the penalty.
Earlier...
(The other team leaders
divide up the points too.)
- Jae Suk gave a lot.
- I really did.
Jae Suk, can you show
the camera yours first?
- My gosh.
- That's a lot.
- It's okay.
- Why did you give me four points?
- Hold on...
- Are you...
I gave you a lot more
than you deserved.
- What's with the four points?
- That's a lot.
It is.
I divided it in half, 20-20.
- Really?
- My gosh.
Heart!
Thanks.
- It's because we just got together.
- Give it to me.
Isn't this too much?
- Why?
- Just accept it.
Hee Yeon, can you show us yours?
(Team Ahn Hee Yeon reveals
theirs next.)
(Team leader: Ahn Hee Yeon, 3 points
Member: Yoon Si Yoon, 7 points)
- What is that?
- What's with you two?
- What is this?
- I feel bad. It's a joint effort.
- What's with you two?
- How sweet.
- She divided it 7 to 3.
- Next up is Jeon So Min.
- A heart.
I gave him a lot.
My gosh.
- I really gave him a lot.
- It's okay.
- He only got two right.
- He said it's okay.
- No, wait...
- How are you okay?
- I didn't do well.
- He didn't do very well.
- That's right. It's all good.
- Right.
The first round is over.
You can change partners now.
Ji Hyo came in first place,
so she can trade Jong Kook
for someone else.
- She won't trade him.
- Of course not.
- I did my best.
- Right.
Does anyone want Jong Kook?
- What is that?
- Why would you ask that?
- I wanted to know if anyone did.
- If you don't want to, don't.
(Ji Hyo conducts a survey.)
Kiss!
- Keep your partner.
- What's the next game?
I can't tell you.
Right. He can't.
I don't think there's anyone,
so I'll keep him.
(She said she'd accept him,
but she's being more forward.)
- Love power!
- Power!
(Glaring)
- Can I trade?
- Yes,
but you can't touch Jong Kook.
Yoon Si Yoon.
This is a predictable move
from So Min.
- You're unbelievable.
- What?
Why? He did his best!
- Wait. He did his best, but...
- Ki Woong did his best.
- He did his best.
- I know he did...
- his best.
- He did his best.
So Min is so scary.
The two of them will switch.
I'm not even surprised.
- Memories are just memories.
- Right.
- He did his best...
- Next, Hee Yeon...
can trade Ki Woong with
one of those three.
Are you going to trade?
You have a lot of options.
You have a lot of options. Why?
- You have a lot of options.
- Do whatever you want.
- There's a variety.
- They get bored of their partners.
Se Chan's a good partner.
(It's a chance to escape
Dr. Yoo's nagging.)
If she chooses Se Chan or Haha,
- it'll be bad.
- I'll go with this.
(She's not going to trade.)
Why?
- Let's use the replacement card.
- Give us a chance!
(Jae Suk, the replacement card.)
- Can you use the replacement card?
- With whom?
- You have a replacement card.
- I do.
Change those guys up.
Change the people who are trying
to start something romantic...
like So Min.
Please use a replacement card,
Dr. Yoo!
I'll trade Yoon Si Yoon
with Ji Suk Jin.
- Why?
- Perfect!
(She went from paradise...)
(to a nightmare.)
- That's great!
- Why?
That's great. You're so wise!
- Okay!
- You're amazing, Dr. Yoo!
You're so wise!
- With her?
- Suk Jin!
- Hey!
- Then...
give me anyone but Suk Jin.
Hey.
How can you say that
when I'm within earshot?
I can hear everything.
He can hear!
Nice.
- Nice ears!
- Nice hearing aids!
Nice ears!
- Okay. Nice.
- Very good!
We'll move onto the location
for the next mission.
- Okay.
- Yes.
This place is nice.
Is the mission outside?
Oh, it's there.
(Everyone comes together
for the next mission.)
This place is really nice.
- It's as if we're outdoors.
- Right.
With Si Yoon on our team...
- He looks more handsome, right?
- Exactly.
You should be glad to join our team.
Plus, he's sitting
between me and Jae Suk.
The seat that makes you
look most handsome.
It doesn't matter
what team I'm on...
as long as I get plenty of airtime.
- He's a pro.
- That's a great mentality.
- Your experience shows.
He's a pro.
It's obvious he's been on
a weekend variety show.
That mentality comes from people
who've done this for ten years.
How incredible.
Why are you having such a hard time
putting that on?
- Just put it anywhere.
- It's a clip.
Just clip it on here.
My gosh.
This mission...
is a chance to get personal points.
The game is
As Long as It’s Not My Partner.
What is it?
This mission is very easy.
We're going to play Mafia,
- a game you're all familiar with.
- Okay.
We're going to randomly choose...
- two Mafia members.
- This sounds fun.
You'll play three rounds, and if
you catch all the Mafia members,
- the citizens will win.
- Okay.
But here's the thing.
If the Mafia wins,
- they will get 50 points,
- Really?
and the citizens will lose
ten points each.
If your partner was chosen
as a Mafia member,
you will lose 30 points.
That's terrible!
I have three partners!
So you'll split up into two.
In teams of two?
How do you want to split up?
We'll split up based on looks.
- Then it's us two.
- Then I'm...
Then the two of us will be a team.
- Why would you say that?
- Hey!
Then we'll end up together.
(Walking)
- We'll end up together.
- I'm dumbfounded.
- Come to the middle.
- It's me and Si Yoon!
- Come over here.
- Move.
- Why would you say that?
- I know.
- Why'd you say that?
- You have high self-esteem.
- It's not a matter of self-esteem.
- Honestly...
- He's in 1st place.
- I'm in 2nd.
- Right.
- You guys are funny.
But we can't choose
3rd and 4th place.
No. I'm in third place.
It's obvious we're in
1st and 2nd place.
Who's in fourth place?
- Hold on.
- He's talking about himself.
I'm dumbfounded.
My gosh, you guys are really funny.
Okay. The key point of this game...
is to figure out whether or not...
- your partner is a Mafia.
- Right.
- You have to figure that out.
- That's important.
- You shouldn't do that.
- I shouldn't do this.
If the Mafia loses,
they lose 30 points,
and the citizens
gain ten points each.
We're going to choose
two Mafia members randomly.
You can't lie.
Don't do anything weird, okay?
- Don't do something randomly.
- I...
I should turn my radar on.
It won't be fair...
if you gave your partner a sign,
right?
- You can't do that.
- You can't.
You can't give them a sign.
(How good are the members
who have 11 years of experience?)
- Should I choose one?
- Yes.
- Suk Jin...
- And...
turn away from the camera and look.
Turn away from the camera.
Then I could get more.
Check it.
(He checked it.)
- It is.
- It'll be hard to guess.
Okay. He's awkward.
Si Yoon is acting awkward.
- Okay.
Next up is Haha.
(The moment they go up, their speech
and expressions are all suspicious.)
(Haha's turn is next.)
- Keep an eye on him.
- Mr. Dirty Mustache.
Mr. Dirty Mustache. Hey, Mr. DM.
(Focused)
Hey, Mr. DM.
Watch his expression.
- He looks awkward.
- He's a citizen.
- He looked at it quickly.
- The third handsome guy is next.
(The Running Man members know
each other too well.)
(Se Chan checks
with poker face next.)
(Next is Jae Suk.)
Look at his expression.
(Laughing)
He's flustered.
- He's flustered.
- What's wrong?
- He's a Mafia.
- He's very flustered.
- I'm not.
- This is random?
- When he denied it,
- it sounded like he was lying.
- I'm a citizen.
- I'm not.
- Everyone stops talking after.
This is random,
so it's hard to tell.
See? Nobody is talking.
- You can tell it's not me, right?
- You guys are weird.
(So Min, who's next...)
(is a citizen!)
(So Min's partner, Big Nose,
is also a citizen.)
- Hee Yeon?
- Gosh, no way.
Why would you open your eyes
so wide?
- Millstone Guy.
- Don't take the card out.
(Millstone Guy Ki Woong is...)
- "Millstone Guy". That's hilarious.
- Millstone Guy.
Millstone Guy.
(a citizen.)
- "Family Guy" and Millstone Guy!
- Millstone Guy!
(Everyone is done checking.)
Millstone Guy.
(These four are all citizens.)
It's not me.
Let's not lie to each other.
I promise.
- You're not, right?
- I'm not.
- This is hard because it's random.
- Be honest with me.
- I'm not. I'm really not.
We need to find the Mafia.
- Are you a Mafia?
- I'm not.
Then why did you say that before?
Were you anxious?
- Right.
- Really?
It's a habit.
- I do that habitually.
- Okay.
Okay. The Mafia needs to find out
who one another is.
Close your eyes
and lower your heads.
- Okay.
Mafia, open your eyes
and make eye contact.
Mafia, raise your heads.
(The Running Man members
who are well-versed in spy games...)
(and actors who are great at acting)
(Who are the 2 Mafia members?)
(The 2 Mafia members checked
each other's identities.)
- Everyone, wake up.
- Okay.
- Who raised their heads?
- I told you it wasn't me.
I felt some movement earlier
coming from Jae Suk.
It wasn't me.
- Are you saying it was me?
- I felt it.
I heard the wind.
I think that it's Si Yoon and...
- Hani.
- Jae Suk.
Se Chan.
- Why? Tell me why.
- Why do you think that?
They're both acting strange.
Si Yoon seems like a Mafia member.
I think Si Yoon is a Mafia.
He's been zoned out
since he came back to his seat.
- Right.
- Okay.
I don't think it's Si Yoon.
He seems really stable.
You look really stable.
- Why is he so zoned out?
- I don't know.
Is it you?
(Is it you?)
- Me?
- Yes.
(He's not.)
- He's not.
- Why are you covering for him?
- What is this?
- I told her it wasn't me.
- "My husband didn't do it."
- I always...
- They're a Mafia Couple.
- Mafia Couple.
- Couple.
Okay.
- Mafia Couple.
- It's the two of us?
- But...
- It might...
Ji Hyo is the hardest to figure out
in games like this.
Right. She doesn't talk.
- She doesn't talk much.
- It's not me. I promise.
She told me earlier,
and I don't think it's her.
- If it's not, kiss. Kiss her.
- I'm being honest.
- I'm being honest. It's not me.
- Hold on.
I'm being honest.
I think Se Chan...
- Why is she targeting me?
- People...
can fool people with their words,
but their behavior...
How can she tell by my expression?
We barely know each other.
- I thought you were weird too.
- His poses.
- It's not me.
- You punk.
- It's not me. This is a mistake.
- She's making good deductions.
- I'm telling you he is.
- He looks nervous.
It's not me. I swear.
Don't target me. This is a mistake.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- When I get targeted...
- That behavior.
- When you targeted me last time,
I turned red because I wasn't it.
Remember?
When people target me, I turn red.
It's not him. He's like that.
- I think...
- It's not me.
- it's my partner...
Can I make a deduction?
I'm 100 percent sure
it's Yang Se Chan.
- There he goes again.
- No.
- Okay. I'll explain.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- This is it.
- Mafia targets people...
- I'm 100 percent sure.
Talk faster.
Look. He can't talk.
I'm 100 percent sure. Go ahead.
They have to target one person
and kill them off...
- to lower the possibility.
- No way.
I think that it's either
you or So Min.
- It's not me.
- Either you talk a lot...
or you don't at all.
Okay, I...
- knew it was my partner right away.
- Where are you touching?
I was trying to feel your heartbeat,
- It was my nipple.
- but I felt something bumpy...
- He kept touching me.
- Stop touching people!
- What?
- Hey!
It's located higher than yours
for most people!
(He tries to counterattack
Low-chested.)
Don't touch people according
to your standards.
No, it was bumpy, so...
I was wondering
what he was doing all of a sudden.
- Wait!
- Stop it.
- You're anxious right now!
- No.
- He's anxious right now.
- Or he liked it!
It's because I take after my dad!
They're pointy.
- Really?
- Haha...
Hold on. He must've been really
bored during his self-quarantine.
You know it.
He racked up a phone bill
of 2,000 dollars.
- Because of you, news articles...
- Isn't that a bit too much?
(Because of you, news articles...)
- That's a waste of money.
- Unbelievable.
Can he be any more annoying?
Isn't Jae Suk a Mafia member?
- No way.
- It's either Jae Suk...
- or Haha.
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk...
- He's slightly flushed.
He's a Mafia.
- Come on.
- Are you?
Suspecting me
only helps those in the Mafia.
- I suspect So Min.
- Out of the blue?
- That was sudden.
- Why me all of a sudden?
That was odd.
- It was out of the blue.
- Hear me out.
- It's you.
- It's Jae Suk!
If you're a citizen,
- don't act out.
- He's terrible at this game.
- Hear me out.
- You're confusing us.
- Go ahead.
- Hear me out.
It's Jae Suk and Haha.
What are the odds, right?
- Why do you think it's me?
- Just remember...
that the Mafia
keeps suspecting others.
- It's like this.
- You...
- I'm sure of it.
- It's Si Yoon.
- It's the most handsome member.
- It has to be Si Yoon.
- I'm sure of it.
- It's Si Yoon.
(The most handsome member
is suspected once again.)
Why do you think it's me?
Because...
you're not the silent type.
- Exactly.
- He was talkative during the intro.
He came here with one goal
and that's to have...
a lot of screen time.
Si Yoon, you're awfully quiet.
- Tell me about it.
- That's not it.
That's not it.
Besides, I'm a citizen.
- How he's sitting is questionable.
- The one...
who suspects me...
- is most likely in the Mafia.
- No way.
- He never sits like this.
- It's always...
the one sitting at ease
with his legs crossed.
Yours is crossed too.
There you go.
It's Suk Jin.
For me, it's a habit.
- We'll begin the first trial.
- Let's do this.
I'm clueless though.
- Choose one person on my count.
- Just one?
- Yes, one.
- One for now.
- Then...
- This isn't easy.
All right. One...
I wonder who it is.
Two...
(Is one of the 3 suspects
a member of the Mafia?)
Three.
Si Yoon.
- Three.
- Si Yoon.
- Hold on a second.
- Who chose Si Yoon?
- It's Si Yoon.
- Si Yoon.
- Then Si Yoon is on trial first.
- It's not him.
- He'll get to say his last words.
- It's him.
I'm a citizen.
If that proves to be true...
The one who chose you.
A member of the Mafia is among those
who were suspected with me.
- I'm sure it's him.
- He seems nervous.
His hands are clasped.
Should we go through with it?
Yes, we should.
Is he the one?
Point your thumb down
if you choose to eliminate him.
- In 1, 2...
- Down?
- Does this mark death?
- Yes, point it down.
In 1, 2, 3.
Let's see how it goes.
(They choose to eliminate him.)
- We couldn't help it.
- All right.
Now, please all drop your heads...
- and close your eyes.
- I wonder who it is.
All right.
Is Si Yoon...
a member of the Mafia?
(Is Si Yoon a member of the Mafia?)
Yes, he is.
(Si Yoon is a member of the Mafia.)
(They got it right.)
What did I tell you?
I knew something was off.
- What did I tell you?
- He was acting strange.
- He never sits this way.
- It's like I said.
(The unlucky Si Yoon
was eliminated right away.)
Then who's his partner?
(After finding out what he was,)
(he talked less and tried to look
like he was suspecting others.)
(His tactics got
the best of him though.)
(He became the most anxious man
in the room.)
(No way)
What did I tell you?
(Their hunch even works
on the guests.)
It's like I said.
- I'm shocked.
- Please take your seats.
It's now the Mafia's turn
to eliminate someone.
- See?
- You...
There's no one to trust
in this world.
- What did I tell you?
- I knew almost immediately.
Everyone, please drop your heads.
Only the Mafia member
will look up...
and choose someone to eliminate.
You can point.
(The remaining member of the Mafia
chose an innocent citizen.)
It's now morning.
- Can we look up?
- Sure thing.
During the first night,
Jae Suk was eliminated.
(Citizen Jae Suk is out.)
Were you a citizen?
Gosh, he was a citizen.
- He was a citizen.
- No way.
It proves just how on point I was.
(Innocent citizen Jae Suk is out.)
(The list of potential Mafia members
is now shorter.)
(Who was the Mafia member
that eliminated Jae Suk?)
Let me say something important.
It's hard to point at anyone...
since the Mafia can't speak
or mouth the name.
That's why it must be
someone in Jae Suk's vicinity.
Hear me out as well.
He either did this...
- See what I mean?
- Hear me out.
- This is what I think.
- Sure.
I kept on saying it's Se Chan.
It has to be Se Chan.
- He keeps on...
- Eliminating Jae Suk...
It'd look suspicious
if he eliminated me.
- I was going to say that.
- That's why...
he eliminated Jae Suk instead.
- It's like this.
- Let me just say that...
we're all citizens over here.
It doesn't have to be someone close.
- Wait.
- It's not that hard to point.
- Are your ears okay?
- It really isn't me.
Hear me out.
If I were a Mafia member,
I wouldn't be able to eliminate
the one who suspected me.
If it were me,
I'd choose someone far away.
It seems off to eliminate
someone random though.
It really isn't me. If it were,
I'd have eliminated
someone far away.
If you eliminate the person
that suspected you,
it would seem...
There's a reason for his choice.
Only a fool would do that.
- Is the Mafia a fool?
- I feel bad for Se Chan...
- being on Jong Kook's radar.
- It really isn't me.
If you take me out,
you'll be in big trouble
during the next round.
- I also believe it's Se Chan.
- Why...
- Go ahead.
- Because...
- It really isn't me.
- If the Mafia...
was smart like Jong Kook,
- he wouldn't kill another suspect.
- Exactly.
- But...
- But someone as stupid as him...
would do the opposite.
- You're a fool.
- If you watch this when it airs,
- you'll see who the foolish one is.
- How stupid can you be?
Let's see who the stupid one is.
- How can you kill another suspect?
- This is frustrating.
Se Chan being all worked up...
makes him look suspicious.
I can tell by the look on his face.
Just his expression alone...
I just know. Come on.
I knew it was Si Yoon
the moment he sat down...
after reading
what's in the envelope.
Then...
And while we were talking,
I looked at Se Chan...
and knew.
The moment the game began,
I knew who was in the Mafia.
- What...
- So there's no need for a debate.
- This is frustrating.
- You know...
I knew the moment
I saw his expression.
- Okay, let's see.
- I won't let it slide...
if you're in the Mafia.
Choose the person to eliminate.
It's you.
We'll hear your final defense.
- Three.
- It's you.
(Se Chan will defend himself
one last time.)
All right.
Let me explain.
Whenever someone targets me,
blood rushes to my face...
and I stutter. However...
- You talk just fine.
- I don't.
That's why...
(The quiet Millstone Guy
lays a shy punch.)
But why am I worked up right now?
- Because I'm innocent.
- Ki Woong...
knows how to punch hard.
- Millstone Guy.
- He saw right through you.
- He talks just fine.
- Anyway, it isn't me.
Do you wish to stay alive
for another round?
- What?
- We'll let you live.
Who should we eliminate instead?
(What?)
Pick a person.
You think you're so clever!
(He ends up exploding.)
- Come on.
- Just kill me already!
Why do you want to kill me so badly?
- You wanted another chance.
- The punches keep coming.
Since you want another chance,
we'll give you one.
Let him live
and we'll see who he eliminates.
We'll let him live.
If we're that sure,
we'll let him live.
- Yes, let him.
- Then he'll eliminate you.
Who were you going to eliminate
if you had made it?
You, of course.
(You, of course.)
Of course it's you.
Who else would I eliminate?
- He's red in the face.
- Look at him.
- Of course it's you.
- Look.
- He's fuming.
- Okay.
- Eliminate me already.
- Eliminate me.
- Let's vote.
- All right.
- Just kill me.
- Kill him.
- I'd rather not.
- We should eliminate him.
- Of course.
- I know it's him.
- Kill him.
(They agree to eliminate him.)
- Now...
- I don't think it's him.
Is Se Chan a member of the Mafia?
(Is Se Chan a member of the Mafia?)
(Se Chan was cornered
due to Jong Kook's tenacity.)
(All members suspected him.
So which role was he playing?)
He is.
(He's a member of the Mafia.)
See? What did I tell you?
(Se Chan was a member of the Mafia.)
- Seriously.
- Are you kidding me?
He's the most annoying person
on earth!
(He tried hard to
suspect others instead.)
(He was targeted by Jong Kook
right from the start.)
(During the first night)
(Him)
(He thought he was being clever
by taking Jae Suk out.)
(He couldn't hold off
Detective Kook anymore.)
Just kill me already!
- I knew it.
- You...
- Get over here.
- Is he insane?
I know who it is instantly
whenever I play this game.
What did I tell you?
- You're incredible.
- I know immediately.
- Their expressions say it all.
- You fool.
Why eliminate someone
that's being suspected?
- That's a bad move.
- I couldn't help it.
This is great though.
- He was cornered too early.
- I guess you couldn't help it.
The stress was real.
Let me announce the scores so far.
(1st place: Jong Kook and Ji Hyo,
10th place: Si Yoon)
What on earth?
- No way.
- Are you kidding me?
Why are Si Yoon and I...
My score is the same,
but I moved up a rank.
- Our ranks are different.
- We moved up a rank.
- You moved up two.
- I know.
- You guys are killing this.
- I moved up two ranks too.
We'll give you lunch
in the order of your ranking.
Is that so?
Our ranking?
- Gosh, I'm so unlucky.
- Jong Kook must be happy.
Let's go have lunch now.
All right!
Thank you.
- We give you a lot though, right?
- Yes.
- Let's enjoy it.
- Have as much as you want.
This is nice. It even got some oil.
I hope you don't pick us...
as your team member this time.
(I hope you don't pick us
as your team member this time.)
You get what I mean, right?
- Why not?
- We need to work with good ones.
You need your points too.
That's why you need someone...
Oh, we're dividing up?
Yes, your team needs to win
to earn some points.
If it doesn't work out
even if I try hard,
I'll just place last
and bring down Jong Kook with me.
But you can't if he's
in 1st or 2nd place.
- Is that so?
- They're in 1st and 2nd place.
You can't pick Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
I'm going to bring down Jong Kook
to third place no matter what.
I know I'm done with.
You must've been
really annoyed earlier.
Of course.
- I was annoyed too.
- I was really upset.
From the beginning, he went,
"Si Yoon is suspicious."
"Se Chan is suspicious."
That was really annoying.
It was as if I was being judged.
I'm going to bring him down
to third place no matter what.
Is this our lunch?
What's this?
(The 4 members in the middle rank
get tuna mayonnaise rice.)
I like this.
We're really good at games.
I think we're really good.
But here's the thing.
- Ji Hyo...
- Don't you have any soup?
Don't you have any soup?
- You have no idea...
- Can you give me some water?
- Hey!
- I'm sorry.
- It wasn't intentional.
- I was talking!
I got really thirsty. I'm sorry.
I might punch him today, but
please pretend you didn't see it.
It's a secret
in the entertainment field.
Even if he punches me,
you don't need to worry.
It won't hurt at all.
(The battle fighting power
has begun again.)
They've been saying the same thing
for over 11 years.
Na Eun is four now, so her punches
must be a bit stronger than yours.
Na Eun's punches
are a bit stronger than yours.
Na Eun's punches are stronger?
(In the meantime,
the 3 in the top rank...)
What's this? Is this Coke?
It's fried chicken gizzard.
There's such a thing?
Are there drumsticks?
Don't they have drumsticks?
- Drumsticks are the best part.
- That's right!
It's gizzard.
Right? It's fried gizzard.
There's such thing as
a fried gizzard?
- It's so good.
- Is it good?
(They enjoy the special food
only given to the high rank.)
Because they're fried
in clean oil...
(Laughing)
- It's a bit spicy.
- This place is really good.
The three of us are the worst...
- at promoting
- It's really good.
It's so funny.
I'm sorry. I was still chewing
the gizzard. It was too chewy.
I was chewing on the gizzard
until now.
You should just stop.
It's my first time trying it.
- This must be about knowledge.
- All right!
If this is the about knowledge...
I think we're playing a quiz.
According to the result
from the game you played,
you can change your teammates.
Right.
Ji Hyo who is in the first place
will go first.
Will you change your teammates
or stick with them?
- Ji Hyo.
You should take
either me or Si Yoon.
Ji Hyo, it's more important
to get scores on the quiz.
We'll bet our lives on it.
This round is really important
because we're playing a quiz.
- It's a quiz.
- Then I'm not that bad of a choice.
I'm pretty quick and good at a quiz.
(He's full of self-love.)
I can do anything.
I can pop all the balloons
if there are any.
All right. I'll pick Si Yoon.
Jong Kook. It's all set.
Is Si Yoon a smart type?
Not really.
- He reads a lot.
- Oh, really?
- How good are you?
- Knowledge.
When you were a regular
on the other show,
were you good at quizzes?
Tae Hyun always told me that
I'm quite dumb...
compared to how much I read.
- I get it.
- He's one of us.
- Also...
- He's pretty good.
Compared to how much you read?
- Why didn't you tell me earlier?
- I know.
You can't change your mind now.
But I'll try my best.
- Who's next?
- Next is So Min.
So Min, go ahead.
If you're satisfied with your
partner, you can stick with him.
(You know what to do, right?)
Go ahead.
- I pick Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- Why you...
- Seriously.
You picked me?
Why did you bump my fist?
- Come here, Suk Jin.
- All right! I got this.
- Jong Kook.
- You belong here anyway.
- You need everything.
- Welcome, Suk Jin!
You need to use
your strength and brain.
Let's go!
- Not me.
- Just do it.
Hee Yeon, go ahead.
(Only Hee Yeon's choice remains.)
(Being careful)
Suk Jin is really smart.
- Since it's a quiz.
- I'll pick a player who will...
score many points for me.
Let's go!
I heard there's someone
who likes liberal arts.
- What?
- Liberal arts?
- Who?
- Suk Jin?
- Yes.
- Him?
- Yes!
- Suk Jin.
- Hani failed again.
- For real?
- Hani failed.
- Goodness, Hani.
We're playing a quiz, right?
- All right.
- Yes, we're playing a quiz.
Let me explain the rules,
and you'll change into new vests.
Don't I have a chance
to change my teammates?
Yes, you have one more chance.
Wait. You looked at me
as you said that.
- You looked at me.
- I think it'd be fun...
if he joins So Min.
You think so?
Wherever I go...
Jong Kook should join my team.
Stop it!
Empty Heads!
- Empty Heads!
- Empty Heads. Come on!
(They scout Jong Kook.)
I'm joining you?
- Empty Heads.
I'm coming, So Min!
They'll never be able to answer
the questions no matter what.
- So Min, we can do it.
- I think...
it's meaningless to play
against them.
- We can disregard them.
- That's right.
So Min, we can do it. Let's do this.
Empty Heads!
- My gosh.
- Empty!
Empty Head So Min
and Empty Head Se Chan.
You ended up with him
after dumping me?
Gosh, you.
What's the point of earning a chance
when you can't answer questions?
(So Min ended up picking
Empty Head instead.)
Empty Head So Min
and Empty Head Se Chan.
Dr. Yoo got new clients.
- It's great.
- Dr. Yoo!
- This is nice.
- That team looks strong.
- Dr. Yoo!
- Dr. Yoo is the best at quizzes.
- That's right.
You'll need to use your knowledge
and wit for your mission.
It's Joint Responsibility Quiz.
The members have played this before.
The theme is "global".
- "Global"?
- I like that!
- I like it.
Each team member
needs to say the syllable...
of the answer. If it's correct,
you'll earn ten points.
(Say the syllable of the answer
in turn and earn 10 points.)
If the answer is "Running Man",
then you'll take turns to say it.
If you say it correctly,
then you'll earn the points.
We can steal
the other teams' answers.
We just need to be witty.
We're pretty witty, right?
- Of course.
- These guys are the worst.
I'll show you how witty I am.
- You're the worst.
- I can just steal your answer.
During the game,
a few balloons will fall
from the back.
One of them has a real sword
for the pop-up pirate.
- That's right.
- Yes!
If the pirate pops out
using that sword,
we'll give you 30 points.
The captains will divide...
the points the team wins.
You can earn up to 200 points
if you do well. You never know.
- This is great.
- I should pick them up well.
Now, change into new vests
and sit over there.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Today's quizzes aren't hard.
Once you call for an answer,
I'll pick a person who can go first.
The first category
is a global figure.
- A figure? Okay, that sounds easy.
- A figure?
- A figure!
- Great!
We'll show you the photo
of a famous global figure,
and you'll tell us their full name.
- Their full name?
- You mean their entire name, right?
Yes, their first and last name.
But it's confusing.
- I'm not good with full names.
- Full names...
Each member will take a turn
to say each syllable.
Call out for an answer first.
Here comes the first one.
- Let me answer.
- He's...
- It's that guy.
- Ki Woong, go ahead.
"Ch".
"Ri".
- "Sn".
- Let me answer.
- Yes, Se Chan.
- "Ch".
- "Ri".
- "S".
- "To".
- You know him, right?
Let me answer!
- Go ahead.
- "Ch".
- They got it.
- "Ri".
"S".
"Hem".
"Ming".
- No!
- Let me answer!
- Jong Kook.
- "Ch".
- "Ri".
- "S".
- "Hem".
- "Wor".
- "T".
- We almost got it.
- Let me answer!
(He got the last syllable wrong.)
- I got it! Let me answer!
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Hee Yeon.
- "Ch".
- "Ri".
- "S".
- "He".
- It's wrong!
- It's "Hem".
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead, Haha.
- "Ch".
- "Ri".
- "S".
- "Hem".
- "Wor".
- "Th". All right.
- Gosh.
It's Chris Hemsworth.
- Great job.
- Good one.
Didn't you just steal our answer?
- What? It was just there.
- You should've said "Hamstring".
Why can't we just pick up
what was already there?
You're practically
taking our answer.
What do you mean?
We know who Chris Hemsworth is.
- You should play better.
- Chris Hemsworth.
So call out
for an answer faster than us.
It's important
to take their answers too.
Here's the next question.
Here it goes.
They're here!
(Randomly dropping balloons)
- They're here!
- What is this?
- Take it.
- Give it to me!
- Is it a real sword?
I should pop it.
- Take it.
- Is it a real sword?
- This is fake.
- Is it real or fake?
- It's fake.
- Pop it.
(This one is real!)
This one is real.
- What were you doing?
- Gosh, I missed that.
- Isn't this the one?
- There are four of us!
This one is fake.
Oh, that's the real sword?
- It might not pop up. Don't worry.
- Stick it in.
- You get 30 points if it pops up.
- It won't pop up.
- We're safe.
- All right.
- It didn't work.
If we get the correct answer,
we get ten points.
If the pirate pops up, we get 30.
- I forgot about the balloons.
- It's going great.
Here's the next question.
Here it goes.
Let me answer! Oh, gosh.
Let me answer!
- Oh, gosh.
- Let me answer!
- "Van".
- "Go".
- Let me answer!
- "Vin".
- Quiet, everyone. What did you say?
- "Cen".
- "T".
- "Van".
- "Go".
- "Gh".
- It is van Gogh, right?
- It's Vincent van Gogh.
(Laughing)
- Hey.
- It's his first time.
I got half of it correct.
(He's happy that he got
just half of it correct.)
- That was unexpected.
- It's all good.
As long as you're happy
to be with your boyfriend.
- It is van Gogh.
- This is great!
- Here's the next question.
- Here they are!
- Se Chan!
- Get them!
(The balloons are dropped.)
(The balloon beast)
- Go get it, Suk Jin!
- Is it the real sword?
- Is it real?
- It is.
- So Min, come here. We got three.
- It's fake.
(So Min, come here. We got three.)
- We got three.
- They brought theirs first.
- One of theirs must be real.
- Here's another one.
- So Min, hurry up.
- That one must be real.
There are four of us,
and we could've gotten
one balloon each!
- I got one, but...
- Why didn't we get any?
We should've gone for it
in the first place.
If we don't earn points here,
we're hopeless.
- Can I stick this in?
- You'll get 30 points.
We get 30 points, right?
It needs to pop up.
- It needs to pop up.
- It'll pop up for sure.
Which slot should I pick?
I hope it just pops out once.
It won't pop up. They'll fail.
They're unlucky with this.
- It won't pop up.
- Please.
- It won't.
Nice!
(Se Chan fails as well.)
- But we had four swords!
- All right!
- That's not the one, right?
- What a shame.
We should get one balloon each!
So Min, let's come up with a plan.
If they get one,
we can steal theirs.
If they pop one, stay next to them
and pick up their sword.
Here's the next question.
- Shout out for an answer.
- Get ready.
Here it goes.
- Here it goes.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Jong Kook.
- Go.
- Go ahead. Three, two, one.
(Time over)
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- "E".
- "Lon".
- "Mu".
- "Sk".
Yes!
(The two Empty Heads
got the answer correct.)
I'm one of many who want to meet
Elon Musk.
I can't believe we got this.
- Thank you.
- I saw his name not long ago.
- Elon Musk!
- You told her, didn't you?
- Not at all.
- No, I heard of him.
- Of course I know him.
- I know who Elon Musk is.
I saw his name
on a show not long ago.
- We were really awesome.
- We were really hot.
- That was so cool.
- We did it.
- You all must acknowledge this.
- Of course.
Here's the next question.
Here it goes.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Jae Suk.
- Who is he?
- I can't remember his name.
- I got it!
- I got it though.
- Let me answer!
I blanked out.
Can we go for it? "E".
Everyone, you need to state
their full name.
- Shin Hyun Joon.
- "La".
I think I got it! Let me answer!
- "Shin"!
- What?
(She confidently says
the answer as Shin Hyun Joon.)
It's Shin Hyun Joon.
- I have no idea.
- It's not Shin Hyun Joon.
- You...
- All right. Let me answer!
Go ahead, Jae Suk.
- "Z".
- "La".
- "Tan".
- "I".
- "B".
- "Ra".
"I".
- Let me answer!
(Let me answer!)
("Zu")
- Let me answer!
- "Zu".
- "La".
(He said "Zu".)
- Let me answer!
- What's wrong with it?
Let me answer. Who should go first?
- Haha.
- Me? "Z".
- "La".
- "Tan".
- "I".
- "B".
- "Ra".
- "Hi".
- "Mo".
- "Vi".
- "C".
- Yes!
- Why was mine wrong?
- He said "Zu".
- But...
- It's "Hi".
- Excuse me. You said "Zu".
- What's wrong with that?
- It's Zulatan Ibrahimovic.
- No, It's Zlatan.
But doesn't that count? No?
- It's Zulatan.
- My gosh.
- Here they are.
(While Suk Jin throws a tantrum,
the balloons are dropped.)
- Get it, Jong Kook!
- Here they are.
Here they are.
- Where did it go?
- Where is it?
- There's nothing in here.
- It's fake.
- I got one.
Is that the real one?
Try this one.
Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- Si Yoon, I...
- I got one.
All right. It didn't pop up.
- It should pop up by now.
- We didn't try the front side.
- I got lucky.
- Stick that one in first.
- It's about time it should pop up.
- Stick it in.
- We need to answer the question.
- You should stick it in first.
- It didn't pop up.
- Great.
- You should stick it in first.
- This is the real deal.
This is the real deal.
I told you to stick it in first!
(I told you to stick it in first!)
I thought I told you
to stick it in first!
How many times did I tell you that?
Jong Kook...
How many times did I tell you
to stick it in first?
- I...
- They had 3, and we had only 1!
You should've stuck ours in
when they couldn't make it pop up!
- There was such a big chance!
- There weren't many slots left.
You did wrong this time.
- Jong Kook was right.
- Seriously.
- You should've stuck it in.
- Why didn't you listen to me?
- Why?
- Why did you do that?
- Why were you waiting?
- I...
- I'm the doctor.
Here's the next question.
- Okay.
Here it goes.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Haha.
- "Syl".
- "Ve".
- "S".
- "Ter".
(Sylvester)
- Let me answer!
- Why you...
- Hey! Unbelievable.
- Let me answer!
Go ahead, Si Yoon.
Let's wait for it.
- "Syl".
- "Ve".
- "S".
- "Ter".
- "Tal".
- "Lone".
- Let me answer!
- She pronounced it wrong!
- It's "Tallone"!
- She said it correctly.
- Sylvester Stallone!
- Stallone!
She said it wrong.
- It's supposed to be "Tallone".
- I said it like that.
This isn't fair.
- But this is...
- She said it wrong.
Who doesn't know Sylvester Stallone?
He's Rambo.
Sylvester Stallone!
Throw the balloons already!
Throw the balloons!
- That's fine.
- If we have a mutual agreement...
- Then it'll be fine.
- They're throwing the balloons.
- All right!
- Where is it?
(Here comes
the balloon beast again.)
- Let go of it. Watch the camera.
- I'm sorry.
- It's fake.
Gosh, I'm so unlucky.
(Meanwhile,
Dr. Yoo got the real sword.)
- I got it.
- This one's real.
(Meanwhile,
Dr. Yoo got the real sword.)
- I got it.
- That one is fake.
- You got it?
- I got it.
- He got it.
Let's pop it up in one blow.
- Let's go.
- It needs to pop up this time.
This one is real.
You have a low possibility
in the beginning.
You got one too?
- Fail.
- That one was close.
- Gosh, this is...
- It'll work.
- There's a low possibility.
- Fail.
- Just stick it in.
Yes!
That was incredible.
I knew you'd make it.
- Just stick it in.
- Yes!
(It popped up!)
- I knew you'd make it.
- This is unbelievable.
Well done, Dr. Yoo!
- Well done, Dr. Yoo!
- Didn't you two fight earlier?
- Great work.
No.
Goodness, Dr. Yoo.
- You two made up.
- We got this.
- Here it goes.
- Please give us another one.
I can't keep my eyes off
of the back. My neck feels stiff.
- Give it to us.
- Here's the next question.
(Next question)
Here it goes.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Ki Woong.
- You know the answer, right?
Let me answer! "Hel".
- What?
- "Hel"?
- Let me answer!
- Are you sure that's the first one?
Isn't it "Nobel"?
- I know it.
- Helicobacter...
- "Tho".
- Excuse me.
Se Chan said he's Helicobacter.
- Let me answer.
- What did you say?
Isn't he Helicobacter?
- Are you serious?
- Go ahead, Jae Suk.
"Tho".
- "Ma".
- "S".
- "E".
- "Di".
- "Son". Yes!
- All right!
- It's Edison.
- Good work.
I thought he was Helicobacter.
- I thought...
- "Helicobacter"?
The team in the first place...
- is still Team Dr. Yoo.
- We're doing great.
Team Song Ji Hyo is in second place.
- We went really easy on them.
- Let's go!
What's our score?
Ten points.
What did you say?
You got Elon Musk right.
Why don't you let them go first?
- Let us go first.
- I have a question.
- It's not that.
- Why won't you look at us?
You guys...
You guys called Thomas Edison
as Helicobacter.
Why won't he look at us?
I can't believe... Here they are!
(Right then,
the balloons are dropped.)
- Here they are!
Here's one! Darn it!
So Min, come here!
So Min, let's go!
There's a low possibility
in the beginning.
You guys
are fully enjoying your date.
- There's a low possibility.
- Look. Over here.
- Stick it in.
- In 1, 2, 3.
They're having such a good time.
- Are you on a date or what?
- Let's try one more.
- What's going on?
- They're holding hands.
- Are you cutting a cake or what?
Are you cutting a cake?
They're having so much fun.
- It's the last one.
- They have so many.
It's the last one.
Excuse me!
Can you hand that over to us?
We'll give you ten points.
- Sorry?
- We'll give you ten points.
Let's just take their ten points.
- Okay. We'll take it.
- All right.
- Give us ten points.
Okay.
- This is our only chance.
- At least we earned something.
If we earn ten points with this...
Are you listening, Hani?
Why are you looking at So Min
while saying that?
Hey, I'm So Min.
Hani, why are you back there?
- I bought this with ten points.
- I feel like it'll pop up.
It's worth 100 dollars.
It shouldn't pop up
so that this will be fun.
Please don't pop up.
Suk Jin, you need to make it pop.
- Kwang Soo! Give me your energy!
- I hope it doesn't pop up.
Give me your energy, Kwang Soo!
Isn't he strange? He's asking
Kwang Soo for his energy.
Kwang Soo, tell me
which slot to stick this in.
Which slot? Near the ear?
- The right one or the left?
- The left one.
- The right ear?
- No, the left ear.
The left one? Got it.
You're only listening to Jae Suk.
Suk Jin, you're only listening
to Jae Suk.
You're not listening to Kwang Soo.
Where is it? It's here, right?
The left ear.
Kwang Soo is pulling a prank on you.
(It popped up!)
What was that?
This is insane!
(Kwang Soo is here!)
I thought Kwang Soo
was pulling a prank on you.
I can't believe it.
How is this possible?
- Wow.
- Seriously.
- It was...
- Kwang Soo told me.
Thank you so much, Kwang Soo.
He only stuck one in.
That was...
- So Min.
- Throw us the balloons.
So Min, come here.
- What are you doing?
- We give up on the quiz.
- We'll only catch the balloons.
- Don't mind us.
Let's play it.
We need to stay on our toes.
Here's the next question.
(Shohei Ohtani,
a popular MLB baseball player)
- I...
- Let me answer.
- Who is it?
- Go ahead, Haha.
- This is driving me crazy.
- "A".
- Let me answer.
- "Oh".
- "Ta".
- "Sik".
- "Ohtasik"?
- Go ahead, Ki Woong.
- "Oh".
- "Ta".
- "Ru".
- Darn it!
- My gosh!
- Go ahead, Se Chan.
- "Oh".
- "Ta".
- "Ni".
(Ohtani)
"Ku"? He's not Korean?
- Go ahead, Jong Kook.
- "Oh".
- "Ta".
- "Ni".
"Ku"!
My gosh. What is he, yakiniku?
My goodness.
- Let me answer!
- I don't know him.
- "Oh".
- "Ta".
- "Ni".
- "Sho".
- "He".
- "I".
It's Shohei Ohtani.
(This is driving me crazy!)
Look at Hee Yeon.
Did you think he's Ohtaniku?
- It's Shohei.
- Shohei. That's right.
- I know him.
- It's Shohei Ohtani.
Hey, throw the balloons!
I thought it was It's Shorei Ohtani.
Shohei!
(They begin a ritual
to call for balloons.)
- Throw the balloons.
- Give us the next question.
Here's the next question.
Bring the balloons.
I got them.
(The balloons are dropped
just in time.)
- Hey!
- It's the real one!
No, it's fake.
It's fake!
Hey!
Did you get one?
It's mine! It's over.
- Did you get one?
- It didn't work.
- I got two more.
- Pop up!
- Please...
- It won't pop up.
Pop up!
(It popped up!)
(They earned the points by giving up
on the quiz.)
Se Chan, we did it!
- Good job.
- We did it!
Se Chan, we did it!
- They caught up right away.
- Can you focus more?
- We're doing fine.
- We're doing great.
- I should've caught one.
All right. The second category...
is a global movie.
- All right!
- It's a movie.
There are so many.
- We're good since we got Ki Woong.
- Yes.
- Let's do this!
- I watched a lot of movies.
We'll show you the poster
of a famous global movie,
- and you'll guess its title.
- My gosh.
It'll be easy.
- You'll take turns to say it.
- Let's play it.
- So Min, you're an actress.
- Ready.
Here it goes.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Jong Kook.
- "Sa".
- "Vi".
- "Ng".
- "Pri".
- "Vate".
- "Ry".
- "An".
- Come here!
- They got it again.
Watch how well I do!
Why is he going that far?
How could you...
How was that?
(These two men are happy about
"Saving Private Ryan".)
- Okay.
- I will watch out for the balloons.
- I give up. No.
- Look at the questions.
- I have no chance.
- Here comes the question.
(Ms. Empty Head is addicted
to a big break.)
- Here come the balloons.
- Grab one!
(The balloons are dropped!)
There are no swords.
So Min, come here.
- So Min, come here.
- Did you get one?
- Let's get 30 points.
- Let's stick to this method.
- We don't need questions.
- They are winning with that method.
- There is no other way.
- Here I go.
- Go.
(She succeeded in one go!)
(Focusing on the balloons
was a big success.)
Unbelievable.
For goodness' sake.
- Let's get back up.
- We can do it.
This is good. Come on.
Let's go.
(The masters of balloons
are winning.)
All right.
- Let's go.
(Let's go!)
(A good example
of forced enthusiasm)
Let's go.
Jae Suk.
(He experiences
zero gravity once again.)
Let's go.
(People would think
that he wants to be an astronaut.)
- Let's go.
- Shall we do something?
- Are you Jae Suk's dad?
- No.
You keep playing with him.
- Let's cheer up.
- It's like an amusement park.
Let's go.
Let's go. Lift me up.
What are they doing?
- We can do it.
- Let's go.
The last category is...
the capital.
- The capital. Okay.
- That's great.
I don't know many capitals.
Listen to the country name...
and say one syllable of the capital
at a time.
Are you good with capitals?
I know most of them.
Okay. Somalia.
Let me answer.
So Min.
- That's...
- So.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
I heard it on the news.
- So.
- Let me answer.
All right. So Min.
- So.
- Hey!
- Let me answer.
Jong Kook.
- I don't know.
- Let me answer.
Ji Hyo.
Let me answer.
- Ki Woong.
- Let me answer.
So.
Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- Mo.
(Se Chan gets a chance.)
Mo.
- Let me answer.
- What is it?
Mo.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- Mo.
- Ga.
- Di.
- Shu.
- Yes.
- It's the title of a recent movie.
The one about the Somali Civil War.
- Mogadishu.
- The movie.
The movie.
Hey.
- Mogadishu.
- I even watched the movie.
So Min is a total Empty Head.
- You know the movie, right?
- Go and watch the movie.
It got over two million viewers.
- I was too busy.
- Mogadishu.
- Good job.
- My goodness.
- Let's go.
- Do it for Ki Woong.
Do it for Ki Woong.
(The amusement park opens again.)
Let's go.
(Ki Woong gets
the unique experience.)
(Haha's tornado spin!)
Okay.
Let's go.
The result is out.
(The result
of Joint Responsibility Quiz)
First place is...
- Team Dr. Yoo.
- Okay.
The points he can distribute...
are 220 points.
(He can distribute 220 points.)
- How much will each member get?
- Dr. Yoo.
- About 50 points, I suppose.
- Good work.
Second place is...
(Second place)
Team Ahn Hee Yeon with 120 points.
Okay.
The remaining 2 teams
used to be 3rd place together.
But thanks to ten points
from Suk Jin,
- Team Jeon So Min is third place.
- That's right.
- Team Song Ji Hyo is fourth place.
- Okay.
All right.
Team Ahn Hee Yeon, 110 points.
Team Jeon So Min, 90 points.
Team Song Ji Hyo, 80 points.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Let's distribute the points.
The captains need to do well.
We worked hard like 220V.
- We are the best.
- Yes.
Jae Suk.
You won't be exempt from the penalty
unless you take first place.
- If you place third,
- Let's go.
I will pick you for the penalty.
The 1st and 2nd places
will be exempt from the penalty.
Hold on. Why would you pick me?
- What?
- Why would you pick me?
You are an eyesore.
You are too good.
It's his ploy
to keep you from giving us points.
- We are at the bottom anyway.
- We have nothing to lose.
- We are vindictive.
- Jae Suk, you will go first.
- Show us.
- I divided the points equally.
So 190 points for me
and 10 points for everyone else.
(Jae Suk, 190 points;
Everyone else, 10 points)
So 190 points for me
and 10 points for everyone else.
(He gave 10 points
to everyone else.)
He doesn't disappoint.
He is a great host.
- You could have given us 20 points.
- I gave you 10 points.
Dr. Yoo, you are the best.
- I divided the points equally.
- It was the perfect operation.
Next comes Ji Hyo.
I divided the points evenly.
- So 40 points and 40 points.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Really?
- Hani.
- Let's go.
I went with 90 points and 20 points.
- Okay.
- What is up with that?
Hey.
I went with 32 points and 58 points.
- Hey, So Min.
- Hey.
Even So Min gave 32 points.
- That leaves me with zero points.
- You are too much.
You are no longer in the negative.
- Okay.
- Thus, the distribution is over.
Now comes
the last team member exchange.
Captain Ahn Hee Yeon,
you can exchange Suk Jin
with a member of your choice.
- This is the last game, right?
- Only one game remains.
I will go with the strongest member.
- That's me. Okay.
- She is ambitious.
Kim Jong Kook.
Okay.
We don't know
what the last game will be like.
Suk Jin keeps coming back
to this team.
I am back...
- because the lease ended.
- We don't know what it will be.
- The lease ended.
- Okay.
- Welcome back.
- All right.
Have you been well?
- Welcome back.
- I am back from that team.
So Min, you are next.
I choose...
- Si Yoon.
- Okay.
- Se Chan, go to that team.
Ji Hyo, you are up.
You can exchange Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Why did she choose Se Chan?
I am sorry, Haha.
That means Haha will stay
with this team.
Okay.
- What is up with you?
- We will take good care of you.
- Take good care of me.
- I will do that.
- For goodness' sake.
- Let's move.
- Okay.
- So Min.
What is this?
I like what I see.
(It looks like the last mission
requires brute strength.)
It requires strength.
I am done for.
In the last mission
of You Raise a Man Up Race,
the team members' strength
is the key.
The game is Hand Fencing on the Log.
- Fencing.
- It will go like this.
This is the last mission.
Dr. Yoo's team...
has four men with low self-esteem.
Four men with low self-esteem.
Low self-esteem?
The three of them fit
the description.
- The three of them do.
- I can't believe it.
The game is in line with reality.
- You don't know real men.
- I can't believe it.
I have three children. Forget it.
I will say this.
We have 3, 2, and 1 children
respectively.
- Keep that in mind.
- One, two, and three children.
The remaining six members
will be a team.
- What?
- Really?
I will give you the rules.
How will that work?
You will play 1-on-1 hand fencing
on the log.
We will count the number of times
you touch the opponent's face.
If you make the opponent fall,
you will gain 20 points right away.
If you make the opponent fall?
If you feel like you will lose,
it might be better
to go down with the opponent.
- That's right.
- Go down with the opponent.
- Okay.
- Decide on the order and tell us.
Okay. Let's go, six of us.
All right.
I should self-destruct.
There are two women.
Oh, there are three women.
Hold on. Suk Jin.
Why are you glancing over at me?
Do you want to go against me?
You, Ji Hyo, or Hani.
- One of the three.
- Then go first.
Okay. I will go first.
The first match is
So Min versus Suk Jin.
Put paint on your hands
and go up on the log.
You actually kept your words.
So Min, don't you need this?
You have no fear.
There is no problem.
It will be an easy match.
(They are confident
about going against each other.)
So Min.
(Face-touching, 1 point;
Making the opponent fall, 20 points)
The staff members will count.
If you make the opponent fall,
you gain 20 points.
- Seok Sam.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
Get ready.
Set, go.
Suk Jin, why are you so excited?
Why are you so excited?
I envy Suk Jin.
(Slapping)
- He slapped hard.
- He slapped too hard.
He slapped hard.
So Min.
Just self-destruct.
So Min wants to beat Suk Jin.
(So Min got attacked by her rival.)
That startled me.
I didn't hit you hard.
So Min is a bit annoyed.
She is annoyed.
- Two points.
- So Min.
So Min.
(Slapping)
Suk Jin is the worst.
What is wrong with him?
- My goodness.
- How did he win?
I heard a loud sound.
- Are you okay?
- I heard a loud sound.
Are you okay?
- I am okay.
- Are you okay?
- Suk Jin is the worst.
- He is the worst.
- He is good at the game.
- I didn't slap hard.
The next player is Si Yoon.
Let's go.
- I have handprints...
- Suk Jin.
- on my face.
- Go up on the log.
I will beat all subsequent players.
Now, watch Si Yoon beat up...
Seo Jin.
Si Yoon, slap him a lot.
The next player is Si Yoon.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- Suk Jin, get in there.
- It gets on your clothes.
- Show me your left-hand skills.
(Suk Jin gained confidence
after a win.)
I am sorry.
Show us your superpower.
Ji power.
Will you self-destruct?
- I can grab him.
- That's right.
- Jujitsu.
- Ji power.
- That's good.
- Did you splatter paint?
Did you splatter paint?
(They splatter paint to each other.)
What is going on?
They are splattering paint.
It's like laser.
(Splattering)
Ji power.
- That's it.
- Good.
- Good luck.
- You haven't won a point yet.
(Sputtering)
(Si Yoon scores right away.)
You need to attack now. Keep going.
It's hard to reach the face.
Si Yoon is good.
(His orange teeth shine.)
It's funny because he got some paint
on his teeth.
(The man with orange teeth
keeps getting attacked.)
(After getting beaten up,
he goes down with Si Yoon.)
Good job.
- Good job.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Who is next?
- Ji power.
I did pretty well, right?
The next match is
Ahn Hee Yeon versus Haha.
Can you use both hands?
- I thought we were using one hand.
- That's right.
She got paint on both hands too.
Let's use two hands in this match.
Okay.
Will you be okay?
- Get ready.
- Haha.
Haha, allow her some points.
- You are a man.
- You are going against Hee Yeon.
The man of Mapo-gu
should allow her three hits.
- Three hits.
- What should I do?
You should allow her three hits.
He looks happy.
Go ahead.
- What should I do?
- It's okay. It's a game.
Slap him. It's a game.
Don't slap me hard.
Just put paint on my face.
Don't go for a full swing.
Allow her some points.
You are doing great, Haha.
- Go.
- My goodness.
- That's good.
- Okay.
My goodness.
You are doing great.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Come on.
- He is such a middle-aged man.
Haha seems like Kim Heung Gook.
(He even has the mustache.)
My goodness.
(He is so annoying.)
- He is like a neighbor.
- A neighbor.
(A neighbor who is shadowboxing
at the water fountain)
(She clenches her teeth
and sets out to strike back.)
(Her entire face gets painted.)
(The onlookers love it.)
(Artist Haha created a masterpiece.)
He painted her whole face.
"Avatar".
(She attempts to strike back.)
(Team Other Members, Team Dr. Yoo)
(She keeps
getting her face painted.)
- Go down with him. There you go.
- All right.
(Self-destruction)
- There you go.
- This is too much.
Good job.
That was funny.
(This man had fun with blue paint.)
It's my turn, right?
I...
- Hani, you will make it big.
- You will make it big.
You became a Smurf.
Hani, you will make it big.
- You look so cute.
- You always score a meme.
(She succeeded in scoring a meme
on Running Man today.)
Se Chan versus Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- It will be a fun match.
Se Chan, go for the mouth.
That's a good tip.
- It's sticking out.
- The closest facial feature.
All right.
- You scooped up paint.
- That's right.
Hey. You scooped up paint.
You scooped up paint.
Get me more paint. Pink one.
(The protruding mouths begin
the match.)
Get ready.
(Hoo!)
It will be fun to watch.
(Men with the protruding mouth
start off noisily as always.)
They won't need to reach far
since their mouths are protruding.
- I know.
- You will hit the mouth anyway.
Even if you swing wildly,
you will hit the mouth.
(Putting paint)
(He throws the paint
he carried in his hand.)
What is that?
Is that snot?
(Team Other Members, Team Dr. Yoo)
(Se Chan scores
while the green snot distracts him.)
Watch out for a counterattack.
- You are doing well.
- Watch out.
They are tired now.
There you go.
(Dodging)
(Team Other Members, Team Dr. Yoo)
(Slapping)
(They scored at the same time.)
- A counterattack.
- The counterattack worked.
What is that?
My goodness.
The counterattack worked.
They are so ugly.
(The counterattack
leaves Jae Suk looking ugly.)
(Team Other Members, Team Dr. Yoo)
(Rubbing)
(Slapping)
(Team Other Members, Team Dr. Yoo)
(Thus began the slapping party.)
(They score points without a break.)
Jae Suk turned green.
They became so dirty.
He is Shrek.
(The gum color
and grasshopper color suit them.)
(Their looks are beyond salvation.)
Se Chan, grab his legs.
(They go down together.)
- How many points did they earn?
- What?
I wonder.
(They earned points
and lost their clean faces.)
Goblins.
They are goblins.
Both of you earned
the highest number of points.
Jae Suk, we earned
Okay.
What will they do
about their faces...
(Gosh!)
The next match is
Ji Hyo versus Ki Woong.
Se Chan is a mafia member.
His face is red.
No.
I am not a mafia member.
He looks like a sweet potato.
Let's begin the match.
A sweet potato.
Let's go.
- Come on.
- Show us how scary you are.
Let's go.
Ki Woong, don't go easy on her.
Go in there.
How dare you!
(Giggling)
- He is really handsome.
- Finish her off.
- They are having a good time.
- Why did it become romantic?
Hey.
(They were having a good time,)
(then he pushed her off.)
Hey, that was funny.
Hey!
That was the worst.
She couldn't hit him once.
(Ji Hyo couldn't hit him once.)
- Hey!
- I am sorry.
Good job.
- He kept his face clean.
- I am sorry.
- Good job.
Now comes the last player,
Jong Kook.
- Here comes the boss.
- Go.
Jong Kook, beat him.
Avenge us.
- Jong Kook.
- Give him the whole container.
All right.
- Will you use the left hand?
- Go.
Currently,
Team Dr. Yoo has 149 points...
and Team Other Members has
142 points.
- Okay.
- You have 142 points.
You should slap him more.
- Slap him many times.
- This match will decide the result.
That's right.
- My goodness.
- Hey, Ki Woong.
(Ki Woong will win
if he goes down with Jong Kook.)
Let's go.
- You need to get over seven points.
- You need to hit him.
I should have put paint
on my right hand.
Don't give Jong Kook a lot of time.
You need to go down with him.
That's the way we win.
Let's go.
You can do it.
In any case...
(Nervous)
You can get dental implants anyway.
Okay. That's good.
Smack him across the face,
Jong Kook.
He brought so much paint.
Should I shoot some paint?
I will shoot some paint.
Go.
- That's good.
- Ki Woong is so competitive.
Ki Woong.
I have a longer reach.
- Come on. Show us a great scene.
- Go.
- Hey.
- It's a chance to slap someone.
- Just knock him out.
If he gets knocked out,
he will get so much screen time.
That's good.
- One hit.
Go.
Let's score one point at a time.
- He is intimidated.
- It seems that way.
- Don't get intimidated.
- Keep going.
You got this, Jong Kook.
- All right.
- Go.
- He seems fast.
- Touch his face.
- Come on.
- Don't let him win.
Intimidate him with a jab.
Just knock him out with a punch.
Look at their feet.
I like how they are fighting
with their legs too.
Did your feet get caught?
It's the other way around,
but it looks that way.
(Ki Woong wants to beat Jong Kook.)
That's good.
It's like the war of nerves
at a boxing match.
He is measuring the distance.
Mayweather versus Pacquiao.
He is going in.
(Hitting)
(Team Other Members, Team Dr. Yoo)
(Chuckling)
My teeth...
- Ki Woong is startled.
- He is startled.
- That isn't blood, right?
- That isn't blood.
- Ki Woong is startled.
- He is startled.
- That isn't blood, right?
- That isn't blood.
- It looks like blood.
(He got paint on his front teeth.)
I think I lost my memories
for two seconds.
You should self-destruct.
- Self-destruct.
- You don't hold a chance.
You don't hold a chance.
- Five points.
Self-destruct. Don't think about...
hitting him once.
Let me hit him once.
Jong Kook, slap him multiple times.
(Thus began
Millstone Guy's challenge!)
Duck your head.
Go in there.
Don't think of him as a person.
(Reaching)
(Jong Kook loses his balance!)
(Will Millstone Guy
succeed in striking back?)
My goodness.
- We lost.
- We won.
- Jong Kook.
(Team Dr. Yoo won.)
- That was perfect.
- That was nice.
- We won.
- All right.
We won.
- That was nice.
- The match was going well.
We won.
- Did we win?
- We won.
Thus, Team Dr. Yoo won.
(Team Dr. Yoo won.)
- Good job. Okay.
- We won.
What happens now?
Now, Team Dr. Yoo...
Okay.
- You can distribute 120 points.
- Did you say 120 points?
As for the rest, each team
can distribute 30 points.
(Each team
can distribute 30 points.)
Jae Suk.
- All right.
- Here are the current rankings.
Let's avoid the bottom.
(Si Yoon and Se Chan
are the bottom two.)
- You have 120 points.
- Yes. Give us 30 points each.
Even if you do that,
you will be in the first place.
- We need to avoid the bottom.
- Okay.
- They have 30 points per team.
- I just need to be 1st place.
- You just need to be first place.
- That will happen anyway.
It's meaningless.
- Jae Suk.
- Do we get 30 points?
Let's check So Min
and Si Yoon's points first.
(They check the points
So Min distributed.)
They got 5 points
and 25 points respectively.
So Min got 5 points
and Si Yoon got 25 points.
- Hey.
- I can't believe So Min.
That's not the way
you treated Se Chan.
- So Min.
- Still...
Next.
I gave 0 points to myself
and 30 points to Se Chan.
Okay.
- Really? Why?
- Why?
Why is everyone going crazy?
Let's see what happens.
Hee Yeon.
I distributed the points evenly.
- Gosh, thank you.
- Both members got 15 points.
Jong Kook won't be at the bottom.
This time, I gave 30 points
to each member.
All the members got 30 points.
That's the right thing to do.
- You're really cool.
- Okay.
You're Dr. Yoo.
Look at the Mafia and his red face.
All right. Keep talking.
What?
- Did Haha just talk to us?
- Yes.
- Did you talk to us?
- He just said,
"Look at the Mafia
and his red face." Okay.
You must feel at ease.
I'll announce the results now.
Number 9 and 10 will get a penalty,
and number 1 and 2 are exempted.
(Number 9 and 10 will get a penalty,
and number 1 and 2 are exempted.)
(Did the 4 members at the bottom
manage to change their fate?)
All right. Here are the results.
Okay.
I'm so relieved.
- Ki Woong is number eight.
- Okay.
Si Yoon gave way to him.
So what do we do now?
First, you should pick a person
to get a penalty with you.
But I can't pick Jae Suk or Ji Hyo.
- That's right.
- I can pick the rest of them.
I see. Is that so?
- You two should talk about it.
- I know we should.
What did you say earlier?
What about the Mafia?
You looked cute.
That's what I meant.
Number three must be
most disappointed now.
- Right?
- I think so.
It will be fun
if you pick number three.
We ate together.
And we did things together.
We planned things together.
I can't stop thinking of the people
who disappointed me.
Those who gave me hard times.
Si Yoon said that
when we ate together earlier.
He kept saying
that the Mafia game was killing him.
- I was humiliated.
- Right.
I was really scared too.
I was so anxious.
Si Yoon and I made a firm decision.
I see.
We will call the name then.
In 1, 2, and 3.
(Who will get a penalty with them?)
- Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook)
(Shaking his head)
- He was so...
- Nice shot!
During the Mafia Game...
- But...
- He talked too much.
It was suffocating.
Nice shot.
So Si Yoon, Se Chan,
and Jong Kook will get a penalty.
And today's penalty is necessary
for men with low self-esteem.
To build up your lower body,
you'll do 100 squats.
- Okay!
- Jong Kook likes it.
- It's good for Jong Kook.
- He loves it.
You'll do 100 squats
before you go home.
(Squats? Okay!)
- It's good for Jong Kook.
- He loves it.
Look, Mr. Director.
It's supposed to be a penalty.
Is this a penalty?
(Jong Kook is getting a penalty,)
(but it's not
a real penalty for him.)
- This is what Jong Kook likes.
- I can't believe this.
- What is going on?
- It's not a penalty for him.
He loves it.
The lower body is
important for a man.
- My goodness.
- Without the penalty,
he will work out anyway.
So the three of them
will get the penalty.
The rest of you may go home now.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay. Squats.
Shall we begin? Ready.
- Is it 100 squats?
- Yes.
All right. Don't go too fast.
You should feel your muscles.
- All right.
- Let's not waste the time.
- Make the most out of it.
- Okay.
You know what I mean.
- Bye.
- This isn't just a penalty.
- Make the most out of it.
- Work out the lower body.
That's right. Let's do this then.
- One.
- Two.
(He's absorbing the energy
from the beginning.)
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
Six. That's right.
- Seven.
- Eight.
Nine.
- Will you slow down?
- Ten.
Slow down.
Hurry and do two squats. One more.
Okay. Let's do it again. One.
- One.
- One. Two.
Two.
- Three.
- Good.
- Jong Kook, I'm reaching my limit.
I'm reaching my physical limit.
- Why did you call his name?
- Jong Kook, please.
(Under Jong Kook's direction,
Se Chan is getting a penalty alone.)
- Eight.
- My legs are about to burst.
- They are about to burst.
- Seven.
My goodness.
Help me.
Ten. Again.
- One.
- My goodness.
- My head hurts.
- Two.
- My gosh.
(It's the new-style forced squat.)
- Three.
- All right.
- Four.
- Gosh.
- Five.
- Stop him.
- Six.
- Now.
Seven. Eight.
- Ten.
- Jong Kook.
- Five.
- My back hurts.
- Six.
- My back really hurts.
Seven. Eight.
- Nine.
- Oh dear.
Ten.
- We have ten squats left.
- Wait, Jong Kook.
Hang on.
Why did you pick me? Why?
- All right. One.
- Hurry.
- Two. Three.
- My friend.
Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
- ten.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Well done.
- I'm honored.
- Okay.
- That was really nice.
Gosh, it feels great.
I wish we would get
this penalty every day.
(The short
but intense penalty is over.)
(Case Number 1617,
Interrogation Room 1)
(Case Number 4075,
Interrogation Room 2)
That's what I always do.
- Making fun of So Min.
- Look at that.
That's because you're the Mafia.
(There's the Mafia
among the 7 of them.)
(There's only one clue.)
(The Mafia has explanations
for his actions.)
I think I know who it is.
(It's Interrogation Room 1 again.)
- I'm going to...
- Why are you upset?
(The interrogation begins to dig
into their abnormal behaviors.)
I said it's not me.
(With the member-specific
interrogations,)
(the Mafia starts
revealing its identity.)
- That's the mission, right?
- Hang on.
(They keep closing in on the Mafia.)
Let's say it's me. I don't care.
(This is it. You're the Mafia.)
(Is it me?)
(And you're trying to frame me.)
(Burping)
(Catch the Mafia,
Running Man in Chaos)