(A shabby container
located in a remote place)
(It used to foster elite athletes
who swept many competitions.)
(But now it is covered with dust
with no people.)
(It's called "Tiger Gym".)
(Trainer Kook dreams
of reviving the gym here alone.)
(He even handed out leaflets
on the verge of going bankrupt.)
(Recruiting new members.
Tiger Gym is all free.)
People should work out.
They shouldn't be like this.
What are they thinking?
They all should be disciplined.
The gym is in danger
of going bankrupt now.
They should come here...
and become a member
of the national team.
But will they join the national team
if they work out here?
What event would it be?
What would they play
in the national team?
- You train athletes of all kinds.
- Really?
Actually, all kinds of sports
have something in common.
(He tries to focus on
his character.)
Gosh, what time is it now?
Why isn't anyone coming?
(The door is open!)
(Slamming the door)
What was that?
(Peeping)
- Why?
- He glared at me.
(The eyes of a poisonous snake)
Our eyes met.
- Who?
- Jong Kook.
He stares at me sharply.
- It was really sharp.
- I'm serious.
I had no choice
but to close the door.
(The old member plucks up
his courage and opens it again.)
- Hey, Trainer Kook.
- Hang on.
- "Hey, Trainer Kook?"
- He's so scary.
- My gosh.
- The thing is...
What time do you think it is now?
It is 10:12 a.m.
- Stand in a line.
- Hello.
- In a line.
- Today...
- Stand in a row.
- What is all this?
- Is this for your YouTube channel?
- We're in trouble. It'll be tough.
(It is expected to be
an exhausting day.)
- Is this "Gym Jong Kook"?
- Stay quiet.
- By the way...
- My gosh.
Hey.
Come on in and stand in a row.
(The man tried to escape,
but he got caught right away.)
- I need to go.
- Just stand here.
I feel uncomfortable
from the beginning.
- I'm tired.
- This is a gym.
It's just...
- By the way...
- What kind of gym is this?
What?
I want to go somewhere else.
Where do you want to go?
- This is...
- You're a member here.
The old man is not good at skits.
- Hey!
- Listen.
What time is it now? You can't join
the national team like this.
Who are you, by the way?
Are you a gangster or what?
Are you a trainer?
He wants you to come close.
(He shakes his finger at him.)
- Hey.
- He wants you to come close.
- Why?
- How dare you...
In the morning...
- Who are you?
- What do you think you are?
(The man in a blue cap
stands in his way.)
- Excuse me.
- You stay out of this.
Who are you?
- You're one of us.
- How dare you...
- Attention.
- He's being cheeky.
- Look straight ahead.
- Look forward.
- Okay.
- Put your legs apart...
- at the shoulder width.
- Spread your legs.
- Do squats.
- My thighs still hurt.
- Just do it.
Do squats.
- One.
- My goodness.
- Just do it.
- Two.
- Continue. Three.
- Just do it.
- Four.
Five, six... My goodness.
Can he beat me?
Just continue.
- Go.
- Hurry.
- Seven.
- Go further down.
Put yourself together. Get a grip.
- Focus.
- Eight, nine,
- ten.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- Go back to your spot.
What do you guys think you are?
Why do you keep meddling?
I've been a member here
for a long time.
"Keep meddling?"
They are old members of our gym.
- I see.
- Hey.
I'm an old member,
and he's just an old fart.
(An old member, an old fart)
An old fart?
Is he an old fart?
Isn't he an old fossil?
- An old fart?
- He's an old fart.
What time do you think it is now?
You can't join
the national team like this.
- The national team?
- Yes.
- Will we join the national team?
- Wait.
The oldest member here...
is 56 years old.
A member
of the national gate ball team.
He can join
the national gate ball team.
- The national team?
- For what?
What event?
Mental strength is as important
as physical strength.
- Okay.
- You should be punctual.
You can't be late.
Excuse me.
Sometimes we can be late.
Aren't you being too harsh?
- What?
- It doesn't happen a lot.
Come forward.
- Come forward.
- Go forward.
- What?
- He is older than you,
but you should discipline him
when you need to.
- Don't spare the rod.
- Okay.
Attention. Look straight ahead
and do squats.
I can do squats.
- What are you doing?
- What was that?
What is he doing?
I can do squats.
(Moving his pelvis back and forth)
- What are you doing?
- What's that? Why is it so slow?
Why does it look strange?
- He got a penalty yesterday.
- Do squats.
Who'd do squats like that?
You're still vigorous.
Squats for your health.
- Love.
- Happiness.
- Stop it and go back to your place.
- American squats.
Okay. Return to your spot.
And about you two.
I heard...
- What?
- you two danced together yesterday.
These two.
You danced to "Rollin'".
(The members had an online
fan meeting the previous day.)
(They showed
some group performances...)
(as well as various
cover performances.)
We danced to "When We Disco".
- Hey.
- I see.
All right. You need to warm up
before working out.
- All of a sudden?
- It's a cardio exercise.
I want you two to show us the dance.
- All of a sudden?
- Out of the blue?
Yes.
What's with this gym?
- All of a sudden?
- Because you need to warm up.
So Min seemed very confident.
All right. Go ahead.
Dance together.
(An automatic response)
They're so good.
- Gosh, I hate that.
- They dance so well.
Good.
Good dance.
(They have
provocative glaring eyes.)
(Disco in perfect harmony)
- Look at them.
- They are really good.
(Disco in perfect harmony)
- They are good.
- They look so confident.
Isn't this nice?
Look. This is a cardio exercise.
They dance so well.
Done.
(The special performance is over.)
That was amazing.
This is a good cardio exercise.
You should warm up.
Dance to "Rollin'" now.
(He summons Ji Hyo
who danced to "Rollin'".)
She danced pretty well.
- There you go.
(This is her cover of "Rollin'",
"Jollin'".)
(After hesitating a little,
she starts dancing.)
Creaking.
Her body is...
Her body is being warmed up.
You're good.
(She dances with a demure smile
on her face.)
This is nice.
Ji Hyo, you're great.
The stingray dance.
There's the stingray.
(A stingray shows up.)
Gosh, this is so...
My goodness.
- She's cute.
- They're dancing together.
I can tell she memorized the moves.
Okay.
The trainer thinks
you're really lovely.
(The trainer thinks
you're really lovely.)
The trainer thinks
you're really lovely.
What's going on?
- It's not like that.
- When Ji Hyo danced like this,
- he found her really adorable.
- No.
You made me dance
because you wanted to see it.
I'm not sure if they're warmed up,
but I do feel better now.
He loves her so much.
The trainer loves it.
I feel better.
There's something going on
between them.
He admitted it.
It did make me feel better.
You find her so lovely.
What?
Isn't that true?
That's enough.
I just saw it myself.
He says he saw it.
- Jae Suk says he saw it.
- Stop it.
- I don't know what will happen.
- What do you not know?
I'm just...
I saw him...
- smile from ear to ear.
- I find her adorable,
but I'll find you dead.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
All right then.
- Now, Suk Jin...
- He was good too.
You should do something.
- He danced to "Summer Ocean Again".
- "Summer Ocean Again".
He danced to "Summer Ocean Again".
I was really surprised.
Is this a talent show or what?
There you go.
Start.
He's cute.
(Smiling)
My goodness.
- He's good.
- This is nice.
- This is exciting.
- Good.
(His dance moves make
everyone want to dance together.)
This is nice.
He looks so healthy.
We wish you all the best.
All right.
This is exciting.
Great. Okay.
Korean culture is the best.
- Nice.
- Korean culture is the best.
- I love Korean culture.
- This is nice.
That was great.
- You did a good job.
- Suk Jin.
- Does it have moves like this?
- Sure.
- Does it?
- I came up with it myself.
- That means stars?
- Yes.
You're really good.
Thanks to you, we're all warmed up.
- We're warmed up.
- Before working out,
we're all warmed up,
and the joints are healthier now.
This is nice.
"Summer Ocean Again" is
perfect for warm-up.
- Someone's coming.
- What?
(The door opens,
and someone shows up.)
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- It's Mi Joo.
- There's Young Ji.
And Sang Jun.
(The 3 new members are
in Tiger Gym.)
My goodness.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Sang Jun.
- Hello.
- Hi, Sang Jun.
- Hi.
- Sang Jun.
Hello.
- You look like catfish.
- What are you talking about?
I can tell how things will go today.
Now that I see the three of them,
I can tell what it will be like.
- This is all about laughter.
- It should be exciting.
I know what it will be like.
- We saw this, so we came here.
- We came because it's free.
- You saw the leaflet.
- Yes, I did.
Hey, Sang Jun.
Mi Joo and Young Ji...
- became stars with our show.
- That's right.
- Don't you think so?
- They are very grateful.
It's like we have
two monstrous rookies here.
Two monstrous rookies and a monster.
- He's a real monster.
- A monster.
By the way, I think...
Se Chan brings
a lot of his friends to our show.
My gosh. You...
I just realized...
- he brings a lot of his friends.
- Did you bring him here?
I did?
- I had no idea.
- I did it for you.
- I bet he recommended you.
- Go further down.
- All right.
- I knew it.
He had no reason to join our show.
But he...
- He joined us for no reason.
- Bow lower.
We can have Sang Jun on our show,
but it doesn't feel right that he's
here with Young Ji and Mi Joo.
- They don't seem to mix well.
- You should do a good job.
All right. I'd like you
to introduce yourselves.
- Okay.
- Young Ji.
I heard a video of Jong Kook doing
weightlifting gets high views.
So I came back...
before the aftereffect of
Suk Jin's vaccination is gone.
I'm Rapper Lee Young Ji.
(Young Ji came back
before Suk Jin's 2nd shot.)
Hello.
I used to be an idol artist...
I mean, I was an idol trainee,
but I had nothing else to do...
- She's a comedienne.
- So I became a comedienne.
- Is she a comedienne?
- Yes.
- She's a comedienne?
- She is.
- She's a monster in variety shows,
- She's a monster.
but she's also a monster
in the world of empty heads.
- Seriously?
- She's unbelievable.
Mi Joo is being...
- trained by So Min.
- Really?
- She's So Min's person.
- They are together.
Right. She's So Min's person.
We are close friends.
- She's my minion. Attention.
- I'm not her minion.
Attention. How dare you...
Do squats. Spread your legs.
One and two.
- Hang on.
- Go further down.
She sounds strict.
Hey, what's that?
This is the old convention
that should be removed.
(Bowing deeply at the waist)
This is the old convention
that should be removed.
(So Min is following the old
tradition that should be removed.)
I don't care about what she said.
When I saw Mi Joo doing squats,
- It was shocking.
- I was astonished.
Why?
I can tell she's never...
A workout...
No.
Isn't this it?
I can tell she's never...
(Shutting his eyes tight)
- A workout...
- Isn't this it?
Hey! Stop it.
(Just like So Min, she has
brazen looks and gestures.)
My gosh. I like...
- Mi Joo's squats for variety shows.
- Hey! Stop it.
My goodness. Do something about her.
- She's Empty Head.
- She's funny.
- She's good.
- This is what Empty Head does.
- Cut it out.
- I like that she has guts.
- She's Empty Head.
- I'm sorry.
- This is a variety show squat.
- A variety show squat?
On a variety show,
this is how I do squats.
Do you have to touch someone
as you do squats?
Is this a variety show squat?
- I see.
- This isn't about exercise.
- Look at Sang Jun.
- Variety show squats.
Can I come back later?
They are getting all the spotlight.
I just can't mingle with them.
- We have nothing in common.
- Sang Jun.
- You picked the wrong day.
- I know.
- This is so sad.
- Because...
- these two are like monsters.
- My point.
If I leave now,
it will be easier to cut me off.
Maybe I should come next time.
(If I leave now, it will be easier
to cut me off. I should come later.)
Sometimes, you have to make
hard decisions in life.
And I support your decision.
- Just give it a try.
- He's quick-witted though.
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
All right. Today, we will...
The thing is,
your goal is to join
the national team.
(Your goal is to join
the national team.)
It can be any even though.
As you know,
I've trained all sorts of athletes.
- That's true.
- Athletes of all kinds.
Actually, he taught
Son Heung Min soccer.
- Really?
- No.
(He is
Son Heung Min's soccer teacher.)
He also taught Park Ji Sung soccer.
That's a misunderstanding.
- It's not a misunderstanding.
- I didn't teach them soccer.
I taught them
other kinds of exercises.
Anyway, he's the best expert
in exercise.
- He's the best in the world.
- All sports...
- share the same basics.
- That's right.
So I will teach you
the basics of exercise.
Who's the man in the blue cap?
- Why do you keep meddling?
- Why are you butting in?
Hey, stay quiet.
Suk Jin, you should fight him.
You punks, how dare you...
- What?
- I'm scared.
What was that?
My gosh.
(The members are having
a hand-to-hand fight.)
Hang on.
- Hey.
- Wait.
The three of you, come on out.
- Come here.
- Me?
Come over here.
- Rotten player, come over here.
- Why me?
You can't fight
with other members in my gym.
- You shouldn't fight.
- I just got hit.
- I'll let them go run a lap.
- That's good.
(I'll let them go run a lap.)
- Who is he?
- What do you think you are?
Who do you think you are?
- I can't believe this guy.
- Jae Suk.
- Who is he?
- Do you see the wall over there?
- Go touch the wall.
- Okay.
- In a line.
- Stand in a line.
What's wrong with him?
Why are we listening to him?
Start with the left foot.
One, two.
Why are we following his directions?
Left foot.
They are walking.
(One and two)
Okay.
- That was nice.
- Isn't that nice?
- It's nice.
- All right.
Pull yourselves together.
Let's move on.
- Trainer Kook, can I drink water?
- What?
- Cool water.
- No, you can't.
I'm talking to the trainer.
- I asked the trainer.
- No, you can't.
You should be patient
when you work out.
Trainer Kook, look at him.
(The old member opened the fridge
without the trainer's permission.)
- It's okay.
- The old member...
I'm not one of them.
(He carefully claims
a special favor for the elders.)
I'm not one of them.
(He carefully claims
a special favor for the elders.)
Hey.
What on earth are you talking about?
- Hey.
- You're being ridiculous.
He wouldn't let me drink, so...
Put it back in.
My goodness.
- We can drink this, right?
- That's okay.
This is okay, right?
We can drink this.
- Come here and drink some water.
- Drink water, guys.
Hey. Is this...
a prison camp or something?
There aren't so many things
we can't do.
- Seriously...
- Is this a prison camp or what?
(Trainer Kook wouldn't
even let them drink water.)
(So it was hard for them
to relieve their thirst.)
Listen while you're drinking.
Today, we have Trainer Kook
who is trying to revive Tiger Gym...
by fostering good athletes...
and the members who joined the gym
just because it's free.
It's called Trainer Jong Kook
and National Team Race.
The nine players will participate
in many different competitions,
and their goal is to collect
prize money from each competition.
The player
with the most prize money...
will receive a special benefit.
- Only one person.
- So it's an individual game.
Trainer Kook will participate
in competitions like the players,
but he can't win the prize money.
However, the athletes may give him
some of the prize money...
- as a membership fee.
- That's great.
Trainer Kook also needs enough money
to get a benefit...
- that helps to win.
- I see.
The winner of each round receives
prize money.
You can give Trainer Kook
as much money as you want from it.
The person who saves the most money
from the prize money...
receives a special benefit.
Trainer Kook has to get as much
membership fee as possible...
- to get a great benefit.
- Oh, I see.
Also, during the race,
Trainer Kook can train the members
whenever he wants.
(Trainer Kook can train the members
whenever he wants.)
- That's great.
- Indeed.
- It's good.
- Director.
That man in a blue cap doesn't have
any authority, right?
- Is it a corrupt relationship?
- Tell us the truth.
Young Ji just said
we're in a corrupt relationship.
- I see you've been studying.
- No.
I guess she's been watching
the news lately.
There will be a captain like him
by Trainer Kook's side.
- "A captain"?
- Great.
Change your clothes and come back
for the captain election.
- Okay.
- We're going to elect the captain.
(The Captain Election)
Now we're going to elect the captain
who will be...
Trainer Kook's right-hand man
and his pet.
- Are we going to elect the captain?
- Yes.
All of you except for Trainer Kook
are candidates.
You'll have time to prepare
for your election speeches.
And then the voting will begin.
Each of you has 1 vote
whereas Trainer Kook has 5 votes.
- That's how... Yes.
- He has five votes?
- Hold on.
- That's really great.
- Was that a complaint?
- Can't he have more votes?
- No, I wasn't complaining.
- Right?
I'll tell you the benefits
that the captain has.
The captain will get 100 dollars
as congratulatory money.
- Really?
- Yes.
- One hundred dollars?
- And the captain will be exempt...
from the training that begins
whenever Trainer Kook pleases.
- Oh, my.
- That's a great benefit.
- Indeed.
- That's amazing.
- The captain will be exempt?
- The first one is chosen by voting,
but after that,
Trainer Kook can replace the captain
as he wants.
- Really?
- Also,
you get an additional 100 dollars...
if you don't get replaced
until the next round.
- Okay.
- We know what type he likes.
- I wonder what type he likes.
- What type does he like?
Since this is a variety show,
the captain should be funny.
- A good sense of humor.
- Then I'm not confident.
I also want the captain
to take working out seriously...
and to be loyal.
- These are important to me.
- The captain should be loyal?
Yes.
Are we electing someone to be
his dog or something? Why loyalty?
- You see, Trainer Kook.
- Yes?
I understand everything else,
but loyalty doesn't sound...
I mean why must the captain
be loyal to you?
Step forward, please.
(Step forward, please.)
- This is great.
- Come on.
(Blue Cap has been called out
while complaining.)
- Hurry up and step forward.
- Oh, gosh.
Stop. Go back to your seat now.
Sit down. Come on.
Gosh, you guys won't even look me
in the eyes.
- Hey, Mi Joo.
- Sit down.
- Young Ji. Hey, So Min.
- He's a stranger to me now.
- You can do whatever you want.
- How can you guys do this to me?
- Sit down. Now, come forward.
- This is ridiculous.
Come forward.
Yes, sir.
Do you think
that loyalty is important or not...
- for the captain?
- I believe it's important.
- It's important, right?
- Yes.
It's such a simple matter,
and you complained about it.
- You shouldn't do that.
- I knew you would be in trouble.
- Understood.
- You may go back to your seat.
- Yes, sir. It won't happen again.
- Okay.
In a nutshell,
we're electing his minion.
The captain will get a benefit.
It's reasonable.
You also get 100 dollars each round.
We won't just make you work.
You'll be paid fairly.
Sir, I'm done writing.
Oh, I see.
Hey, you wrote a lot of stuff.
- I'll show you my loyalty.
- I'm sorry, but is it...
- Should I go first?
- Is it a letter of apology?
- Pardon me?
- No, it's not.
- Really?
- It's true. I...
- That was so fast.
I bet he wrote all the things
that can please Trainer Kook.
- What's that?
- I didn't have to think about it.
- It took me only 30 seconds.
- How did you finish so quickly?
- That's amazing.
- Since I respect you,
- I just wrote down my feelings.
- I see.
- It was easy.
- You used difficult words...
and wrote in different colors...
Then I'll go first, sir.
Hey, I'll go first.
- I'll go first.
- I'll go first, sir.
- That's good.
- It's a good attitude.
- I'll go first, sir.
I'll remember your passion.
- Let me go first, sir.
Great. Then...
- Pro can go first.
- Yes, sir.
But I finished before he did.
What is wrong with you?
- What is wrong with me?
- I'm sorry.
- Come forward.
- I said, come forward. Now.
- I'm sorry. It wasn't like that.
- Hurry up. Run.
- Come forward.
- I finished writing before he did.
- Stop talking.
Do ten squats. Ready, go. One.
Lower. That's two. Three.
- Three, four, five,
- That's how you should do squats.
- six, seven...
- That doesn't count.
- Squat lower than that.
- He's doing it wrong.
- Lower.
- Six, seven.
- Hold on. Stop.
- Yes.
- The way you're doing squats...
is how elderly people do squats.
You mean jumping as I come up?
- No. I mean the angle.
- I see.
- That's perfect for elderly people.
- Really?
How did you know that?
Well, I wasn't aiming to do it
at a particular angle.
I'm sure that the energy I got
from you helped me. Ten.
- It's a good method for your body.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- Sir, then I'll begin...
- my speech.
- Sure. Go ahead.
First of all, I'd like to say...
that I'm honored to be the first
to give a speech...
as a candidate for the captain
who will put our team together.
That's great.
(He sounds disciplined
as a captain candidate should.)
- I like your attitude.
- Thank you, sir.
- Then I'll begin my speech.
- All right.
(The ambitious candidate
Jae Suk's promises)
"My Oath".
"Oath".
First, if I become the captain...
I will give away 90 dollars to you.
- That's a good one.
- That's tempting.
Second...
(Second!)
I'll make sure everyone gets
a buzz cut to unify the team.
(To make sure everyone has
a buzz cut to unify the team)
Hey.
- We'll show the power of unity...
- What is that?
- by having the same buzz cut.
- Great.
- That's a good idea.
- We'll have to get haircuts?
- A buzz cut?
- Third,
we will get rid of hierarchy,
so the youngest will be treated
with the highest respect.
- Great.
- I like that.
- I should vote for him.
- We should all vote for him.
- This is a promise to Trainer Kook.
- All right.
I promise I will never talk about
Yoon Eun Hye.
(I will never talk
about Yoon Eun Hye.)
I promise...
From now on,
I will never even bring up
her name again.
You just said her name four times.
I mean I won't do it again
in the future.
I'm saying this to show you
how determined I am.
Fifth,
there will be no romance
between the gym members.
To help everyone focus
solely on the training,
I'll make sure
to tell Trainer Kook...
- I don't like that.
- if there are any romantic vibes.
I like that one.
- Sixth,
- Okay.
I'll provide you
with vitamin drinks...
and get product placement
for our show.
We'll need money to get a vehicle...
- for the gym members, right?
- That's great.
- That's all.
- That's interesting.
My, that was fun.
- Thank you, sir.
- Good job.
I think he can get many votes
from the gym members.
But he didn't say much
about how he'll assist me.
- Who will go next?
- Yes.
- I'll go next.
- I'll go next, sir.
All right. So Min,
come forward to deliver your speech.
When will it be my turn?
Wait for a while.
- It's not fair.
- Just wait.
What's the rush?
Hello. I'm candidate number two,
Jeon So Min.
You may think that I'm too weak
and not good enough to be a captain.
- So I'll tell you about myself.
- Great.
Here are the things about me
that you should know.
My father is the coach and player
of a morning soccer club.
- He played soccer in high school.
- What is that?
- Your father played soccer?
- Why would you talk about him?
My younger brother
majored in taekwondo.
He's a fitness trainer now.
He won several fitness competitions.
- He works as a trainer currently.
- He sounds similar to me.
My mother has been doing
aerobic dance for ten years.
My uncle has been playing tennis
for more than ten years...
and is a morning soccer club member,
playing an important position.
My aunt majored in
traditional Korean dance.
My great-aunt won
several singing contests...
and worked as a singing instructor
for housewives for over ten years.
And my aunt on my mother's side...
enjoys different sports
including cycling and hiking.
- I have a question.
- Yes.
- Your entire family seems...
to be quite athletic.
- Then why are you so bad at sports?
- Then why...
- She doesn't have what it takes.
- I agree.
- I'll do my best. Thank you.
- Good job. Go back to your seat.
- She's not captain material.
- Right.
Especially, she has a soft spot
for love.
- That's true.
- Yes.
I'm the best when it comes to love.
- That's not true.
- She's the worst.
All right. Who wants to go next?
I think it's time for me
to deliver my speech.
- I'll go next.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Darn it!
- One, two. Here we go.
- Gosh, seriously.
It's Yang Ssaebssaeb's turn.
(Captain Candidate, Yang Se Chan)
- I'll be your dog.
- Okay.
I can't believe him.
- Paw.
- You won't get any votes from us.
- None of us will vote for you.
- I'll make realistic promises.
- Okay.
- First,
if anyone acts up,
I'll take off his glasses...
- and slap him in the face.
- Okay.
The few members who wear glasses
have been acting up.
- They've been acting up.
- He's the worst.
- You refer to specific members.
- If any of them acts up,
I'll slap him in the face at once...
- to stop him.
- I can imagine that.
- It's a realistic promise.
- Okay.
- Second,
- Yes.
as the captain,
I promise I'll become
Trainer Kook's mad dog.
I'll bite and bark
as you tell me to.
Okay.
- Hey, but...
- He's the worst.
That's what you always do.
Hey, do you really want to live
like that?
Third... This one is
really practical.
From 100 dollars
of the congratulatory money,
I'll give Trainer Kook 50 dollars...
and ten dollars to Mi Joo, Young Ji,
So Min, and Sang Jun each.
I'll keep ten dollars for myself.
I promise I'll give you the money.
- You promise?
- He abandoned us.
- That's tempting.
- I'll take care of you guys.
I promise. You can trust me.
- I don't think he's lying.
- That's great.
- That's the worst.
- Last but not least,
if you vote for me,
I'll transfer 50 dollars
to your account...
- right after the election.
- What?
- Real money?
- I'll give you 50 dollars.
- Are you serious?
- For me,
you'll have to find an ATM.
(You'll have to find an ATM.)
I still don't use Internet banking.
- Start using it. It's convenient.
- The same goes for me.
- I...
- Why?
- I'll need mine in cash.
- Same here.
These are the realistic promises
I make to you.
- They really are realistic.
- Yes.
- Those are all realistic.
- Okay.
I like his promises.
- Those are all realistic.
- Yes.
- You may go back to your seat.
- Will you really give us the money?
Will you really give us 50 dollars?
He's losing his chance to win
the election.
- I should've gone first...
- He's losing his chance.
- You should hurry up.
- Okay. Next.
- Who's next?
- Will you go next?
- I'll go next, sir.
- Good. Go ahead.
Come forward.
The promises they made are similar
to one another's.
- I won't make lots of promises.
- He's at least consistent.
- I believe the mindset is the key.
- By the way...
- That's what matters most.
- Dr. Oh Eun Young is here.
- Dr. Oh.
- She looks like Dr. Oh.
- So... This is what I wrote.
- Okay.
Let's check it out. "Tiger Gym".
- "Tiger Gym. These are..."
- What's this?
- "my promises to Trainer Kook."
- She drew a tiger.
Is that a poster or something?
Maybe that's what she calls him.
Hey, do you think
that's good enough?
- Be quiet.
- Go on.
- I'll continue.
- Yes.
"I respect you. I love you.
I'm grateful to you."
She said she loves him.
- She loves him.
- Oh, my.
- Continue.
- Just ignore what they said.
"I respect you. I love you.
I'm grateful to you."
- Thank you.
- "With this mindset,"
"I'll serve Trainer Kook
and all the gym members."
And there's more.
"Song Ji Hyo,
the perfect candidate..."
"to be Trainer Kook's
right-hand person".
- All right.
- She thinks she'd be the best...
- Of course.
- As his right-hand person.
- It's because she's right-handed.
- It's simple. I like the drawing.
- You put so much effort into it.
- You know...
Trainer Kook seems to find her
so adorable.
(The man in the blue cap
couldn't hold back.)
- Come forward.
- I mean... Seriously.
- If anyone acts up,
- I'll slap him in the face.
- Come.
- If you just let me, I'll slap him.
- But it's true.
He looked at Ji Hyo
with so much affection. Didn't he?
- Come forward.
- I could see that.
- Right? You could see that.
- That's true.
- Sit down.
- I don't really care about you two.
Just sit down.
- Do squats.
- Sit down.
Sit down. Hands on your ears.
My gosh.
- Go touch the wall and come back.
- He gets all types of penalties.
- Trainer Kook.
- Yes?
You can't make me do that
on a variety show.
- Touch the wall and come back.
- Just do it already.
- This is good exercise.
- Just do it.
Sang Jun came on a variety show
after a long time.
Go now.
- My junior comedians...
- I...
I respect you.
Our senior comedian
whom we respect...
Do you always do things like this
on your shows?
- Go on now.
- My gosh.
- Go.
- Keep going.
- That's good. You're doing well.
- Make him imitate a duck too.
- Good.
- Make him imitate a duck.
- Right.
- I feel bad for him.
- Imitate a duck while doing it.
- What does a duck say?
- Quack.
- I feel bad for him.
- I said the truth. Why is it wrong?
- Come on. Keep moving.
- It's humiliating.
- Hurry.
- Okay. I'm moving.
- You may stand up now.
- Yes, sir.
He's taken aback.
- Don't make unnecessary remarks.
- I won't do that, sir.
- Okay. Go back to your seat.
- Yes, sir.
- You did an excellent job.
- I'll go next, sir.
- All right. Mi Joo will go next.
- Go for it, Mi Joo.
Okay. Nice.
- Mi Joo is So Min's person.
- With light steps
(Hopping)
(The next candidate is cheesy
just like So Min.)
I like how she's making
her entrance.
I like it very much.
- Let's go.
- Is she So Min's person?
(I was born)
(As a man)
- You're not a man.
- I have a lot to do as a man
- Nice.
- Here we go
- She's good at it.
- Hello.
I'm candidate... It's 1, 2, 3...
I'm candidate number 7,
- Candidate number seven.
- Lee Mi Joo.
- What's that?
- It says "Mom" and "Dad".
- Is your father a PE teacher?
- Yes.
My mom and dad got married
and had me.
And my dad is...
- a PE teacher.
- That's true.
- That's the truth.
- Yes.
- He's a real PE teacher.
- Really?
An athlete's blood runs
through my veins...
- in my body.
- Right.
- I'll donate my blood. Go ahead.
- All right. Done.
- He played along with that.
- Done.
(He played along with her joke.)
- He played along with that.
- I can't believe it.
- He played along with that?
- Why?
- That's not fair.
- Hey...
- But she... Why?
- I can't believe him.
- How could you do that?
- It was funny. She did well.
- I can't believe you just did that.
- "Done."
She was funny.
Why would you eat her blood?
- I tasted her blood.
- Why would you do that?
She does have an athlete's blood
running through her veins.
I'm so upset. I can't believe
he played along with that.
It took me four years
to get that reaction from him.
- You taught me well.
- He's the worst.
- It took her 4 years.
- It took me 4 years.
I can do push-ups.
- I've learned archery too.
- Really?
- I've played volleyball too.
- Volleyball?
- I've played basketball too.
- Nice.
I'm good at every sport.
Are you good at playing
foot volleyball?
As for foot volleyball...
I'll learn fast
because I'm athletic.
- She was born athletic.
- I can learn fast.
- Exactly.
- My stance is good, right?
I can do it right away.
If you trust me and choose me...
But why did you release the bow,
not the arrow?
- Exactly.
- Wouldn't it hit your face?
You'd probably get hit by the bow.
That's funny.
Mi Joo is really bad at sports.
Mi Joo is not athletic at all.
Then which part do I release?
You should release the arrow
like this.
If you release the bow,
it would hit you in the face.
I can do that.
- Did you see that?
- "Then which part do I release?"
That's not good.
Do the "Pick Me" dance.
- Pardon me?
- Do the "Pick Me" dance.
- Oh, right.
- The "Pick Me" dance.
I'd appreciate it
if you vote for me.
(She starts dancing so suddenly.)
(Dancing excitedly)
(Her dance moves won
the voters' hearts.)
That's great. Keep going.
(Her dance moves won
the voters' hearts.)
(She's dancing in double time
to redeem herself.)
- That's great.
- Look at her.
I think her pelvis just popped.
- She's amazing.
- Thank you.
(She finishes with a 90-degree bow.)
(Impressed)
- Thank you.
- That was unexpected.
- She's so good at it.
- Great job.
You see... She does seem...
- like So Min's person.
- Yes.
- But she's an upgraded version.
- That's right.
- I'll go next.
- Okay.
- I'll keep it short.
- I wrote it from my heart.
- Good.
- Didn't you go already?
- What?
- What's that?
- Although...
Oh, gosh.
(What did he write
with such neat handwriting?)
- He's sad.
- My gosh.
- What's the matter?
- Don't do that.
- What's wrong?
- I grew up in an unhappy family...
What's this?
- He's appealing to pity.
- What is he doing now?
I like it
when he does things like this.
- I see what's going on.
- I like this.
- Go on.
- He's trying to gain sympathy.
(He's asking for votes
while wrinkling his nose.)
What? Why? Go away.
- Stop it. Don't rip it.
- Why?
- Go on.
- What? Why? Go away.
(Jae Suk came to stop him
from using pity.)
- Hey.
- Let go of me.
- Mister.
- Why? Hey.
- What's wrong with him?
- Kick him out.
- Calm down.
- How dare he...
- use pity to win votes?
- He's using pity.
- How dare you?
- With a sad story,
- he's appealing to pity.
- You can't use pity to get votes.
- Let's hear him out.
- I didn't make up this story.
All right. We'll hear you out.
It's a true story.
As Trainer Kook...
- and some others know...
- Yes.
I didn't grow up in a happy family.
(I didn't grow up
in a happy family.)
- I really like this.
- My mom and dad...
That's right. My dad went broke.
(My mom and dad...
That's right. My dad went broke.)
- You punk.
- Come on. Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
- Go away.
- Don't do that.
Leave me alone.
- He hates it when Haha does that.
- I really hate it.
- "Don't appeal to pity."
- Some of us like it...
- when he does that.
- Take this seriously.
You all made empty promises.
Is it my turn now?
It's over.
He says it's over.
(The speech time is over.)
- What about me?
- We heard everyone's promises.
It's time to vote.
Yes. Let's begin voting.
- Hey.
- We'll wrap things up here.
- But I haven't...
- Please sit.
- These are incredible promises.
- Sit down, please.
- Just get a close-up shot of it.
- You'll regret this.
Take a picture of it
and post it on social media.
- Assistant Administrator,
- Yes?
you can go ahead
and give your speech.
- Right. Go ahead.
- What did you call me?
- "Assistant Administrator".
- "Assistant Administrator"?
- Assistant Administrator.
- Why would you call me that?
Let's hear it.
Actually,
I finished writing this
in only 30 seconds.
- But...
- That sounds half-hearted.
He didn't give me a chance.
- Because you were half-hearted.
- I realized...
that I wrote everything
that the others already said.
(I realized that I wrote everything
that the others already said.)
"I'll be your dog."
And everything else.
He's so cute.
"My only hope is to become
your minion."
I wrote all the stuff they said.
Seriously.
(As he goes on complaining,)
(the voters started losing
their interest.)
So I got rid of it
and wrote a new one.
I thought...
- that I would...
- We're dying from boredom.
(One of them even fainted.)
(Slipping)
- Oh, gosh. Let's just vote for him.
- All right.
- Let's vote for him. It's not over?
- Hey.
I summarized what I wanted to say
on one piece of paper.
Check this out.
If I become the class president...
(If I become the class president...)
"Class president"?
He said "class president".
It's "captain".
My gosh.
"If I become the class president"?
- We're not at school.
- "If I become the class president"?
- That's it.
- "Class president"?
- It's not a class president.
- Hey.
- Is it a class president campaign?
- Yes.
The class president election is held
in the next building.
Hey, stop it.
- You should go...
- "Captain" or "class president"...
- They're all the same.
- No.
He doesn't know
what he's running for.
- "Class president"?
- Take him out.
If you vote for me,
I'll put my apartment in Jamwon-dong
under your name.
- Come on. That's a lie.
- As if.
- Are you serious?
- That's nonsense.
- Who will receive it?
- It's a lie.
He said "class president" too.
I can't believe him.
You should've given me
the chance sooner.
They already made the promises
that I came up with.
- Go back to your seat, please.
- "Class president"?
- Gosh, seriously.
- He's running for class president.
He's running for class president.
"If I become the class president..."
- Hey.
- Yes?
Let's begin voting.
We'll hand out the ballots.
- Good.
- You came to the wrong place.
(Trainer Kook has 5 votes.)
Good.
- Am I allowed to write my own name?
- No.
I can't vote for myself, right?
- It's not allowed, right?
- I think that Se Chan...
It's important to choose
the right side.
It'll be a disaster
if Se Chan gets chosen.
Who we vote for matters,
- but not as much as our trainer's.
- Exactly.
- He has the power.
- He has a total of five votes.
- It'll show who he's fond of.
- I didn't vote for only one person.
I'm putting my faith in you.
(They all cast their votes.)
- All right.
- I'll mark the votes.
- You...
- Yes?
- It suits you.
- So...
You know how it's done, right?
(Sang Jun will help
count the votes.)
- All right. Yoo Jae Suk.
- What...
Did you hear him just now?
Yoo Jae Suk.
Me?
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Put your faith in me.
- He's acting like he already won.
- Okay!
- Hold on a second.
- Is it Jae Suk?
- Is it Sang Jun?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
(The second vote
also goes to Yoo Jae Suk.)
- Everyone.
- This is bad.
- Hold on.
- I'll get the job done.
- How did you win them over?
- I'll be of service.
I'll get it done.
- What is it?
- Is it Jae Suk?
Why...
Again?
- Jeon So Min.
- What?
(Jeon So Min, 1 vote)
Someone wasted their vote.
It's as good as not voting.
- You can't write your own name.
- No way!
Who was it?
- Who was it?
- But...
- Who...
- Who was it?
- You two...
- You and Mi Joo...
Did you write each others' names?
- Seriously?
- What is it?
(Seriously?)
I went about this all wrong.
- Who is it?
- It must be Jae Suk.
Is it Jae Suk?
(Who got the vote
that startled the trainer?)
It must be Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes!
He must've bought the votes.
- This is bad.
- Everyone...
Us?
- Did you buy the votes?
- I'll keep my word,
- so don't worry.
- I wasn't expecting this.
It's why you had to be smart
with your five votes.
Things have taken a weird turn.
He'll suffocate us all
if he's the captain.
- Hold on a second.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Nice!
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- You wasted your five votes.
- Jong Kook...
must not have wanted this.
(He opens the next ballot.)
It must be Jae Suk. He must've won.
- Are you kidding me?
- What?
- Why?
- You voted for Jae Suk too.
Of course.
- Who else would I vote for?
- Hold on.
What other option did I have?
(After all the complaining)
- Thank you.
- I had no choice.
- What...
- Here you go.
Come on.
I mean,
he made a few promises.
After all the complaining you did?
He promised us benefits.
- Our welfare...
- He always does this.
He always votes for me.
He said he'd give us money.
- You also voted for him.
- He promised us money.
He complained endlessly...
- when he had voted for me too.
- What?
- Yang Se Chan.
- Yes!
Trust, faith, and love.
- Jong Kook adores Se Chan.
- Se Chan as captain will be bad.
If he becomes the captain,
we'll be in trouble.
I hope I become the trainer's pet.
- Suk Jin...
- We have our top two candidates.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Nice!
- Young Ji...
- Of course.
- Thank you, Young Ji.
- I voted for him.
- Young Ji...
- Yang Se Chan.
That's what I'm talking about.
- The trainer's pet is coming!
- No way.
It could be anyone now.
Se Chan as captain
will be a disaster.
- Just wait and see.
- It'll be a dictatorship.
- Oh, no.
- I won't wait once I'm the captain.
- He won't hesitate.
- Glasses Tribe will be annihilated.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes!
Okay, fine.
Yoo Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk 5 votes, Se Chan 3 votes)
- Yang Se Chan.
- Yes!
Thank you, my comrades.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Okay!
- He's closing the gap.
- This is bad.
Yoo Jae Suk.
- Gosh.
- Oh, no. He's falling behind.
Let's widen the gap!
- There are only two votes left.
- Se Chan and...
- Only two votes.
- Only two votes remain.
- Wait.
- What is it?
- Who is it?
- Did someone write Haha's name?
It must be Se Chan.
- Who is it?
- Hold on.
- This...
- It can't be Se Chan.
It will be a bloodbath.
Just you wait!
Please.
(2 votes will decide
who will be captain.)
Yang Se Chan.
(Se Chan wins a vote.)
(Jae Suk 6 votes, Se Chan 6 votes)
- It'll be the end if he's captain.
- Trainer Kook...
- It'll be over for us.
- Hardly.
- It'll be over if it's Jae Suk.
- Trainer Kook...
- Please.
- Let it be Jae Suk.
- Trainer Kook.
- Let's see.
(Will it be buzz cut Jae Suk...)
(or Trainer Kook's loyal dog
Se Chan?)
(The last vote will decide
who becomes captain.)
Is it Jae Suk?
Yang Se Chan.
(Se Chan is captain!)
(The result: Se Chan 7 votes,
Jae Suk 6 votes, So Min 1 vote)
To the front, everyone.
Gather around!
That's what I'm talking about.
- Trust, faith, and love.
- Nice.
- Faith, love, and hope.
- Trust, faith, and love.
- Young Ji, join me.
- Faith, love, and hope.
Trust, faith, and love.
- How did this happen?
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Take off your glasses.
Take out your phone and pay up.
You...
- Pay up.
- Come on.
Where's your phone?
- All right.
- I voted for you.
- Hurry up.
This is what happens when the one
with power favors someone.
How cool is that?
So Min is completely
on his side today.
(Captain)
- Thank you.
- That's so cool.
- All right.
- The leader of the gag squad.
You'll now enter
your first competition.
In this first competition,
you'll have to guess your ranking.
It's the 2021 Guess Your Ranking
Asian Games.
- Sounds like fun.
- We'll be aiming.
I'm quite good at it, you know.
No, this is how you shoot a rifle.
In collaboration
with a survey center,
we showed your names and faces...
to people within the age range
of 10 to 69...
and conducted various surveys.
Your job is to guess
your own ranking.
The team who guesses
more correctly will win...
and receive the prize money.
You can start off
by splitting into teams.
- Go with those wearing spectacles.
- Spectacles?
Those with spectacles.
Okay, we'll go with glasses.
- Who wears contact lenses?
- We'll go with Team Glasses.
Join us if you've had
laser vision correction.
- Join us if you've had...
- Mi Joo.
- Laser vision correction.
- I wear contacts.
Laser vision correction.
- You?
- Yes, me.
- You're one of us, right?
- She wears contacts.
- No, I have great vision.
I have 12-12 vision.
- Get over here.
- Come on.
You wear contacts.
- Okay, this will be the teams.
- Sure.
We'll begin the ranking game then.
- All right.
- Let's do this!
(Tiger Gym)
- We will see results.
- Love for Jong Kook!
- Love!
Loving Jong Kook
is like loving your country.
- Love!
- Unbelievable.
It sounds like
you're not happy at the moment.
Wasn't he acting up just now?
I wouldn't put it like that,
but he is ruining the mood.
- I'd appreciate it if...
- Come on, Trainer Kook.
Am I not allowed
to even make sounds?
Hold on a second.
Why did you raise your tone
at the end?
- What was that?
- That's just how I speak.
You're allowed to make
any exclamations you want,
but please remember
that we're a group.
That's how Team Glasses speak.
- He scanned you up and down.
- Did you see his gaze?
You two, please stand up.
(The bold duo
has been asked to stand.)
- Get up.
- He's talking to you.
You two, stand up.
Get them on their feet.
Okay, fine. Seriously.
The one with glasses
sitting next to them.
He should stand as well.
- But I didn't say anything.
- No, you need to stand.
The three of you...
will be punished together
if one is out of line.
Do better, all right?
Put your arms around
each other's shoulders.
- What?
- Is this a prison camp?
- Is this necessary?
- You'll do ten...
Quiet!
I'm sorry, but can I join them...
since I haven't been doing anything?
- I'll join them.
- Stick to his side then.
Tell us what we did wrong.
Do ten squats.
Squat ten times.
- Mi Joo should join us too.
- Why?
Mi Joo can't do it
since her legs hurt.
Join them.
(She tried to be cute.)
(But it didn't work
on Trainer Kook.)
- He hates that the most.
- Put your arms around each other.
- He loathes it.
- Got it.
That muscular pig.
- Jong Kook!
- Love!
- Love.
- Jong Kook.
- Sit.
- Jong Kook!
- Love!
- Sit.
- Jong Kook.
- Love.
- Love!
He didn't say it.
Squat ten times.
- Go ahead.
- Wait.
- You never pointed at me.
- Do it.
Suk Jin is getting
a good workout today.
Say "Jong Kook, love"
while you're at it.
Jong Kook, love.
- Good.
- Jong Kook, love.
- Nice.
Love.
Love who? Jong Kook.
Love!
That was great.
See? It livened up the mood.
Wasn't it nice?
Did you see Suk Jin at the end?
(Jelly legs)
The mood became better instantly.
- I did a year's worth of squats.
- That alone livened up the mood.
- Nice.
Just so you know,
this isn't the military.
- You're members of his gym.
- We're athletes.
- It's supposed to be a gym.
- He makes it seem that way.
Squats are a great workout.
Why give the trainer
a total of five votes?
- Unbelievable.
- It's unfair.
Anyway, you're competing
in the first tournament.
Here's the first survey
that was conducted.
We asked those in the age range
of 10 to 69.
If someone upset them,
who'd get revenge
in any way they can?
(If someone upset them,)
(who'd get revenge
in any way they can?)
- This one...
- It has to be So Min.
- She probably got the most votes.
- No.
I'm probably ranked second...
- because of my image.
- It's your image.
- Right. I'm pretty 2nd.
- I bet she came in 2nd.
- I bet she's ranked pretty high.
- So Min...
- must've gotten the most votes.
- You must be ranked pretty high.
- It has to be you.
- If Kwang Soo were here,
- he would've gotten the most votes.
- Right.
What about me?
- Do you think I'd take revenge too?
- Revenge...
You'd do it if we're filming.
- But your image...
- Yes.
People see you as a nice guy.
- So you're probably ranked low.
- That's true.
- Here's why.
- I don't do that personally.
- I'd do that on variety shows.
- He'd do it on camera.
- He must be ranked 8th or 9th.
- Right.
He's either 7th or 8th.
- What about you, Young Ji?
- I'm pretty young,
but people think I'm evil.
- So I might've been ranked high.
- Right.
- That's true.
- People think I'm evil and mean.
- You're energetic and hyper.
- Right.
- She surprised us at first.
But you don't take revenge
on people. Right?
- In real life,
- You're a cool girl.
I can be pretty evil.
(In real life,
I can be pretty evil.)
- Even in real life?
- I get even. And I double it.
- Really?
- Yes.
- She does take revenge.
- I'm totally for revenge.
- Right.
- Totally.
- That's cool.
What about you, Mi Joo?
I think Jong Kook
will be ranked first.
- You'll be 2nd.
- I'll be ranked 1st.
- You're 3rd. You, 4th.
- I'm sure I'll be ranked 1st.
- You're 5th. You, 6th.
- Me? Why?
She's ranking us based on our looks.
- Other than Jong Kook,
- Hey.
- she ranked us based on looks.
- Mi Joo.
- Right?
- First, second, third,
- I'm so angry.
- This is so annoying.
- Hey.
- You're unbelievable.
- Who's ranked fifth?
- You'd better be smart about it.
- Why am I...
First, second,
third, fourth...
So being ranked fifth is good.
Right? That's good.
So Min, do you take revenge?
I don't openly talk about it.
She definitely gets even.
- I...
- She should get the most votes.
I make my move after coming up
with the best plan.
- It's a long-term project.
- That's the scariest.
That's the scariest.
Here's what I did a long time ago.
I was so angry. And it was when...
- people used wired earbuds.
- Right.
The wired earbuds
were neatly organized.
But I got the wires all tangled up
on purpose. That's my revenge.
- That's...
- That's your kind of revenge.
- So you thought about doing that?
- What?
- That you should do it?
- No, I even carried it out.
- Gosh.
- She did it.
- She would carry it out for real.
- Jong Kook would get even.
- Totally.
- He'd do it, no questions asked.
- In fact,
up until my mid-30s, I thought...
I should get back at people
and that was the nature of things.
- The nature of things?
- Yes.
- I thought that was fair.
- That's scary.
I thought it was fair for everyone.
Jong Kook has gotten very kind now.
- I thought that was justice.
- Justice.
- What about now?
- I don't do that now.
I thought about
what my biggest revenge was.
- It's working hard like this.
- Right.
Are you watching?
I'll make you see me
on every channel.
- That's enough!
- Stop it!
- Are you watching?
- Someone must be...
shaking with the remote control.
- I'll make you see me on TV.
- "So Min."
- "Are you watching me?"
- I'm so sick of that.
- Any stories, Young Ji?
- You should ask me...
if I ever had a boyfriend first.
- Right. Don't ask her that.
- That's the right order.
- You've never had one?
- No.
- I've never had a boyfriend.
- Really?
- She's young.
- Not even one.
Don't you meet guys
now that you're a rapper?
Well, those guys like...
women, cars, and money.
- We have nothing in common.
- I see.
- It's strictly business.
- Right.
- She's professional.
- You keep things professional.
- See?
- Right.
Do you get why I said
Young Ji and Mi Joo are amazing?
- I'm more like PG-13.
- She's bold.
- Their ratings don't match mine.
- She's hip.
- Sang Jun, watch.
- Okay.
Did you listen to their stories?
- You need stories like that too.
- What's happening?
- I'm sure you'd get even too. Yes.
- Me?
Even when people tease me,
I don't do say anything.
- What about how...
- Really?
- your ex hurt your feelings?
- By the way,
you might be surprised to hear this,
but he's usually the one...
who hurts girls,
instead of getting hurt by them.
- No way. Seriously?
- He's a bad guy.
- How does he do that?
- He's really popular.
- Really?
- He dates a lot of people.
- He's popular?
- He's very popular.
- Why?
He's popular?
- And he's a typical bad guy.
- You?
No. But I don't take revenge.
- Do they want to experiment?
- What?
- Is this just an experiment?
- No.
I'm just popular among girls.
- Once I ask them out...
- You're just popular?
I'm popular.
- They laugh at my jokes.
- You're popular?
It's embarrassing to say it myself,
but they laugh at my jokes.
But when I ask them out,
they don't call me back.
- They don't call him back.
- But women like...
- guys like him.
- Right. They are popular.
He's likable.
- Sang Jun is very charming.
- Right.
He's the kind of guy
I would want to have meals...
- and drink tea with.
- But...
- you can't possibly kiss him.
- Really?
- I would never kiss him.
- What about kissing him?
- I'd never kiss him.
- Look at him.
- No. I'd only eat with him.
- Imagine kissing that face.
- You'd never kiss him.
- Never.
- He's just a close friend.
- Right. A close friend.
- Just a close friend.
- I see.
- Don't you get friend-zoned a lot?
- That's how it all starts.
Don't people say
they could bathe with you even?
Guys tell me that from time to time.
- Bathe?
- "I could even bathe with you."
What does that mean exactly?
So nothing will happen between us.
- Nothing will happen.
You'll be a good friend to girls.
- That's true.
- I'd like to get to know him.
- Right? He's charming.
- Right.
- Okay. I'll ask you out soon.
- But there's no progress.
No.
Do you know how
Sang Jun gets back at people?
It's asking them out.
"I like you."
- Recently... Yes.
- That's so true.
- You know?
- "I became to like you."
When people break up,
- they wish each other good luck.
- Right.
So that way...
I'm sure you wished her luck.
But do you think
she wished you luck too?
- Hold on. That was random.
- You're trying to provoke him?
You're doing that now?
Yes, now.
- Okay.
- Hey, your eyes are back.
You're in your 30s again.
Look. Those are the eyes I remember!
- Those are the eyes.
- These are the eyes.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
- His eyes are back.
- Let the nature take its course.
I saw those eyes again.
- I must get even.
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook in his 30s...
- Okay. Great.
All right. Let's come up
with the order now.
- I think I'll be ranked first.
- Let's do this. Me too.
- Jong Kook too. This is our bet.
- Yes. Put me there too.
You and I should be ranked there.
This is all about our image.
It's about our image.
I think I'll be ranked fourth.
Fourth.
- Fourth.
- Fifth.
- I'll go with fifth place.
- Okay.
- Fifth place.
- No, fourth place.
- Put me in sixth place.
- It's iffy. Sixth place.
- I'll go with seventh place.
- No.
I'll go with seventh place.
It won't matter.
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Suk Jin
are expecting to be ranked low.)
- Ninth and eighth.
- Ninth.
- Trust me and pick the ninth place.
- Okay.
All right. You're done.
I'll reveal the result now.
Bring in the result.
(Is it what they predicted?)
- We were spot on.
- Let me see.
- See?
- Gosh.
- It's what Jae Suk said.
- I told you.
Did I get it right?
- Sang Jun is ranked first.
- Really?
- Me? Why?
- It's him.
- You're ranked second.
- Gosh, Sang Jun.
Se Chan was right.
- I was right.
- Why am I ranked so high?
- I was ranked ninth.
- It's about our image.
We were right. Mi Joo,
where did you get ranked?
- Mi Joo.
- I was ranked eighth.
(Only Se Chan and Suk Jin
were right.)
Me? Why?
(Only he can't understand
the rankings.)
Why am I ranked first?
I'm ranked tenth.
(He's the least likely person
people expect to take revenge.)
Only Se Chan guessed right.
- I was right.
- I don't take revenge.
- And Suk Jin.
- I was right too.
- Gosh. Sang Jun.
- You were right too.
- Why am I ranked first?
- Se Chan's guess was right.
I was right.
Can you tell us why?
People chose him because...
they thought physiognomy is science.
"Physiognomy is science."
- "Physiognomy is science"?
- Isn't that too harsh?
- How does my face look?
- It's the mole.
That brings revenge.
No, this mole brings food.
- You have the eyes of a snake.
- That's how I look?
- You might start an uprising.
- You are like...
- I have a likable face.
- His face screams revenge.
Here's why.
He played some distasteful roles...
- Right.
- in "Comedy Big League".
- His lines are brutal.
- Right.
But I'm not like that in real life.
- Tell people about that.
- I know you're not like that.
- I don't do that.
- He's such a good friend.
- They are all scripted.
- He's a nice guy.
And Jong Kook was ranked second
because people thought...
Jong Kook would bully and torture
them until they fully realize...
their mistakes and sincerely
reflect on their wrongdoing.
- That's so spot on.
- He'd be stubborn.
Well, his gaze has changed a lot.
- He has a kind gaze now.
- Right. My gaze is gentle.
- Look. He's smiling with his eyes.
- Right.
- Yes.
And people ranked Jae Suk last...
because they thought
he'd know nothing about revenge.
- It's about his image.
- Seriously.
I'm so sick of hearing that.
- I'm sick of it.
- He has such a nice image.
- The 1st and 10th places...
- But...
are sitting together.
- Mr. Physiognomy...
- Hey.
- It's true that I don't do revenge.
- That's physiognomy too.
I don't take revenge
because it's a hassle.
That's interesting.
Jong Kook's team won...
- by one point.
- Okay!
- Well done.
- Good job.
You picked the right captain.
- Gosh.
- All right.
The members of the winning team...
will get 200 dollars
except for the captain.
And the losing team
will get ten dollars each.
That's all you'll get.
And the winning team
must come forward and show me...
with their fingers how much they'll
put away for the membership fee.
Then I'll give you the money
after I deduct the fee.
- But...
- I should have picked good ones.
And the fees will go to the trainer.
But I won't disclose the amount.
- You won't disclose it?
- Right.
- So you won't tell him?
- Are you sure?
- Young Ji.
- Okay.
I'll only disclose
the amounts of money,
but he won't know who paid how much.
- You should disclose the numbers.
- Gosh.
I can just tell that Young Ji is...
- quite extreme.
- I'll give you the money for sure.
Young Ji, you can start.
Gosh, what a shame.
Come on. Be generous.
Point at the number you want to give
away as the membership fee.
If we give him 50 dollars each,
he'll get 200 dollars.
(How much will she pay
for the membership fee?)
Okay.
Gosh. I love Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo, you're next.
- For the membership fee?
- Yes.
- Point at it.
- I can give him half.
I won't hesitate.
How much for the membership fee?
I don't even expect you
to give me 50 dollars.
- Have a conscience though.
- You need to get 50 dollars.
Come on. Don't be so stingy.
We all worked hard.
So Min, are you
looking for the number, zero?
- No.
- That wasn't on the book.
(She's caught red-handed.)
Are you looking for a zero?
(She's trying to skip paying
the membership fee.)
You know...
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
(Next up is the captain, Se Chan.)
I can sort of see
where your finger is headed.
(He's Trainer Kook's right-hand man.
What about Captain Yang?)
- Se Chan's finger didn't go down.
- No.
When I looked,
the number I wanted was at the top.
All right.
I'll give you four numbers.
Trainer Kook, you can ask me...
how much 1 out of the 4 paid
for the membership fee.
- Just one.
- What?
- You didn't tell us about that.
- Right.
- He should ask.
- I just need to ask one person.
- He should have a chance.
- The fees you got...
(Paid amounts
for the membership fee)
are 10 dollars, 10 dollars,
10 dollars, and 30 dollars.
(10 dollars, 10 dollars, 10 dollars,
and 30 dollars)
(3 of them only paid 10 dollars.)
Gosh.
Who was that?
You can just pick anyone.
- He needs to know who paid 30.
- Gosh.
- If you picked us...
- I pointed at the wrong number.
- Come on.
- Everyone, get up.
- I pointed at the wrong number.
- Up.
Totally.
I picked the wrong number.
You got 200 dollars.
How can you only give me 10 dollars?
- How could they?
- Are you even human?
- How could they do it?
- What do you think, Blue Hat?
I told you, didn't I?
- Listen.
- You picked the wrong people.
- You should've picked us.
- We don't do pull stuff like that.
Listen. You chose
such dishonest people.
Pick another captain
and join our side.
I paid 30 dollars.
No, I paid 30 dollars.
- No, I did.
- I paid 30 dollars.
May I ask now?
You can ask how much
just one person paid.
All you need to know
is who paid 30 dollars.
- Find who paid 30 dollars.
- It was me.
- I paid 30 dollars.
(He'll know about the rest...)
(once he finds out
who paid 30 dollars.)
I choose Ji Hyo.
(My Ji Hyo...)
- Tell me how much she paid.
- I bet she paid ten dollars.
Ji Hyo...
(If Ji Hyo paid 30 dollars,
it'll mean the rest paid 10.)
Ji Hyo paid 30 dollars.
(Ji Hyo paid 30 dollars.)
(He killed 3 birds with 1 stone.)
- Can you believe it?
- Busted!
Darn, he's scary.
- She must love him a lot.
- I did it for the team.
It's not like 30 dollars is a lot.
- Let's be honest.
- It's more than ten dollars!
- It's more than 10 dollars!
- It's 3 times more than the others.
I know it's three times the amount,
but it's not a lot.
I would've at least paid 50 dollars.
There's no big difference between
10 and 30 dollars.
- You...
- My gosh!
Do ten push-ups right now.
Do it this instant.
- Get on with it.
- Do ten right now.
- But I'm the captain.
- Captain?
Captain, my foot!
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
Go down deeper.
You haven't even done one yet.
Three, four,
- five, six.
- He's good at them.
- Seven, eight.
- Anyone could do that.
Nine, ten. Good.
- Sit back down.
- That was cool.
Suk Jin said that
anyone could do it.
Okay, go ahead.
Do ten.
Ten? I could at least do 30.
Then do 30 push-ups.
If you manage 30 push-ups,
I'll give you 150 dollars.
- You'll give me 150 dollars?
- Yes.
- So 150 dollars for 30 push-ups?
- Proper push-ups though.
- Money motivated him.
- Here he goes.
They must be proper push-ups though.
I see he's motivated by money.
- One, two.
- No, go down deeper.
- Three, four.
- This will do, right?
Five, six, seven, eight.
(He's on his way to winning 150
dollars by doing proper push-ups.)
That's 10, 11, 12.
And 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18.
And 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25.
That's 26 and 27.
- Oh, no.
- And 28, 29.
- Thirty.
- Nice!
(He managed 30 push-ups.)
Thirty!
- Thirty!
- Bring over my 150 dollars.
Why?
You agreed to pay me 150 dollars.
No.
(He suddenly changed his mind.)
I just don't want to.
- It was only a verbal contract.
- It's understandable.
- It's possible.
- That could happen.
(He unexpectedly
lost all his energy.)
(Lunchtime)
"Eating is part of the workout."
(Eating is part of the workout.)
- My gosh.
- Everything looks good.
- No way.
- "Eating is part of the workout."
The training and competing
must've made you hungry.
- You'll now have your lunch.
- Right.
Despite not having enough to spare,
Trainer Kook prepared...
- a healthy meal for you.
- Really?
Jong Kook will hand out
the rice and main side dishes.
- Me?
- Yes, at your discretion.
He holds the ultimate power.
Since being frugal is in his nature,
he didn't prepare enough
for everyone.
There's not a lot of food.
The gym doesn't make
that much money, you see.
Not a lot.
I'd like to make a contribution.
Well, what you give me personally,
- I won't reject.
- Right.
I'll hand some over.
- Do I give out the food myself?
- Yes.
He'll be handing out
the food himself.
There really isn't a lot,
but it still looks good.
Look at Captain Yang.
He should be helping,
not be first in line.
- Unbelievable.
- You should give him a hand.
This is what loyalty looks like.
This is loyalty.
Darn him.
(A big smile)
- There you go.
- He's not wrong though.
That's ten dollars.
(Captain Yang shows loyalty
in exchange for stir-fried squid.)
(This is 10 dollars' worth.)
- Seriously?
- Hold on.
- This is loyalty.
- Yes, loyalty.
- I see you're loyal.
- I sure am.
Are you kidding me?
- I see only two pieces of squid.
- There's really not a lot.
- The squid...
- It'll be tough competition.
What on earth?
- Even though you paid?
- That's right.
This is a miniature version
of society!
He won't give you a lot
even though you paid?
This is loyalty.
No, this is bulgogi.
Okay. That's great.
Okay.
I should just open a gym of my own.
Are you serious?
How much did you pay for this?
- A total of 40 dollars.
- For that?
What he got was 40 dollars' worth?
I'm considering
the distribution of wealth.
(A 40 dollars' worth feast)
Darling.
Did you hear her?
(A bulgogi side dish
got him a girlfriend.)
She just called me "Darling."
How dare you flirt with my man!
Are you kidding me?
You have no idea.
Right. One should eat her fill.
- There really isn't much.
- We'd get nothing at this rate.
Did you say "we"?
Don't touch the rice!
- Leave it.
- I actually almost cried just now.
It's been a while since anyone
told me not to touch the food.
- I want some food.
- No.
This buys you squid.
And this buys you bulgogi.
- You dirty pig.
- No, don't!
Why would you eat with your hands?
This truly is upsetting.
How can you take
all the bean sprouts?
Move, mister.
- You took all the bean sprouts.
- There's no more soup.
- It's good though.
- It really is.
(Lunch at Tiger Gym teaches you
to be hungry for success.)
We're sweet enough
just to eat what we're given.
There's not a lot for me.
This is what I get
for being considerate.
I have nothing to eat.
Is that all for you?
(A plate full of bulgogi)
(A bowl full of bean sprouts)
- There isn't a lot.
- Check out all the bean sprouts.
(Now's the time.)
There's practically nothing to eat.
(Hey!)
Hey!
You're done as captain.
Get up. I'm taking that.
No, I'm sorry.
(Captain Yang loses his position
after stealing bulgogi.)
Get up.
I hate it when people steal my food.
- Get over here.
- Sure thing.
You're out. I've had it with you.
Here's the congratulatory money
for the new captain.
- Thank you.
- You receive 100 dollars.
- Goodness.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- It's my pleasure.
- All right.
- Move!
- Captain Yang.
- Help us out a little.
Can we each get ten dollars?
- Thank you.
- It's what you promised.
Thank you so much.
(Captain Yoo starts his term by
helping his teammates financially.)
Thank you.
- How cool is that?
- We're in it together.
Here's to celebrate
my term as captain.
- Is that ten dollars?
- What?
- Seriously?
- Just ten dollars?
- Are you serious?
- Hold on a second.
- I mean...
- How much did you receive?
- Only 100 dollars.
- He got it just now.
Do better, all right?
- Got it.
- Don't cross the line.
I'll do my best.
Since I just made captain...
(Since I just made captain...)
- More congratulatory money?
- Well,
I'll be collecting a membership fee.
(A membership fee)
Are you kidding me? Darn it!
This is wrong. He can't do this.
- This can't be allowed.
- Why not?
It makes no sense.
- Twenty dollars.
- After you eat...
Collect the membership fee
and split it with me.
Of course. You don't have to worry.
- Once you're done eating...
- This is close to stealing.
We'll gather around, all right?
- No way.
- Sure.
- He's good at things like this.
- He's different, isn't he?
The food is tasty though.
- It really is.
- Right.
(After a delicious and healthy meal)
Are we playing
foot volleyball again?
- Everyone!
- Hold on a second.
Guys, since I just made captain,
I'd like to ask
for your cooperation.
We'll celebrate my first term...
by paying 50 dollars each.
- What?
- That's too much.
(To even out the wealth,
he proposes a high membership fee.)
- As a membership fee.
- But 50 dollars?
- That's...
- I only suggest this because...
It's too much,
and no one has that kind of money.
- I don't have that.
- Let me handle him.
Why are you stealing from the poor?
What authority do you have?
- I'm the vice-captain.
- Vice-captain, my foot.
- Hey.
- Come on.
Guys, hold on a second.
We may have a new captain,
but that doesn't mean
Team Glasses...
climbed up the social ladder.
- Dorks in glasses...
- I knew it.
- Dorks in glasses?
- Get back.
Those wearing glasses...
I may trust the captain,
but not all those wearing glasses.
I'll collect 30 dollars
from each member, sir.
That I approve.
- You.
- Fifty dollars was too much.
We're going to
confess our love to you.
Keep this up
and we'll declare our love.
- To me?
- Yes.
- Okay, fine.
- You've been warned.
- A confession of love?
- Hold on a second.
- Confess our love.
- I'm going to.
- Go ahead.
- How will you do it?
How about 20 dollars?
Pay up the 30 dollars.
- But 30 dollars is too much.
- It's too steep.
- Pay up the 30 dollars.
- Hands out of your pockets!
Do we really have to pay up?
Hold on a second.
Big Glasses, shut it.
- Hands out of your pockets.
- So 30 dollars.
Just think of it...
- as a fee you must pay.
- Members should have equal amounts.
Yes, exactly.
- So Min.
- He just took my money from me.
- This is unfair.
- You can't do this!
- This shouldn't be allowed.
- How can he do this?
Think of it as a membership fee.
- How will this be spent?
- It'll benefit all members.
How will this be spent?
- To help the members in need.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- I'm the one who needs the money.
I'm in need of the money too.
- Okay.
- I'm the one who needs the money.
(Come here.)
He's like a thug!
Did you see him just now?
- What was that?
- They have collusive ties.
- People are watching.
- They're conspiring.
What on earth is this?
- Is he working for him?
- Seriously?
- We'll sort this out later.
- Is this the Mafia?
- Exactly.
- Are you forcing us to pay?
Meanwhile, the members
who weren't on the winning team...
- Right.
- Here!
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
Hold on a second.
- He took 30 dollars from 4 people.
- That's right.
- Hold on a second.
- Not so fast.
- Why?
- Get over here.
- You collected from four people.
- This will be the team's money.
- Wait.
- We could get on a bus...
and buy some hotteok to eat.
Get over here for a second.
The captain can fend for himself.
I should get one per person.
- Get what?
- One bill per person.
You collected from four people
and only gave me this.
He collected 120 dollars in total.
Hand it over.
But you see...
It should look amicable,
so hand it over with a smile.
(It should look amicable,
so hand it over with a smile.)
- Trainer Kook, here you go.
- Right.
Thank you for this.
Trainer Kook, does such a gym
exist in real life?
I know. Even I think...
- This gym is so corrupt.
- Listen.
He picks a captain...
and makes him collect money.
The gym is free.
- Hold on.
- The gym is free.
Stand properly.
- Besides,
Trainer Kook needs some money
to operate the gym.
I don't know anything.
- It's for the facility.
- This is too much.
Please make me the vice-captain.
- What?
- The vice-captain.
Get down on the floor.
For real?
- Watch what you say.
- Will you allow that?
- I will see what he does.
- Sang Jun, come here.
- Okay.
Hey, move to the end.
Didn't the men in glasses
make a trio?
- No.
- The group fell apart.
- They are different.
- Listen.
There is a difference
between our glasses.
- Their glasses are fake.
- Yes.
Their glasses have no lenses.
No lenses.
- Seriously.
- Their glasses are fake.
- Only one wears real glasses.
- No lenses.
- Lenses versus no lenses.
- His glasses are the original.
That's right.
The second game is...
the World T.T.F. Championship.
- What?
- T.T.F.?
T.T.F.?
It's a combination of tennis,
table tennis, and foot volleyball.
- You use the table tennis rackets.
- The table tennis rackets.
On the court that resembles
a table tennis table,
the players will use a tennis ball
and table tennis rackets...
and have a rally as they follow
the foot volleyball rules.
Only the rules are
from foot volleyball.
A round ends
once a team scores seven points.
Okay. We have a chance of winning.
But for each round,
we will have a draw...
for an action you need to follow.
That's the catch.
If you don't follow it,
two points will be deducted.
Okay.
- How will the teams be decided?
- This time,
we will have Team Young Ji
and Team Mi Joo.
Team Young Ji and Team Mi Joo.
They are neck-and-neck.
- I know that...
- I am good at foot volleyball.
- Young Ji has no athletic skills.
She is the worst player.
Pick the team members.
- Do they get to pick?
- Play or lose,
- rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Gosh.
Trainer Kook.
You can pick only if you win, right?
Play or lose, rock-paper-scissors.
- Haha.
- Okay.
Play or lose,
- rock-paper-scissors.
- Jae Suk.
(Team Mi Joo:
Mi Joo, Haha, Jae Suk)
- Se Chan.
Hold on. Please look this way.
Please look this way.
- Play or lose...
- All right.
- Consider the gender ratio.
- I know.
- She picked all the men.
- Play or lose,
- rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
We need Ji Hyo.
(You wench!)
Mi Joo, we need Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- We need Ji Hyo.
Mi Joo, you should take So Min.
The rest of the members
are in Team Young Ji.
Gosh, I am on the same team
as Jong Kook.
Make up the team
for the rounds like this.
Two men and one woman,
one man and one woman,
and one man and two women.
Okay. We got it.
There is an option for this round.
- An option.
It might be something like
"Don't speak English."
This is the option for Round One.
Taking a formal tone is prohibited.
- It's too hard.
- Okay.
- They are at a disadvantage.
- It's too hard.
- All right.
- Do I speak casually to Suk Jin?
- Hey.
How about him?
- Do I speak casually to Suk Jin?
- Hey.
Do I speak casually to Suk Jin?
- Come on.
- Suk Jin.
- Don't intimidate him.
- Hey.
Do we take a casual tone?
- Do we take a casual tone?
- Yes.
- How about "Big brother"?
- You take a casual tone.
- Yes.
- Jong Kook, you take a casual tone.
Suk Jin, let's go.
You take a casual tone.
Hey, don't you understand?
- Jong Kook, you take a casual tone.
- Can't you get it in your head?
- Jae Suk.
- I didn't mean it like that.
I just wanted to check
if you understood.
- What did you say?
- He teased you too.
- Calm down.
- It's just a casual tone,
but some people take it too far.
The round ends
once a team scores seven points.
- Seven points.
Seven points. That's good.
- We can do it.
- Where is the ball?
Okay.
Give me the ball.
Suk Jin,
why is your team going first?
Let me serve. What?
Why is your team going first?
- Then go first, you punk.
- Hey.
- Why did you get angry?
- What are you doing?
Why did you get angry?
Not taking a formal tone
is the rule.
- Suk Jin, don't swear.
- Suk Jin.
- Don't get angry.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
- You shouldn't be like that.
It's just a game.
- Don't misunderstand.
- All of us are friends.
Okay.
- All right.
- Suk Jin, apologize.
- I am sorry.
- All right.
- There you go.
- Suk Jin.
Don't misunderstand.
- All right.
- For goodness' sake.
I am a bit out of it.
He has always used
a lot of swear words.
Seriously. Suk Jin has a problem.
Serve from the back.
- Okay. I will serve.
- You can do it.
Here I go.
Hey.
- Hold on. The tennis ball...
- Here I go.
(It goes under the net.)
- What are we going to do?
- It feels different.
- Is the score 1 to 0?
What? Already?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Suk Jin.
I am sorry.
The ball hit the end of the racket.
The court is big.
- Okay.
- Do well.
Let's go.
Seok Sam, can I serve?
I am Suk Jin, not Seok Sam.
- Suk Jin, can I serve?
- Yes.
(It's Se Chan's turn to serve.)
- Go. Hurry up.
- Go.
There you go.
- Okay.
- There you go.
Hey.
Se Chan!
- Hit harder.
- Hit harder than you usually would.
It didn't go
as much as I thought it would.
- You can serve from the two blocks.
- Really?
Guys, you can serve
from the two blocks.
- "Guys"?
- Yes, sir.
Oh. Okay.
- "Guys"?
- Yes, sir.
Oh. Okay.
- Team Young Ji lost points.
- Why?
Young Ji used a formal tone.
Okay.
- I used a formal tone.
- Don't do it.
Confucianism is in my blood.
Do we lose points...
- if we use the wrong tone?
- Yes.
We need to use a casual tone
with the production crew, right?
- You should...
- We can't use a formal tone.
You should use
a formal tone with me.
Bo Pil, we should be able
to use a casual tone with you.
- You told us to use a casual tone.
- This is too much.
- Scrap the points. You messed up.
You are the one who messed up.
(You are the one who messed up.)
(My goodness.)
That's it.
Hey.
You should take responsibility.
Good job.
This is great.
The score is 2 to 0.
Let's go Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Gosh, this is...
- Receive it.
- Okay.
I will bounce it. Come and take it.
Don't be ridiculous.
- For goodness' sake.
- It was the worst toss.
Hey, we want to sweat.
- Suk Jin.
- Seok Sam, what was that?
I am sorry.
You usually aren't this bad.
We need a balanced team.
- You should receive it.
- I will stand in the middle.
- It's not like you need to kick.
- Okay.
Focus.
- Let's go.
- I will receive it.
- I think he is bad at this game.
- Focus.
- Okay.
Focus.
Receive it.
- He received it.
- That's good.
It's too high.
- Hey!
- Out.
Hey, come here!
(Hey, come here!)
- Hey!
- Out.
Hey, come here!
- I needed to practice.
- Did he get it over the net?
I needed to practice.
- I needed to practice.
- Do ten push-ups.
One. Wake up.
- Hey.
- Wake up.
Wake up.
- Seriously.
- Jong Kook,
we got your point already.
- Come on.
- Friends can say that.
- I know. I am just looking.
- Okay.
- Let's focus.
- My goodness.
Let's make it fun.
- He is scary.
- Come on.
Let's go.
- Here I go.
- We can do well.
- Receive it.
- You can receive it, right?
- He will send it over the net.
(It's time to show
the result of the fierce training!)
He will send it over the net.
Okay!
(Se Chan fails to receive it.)
Good job. That's the power
of a middle-aged man.
That's it.
Suk Jin is good.
- That's it.
- Good job, Seok Sam.
I did a good job, right?
- I will give it to you.
- Give it to me.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- It was meant for me.
- Nice.
Send it up.
- Hey.
- Okay.
(Despite the shaky toss,
Sang Jun saves the ball.)
It didn't go out.
(Spike)
- You are good.
- Okay.
You should have used a spike!
- Good job.
Good job.
- We have good teamwork.
- Did you see that?
- Hey.
- We have good teamwork.
- You should receive it like this.
- How did I receive it?
- Those rookies.
- Good job, Suk Jin.
- We can do this.
- Seok Sam is good.
- Those rookies.
- Good job, Suk Jin.
- We can do this.
- Seok Sam is good.
You need to score seven points.
I won't play around.
- Go.
- Go, Sang Jun.
- Shall I begin?
- Yes. Go.
- Okay.
- He is good.
Be careful.
Okay.
(Se Chan sends the ball
over the net.)
All right. Send it up.
Young Ji.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
Young Ji.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
(My goodness.)
(The ball took him by surprise
when he thought they had scored.)
That was cute.
(Their power evaporated
in less than a minute.)
(Seok Sam.)
Are you okay?
Seok Sam,
you should have received it.
Why did you just stand there?
Suk Jin.
I mean...
- Let's go.
- Set point.
- What's the score?
- Let's end the round.
It will end in a boring way.
(If Team Mi Joo scores again,
the round will end.)
- Be careful.
- Let's go.
Don't be too confident.
- Okay.
- Don't be too confident.
Okay. That's good.
They won't be able to receive it.
- Receive it.
- Run.
- That's it.
- Receive it.
- Spike. There you go.
(They have a rally
for the 1st time in 30 minutes.)
- All right.
- Send it up.
Okay. I got it.
- Young Ji.
- It's over the net.
(The ball is over the net.)
It's over the net.
(Spike)
(The ball hits Young Ji's body.)
There you go. Good job.
Send it over the net.
(He messed up.)
Hey, we won.
- Good job.
- We won.
- We did it.
- It was one mistake.
Get up.
It was one mistake.
What was that?
Why couldn't you send it
over the net?
Is the round over?
For goodness' sake.
- It's time for Round Two.
- Is the round over?
- Be careful.
Use a formal tone now.
- Oh, is it over?
- For goodness' sake.
I will pick the second option.
Okay.
Here comes the second option.
Speak with a smile
and don't get angry.
- Okay. Don't get angry.
- This is...
- Give me the ball.
- Trainer Kook, don't get angry.
- Don't look so serious.
- Trainer Kook, smile.
- Jae Suk.
- Toss the ball.
- Okay.
(Happy)
Okay.
- Trainer Kook.
- Yes?
You are bound to get angry.
I won't get angry.
- You are playing with So Min.
- I won't get angry.
- Really?
- Of course.
You are bound to get angry
when you play with So Min.
That won't happen.
If we decide that you got angry,
we will deduct points.
- Okay.
Smile.
- Let's go.
Smiling will bring good fortune.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Smile.
- Good shot.
- This is fun.
- Let's go.
- We need to win this round.
- Okay.
So Min, let's go.
(Laughing)
(He feels anger,)
(but he manages to suppress it.)
(So Min is happy
to see Jong Kook laugh.)
My goodness.
Jong Kook bit his lips.
So Min.
We only have three chances.
- For goodness' sake.
- The score is 1 to 0.
- Hey.
- That was great.
The score is 1 to 0.
Enjoy the game.
Enjoy the game. Smile.
Seok Sam, move out of the way.
Keep smiling.
That's right, Seok Sam.
That's it.
(Positive energy fills the gym.)
I wondered
if I should say this earlier.
You look so old today.
(Laughing)
Nice comment.
- It has always been that way.
- Okay.
- That's it.
- It's nothing new.
- It's okay.
- All right.
- It's nothing new.
- Let's resume.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Okay.
(He is all smiles.)
Get on the floor.
- Get on the floor.
- What was that?
(They laugh at Jong Kook.)
Hurry up and get on the floor.
- Come on.
- Get on the floor.
- I am a trainer.
I am a trainer.
- I don't care.
- I am a trainer.
Do it like we did
when we made a mistake.
- No way.
- Get on the floor.
- I am a trainer.
- He is so cheeky.
Gosh, he refused
to get on the floor.
- I am a trainer.
- He is witty.
I went easy on them.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- Let's go.
- Put a smile on your face.
- I am smiling.
I am smiling.
(She makes a mistake
with the serve.)
(Her face turns serious.)
You need to smile.
(They use Kwang Soo's techniques
to ridicule her.)
- I am sorry.
- It's okay.
What was that?
(Ji Hyo, what was that?)
- What was that?
- Okay.
- Let's do better, Ji Hyo.
I am sorry.
That was so witty.
(Why aren't you smiling?)
Are you frowning?
- Ji Hyo, smile.
- I didn't know the rules.
I am sorry.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- That's good.
There you go.
- Come on.
- Hit it lightly.
- Hit it lightly. That's it.
- Okay.
You are good.
Okay.
(Team Young Ji made the score even.)
Good job.
- Ji Hyo, it's okay. Smile.
- It's okay.
- It's okay, Jae Suk.
- We are doing well. It's okay.
We can do this.
(This is so much fun.)
(She ridicules them
for the 2nd time.)
You are so bad at this.
- What was that?
- What?
- I gave her the ball.
- Did you see that?
He hit her head with the ball
because he was angry.
- Didn't he show anger?
- Give him a warning.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
Get lost if you aren't playing.
(Laughing)
For goodness' sake.
That little insect.
All right.
- For goodness' sake.
- Okay.
- Shall we begin?
- Ji Hyo, move to the front.
Bounce it on the floor
before you hit it.
So Min, move up a little.
Stand before the line.
(Laughing)
There you go. Why on earth
would you stand so far behind?
You can serve from here. All right.
- There you go.
- Good job.
- So Min.
- Okay.
- That's good.
(Jong Kook sends the ball over
pretty high.)
- Spike.
- Nice.
(My goodness.)
(Laughing)
- What was that?
- Hey.
That was So Min's ball.
- Smile.
- So Min didn't move toward it.
That was So Min's ball.
I tried to get the ball
because she didn't move toward it.
(The little ones aggravate them.)
That was So Min's ball. Hey!
- Come on!
- You did well.
- He got angry.
- Suk Jin got angry.
- Hey.
- Leave the court.
Suk Jin, you lost points.
Why?
- You yelled at So Min.
- We received a report.
- From whom?
- Why did you get angry?
Suk Jin is happy.
- When did you get angry?
- It didn't bother me.
I simply called her loudly.
Hey, you got angry.
Smile.
You pulled my ear.
You got angry.
- Gosh.
- Come on.
Gosh.
(Jae Suk runs away
with the glasses without lenses.)
What a punk.
Bring them back.
Hey, bring them back.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, throw them here.
Hey.
Bring them here!
What?
- He got angry.
- He was smiling.
- I was smiling.
- I am sorry.
- He was smiling.
- I was smiling.
He is gentle on the inside
and tough on the outside.
Suk Jin.
Stop losing points
and go back to your seat.
Go.
I can't tell if people are smiling
or crying.
Let's go.
Hit hard, So Min.
- Okay. Here I go.
- Hit hard, So Min.
- Good luck.
- Hit hard.
- Okay.
- You are good.
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, send it over.
- That's good.
Ji Hyo, that's good.
- Okay.
- Send it over.
(Locust smash)
- Okay.
- There you go!
(Gosh.)
(I am happy!)
(Hold on.)
Jong Kook bit his lips.
No, I didn't. When did I do that?
I didn't do anything.
He just has healthy teeth.
Here is a replay.
- Here.
- Jong Kook, are you okay?
- Okay.
- Of course.
- Are you okay?
Of course.
- Let's go.
- This isn't hard.
- We can do it.
It's the worst player,
Ji Hyo's turn.
- She is really bad.
- That's it.
Okay.
- She is really bad.
- That's it.
(She served to the ceiling.)
(The original boomerang serve)
I am sorry.
It's okay.
(They ridicule Ji Hyo
for the 3rd time.)
I can't contain my laughter.
You hit it like this.
The ball hit the side.
- You are really bad at this.
- I am sorry.
I didn't know
the game could be this funny.
- That was fun.
- Ji Hyo, you are so funny.
That was fun.
It's nice to laugh.
- I know. It's nice.
- It's nice.
- Here I go.
- It will bring good fortune.
My goodness.
Okay.
(Locust failed to receive it.)
(Come here, Jae Suk.)
Hey.
I told you to get a grip.
(They give him full-body therapy.)
- He is really bad.
- Isn't that anger?
I told you to get a grip.
Good job.
(They continue to smile.)
We were close to winning.
- Okay.
- You are really good at this.
Give us the ball.
- It's here.
- The ball is on your side.
Is that so?
Good luck.
That's good.
- Out.
- Edge.
- Line.
(Did it go out?)
That's good.
(It's in because it hit the line.)
Edge!
(The athlete's daughter completes
a difficult technique.)
Edge!
- It's okay.
- It hit the edge.
That was nerve-racking.
Gosh.
So Min, you are edgy.
That was nerve-racking.
Tease them.
(She dances in a flippant way.)
- Go.
- Are you angry?
- Just go.
- I think she is angry.
Just go.
- I can't believe I did that.
- I think that was anger.
- That was so cool.
- What's the current score?
Let's do well. Let's go.
- Do you want to serve?
- Yes.
All right. You are good.
(So Min receives
Trainer Kook's trust.)
Okay.
(She loses a point
as soon as she gains trust.)
(What was that, So Min?)
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- We are saved.
- Get on the floor.
We won.
- So Min is so funny.
- Did you see that?
You should have checked the floor.
Let's do this.
The current score is 6 to 5.
Let's receive the ball.
- Let's go.
- Match point.
Okay.
- Okay.
We need to win this round.
You can do this.
- You just need one more point.
- Okay.
(He shows off his healthy teeth.)
Smile. You have healthy teeth.
It's Locust
who's really bad at this.
- He's terrible at this.
- He's so mean.
He's really annoying.
(I'll send the ball to you,
so make sure to hit it.)
(She's feeling excited again.)
(A surprise attack)
(Making a fuss)
(Suddenly dodging the ball)
Hey. What?
(Trainer Kook failed
to receive the ball.)
(The game is over
with Team Mi Joo's victory.)
The game is over.
Whose fault is that?
Why did you dodge the ball?
- Whose fault is that?
- Why did you dodge the ball?
So Min.
(So Min tested Trainer Kook's
patience until the end.)
Hey!
Okay.
All right. Team Mi Joo wins.
- Okay.
- Nice.
That's corruption, right?
I won without doing anything.
The 4 members of
Team Young Ji get 10 dollars each.
And you guys should decide
how much you'll pay.
The membership fee? Okay.
- Come over here one by one.
- For Trainer Kook...
- Trainer Kook took good care of us.
- We should be nice to him.
I did a lot of things for you.
I'll leave it up to you.
- Make it reasonable.
- Right.
All right. Jong Kook, you can
ask about one member.
- The total amount is...
- Okay.
(How much is
the membership fee collected?)
They are 10, 20, 20, 30,
and 30 dollars.
That's a lot. It's generous.
- That's a lot.
- They paid good money.
My previous team was really mean.
What? Who paid only ten dollars?
Who paid only ten dollars?
- I know.
- It's 10, 20, 20, 30, and 30.
Did you say
10, 20, 20, 30, and 30 dollars?
Hang on.
It's 10, 20, 20, 30, and 30 dollars.
No. It's not me.
Ten dollars?
(Trainer Kook turns into
Detective Kim to interrogate them.)
It's not you, is it?
- It's not me.
- I swear it's not me.
It would be shocking
if it was the captain.
- You seem nervous.
- Me? No, I paid 20 dollars.
(Me? No, I paid 20 dollars.)
(What?)
Now that Se Chan says 20,
I think it's him. Hang on.
He doesn't say he paid 30 dollars.
He said 20 instead.
- Whether it's 20 or 30...
- I paid 20 dollars.
(Se Chan claims
that he paid 20 dollars.)
(What's Detective Kim's choice?)
I pick Yang Se Chan.
(I pick Yang Se Chan.)
I'll give you another chance.
- I pick Se Chan.
- Se Chan paid...
- He must've paid 30 dollars.
- No, he paid 10 dollars.
- I wish he paid 30 dollars.
- I'm sure he paid 10 dollars.
He's the only one
who paid ten dollars.
(Yang Se Chan paid ten dollars.)
He's the only one
who paid ten dollars.
Hey, you. Come here.
Get ready for burpees.
(He pretended to hesitate
and chose ten dollars right away.)
(He's doing the burpee test
as a penalty.)
- Hurry.
- Jong Kook is the best.
Hurry. We don't have time.
- Hurry.
- Jong Kook is the best.
- Are you kidding me?
I was going to give you
some money in secret.
- He's nothing like how he looks.
- Se Chan is unbelievable.
He's the worst.
Guys, please gather around here.
- Okay.
- I feel dizzy.
- We've got an invitation.
- An invitation?
I want the trainer to read it.
What is it about?
Who is it for?
(An invitation has arrived
at Tiger Gym all of a sudden.)
An invitation?
(What is the invitation about?)
- What?
- Why?
- What is it?
- The 2021...
(The 2021 New Female Player Draft)
(Trainer Recruitment)
The 2021 New Female Player Draft,
Trainer Recruitment.
- What?
- What is that?
Kim Yeon Koung, Kim Hee Jin,
Oh Ji Young,
Eom Hye Seon,
Lee So Young, Ahn Hye Jin,
and Park Eun Jin will be placed
in the draft on Running Man.
They fascinated the whole nation...
(Kim Yeon Koung and Kim Hee Jin)
The nation's beloved center.
(Eom Hye Seon and Oh Ji Young)
(Ahn Hye Jin,
Lee So Young, Park Eun Jin)
(The volleyball players are
placed in the Running League Draft.)
(Trainer Kook is excited
to see the super rookies.)
(However...)
(The bold rookies don't care
about the gym's financial problem.)
(They only care about their pay.)
(The rookies' assertive attitude
leaves Trainer Kook dumbfounded.)
(And Trainer Yoo?)
(The two gyms will have
nerve-racking battles.)
(However...)
(Jae Suk!)
(The rookies are so competitive
that they get out of control.)
(A tall player shows up...)
(to toy with Trainer Kook!)
(Okay, Long Legs. Bring it on!)
- Hey.
- Hello.
(If I get paid 130 dollars,
I'll do as much as 130 dollars.)
(And they get paid 320 dollars,
they'll do as much as 320 dollars.)
(Her negotiation skills
make people lose court.)
(She makes puppets
of the two trainers.)
(Okay, Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo!
- Don't blame Ji Hyo.
(The real Long Legs who are worse
than Kwang Soo visit Running Man.)
(Female Volleyball Team,
Fierce Transfer Contract)