(Generation X appeared
to sweep the 20th century.)
(Here come 8 unique,
freewheeling college students!)
(The fashion leaders
from the 20th century are back.)
(The Entering Class of 1991
Is Back!)
(Jeon So Min, a coy freshman)
Ji Hyo, you look pretty today.
(Song Ji Hyo,
Miss Korea Applicant)
(They are all dressed up
for their blind dates)
Again?
He's Ji Seok Sam.
(Their dates are
old college students.)
Seok Sam born in 1966.
(Can I call you Seok Sam, then?)
No, no.
You should call him "mister."
(Seok Sam has mature charm
like a grandma's doenjang.)
How can you call him by his name?
(While they force themselves
to smile for their dates...)
- What's going on?
- Aren't they together?
(Generation X shows up
looking chic.)
What are you wearing?
(The Orange Gang shows off
their outstanding fashion tastes.)
Who are these thugs?
(Hello, guys?)
(While Generation X
boasts their charms...)
I'm sorry, but don't you think...
(Don't you think he's too into
his character all of a sudden?)
(Ha Jackson misunderstood
today's concept.)
(He breakdances
to hide his embarrassment.)
He's dancing out of the blue!
Beat it!
He misunderstood today's concept.
(Back to 1991 with Ha Jackson)
His belly is so plump.
Today, you'll be a senior
who entered college in 1991.
You're to introduce the culture
of the 1990s...
(The Entering Class of 1991
Is Back Race)
All right.
(Popular items from 1990s)
- Really?
- That sounds like fun.
(They will get the penalty
by the number of items they missed.)
We'll determine
who'll get the penalty...
by the number of items you missed.
Before we begin the main mission,
let's play a simple game
to determine who'll get the items.
The members of the winning team
will win the items.
(The first place for the mission)
(A pool hall)
It has been a while since I played.
(It's a place
where they spent their 20s.)
(It's a pool hall
from the year 1991.)
The first mission...
will take place in the pool hall
where young people wasted...
- their youth in 1991.
- A pool hall.
It's called Pool Hall Grand Prix.
Why did I waste my youth like that?
- I have a lot of memories of this.
- Me too.
You will play pool
and four-ball billiards,
and two members
of the winning teams will get items.
We need two male members
to play pool.
Isn't my outfit perfect
for playing pool?
- All right then.
- That's colorful. You play pool.
I think Michael Jackson will be
good at playing pool.
- Right.
- Michael Jackson would be good.
It would look good.
- Michael Jackson, come here.
- All right.
I was going to play billiards.
Michael Jackson
can't play billiards.
You don't know
how to play four-ball billiards.
I should wear arm warmers.
He's practicing.
The ball should go like this.
- Everyone.
- Ji Hyo, can you play?
We should decide
who will hit striped balls.
- So, for pool...
- Good.
I haven't done this for a long time.
- This feels good.
- Do you want me to hold the cue?
- Yes.
- Guys.
Please listen to me.
- Okay.
- People didn't listen in the 1990s.
- Let's do this.
- If you make a ball into a pocket,
you claim the type of ball.
You know that, right?
I can pick one of the two types.
Then you can shoot any ball you want
from 1 to 7.
You need to sink
the eight ball last.
The first ball to sink
will be Jae Suk's ball.
You should sink the eight ball last.
He doesn't look so good
from the beginning.
He's wearing gloves.
You should hit the balls this way.
(The yellow cap
looks quite serious.)
Nice.
- None of them are going in?
- None of them went in.
Good. They are scattered.
There are a lot of balls to sink.
If Haha sinks a ball,
he can claim the type.
If he sinks a ball.
This is a good one.
Ha Jackson has good posture.
- Michael Jackson!
- Jackson has good posture.
Nice.
(He sank the ball easily.)
- Nice.
- All right.
Stripes.
I bet he can make it.
- This isn't easy.
- Gosh, I didn't make it. Go in!
- We don't know yet.
- It's not in.
All right. Move over.
- Go, Jae Suk.
- Move over!
You're wearing the glove alone.
- Obviously, he's bad at this.
- He's the only one wearing it.
He's never done this before.
He has poor posture.
- You might die.
- He would sink the cue ball.
Hit heavily. Am I right?
- He will make it.
- Nice.
(He made a clean shot.)
He will make it.
- Nice.
- Move over.
You just got lucky.
Jae Suk, start with the seven.
- The seven ball.
- You look cool, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, two points from here...
Can't you hit this one?
Hey, who are you playing with?
Hang on. Are you pointing
the cue at me now?
Be positive.
- Okay.
- Kim Positive.
- Let's do this.
- This is hard. You can't make it.
- Hit it gently.
- You should hit this one.
Look at his mouth.
He's trying his best.
(He pouts when he focuses.)
- Make it gentle.
- He pouts when he focuses.
- He's serious.
- Gosh.
- That was close.
- How could you miss that?
That was good, right?
I can't believe he missed it.
Hit the ten ball.
Do you play pool in the States?
We do.
Of course they do.
This is from the States.
- It's from the States.
- I think he'll make it this time.
He's good.
- Haha.
- Jackson.
Good luck!
(Celebrating with the moonwalk)
Haha is good at this. He looks cool.
This is hilarious.
- Back.
- That's right.
(He made a difficult shot.)
Michael Jackson!
(He returns the compliment
with his ceremony.)
Gosh, he's pretty good.
It's done.
Jackson, you're so cool.
- There's nothing you can sink.
- I think...
Just block the ball.
So Min, just hit this hard.
You should hit it hard.
What are you doing?
- What do you think you're doing?
- Hey.
Why do you try useless things?
What are you doing?
- So Min, you can't do that.
- You can't hit it like that.
- Hey.
- You can't do that.
You don't have to do this.
- Why are you being like this?
- I want to look sexy.
- That's not important.
A sex appeal.
She wants to look sexy.
Where did she learn that from?
Gosh, So Min.
Your boyfriend will be really tired.
(So Min's boyfriend has to react
to every move she makes.)
- Hit the ball?
- Yes. Hit it hard.
So Min, are you doing that
on purpose?
- Yes.
- Stop touching your hair.
Just hit it.
Go ahead and hit it.
We don't have guests today.
- Just do it.
- So Min, you should do this.
- Do you need some wind?
- It's done.
- Hey.
(She learned how to play pool
in the wrong way.)
Don't do that. Just split the balls.
Only those who are good
at playing pool can do this.
How should I split them?
- Good.
- That's right. Well done.
It might work.
- It's going in.
- It's done.
- It would've been nice if it sank.
- Hit this hard.
I wish it worked.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
- You sank only one ball.
- Don't worry.
I'll sink three balls in a row.
Just try to push the ball.
Look. The cue and the ball
should be in a straight line.
Hey, you can't give a lesson here.
Move over.
- Here?
- He sounds nothing like his outfit.
My gosh.
Michael Jackson sounds
like a Korean man.
- Hey, mister.
- Make it straight.
Jackson speaks good Korean.
Hit it.
Just hit it gently.
Gently.
(One shot, one kill)
This isn't your first time, is it?
Gosh, I made it.
That was amazing.
That's because you taught me well.
That wasn't an easy one.
Are you sure this is her first time?
- You can't hit it this way.
- Hang on.
- Why is she playing like this?
- I'll hit the green one.
- The green one?
- Hang on.
- Are you left-handed?
- Aren't you a right-hander?
- I'm right-handed.
- Why are you playing like that?
Why? Isn't this right?
You're not playing
with your right hand.
Why are you playing
with your left hand...
when you're right-handed?
- I thought something wasn't right.
- That's for a left-handed person.
- Should I do it this way?
- Why are you wearing the glove?
- How could you do it so well?
- This is more comfortable.
She says this is more comfortable.
She used her left hand,
but she did a great job.
- This is a lot better.
- Put a glove on this hand.
Ji Hyo, hit it lightly.
Stay focused.
Don't listen to anyone.
Ji Hyo, just try to hit the ball.
- It's okay.
- Ji Hyo is so funny.
- I didn't know.
- "This is more comfortable."
- This is a lot better.
- Of course it is.
Haha.
She hit the wrong ball,
so you can start from two points.
Two points.
You can start within the two points.
I'll start from here.
No, it's not like that.
It's two points.
I know that.
- But this is three points.
- Mister.
- I said two points.
- I'll just start from here.
- No.
- He just does whatever he wants.
I want to start from here.
She hit the wrong ball,
so it's two points.
You have bad manners.
Hey.
- You have no manners.
- Hey.
- What's wrong?
- It's two points.
Mr. Michael Jackson.
I can't believe this.
Move over, So Min.
Hey, you should start
within the two points.
Within the two points,
- you can choose a spot you want.
- I know that.
But I want to start from here.
- Will you just hurry?
- You have to stick to the rules.
- You should get on here.
- Why?
Aren't you a ball?
Why am I a ball?
You can hit this one.
Go ahead and hit it.
- Just hit it lightly.
- It doesn't have to be hard.
- Gosh.
- Oh, dear.
- Jae Suk.
- That was so lame.
- You're really bad at this.
- He's not good at this.
- Jae Suk.
Gosh, I said I'm not good at this.
Michael Jackson is so good at this.
He has only one ball left.
- Jae Suk.
- But this one isn't easy.
(Hyun Mee is back.)
He looks really scary.
(A horrible mix of Hyun Mee's
hairstyle and Jackson's costume.)
- Just hit this.
- Can't you put it back on?
I love his costume.
- Miss it.
- Hit it.
He did it.
(A clean shot)
- Haha is really good.
- Now he should sink this ball.
It will end in the next round.
- It'll be over.
- My gosh.
- It's going in.
- It's over.
(He sinks the last ball as well.)
It's done.
(The grand finale)
(Thanks to Ha Jackson,
Team Mapo wins the game.)
Mapo!
Good luck.
They won.
Okay.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan win
the four-ball billiards game.)
- It feels so good.
- I'm really upset.
- This is billiards.
- I'm really mad.
So we have four winners now.
Since we have only two items,
you will play rock-paper-scissors
and the winners will get the items.
- Okay.
- Let's play 2 to 2.
The final winner's team
will get the items.
We will take the items.
Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay!
- That's good.
- You have to win.
- Oh no.
How can I possibly beat
Michael Jackson?
- He's collecting his energy.
- Go, Michael Jackson.
Go, Jackson.
Jong Kook, stay positive.
You can win with a positive mindset.
- Today is Jackson's day.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Ha Jackson wins.)
Nice!
(He couldn't beat Jackson
with the power of positiveness.)
- He's cool.
- Haha and Ji Hyo can pick...
an item each.
Is Haha getting another item?
This is his second item.
I'll have the LP player.
I'll have...
- the nickel-silver table.
- The nickel-silver table?
- Yes.
- My gosh.
(So far, 4 items are gone.)
Before we move to the venue
for the next mission,
you will play a game to determine
the number of presents.
- I see.
- All right.
Kwang Soo,
you paid for the drinks earlier.
You should go down
to the fourth floor.
- It's one floor down.
- One floor down.
- Behave yourself.
- Right.
We will be watching you.
I will just follow my feelings...
to pick a person.
I feel it.
(They should do this well to get
more presents on the next mission.)
(Kwang Soo enters looking nervous.)
Hello.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
Did you just push or pull the door?
I pushed it.
This is what you do.
You should guess
what the next member will do.
Since you're the first one
to come in,
- we consider it a success.
- Okay.
If you guess
the next members' behavior right,
you'll get more presents.
Now, name the next member
to come in...
and guess if that member will push
or pull the door.
(He should guess it right
to get more presents.)
I'm sure about this.
Jong Kook will push the door.
(He thinks Jong Kook
will push the door.)
He pushes the door...
even when it says "pull."
I'm sure he will push.
(It's his instinct
to push the door.)
- Next up is Jong Kook.
- Me?
- Why me?
- Go downstairs.
I guess Kwang Soo named Jong Kook.
- Is that it?
- Jong Kook, stay positive.
Of course.
- Did he pick Jong Kook?
- Okay.
(Master Kim comes down
with a positive mindset.)
Please.
(Will he push the door
as Kwang Soo predicted?)
Okay!
(His prediction is right.)
What?
- Jong Kook.
- All right.
- Aren't I the next to come?
- Jong Kook.
- You just pushed the door.
- Right.
And Kwang Soo predicted
that you'd push the door.
(Kwang Soo guessed it right,
so they get 2 presents.)
Okay!
(What was that sound?)
- What?
- He shouted.
I think he got hit.
Did he shout because he got hit?
He just said, "No!"
Jong Kook, you should name
the next member to come in...
and guess if that member will push
or pull the door.
- We usually push the door.
- It should be Suk Jin.
And he doesn't pull. He pushes.
- I agree.
- He doesn't bother to pull a door.
- He finds it cumbersome.
He will definitely push the door.
Next up is Ji Suk Jin.
He will push the door.
- It's easier to push.
- Sure.
This is all about science.
(It could be possible to guess
all the members' behaviors right.)
Here I go.
(Next up is Big Nose.)
(He always tries to save his energy
as much as possible.)
He wouldn't waste his energy
for no reason.
- He always pushes the door.
- Right.
- Okay!
- See?
- He always pushes the door.
- Right.
Okay!
See? I told you.
- I knew he would push.
- What?
Is it push or pull?
Okay!
- Oh, I get it.
- What is it?
I think it's like left or right.
Or it's like number 1 or 2.
Or it might be about which foot.
- It's about feet.
- Which foot you put first.
- I'll go in with both feet.
- Me too. With both feet.
- I should do that too.
- Jae Suk.
Go in with both feet.
Then we will win.
You should go in on your hands.
I guess that's it. Okay.
- They mostly push.
- Did you push?
- Pick the next one to go.
- Pick the next member.
Pick someone lazy. Like Ji Hyo.
- She will also push the door.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- She will push.
- Right?
There's no way she will pull.
Ji Hyo might do this.
"What?"
- Then she might pull.
- That's possible.
She jumped with both feet last time.
Right. That's what she does.
She wouldn't pull.
She'll definitely push.
I know.
I bet she will push.
I think So Min will push as well.
See what she does?
(As Jong Kook said,
she hesitates in front of the door.)
- See what she does?
- You guessed right.
I know.
Okay.
(It's 100 percent.)
- What?
- Am I right?
She didn't come in right away.
- She was like this.
- What's going on?
- I'll pick So Min.
- Okay.
- She'll push.
- She will push.
See?
(I knew it.)
- The door is supposed to be pushed.
- What...
- It was about pushing or pulling.
- I see.
The door is supposed to be pushed.
Everyone will push the door.
I bet they will all push.
I think it'll be strange
to pull the door.
- They will all push.
- It shows an abnormal personality.
Those who pull
the door are perverts.
- I agree.
- Right?
- I pick Yang Se Chan.
- Push?
- He'll push.
- Definitely.
He'll push for sure.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
(Next up is Se Chan.)
(If he pushes the door again,
they will get 6 presents.)
If you want to pull the door,
you have to use both hands.
- There's no room for that.
- I never thought of pulling it.
You need to do it with both hands.
It will be uncomfortable
to pull the door.
(He goes against their expectation.)
My goodness.
What?
I came in with my left foot.
(He made a wrong guess.)
- What's wrong with you?
- Why?
I came in with my left foot.
I can't believe this.
He's the weird one.
What's wrong with him?
- What was that?
- You're the strange one.
He's even wearing a strange hat.
What's wrong with him?
What did I do?
- He pulled the door?
- Hey.
- You should push the door.
- How could he pull it?
- I see.
- People usually push the door.
Why did you pull it?
What were you thinking?
- Why did you pull?
- If I pushed,
it would've covered my face.
I wanted to show my face first.
- Are you an attention seeker?
- He's an attention seeker.
- Did you push?
- Yes.
We all pushed the door.
I bet those who like
to get attention...
will pull the door. You'll see.
- Did we fail?
- Yes, you did.
Se Chan, pick the next member...
- and guess if he will push or pull.
- Jae Suk.
We all pushed the door.
If you think about the probability,
you should go with pushing.
- He might pull it though.
- We all pushed.
- Just do whatever you want.
- Why did you pull?
I think Jae Suk will pull.
- Jae Suk...
- We don't know that.
Jae Suk will pull the door...
and bump his face into it.
(It's possible
because he has a protruding mouth.)
(Jae Suk shows up.)
I think he will pull.
(Se Chan predicted
that Jae Suk would pull.)
(What's Jae Suk's choice?)
Hello, my love
See? He pushed.
- See?
- I knew it.
He's not in yet.
He's not in.
He's so flippant.
(He's so flippant.)
- He...
- A lot is going on in his head.
- He's confused.
- But he already guessed wrong.
- Jae Suk.
- Are you trying to figure it out?
You already guessed wrong.
- It's not what you think it is.
- You're wrong.
- Jae Suk, try something else.
- Isn't this it?
- That's not it.
- Jae Suk, start over again.
You can close the door
and open it again.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Isn't this it?)
- It might be different this time.
- If he fails again...
- This is stressing me out.
- Hold on.
(He's pushing the door
while walking backward.)
(Oh, boy.)
That's not it.
- You're in now.
- Come on in now.
(It took him so long to come in,
but he failed to figure it out.)
- See? Pushing it is more probable.
- Pushing or pulling the door.
You failed.
Se Chan predicted
that you'd pull the door, Jae Suk.
- What would you have predicted?
- Of course, I would push it.
- Most people push doors.
- We all pushed it except for him.
- Only Se Chan pulled it.
- He was the only one.
- Why did I do that?
- Most people push doors.
Haha might pull the door
and enter while moonwalking.
- That's possible.
- He might do that.
- Will Haha push or pull it?
- I'm sure he'll push it.
I'm 100 percent sure
that he'll push it.
- We all pushed the door.
- Only I failed.
- Haha, you may go now.
- Okay.
(They already failed twice
and lost 2 presents.)
He'll definitely push the door.
I'm 100 percent sure of it.
(Haha should push the door,
so they can get another present.)
(What could be Haha's choice?)
(He's pulling the door
with all his might.)
My goodness.
(Goodness gracious.)
- Why? What's wrong?
- See?
What was that?
- My gosh.
- Nice!
- What's wrong with him?
- It's a habit.
- He's an attention addict too.
- Why did you pull the door?
- What's wrong?
- Why would you do that?
- Why, Michael?
- Why pull it?
There's nothing wrong
with pulling the door, right?
- Why would he pull it?
- My gosh.
I didn't want the staff behind me
to get hurt.
That's what I thought too.
I was considerate of them.
- Nonsense. There was no one there.
- There might have been.
Five of you in total succeeded.
Therefore, you will receive
five presents in the next round.
- Got it.
- Five presents?
Let's move to the next location.
We're going to a cafe this time.
- Nice.
- Really?
- I'll drink coffee.
- Can we have some parfait?
- What will you do? Will you hit me?
- Hold the edges on both sides.
- Here too.
- You can use nicer words.
- But it's embarrassing.
- It's underwear.
- So Min, you always do weird stuff.
- What are you two doing?
- Haven't you tried this at school?
- Are you enjoying a romantic time?
- That's so weird. Do you know this?
- When you were in college...
I'll make a fish for you.
- A fish?
Jae Suk is a romanticist.
- Isn't he romantic?
- He must've made many paper cranes.
And paper crane eggs.
I'm sure he made
more than 10,000 paper cranes.
- He must've made 50,000 of them.
- No, 500,000 of them.
- He must've asked many girls out.
- And paper crane eggs.
- And then he got rejected?
- Yes.
- Then he asked another girl out.
- I received 3,000 paper crane eggs.
- Has anyone received that much?
- Of course.
- I made them.
- It's true. Suk Jin received...
- crane eggs...
- I received a lot.
from someone who was raising cranes.
- You mean, actual crane eggs?
- Yes.
- Crane eggs?
- That's right.
Did you fry them?
- For his health...
- Hey.
- You ate a lot of protein.
- For his health...
- I was very popular in college.
- That's so funny.
- Should we go to the rooftop?
- To the rooftop?
The rooftop?
This place is so nice.
(Cute and pretty teacups
used back in the days...)
- This place is so nice.
- That's nice.
Look at this. I like this place.
(And an old, nostalgic radio)
- Guys. Oh, my.
- Why?
(And on the rooftop...)
- Look at that.
- Oh, wow. This is the real deal.
- I love it.
- Is this place always like this?
(The 1990s style rooftop cafe)
Look at that. "I love you!"
(The ads and movie posters add
the 1990s sentiment to the place.)
My gosh. There are
Chow Yun Fat and Leslie Cheung.
"The General's Son!" Oh, my.
Park Sang Min played Kim Doo Han.
I got into a fight
whenever I watched that movie.
- "Once Upon a Time in China."
- Such movies make you feel like...
- you're a good fighter.
- True.
The weather is really nice today.
- It's nice.
- Indeed.
Have a seat.
- Thank you.
- "Thank you."
(Cheesy)
- I'm not sure how this might sound.
- What is it?
You all look ridiculous.
- So do you.
- You don't look so great either.
- Didn't you see yourself?
- Hey, the year 1991 is my world.
- That's nonsense.
- Look behind you. Be careful.
- Be careful.
- It looks good.
- Parfait.
- Can we have some parfait too?
- They have these old-style cups?
- This place is so nice.
- If you look at it...
It's a multigrain shake.
Yes, it looks delicious.
- I'll drink a multigrain shake.
- Won't you drink coffee?
- I want coffee. I want it.
- I'll drink coffee.
- This is a multigrain shake.
This multigrain shake is amazing.
The multigrain shake is good.
(Even Michael Jackson fell in love
with a multigrain shake.)
(Whenever she hears this song,)
(So Min starts dancing
the cheesy dance.)
She starts dancing automatically.
- I like things like this so much.
- So Min...
- I really do.
- I know. You like it so much.
Show me how to do that dance move.
Do you put your hands together
behind your back?
So Min looks so happy.
(Dancing lightly)
- Is it good?
- By the way...
I used to hang out with Suk Jin
and Yong Man very often.
When we went to a cafe,
we always ordered parfait...
- or hot chocolate.
- Hot chocolate.
- That's cute.
- When we ate parfait...
Almost all the other people ordered
beer or alcoholic drinks.
"Can I have draft beer, please?"
- We didn't.
- But we ordered hot chocolate.
- Something sweet and delicious.
- "Can I have parfait, please?"
"Do you not have
non-alcoholic drinks?"
"Oh, I see."
(The non-alcoholic drink lover)
"Don't you serve
non-alcoholic drinks?"
Then why did you even go out?
You should've just stayed at home.
- Did you go to bed at 10 p.m.?
- Hey!
- You could drink that at home.
- I went out to have fun.
- I mean, what would you have done?
- Eat parfait?
- I went out for some parfait.
Gosh, seriously.
- You're the worst.
- We always ordered such drinks.
Were you expecting something
when you went out?
- What do you mean by that?
- Did you expect...
- Expect what?
- something romantic to happen?
- Of course, I did.
- Romance?
- Did you, really?
- Of course, I did.
Did you dress up nicely too?
Of course, I dressed up nicely.
Has anyone tried to
hook up with you?
No.
Of course, that never happened.
Did he look all right back then?
Tell me honestly.
He just attracted attention...
To put it simply...
- There were peddlers in the past.
- He was a wingman?
- And there's always a monkey.
- Like drug peddlers.
- The monkey attracted attention.
- That's right.
He played the role of that monkey.
While he was making jokes
to attract girls' attention,
we were sitting down
trying to look cool.
- And then...
- Did he even make anyone laugh?
- Jae Suk?
- Didn't he get nervous?
- He never got nervous about it.
- Really?
- Gosh. That's so funny.
- We always said,
"He's so funny
when he's with his friends,"
- "but he gets nervous on stage."
- That's the biggest problem I have.
He got too nervous back then.
I still remember
what Suk Jin used to say.
- What is it?
- People would come and go, right?
- Right.
- Many would do that.
- To meet other people?
- Yes.
Suk Jin would say,
"Come join us!
Our room is the room of freedom."
- Yes, I did that.
- What a lousy comment.
I used to say that.
- What's "the room of freedom?"
- "You can..."
- "stay or leave just as you want."
- To come and leave freely.
- The room of freedom.
- "No pressure."
"Our room is the room of freedom."
- Also...
- I was lucky to meet you
(They sang "Beautiful Restriction"
while seeking freedom.)
If a girl they like comes in...
If a girl they like comes in,
they would sing that song.
That's so cheesy.
- You guys wouldn't know.
- Those were good old days.
It's hard for me to picture him
acting so playful...
- in front of women.
- He wasn't shy.
- He was so flippant.
- Exactly how did he act?
- Was he?
- Yes, he was.
- He was...
- I was that type, you know.
I was shy
in front of someone I like.
- I know how that feels.
- But if I wasn't interested in...
- All ugly guys are like that.
- The same goes for Se Chan.
- Se Chan is just like that.
- Ugly guys...
(The tradition of ugly boys
that continued for over 30 years)
- always try to look cool.
- Se Chan is...
He's acting as if he's a celebrity.
Beggars can't be choosers, Jae Suk.
- I just...
- I know how he must've felt.
I couldn't be funny
in front of someone I liked.
- Was anyone your type?
- I just couldn't be funny.
He once...
I think he was 20 something.
He cried his heart in front of me
after a breakup.
- That's true. I cried.
- Yes.
My goodness, Jae Suk.
- I just heard he had a girlfriend.
- Did he have a girlfriend?
- What really happened?
- He pretended he had one.
- There's no one who really exists.
- He lied about it.
- Actually...
- Isn't it so creepy?
He cried when he didn't even
date anyone.
That's creepy.
- Just to make it convincing.
- Exactly.
- "We broke up today."
- No.
- Jae Suk.
- I'm angry but holding it back.
He said he had a girlfriend,
but I never saw his girlfriend.
- He never introduced her to me.
- By the way...
I didn't tell you this, right?
Suk Jin also cried his heart out
in front of me.
- Really? Really?
- Yes.
- Did he cry in front of you?
- Really?
- I can't imagine that.
- Did he really cry?
- I can't imagine them crying.
- He said...
He said it was too painful
while crying.
- That happens when you're sad.
- It's so hilarious.
Also, we didn't have a lot of money
but acted like we were rich.
Pretending to be rich,
we went to a soju bar...
Suk Jin, let's stop it here.
- They won't let us talk.
- What did you say?
- We have good memories too.
- Gosh. Hey.
- You talked about your memories.
- They won't stop talking.
- Can't I talk about mine?
- How much longer will you continue?
- However long it may take.
- I don't want to hear it.
Stop talking about the old days.
Have you two ever succeeded in
hooking up with girls?
Hey, we were awesome.
- Really?
- Of course.
Have you ever succeeded?
- You spent a lot of money, right?
- Of course.
Yes, we did.
(They kept failing
and running out of money back then.)
- He really is talkative.
- I didn't know that happened.
I really am curious how they were
at the time.
The mission
you will carry out here is...
what people who were in college
in the 1990s must've done before.
It's the top-spinning game.
(Top-spinning game)
- I haven't done it in a long time.
- Me neither.
(We rarely see spinning tops now.)
You should make your top
hit someone else's.
- That's right.
- You should tie a knot at the end.
(Whoever is good at spinning tops
was a superstar in the area.)
- We'd put it on the palm of a hand.
- Right.
- We'd drop it onto someone else's.
- After making it spin,
we would make it jump
with the string.
2 groups of 4 people will
have a match,
and only 3 people in each group will
advance to the final match.
Only 5 out of the 6 people will
receive a present.
I haven't done it in a while either.
Do you know how to do it?
Of course, I know.
- I played with it as a little boy.
- Okay.
- Dropping onto another was allowed.
- So Min, I'll show you.
- Watch me.
- You have to tie a knot on top.
- Wrap it around here.
- Like this.
You should wrap it
around your pinky, right?
- Shouldn't you hang it somewhere?
- No, here.
You should wrap it around the top
tightly to make it spin faster.
(Wrap the string around the top
and throw it.)
- And then wrap it around the top.
- Se Chan, you must be good at this.
- I'm a pro at this. I'm worried.
- This makes it spin fast.
- Se Chan, you must be good at this.
- Of course, I am.
I often played with tops
at Dongducheon.
- When you asked for chocolates?
- That's right.
I gave a performance
in front of American soldiers,
and they gave me chocolates.
You should wrap it tightly.
(The more tightly you wrap it,
the better the top spins.)
Oh, my. He's good at it.
But it keeps loosening.
- Why does it look like this?
- You should tie a knot on top.
(Ssaebssaeb's top performance
that mesmerized American soldiers)
- Se Chan is so good at this.
- I did it, but it doesn't work.
Oh, my. He's good at it.
When I did this,
they gave me chocolates.
He's really good at it.
You're so good at this, Se Chan.
You're wearing the perfect beret
for this game.
(The top-spinning master looks great
in a beret too.)
This brings me back
a lot of old memories.
(He's quite good.)
(Michael Jackson also succeeded in
spinning his top.)
Haha is good at it too.
It's so weird to see Michael Jackson
spinning a top so well.
(Michael Jackson mastered
all Korean cultures.)
I haven't played with a top...
in such a long time.
- Everyone, please step back.
- It's been a long time.
- Oh, no. I failed.
- Hey, hey.
- You just threw it.
- You don't know how to do this.
It's hard to do
if you haven't done it in a while.
- It's not easy.
- It's because it keeps loosening.
- Se Chan is good at this.
- Se Chan is really good at this.
You move your top around
with the string like this.
Am I doing it the right way? No?
- I failed.
- Come and watch this.
- No. It doesn't work.
- Let me see it.
I don't think we can play this game.
Okay. I got the hang of it.
That's amazing, Jae Suk.
Good. Jae Suk, we should move
closer to each other.
- That's right.
- Let yours come closer to mine.
Lower your body. That's good.
- This is how it's done.
- Yes.
- You're good at this, Jae Suk.
- Of course.
It doesn't require special skills.
Make it spin and hit another top.
- He'll be too nervous in the match.
- You won.
You pulled it off.
You saw that, right?
- You're all used to it now, right?
- Yes.
No. Not at all.
- Let's divide groups by ages.
- Okay.
The 4 oldest members will be
in the 1st group.
- Okay. How does it work?
- How many will move up?
From each group, 3 will move up,
and 6 will go to the final round...
- where only one will be eliminated.
- Okay.
- Let's start with the older group.
My, this brings me back
good memories.
- You may begin.
- Let's begin.
1, 2, 3.
(Only 1 out of 4
will be eliminated.)
(Which of them will be eliminated
in the preliminary round?)
- Okay!
- Oh, no.
1, 2, 3.
- Okay!
- Oh, no.
- The 3 of us are safe.
- We'll move up.
- Good.
- Haha.
(Michael Jackson was hit
by Jae Suk's top.)
- Let's continue the match.
- Keep going.
- Come here.
- You come to me.
- He sounds like a foreigner.
- I'm so sorry.
- He even groans like a foreigner.
- Haha, I'm sorry.
(They'll advance to the final round,
but their pride is on the line.)
- Come over here.
- Come on.
I'll just let it spin
as long as it can.
- I have no reason to attack.
- Come on.
Hey, come over here.
- Let's fight. Come here.
- Come on.
I already made mine jump twice.
Which is the right direction?
None of them will start attacking.
- What's going on?
- It's because we're all so nice.
- Haha's top stopped spinning. Wait.
- That...
- Hey...
- Suk Jin came in last.
- Haha came in second...
- But it doesn't matter, right?
You will be in the final round.
- Next group.
- It's disappointing.
- The group of younger members.
- You never know.
Do you want to try it one more time
in this group?
- What? Yes!
- We won't accept him.
- I'll join that group.
- No way.
- We don't accept any old fossils.
- We won't accept him.
Since I entered college in 1991...
Why would you try to play
with younger members?
Please let me join you.
- It's done.
- All right.
That's good. Yes.
- That's it. Lower your body.
- He did a great job this time.
He'll get too nervous
in the match anyway.
- Why would he be so nervous?
- You do so well when practicing.
You see how I am, right?
Please take some herbal medicine
for anxiety.
- Hey.
- He would shake so much.
You should pull it well
when you throw it.
- Yes, you should pull it.
- Should I pull it hard?
You should pull it well.
What do you mean by that?
How exactly should I pull it?
Watch this, Kwang Soo.
I'll show you.
Don't just throw it.
- You see what I mean now, right?
- What?
Why would he teach the others
when he's not even good at it?
It was supposed to land
in the center.
But his top flew over there.
Does it make sense?
You should only boast
if you're actually good at this.
- Come on.
- Kwang Soo.
Don't pull it too hard.
Once three of you are left,
the game will be over.
Be calm and cautious. Ready, go.
- He's so mean, right?
- Good.
It's spinning. Okay!
- It's spinning.
- Make it spin faster.
- I pulled it off.
- The three of you will compete.
So Min, bring it on.
(These three will advance
to the final round automatically.)
- Come here.
- Right. You two fight.
You two go ahead
and fight each other.
Hey, stop it.
Both of us can move our tops.
I'm allowed to move my top too.
She's blocking me.
It's moving slowly.
Mine is moving slowly.
No. You should wait. Okay.
(So Min is out!)
- It doesn't matter anyway.
- Hey, you're so sly!
You should've fought too.
Why were you hiding here?
(While So Min
and Se Chan were competing,)
(Jae Suk was waiting anxiously.)
- How could you call me "sly?"
- He was hiding there.
Okay!
We'll begin the final round.
Still, I made it to the final round,
didn't I?
Only one of you will be eliminated.
- Really?
If your top doesn't spin, it's over.
He's right.
We'll give you another chance
if it doesn't spin...
- One more chance? Okay.
- because this is the final round.
I must say,
whatever the director says,
- He listens to the director.
- you follow his decision.
- He always listens to the director.
- He's the decision-maker.
- I mean, earlier on...
- Listen. He's the decision-maker.
Gosh. I mean... Seriously.
- He's the decision-maker...
- Suk Jin, don't call Bo Pil...
to ask him to only use the parts
where you did well when editing.
- I must say, he's unbelievable.
- He's unbelievable.
- He really is unbelievable.
- Gosh.
You don't seem to know
how things work.
I'm impressed. Let's begin.
- Let's begin.
- Shall we? Shall we begin now?
Yes. Ready. Get set. Go.
- Good.
- I threw it too hard.
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin,
So Min, Se Chan, Jae Suk, Haha)
- Good.
- I threw it too hard.
- It's good.
- Good. Keep spinning, Yellow.
- Jong Kook, be careful.
- I should move this chair.
Jong Kook is fighting with a chair.
- No presents for the last place.
- I know.
- All of our tops are spinning.
- Let's fight.
- It's spinning fast.
- They're all spinning fast.
- We shouldn't fight.
- Mine looks precarious.
If we fight, we'll lose.
Your top is
about to touch the camera. Good.
It won't. I'll move the camera.
- Maybe the floor isn't even.
- I'm sweating so much.
- Oh, no. It's uneven here.
- Look.
- His top will stop shortly.
- I'm in trouble.
Oh, gosh. What do I do with mine?
(Jae Suk and Haha's tops are
about to stop.)
- No. It's moving toward the camera.
- His top is going downhill.
- Hey, move aside.
- What is he doing?
- No!
- Kwang Soo, hold this for me.
- Kwang Soo, hold the camera for me.
- Darn!
(Haha's top stopped while Haha was
trying to avoid the camera.)
Hey!
The camera!
Haha is out.
- The camera!
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why were you standing there?
- Is this yours?
- Why would you move the camera?
I'm sorry.
There's no space behind it.
It needs more space. Gosh.
Jong Kook is in fourth place.
No. I mean, fifth place.
- Gosh. Darn it.
- He's out.
Jae Suk is in fourth place.
Gosh. I'm so disappointed.
- So Min is in third place.
- So Min is out.
Let's do nothing and let it spin.
(Only Se Chan and Suk Jin's tops
are still spinning.)
- No! Keep spinning.
- Maybe I shouldn't have hit it.
(Who will be the winner?)
Let's do nothing and let it spin.
No! Keep spinning.
(Se Chan is out!)
- Keep spinning. I lost to Suk Jin.
- No, no.
- Suk Jin is the winner.
- Suk Jin won.
Suk Jin is in first place.
(Suk Jin is the winner!)
- I knew it.
- He won just as I thought.
- He has a lot of experience.
- You camera!
- I knew it.
- The fifth place gets one, right?
Haha's top was spinning faster
than the others.
Haha, I'm... I'm so sorry.
All of you except for Haha,
please choose a present you want.
- The glass bottle.
- The vintage doll.
I pick the comic books.
You'll leave 1 by 1
just as you did earlier...
to decide the number of presents
you'll get on the next mission.
Okay.
Suk Jin will go first
since he won the game.
(Big Nose,
the top-spinning winner goes first!)
(The number of presents
will be decided through this game!)
Is this it? What should I do here?
- Starting now...
- Yes.
- Do you see the snack over there?
Throw and eat as many pieces as
you can.
- Throw and eat?
- Yes.
This? Okay.
This is my favorite snack.
- I'm good at this.
- Okay. The mission ended.
It's over.
- Please give me the bag.
- I didn't even start.
You're ridiculous.
You should've at least told me
when to begin.
Eating the snack wasn't the mission.
We wanted to see how you open
the bag.
My gosh.
You ripped it open lengthwise.
The number of the members
who open it the same way as you...
will be the number of presents.
However, we'll tell the next person
to throw and eat the snack...
just as we told you.
- Pretend like that's the mission.
- Got it.
I should hope many of them
will open it the way I did.
That's right.
I think most of them will.
(How many of them
will open the bag lengthwise?)
(Next up is Se Chan.)
- Should I go in?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Suk Jin is wearing a mask
not to say anything.)
Throw and eat the snack over there.
You have to eat more than he did
to succeed.
We won't tell you how many he ate.
- Can I start now?
- Yes.
- I should throw and eat?
- Correct.
(If he opens it lengthwise
as Suk Jin did, it's a success.)
I'm sure he didn't eat a lot.
(Se Chan grabs the bag widthwise!)
(But then...
He picks up the scissors!)
I should eat more
than he did, right?
If you eat more than he did,
you succeed.
The mission is over.
(The mission is over!)
(Why?)
- My gosh.
- Actually, the mission is not...
- about eating the snacks.
- Did you use the scissors?
You succeed only when you open
the bag the same way Suk Jin did.
But he ripped it open lengthwise.
(Suk Jin ripped it open lengthwise
whereas Se Chan used scissors.)
Why would you use scissors?
I felt like it was a hassle,
so I used the scissors.
The scissors are a trap.
Think about it. Why would there be
saw-tooth patterns on top?
- It has that shape...
- I know.
- to make it easy to rip it.
- I get that, but...
(While Suk Jin is claiming
it's easier to open it lengthwise,)
(So Min enters.)
Throw and eat the snack
in 30 seconds.
There's no way I can succeed.
Se Chan is good at it.
(Without hesitating,)
(she picks up the scissors!)
But why do we open a new bag?
The mission is over.
Why?
Actually, you had to...
open the bag the same way
as the first person did...
to succeed.
Suk Jin, why didn't you
use the scissors?
- Exactly. Right?
- They were right here.
This way?
(Jae Suk, the fourth member!)
(He's trying to get a hint
with all his might.)
There he goes again.
He won't come in.
- He's trying to figure it out.
- He's doing it again.
- He's pretending to be smart.
- Come on in, Jae Suk.
Should I sit in the center?
No, that's not it.
So Min, please don't say anything.
Jae Suk, please come in.
- We're not allowed to speak.
- You must not speak from now.
All right. You will...
throw and eat the snack.
You'll succeed if you eat more
than the previous member did.
We won't tell you...
- Should I throw and eat it myself?
- Yes.
We won't tell you.
(Jae Suk is fooled
by the fake rule.)
(He's walking toward the snack
with swag.)
(The others are quietly watching
everything Jae Suk does.)
Well... This is...
(He grabbed the edge of the bag!)
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin have been
friends for 30 years.)
(What could be his choice?)
Well... This is...
The mission is over.
(Jae Suk used the scissors too!)
(What?)
- Hey.
- Actually, the mission wasn't...
about eating more snacks
than the previous person,
but about checking how you open
a bag of snacks.
Why would you rip it open
when you have scissors?
Gosh. Why would the top side
be saw-toothed?
- For you to rip it open easily.
- But the scissors are right there.
But using scissors makes it
even easier to open.
We are so different
from one another.
- It's interesting.
- I can trust only Jong Kook.
He wouldn't use the scissors.
Who's the next?
(Big Nose's only hope,
Jong Kook is here.)
You'll succeed if you eat more
than the previous member did.
Oh, I throw it myself?
I see, but Suk Jin is good
at things like this.
You have to eat more than he did
to succeed.
(How will Jong Kook,
whom Big Nose trusts, open the bag?)
(He chose to use the scissors.)
The mission is over.
(He only cut the corner.)
- See?
- I knew it.
(All of them except for Suk Jin
used the scissors!)
- I knew it.
- What is wrong with you?
- Hey, why did such a strong man...
- Of course, he used the scissors.
- use scissors?
- Of course, I used the scissors.
- You should rip it open this way.
- Did you open it like that?
He only ripped it that way
to seem younger.
I would've too
if the scissors weren't here,
- but they were.
- Exactly.
I thought we were
supposed to use it.
Be honest with me.
- Did you give me the scissors?
- Yes.
I never saw them though.
Suk Jin, please.
Don't be like that.
- Is it this way?
- His appearance makes me laugh.
Look.
- Come on in.
- It's Michael Jackson.
- Michael Jackson.
- He's back.
There's no need to be tense.
His entrance always gets me.
I laugh every single time.
It's not at all difficult.
(After hearing the fake rules,
he heads to the snack pack.)
All you have to do
is eat more than the one before you.
(Glancing)
How should I rip it open?
(Michael Jackson is onto something.)
(All eyes are on the member
who guessed the real mission.)
(Which way will he
rip open the bag?)
(Contemplating)
Wait.
(Suk Jin couldn't seem
more desperate.)
This is how people usually
rip it open.
But I open it this way.
(But I open it this way.)
Do I go with the American style?
Americans open it this way.
Don't worry about what they think.
I'll give you 3 seconds. 3...
- Hold on a second.
- Two.
(He dances his old move again
and turns his back to the camera.)
(He then makes eye contact.)
This is hilarious.
(What will MJ choose to do?)
(He chooses the American way.)
- The mission is over.
- What? Why?
- I'm such an idiot.
- That was smart.
- What? Why?
- You're the weird one, Suk Jin.
This is crazy.
The mission is over.
Don't people open snacks this way?
(Ji Hyo chooses the scissors
while Kwang Soo makes a fuss.)
(He ends up choosing the scissors.)
The mission is over.
Why was it so much work for you?
Use your brain.
He almost cut his hand just now.
- What is it?
- This mission...
was about opening the snack...
in the same way Suk Jin did.
- No one did.
- No one.
Don't you open it
from top to bottom?
But it wouldn't open.
Why would there be
a serrated edge here?
- See this right here?
- That's not the issue...
- because we had scissors.
- This is how you should open it.
We were given scissors
to open it easily.
The scissors were provided.
No one opened the snack
like Suk Jin did,
so no gifts will be picked up
at the next location.
This is bad.
Let's go and eat next.
- This is bad.
- We just don't click.
- It must be shaved pork belly.
- No way.
Frozen pork belly.
- It'll be delicious.
- This is really good.
Frozen pork belly?
(Frozen pork belly was the soul food
of students...)
(in the 1980s and 1990s
who desired cheap but hearty food.)
Look at him walk into
the pork belly restaurant.
Could the picture be any weirder?
- MJ!
- Why are you all looking at me?
- You look weird almost everywhere.
- Was it this easy to be funny?
It's just too much.
Being funny is the easiest.
- I love it.
- I love it too.
Today, you're more of a thug.
One that beats laughter out of us.
I love it.
There aren't any gifts
to be won in this round,
so you'll go ahead and eat.
- I'm hungry.
- Bring it in.
- Can we all eat?
- Of course.
Frozen pork belly is to die for.
- It's been a while for me.
- This looks delicious.
- The plates are old-fashioned too.
- This is authentic...
- Korean food.
- It brings back memories.
Frozen pork belly is the best.
Okay, let me.
(Se Chan's about to grill
the meat when...)
(He places them on the grill
one by one.)
This looks delicious.
Hey.
Just pour them on there.
Don't you know how it's done?
(Don't you know how it's done?)
Just put those all on there.
- There's no need to be angry.
- Exactly.
- I just...
- Why does that anger you?
I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- Unbelievable.
- Tell me about it.
(Seok Sam just froze the mood.)
- Can't we eat comfortably?
- I don't get it.
- That's not it.
- Suk Jin...
That was me being opinionated.
(Seok Sam is too excited
by this trip down memory lane.)
There's no need to get angry.
How can I be angry when I'm smiling?
Should I sprinkle the pepper?
- I would...
- A little later.
- Hey.
- Really?
- Not yet.
- Of course you should.
Haha says not now.
- What's going on?
- Exactly.
- Can you let us eat by ourselves?
- And the motorcycle.
I'm sorry to ask,
but can you just stick to your side?
What are you saying?
Are you drawing a line between us?
You're unbelievable.
Aren't we here on a trip together?
- A trip?
- What?
- How is this a trip?
- That's not the case.
We're filming a variety show.
Why would you
sprinkle pepper on these?
- He did it on ours.
- It's the highlight of this dish.
- We don't want any pepper.
- But frozen pork belly...
We don't like pepper
with our frozen pork belly.
- Are you kidding me?
- Jong Kook,
- take that from him.
- Hey.
- I don't want any pepper with mine.
- Suk Jin.
Sprinkle some on your head,
why don't you?
(Sprinkling pepper on his head
is recommended.)
That's a good idea.
Very good. Nicely done.
- Yes, just like that.
- That's the best option.
It's a good idea.
- Does it seem denser now?
- Yes.
Anyone who needs it should go next.
- Should I sprinkle some more?
- No, I'm good.
Right on top of the head.
- They're good to eat now.
- Gosh.
- Let's enjoy it.
- We'll enjoy it!
(Seok Sam enjoys it too...)
(despite not getting his way
with the pepper.)
How is it?
Can you say this is cooked?
It's good.
(It fills the stomachs
of hungry students.)
(Haha is welcomed into
the world of frozen pork belly too.)
It's to die for. This is crazy.
(Haha is welcomed into
the world of frozen pork belly too.)
You know,
to be here with Michael Jackson...
Tell me about it.
- The restaurant will get famous.
- It'll hit the jackpot.
Do you like frozen pork belly?
- Bacon?
- Bacon.
- Nice bacon.
- This is killing me.
- Gosh.
- How is it?
This is crazy. It's really good.
Why does he sound so awkward?
Why...
Come on. You should elaborate.
Why? I don't want to be good at it.
You don't want to be good at it?
(What does he mean by that?)
- You don't want to be good at it?
- I'm not good at it.
Shouldn't one say
he's not good at it?
Suk Jin,
- are you a foreigner too?
- Are you Michael Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin Jackson?
- You're not making any sense.
Why not just dress like Haha?
Which Korean language school
do you go to?
- Yonsei.
- Yonsei?
- I'm like this at home though.
- You can start eating now.
- This is hilarious.
- So don't say it's weird.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
It's Chapaghetti.
Gosh, thank you so much.
You should eat that with...
- With the noodles.
- It's to die for.
- That's mine.
- No, it's mine.
- It's mine!
- The Chapaghetti.
It's mine!
What's wrong with you?
- Let's share.
- You can have some later.
I haven't seen anyone
be this childish before.
Unbelievable.
How many do you have left?
What?
- None?
- I'm sure there's more.
Hey. Darn you.
What's the matter with you?
Unbelievable.
(Seok Sam's outcries
lead them to share.)
- It's been cooked well.
- I can't believe it.
Why don't I...
eat it deliciously?
(After cooling down
the noodles a bit...)
He's making it look so good.
- South Korea.
- No one eats noodles like he does.
He makes it look good.
(What's enjoyable
is considered as protein.)
What do you need?
Aren't you curious
as to how that tastes?
- Do you want some?
- Sure.
(Smirking)
- That...
- Michael, do you want some?
- Does it intrigue you?
- Yes.
("Running Entertainment News")
What's that?
Is that jjamppong?
- No, it's not jjamppong.
- It's jjolmyeon.
- Jjolmyeon?
J, j, o, l.
J, j, o, l. Jjol.
I get it. It's jjol!
I had forgotten
how good frozen pork belly is.
(Suk Jin steals it
as soon as it's cooked.)
My gosh.
This is the best.
- The kimchi.
- Isn't the kimchi good?
- Look at Suk Jin's eyes.
- Why?
He's dead serious and hungry.
He's set on having his fill today.
- Suk Jin, my friend.
- Yes.
Oh, no.
- No.
- No?
That's not what I like.
(Michael's generosity
is too much for Seok Sam.)
(After enjoying
a good amount of pork...)
I'd love some rice with this.
I see you eat meat with rice.
Yes, I do.
How many would you like?
- I think it's just Suk Jin.
- Well...
But you had the noodles.
- But still.
- You still want the rice?
- There's always room for rice.
- Can we get a bowl of rice?
Sure. Don't you think about
stealing from me.
(Suk Jin answers...)
(when the order is made.)
Suk Jin.
(Seok Sam's blinded by gluttony.)
- Why did you answer him?
- Am I not allowed to do that?
What do you mean?
I'm genuinely worried now.
- Are you okay?
- Suk Jin.
The bowl of rice...
What's with you today?
Is something up with you?
Is this a restaurant you know?
(Nothing's up with him,
and it's not a restaurant he owns.)
- What's with him?
- What's gotten into you?
Thank you.
(Suk Jin's bowl of rice is served.)
Nothing beats this, you know.
With the rice?
(He's curious.)
No one's eating rice over here.
(He said that when
it's only him eating rice.)
- I...
- Suk Jin's out of it.
Why?
He needs to eat,
respond to what we say,
work the show,
and listen to the director.
- Right.
- He has so much to do.
That's why...
Suk Jin.
Look at him eat.
He just won't stop eating.
- I know.
- Look at his chopsticks move.
Who knew they could move this fast?
What's with you today?
I'm so glad this was fully cooked.
He's nimble today as well.
(After eating their fill...)
Gosh, that was enjoyable.
I'm full now.
I'm turning off the stove.
We're done, right?
Does anyone want more?
Me.
(Me!)
For how long are you going to eat?
- What about the show?
- That's enough.
You should eat more
when you get home.
- Suk Jin's eating a lot today.
- Tell me about it.
- His appetite must be back.
- I think that's the case.
Gosh, this is good.
It'll be funny
if Suk Jin gets a stomachache.
- "I'm not feeling well."
- "What... What's wrong with me?"
"We should stop filming
for a second."
- "Something's wrong."
- "Bo Pil, hold on."
"Bo Pil, can you edit this out?"
- "Call an ambulance."
- "An ambulance."
No way.
He'll be like this. "Gosh!"
"Bo Pil, only air the scenes
where I look healthy."
"What could be wrong with me?"
"I'm dying over here."
If that happens,
it'll be a funny way
to end the show.
Suk Jin develops a stomachache.
- That's the worst.
- Suk Jin's stomachache.
Imagine calling him tomorrow
only to hear him say this.
"I'm in the hospital."
(He'd say he's in the hospital
if Jae Suk calls him tomorrow.)
(Suk Jin's story would suddenly
develop into a hospital scene.)
"Did I add too much pepper?"
"The doctor told me
not to eat burnt food."
It's killing me.
When will you put down
your chopsticks, Suk Jin?
(The pork belly lover
finally puts down his chopsticks.)
- Everyone. Now we'll decide...
- It was good!
on the number of gifts
you'll acquire in the next spot.
This mission is to take selfies...
to capture your happy moments
right now.
(Taking Selfies to Capture
Your Happy Moments)
Everyone will stand
in front of the camera.
Once the three-second timer starts,
you'll hide so that no one
can be captured in the picture.
- The picture?
- We have to hide?
You'll get a total of eight chances.
Each time you fail,
the number of gifts will be deducted
by one.
(1 gift will be deducted
each time they fail.)
We will make it easier gradually.
(But it will get easier gradually.)
We have to hide?
- All right.
- We can't just turn our backs?
You have to hide
your body completely.
- There's nowhere to hide though.
- How are we supposed to hide?
There's no way
we can hide completely in here.
We should all hide under the tables.
- It's a group mission, right?
- Yes, it's a group mission.
Let's give it a try
since you have many chances.
Here we go. Get ready.
It's three seconds.
Set, go!
(3 seconds start.)
2, 1.
Why are you blocking me?
(Wrestling)
- Why would you block him?
- Why are you doing this?
- Why did you block me?
- What's wrong with you?
- My gosh.
- I was trying to hide, but...
- You're so mischievous.
- This isn't an individual mission.
- It's not an individual mission!
- You should've moved!
It's a group mission.
- My gosh.
- We lost the chance.
You see? Everyone is in the picture.
They are.
Anyway, that's a fail.
We'll move to a spot
that's a little easier.
- My gosh.
- It's close by.
(The alley outside the restaurant
is a little more spacious.)
Isn't the alley more difficult
than the restaurant?
(So Min came outside first
to look for a spot to hide.)
There's nowhere to hide.
(Smiling)
Let's take a photo, Ji Hyo.
Shall we jump?
(Precious sisters,
the sentiment of the old days)
(These girls are having fun
with the burst mode.)
- We have to hide in the alley?
- Yes.
- I'll hide here.
- Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo! Can you see me or not?
- I can't see you.
- I'll hide here.
Can you see me, Ji Hyo?
What about me?
Kwang Soo, that won't work.
I think putting this on will help.
- You want me to put that on?
- If you put this on...
If you put this on and stand,
they wouldn't know.
(Se Chan suggests Kwang Soo
put on a safety cone to hide.)
Put it on.
- Like this?
- No one would know it's you.
- I can't see you.
- Right?
- You can't see me?
- No.
Where did Kwang Soo go?
- Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo passed.
- He passed.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You'll let me pass if I do this?
They're making fun of you.
(Darn you.)
Where will you hide?
I'll go up there with Se Chan.
- Kwang Soo, listen.
- So Min and I'll go there.
Gather around, everyone,
so I can see all of you.
- This is... Wait a minute.
- Gather around.
You should press the button, Haha.
Run as fast as you can.
- I'll run right after you do.
- Don't hide there.
Okay!
- Wait.
- Okay!
Wait. Why is he so tense?
- What's wrong with you?
- I'll run that way.
- Okay. Run that way.
- You're sweating.
I'll run that way.
Press it.
1, 2, 3.
Move!
(3 seconds start.)
(Seok Sam and Jong Kook
run and hide behind the door.)
(Ji Hyo and So Min hide in front
of the door as promised.)
Move!
(His overalls slipped down?)
(He reveals his underwear
while trying to climb up the wall.)
(He freezes in shock.)
(He's like a salmon flapping around
after failing to return home.)
What are you doing? Come on.
- Come on, Kwang Soo!
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- My gosh, seriously.
What's with you?
One of you should've hidden
somewhere else.
- Hey!
- Why did you...
- I'm sorry.
- His pants came off.
- Listen.
- Let's check out the photo.
- All right.
The one who presses the button...
- should hide somewhere close.
- He's right!
The one at the back
should go the farthest.
Look at Kwang Soo.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- Darn it.
You should grab me, Se Chan.
I shouldn't run.
Why are your pants off?
- This thing just slipped.
- He took them off himself.
- Seriously.
- This slipped.
We should move a little faster.
- I'm in the picture too.
- You are?
I'm almost in the picture. You see?
Everyone, please gather
in front of the camera.
Hurry. Let's do this then.
The ones at the back...
- should go the farthest.
- Hide as much as you can.
Also, I'm really fast,
so make way for me.
- I think...
- You're fast?
you'll fall when we do the mission.
- I think you'll fall.
- Make way for me since I'm fast.
Kwang Soo, don't stand there.
Stand with Se Chan.
- I'll go over there.
- That's right.
- I couldn't climb the wall.
- Ready.
- I'll hold you.
Run fast.
Set, go!
- Hurry!
- You punk.
(Hurrying off)
(They manage to hide
faster than before.)
We got it.
- No, no.
- We aren't in the photo.
- What was I supposed to do then?
- We chose the same spot.
- Haha didn't...
- I think we got it.
- Come on, Suk Jin!
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin. Jong Kook!
- Why? What's wrong?
Haha and I hid in the same spot.
It got messed up.
Suk Jin is actually showing
a V-sign.
What were you doing?
- Suk Jin is showing a V-sign.
- Wait, am I in the picture too?
- All right.
- I laughed because it was funny.
We'll give you
five seconds from now.
- Okay.
- Five seconds is more than enough.
We can hide in five seconds.
- We have enough time.
- Just run as fast as you can.
Everyone, run.
Ready. You need to run fast.
- You too, Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- I'll push you.
- Ready.
Set, go!
Go, go, go!
Go!
(Amid the busy crowd,)
(the two middle-aged men
struggle to hide.)
Who grabbed me? Darn it.
- I... Who was it?
- Come on!
- Why would you grab me?
- I didn't grab you!
This is...
Gosh, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin.
- What's wrong with them?
Does everyone have to hide?
Of course.
Everyone needs to hide?
- That's what we're doing!
- By the way,
- Who made this rule?
- why does everyone have to hide?
- Why do you need to be so strict?
- Seriously.
You're too strict.
We have only a few left.
- How many do we have? 4?
- There are 4 gifts left.
- If so, then let's try again.
- Only four can get the gifts.
You need to gather in front
of the camera before beginning.
- Jackson, look at the camera.
- Jackson.
1, 2, 3! Move!
(They're off!)
Three! Move!
(Stampeding)
(After a few trials,)
(they hurriedly run and hide
behind the doors.)
I might be seen.
(Ha Jackson does not lose his pose
until the end.)
(Did we get it?)
All right. Please check.
- Did everyone go inside?
- Why are we fighting...
- among ourselves?
- I'm sure we got it.
We got it.
- We got it, didn't we?
- We got it, right?
- Gosh, Jae Suk!
- If you are in the picture...
- Jae Suk is in the picture!
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
- You should've moved inside.
- Jae Suk.
- Whose are these colorful shoes?
- I really moved deep inside.
- Darn you.
(A colorful shoe
was caught on camera.)
- I mean...
- Whose are these colorful shoes?
- I mean, I did move...
- What on earth happened?
I really moved deep inside.
What's wrong with him seriously?
This is unbelievable.
- You should just run.
- What's wrong with you?
- This will be our last chance.
- For real.
- Let's go, entering class of 1991!
- Let's do it!
- Let's do it.
- You should run to the restaurant.
- I'll do that.
- We need to succeed this time.
Just hide behind the doors!
Come here, you.
- Just hide behind there.
- Go behind there.
- Run.
- I'll follow you.
Just follow me.
We can all hide there
since we have five seconds.
Let's all hide behind the doors.
Yes, we have more than enough time.
You'll have to look at the camera
before you start.
- I can't...
- Jackson.
- Stand in front of me.
- Guys.
- Haha, come to the front.
- Jackson.
- I can see my face.
- Jackson, you're too far away.
- Come closer, Jackson.
Come on.
You'll keep calling me Jackson?
(He's happy about it.)
He likes it.
Ready.
- Go! Run!
- Run!
(They try hiding within 5 seconds
for the 6th time.)
Come inside. Stick to the wall.
(Almost everyone managed
to reach the doors.)
(Michael Jackson who lives for style
manages to strike a pose.)
Come inside. Stick to the wall.
Okay.
There's no way we'd fail this time.
- Did we get it?
- I have a bad feeling about it.
(They come outside
with much confidence.)
(There's no way
we'd fail this time.)
- We got it, right?
- We got it this time.
- I think we got it.
- I think Jae Suk's in it.
- No way we'd fail this time.
- I'm not in it.
(They need to succeed this time
to get 3 gifts at least.)
(Although he was the main reason
for failing so far,)
(Jae Suk seems confident.)
- He's in it, right?
- No, he's not.
- We got it!
It's perfect.
I can't believe this worked.
We did it.
- Go! Run!
- Run!
Come inside. Stick to the wall.
(It's a complete success.)
(They succeed after 6 tries!)
- Isn't it amazing?
- We did it.
Let's move to the next spot.
You can get in the car now.
- Let's go.
- It was...
The place we're heading to next
is a comic book store.
- I love comic book stores.
- Wow, really?
Comic book stores are really nice
these days.
- It's the sentiment of the 1990s.
- This place is amazing.
- Wow.
- There are so many books.
Look, it's an old-style sofa.
Jae Suk,
they must've read this many times.
I know.
The popular ones are all tattered.
It's "Champ."
- I had one in my neighborhood.
- I practically lived there.
How about "Urban Legend?"
"City Conquest" is right here.
I can't remember
how far I read "City Conquest."
Of course you can't.
Wow, there are so many new ones.
- It's "Princess Hours."
- "Princess Hours."
- Ji Hyo, it's "Princess Hours."
- This is amazing.
("Princess Hours" is
the original comic...)
(of the drama Ji Hyo was in.)
I also read
the comic book version first.
(The original pretty girl
from comic books, Ji Hyo)
Should I take "Princess Hours?"
Yes, you should.
"Vitamin!"
(Oh, gosh, it's "Vitamin!")
I learned about love
through these books.
(The romance comics that taught
Love Frog about love)
(Michael Jackson is immersed
in the basketball comic.)
This is the best scene.
This one right here.
I bawled my eyes out.
"Mr. Ahn."
(Mr. Ahn.)
"I want to..."
(I want to...)
"play basketball."
(I want to play basketball.)
(Jackson chokes up.)
- Eight.
- Wrong.
- What's the line again?
- You won't get a prison sentence...
- You won't get a prison sentence,
but you'll have to pay a fine.
Of course.
- Glass.
- That's it. That one's nice.
- It's pretty.
- Pencil sharpener.
Where are we going
for the last spot?
- Where do you think we're going?
- Pil-dong.
Hyehwa-dong?
- Where are we going?
- Samcheong-dong?
- It must be a retro town.
- Insa-dong!
- Suk Jin! Suk Jin.
- It's Gwanghwamun.
- Isn't this where you used to live?
(Gyeongbokgung Palace)
- Isn't this...
- Oh, right.
I used to
sweep the garden a lot here.
This is the place.
I had to stoop down all the time.
- Right?
- I never got to see the sky.
(Leaving the place
of Suk Jin's memories behind...)
The last place we're going to
is an LP bar.
(The last place of memories
is an LP bar.)
I love it!
That'll be our last place.
Seriously, music is...
Lee Sang Woo's song
we listened to earlier...
- I loved it.
- "La Boum."
We should listen to the Beatles.
Look at these.
I want to have one too.
- I love this song so much.
- I love this song too.
It's my favorite song. Hello, sir.
- It's "Take On Me."
- It's A-ha's song.
It's "Take On Me" by A-ha.
(Excited Michael Jackson
enters the LP bar as well.)
- Look at him.
- Haha, come on.
He automatically becomes
Michael Jackson.
We finally found a place
that suits Haha!
We finally found it!
Michael Jackson!
(Michael Jackson finally found
a place that suits him.)
It's A-ha's song.
(They take a trip down memory lane
with an LP song.)
(The middle-aged men
move to the music.)
(Too immersed)
(Everyone around the globe...)
(dances to the masterpiece
of memories.)
So this is how an LP sounds?
It's A-ha. You know A-ha, right?
It's "Take On Me" by A-ha.
I used to love A-ha.
The music video of this song
is a montage of pencil drawing.
That's right!
(The music video
of A-ha's "Take On Me")
They made a parody
of this music video...
and shot a commercial for a drink...
with Cho Yong Pil.
- It was a commercial for McCOL.
- McCOL?
- They parodied this music video.
- Right, I remember.
A-ha is an amazing band.
This song still sounds amazing.
This place is an LP bar.
You must listen to the stories
of others and songs in an LP bar.
- That's right.
- In an LP bar?
We'll give you a chance
to earn extra gifts here.
(It's a chance to earn extra gifts.)
Please briefly write your story
related to...
the song you're requesting
and give it to us.
The owner will choose one,
and we'll give that person a gift.
- Oh, we're writing our own story?
- Just like how we...
- used to request a song to DJs?
- This is... Wait a minute.
Shall we take a trip
down memory lane again?
I do have good memories.
(Radio shows used to read out
handwritten stories and play songs.)
Shall I reminisce the old days?
- Gosh.
- The old days...
This won't be enough
to write my story.
(This won't be enough
to write my story.)
The owner will pick
the story he likes?
He'll read your stories and...
Sir. I'll write a story
about my breakup.
- Me too.
- You can't do that.
- You can't hint at him like that.
- Why not? What's wrong with it?
- I mean...
- I'm just telling him.
I'll write
about my beautiful breakup too.
Wait, I should write about that.
I was a high school senior...
when I met this woman.
- Wait, is it okay...
- I was a high school senior.
- to talk about other women?
- It's fine.
- Of course.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
- Is this okay?
- Doesn't your wife watch the show?
- You mean my wife?
Of course it's okay.
It's been decades already.
But I think she wouldn't like it.
I know I wouldn't.
I failed the college exam,
but she passed.
So we had to break up.
I gave her...
I gave her a gift.
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry,
but today is not your special.
- Why would you...
- You gave me happiness
(Immersed in memories)
That's Sunflower's song.
- You know that song, right?
- I know that song.
It was when I was
a high school senior.
Oh, was it?
- I...
- Is that so?
- went on a blind date.
- Wait a minute.
No, this song is...
I can't choose this song.
I'm reminded of someone else.
- Hold on.
- I should pick Kim Jong Seo's song.
I should pick "You Do Not Answer"
by Kim Jong Seo.
I can't forget the girl I met
by chance on the bus.
I can't forget...
(I can't forget...)
the girl I met by chance.
Why do you two read it out loud
when you write something?
- When I saw you...
- Why do you do that?
- That's how you write a story.
- Please.
- I can't forget...
- That's what old people do.
It's what old people do.
They also read it out loud
when they text someone.
He also says his password
out loud when he presses it.
The song that was being played
on my cassette player...
I almost wrote
"cassette player" too!
- I'm writing it again.
- The song that was played...
I need to read it out loud
to write it.
My goodness.
What can I do then?
This is the only way I can write.
(Glancing)
- Hold on.
- What? What is it?
It's true. It's a true story.
Why would you write that a big fire
broke out in your house in 1995?
- It's a true story.
- Don't try so hard...
- to be picked.
- I'm just writing my story.
- Don't lie.
- It really was on fire.
I'm done.
(I'm done.)
I kept it short.
What? Do you think I wrote it long?
I'll read them for you.
Give them to me.
- So then...
- It's a true story.
- Don't write something like this.
- Let us hear it.
"Dear owner."
Why would you write this?
- But still...
- I'll just skip it.
- Don't write things like this.
- Right, you shouldn't.
"The interior design
of your bar is really pretty?"
Someone needs to butter him up.
"There was a big fire in my house
in 1995."
Why would you talk about this?
- This is so sad.
- Why would you tell us this?
I just wrote my story.
- It must've been shocking.
- Right.
"I was immature,"
"and I asked my parents for money
to go to an arcade."
"I'm still embarrassed
by what I did."
"To reflect on my bad behavior,
I request 'Arcade' by Han's Band."
- That's a good choice.
- Han's Band's "Arcade."
- It's a great song. Of course.
- It brings back the memories.
(Everyone who loved going to arcades
must've hummed to this song.)
Yes. My gosh.
(I love it.)
- It's a great song.
- "It was..."
"It was when I was
a high school senior."
"I went on a blind date..."
(It was when I was
a high school senior.)
I don't understand what he wrote.
- The next paragraph says...
- Are you just skipping it?
I'll read it.
(I'll read it.)
- Wait.
- Hey.
- How can a DJ do this?
- I mean, the story...
- Hey, what kind of a DJ...
- The story was too...
It made me yawn
from the first paragraph.
You'll get a chance
to read it someday.
My gosh, how could he disregard
my memories like that?
I'll try not to fall asleep.
Okay. Let me read it again.
"It was when I was
a high school senior."
"I went on a blind date..."
"with a girl who was a May Queen."
"When we started
developing feelings for each other,"
"I failed the college exam,
and she passed it."
"I want to listen to the song
I gave her as a gift..."
"when we broke up at a bus stop."
"That song is Sunflower's
'Someone Who Gives Me Happiness.'"
It's a very ordinary story.
You think that's ordinary?
- It is.
- Hey.
It's ordinary.
- I failed the exam, but she passed.
- This isn't anything special.
That's why we broke up.
Isn't that sad?
It's one of those stories
that radio DJs get all the time.
He's right.
- You've never been a DJ.
- I'll read the next story.
"Have you ever had a coffee
with an angel?"
It's a song title.
"Would you like to
have one with me?"
"Where are you looking at?"
"I'm looking at you."
- It's So Min's.
- It must be So Min's story.
- Just rip that story, Jae Suk.
- It's So Min's story.
It's the worst.
What kind of story is that?
- It's full of nonsense.
- Why?
- Is it one of your stories?
- Just rip it, Jae Suk.
It's too corny.
- Why?
- I always say this,
- She's just...
- but...
I've never thought
that a woman could be corny.
She's too corny.
All right. Here's the next story.
He requested a song first.
It's "Fate" by Lee Sun Hee.
"A burglar broke into my house
in 1990."
Who is it?
Didn't someone talk about...
a burglar already?
"A burglar broke into his house."
A fire and a burglar.
- Whose story is it?
- It's a true story.
- Who would...
- Why did everyone suffer so much?
So is it a story about how you
made friends with the burglar?
- No, it's not.
- Is that it?
"A burglar broke into my house
in 1990."
"My mother had a hard time."
"This is my mother's favorite song."
"That's right. I'm a bad son."
"If you pick this song,"
"I will be a filial son
for the first time."
(He tries to appeal to emotions
with talks of filial love.)
He is appealing to emotions.
- Kwang Soo.
- That's not true.
- This is messed up.
- "I will be a filial son."
"Please let me be a filial son."
"I want to see my mom's smile."
Ji Hyo, you wrote something too.
(It's time to read the story
by the girl with purple eyeshadow.)
"They say the higher power sent you
a mother..."
"because it can't grant
your every wish."
"This is for all the mothers
in the world."
(That came out of nowhere.)
- That came out of nowhere.
- What is this?
- What does that make us?
- I wanted Na Hoon A's song,
- so I wrote something fitting.
- "I respect them."
- "I love them. They are precious."
- What's the song?
It's "Don't Cry, Hong Do"
by Na Hoon A.
- There is more.
- What?
"I am dying for a smoke right now,"
"so please play
'Cigarette Girl' as well."
(Jackson slanders her.)
Jackson.
Jackson, that's rude.
- No smoking. No smoking.
- That's rude.
- No smoking.
- That's hilarious.
All right.
"There was a shy child."
"He was a particularly shy child."
"He couldn't even order jjajangmyeon
at a Chinese restaurant,"
"so he would trudge home
on an empty stomach."
"He would trudge home."
"He was a particularly shy child,"
"so he couldn't even tell the girl
that he likes her."
"He had to see her leave
without a word."
"On his way back,
he cried his eyes out."
"A woman and man
who were passing by said,"
"'Child, are you okay?'"
"'Child, why are you crying?'"
"'Child, it's okay.'"
(His writing skills
make them laugh.)
"That child now lives
as a father of three children."
"I want to tell him,"
"'Child, are you okay?'"
"'Child, I love you.'"
"Earth, Wind and Fire's
'September.'"
(The story is a mess,
but he picked a nice pop song!)
- "September."
- Do you remember?
(He feels proud.)
All right. Here is another one.
"I was in 11th grade."
"That girl was standing
at the bus stop."
"She caught my eyes at first sight."
- Jae Suk, I heard it before.
- Is it yours?
- Really?
- You read it as you wrote it.
"Red Rose on Wednesday."
(Yellow Cap revealed the story
as he wrote it.)
I see.
- We are done.
- There is another one.
Jong Kook's story.
"I dreamed of becoming a singer,"
"but I wondered if I should give up
since my parents were against it."
"Many songs comforted me,"
"but I listened to this often
when I lost my way."
"It was played on the streets.
It's Choi Ho Sub's..."
- "As Time Passes."
- It's an incredible song.
- I know.
- As time passes
You will forget about
how your heart almost burst
With longing
"I want to feel those emotions again
after all these years."
"Please take me
on a time machine ride."
The owner listened
to all the song requests.
Sir, please play a song.
Everyone had a nice story.
- Sir, please play a song.
- Which song would he like?
I think he will play Haha's song.
- A pop song would be nice.
- He is taking it out.
He is choosing it.
Red rose on Wednesday
- As time passes
- Do you remember?
Please play it.
- It must be something upbeat.
- I know.
No.
There is this sentimentality.
Hey!
(He recognizes the song
from the first note.)
- "As Time Passes."
- All right.
He took me on a time machine ride.
I admit defeat.
Choi Ho Sub's "As Time Passes."
- He is going back in time.
- He took Jong Kook...
- on a time machine ride.
- Seriously.
- He took me on a time machine ride.
- I am becoming absorbed.
- Seriously. This song is nice.
The chorus is really sad.
That's right.
(This song helped him find his way
and debut as a singer.)
This song...
("As Time Passes" by Choi Ho Sub)
I listened to it so many times.
(For me)
(You show a smile)
Isn't there a version
by a female singer?
(But you can't hide
a dejected look on your face)
- Park Bo Ram sang it.
- You are right.
(But you can't hide
a dejected look on your face)
(Weakly)
You turn around
This is so nice.
I really like Suk Jin's voice.
I really like his voice.
Sir, please get us a bottle of beer.
A bottle of soju too.
I know it
- When it comes to our love
- This is the end
Even if we want it to,
it can't last forever
Why are you crying?
- Time passes without fail
- As time passes
- You will forget about
- How your heart almost burst
- With longing
But there was love
you cherished dearly
- Please remember that
- As time passes
- You will forget about
How your heart almost burst
with longing
But there was love
you cherished dearly
- Please remember that
It's a masterpiece of a song.
You chose a great song. Thank you.
It was amazing.
Did you watch a performance?
- Did you watch a performance?
- No.
It's such a sad song.
- Stop crying.
Why are you crying?
Did you watch a performance?
It's such a sad song.
She drives me crazy.
"Please remember that."
- Please remember that
"Your heart almost burst
with longing."
Why is Ji Hyo so funny?
Look at Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
(She is drunk on the song.)
Can I take a photo?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Sir.
I am sorry,
please play an upbeat song.
I want to shake my body.
Why don't I choose one of you
to pick a present?
- Shall we do that?
- Yes.
- All of us will shake our bodies.
- He picked a song.
- It will be amped up.
(The upbeat song is on standby.)
All right.
(This song is...)
It's the song we talked about.
I took a trip down memory lane.
Is it a song by Two Two?
It's the song we talked about.
(She begins to make herself pretty.)
My body remembers the song.
- She is so scary.
- What?
(I don't know anything.)
- When did she start doing that?
- Do you have a split personality?
When did she start doing that?
(Her mood changes with the song.)
- What is going on?
- She was just crying.
- She was crying.
- Hold on.
Weren't you crying?
(When did I do that?)
She is scary.
(Dancing)
Hey.
You are ridiculous.
(Generation X has
shocking mood swings!)
(Her cute steps
liven up the atmosphere.)
You should dance too.
Come on and dance.
Come on, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo comes forward in the end.)
(Her fans double over.)
(Haughty)
That dance suits her.
(I became two)
This is crazy.
That dance suits her.
Good job. Good job.
She is so funny.
(The queen bee
of the roller skating rink is back.)
She is good.
That dance suits her.
She is so funny.
I love it.
- She is the best.
- You know...
Sir, it was a great song.
Thank you.
It was the best.
You know, I must point this out.
In Part One, So Min cried.
(Then she transformed.)
- She wiped her tears.
- It was scary.
- In Part Two,
she got up from her seat.
- She was like a princess.
- Ji Hyo.
- Seriously.
- It was so funny.
These sisters are funny.
I became a fan of them.
(Double Bells Sisters
have distinct charms.)
- I feel faint.
- I almost died from laughing.
I went to the roller skating rink
so often.
"La Boum?"
- What is this?
- "Touch by Touch."
- Gosh, this song...
- What is this?
What is this?
He loves it.
- What is this?
- Don't you know this song?
I don't know it.
Look at Suk Jin.
He loves it. Suk Jin loves it.
He loves it.
- What is this?
- His face turned red...
because he is so happy.
(The 20-year-old Suk Jin
loves the song.)
Look at Suk Jin.
It's so funny.
Seriously.
He is the only one who is excited.
I will dance with Suk Jin.
(I will dance with Suk Jin.)
- This dance.
- What is this song?
(The ugly duo in the ballroom)
Did they dance at the club
like that?
(Did they dance at the club
like that?)
(Surprisingly,
they used to dance like this.)
Did they dance at the club
like that?
They are the only ones
who are excited.
- Why are they so happy?
- I don't even know.
(No women would approach them.)
Those women keep looking at us!
Dance diligently!
They are looking at us.
- They are looking at us.
(The queen appears.)
Would you dance with us?
How old are you?
I am 25 years old.
- Suk Jin is excited for real.
- Would you dance with us?
Dance with us.
The friend.
Hey, I talked to her.
- Really?
- I talked to her.
"I talked to her."
I talked to her.
(The two men's timid outing
ends with a misunderstanding.)
Thank you.
I haven't danced like this
in a long while.
Everyone danced like this back then.
- So this is how they partied.
- That was funny.
They partied in a fun way.
After two songs,
- our clothes were sweaty.
- They were sweaty.
(They always ended up sweaty
after a grand outing.)
After this,
you guys trudged home together.
- Right?
- In the rain.
I bet you guys didn't have bus fare.
We took the bus home.
We danced until we turned sweaty.
The owner...
will choose someone who expressed
the good cheer of the song.
Everyone did well,
but one member danced diligently...
even though the song was old.
So Min.
(So Min!)
Thank you.
So Min acquired a present.
Pick one present each.
I will pick the pager.
- It will be nice to have it.
- I will pick the retro crayons.
(6 presents remain.)
(Robot puppy, song encyclopedia,
Sarangbang candy, video cassettes)
1, 2, 3.
(4 people will acquire the present!)
(Who will take 4 presents
through this mission?)
This mission will decide
who will get the four presents.
It's simple.
I divided you up into 2 teams of 4,
Team Old and Team Young.
You remember how
you were divided up earlier, right?
- Yes.
- That will be your team.
(Glancing over)
- Am I Team Old?
- You are Team Old.
- I brought a story...
from the production crew.
Find the LP record
of a song that suits the story...
and play it.
Then the production crew
will pick a song.
- Okay.
- A song that suits the story.
- The production crew's story.
- We will win.
- In any case,
- We have that sentimentality.
the production crew members are...
about our age.
We have the same sentimentality.
So this is the story.
The title is,
"I Am Going Crazy Too."
"Hello, I am So Min's cameraman,
Ji Bong Jo."
- It's Bong Jo's story.
- Bong Jo?
"Due to the incessant complaints
by a fellow cameraman, Yun Sang,"
- "I am losing weight day by day."
- Really?
Oh, no.
"It's all because of Kwang Soo."
"As soon as the shoot begins,
he complains about Kwang Soo..."
"and it honestly gives me
a headache."
"I am exhausted
because Kwang Soo runs too fast."
"Gosh, Kwang Soo got the penalty.
I will have to go home late."
- My goodness.
- I understand how he feels.
I can relate to him.
I am so disappointed in him.
"Yun Sang..."
Seriously.
"Yun Sang is old,
so he doesn't have enough energy."
"Since it gets repeated every week,
I don't know how to react."
"What should I do?"
"Please tell me what I can do..."
"and recommend a song
for the complaining cameraman."
A song
for the complaining cameraman.
Two people from each team.
You have a minute.
Are most songs here?
That's perfect, So Min.
- Nothing can beat it.
- Right?
That song will bring us victory.
That's right.
- So Min.
- Sir, we chose this one.
Did you choose a song?
It's for Bong Jo.
Please play Team Old's song first.
I hope it will help him
find comfort.
Until when will you be able
to deal with his complaints?
(Team Old creates
a heartwarming atmosphere.)
(Which song did they choose?)
Gosh, it's this song.
It's a masterpiece.
("White Butterfly" by Kim Jung Ho)
What's the title?
"White Butterfly."
I think I know this song.
(Team Young barely recognizes
the song.)
(They are already absorbed.)
(Oh, don't think)
It's incredible!
Hey, don't think. Forget everything.
(About what's in the past)
Why did they choose this song?
It's too depressing.
The cameraman might not know it.
He is unsure.
(Don't be sad)
(They are absorbed
in the song they chose)
- When it's time
You know,
we are listening without a thought.
Look at them. They became emotional.
They are old and we are young.
Michael Jackson, don't cry.
- Don't cry, Michael.
- Don't cry.
Don't be sad.
Once it's in the past,
you will see that it's nothing.
It will pass.
This song is too depressing.
Don't be sad.
The song is really nice,
but it doesn't go well
with the story.
You should have thought
about Bong Jo's feelings...
and what he wanted to say
to Yun Sang.
- Here we go.
- Let's hear it.
This song represents his feelings.
Let's go.
Oh, this song.
- I knew it.
- Let's go.
- I thought about this song.
("Speed Up Losers" by Crying Nut)
(The strong lyrics
made the song popular.)
(This song will represent
Bong Jo's feelings.)
Yun Sang!
- Shut up!
One more time! Yun Sang!
There you go.
(Yun Sang feels faint.)
(Bong Jo laughs so hard
that his glasses become foggy.)
Yun Sang!
- Shut up!
There you go.
- They won.
- 2, 3, 4.
- Shut up!
- Yun Sang! Shut up!
- Yun Sang! Shut up and listen!
- Shut up and listen!
(Team Young livens up the atmosphere
with the karaoke hit song.)
(Speed up, losers)
(Yellow Cap crashes the party.)
(Michael Jackson runs out
as if he is in a trance.)
(They are relieving
their pent-up stress.)
(The one-shot addict
hogs the camera again.)
(Uncomfortable)
(Because of Yellow Cap
who jumped around excitedly,)
Okay.
(the messy performance
livened up the atmosphere.)
It was perfect.
Team Young doesn't disappoint.
- You need to delve into the story.
- That's right.
We thought of this song too.
Seriously.
The person who wrote the story
will announce the winner.
- Bong Jo will do it.
- Yes.
(Which song will Bong Jo choose?)
My body reacted right away.
His body.
So Min's team.
That's it.
We share that sentimentality.
He made that choice
because he is So Min's cameraman.
(Jae Suk suspects them
of collusion.)
- Why did he share the story?
- Hey.
To be honest, I doubt Yun Sang said
anything useless.
- Seriously.
- It was Kwang Soo's fault.
They are old farts.
You are unbelievable.
Nice choice.
(A Western old fart appears.)
We should listen
to "White Butterfly."
That's right.
That's so funny.
(Team Old wins the next match.)
Pick two people from each team
with rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Since there are 4 presents,
each team picks 2 people.)
- Rock-paper-scissors
My goodness.
(Jong Kook, Jae Suk, So Min,
and Kwang Soo get the presents!)
That's good.
I will get the robot puppy.
I will get the Sarangbang candy.
(Thinking)
"Farewell My Concussion."
It's "Farewell My Concubine."
(What?)
It's "Farewell My Concubine,"
not "Farewell My Concussion."
Okay. "Farewell My Concubine."
(She isn't good with big words.)?
Right?
I will get the one
that is in Chinese characters.
This one.
(He chooses
by looking at the pictures.)
This one.
You will get the presents
right away.
Since 2 presents remain,
2 people will receive the penalty.
(Since 2 presents remain,
2 people will receive the penalty!)
The ones with the fewest presents
will receive the penalty.
Se Chan and Ji Hyo have one present.
Excuse me?
You will see the presents first.
The LP record.
It's a turntable.
It's a nice present.
Look at this.
I got the best presents.
What is this?
- It's the best.
- I know.
(Ha Jackson
got a lot of presents in Korea.)
The two of you will receive
the penalty.
I will tell you what the penalty is.
Use the sentimentality
of the 1990s...
including the cringe-worthy comments
and actions...
to make a one-minute commercial
for Running Man.
A one-minute commercial?
That's long.
The completed commercial
will be posted...
on Running Man's social media
for promotion.
The entering class of 1991's
introduction to 1991...
will end here.
- Thank you.
(The short trip through memories
comes to an end.)
(Behind-the-scenes)
- This is...
- You are an actress!
This is ridiculous.
Let's get ready.
It's an honor to work
with a great actress like you.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- It's an honor, Ji Hyo.
You know, it's rare for you...
to work with a comedian.
When else would I work with Ji Hyo?
I am free at 5 p.m. on Sunday.
Shall we watch Running Man together
at 5 p.m. on Sunday?
(They look pretty serious.)
(You can check out the commercial
on our official social media.)
It's pretty.
(The members have a relaxing time
on the rooftop.)
Let's have a glass of beer.
(They enjoy the camping trip.)
(A text breaks the peaceful moment.)
(184 dollars, Running Campground)
(24 hours at the TV station
you enjoy with someone else's money)
(It costs a lot of money
to spend a day at the TV station.)
(A meeting with the director
is a must at the TV station.)
- The legendary director?
- This is ridiculous.
That's just wrong.
- Hello.
(The members have a tearful show
to avoid the meeting.)
(It isn't easy to spend a day
at the TV station.)
(Everything will be paid
with someone's money.)
(Who will be the one
to pay for everything?)
(Credit Card Payment Race,
When You Go to the TV Station)