(A strange energy covers the peaceful Running Village.)
(And there's a mysterious jar.)
Let's go.
(The residents enter the village without any idea.)
Hello.
Stay quiet.
The camera isn't even on yet.
(Unwelcome guests visit...)
- Hello. - This feels strange.
(cheerful Running Village.)
Hello.
(What's happening in this place?)
Today,
(Four guests from the Joseon Dynasty...)
- you will travel back in time. - Is that so?
- That's what we're doing. - We're going back to the past.
(summon them to the past.)
We have four guests who are perfect for the Joseon Dynasty.
- Joseon Dynasty? - How dare you!
There they are.
(Park Sung Hoon)
Sung Hoon.
(Kim Dong Jun)
- There's Dong Jun. - Dong Yoon!
(Jang Dong Yoon)
Dong Jun is back after a long time.
(Keum Sae Rok)
- Hello. - And there's Sae Rok.
(Human's fierce battle against evil spirits trying to destroy Joseon.)
- A disaster has broken out. - Joseon will be...
- seized with terror. - What is happening?
(Korean exorcism fantasy drama, "Joseon Exorcist")
I'll stop it before it becomes the living dead.
(Jang Dong Yoon playing Prince Chungnyeong)
Why do they not die?
You have to save his life before they do.
(Park Sung Hoon playing Prince Yangnyeong)
This country is going to be theirs.
Is there any way to get rid of them?
(Kim Dong Jun playing an acrobatic actor, Byuri)
Why do they not die?
(Keum Sae Rok playing an acrobatic actress with secrets, Keum Sae Rok)
Give up your life and protect Joseon.
(Jang Dong Yoon, Park Sung Hoon, Kim Dong Jun, Keum Sae Rok)
It's "Joseon Exorcist".
(Four actors of "Joseon Exorcist" visit Running Man.)
We have four actors from the drama.
- "Joseon Exorcist". - Please give them a big hand.
(Welcome.)
"Joseon Exorcist".
It's set in Joseon Dynasty.
I heard Sung Hoon...
(Are Sung Hoon and So Min friends?)
is So Min's close friend.
- Really? - Is that true?
- We did a drama together. - Which one?
(They played a couple in the drama in 2018.)
- What was the drama? - A one-act drama.
What is Sung Hoon like?
Sung Hoon looks cool,
but he's very weak.
- He's clumsy. - Right.
(Agreed)
If he fights against Suk Jin, Suk Jin might beat him.
(Is he as weak as Suk Jin?)
Seriously? He must be feeble.
Sung Hoon, do you not work out?
(He hates it.)
Never.
That's good.
(Weakling 2 is glad to meet a new weakling.)
He's...
- perfect for our show. - I know.
He would be like the second Kim Hee Won.
What's your hobby, Sung Hoon?
- I like to lie in bed. - Good.
(He's like us.)
- He's just like Suk Jin. - You're like me.
He likes to lie still.
(Weak)
My gosh.
- It's not that everyone... - You're right.
- has to work out hard. - I agree.
(Laughing)
- His arm is so soft. - I like that.
- He's so skinny. - It's like a sticky rice cake.
(He can't stop touching Sung Hoon's soft arm.)
And we have Jang Dong Yoon here.
(Next to the weakling, there's a pure, elegant guy, Jang Dong Yoon.)
Dong Yoon is really handsome.
Hello. I'm Jang Dong Yoon,
and I'm playing Prince Chungnyeong in "Joseon Exorcist".
- He has a great voice. - Wish me good luck.
(He has an unexpected low voice.)
- I like his voice. - I'll try my best.
- It sounds so good. - You know what?
- Dong Yoon is... - What about him?
(There's another twist.)
He got a full mark in math on the college entrance exam.
(He got a full mark in mathematics on the college entrance exam.)
- My gosh. - He's smart.
This isn't a quiz show though.
At a convenience store, he saw the clerk...
(Young men who stopped robbers by their wits)
being threatened with a weapon and stopped the robber with his wits.
(He became the talk of the town after catching a robber.)
I told them the address...
(Handsome)
as if I was talking to my friend.
(He went out on the news and made his debut later on.)
I feel so small.
I got four points in math.
Then you should just focus on your studies.
(Jealous)
- Hang on. - Why did you...
Then you should just focus on working out.
I do work out.
(Jong Kook got angry at how smart he is.)
I spend half of my time working out.
He got into the harsh world of show business instead.
Dong Yoon is...
(He's handsome.)
Hello.
What makes you so happy?
I just met eyes with Dong Jun,
so I said hello to him.
- Why did you say hello like that? - This is crazy.
(She used all her facial muscles to say hello.)
It's just...
I couldn't wave at him.
You're wearing...
- an old lady's jacket today. - Gosh, no.
She's even wearing a pearl necklace.
(A luxurious tweed jacket and a pearl necklace)
It's like you're attending your kid's school play.
(It's her outfit for guests only.)
- Hey, stop that. - I'm all dressed up today.
Next to Dong Yoon,
(Followed by Dong Yoon,)
- we have Keum Sae Rok here. - Welcome.
(it's a familiar face, Keum Sae Rok.)
I'm acquainted with Sae Rok.
I said I'd make you become a star.
(Taking credit to himself)
And you became the most searched word that day.
- I did. - Right.
(She became the most searched celebrity...)
(and shot a commercial.)
And I even did a TV commercial.
I made Sae Rok a star.
(Taking credit)
(Sae Rok met the star-maker, Big Nose.)
- Do you want me to make you a star? - Yes.
- Don't fall for that. - That's fake.
(Without Suk Jin's help,)
(she became the most searched word with her powerful shoulder dance.)
Gosh, Keum Sae Rok.
(She made herself a star with her abdominal shout.)
I knew it.
(Suk Jin didn't do anything.)
I told you I'd make you a star.
He's a star-maker.
(Sae Rok did the work, and Suk Jin took credit.)
I was surprised too.
I made a joke about the search word rankings.
(In the last episode...)
I said she was number four,
- and she really was ranked 4th. - I was ranked 4th.
That's how it started.
You should do the same thing for your stock investments.
(He causes companies to be delisted in stocks.)
Mr. Shipbuilding.
"I'm Suk Jin who invested in J Shipbuilding."
(He has no foresight of his near future asset.)
Today, with the actors from "Joseon Exorcist",
(Records of the Running Dynasty Race)
you will have the Running Dynasty Records Race.
And you will be in a hierarchical society...
(A hierarchical society...)
where the king's words are the law.
(where the king's words are the law.)
- What does that mean? - Oh, really?
So what matters is who will become the king.
(Who becomes the king is crucial to this race.)
You will decide the king right away.
(Time to pick the king)
- What? - Is it a random game?
- A random game? - I want you to pick one scroll.
(Only the king's scroll has the Royal seal.)
If Kwang Soo becomes the king, things will get bloody today.
- I know. - No, I'm...
- You know what I mean. - I want to be the king.
(Will they have a tyrant or a wise king?)
- Should we just pick one now? - Yes.
- Just pick one. - We don't know who'll be the king.
I really want to be the king.
- I'll put you guys in prison. - You don't want me to be the king.
I'll just pick what's left.
(Discreet)
(I picked it first.)
And?
(They carefully choose their scrolls.)
- Okay. - All right.
- One. - Hang on. Let me open it.
(Who will be today's king?)
- Two. - The last one...
Three.
(Empty)
- Darn it. - What's this?
It's empty.
(Is Dong Jun the king? No.)
- Is it Dong Jun? - I didn't see it yet.
What is this?
(Flustered)
- I think it's you. - It's him.
(Royal Seal)
- You're the king. - Oh, no.
(Se Chan becomes the king.)
I'm the king!
We have a horrible king.
- He can't be the king. - This isn't right.
(Complaining)
Take off Ji Suk Jin's pants.
(His first command on the throne, "Take off those yellow pants.")
- Take off his pants right away. - Hey.
- And send him... - Okay.
- to the mountain. - The mountain?
(It's expected to be a tough day.)
Am I the king?
(Exhilarated)
- I can't believe he's the king. - He's our king.
It's a hierarchical society.
So today's king is Yang Se Chan.
- All day? - Yes.
- What? - All day?
(He's King the whole day?)
It won't change at all?
In today's race, there will be three different classes.
The first is the nobles.
(Nobles: King, Queen, Premier, and Vice-premier)
They are King, Queen, Premier, and Vice-premier.
These four people are nobles.
(Classes)
- And there are four eunuchs. - What?
(Nobles, Eunuchs, and Slaves)
And there are four slaves.
(There are eunuchs.)
- There are slaves too. - I'd rather be a slave.
- I'd rather be a slave. - A slave is better than a eunuch.
(Their last pride to defend)
Don't you think so?
Those who are in the same class are in one team.
(Those of the same class are a team.)
Each team will earn rice...
(Each team will obtain rice from missions.)
through each mission.
You will get rice according to the results of each mission.
(They get different amounts of rice based on the mission rankings.)
The king gets to decide the classes of all members.
(The king gets to decide the classes of all members.)
And he can switch the classes of two members before each mission.
(And he can switch the classes of two members before each mission.)
Can I do that?
(The absolute power)
- And he can do that all day? - I'm the real king.
That is, those who want a better social status should...
get on the king's good side.
We should be nice to Se Chan.
We will be discriminated against for sure.
I'm so glad that I've always been nice to Se Chan.
(A thumbs-up)
It's started already.
Okay. I'm going to win today.
(The flatterers get to work.)
- I have to flatter Se Chan. - He's my favorite.
I don't like to flatter others.
You're dressed like a slave.
Look at his pants.
(Yellow slave pants)
During the race,
the king can talk down to everyone.
And the rest should use honorifics to the king.
- That's so nice. - This is crazy.
I love that. It's great.
(It perfectly suits the king who likes role-plays.)
Now, Se Chan, you should decide the classes...
of the 11 members as the king.
- My gosh. - I'm nervous.
(Their classes depend solely on the king.)
My goodness.
Hang on. So I'm the king.
(He should select the queen first.)
- Pick the queen first. - I see.
(She takes one step forward quietly.)
Hang on. Why are you acting like that already?
(She shyly uses hand gestures.)
Could you dance for me?
(She shows off her dance moves for the king.)
That's the filial dance.
That makes me feel uncomfortable.
(Sae Rok also shows a much softer shoulder dance.)
Oh, dear.
- Oh, what is going on? - Sae Rok is a good dancer.
- My gosh. - Please, Your Majesty.
She looks beautiful.
She dances well.
Her dance...
("Queen Pop Star". Criterion: Dance.)
- Her dance was beautiful. - She dances well.
Can a man...
- become the queen? - It's possible.
It can be a man.
(All right then.)
(They all dance together in unbiased Running Man.)
- Good. - Hey.
(Shuddering as he sees their awful dancing)
Gosh, look at them.
You guys are unbelievable.
(I'm here too, Your Majesty.)
Stop that. Enough.
- Come here. - That's dirty.
(He fails to seduce the king with his nasty twerking.)
- It's not dirty. - My gosh.
Hey, look at him.
He has long hair.
(He shows off his feeble charm.)
I'll select the queen.
(I'll select the queen.)
- What? - The king is...
(It's my first time being the King.)
That's because he's never been a king before.
(Slightly embarrassed)
I've never done this before.
- Just let it go. - Hey.
- Kings can make mistakes. - There are...
kings who aren't so smart.
- He's right. - It can happen.
(Se Chan has a hard time getting used to being the King.)
"I'll select the queen."
- I'll... - It's hard...
- select the queen. - to be the king all of a sudden.
My gosh.
The queen is...
We don't know it yet. It might be you, So Min.
(Is it So Min whom he sees every day?)
(Is it Sae Rok whom he met again after a long time?)
(Or a shocking choice?)
I think the queen has been decided already.
The queen is...
Keum Sae Rok.
She's the queen.
(Sae Rok is selected as the Queen.)
- Yes! - All right.
This is what the queen should do.
- He has an ulterior motive. - There are two people left.
(I was looking forward to it.)
- Premier and Vice-premier. - I think it's hard...
(It's time to choose the Premier and Vice-premier.)
to be the Premier and the Vice-premier.
I think they will be Jong Kook and Haha.
For Premier and Vice-premier,
you should choose the people whom you're comfortable with.
(He appeals to familiarity.)
- Okay. Good. - Yes.
What about me?
Shut it!
How dare a slave talk to the king?
- He's a slave. - A slave?
(He becomes a slave for saying a sentence.)
- Are you a slave? - A slave?
Otherwise, you should be a eunuch.
I don't want you to be my eunuch.
You should pick someone educated...
for the Premier.
He got the perfect score in math.
(Recommending Dong Yoon as the Premier)
Hang on. That sounds like a good idea.
But I don't want him because he will stand out.
(He's out because of his outstanding looks.)
Then why don't you pick this guy...
who's smart but ugly?
Right. He's uglier than me,
- but he's smart. - He is smart.
I want Jae Suk to be the Premier.
(Jae Suk becomes the Premier.)
- Really? - You're successful.
(He succeeded with his looks.)
- He's not good-looking. - He's not good-looking.
(He succeeded with his bad looks.)
- But he's smart enough. - That's right.
Your Majesty. If you want someone ugly,
I can be a perfect fit.
(His successful looks were shielded by his glasses.)
He looks horrible.
- What's wrong with your face? - Your Majesty.
(Swollen)
(What happened to your face?)
He looks like a middle-aged man.
What happened to your face?
What's wrong with your face?
(His face is particularly swollen because of his medicine.)
What's wrong with him?
The medicine is too strong.
What happened to your face?
(The classes are chosen like so based on looks and familiarity.)
All right then.
I want someone quiet...
(King Se Chan, Queen Sae Rok,)
(Premier Jae Suk, and Vice-premier Ji Hyo)
and obedient for the Vice-premier.
He's obviously a eunuch.
(4 Eunuchs: Jong Kook, Haha, Sung Hoon, and Kwang Soo)
Long hair.
(4 Slaves: Dong Yoon, So Min, Dong Jun, and Suk Jin)
Those who hold high office should take good care of me.
Considering regionalism and kinship.
I like the members of Team Slave except for Suk Jin.
- I like my team. - You do?
(Good-looking Slave 1, 2, and a regular Slave 3)
This is nice.
(Getting in between)
Why did you push me?
(While they're somewhat satisfied with their classes...)
- Your Majesty. - Team Slave has good members.
- Your Majesty. - What?
- What's that, Hyeong Gu? - Hey, Hyeong Gu.
He's a eunuch.
(Hyeong Gu, specializing in small roles)
It's an urgent public appeal from the capital.
Hyeong Gu.
He joined SBS through open recruitment.
Really?
(Startled)
You went to a good college. Life must be so hard.
(Hyeong Gu, graduated from a good college, a eunuch for today)
Is this what you want to do with your career?
- Yes, it is. - Thank you.
(The cameo has given up now.)
You may leave now.
Your Majesty.
- He must've studied hard. - Please take a look at this.
(What's the appeal that Eunuch Hyung Gu brought say?)
Read it for me, Premier.
Okay. I'll read this for you.
"Your Majesty, there are..."
"evil spirits that possess people's bodies..."
"and disturb the public order outside the castle."
(Evil spirits)
How terrible!
"And two of them made their way into the castle..."
"and are hiding among people."
"Please hold a trial..."
(They must catch the two evil spirits.)
"and make sure to arrest the evil spirits."
I got you!
- You're busted! - I'm not an evil spirit.
- Are there evil spirits here? - I got one already.
(They suspect him to be an evil spirit for his usual conduct.)
- Okay. - It's not me.
- I'm not an evil spirit. - I smell something fishy.
I think this guy...
- And that... - and the guy in strange pants...
(They suspect him to be an evil spirit just for fun.)
That slave. It's him.
I think the slave is an evil spirit.
There are...
two evil spirits here hiding among people.
- This is hard. - There are two.
(Jong Kook's radar starts operating.)
I think I know who they are.
You can eliminate the evil spirits through a trial.
(Three trials to eliminate the evil spirits)
If you eliminate all the evil spirits...
through three trials today, humans will win.
(If both evil spirits are caught, the humans win.)
And the two humans...
(Then the humans get prizes according to the amount of rice.)
with the most rice will get the prize.
And the evil spirits will get the penalty.
(The 2 evil spirits have been given their rules before the shoot.)
Do the evil spirits know about their identity?
They know that they are evil spirits.
But if at least one evil spirit survives, the evil spirits win.
(If both evil spirits aren't caught, they win.)
They will win the prize,
(Two humans with the least amount of rice will get the penalty.)
and two humans with the least rice will get the penalty.
Now I'd like you to change into your costumes...
(They will change their outfits...)
(and move to the first court to catch the evil spirits.)
and move to the first court.
Okay.
(The Running Dynasty of King Se Chan begins with hidden evil spirits.)
Hurry up.
You don't look good with a real mustache,
but the mustache drawing looks great on you.
"You don't look good with a real mustache?"
- Is there a camera? - How could you...
- say such a thing to the king? - I'm sorry.
(Eunuch Kwang Soo forgot about his identity.)
If you're a eunuch, act like one.
Come here.
(Using the permanent marker to strengthen the royal authority)
Do you want to draw a mustache?
A eunuch can have a mustache.
- Can a eunuch grow a mustache? - Sure.
(It's possible only in Running Dynasty.)
A eunuch can't grow a mustache.
What's that mole for?
All right. It means you're mine.
I picked you. You're dismissed.
- Next. - Hello.
(The King's man appears.)
Come here. I'll fix your dirty mustache.
Don't make it look really dirty.
It's really is dirty.
(He makes it look even uglier.)
(He draws a mole again.)
You're dismissed.
I'm upset with you these days.
What are you upset about?
We should play the King Game together later on.
Let's do that.
(Deal!)
Number 1 and 4 should kiss. Okay?
Darn it. I'm number four.
- What's your number? - I'm number one.
Good.
(They have fun playing the King Game.)
Go on in.
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
(Slave Ji, worried about the country, got on the bus first)
The ignorant king is in power. We're in trouble.
Did you come early to sit here?
No, it's not like that.
(He quickly got on the bus to secure his seat.)
I just got changed and came here.
(Glancing)
(Bursts out laughing)
My gosh.
You look like a real eunuch in that costume.
Hey...
Do not speak to us casually like that.
(Their social classes are effective even on the bus.)
Right. We're in different classes.
But...
(Flustered)
- Don't act like you don't know. - Are you serious?
You should apologize to him.
(They're talking out the anger on the slave.)
Has it begun already?
Hey, but you...
"Hey"? Hey, Ji Suk Jin.
Gosh, seriously.
- Keep it together. - You don't even have it.
What did you just say?
- But that's true. - How dare you?
Not now. I'll let you do it later.
(The tyrant is abusive toward his slaves too.)
I'll let you do it if you promote me to a eunuch.
I have the authority to do what I want as your king.
(The marker tyrant)
How dare that punk have pictures taken in a cool pose like that?
(He's posing as a slave.)
He's posing for pictures when he's a mere servant.
(His beauty will anger the king.)
He even has female fans too.
(The king imposes a drastic measure to make the slaves look ugly.)
No one follows the King.
You two will have a unibrow.
(After drawing monobrows on the slaves,)
- No. - Come here.
(he discovers Eunuch Sung Hoon at the corner.)
You're a eunuch.
Yes, Your Majesty.
- Wait. - I want to watch.
But I thought eunuchs have no body hair.
It is I, your king, that decides. Do not say anything.
(Hair shall be made by the king.)
(Timid)
- My apologies. - I hate your mullet.
I used to hate another punk with a mullet.
I'm glad you're here.
Just stay still.
(His sin is having a mullet.)
- Wait. - Stay still.
I think I know what you're drawing.
Don't move. This will look great.
- Queen, you may get on the bus. - Yes, Your Majesty.
You look so pretty.
(The fool king is generous to his beautiful queen.)
- Thank you, Your Majesty. - Go on in.
Won't she get a mustache?
(Relieved)
(Eunuch Kook, understands the power structure, surrenders to the power)
Jong Kook is waiting quietly.
(He's done drawing a circle.)
I shall think of you as my little brother.
(A brotherhood is formed over a circle.)
Go on in.
Thank you for your boundless generosity.
(Eunuch Kook is the last to go.)
Next.
- Aren't you Kim Jong Kook? - Yes, Your Majesty.
(Shy)
(Contrast to his shy smile, his muscles are very predominant.)
You are quite muscular for a eunuch.
(Laughing)
I do not know where the testosterone comes from.
I shall help you produce even more testosterone.
(He shall have mustaches instead of protein.)
- Come closer. - I don't think that's possible.
Don't you all think that our king is too ignorant?
"Ignorant"?
(Slave Ji expresses his concerns about the country passionately.)
- I'm sorry. - That's treason.
- But the King is too ignorant. - As a matter of fact,
the Premier deserves the throne.
- I agree. - Of course.
I also think that's right.
He's practically ruling the country on the King's behalf.
(They're starting to plot a revolt...)
(against the tyrant.)
- Stop it. - You have control over him.
You are the King to us, my lord.
Do I have the face to become a king?
Yes, my lord.
(Satisfied)
I'm pretty sure that Jae Suk will have to change into...
a slave's costume later.
He'll go down step by step and end up being a slave.
(He'll eventually be ousted due to his words.)
That's possible.
(Airhead King is getting on the bus after drawing on the others' faces.)
Why are the slaves sitting there? Come forward.
- Pardon? - Come forward.
(He picks on a fight for no reason.)
- But... - Hurry up and come.
- This has been my seat for so long. - How dare you?
- That's funny. - How dare you talk back to me?
(He has no choice but to give up his seat.)
- Sit in the front seat. - Yes, Your Majesty.
Go to the front seat.
Where should I sit?
(The treacherous)
Do not think it's a joke and do as you're told.
- Exactly. How dare he? - Where should I sit?
- A mere slave... - Oh, I can sit here.
How dare you sit with a backrest?
(The slave is not allowed to sit on the seat with a backrest.)
Can't I even sit with a backrest?
Sit on the floor, not a seat!
- I shall allow it just this once. - Run now!
(Everyone else is as mean as the King.)
All of you must impress me today.
(No dignity)
- Yes, Your Majesty. - Yes, Your Majesty.
The King speaks like a thug.
(What?)
"A thug"?
- I didn't mean it like that. - How dare you?
How impudent! That little punk.
(Premier Yu, the treacherous, impudent punks)
"Punk"?
You shouldn't say such a vulgar expression as the Premier.
- Those impudent punks. - How dare you?
Slave Ji, how dare you raise your voice?
I shall not let this slide. Slave Ji.
Sell all the stocks you own this instant.
Sell all of them!
(He gets uncomfortable upon the order to sell all his stocks.)
- How can I sell them? - That is impossible, Your Majesty.
- The stocks he owns... - No one will buy them.
(It's a sad story.)
His stocks are not worth much even after selling them.
(Slave Ji's stocks are worth chump change.)
Then forget what I said.
His stocks are about to be delisted.
Is that so? Then you may hold on to them.
(All stocks he invested are about to be delisted.)
We can change our social classes except for the King, right?
(It's possible to change their social classes, but...)
That's correct. Except for the King.
By the way... I'm asking this...
- out of curiosity. - Yes?
Are you the manager of these two?
That's irrelevant to the context.
(The manager who tries to take care of handsome slaves.)
- This is set in the old days. - I mean...
(I'm Director Kwang of Suck-Up Entertainment.)
Why are you shooting another show here?
Are you shooting "Omniscient Interfering View"?
- No. - "Omniscient Interfering View"?
(Omniscient Interfering Eunuch)
Don't be ridiculous.
Are you here as Dong Jun's manager?
(Dong Yoon and Dong Jun's Manager)
- Or as Dong Yoon's manager? - No.
That suits him well.
(Patting)
Why aren't you two saying anything? Why would you pat me?
(Why aren't you two saying anything? Why would you pat me?)
All right.
I shall tighten the discipline, Your Majesty.
(This is how...)
Correct.
- "Correct"? - "Correct"?
(Airhead King's words and actions are very awkward.)
- You can just say, "Go ahead." - What was that?
- What was that? - You see...
- Are you intimidated? - You can just say, "Go ahead."
(This comedian is used to being a eunuch or a slave.)
You see,
- I've never... - You are so ignorant.
- played a role as a king before. - Are you intimidated?
- He's never played... - "I have no experience, my lord."
(He directly copies...)
I have no experience, my lord.
(Premier's words.)
- "My lord"? - Wait.
He looks like a pushover.
- Who are you to control me? - That is not true, Your Majesty.
- My apologies. - He keeps trying to control me.
- This is what's called "regency". - Exactly.
You must take him down.
- Do you know what "regency" means? - Do you know what it is?
I believe that it means "refreshed areas".
(Airhead King, I'm sure it refers to refreshed areas!)
- Airhead! - I know what it means.
Please lift the restrictions on the greenbelt.
(Airhead dictionary: regency, refreshed area, greenbelt)
What is he talking about?
Eunuch Ha, how come you have three children as a eunuch?
Before I lost it...
He was a step ahead.
(His family plan came before his future.)
My, I didn't know he was so virile.
- Sae Rok, why are you so quiet? - Yes?
Why?
- She's so playful on set. - Really?
(The Queen is very playful on set.)
Sae Rok, what do you do on set?
I'm not playful.
(Queen Sae Rok, Ex-playful, I'm not playful)
You're the most playful one there.
(She maintains her dignity.)
- Please show us. - No, I'm not.
Actually, Ji Hyo is also quite playful off camera.
- When can we see that? - Ji Hyo...
(Ji Hyo is also very playful behind cameras.)
- Ji Hyo is... - When can we see that?
the type that acts playful when the camera goes off.
(Only the members know the true character of Ji Hyo.)
She's playful in real life.
- That's true. - But when the camera is rolling,
(She's been shy in front of cameras for 11 years.)
she becomes shy, and it's been that way for the past 10 years.
Meanwhile, Suk Jin acts playful on TV shows,
but he's actually very quiet in real life.
(He makes all kinds of accusations.)
He doesn't even greet me back when I say hi to him.
(A true professional)
That's true.
(He tries to act friendly a little too late.)
- Right. - He doesn't speak until he's paid.
I guess it's true.
Suk Jin, why is your hand so sweaty?
What? It's because I'm hot.
(Why is Suk Jin's hand so sweaty?)
- What? - Aren't your hands sweaty?
- No, see it yourself. - Something must be going on.
Are you one of the evil spirits?
- No, I'm not. - You must be.
(Is Suk Jin nervous because he's an evil spirit?)
- I'm just feeling hot. That's all. - He's suspicious.
I'm really feeling hot.
I'm sure he was given the role.
(Denies fervently)
No. That's not true.
You're blushing too.
- No. It's not the case. - It wasn't because of his pants.
(His face is red.)
Jong Kook, touch his hand just once.
- This is... - If you're not...
an evil spirit, you must be going through male menopause.
- It's because... - That was...
(Hormones can be scarier than evil spirits.)
an awesome punch line.
I hope he's an evil spirit.
(He really means it.)
I can finally smile as I'm relieved now.
You became so talkative suddenly.
Queen, which of us are the evil spirits?
Before I answer that, I have a question.
Go ahead.
Is it possible that you are one of the evil spirits?
- Of course. - Yes.
Can the King be an evil spirit?
(The King may be an evil spirit too!)
- He may be an evil spirit too. - Of course.
Of course.
(Anyone can be an evil spirit.)
- The King may be one of them too. - Right.
I have a good feeling about this.
(Who are the 2 evil spirits acting as humans among them?)
I may be one of them.
How about we choose one before we arrive?
(Running Palace where the King and the ministers discuss affairs.)
This place is decorated like a period movie filming set.
(There are solemn-looking thrones too.)
It looks amazing.
- It looks nice. - Look how the chairs are placed.
- How nice. I'm so upset. - Let's sit down.
(The seats are based on their social classes.)
Did you really have to place them like this?
- Of course, I know. - Sit down quietly.
- Give us some cushions at least. - Just sit down.
(A representative of the slaves)
What about the slaves?
(Seats for eunuchs, Seats for slaves)
Oh, yes. I can sit on the throne.
(Airhead King and Queen Keum are sitting on the thrones.)
Queen, please sit.
- Did you really have to do this? - Do you want to sit here?
(Satisfied)
No, that's okay.
(Everyone found their seats according to their classes.)
Starting with the slaves...
Why hasn't the Vice-premier come yet?
(Wait a minute.)
- She went to the restroom. - She went to poop.
(Making accusations)
Oh, she went to poop?
How dare you describe the act of the Vice-premier...
as "pooping"?
- You punk. - Then...
Not every eunuch is the same.
(Then what?)
(He distances himself from Kwang Soo quickly.)
Refrain yourself from saying anything disrespectful.
(Dignified)
That ignorant punk.
- He sounds like a eunuch. - Oops.
(His words are not suitable to be of a king's.)
- What was that? - It's just...
- He sounds like a eunuch. - It's not like that.
(Even the treacherous retainer doesn't know how to react.)
- He sounds like a lowlife. - It's my old habit.
(Your speech style)
- "That ignorant punk." - What kind of king...
(The Airhead King must have been a eunuch in the past.)
Actually, His Majesty used to be the lowliest...
You brat!
How dare you say that as a mere premier?
(The skit starts.)
You might become a slave if you keep acting like this, you brat.
(A very typical skit tone)
- Please forgive me. - "You brat."
(His speech, gestures, and facial expressions are far from a king's.)
- No king would put on such a face. - Please forgive me.
You all will be killed when I speak the way I used to speak again.
(It's almost a threat.)
(Threatening words of a king with a dark past.)
I'm trying to act solemn,
but if you keep acting up like this,
(He's angry.)
- I might go back to the way I was. - Your Majesty,
please forgive me.
- Do not provoke His Majesty. - I'll go back to my old self.
(He hid his past to become a king.)
- Your Majesty. - Do not provoke him again.
While I am acting with grace and dignity...
I beg your forgiveness, Your Majesty.
(Soothing the baby)
- So Min, what are you doing? - What are you doing?
(Slave So Min has something in her arms.)
What are you doing?
This is my baby, Your Majesty.
(Crying)
(What?)
- Who is the father? - Is he in here?
(Her baby looks like someone.)
Is the father of the baby in this room?
(It's definitely Woong, Woong's Father)
- He's right here. - Here.
- He's here. - Take...
Take...
(Airhead King, Woong's father in his past life)
Take that crazy woman out of here immediately!
- What do you think you are doing? - She's crazy about role-playing.
- Isn't this... - No. Please.
- Did you draw the King's face? - Please don't do that.
- How dare you... - He's my baby.
(Genes are powerful.)
Send her to prison!
(He rejects this setting.)
- Send this crazy woman... - How dare you...
- Please. I beg you. - She gave birth to the King's baby.
He's my child.
- You wench! - "You wench."
You wench!
(Queen Keum got furious as she saw the baby that looks like the King.)
"You wench."
The baby looks just like the King.
(Please, save my baby.)
- What kind of role play is this? - She drew the King's face...
Doesn't he look just like the King?
(Even the king of skit wants to end it quickly.)
- Send her to prison. - How dare you draw his face?
- He's my baby. - He looks just like the King.
- Then Sung Hoon starts crying. - Look at him.
(He's very addicted to this type of genre.)
(The baby looks like Sung Hoon too.)
- He turns out to be Sung Hoon's. - He looks...
(Please have a good life.)
He has a similar mustache to Sung Hoon's.
(This is how "The Child of Tiger Moth" went down history.)
But he looks just like the King.
This is hilarious.
(Crying her heart out)
Director, let's begin.
This is the first trial where you can eliminate an evil spirit...
(Before the mission)
(It's the first trial where they can eliminate an evil spirit.)
before you carry out the mission.
We must eliminate the evil spirit.
Every one of you is free to talk about the person...
(They are free to talk about those who might be evil spirits.)
that you think is the evil spirit.
But the King will select the person...
(However, only the king can decide...)
to be tried.
(the person to be tried.)
After the discussion?
- The King has all powers. - It'd be the best if he's one.
Exactly.
However, the King may also be one of the evil spirits,
(However, the king may also be one of the evil spirits.)
and you may oppose the King's opinions.
(There also may be people who oppose the king.)
Those who are against his opinions can revolt against him.
(People can revolt.)
- That's great. - Revolt?
The revolt succeeds...
if more than half of you break the dried gourd with the head.
(The revolt succeeds if more than half...)
(of the members break the dried gourd with the head.)
In that case, you'll select the one to be tried through a vote.
(Once successful,)
(they can select the one to be tried through a vote.)
Let's eliminate him before we begin.
If the evil spirit is caught,
(If the evil spirit is caught,)
the evil spirit will stay as a slave to the end of the show.
(the evil spirit will stay as a slave to the end of the show.)
Really?
If the evil spirits lose the race, the one with less rice...
(If the evil spirits lose the race,)
(the evil spirit with less rice will receive a penalty twice.)
will receive a penalty twice.
If you put an innocent person on trial,
(If you put an innocent person on trial,)
the evil spirits will choose one person...
(the evil spirits will choose 1 person...)
to take all the rice that person has behind your backs.
(to take all the rice that person has behind your backs.)
And they will share the rice.
The evil spirits must complete a hidden mission...
(The evil spirits must complete a mission before the trials!)
before each of the three trials.
The evil spirits had a mission to complete on your way here.
(The evil spirits already completed their 1st hidden mission.)
- Did they complete it? - Oh, gosh.
The evil spirits had a mission to complete.
Did they complete it?
- They drew a mole on the face. - Did they complete the mission?
They drew a mole on the face.
He has a mole under his eye.
(Is the mole under the eye the mark of the evil spirits?)
He drew a mole under the eye.
(Approaching)
Why?
He drew that mole.
- Was it the hidden mission? - What? I didn't draw it.
(Slapping)
Was it the hidden mission?
What? I didn't draw it. I didn't draw this mole.
(It's absurd.)
I bet it was the hidden mission. The King drew it.
- That's right. - The King drew it.
(The person who drew the mole is...)
That's right.
(the King.)
I am not an evil spirit.
Why would I have a mole under my eye?
- See? - That makes sense.
(Se Chan put a mole under Kwang Soo and Haha's eye.)
That's not true. I drew moles on randomly chosen members.
(Taken aback)
Your face is so red!
- Your face is so red! - Look at his face.
No. That's not true.
(His face turns red as he becomes a suspect.)
- He got caught. - Trust me.
Hey, change your clothes. Take that off now!
Listen. I'm telling you the truth.
- Why is your face so red? - No. I was just taken aback.
I'm really not an evil spirit.
- That's why I'm taken aback. - Hang on a second.
(He really is suspicious.)
- I know who the evil spirits are. - By the way,
the King also has a mole under his eye.
Do you think I would make it that obvious?
(Is putting a mole under the eye a hidden mission?)
- What was the hidden mission? - Listen to me.
I would never do that. I just stopped drawing moles.
What? Se Chan is crying.
- Hold on. I have... - Trust me.
- Why would I do that? - Se Chan, don't cry.
I think...
- I'm really not an evil spirit. - Investigator Kim.
(Eunuch Kim starts investigating.)
- I'm not. Trust me. - Investigator Kim.
- I swear. - Jong Kook, hold back for a while.
- Here he goes again. - It's not the right time.
(It's not time to oppress them yet.)
- I have things I want to say. - Wait a little longer.
- But I can't. - I'm sure he's an evil spirit.
He became the King when he's an evil spirit.
- That's right. - This is the true regency.
We had a similar mission before.
- Wait. Hey... - They lured us into choosing...
- Eunuch Ha. - Yes?
He became the King...
when he's also an evil spirit.
(The situation just now barely fits...)
And you call this the true regency? I don't think that's what it means.
(the definition of the regency by the queen mother.)
That darn stupid regency.
Do you even know what "regency" means?
That doesn't make sense.
(Do you know, Your Majesty?)
(Haha's mistake made everyone laugh.)
- Let's drop it. It's a happy day. - How many of us would know?
(Stroking)
(It's such a great day.)
Oh, boy.
- The Queen... The Queen... - How many of us...
(She's laughing louder than anyone.)
- The Queen is laughing hard too. - Please...
- Leave her alone. - I think she's fake laughing.
(The thought of regency by the queen mother makes Queen Keum grin.)
Isn't this funny, Your Highness?
What is your opinion, Your Highness?
(Who does she think the evil spirit is?)
I think... Since my...
My husband...
The King's face turned red.
- So I'm suspicious of him. - His face did turn red.
- His face is still red. - You're right.
(Everyone suspects Airhead King as his face turns red.)
I also suspect the King.
- What? - He drew moles on two people.
- And his face turned red. - You're corning me like this?
- "Corning"? - "Corning"?
(Eunuch Kim never misses a thing.)
"Corning"?
You mean "cornering".
- It's not "corning". - Just tell me one thing.
Why did you draw moles on our faces?
(Why did he put a mole only on Haha and Kwang Soo?)
So Min drew a mole on my face.
(So Min drew a mole on my face,)
So I thought it'd be funny to draw a mole on everyone...
thinking of you all as my children. While doing it...
(so I put a mole on Haha and Kwang Soo who are my children.)
I'm sorry.
(Chuckling)
- He stopped drawing it. - Actually...
It's all because of Eunuch Kim.
I shall clear my name.
- I shall... - Please don't.
(As Eunuch Kim narrows it down on him,)
prove that I'm not an evil spirit...
- Please calm down. - I shall take my clothes off...
(Airhead King takes off his robe.)
- Please calm down. - to prove...
Please calm down.
Do not stop me!
(Airhead King takes off his robe as he gets angry.)
- Please don't. - Because of Eunuch Kim...
- Your Majesty, please calm down. - I don't want to play this role.
(He means it.)
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Please explain so we can understand.
(The strict investigator makes the King want to quit.)
- For that petty thing... - Unfortunately, there's no one...
who can torture that eunuch in this country.
(No one can punish scary Eunuch Kim.)
- This is unfair. - No one can punish him.
My wish is to get a chance to slap him in his butt.
I'm so upset.
Let's move on for now.
(He stops the investigation.)
Since we're all confused, how about we choose the opposite?
(Premier Yu)
- What do you mean? - I think it can be a solution.
(How?)
How about we put Eunuch Lee on trial?
(Let's put Eunuch Lee on trial!)
(When it's hard to decide, it's always Kwang Soo.)
My gosh. This isn't right.
- I know you picked him... - This isn't right.
(He picks Eunuch Lee for fun.)
- just for fun. - When it's hard to decide...
I can't put him on trial just because you think...
- it'll be funny. - When it's hard to decide...
(He believes in that theory.)
It's best to put him on trial, Your Majesty.
Please do not play along with him. He's just being playful now.
- Stop it. - Then how about Eunuch Park?
(Suspecting Eunuch Park)
He won't stop shivering.
- He's been shivering all day long. - He's not an evil spirit.
(The flour doll is pale all day.)
- Right, Sung Hoon... - We should wait for now.
By the way, Sung Hoon really looks...
He does look so weak.
- Indeed. - He looks so weak and fragile.
(He's clearly sick.)
He was the first person who lost it.
Did both evil spirits complete their missions?
(Back on investigation)
Both of them have a mission,
and both completed it successfully.
(Both of the 2 evil spirits completed their missions!)
- Really? - I see.
Both completed it successfully.
- Let's talk! - Here they are.
- Hello. - Dong Jun is here!
(From the opening when everyone was watching...)
Here I am!
- This is ridiculous! - What about me?
(And even on the bus where they were all sitting together)
- That suits him. - I mean...
Who are you to control me?
(They completed their missions without letting the humans know.)
I'm sure they did something on the bus.
(2 evil spirits succeeded the hidden mission.)
- While we were talking on the bus? - Think carefully.
(Who could be the evil spirits?)
- They must've done it on the bus. - Think carefully.
(On the bus)
I was sitting at the back, you know.
And I think Dong Yoon is an evil spirit.
- What did he do? - Dong Yoon...
- What did I do? - hit Sae Rok in the head...
and joked around with her.
He hit Sae Rok in the head and joked around with her.
(Dong Yoon must've joked around with her to complete the mission.)
- Dong Yoon... - He must be an evil spirit.
(People start to believe that Dong Yoon's an evil spirit.)
kept joking around with her like hitting her head.
- But... - Hitting her head...
(Explaining)
- we all do that on set. - sounds too simple for a mission.
Dong Yoon?
(Is Dong Yoon...)
Dong Yoon, you were given a role, weren't you?
- No. - That's funny.
No. I'm telling you the truth.
But he always does that to me.
- He always plays jokes... - That means...
he has a crush on her.
He has a crush on her.
(What?)
- How dare you lay sight... - Is that so?
on the Queen as a slave?
That means he has a crush on her.
- Is anyone out there? - This is like a soap opera.
- Set in the Joseon Era. - How dare he?
(The handsome slave who falls in love with Airhead King's woman)
(The Joseon Dynasty Drama, "The Queen and the Slave")
Are you in love with the Queen?
I heard that social status doesn't matter in love.
That little...
- You little... - I think...
- I think I'll lose her to him. - To be honest...
(What do I do?)
- I think I'll lose her to him. - Your Majesty.
(Airhead King isn't better than Slave Dong Yoon in any way.)
- I think I'll lose her to him. - To be honest,
I think that Dong Yoon is a better match for her.
How dare you? I think I'll lose her to him.
(In crisis)
Hold on. Then... Hey, Eunuch Lee.
(He suddenly spoke casually to him.)
Then... Hey, Eunuch Lee.
(Eunuch Ha suddenly disrespects him.)
"Hey, Eunuch Lee"?
- "Hey, Eunuch Lee"? - That was funny.
(Angry)
Hey, Eunuch Ha. Why?
How are the eunuchs ranked?
- In the order of employment. - Eunuch Kim is first in rank.
(They decide the rank in the order of employment.)
Eunuch Kim is first in rank.
(1st place, 2nd, 3rd, the youngest)
- I'm the head eunuch. - I see.
Did you see Dong Yoon do it?
- Do what? - What do you mean?
Why would you speak casually to me?
(The youngest)
- Aren't we in the same rank? - He has seniority over you.
(Eunuch society has a strict rank.)
- We're not in the same rank. - You rude punk!
- Hey, he's your senior. - They were hired at the same time.
(Look at the way he talks to his senior.)
- How dare you? - Even though we're eunuchs...
- I didn't realize it. - who don't have it...
I thought we were in the same rank.
Let's have Sung Hoon slap him in the butt.
- I didn't know. - Lie down.
(Spitting)
It wasn't like that.
- I have seniority over Sung Hoon. - I won't let this slide.
(The order is clear between eunuchs.)
But...
- The youngest always does this. - Prove you're not weak.
- Show us. - But I didn't...
(Slapping)
- That was so weak. - But I didn't...
(Did he really hit me?)
That was so weak.
(The flour doll's slap only caused dust.)
- Sung Hoon, your hand must hurt. - It doesn't hurt at all.
That was so weak.
- I hit him as hard as I could. - Come back to your seat.
- He's so weak. - What was that?
(What was that?)
(He's got the best body to be a eunuch.)
He's so peculiar.
- It didn't hurt at all. - Even though we're eunuchs...
Didn't Dong Jun do anything suspicious?
- Dong Jun? - I'm not an evil spirit.
(This time, they suspect Dong Jun.)
Dong Jun came on Running Man many times before.
He seems quieter than the last time he came on the show.
(That reminds me.)
- You see... - He's been too quiet.
It'd be easier for him to play an evil spirit.
(Eunuch Kim's deduction)
When we were on the bus, Dong Jun...
- held my hand like this. - No way.
(He suddenly grabbed Kwang Soo's hand.)
- Really? - Did he really do that?
- So... - That's because he pitied you.
- I did it out of pity. - He just felt sorry for you.
- Out of pity? - Yes.
But men rarely hold...
(Eunuch Kim doesn't stop making deductions...)
- another man's hand. - True.
(even when everyone's laughing.)
- I like Kwang Soo. - Isn't it odd?
- He held Kwang Soo's hand? - It's not that kind of mission.
(It's hard to read Dong Jun's face.)
(While they were on the bus,)
Are you here as Dong Jun's manager?
- Or as Dong Yoon's manager? - No.
(Dong Jun suddenly held Kwang Soo's hand.)
Why aren't you two saying anything? Why would you hold my hand?
(Could that be the hidden mission?)
No, that's not why did it.
It's hard to tell if Dong Jun and Dong Yoon are evil spirits.
(They narrow it down to guests.)
I'm suspicious of Dong Yoon and Sung Hoon.
- Dong Jun is suspicious too. - I think...
You see, the Queen may also be one of the evil spirits.
- Don't you think? - Right. She may be one of them.
- That's possible. - If you think about it...
(Could it be Sae Rok who's been quiet the whole time?)
Could it be Sae Rok?
(Was she staying quiet to avoid suspicion?)
That's so random.
Now that we know about the hidden missions, it'll get harder for them.
Anyway, we'll put the person...
- that Mr. Yang chooses on trial. - Correct.
- Your Majesty, tell us... - I will...
(Wait.)
- who you think it is. - I'm sorry,
- but did you call him "Mr. Yang"? - The most suspicious person.
Was that a hidden mission?
(Why did he suddenly call Se Chan "Mr. Yang"?)
- "Mr. Yang"? - You called him "Mr. Yang".
I was just being polite.
Do you want me to speak in a girl's voice because I'm a eunuch?
(The sorrow of a eunuch's life without such ordinary freedom)
- That's not how you address a king. - I was just being polite.
- That's not appropriate. - I just addressed him respectfully.
(Without realizing)
- It's time to make a decision. - Okay.
(After Eunuch Lee calls Se Chan Mr. Yang, it's time to decide.)
Your Majesty.
Gosh. This is so complicated.
I think that one of the evil spirits is among our members,
and the other is among the guests.
You have to choose just one.
Will you choose one of the members?
By the way, why is So Min so quiet today?
(All of a sudden)
Exactly. She's been too quiet too.
(Suspicious)
- So Min? - She's holding the dried gourd...
I find it suspicious that she drew a mole on my face.
- Gosh, I'm not an evil spirit. - Could drawing on it...
- Hold on a second! - Gosh, I'm not an evil spirit.
Could drawing on it...
(Could that be her mission?)
- be her... - Is that her mission?
- Is that her mission? - No. I drew it for no reason.
Hold on a second!
So Min drew a mole on the King's face.
(That reminds me.)
- Gosh. - On the King's face.
She drew a mole on his face.
(So Min drew a mole on the King's face.)
- This is driving me nuts. - Vice-premier Song...
She drew a mole on the King's face.
(Could that be an evil spirit's hidden mission?)
I'm really not an evil spirit.
- What? - Was that your mission?
You drew a mole on my face and drew my face on the dried gourd?
- That's suspicious. - Try to remember.
Try to remember when I drew a mole on your face, Your Majesty.
(The strong suspect denies.)
Jae Suk and Jong Kook were...
See? She keeps making excuses without denying it.
- You can put me on trial, but... - Exactly. If she's not,
(So Min suddenly became chatty.)
she wouldn't mind going on trial.
- That's right. - I mean, why do I always...
She became so talkative suddenly.
(Is she trying to avoid getting caught?)
Jong Kook always eliminates me first.
Premier Yu, I've made my decision.
- Please tell us your decision. - I'm not one of the evil spirits.
You know that I don't talk much when we have male guests, right?
I shall...
put Jeon So Min on trial.
- Gosh. - I don't think so.
- I shall put Jeon So Min on trial. - Gosh.
- I'm not an evil spirit. - We can break our dried gourd.
I said I'm not!
It hurts.
(So Min breaks a gourd to prove innocence.)
She even smashed the face of the child she cares about.
- It isn't me. - I don't think it's her either.
(But no one breaks another gourd to help.)
- Then... - I don't think so.
The King made his decision.
It really isn't me.
(Was the evil spirit's hidden mission...)
I'm sorry but...
(to mark a dot on the King's face?)
- You know me, right? - It can't be.
Guys, please. The mission was completed...
on the bus where I hardly did anything.
Have a seat for now.
If he's right though, that means he's an evil spirit too.
(Is So Min an evil spirit as the King guesses?)
If he's right, he'll be taken off the hook.
- It's not me. - It's not her.
(Or is she innocent who was falsely accused?)
- I doubt it's her. - Then...
I'll reveal the result of the first trial.
(Announcing the result of the 1st trial)
If So Min is an evil spirit,
she'll drink all of the sophora root tea...
(If she's an evil spirit, she'll be the Slave...)
and stay as a slave forever.
(after drinking sophora root tea before her.)
That's bitter, you know. The bitter flavor will linger.
Then...
- I don't think it's her. - So Min...
(Worried)
- Is she an evil spirit? - She isn't.
Is she an evil spirit?
- She isn't. - See? What did I tell you?
(She was not an evil spirit!)
(They failed to find the evil spirit in the first trial.)
- What? - See?
(Innocent)
It isn't me.
Since you accused an innocent person,
(For putting an innocent person on the Judgment Stand,)
the evil spirits will steal the rice...
(all rice of 1 member chosen by the evil spirits...)
from the person they choose.
(will be given to them.)
Please put on the blindfolds in front of you.
(Now the evil spirits must decide.)
After taking their blindfolds off,
the evil spirits will choose the person they will steal from.
I said it wasn't me.
- Why did you end up choosing me? - The majority ruled.
The King made up his mind quite fast if you ask me.
(Se Chan accused innocent So Min because he's an evil spirit?)
- I'm suspicious of him. - It's not me.
His actions were questionable.
All right.
(2 evil spirits will take off their blindfolds and choose 1 member.)
The evil spirits will take off the blindfolds...
and choose a person.
(The evil spirits will now steal from one of the people.)
And choose a person.
(That's when...)
(Dong Yoon takes off his blindfold.)
(That means...)
(Earlier, Dong Yoon entered an empty room alone.)
What's this?
(A mysterious jar looking suspicious)
Did someone leave this behind?
(His curiosity gets the best of him, so he opens the jar.)
(At the very moment...)
(The energy of the evil spirit gets sucked into Dong Yoon.)
(That's how Dong Yoon became an evil spirit.)
Am I at Joseon's palace?
Let's have some fun then.
(Glancing)
What else am I supposed to say?
(Cheesy)
Are you serious?
(He overcomes the silly lines and enters the Running Man Universe.)
Do you do things like this on Running Man?
You're joining us today on the Records of the Running Dynasty.
(He was...)
You two are the evil spirits living among humans.
(an evil spirit hidden among the humans.)
Evil spirits?
While keeping your identities a secret,
(The evil spirits must complete 3 hidden missions in secret.)
you must complete hidden missions.
Every time you fail your missions,
(Every time they fail,)
a letter from your name will be revealed.
(their initials will be revealed one by one.)
For your first mission,
you'll be making three hearts...
- at the camera. - Hearts?
One must do so during the opening scene...
(One must do so during the opening scene...)
while the other does so on the bus.
(while the other does so on the bus.)
Must the both of us succeed?
And you will be in a hierarchical society...
(The humans open the show unaware of the situation.)
where the king's words are the law.
(While everyone is focused on the King's power...)
- What does that mean? - Oh, really?
(He succeeds in making his first heart.)
(While the others were busy with their statuses...)
(He easily makes his second heart.)
Am I the king?
(While the others were focused on Se Chan being King)
(He was bold enough to make two hearts in the end.)
- You're the king. - I really am.
(Dong Yoon was able to carry out his mission.)
Choose a person.
(The two evil spirits even survived the trial.)
(The evil spirits chose the person they will steal the rice from.)
Please put your blindfolds back on.
(Whose rice was stolen by the evil spirits?)
- You can take them off. - Can we?
(The humans remove their blindfolds without a clue.)
Wait, it's already done?
All right.
- Who are they? - The evil spirits...
The human chosen by the evil spirits...
(The person the evil spirits will steal the rice from is...)
was Jae Suk.
All your rice...
(Premier Jae Suk lost all of his rice behind his back.)
now has been split between the evil spirits.
- Then he's not an evil spirit. - No, not Jae Suk.
Wait. You never know.
Yes, it could be a trick.
- To not be suspected. - Exactly.
It could've been done on purpose.
- He could've chosen himself. - Of course.
(The evil spirit tries to keep a straight face.)
That's possible.
Before we begin the first game,
(The 1st trial ends without any significant clues.)
the King...
can swap the status of two people.
(Now the King can switch the status of two people.)
Your Majesty!
(The people dream of rising in status.)
I will be by your side with a gyeonmajiro attitude.
Gyeonmajiro?
That's a nice attitude to have.
(He also doesn't know what it is.)
Gyeonmajiro...
I too will have a gyeonmajiro attitude.
To make it fun for me...
(Glancing)
It'll be fun...
to see the Premier swap places with Eunuch Lee.
Okay!
It'll be fun to see the Premier swap places with Eunuch Lee.
(A change in rank)
Okay!
Swap places.
(Airhead King appoints people just for his own amusement.)
(Come here.)
Get going.
(Jae Suk goes from Premier to a eunuch.)
- I need a mustache. - A mustache?
Let me give him a beating first.
Sure thing.
The Premier can do what he wants.
Get down on the ground.
Do as you please.
(Spanking)
This is for being cheeky earlier!
Take that.
It serves you right.
(Being humiliated after abusing his power)
Do as you wish Premier Lee.
- Darn it! This is so humiliating. - Hey.
You're the lowest in rank among us.
(You're the lowest in rank among us.)
(Their ranks are decided based on who first became a eunuch.)
Kiddo, can you clean this up?
Kiddo, clean this up.
(Humiliated)
- Unbelievable. - Clean this up.
You can let one more person trade ranks.
Unbelievable.
- I want to be Vice-premier. - I wish to be Vice-premier.
(Eunuch Ha and Slave Ji are after the vice-premier post.)
Your Majesty, I wish to be a queen.
- The Vice-premier... - How dare you!
(While everyone wants to rise in status,)
Your Majesty.
(who will be blessed by the King?)
You sure are pretty.
(Out of the blue?)
That's out of the blue.
(Slave Ji feels bashful for being chosen by Airhead King.)
- This is utter nonsense. - Who do you think is pretty?
This just doesn't make any sense!
(It's disgusting.)
Are you kidding me?
(An awful role-play they wish they've never seen)
Seriously?
No one has ever said that to me before.
("You sure are pretty"?)
There wasn't even any build-up.
- What... - I mean...
(Slave Ji blushes to an unexpected blessing.)
Unbelievable.
Gosh.
- You must've flirted with him. - How pretty.
You can be my queen.
(Me?)
You will now be a slave.
(Slave Ji turns his life around by becoming the Queen.)
- Slave Ji. - This isn't bad.
- It's not bad. - A rise in status.
- He's been blessed by the King. - Sae Rok's a slave now.
- Sae Rok... - Goodness.
This is upsetting.
"You sure are pretty" was hilarious.
(Sae Rok goes from the Queen to a slave.)
- Goodness. - Suddenly?
He needed a reason,
so he went and said "You sure are pretty."
Suk Jin seemed embarrassed by that statement.
Higher.
(Slap!)
Right? The Queen is of a higher status.
(Queen Ji shows his true colors.)
How dare you.
How dare you lay your hands on the Queen?
(How dare you?)
You shouldn't.
(The Queen's hoarse voice sounds like a smoker.)
Can a queen have such a husky voice?
You. You're awfully quiet.
Weren't you up here just a moment ago?
Close your mouth.
Close your mouth!
(Getting back at Jae Suk for humiliating him)
I told you to close your mouth.
Yes, Your Highness.
Close your mouth!
(I'm going to get you.)
(What an insult.)
- Gosh. - you.
- You know I like you, right? - Thank you.
He suddenly got to be a queen.
(The 1st trial ends with the Airhead King's appointments.)
I sure am pretty.
So pretty.
(Se Chan's people change locations.)
(Queen Ji acts cute.)
No, don't do this.
You're giving me the creeps.
(It makes Se Chan dizzy.)
- Don't do this. - Honey!
In the first game,
(The first mission each class will try)
you'll be explaining words in the format of old poems.
(They'll be explaining words in the format of old poems.)
This is Syllable Count Poem.
(Syllable Count Poem)
- That sounds difficult. - Just the sound of it...
Each team will take turns.
(Each class will take turns.)
The three explaining the word...
(The 3 explaining the word will keep the syllable count of 4, 3, and 4.)
will do so by keeping the syllable count...
(Running, name tag, tearing show, Running Man)
- of 4, 3, and 4. - No way.
- 4, 3, and 4 syllables. - Like a poem.
(The rhythm is important like the rhymes of a poem.)
Sounds like fun.
- 4, 3, and 4 syllables. - 4, 3, and 4.
Each team will get three words to explain.
(Each class will explain 3 words and get a chance to scoop rice...)
Once the game is over, you'll be able to scoop up rice...
and the amount will depend on how well you do in the game.
(based on the rankings.)
(Team Eunuch will go first.)
- Let's do this. - You're all good with words.
- Team Eunuch. - Let's go!
(The eunuchs gather their hands and cheer.)
Let's have some fun.
1, 2, 3.
Go, go!
Let's do this.
Here we go.
(Starting with Eunuch Yu, which word must they explain first?)
Give them the word.
(Playing the field)
(He must start off with 4 syllables.)
You can do this. I believe in you.
- Of course. - I believe in you.
- "Of course." Are you done? - "Of course."
(That's right!)
- He said his. - No way.
(He wasted 4 syllables in a second.)
- "Of course." - Just let him have that.
(Gosh.)
- But he said it. - "Of course."
- "Of course." - Seriously?
(Sung Hoon must explain in just 3 syllables.)
(Groaning)
(He suddenly lets out an elegant grunt.)
(The modern-day concept is hard to explain.)
What's with his pose?
(He twists his upper body as he's at his wit's end.)
- Go ahead. - What's wrong?
(Telling him off)
We got off to a bad start.
(Playing the field: Of course, Prior)
Prior.
- Will they, won't they? - Playing the field!
- Nice! - Are you kidding me?
(Thanks to Jong Kook's wit, they get the first one right.)
- Playing the field! - Nice!
I already knew when Sung Hoon said his word.
(Composed)
- I can't believe it. - What a relief.
(Jong Kook's hunch is scary.)
Okay, nice one.
(The next word is trickier to explain.)
This...
(A sitz bath)
While seated.
(A sitz bath: While seated)
(Sighing)
- He needs to say a good one. - While seated.
(A sitz bath: While seated, Warm)
It's not an easy one.
Warm.
While seated and warm.
Anus bath.
(A sitz bath is a bath for the anus.)
(The immature wording gets Jong Kook the answer.)
- Nice one. - Nice.
- A sitz bath. - Nice!
- I already knew what it was. - Nicely done!
(They get 2 in a row correctly thanks to Jong Kook.)
I told you to just make sense, right?
Haha was right to say it.
- Can one say that? - If not,
(Shocked)
it could've been lower-body bathing.
(Fascinated)
I have to give them credit for that.
I knew it was a sitz bath though.
(They get all 3 right if they guess this one correct.)
Nicely done.
You're getting the hang of it.
(Team Eunuch is on a roll. Will they guess the final one?)
- Nice! - It's perfect.
Nice!
(Nolboo)
With Heungboo.
(Nolboo: With Heungboo)
They're brothers.
(Nolboo: They're brothers.)
Budaejjigae.
(Nolboo: Budaejjigae.)
Nice one!
(The budaejjigae place is famous even among the eunuchs.)
Nice.
Nolboo.
(Team Eunuch got all three questions correct.)
Nice one!
- Nice. - Team Eunuch got all three right.
(The new queen is very satisfied.)
That was funny.
- All right! Let's go. - Let's do it well.
(It's Team Slave's turn.)
So Min is the oldest on her team.
I'm the leader. I'm the leader, you guys.
- Get ready. - This is great.
(Team Slave consists of the youngest members.)
- Here we go. - I'll do my best.
You guys look fresh!
Get ready, set, go!
(The first word is...)
(eunuch.)
Those guys...
(What?)
"Those guys"?
(It refers to those guys...)
Refers to. It refers to those guys.
- Why would you say "refers to"? - I know you can...
Why would you say "refers to"?
(The last player makes a complaint.)
- I know you can wrap it up! - Why would you be so serious?
(Sae Rok complains about the unexpected twist in the plot.)
Why would you be so serious?
- She put on a straight face. - Don't be so serious.
(You're done.)
- You blew your chance. - "Refers to".
(They get it wrong.)
Come on!
You should've said a four-letter word instead!
Maybe she's an evil spirit. Maybe this is her mission.
(They lose the first question from Sae Rok's complaint.)
It is eunuch.
Sae Rok is doing a good job!
(Pork cutlet)
Swings.
- That's a good approach. - That's a good one.
Lined up.
To sell this food.
I don't know what that is.
- You know the food he likes! - She doesn't know this?
(They get it wrong...)
She's behind in trend.
(because So Min didn't get it.)
- It's... - So Min is old-fashioned!
Maybe she got it wrong on purpose. Oh, she's not an evil spirit.
Seriously, this guy...
(A reboot of the evil spirit hunt)
- I can't do this. - I know you're not it.
- I know you're not it. Sit down. - Come on.
So Min is not an evil spirit.
(He forgets about the 1st trial and accuses So Min.)
- You got it wrong on purpose, no? - They said she's not it.
- You're an evil spirit, aren't you? - I'm not!
- Aren't you an evil spirit? - Hey.
(Even the real evil spirit suspects her.)
- Why are you so bad at this? - So Min.
Can the evil spirit leave her body for a second?
Can it leave and go back in?
(The answer is...)
It's pork cutlet.
- I didn't know that. - Hey.
(Eunuch Ha has something to say.)
- Hey. - She's only interested in love.
Kim Jong Kook and Haha's...
- Right! You should've said that. - Then she'd have gotten it right.
(He apologizes right away for his poor writing skill.)
I'd have gotten it right.
She'd have said the answer right away.
(They credit the pork cutlet made by the eunuchs a little too late.)
- Of course. - She'd have figured it out fast.
Their pork cutlet is the best.
I'll send you some.
So Team Slave got all three questions wrong.
(Despite their big fuss, they got all 3 questions wrong.)
They did well, but I couldn't get it right.
(Disappointed, but they accept the result.)
Well done.
What's our score?
(Right then)
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon cuts across the set...)
They did well,
but I couldn't get it right.
(and heads to the back.)
Well done.
Good job.
- That was close. - Only if they got one right.
(Why is he greeting all of them in the middle of the mission?)
- Well done. - Okay.
- Well done. - You did well too.
As a result, Team Eunuch is in first place.
(Why did Dong Yoon go around and tell them they did well?)
(Before the shoot)
Here's the hidden mission the evil spirits need to accomplish.
The second mission is to touch the name tags of everyone.
(The 2nd hidden mission is to touch the name tags of everyone.)
Touching their name tags?
- You can divide the mission. - We can do it together?
(The two can divide the mission too.)
(They received the hidden mission to touch everyone's name tags.)
Got it.
(From then, they looked for every chance they could get...)
1, 2...
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
(to touch everyone's name tag.)
The first person needs to do well.
Well done.
(He managed to touch most of their name tags before the mission ended.)
- That was close. - Well done.
Well done, well done.
(Who is the other spirit that touched the name tags?)
We did it.
(After Team Noble,)
Now it's time to take the rice according to the ranking.
(it's time to take the rice according to the ranking.)
The 1st place team can scoop 3 times.
(Team Eunuch in 1st place can scoop 3 times.)
(Team Noble in 2nd place can scoop 2 times.)
The 2nd place team can scoop 2 times.
And the 3rd place team can scoop 1 time.
(Team Slave in 3rd place can scoop 1 time.)
Move the rice to your pot.
We never know.
(To avoid the penalty, they'd need to secure as much rice as possible.)
All right.
- It goes deep. - He can scoop out a lot.
(Kwang Soo will be the first one to scoop the rice.)
Wow, Kwang Soo is taking a lot at once.
You scooped out a lot.
(Taking a full bowl of rice)
He filled the entire bowl.
- That's amazing. - You're amazing.
(His apt transport skill even impresses other members.)
That's as much as a bowl and a half.
(Pouring the whole bowl into his pot securely)
- He got the most rice. - Let's give it up for him.
(His great performance calls for a round of applause.)
There's a lot!
You...
Wait a minute. What's this, Kwang Soo?
No one interrupted him too.
There's another name tag on top of his.
(Changing the pot)
He poured the rice into Jae Suk's pot.
(He donated the rice to someone else's pot.)
Is this for real?
(The owner of the pot magically changes in an instant.)
(While Kwang Soo is scooping out the rice,)
(Jae Suk put his name tag on Kwang Soo's.)
It's like "The Usual Suspects".
(Goosebumps)
He peeled off Kwang Soo's tag and his name was there.
Kwang Soo must really like Jae Suk.
(Starting from Kwang Soo, Team Noble finished scooping rice.)
And the 3rd place team can scoop 1 time. Move the rice to your pot.
The 1st place team can scoop 3 times.
(All teams have scooped their rice as well.)
There's a limit to how much I can scoop.
Let's move on to the second trial.
(It's time for the second trial.)
Let's go!
(Will they be able to find the evil spirits this time?)
Let's go.
(The people of Running Dynasty gather in the court.)
My seat is right next to the King's.
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon seems excited to have finished all the missions.)
That means someone pulled off the hidden mission.
It was really hard to play the game and look for the evil spirits.
(The atmosphere is very intense ahead of the trial.)
- But I've never looked for them. - You looked for them?
We can just depend on Jong Kook.
- But when he does observe, - I observed everyone.
(Mysterious)
we tend not to.
I'm sure I've found one this time.
- You did? - Hey.
(He's sure that he's found an evil spirit?)
- I'm sure I've found one this time. - You have?
(Dong Yoon gets nervous as Jae Suk is sure to have found one.)
I have a few suspicions,
(In the midst of such intense mood,)
(everyone else, including the king, has arrived.)
but let's see what they have in common.
We're reassured since we have a detective.
(This trial is very important to the people.)
We need to catch one this time.
(If they fail, they'd need to find all 2 during the final round.)
We must catch one.
I'll switch your status.
- During the mission... - It's all up to him.
- The eunuch here... - I think he wants to say something.
(One of the eunuchs asks for permission to speak.)
- Eunuch Kim seems to have... - The youngest eunuch.
observed everyone thoroughly.
- Eunuch Yu, our youngest... - Eunuch Yu,
- go ahead and speak. - He made a mistake this time.
He made a mistake this time.
(An evil spirit made a mistake?)
What kind of mistake?
- Let's hear him out. - Let's hear about it.
- He made a mistake this time. - What kind of mistake?
(A mistake?)
- Let's hear him out. - Let's hear about it.
I think the hidden mission was to touch our name tags.
(Jae Suk figured out the hidden mission of the evil spirits?)
Name tags?
Toward the end...
Do you remember?
After Team Slave was done playing the game,
Dong Yoon...
(He named precisely Evil Spirit Dong Yoon.)
Who sat next to me?
- He touched my name tag too. - He touched our name tags.
- Well done. - That was close.
(While Dong Yoon was doing the hidden mission,)
- That was close. - Only if they got one right.
(they got suspicious of his behavior.)
"Well done."
- That's right! - That's right!
(Everyone seems to agree...)
(with Jae Suk's claim.)
- Let me tell you the reason. - Yes.
I can explain.
- Go ahead then. - All right.
Let me explain. I only touched their shoulders.
(He tries to argue that he just tried to touch the shoulder.)
- You only touched their shoulders? - Yes.
If you can't explain yourself well,
(But Jae Suk is very confident.)
- you'll have to be tried. - That's right.
We must have him tried.
(People now suspect Dong Yoon due to Jae Suk's confidence.)
Yes, we must. I'm sure it's him.
- I'm telling you, it's not me. - Then this must be what happened.
Then why didn't you touch my name tag?
- I know. - Don't be too disappointed.
But he didn't touch my name tag.
(So Min is sad because no one touched her name tag.)
You could've not felt it.
(That's what happened.)
(Is that so?)
Let me explain.
It must be hard to touch everyone's name tag though.
- Go ahead then. - It must be hard.
First of all, I did not touch everyone's name tag.
Then the mission must be to touch only a few.
(If that's the case, then the mission...)
- No, that's not true. - Maybe you had to touch three.
(Even if he tries to defend, everyone is sure that he's the one.)
It's my habit to encourage people while grabbing their shoulders.
- But he's never done that before. - He's never done it?
- No, it's just that... - He's never done it before.
- You only skipped out on me? - It's not that.
Why would everyone get so sullen?
- We're here to investigate. - Their friendship is damaged.
(Everyone is more anxious to know if their name tags were touched.)
Maybe he was told to touch only the male members.
But you need to remember this.
If Dong Yoon isn't the evil spirit,
we need to catch two at once in the next trial.
We need to catch one now.
(King Se Chan wants to use this opportunity more cautiously.)
I told you, I'm sure about this.
But what if Dong Yoon is not an evil spirit?
- We need to catch one now. - Let me tell you one more thing.
(Eunuch Yoo proposes another evidence to persuade the hesitant King.)
- Here's one more. - We'll hear you out.
But...
Dong Yoon was playing the game on this side, right?
Yes, he was on that side.
He went around the room...
(He went around the long way.)
and came behind us to tell us we did well.
He didn't have to go around the room.
- He didn't have to. - That's right.
(Dong Yoon's face turns red at Jae Suk's replay.)
- He could've just said it there. - No, that's not true.
So that's what happened.
I told you it's him.
That's right.
(It must be him.)
You must've been in a hurry.
Why did he go around the room?
(Now everyone is sure...)
(that Dong Yoon is the evil spirit.)
- We're now sure that it's him. - You got the wrong guy.
Why did he go around the room?
Why did you do that? Tell us your reason.
- Well, that's... - You didn't touch So Min's.
(Dong Yoon is being cornered.)
- Why did you touch everyone else's? - Are you usually that affectionate?
He didn't touch mine.
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon is cornered and is on the verge of arrest.)
I'm usually affectionate toward...
- If you can't explain yourself... - Okay, you can put me on trial.
If you can't explain yourself...
You can, but I'm telling you, it's not me.
Toward the end...
Seeing how confident he is, it feels like we got the wrong guy.
(Dong Yoon makes an aggressive move.)
Isn't it much easier to catch an evil spirit...
once they get someone wrong?
Did you hear what he just said?
(Isn't it Dong Yoon?)
Then you can... Even if I'm tried,
- it's my loss. - Since we're confused,
let's just put Kwang Soo on trial.
Let's just put Kwang Soo on trial.
(He's always suspected when they're not sure.)
Do you want to get a beating?
Do you want to get a beating again?
(His threat is not scary at all.)
When we're confused, just pick Kwang Soo.
(They will save that option for now.)
Please make your decision.
- All right, then. - Let's just stick to Dong Yoon.
(It's time to check 1 person through a trial.)
- Your Majesty. - If everyone agrees,
- Let's just pick him. - I'll pick him then.
(The King respects his people's opinions.)
- Your Majesty. - Let's go with him.
- We should try him. - All right.
- Even in the first game... - I'll put Dong Yoon on trial.
(They decide to put Dong Yoon on trial.)
- But he seems so confident though. - I know.
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon ends up sitting on the sack.)
- I don't think it's him. - Your Majesty, it is him.
- We could be wrong. - How dare you?
Then who's the other person that touched the name tags?
(Hold on.)
- There must be another one. - This is crazy.
(Even if Dong Yoon's arrested,)
I didn't touch everyone's name tag.
(there's still 1 more evil spirit left.)
Let's just see if he's the one.
- Okay. - All right.
All right. Dong Yoon is...
the evil spirit.
He is the evil spirit!
(They managed to catch Dong Yoon only after 2 trials.)
- I will... I will... - Your Majesty.
- think... - We managed to catch him.
very highly of you.
We managed to catch him!
(Eunuch Yoo and Eunuch Kim...)
You evil spirit!
(played a big role in catching Dong Yoon.)
- I am going to... - You wicked evil spirit!
(Too immersed)
How dare you touch our name tags?
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon drinks up the sophora root tea.)
- Gosh, this is really bitter. - That's enough.
Is it good for my health?
(Then Slave Jeon walks out from somewhere.)
- Okay. - Of course.
- Then... - We caught him.
(She grabs a candy...)
Don't finish it. It's really bitter.
(and hands it to Dong Yoon.)
He acted so well until the end.
(She quietly runs away.)
- Why did you leave quietly? - What?
(Witnessing the sight)
What do you think you're doing?
(The romance lover spotted it.)
- Nothing. - What was that all about?
(Giggling)
What?
- She gave... - So Min.
Have you ever brought us candy...
- when we drank something bitter? - I know!
- Is today Valentine's Day? - What was that all about?
(It's Valentine's Day surprise during the trial.)
- You just gave him candy? - Valentine's Day?
Why did you do that when we caught an evil spirit?
Because it's bitter.
What was that? You're an evil spirit, aren't you?
No! They said I'm not!
(They continue to suspect her as an evil spirit.)
- You see? - Okay.
If we didn't try her earlier, we'd have kept suspecting her.
- Of course. - I know.
Look what she just did.
- We did a good job. - We really did.
(It was a good idea to eliminate him at 1st.)
That was a great choice.
(The 2nd trial ends in success by arresting Dong Yoon.)
Now it's time to change your status.
(Time for King Se Chan's personnel reshuffle)
Obviously,
Eunuch Kim and Eunuch Yoo did a wonderful job.
(Eunuch Yoo and Kim played a big role in arresting Dong Yoon.)
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But I was offended...
by Premier Lee.
Me? Why?
- What did I do? - If I do not know the answer,
you are supposed to butter me up and tell me the answer.
How dare you keep your mouth shut?
(The King hated Premier Lee who doesn't kiss up to him.)
But I...
Your Majesty, I am all ready.
(Ready to get promoted)
- Your Majesty. - I'll switch Premier Lee...
I'll give you my rice.
- You're speaking informally to him? - I'll give you my rice.
(He tries to bribe as he's cornered.)
And before the next mission starts,
I'll wire you some cash.
Cash?
Your eyes tell me that you are going to betray me.
(His offer to bribe doesn't work on the King.)
I will switch Premier Lee...
(Your Majesty!)
with...
- Eunuch Yoo over there. - Yes, Your Majesty.
(Premier Lee and Eunuch Yoo switch.)
I will switch him back to being a premier.
(A glorious return of Premier Yu)
- He's back to his position. - But...
Move!
It's better to stay as Queen. I'm so lazy to change the costume.
(What?)
You're lazy to change the costume?
What's wrong, honey?
I just realized...
how ugly you are.
(The Queen needs to be switched fast.)
I need to switch you with someone else.
Your voice is beautiful.
Will you be my queen?
- My goodness. - Come on up!
(Eunuch Kim seduced King Se Chan with his beautiful voice.)
That seat is really uncomfortable.
- Get out of here. - Okay.
(Jong Kook becomes the Queen.)
- Get out of here! - Move!
Hey, you're the youngest now.
My goodness.
(Ji Suk Jin, former Queen, currently the youngest eunuch)
I am? Gosh.
- All right! - All right!
(The new Queen is energetic.)
- How gross. - He's so cute though.
Queen Jong Kook is so cute!
(Two eunuchs that made a big contribution got promoted.)
- I need to erase my mustache. - You should.
Now I'll tell you the rules of the final mission.
(The final mission of Records of the Running Dynasty)
In the final mission,
you could be a prey or you could be a hunter.
(You could be a prey...)
(or a hunter.)
It's called the Ironic Survival Game.
(Ironic Survival Game)
It's a survival game where you'll use a toy gun.
(It's a survival game where you'll use a toy gun.)
- It sounds fun. - Sounds like fun.
You'll each attach five balloons to your body.
(You'll each attach 5 balloons to your body.)
We'll give you 30 bullets.
(We'll give you 30 bullets.)
- It's that game. - We're using balloons again.
You can't shoot at just anyone on the opposite team.
(You can't shoot at just anyone on the opposite team.)
At two different spots in this building,
(There are two roulettes with your names on them.)
there are two roulettes with your names on them.
You should spin the roulettes,
(The name you get after spinning the roulette will be your target.)
and the name you get will be your target.
- I see. - We have different targets.
(It means your target will continuously change.)
So we don't know who will be our targets.
Your target will be changed every two minutes.
(Your target will be changed every 2 minutes.)
The person you get after spinning the roulettes...
will be your target for two minutes.
When all of your balloons pop, you'll be out.
(The game will be played for 20 minutes.)
The ranking of the teams will be determined by who remains last.
(The ranking will be determined by the number of balloons.)
The final winner can scoop out the rice.
All right. I got good team members.
(Dong Yoon will pull off a hidden mission with another evil spirit.)
- Of course. - You picked the good ones.
Let's move to the starting point of the last mission.
(Who will be the last team to survive?)
- Let's go! - Let's go.
Since I got busted already,
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon got arrested in the trial.)
I think I can do a good job in helping the other evil spirit.
Wish me luck!
(He has to pull off the hidden mission with the other evil spirit.)
Hold on.
- Haha. - Yes?
- Are you busy? - Why? What's up?
(Dong Yoon suddenly visits Haha.)
Can I put my forehead against yours?
- What? - Can we put our foreheads together?
(He suddenly puts his forehead against Haha's.)
Oh, you're just doing the mission plainly?
What's this? Am I becoming an evil spirit?
Will this make me an evil spirit?
- What was that? - I'm off now!
(Is holding hands and touching foreheads the last mission?)
I'm off! Was that okay?
Okay.
(Meanwhile, the King and Queen are outside.)
- Hey... - Since we're on the same team,
- I know that. - if I'm cornered,
you need to come and help. You know that, right, King?
(Same team)
- Do not worry, Queen Jong Kook. - Honey.
I will protect my queen.
- Honey. - I'm here, and you're there.
I'm here, and you're there.
(He's the King's man.)
- Honey! - Gosh. What is it?
It's so gross. It feels like...
- You need to protect me. - Don't worry.
(Airhead King loves how cute Muscle Queen is.)
- How adorable. - Honey.
You're so cute!
(My Queen is so cute.)
(Stamping his feet with his big build)
I'll be waiting. You need to come to me.
(Queen Mustache has too much testosterone and is too cute.)
- Don't worry! - Okay? To over here.
The race will start now.
(Then the alarm rings, and the race begins.)
Okay.
The targets are...
(Announcing the first targets)
(Who will be the first targets that will be attacked by everyone?)
The targets are...
(The first targets are...)
Kim Dong Jun and Song Ji Hyo.
(Kim Dong Jun and Song Ji Hyo)
The first targets are Kim Dong Jun and Song Ji Hyo.
(They're the targets!)
(They run away first.)
This is driving me crazy.
Kim Dong Jun and Song Ji Hyo? I'm coming! Bang, bang!
- Song Ji Hyo and Kim Dong Jun. - Dong Jun?
(So Min and Sae Rok have to protect Dong Jun.)
We need to protect Dong Jun.
Wait a minute. Where could Dong Jun be?
Song Ji Hyo and Kim Dong Jun?
Okay, no one on our team is a target.
(They need to protect their team members to win.)
I should hide in here.
(Ji Hyo plans to hide inside a lecture room.)
Come in quickly.
(Dong Jun is at the end of the corridor.)
Look for Dong Jun now!
(Jae Suk appears right then.)
Dong Jun is on Team Slave.
(He spots Jae Suk in red from afar.)
Darn it.
(He quickly flees downstairs.)
(Eunuch Park Sung Hoon appears.)
(There's my target!)
(The first chase begins.)
(Sung Hoon does his best to chase Dong Jun,)
(but Dong Jun is getting further away.)
(Dong Jun runs away relaxedly.)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
(Paper Doll Sung Hoon appears way too late.)
(He misses all his shots.)
Why doesn't it work? I can't shoot the bullet!
I can't shoot the bullet!
(Blaming the bullets)
(Relaxed Dong Jun...)
I can't shoot it!
(and the guy with a mullet who runs as fast as he can)
Darn it!
Darn it.
(We can only hear his sound of breathing.)
I could've shot him.
(Showing off his poor stamina as soon as the chase starts)
(Another guy with a mullet appears.)
Dong Jun?
I got him!
Hey, Dong Jun.
(Dong Jun ran into Haha...)
Haha! We need to finish him!
(while running away from Kwang Soo.)
(It popped!)
(Haha's camera)
(Another one popped.)
Finish him!
(2 of Dong Jun's balloons popped in an instant.)
No, no!
This is exhausting.
(He confronts Kwang Soo with a door in between.)
It will work. It's open!
It's open!
(Kwang Soo squeezed himself through the door.)
Here.
(Dong Jun is in danger!)
(All balloons popped.)
He's out!
(Kwang Soo hit the balloon when Dong Jun was about to flee.)
- Kim Dong Jun is out. - All right!
- Kim Dong Jun is out. - I did it!
(Kim Dong Jun is out.)
(Unfortunately, Dong Jun becomes the first target to be eliminated.)
I couldn't do anything.
I was about to...
Kim Dong Jun is out.
(Right then, Dong Yoon puts his forehead against Dong Jun's.)
The second targets are Kim Jong Kook and Park Sung Hoon.
(Targets change)
(Turning)
- Hey, I'm on your team. - Oh, right.
(He automatically aims his gun.)
My goodness. Hey!
(He gets ready to attack before distinguishing the team.)
- I'm sorry. - That's quite upsetting, you know.
I'm so sorry.
- Who's the other one? - Who's the other target?
(They set off to find Sung Hoon the target.)
Who's the other target?
- Oh, Sung Hoon? - It's Sung Hoon.
(The tall guy with poor stamina is the second target.)
He's over here!
- Come here, everyone! - Run, Sung Hoon!
(He runs away first.)
- Run! - Shoot him! What are you doing?
(Se Chan chases after Sung Hoon right away.)
Why would I? He's on my team.
Run!
Run, Sung Hoon!
(He runs at full speed without even turning back.)
- Who's the other target? - Jong Kook.
Gosh, this is really exhausting.
(His breathing gets heavy as though he's about to throw up.)
(He's about to pass out.)
They said you can't get out of bed for two days...
if you shoot Running Man.
I should stay in bed for three days.
(While Sung Hoon announced that he'll stay in bed for 3 days,)
(what has Dong Yoon been up to?)
How come...
Excuse me.
- What is it? What are you doing? - Let me put my forehead...
Wait. Hey!
Hey!
(He tries to hold Jae Suk's hand and put his forehead against him.)
Why would you...
I did it. I did it for him.
- But... - I did it for him.
(Dong Yoon is openly doing the mission here?)
- Just do it for him. - Yes?
(Jae Suk puts his forehead against Dong Yoon's for now.)
The current targets are...
(Then new targets are announced.)
Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk?)
(Current targets: Jae Suk, Suk Jin)
(Dong Yoon was right next to him.)
(He succeeds to pop 1 of Jae Suk's balloons.)
Hey! Hey!
(1 more balloon pops.)
Ji Hyo! Hey!
- Ji Hyo, I am on your team. - Oh, you are right.
- Oh, you are right. - I popped two balloons.
(Dong Yoon chases after Jae Suk.)
(He's out of bullets.)
- I used up my bullets. - You are out of bullets.
(Jae Suk succeeds in getting away.)
(This is such an important moment.)
You are out of bullets.
Where is Suk Jin?
(Suk Jin is the other target.)
(The targets got announced when Suk Jin was with Se Chan.)
(He shows his pitiful back as always.)
(He runs to a dead end.)
You are out of bullets.
(He manages to prolong his life because Se Chan is out of bullets.)
No way!
- Suk Jin, run! - Help me!
- Help me! - Suk Jin!
- Help me! - Don't go that way!
(He runs into the muscular queen.)
(Jong Kook's camera)
- Help me! - Don't go that way!
(His scream fills the studio.)
- Suk Jin! - No!
- Run! - No!
(He runs with hunters chasing him.)
Run!
- Why won't the balloons pop? - Run!
(Everyone is obsessed with the shooting game.)
- Help me! - Run!
(Even Dong Yoon joins the hunt for Eunuch Ji.)
No!
(Dong Yoon's camera)
- Help me! - Run!
Run!
Run! Run!
(Kwang Soo the eunuch blocks the door with his body.)
Run!
(He runs away with 2 balloons thanks to Kwang Soo.)
No.
(Ji Hyo chases after him!)
- Suk Jin. - All right.
(Suk Jin has no energy left to run away.)
- I am sorry. - It's okay.
Isn't it time to spin the wheel?
(Bang! Bang!)
(Two balloons pop at once!)
(Ji Hyo popped 2 balloons with 1 bullet.)
Did both balloons get popped?
(She's surprised at herself.)
Why did both balloons get popped?
Did she pop two balloons at once?
- Really? - Did I do that with one bullet?
Suk Jin is out.
(Suk Jin's out in an instant.)
- Gosh. - Suk Jin is out.
Did anyone else get eliminated?
(Suk Jin's race lasted for less than 10 minutes as usual.)
I am the first one, right?
The race...
(It's been a while.)
starts.
(After Dong Jun, Suk Jin gets eliminated.)
Did you see Jae Suk?
- I popped two balloons. - Where is he?
(Kwang Soo runs into Evil Spirit Dong Yoon.)
What?
Let me put my forehead against yours.
(He tries to hold Kwang Soo's hand and to touch his forehead.)
- Why? - Let me do that.
Why do you need to do that?
- What? - What is up with him?
- Hey. - What?
(Dong Yoon tries to hold Sae Rok's hand too.)
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it!
(Every time he sees a member,)
(he holds their hands and touches their foreheads.)
Let go of me!
(Is Dong Yoon carrying out a hidden mission?)
I... I...
He is so suspicious.
Is there a way to make more evil spirits...
- or turn someone into one? - The current targets are...
Sae Rok and Se Chan.
(Sae Rok loses 3 balloons because of Jong Kook right away.)
No!
(With no place to go,)
(the former queen gets taken out by royalty.)
(Se Chan, the other target, gets chased for a while.)
(He gets eliminated when the last balloon pops.)
Se Chan and Sae Rok are out.
- No! - The current targets are...
Jae Suk and Sung Hoon.
(The current targets are Jae Suk and Sung Hoon.)
(Jae Suk tries to go to a secluded place.)
(Panting)
(So Min sees him.)
(Jae Suk's location)
(While she prepares to attack, Dong Yoon appears.)
I don't have many bullets.
Dong Yoon, come here.
(Whispering)
Jae Suk is in here.
(Jae Suk doesn't have many bullets.)
Is that door open?
Do you want me to go in?
- Aren't you going to shoot him? - I guess I should.
You are acting strange.
(Dong Yoon looks strange.)
What is up with you?
(He turns around.)
You are acting strange.
(Why isn't Dong Yoon attacking Jae Suk?)
You are acting strange. What?
- No, no. - Hold on.
Okay.
So Min.
(Is he trying to protect a fellow evil spirit?)
It's not like that.
You are acting strange.
(Or is it Dong Yoon's highly sophisticated strategy?)
That's so suspicious.
Why doesn't Dong Yoon want to shoot Jae Suk?
The current targets are...
(Meanwhile, the targets...)
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
(are changed to Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
Gosh, the targets changed.
(An evil spirit candidate, Jae Suk comes outside.)
That's so suspicious.
Why didn't Dong Yoon want to shoot Jae Suk?
Why did he hesitate?
(Dong Yoon seemed to hesitate when he could take out Jae Suk.)
Who? Dong Yoon?
(So Min finds it strange.)
Okay.
(The current targets, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
(Kwang Soo the eunuch was picking up bullets.)
(What?)
What? That startled me.
What are those neon shoes?
(He spots familiar fluorescent color shoes.)
Jong Kook is a target, right?
- Yes. - Gosh, that startled me.
How do I open this?
(Jong Kook who was hiding in the restroom got caught.)
I was going to go out when Kwang Soo left.
Jong Kook is here.
(Eunuchs gather at the news of finding the target.)
What should we do?
(But they don't know what to do.)
(They start spraying water.)
(For goodness' sake.)
(He even spits out water.)
The current targets are Haha and Ji Hyo.
(He gets caught when the targets change.)
Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo.
(It lands on his face.)
(Jong Kook leaves to find Haha after getting wet.)
Haha, run!
Haha!
- You are here. - Jong Kook.
(Haha hid in the next restroom.)
Jong Kook, I have a bad back.
- He is here, Jae Suk! - I have a bad back.
- Haha. - We need to finish him off.
Come on.
(Jong Kook's camera)
- Haha! - That stings!
- Ouch. - Haha.
(Haha has 1 balloon left.)
Turn around.
Come on out.
(It popped.)
My goodness.
I couldn't run away.
(Haha is out.)
Haha is out.
- Haha is out. - Sung Hoon.
(Only 4 minutes left.)
The current targets are Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Suk, the new targets get announced.)
(Team Eunuch: 3, Team Slave: 2, Team Noble: 2)
I have three bullets left.
(The survival of one person could affect the rank.)
With these three bullets, I will make a difference.
(He is overly absorbed in the game.)
What are you doing?
Dong Yoon, hold on! Listen to me!
(Dong Yoon attacks Kwang Soo when his guard is down.)
Dong Yoon, stop! Dong Yoon!
(Both teams are in second place.)
(If Kwang Soo gets eliminated, Team Eunuch will place last.)
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk?
(While the two of them fight, these people go after Jae Suk.)
(They spot Jae Suk.)
(The weak duo goes after Jae Suk as well.)
By the way, Jae Suk is really fast.
I am exhausted.
(Kwang Soo's last balloon is before his eyes,)
(but Dong Yoon keeps missing it.)
(Jae Suk is being chased.)
- The other way. - The other way?
(The weak duo chases him.)
It's too late for that.
(The last targets will determine the result.)
Please.
Come on!
(Kwang Soo is using strength,)
(and Jae Suk is using speed.)
I refuse to go out.
(The two targets must survive to keep the teams' ranks.)
(What will be the result of the final race?)
Welcome back.
(The race ends.)
- Kwang Soo, did you survive? - I survived.
(The final survivors enter the courtroom.)
Good work.
I can't guess the result.
(What's the final result of this race?)
Firstly,
the evil spirits succeeded to do the hidden mission.
(The evil spirit succeeded the hidden mission.)
- Was there another one? - What could it be?
I guess there was something other than the forehead touch.
(The 1st place)
I will announce the result. The first place is...
(It goes to Team Noble with 3 survivals.)
Team Noble.
Then the other 2 teams placed 2nd.
(They won thanks to Jae Suk who survived.)
They will scoop out rice two times.
(Team Eunuch and Team Slave both placed 2nd.)
Now,
(They get to scoop out rice according to the result.)
shall we begin with the slaves?
It's game over.
(Everyone scooped rice.)
The tables have been turned.
We don't have much.
After a general meeting,
(The final trial)
the king will decide who will be put on a stand.
(This is the one last chance.)
This is driving me crazy.
- Jae Suk, I keep hearing tip-offs. - What?
(Jae Suk became an evil spirit candidate during the mission.)
Some people saw...
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon didn't attack Jae Suk.)
how Dong Yoon avoided popping your balloons.
This is bad.
Jae Suk is suspicious.
- Jae Suk is suspicious. - That's right.
It must be true.
When you said that Jae Suk is suspicious,
(Dong Yoon strongly denies as So Min suspects Jae Suk.)
Dong Yoon said no.
- Is there a reason to say no? - Seriously.
- Seriously. - I know.
(If Jae Suk isn't an evil spirit, he doesn't have to say he's not.)
He had no reason to say no.
- To be honest... - I mean...
He got caught.
He is too pure.
Let me tell you this.
- I am not an evil spirit. - He is changing the subject.
Think about the seating arrangement we had on the bus.
(On the way here)
If you think about it,
Jae Suk and Dong Yoon sat together.
(They were sitting in the corner together.)
They sat by the window.
- Jae Suk sat by the window. - That's right.
(The corner is the perfect place to make a heart.)
- They were behind me. - Yes.
- Dong Yoon tried to depend on him. - Did they sit together?
(Did they sit in the corner together for the hidden mission?)
They sat together.
Dong Yoon tried to depend on him. That's why he sat next to Jae Suk.
(They look even more suspicious after going over the detail.)
If I am not an evil spirit,
you will be in big trouble.
(Jae Suk argues, but no one listens to him.)
- You have one chance. - We are simply throwing out...
- ideas. - Okay, okay.
Can I give you an alibi?
Go ahead.
Are you trying...
- to protect Jae Suk? - An alibi?
(Jae Suk's alibi?)
Why are you protecting him?
(Jae Suk)
- I mean... - It's so confusing.
Why are you protecting him?
Are you trying to protect me?
You are making it look weird.
(Jae Suk's in danger.)
Everything he does seems suspicious.
(And Dong Yoon defends him.)
- Dong Yoon... - Look at that.
He lost control.
- He lost control. - He lost control of the situation.
(Dong Yoon.)
(Whether it's a mistake or strategy, it's getting out of control.)
Are you trying...
- Dong Yoon. - Give us the alibi.
- His ears turned red. - He dug himself into a hole.
His ears turned red.
- I will talk. - Okay.
Why did you take Jae Suk's rice?
(Why did he steal Jae Suk's rice after the first trial?)
- Why did you take it? - I thought...
he would acquire a lot of rice.
(Simple)
Was that the reason?
(Dong Yoon's words are unclear.)
Most people would have chosen Jong Kook.
- I can't believe him! - Let's send Jae Suk to the stand.
- We have the answer. - It's pretty clear.
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon keeps defending Jae Suk.)
Jae Suk is suspicious.
Dong Yoon and Jae Suk are suspicious.
The other evil spirit must be a veteran.
(It's definitely Jae Suk.)
The Running Man members are better at carrying out...
(The hidden missions were quite hard for a guest.)
a mission such as touching the name tags...
(They expect him to get help from another evil spirit.)
- in secret. - That's right.
We should be suspicious of Jong Kook too.
That goes without saying.
(Based on experience, the other evil spirit must be a member.)
The other evil spirit must be a Running Man member.
- That must be the case. - But...
Kwang Soo...
Oh, he isn't Kwang Soo.
He resembles Kwang Soo.
(It's hard to tell with the foolish mustache.)
- Seriously. - He resembles Kwang Soo.
- I am here. - He has long hair too.
(The mullet doppelganger causes a ruckus.)
- He resembles Kwang Soo. - He looks the same.
- He resembles Kwang Soo. - I see the resemblance.
(The handsome guest reminds them of Kwang Soo.)
I would believe it if someone said that they are brothers.
Sae Rok, who do you think is the other evil spirit?
(Who does Sae Rok think is the evil spirit?)
- I think it's Jae Suk. - Why?
- This is driving me crazy. - Earlier,
(Popular)
So Min said repeatedly...
(She's persuaded after hearing that Dong Yoon didn't shoot him.)
that Dong Yoon didn't shoot at Jae Suk.
I suggested that we go and attack Jae Suk together.
(It's hard to read Jae Suk's face.)
When I gave you his location,
(She talks about how he let go of Jae Suk excitedly.)
you were like, "Why?" He was hesitant.
- He wanted to go someplace else. - So Min spread this story.
But So Min isn't an evil spirit.
(But So Min is not an evil spirit.)
- She isn't an evil spirit. - Be honest.
(She checks again.)
- You aren't an evil spirit, right? - Are you?
- She is too suspicious. - I am not an evil spirit.
(It's very strange that she's not an evil spirit.)
Let's send So Min to the stand...
one more time to be certain.
(Everyone can't help but think there must be a mistake.)
I am not an evil spirit.
Why are people so suspicious of me?
Dong Yoon was with me for a while.
(Haha reports what he saw on Dong Yoon.)
- That's right. They were together. - And...
Dong Yoon held people's hands and put his forehead against theirs.
(He tried to do his mission on everyone he sees.)
- That's right. - When he did that,
Sae Rok ran away and Dong Jun refused to do it.
(It was normal for everyone else to run away.)
Everyone ran away.
But Jae Suk went,
"Really?" Then he put his forehead against Dong Yoon's.
All right, Dong Yoon.
(He let Dong Yoon hold his hand and put his forehead against his.)
It's strange.
He is either an angel...
(He is either a saint...)
- or someone with a mission. - No.
(or an evil spirit who acted very obviously.)
I let him do it because I thought he was faking.
- I can explain clearly. - Hold on.
You haven't explained anything clearly!
- Hey! - Wasn't it locked?
(The Premier loses temper.)
You haven't explained anything clearly!
Jae Suk.
Why do you think Dong Yoon keeps protecting you?
He is trying to hide his partner.
Everyone thinks I am the other evil spirit,
(Jae Suk argues that everything is Dong Yoon's strategy.)
so Dong Yoon is driving a nail into the coffin.
(But it could be the last attempt to defend himself.)
He is doing this to help the team win.
Are you saying he twisted it twice to frame you...
when someone else is the other evil spirit?
That would make him a genius.
(Is it Dong Yoon's big mistake? Is it his flawless strategy?)
So this might be a feint?
There is the fanny pack.
(Jae Suk dozed off staring at Dong Yoon.)
- You know, - But an evil spirit...
your Highness.
If you are unsure,
choose Eunuch Lee.
Why do you keep framing me?
(If you are unsure, choose Eunuch Lee.)
Why would he choose me? I didn't do anything today.
(That's not fair.)
Hold on. It's true.
(What?)
- It's over. - It's over.
It's over. His rice is gone.
(I beg your pardon?)
- It's over. - His rice is gone.
- Let go. - It's over.
(Eunuch Lee lost all the rice he gathered.)
- Leave it. - Don't touch the rice.
- Leave it. - Don't touch it.
(My rice...)
It isn't allowed.
- It was a mistake. - It doesn't matter.
(The staff member will collect the spilled rice on the floor.)
- Leave it. - Leave it.
You spilled it.
- You spilled it. - Leave it.
(He lost all his savings.)
It's not like someone else spilled it.
There are about 12 grains of rice inside.
(Now...)
Who is the other evil spirit? Who is the other evil spirit?
Who is it?
- You need to catch the evil spirit. - Who is it?
(If Kwang Soo is a human and Team Human loses,)
Will Kwang Soo get the penalty if we don't catch the evil spirit?
- Yes. - Yes.
(Kwang Soo will get the penalty.)
Then we won't need to do it.
Hold on.
Please make a decision.
Let me be honest.
Isn't it a bit late?
When the evil spirits removed the blindfolds,
(When all humans wore blindfolds after the first trial,)
we heard music.
- But I heard a sound from my right. - That's right! Who made it?
Who was to your right?
(Who was sitting on the right of Kwang Soo during the first trial?)
- I didn't hear anything. - Didn't you sit over there?
- Did you sit here? - No, no.
Sae Rok, Ji Hyo...
(It's one of Sae Rok, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook.)
- Me. - Jong Kook, Ji Hyo...
I don't think it's Sae Rok.
(He heard a sound that came from the three of them?)
- I heard a sound. - What sound?
- Okay. - Jong Kook sat there.
I heard the ping of a rubber band.
That was me.
I kept doing this since the blindfold wasn't in place.
I kept doing this.
The rubber band could be a big hint.
(Seriously)
- I heard a sound. - Seriously.
(Jae Suk becomes lively again.)
- Look at Jae Suk. - I am serious.
- Jae Suk suddenly became lively. - Look at Jae Suk.
(He can't hide his facial expressions.)
He wants to hold on to the smallest suspicion.
"That's right. That's it."
(He deduces without any reasons.)
He is in a hurry.
Seriously. Jae Suk is so funny.
(In contrast, Jong Kook looks very relaxed.)
- Jae Suk. - Everyone.
What Kwang Soo said is a big hint.
- I heard a sound. - The rubber band.
Earlier,
(Speaking passionately)
- I continued... - He is coming up with excuses.
(Laughing)
For goodness' sake.
(Are you mocking me?)
The more you talk, the more pitiful you seem.
(Even at the news of Jong Kook's suspicious rubber sounds...)
Jae Suk, this is what everyone wants.
(But...)
That's right.
- This is what everyone wants. - That's right.
(But the majority is suspecting Jae Suk.)
- Kwang Soo is our plan B. - Premier Yu.
(Jae Suk is framed due to Dong Yoon's strategy or mistake.)
I am not an evil spirit.
- Maybe he isn't one. - I am really not an evil spirit.
(Wait. Why does he look more innocent?)
Maybe he isn't one.
- At this point... - Maybe he isn't one.
I think it's Jong Kook. But I can't be sure.
(Kwang Soo suspects Jong Kook until the end.)
- Then I will go up the stand. - We can't be sure.
Do you want me to go up?
If you want me to go up, I will do it.
(Jong Kook's provocation)
If Jae Suk is an evil spirit, he will get the penalty, right?
(If Kwang Soo is a human,)
He is scary.
(and Team Human loses, Kwang Soo will get the penalty.)
If I am not an evil spirit, you will get the penalty, right?
I will go up.
(If that's the case...)
(Jong Kook is pushing away Jae Suk?)
- It's up to the king. - I will go up.
- I will go up. - Come on.
I am serious.
- I will go up. - No, no.
- Jae Suk is happy. - I am serious.
No, no. Jong Kook.
(Why is he smiling after he's removed from the stand?)
Jae Suk is happy.
- Why are you smiling? - It's Jae Suk!
Why is Jae Suk happy?
(I caught you, you evil spirit.)
He is happy.
(Is it an evil spirit's smile seen from Jae Suk's smile?)
- Why are you smiling? - It's Jae Suk!
- Jong Kook, I am sorry. - I want him to get the penalty.
(He apologies to Protein Monster who voluntarily stepped up.)
I am sorry.
- You were suspicious of me. - I am sorry.
(Everyone's leaning toward Jae Suk after his smile.)
You aren't an evil spirit.
- You aren't an evil spirit. - I will go up.
Sit down, evil spirit!
He couldn't hide his smile.
(He returns soon.)
As soon as he turned around, he showed a smile.
He smiled as he walked away.
He smiled.
My goodness.
(The smiling saint is quickly arrested.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's put Jae Suk on trial.
(The King picks Jae Suk.)
Okay. I agree.
- No. - I put Premier Yoo on trial.
I can't believe Dong Yoon.
(He either fell for Dong Yoon's tricks...)
(or Dong Yoon made a mistake.)
Jae Suk is so funny.
I will tell you after this.
Dong Yoon saw someone.
If Jae Suk is an evil spirit,
(If Jae Suk is an evil spirit, Team Evil Spirit will lose.)
Team Evil Spirits will lose.
If he isn't an evil spirit,
(If he isn't an evil spirit, Team Evil Spirit will win.)
someone else would be one.
You are frustrated because of Dong Yoon, right?
- All right. - It has to be Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk is on the stand after Dong Yoon's few words.)
It would be strange if he isn't.
Jae Suk...
(What did his smile mean when he was saved?)
- is... - No way.
Jae Suk...
Let's see.
No way.
(Jae Suk's identity that everyone wanted to know)
- Is... - An evil spirit.
- An evil spirit. - An evil spirit.
Not an evil spirit.
(He is not an evil spirit.)
Yes!
(Jae Suk is a human, not an evil spirit.)
- Yes! - Not an evil spirit.
Yes!
You should have objected more.
(Dong Yoon won.)
- Why did you smile? - Yes!
You should have objected more.
(Team Human lost.)
I objected as much as I could.
- You should have objected more. - I objected as much as I could.
(Everyone is shocked.)
- Why did you smile? - I...
Oh, no.
He really wasn't one.
Does that mean Dong Yoon twisted it twice?
(Amazing)
The evil spirits won.
(The evil spirits won.)
The one who succeeded in doing...
(The one who succeeded as many missions as Dong Yoon...)
as many missions as Dong Yoon...
I am so curious.
- The second evil spirit is... - Who is it?
(The second evil spirit's identity)
(The perfect execution of the hidden missions...)
(along with even more perfect acting)
(The second evil spirit's identity is...)
Congratulations,
Sae Rok.
(Sae Rok is an evil spirit.)
What?
I said that two guests could be the evil spirits.
(Shocked)
Two guests.
I said that two guests could be the evil spirits.
(Two guests were the evil spirits.)
Two guests.
I said that two guests could be the evil spirits.
(Sae Rok, the second evil spirit was daring and secretive.)
(A few days ago,)
(Sae Rok found a suspicious jar.)
What is this? A pot?
(She opens it naturally as if she was told to do it.)
I finally got a body.
Shall I party now?
(She's very good at this type of acting.)
(Thus, Sae Rok was reborn as an evil spirit.)
Today, we will have the Records of the Running Dynasty Race.
(They'll enter Running Dynasty Palace as evil spirits.)
You are the evil spirits that are hiding among people.
(Sae Rok's secret and daring hidden mission)
Okay.
Evil spirits.
(Hidden mission 1, Make 3 hearts in the car)
(She made hearts even during a conversation.)
(Then the 1st trial took place.)
- Your Majesty. - Like I said before,
Dong Yoon hit Sae Rok in the head and joked around with her.
(Kwang Soo was suspicious of Sae Rok and Dong Yoon.)
- Both of them did that. - Could it be Sae Rok?
(Is it Sae Rok?)
- That's so random. - We know there are team missions.
(They kept a distance and shook off people's suspicions.)
(Exchanging a signal)
Dong Yoon.
(They met up throughout the missions.)
I will touch the red and you will touch the green.
(Touching the nametags)
Come in a bit later. Go to the restroom.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
(Touching together)
- Third? - I added so much.
(Touching)
(She remained confident and avoided suspicion.)
The last mission is holding hands for a minute...
(The last mission is to hold hands for a minute...)
while you are on the same floor as another member.
(while you are on the same floor as another member.)
(The last mission was hard.)
Hold other people's hands.
Link arms with them.
(She instructs him.)
Do something, okay?
Okay. I will do it.
(As Sae Rok instructed, Dong Yoon held people's hands.)
Do it right.
Can I put my forehead against yours?
Oh, you're just doing the mission plainly?
What are you doing? Stop it! Stop it!
(He carried out a hidden mission with Sae Rok in plain sight.)
Stop it!
(Holding hands)
Let go of me!
(Although Sae Rok shouted, she held his hand tighter.)
(We did it.)
Come here.
(They held hands for over 3 minutes.)
(Sae Rok and Dong Yoon had a perfect victory.)
Let's go, Dong Yoon!
Yes!
(The two guest evil spirits had a perfect victory.)
(Their teammates are shocked.)
I was totally fooled.
The guests.
(Members are shocked to find out the two guests were evil spirits.)
Since you always expected to see 1 member and 1 guest,
we gave the roles to two guests this time.
They made us suspect each other.
(The members were suspicious of each other.)
I suspected Ji Hyo until the very end.
(It has been a few years since the guests did it by themselves.)
I thought there would be a Running Man member.
- Seriously. - I was suspicious.
- Dong Yoon. - Yes?
Why did you protect Jae Suk? Was it a strategy?
- It was a strategy. - Of course it was.
I can't believe him.
(This is how scary a smart person can be.)
- It was a strategy? - He did well.
I kept laughing and exchanging looks with Dong Yoon.
(Throughout the trial)
- Really? - Did you exchange looks?
(The two had all the fun while members argued.)
I had no idea.
I got goosebumps at the end.
It was a strategy.
Dong Yoon didn't look in this direction.
(I saw it.)
- He kept looking this way. - Jae Suk.
- Sit down. - Sit down.
Stop pretending to be sharp and sit down.
You should have said that earlier.
You didn't trust my words!
(After being scolded by Jong Kook, he takes it out on Kwang Soo.)
- I am sorry. - It was so hard today.
(Suspicious evil So Min is desperately begging.)
Every time I said something, he went...
(He was hurt the most by Sung Hoon's mockery.)
It was the most annoying.
Every time I said something,
(His dirty mullet made Jae Suk lose his cool.)
he went...
(The Premier lost his confidence at the weakest Sung Hoon's gaze.)
I couldn't believe it.
I thought it was obvious.
The prize of the day comes from the West.
(Prizes for the two evil spirits that won)
Western fruits and a Western snack, macarons.
(Western fruits and macaroons imported by a Western missionary.)
A Western snack.
The prize will go to the two of them.
(They can finally have a taste of the Western world.)
And the penalty for today is flogging.
(Kwang Soo with the least amount of rice among humans...)
(will receive a penalty.)
It's not like you're dying.
(Flogging by the King)
Se Chan, hit him hard.
- It won't kill you anyway. - Make it hard.
(People start saying that they don't care.)
It's just loud. That doesn't hurt.
It won't kill you.
- I'll begin. - Oh, no.
(Eunuch Lee's career ends with a punishment.)
This is for fun.
- It doesn't hurt, does it? - It doesn't.
- There you go. - It won't hurt.
(Thudding)
(The king's power)
(The king's power makes him bow automatically.)
That was amazing.
It sounded great.
Say, "I'm the king."
Well done. That was good.
- It felt great. - That was great.
(Thanks to Jang Dong Yoon, Park Sung Hoon, Kim Dong Jun...)
Good. Okay.
Good work today.
(and Keum Sae Rok for their appearance.)
(We hope "Joseon Exorcist" will be successful.)
- Good work. - Good work.
This is the only variety show that has...
two Grand Award winners.
I'm so proud.
You can pick a captain you want...
(Yoo Jae Suk or Kim Jong Kook. Pick a captain you want.)
and perform missions with him.
I feel uncomfortable already.
(They feel uncomfortable already.)
- Don't look at us. - Don't give us a look.
(They sign the oath that says they will never get upset.)
Don't glare at us.
- Look. He's glaring at me. - I swear I won't be upset.
(Will they be able to spend the day without getting upset?)
Good, good! Let's go!
(They show the Pumbaa dance to liven up the mood.)
- Do this with your upper body. - Why are you doing squats?
(That's when...)
- Make sure it's well-cooked. - Okay. I'm uncomfortable here.
(the Grand Award winner starts acting high-handedly.)
- That darn beanpole. - Ji Hyo,
(The members can't take it anymore and run away from the captains.)
Hey, Kwang Soo jumped into the sea.
(They even ran away to a mud flat.)
Why is he hiding in there?
- What? - That beanpole...
(The Grand Award winners are coming to find them.)
It will snap, you fool.
Why are they all in that place?
- You promised you won't be upset. - I'm doing this alone today.
(Who will keep their promise and upgrade the dignity of the award?)
It's upsetting for those who didn't win the Grand Award.
(Yoo Jae Suk versus Kim Grand Award, Dignity of Grand Award)