(The fresh air of May
with the smell of summer)
- Hello.
Hello.
- Hello, Se Chan.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello, Kwang Soo.
Hello.
I was enjoying a hot iced...
I mean...
I was reading an English newspaper
with a hot Americano.
Good morning.
(The English newspaper reader
with poor language ability)
- Hello.
- Hello. Good morning.
Good morning.
Jae Suk,
do you think you are quick-witted?
I don't think I have quick wits.
I'd rather say I'm slow-witted.
Then I have bad news for you.
Today, the members with quick wits
will get more coins.
It's called the Read the Room Race.
The Read the Room Race?
"The" is spelled T-H-E.
Are you kidding me?
Of course I know how it's spelled.
(The English newspaper reader
just learned a new word.)
In today's race,
the coins are as important
as quick wits.
And the number of coins you get
will decide the time you go home.
(The number of coins they get
will decide the time they go home.)
If I win,
will I get to go home early?
If it ends quickly,
you might be able to go home
right away.
Oh, it's about what time we go home.
I'm serious now.
We'll now begin
the preliminary mission...
to get your first coins.
We have two restaurants
where you can have breakfast.
You can go to a restaurant you like
and have a satisfying breakfast.
I already had breakfast.
Why would I eat again?
- That means you're slow-witted.
- Gosh.
- I'm serious.
- What?
But the number of coins you can get
in each restaurant is different.
Is it different?
30 coins for the Chinese restaurant
and 80 coins for the Korean one.
(Chinese 30 coins,
Korean 80 coins)
My goodness.
You will split the coins evenly
with the members...
who come to the same restaurant
as you.
So you should go to the restaurant
that you think will be chosen...
by fewer members.
This is complicated.
I should go to the place
with fewer members...
in order to get more coins, right?
That's right.
I understand so quickly.
That means I'm quick-witted.
You can say I have quick wits.
I'll give you the information
on the restaurants...
and ten coins first.
- Do we start with ten coins?
- Yes.
(He's calling Se Chan.)
I should decide where to go.
- Hello?
- Hey.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
You're going to
the Japanese restaurant, right?
(You're going to
the Japanese restaurant, right?)
(The options only include
Chinese and Korean restaurants.)
- Hello?
- Yes.
- Hey. You...
- Hey, what about the Vietnamese...
- Yes?
- Seriously,
you might jinx me.
You're the first one I called.
Don't be like that.
- Okay.
- Why would you say Japanese?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
What did you eat yesterday?
I barely ate yesterday.
Why?
Did you have nothing to eat?
Did you have no appetite?
(Did you have no appetite?)
- Hey.
- Are you all right, Kwang Soo?
Don't make me feel timid
from the beginning.
Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
(He wants to cheer up
Long Legs for no reason.)
I'll go to the Chinese restaurant.
I'm leaving now.
- I'll go to the Chinese one.
- Let's choose what sounds good.
Okay.
Call Kwang Soo Is Not a Fool.
Calling Kwang Soo Is Not a Fool.
(Calling Kwang Soo Is Not a Fool.)
- Is that how you saved his number?
- Yes, it is.
(He's always serious
about teasing Kwang Soo.)
- Hello?
- Where are you, Kwang Soo?
I'm now...
(Thinking of petty tricks)
I'm somewhere in the middle.
By the way,
I heard you're leaving our show.
(As if he didn't know before)
Why are you saying that
all of a sudden?
We were trying to decide
between Chinese or Korean food.
- Why?
- What are you talking about?
What's wrong?
- Why are you...
- I read the articles.
This isn't about the articles.
- I always have breakfast at home.
- I know.
I'll have to go
to the Chinese restaurant.
(Jae Suk threatens that he'll go
to the Chinese restaurant.)
Please go to the Chinese restaurant.
(Kwang Soo has decided to go
to the Chinese restaurant.)
Hello?
I heard you're leaving Running Man.
This is crazy.
- Are you all right?
- Why are you doing this?
Are you going to have your last meal
at a Korean restaurant or Chinese?
I mean...
You can just ask me that right away.
My gosh.
How do you feel
about leaving our show?
My goodness.
Kwang Soo.
I can't lie to you
when you're being like this.
(I can't lie to you
when you're being like this.)
(Kwang Soo, the guy who's leaving,
still has a grain of conscience.)
Now that you're leaving,
you should work even harder.
Gosh, I'm going
to the Chinese restaurant.
I'm going to the Chinese one.
Why is everyone being like this?
You're supposed to choose
between Korean and Chinese.
You're leaving our show.
Behave yourself.
(Kwang Soo arrives somewhere.)
(The restaurant he chose is...)
(The Chinese restaurant)
No one's here.
- Hey, you punk!
- No one's here.
(That's when he hears the roar.)
Jong Kook, did you really pick
the Chinese restaurant?
Hey, you must be out of your mind.
Jong Kook, no one else is here.
- What do you mean?
- No one else is in there.
Did you have breakfast?
I didn't.
You didn't?
You can't eat Chinese dishes...
on an empty stomach!
(You can't eat Chinese dishes
on an empty stomach!)
You should eat...
Korean food on an empty stomach.
I'll go to
the Korean restaurant then.
Okay. Start the day
with Korean food.
- Gosh, you...
- No one's here.
- I already told you.
- Jong Kook. It's just you and me.
Why would you have Chinese food
on an empty stomach?
You should eat some rice instead.
- I can't believe this.
- I'll have fried rice then.
Fried rice? That's too greasy.
Why are you here?
Let's just go in anyway.
(They go into the Chinese restaurant
with some scolding.)
Look. No one's in here.
Hello.
(However...)
Kwang Soo.
I wanted to eat with you.
Hey, why did you...
- Hello.
- Come here. Stand in line.
Come over here.
- Jong Kook. I'm...
- Kwang Soo and...
- Jong Kook.
- Hang on. Kwang Soo,
now that you're leaving,
you're just doing whatever you want.
You never listen to me.
Gosh, it's not like that.
- Hey.
- Why is everyone...
Aren't you going to see me again?
Gosh, Jong Kook. No.
- It's nothing like that.
- Hang on.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm just having Chinese food.
You know what?
It seems like...
you're trying to look sad
about leaving our show.
- You're growing a mustache.
- No.
That's not why.
- It's not like that.
- Look.
- It's like...
- No.
- You want to look distressed.
- That's not why.
- I know what you're up to.
- Hey.
- This is for a movie.
- You know what I mean.
Is anyone in there? Darn it!
- Darn it!
- I can't believe this.
- Why did you...
- I told you not to come!
I told these two not to come
earlier today.
I told you not to come.
- Why are you growing your mustache?
- No.
This is too contrived.
- My gosh.
- I just had to.
This isn't about my agony
or anything.
You pretend to be in anguish.
It's not like that.
- This is really annoying.
- I said no.
Hey, this isn't a drama.
Get me a razor.
This isn't anything like that.
- My gosh.
- Let's just sit.
I guess it's the four of us.
- I hope so.
- We don't know that.
And the thing is...
- Bo Pil.
- Yes?
Don't let Kwang Soo
pay for his meal.
Why not?
- I'll pay.
- You don't have to pay.
You don't have to.
(They're being generous to Kwang Soo
who's stingy about money.)
Well...
- This is crazy.
- Kwang Soo is...
I'll give all my coins to Kwang Soo.
You can keep all my coins.
- Don't do that.
- Keep the coins.
- Just take them.
- Why are you doing this?
Seriously, just take them.
- Why would you give me the coins?
- Let's give the coins to him.
- Let's give them to him at the end.
- I don't need them.
Why are you being like this?
- I don't need these.
- Don't do that.
Kwang Soo,
these coins mean nothing to me.
- Why are you being like this?
- Just take them.
Jae Suk!
(Giggling)
- You punk.
- Give those to him.
You silly brat.
He just slapped you in the face.
Jae Suk knows
he can't do it anymore.
So he slapped Kwang Soo in the face.
He should.
I'll slap him like 100 times
before he leaves.
- That's your mission for today.
- 100 times?
- That's his mission.
- That's my plan.
- Make sure to do that.
- He slapped him once already.
- Why would you...
- Someone's here.
Darn it!
- My gosh.
- I told you.
(There are 5 members.)
I told you I'd come here.
- Why did you come here? Why?
- I'm not even angry anymore.
- Did you have breakfast?
- Yes.
You must've eaten Korean food.
No, I just ate...
What? Didn't you leave our show?
(Didn't you leave our show?)
It hasn't happened yet.
Not yet?
Why would you say that?
Is this your last day?
You're making me sad.
- When are you leaving?
- I'm not leaving yet.
- I still have some time.
- You do?
Is this it?
- I guess.
- I think this is it.
But this is... Gosh.
All right. It's the five of you.
So you get six coins each.
It's okay. We can take our time.
There are five of us.
In the preliminary mission,
only three members chose
the Korean restaurant...
where you get 80 coins.
(They divide 80 coins among the 3.)
- I can't believe this.
- This is amazing.
This is great.
(The 3 members get 26 coins each.)
Seriously?
- Only three of us?
- This is unbelievable.
I never imagined this.
I thought there would be about six.
Me too.
- How many?
- Six each.
Six each.
- I'll give mine to Kwang Soo.
- Then they got 80 coins.
- Here.
- They got 26 coins each.
- Kwang Soo.
- You take them all.
Don't do this.
We should divide them evenly.
- Just take them.
- Thank you for everything.
Just keep them with you.
No. Take six coins each.
- Just take them.
- Here. Take six coins each.
Jae Suk took his share
in the middle of everything.
(Jae Suk took his share
right away.)
- This is disappointing though.
- You know what?
He will tease you all day.
- I feel disappointed either way.
- Why are you disappointed?
I need one more.
Six coins.
- 3, 4, 5...
- 3, 4...
Six.
- Kwang Soo, did you take one more?
- No.
I only have five.
He's at it again.
(He's at it again.)
Look at him.
- He's smiling.
- My gosh.
- His face shows everything.
- He's smiling.
- His eyes are smiling.
- I'm sorry I suspected you.
He couldn't hold back his laughter.
I thought it was you.
(They all got 6 coins each.)
Gosh, the coins don't matter.
All my favorite people are here.
Right.
All right. Let's do this.
(He's trying to create
a touching moment.)
- Go ahead and cry.
- What?
Just cry.
Why would I cry?
Shed some tears.
Get him some soju.
It'll look good with his mustache.
- Hey.
- Kaoliang liquor would work.
- Why would I drink kaoliang liquor?
- Drink some strong liquor.
No, it's okay.
All right. Let's watch
some of his best performances.
- Hey!
- Let's watch.
What are you looking at?
It's playing here.
- There aren't any.
- There aren't any?
Why would you say that?
(Watching Kwang Soo's performances
ends in a second.)
There aren't any.
All right.
Now, I will tell you the rules...
of the Read the Room Race.
I told you
the coins are very important today.
Anytime throughout the race,
once you collect 50 R coins,
you can go home right away.
(The members who collect
50 R coins go home right away.)
(As soon as they get 50 coins,
they get to leave immediately.)
Right away?
And the rest of the members
must continue with the race.
That's the rule for today.
Those who fail to collect 50 coins
can't go home.
Just in case,
we had all the missions
and venues ready...
so we could continue the shoot
until midnight.
You can get the coins
during each mission,
but you can also get extra coins...
according to the results
of how you act in Games of Wits.
Is that so?
For your information,
the actions you must carry out...
in the Games of Wits
are decided by specific conditions.
It's not like the crew members
decide them randomly.
You'll try to figure out
what the specific conditions are.
Now, you will order your breakfast.
I'll ask the waitress to come in.
How many coins do they have?
They got 26 coins.
They would go home soon.
So there are specific conditions.
It might be offering food to others.
- It might be something like that.
- I think so.
(They earn or lose coins
according to the specific actions.)
- We'd like to order.
- Right, we have to order.
- Hello.
Would you like to order?
- Thank you.
- They have 36 coins in total.
- Right.
- This is...
They have this famous dish.
There's jjajangmyeon...
- with cuttlefish.
- Is there something like that?
Jjajangmyeon with cuttlefish.
- Cuttlefish sounds good.
- I like that.
I think the waitress has something.
Can I order soybean noodle soup?
No. It's available only in summer.
- It's the seasonal menu.
- Right.
Ma'am, I heard this restaurant
is really famous.
I've wanted to come.
Ma'am.
For the main dish,
we have jjamppong or fried rice.
Hang on. What should I eat?
I think the jjajangmyeon with cuttle
sounds good.
- What?
- These are famous.
- Is this famous?
- Do they have this?
It's a non-recommended menu.
I'll have the abalone rice porridge.
- It's not recommended.
- I want something spicy.
- Is the porridge not recommended?
- No.
How bad is it?
That's not what we usually offer.
Really?
- There's something.
- Non-recommended?
- I'll also have the porridge.
- This is a Game of Wits.
- This is it.
- The non-recommended menu?
Can I order a double helping
of abalone rice porridge?
I'll have five servings
of abalone rice porridge.
Gosh, this is...
I think I should order
something on the menu.
The non-recommended one.
- This is a Game of Wits.
- I know.
But we all can't order it.
Kwang Soo, you should try it alone.
- That's a good idea.
- We will eat something else.
She says it's a good idea.
- Ma'am.
- Kwang Soo.
Why are you being like this?
I'm fine.
She says you should try it.
Just listen to her.
She's looking out for you.
Kwang Soo, what about this?
- What?
- The other dishes taste better.
Gosh, why are you slapping me?
- What was that? Why is he...
- All right, that's two points.
- Why...
- Two points.
He's quick-witted.
That's two points.
He's got two points.
I'll have
the jjajangmyeon with cuttlefish.
- I already had breakfast,
- Thank you.
so I will have...
the jjamppong with seafood.
I'll have rice with japchae.
So only one of you will have
the abalone rice porridge?
- I think it's a good thing.
- Hang on. Abalone rice porridge?
I bet abalone rice porridge
would taste good.
- It's not recommended.
- Is it a bad thing?
I bet we will get coins.
It's not recommended.
I'll have rice
with spinach and pork.
Hang on.
Should I order the porridge?
- Kwang Soo.
- With fried eggs?
You should order
the abalone rice porridge.
- I'll have the porridge.
- Abalone rice porridge?
Yes.
I'll have the dishes ready for you.
Do you offer any tea?
We have jasmine tea.
Please get him some quitting tea.
Jong Kook!
- Hey.
- I want jasmine tea.
That's enough.
- This is crazy.
- What's wrong?
All right.
Are you the only one
who ordered abalone rice porridge?
I bet you will
have to turn in 10 coins.
I think so.
It's ridiculous that they have
a non-recommended menu.
But the thing is,
only they know the conditions.
They might take and give back
the coins as they want.
They will tell us
the conditions later.
- They will?
- Yes, why we get or lose coins.
How do you know that?
I guess he's the protagonist today.
Did you shoot something
before we started?
No, that's what we just heard.
That's what you did when you said
you had something to shoot.
You had another shoot.
- And you grew a mustache.
- It has nothing to do with this.
It's not like that.
Jong Kook. Is this perhaps...
Do you think
we will get five coins...
- if we shave his mustache?
- What are you talking about?
You...
When he says things like that,
he always talks to Jong Kook.
There must be something. I'm sure.
My goodness.
(Staring)
What?
- Did you figure something out?
- Do you have any idea?
- I don't know.
- Why are you crying?
What would you do
after going home early?
Are you sad? Haha is crying.
It's because he keeps staring at me.
Stop it. Don't cry, Haha.
It's just the beginning
of today's show.
- Hey.
- That's not it.
- Don't cry.
- He knows what's going on.
No, that's not why he's doing this.
Did you get any sleep?
(Did you get any sleep?)
He's wrinkling his nose.
That's so annoying.
(He's putting on a contrived frown
to create a touching moment.)
Which one would you like to use?
- Thank you.
- What?
- What is this?
- It's a Game of Wits.
We don't usually use forks.
- I'll use a fork.
- I'll use a fork as well.
I'm sure this is a Game of Wits.
- They have five forks.
- Why else would there be forks?
It's a Game of Wits.
We should have quick wits.
- Look.
- I'll use chopsticks.
(Jae Suk and Haha
choose chopsticks.)
We're done making our choices.
Hang on.
Is this about the forks?
- Right.
- Exactly.
Maybe we'll share some coins again.
- Everyone.
- I guess I'm right.
Which of you chose a fork?
- Me.
- I did.
The 3 of you have to give us
5 coins.
Okay!
(You'll lose 5 coins.)
(Those who choose a fork lose
5 coins.)
I hate you!
I wasn't going to choose a fork.
(Kwang Soo chose it
as Jae Suk recommended.)
He put this fork in my hand.
Give five coins to Hyeong Gu.
We do have reasons
for making the rules.
Is that so?
(The staff members are checking
their moves according to the rules.)
- I was so tactless.
- Okay!
People use chopsticks
at a Chinese restaurant.
Of course.
Then I guess the underlined items
didn't mean anything.
Kwang Soo, you gave me four coins.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Oh, okay.
- It wasn't intentional.
- He's playing dirty to the end.
Why would you play dirty to the end?
- That's so pathetic.
- I just wasn't sure.
That's enough, you punk.
I mean, there will be no one
to tease like this.
What is wrong with him?
Stop wrinkling your nose, Haha.
- Stop it already.
- He keeps wrinkling his nose.
- We'll see him for two more weeks.
- We'll have more chances.
- Let's make the most of the time.
- Let's make acrostic poems.
- With what word?
- With "stepping down."
Say the initials.
- S.
- Select one person to cast.
- D.
- Definitely Cha Eun Woo.
What kind of acrostic poem is that?
- I'll do it.
- S.
- Select one more person to cast.
- Who would that be?
- D.
- Definitely Cha Tae Hyun.
S. Select one more person.
- D.
- Definitely Cha In Pyo.
- Please join our show!
- That's funny.
(They're discussing
the new member already.)
- Hit me.
- S.
- Shut it!
- D.
Dudes!
- Nice. It lightened up the mood.
- Yes, it did.
- The acrostic poems made us laugh.
- Oh, gosh. Kwang Soo...
We'll give five coins
to those who chose chopsticks.
You'll give five coins to them?
- Really?
- This is awesome.
I wonder how they made the rules.
We could go home quite early
if we keep this up.
- The other team earned more coins.
- There's a big difference.
We do have reasons
for making these rules.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I suppose you'll reveal
the reasons later on.
It'd be weird
if Kwang Soo leaves early today.
- Indeed.
- Yes.
We should help him stay
as long as he can.
I think they already set up
the rules.
- Of course.
- Then let's do this.
Since many people are sad
that you're leaving this show,
you stay.
We'll leave the show instead.
Gosh. Stop it!
(You stay.
We'll leave the show instead.)
What would I do all by myself?
Don't be ridiculous.
- Jae Suk.
- What is he talking about?
Do you mean Kwang Soo should be
on the show alone?
That's ridiculous.
I go solo on a Saturday show,
so you do it on a Sunday show.
- Come on. Don't be ridiculous.
- Right.
- That's so funny.
- Call it "Step Down with Lee."
- That's a good idea.
- "Step Down with Lee"?
- I like the title.
- That's a great idea.
After two weeks of being teased,
Kwang Soo might say,
"Fine. I'll stay!"
"I'll stay."
"You win."
(They're saying goodbye to him
in their own style.)
Someone at the other place might
go home now.
- No, not yet.
- Not so fast.
If he or she earned coins
twice in a row.
- They wouldn't let it happen.
- That's right.
I think that's possible.
No, never.
The two of you seem so close
these days.
- You're not making any sense.
- Of course, we're close.
I'm close with Trainer Kook.
Suk Jin would refuse to leave
even if he can go home.
I think so too.
- It's So Min.
- What?
(Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, and So Min were
doing the same mission.)
Hi, So Min.
Haha, Suk Jin will go home
very soon.
Suk Jin will go home soon?
- We were just talking about it.
- Really?
- Tell him to go home.
Suk Jin, why do you look so sad
when you can go home early?
Suk Jin, that means
the staff threw you away.
Hey, I have 48 coins right now.
- He needs only two coins.
- Really?
(Big Nose is only 2 coins short.)
(This is how he became rich.)
The total number is three.
(He chose the Korean cuisine
and earned 26 coins.)
(Suk Jin continued
collecting a lot of coins.)
I choose chopsticks.
See?
- You'll give me?
- Yes. Those who chose chopsticks...
- See? I was right.
- will receive five coins.
But why?
Why would you give this to me?
Hey, why are you trying
to send me home?
That's not true.
- Why are you trying to let me go?
- That's not true.
Rock-paper-scissors
I lost.
(He defeated
both Ji Hyo and So Min.)
Let's play it just one more time.
- No.
- Please. Just one more time.
- I'll be going home soon.
- How many coins do you have now?
Me?
I have 48 coins now.
He'll probably leave while eating.
- Suk Jin will...
- I don't think I'll see you guys.
- He'll go home soon.
- I'll probably go home from here.
By the way, I realized...
- that they'll get more airtime.
- I know, right?
Ji Hyo, I noticed something
while talking on the phone.
Suk Jin seemed disappointed
when he saw them, right?
- He wanted to be with Kwang Soo.
- I wish I was with them.
They'll get a lot of airtime.
You want to join them, right?
- Yes.
- They'll get more airtime than us.
- Short rib soup is here.
- Here's your food.
- That's for Suk Jin.
- Short rib soup with Korean beef.
(Meanwhile, the food
that Suk Jin ordered came!)
It looks delicious.
- Thank you for the food.
You should always say thanks
before eating.
(Whistle blowing)
- That startled me.
- Suk Jin, turn in your coins.
- Is he leaving now?
- What?
(Turn in his coins?)
Is he going home now?
(Why?)
Congratulations, Suk Jin.
You have collected 50 coins
that you need to leave for the day.
The car is ready.
- You can go home right now.
- Really?
Really? Really?
- But why?
- Why? Why?
- How did he earn two more coins?
- Why should I leave?
Kwang Soo just sent two coins
to him.
So he can leave for the day now.
Wait. Are you serious?
Should I leave now?
Are you serious?
- Go home, Suk Jin.
- Bye.
We're not allowed to give our coins
to someone else, right?
Of course, you can do that.
Then let's give Suk Jin two coins,
so he can go home.
Let's do that. That's a good idea.
Let's just send him two coins.
I'll give him mine
since I have the most.
- Right. Give him two coins.
- Yes, give him yours.
- It'll be so funny.
- Think of it as the last gift.
(Kwang Soo volunteered to give
Suk Jin a perfect gift.)
- Suk Jin sounded...
- Two coins.
- worried about going home early.
- He sounded anxious.
Suk Jin, I haven't done anything
for you until now.
It's not much,
but I'm giving you two coins.
This is a token of my gratitude
and respect toward you.
Suk Jin, thank you for everything.
I love you.
You can go home now.
Hold on. Do I really have to leave?
Are you serious?
- You're joking, right?
- No.
You can actually leave for the day.
(Suk Jin is about to cry again.)
I'm actually going home now?
Kwang Soo, that punk.
But am I really going home?
I'm just taken aback. I mean...
We started the shoot
a little after 10 a.m.
What's going on?
And I'm going home already?
Yes. We'll also film you leaving
as well.
Will you guys be okay?
- Will you be okay?
- Of course, we'll be fine.
You'll need me to make things work.
- You did a great job today.
- See you later.
- I'm glad you talked to the others.
- But I haven't finished the food.
- It's okay. You can go. It's over.
- Should I just leave?
He looks sad and disappointed.
I'm a little sad indeed.
You see, I like...
- shooting this show with you guys.
- Go on.
- Bye.
- Then don't call me, okay?
- Okay.
- I won't pick up.
I'm off.
- Bye, Suk Jin.
- Bye. See you later.
I'm leaving. I'm actually leaving.
- You did great today.
- Don't regret it later.
- He's actually leaving.
- What's going on? This is weird.
(He's walking slowly
hoping that someone will stop him.)
I can't believe I'm going home
so early.
I didn't intend to leave this early,
but it happened that way.
I'm off.
I can't believe this.
I'm actually leaving.
(It's the 1st time in 11 years,
so it's hard to believe.)
It doesn't make sense.
Can I really go?
(A staff member will drive him home
as his manager is not here.)
You left unexpectedly early.
- I'm not actually leaving, right?
- Yes, you are leaving.
- Really?
- Yes, you can get some rest today.
(1 of the cast members left
only in 1 hour.)
- It's here.
- The food is here.
(Meanwhile,
at the Chinese restaurant...)
It looks good.
(Both stir-fried noodles
and jjamppong with seafood came.)
- Tangsuyuk.
- It looks so delicious.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
Kwang Soo who ordered
the non-recommended menu...
(Kwang Soo who ordered
the non-recommended menu...)
- What's a non-recommended menu?
- Look here.
(Was it a good choice?)
You should give us five coins.
I knew it.
- Of course.
- That's Kwang Soo.
Of course.
Kwang Soo, you're back
to your old self.
But he didn't lose that many.
- You had 15 coins before.
- Guys, try some of mine.
Okay.
(He's turning in 5 coins
just as he was told to.)
This is a healthy meal.
(Looking around nervously)
(Se Chan is looking around
nervously too.)
Why are you looking at us like that?
- Pardon?
- Why are you looking at us?
I was just wondering
if there would be something else.
(They can't let their guard down.)
I gave up on leaving early.
I'd rather spend
one more hour with Kwang Soo.
Let's have a toast.
I'll say the toast.
(The toast for only 1 person)
To my endless success!
(He's celebrating his own future.)
Cheers!
- Cheers!
(He was too excited about teasing
Kwang Soo to pronounce properly.)
He won't stop making jokes.
All the pranksters on the show
gathered here.
(They're so cheeky.)
I think Jae Suk is determined
to joke around with you.
He wants to do it
as many times as he can...
because he won't get to do it again.
He'll make 500 jokes at least.
I think I'll lose some weight.
- What? Hey.
- What?
- What brings you here?
They told me to actually leave.
(The man in a colorful shirt
who left for the day appeared.)
- I thought it was a joke.
- Why are you here?
- Go home now.
- I just wanted to say hi to you.
- I didn't expect...
- Why did you come here?
I'm so confused.
Let's meet up later.
I asked them many times,
but I was told to leave.
- You didn't even get to eat?
- They told me to go home.
Why did you give me two coins?
I haven't given you anything
until now.
- Hey.
- Say the chant with him at least.
- "Feeling! Intuition! Cross!"
- What?
Why would we do that?
- Do it so we can send him home.
- Let's do it.
- Let's say the chant together.
- I don't think I can watch it.
- Let's do it.
- Come on.
- Kwang Soo.
- What is this?
- Stop it. I said, stop it.
- Come on.
- Why should I do that?
- Just do it.
Honestly, when Se Chan suggested it,
I got a little emotional.
- Come on. Do it for him.
- Gosh.
Suk Jin is going home now.
- Do it for him just this once.
- Why would we say the chant?
Let's do it once in every episode
until you leave the show.
- Starting today.
- He said he'd slap me every week.
Why would you add this?
- Just once in every episode.
- Do it for him...
just for the next two weeks.
(Since the beginning
of Running Man,)
(the weakest duo has been together
with their feelings and intuition.)
(Lee Ji Brothers formed
the Feeling Intuition Alliance.)
(They must've shouted the chant
so many times in the past 11 years.)
How many times do we have left?
Three times, right?
We can say this three more times.
Let's do it right here today.
Feeling!
- Intuition! Cross!
- Cross!
This will be remembered
for a long time. Haha.
(Touched)
Don't wrinkle your nose.
- Don't cry, Haha.
- Stop faking it.
Stop wrinkling your nose.
Jae Suk, I'll get going now.
Jong Kook.
- I'm off now.
- See you later.
- I'm really leaving this time.
- Bye.
- Bye, Suk Jin.
Go home and practice singing.
Okay. I'll do that.
Why would you bring that up here?
(After Suk Jin left...)
I'm planning a new show.
- I'm not sure when I can start.
- I see.
I haven't told anyone about this
until now.
The show is about people I like...
Well... There's a lot of people
I'm grateful to, you know.
Including Cho Sae Ho
and all of you here.
In the first episode,
I'll be with Suk Jin,
Kwang Soo, and Sae Ho.
We'll go to a remote area,
and they'll prepare all three meals
for the day for me.
We'll cook for you?
Why should we cook for you?
That's what this show is about.
You three prepare breakfast, lunch,
and dinner for me.
Why should we do that?
- That sounds so interesting.
- Yes.
We'll all wear hanbok.
I'll dress as a nobleman.
- And the other three...
- Why would you dress as a nobleman?
Will the other three be your slaves?
Will you eat with them or alone?
- I'll eat alone.
- Oh, I see.
They'll cook for you and then leave?
There will be a small table
for the three of them.
Why would he not eat with us?
- I don't get it.
- Of course, he'll eat alone.
- He won't eat with the others.
- Why?
- It's "Three Meals for Jae Suk."
- I see.
That sounds interesting.
(Could Jae Suk's dream come true?)
Do you need anything else?
- Can we get small plates, please?
- Of course.
Kwang Soo just came out
to get plates.
Did he?
He came out to get plates.
(The waitress suddenly dropped
a pouch.)
(What?)
You dropped this.
- Can we get scissors as well?
- You dropped this.
(A pouch full of coins?)
(Looking at the staff nervously)
(Surprised)
Can I have this?
Hey, wait.
(Have it.)
- I saw... Yes.
- She dropped this?
Am I supposed to give it back
to her?
- How many coins are there?
- Well...
- Let me see.
- Why is it so complicated?
- Is it a test?
- Maybe.
(Whether he'll have it or not
is his choice.)
I'll give it back to her.
- Oh, he'll give it back.
- I'll give it back to her.
The waitress dropped this
in our room.
I want to give it back to her.
Se Chan who found the coins
that the waitress dropped...
and gave the coins back to her...
(Se Chan who gave the coins back
to the owner...)
It's all yours.
(It's all yours.)
(Se Chan gets all the coins.)
- Are you serious?
- Can you go home now?
- No, I don't have enough coins.
- How many do you have?
How many coins are in here?
- 20...
- Count them by yourself.
(5 coins were deducted for choosing
the non-recommended menu.)
(5 coins were deducted for a fork.
5 coins were added for chopsticks.)
I'm so taken aback.
This is...
To be honest, whenever we heard...
that we could go home early,
we lost some points intentionally
not to go home early.
We should stop doing that.
We should always wrap up
and go home on time.
That'd be the true variety show.
Wouldn't you agree?
I'm going home.
I'm really going home.
Okay.
You did great today.
I'll see you next week.
I still can't believe this.
Get some rest.
- It's a shame. I love your shirt.
- I know, right? It's a nice shirt.
- Bye.
- See you later.
(Suk Jin arrived home.)
(So the 1st one to leave went home.)
Let's move to the next location.
- Hey, Se Chan, Se Chan.
- Yes, yes.
Where are we going?
- We're going for the next mission.
- Okay.
Before that,
we need to settle things.
- What?
- What is it?
- What's there to settle?
- Wasn't it all settled?
Kwang Soo and Haha get 10 coins.
- What?
- Why?
- Is it the order of leaving?
Is it?
And Kwang Soo gets 10 more coins.
- Why?
- What's going on?
Kwang Soo, you should give me
two coins.
Kwang Soo, can you go home now?
You don't have enough yet, right?
- I got 10 more coins.
- What's going on?
- Why did I get the coins?
- Why...
It's a result of your behaviors
when you left the restaurant...
and got in the vehicle.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
(Those who said they'll come back
earned 10 coins.)
- Goodbye. I'll come again.
- Thank you. Goodbye.
- Thank you.
- Please come again.
- I'll come again.
- Look.
- I promise.
- They're still filming us.
- They're filming us.
- Right.
Is it? I'll lift it up for you.
(And the mission
that only Kwang Soo succeeded in...)
Hello.
(Hello.)
(The one who said hello
to the driver got 10 coins.)
Oh, I think I didn't say hello
to the driver.
I think... Hold on a second.
I think...
that someone predicted in advance...
- That's right.
- how we would behave.
I don't think so.
(Kwang Soo got much closer
to 50 coins in an instant.)
- By the way,
- There are things we should say.
- when we didn't get to go home,
- Is that the case?
we got excited to receive coins.
- It's a little baffling.
- But now...
- We don't get excited about it.
- It makes us feel uncomfortable.
- "What did I do wrong?"
- Exactly.
Haha just said quietly,
"Gosh, I got more coins."
I regret greeting the driver.
- You see,
- I collected almost all the coins.
I haven't gotten any coins so far.
So I feel so calm.
- Jong Kook must feel relaxed.
- I won't do anything from now on.
- Because I didn't get any coins...
- What did I do...
It feels like getting coins is
a penalty.
I wonder where we're going.
Me too.
(They're going to a mysterious place
for the next mission.)
The weather is so nice.
Wait. Kwang Soo.
What did you just say?
(Wait. Kwang Soo.
What did you just say?)
I said I was...
(Murmuring)
Didn't you say
that the weather was nice?
- He said that.
- Yes, he did.
(Didn't you say
that the weather was nice?)
Kwang Soo, you got five coins.
- What?
- What was that?
- Kwang Soo might go home soon.
- Don't lie to me.
- If you say...
- Bo Pil.
Are you trying to send
Kwang Soo home?
No, I'm not. It's written here.
- Oh, no.
- Really?
He said the exact words.
Hey, are you not joking?
Hey, I think you have 50 coins now.
How many coins do you have now?
I think I have 50 coins now.
- It's weird.
- I'll count the coins for you.
I think he collected all 50 coins.
Go home, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo must have 50 coins.
- Kwang Soo always liked coins.
- But today...
- I didn't expect this. Gosh.
You don't like coins today, do you?
What? Hey, you're done.
Do you have one more coin
than I do? No, I have more.
It's right here.
Kwang Soo.
- He's going home.
- You can go home now.
Oh, my goodness.
You're sending me home
because I talked about the weather?
Please pull over here.
Here?
Hey! How can you...
At least let me go
to our destination!
My gosh. Poor Kwang Soo.
How can you drop me off here?
- Hey. Then...
- Hannam Bridge is near here.
Guys, try to stop him.
(He'll end up on the street
about 2 hours after he left home.)
At least let me go
to our destination!
My gosh. Poor Kwang Soo.
(He'll go home alone
carrying the mission bag.)
Guys, try to stop him.
- What could we do about it?
- It's not far from your house.
Is he actually leaving?
- Kwang Soo, see you later.
- Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
How can I go home
if you drop me off here?
- Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
- We'll give you a ride.
- Congratulations.
- You should get out to the right.
- I don't even have my wallet!
I know, Kwang Soo. See you later.
Hey, you can use those coins.
- Kwang Soo.
- You mean these R coins?
- Kwang Soo, get out of the car now.
- Go home.
- Bye.
- Get out of the car.
(Hyeong Gu and a cameraman are
running to help Kwang Soo leave.)
- This is driving me nuts.
- Go to Suk Jin's house.
- He's actually leaving.
- Call us later.
- But...
- Just get out of the car.
- Go home.
- Okay.
- I'll get going.
- Bye. Get going now.
- Bye.
- I'm off.
- See you.
- I'll call you later.
- Okay. Bye.
- Am I actually leaving?
- Yes, you are. Go.
- What is going on?
- Go on.
I don't believe this.
(He's going home in broad daylight.)
You can go home.
- What is going on?
- Go on.
- It's so weird.
- What is this?
What are you going to do
if we don't get enough airtime?
- Someone is controlling this.
- Could this be...
some kind of practice?
(Could this be
some kind of practice?)
- Saying goodbye to Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
- They want to see if we can...
- Before he leaves the show.
- do well without him.
- Right.
We should do well.
(As Kwang Soo leaves early,
they think of it as a rehearsal.)
- Can I really go?
- Yes.
(The car where the casts are in
is leaving.)
(Kwang Soo is left alone.)
I mean, is this...
(He's leaving with staff members
just as Suk Jin did.)
- Is this it?
- Yes, this is it.
You can go home now.
(He's leaving with staff members
just as Suk Jin did.)
Let me stay a little longer.
What is this? Are you serious?
It feels weird.
(He's never left for the day
in 2 hours in the past 11 years.)
- Hello?
- Suk Jin.
- Hi.
- I'm going home.
What is this?
(Laughing)
Suk Jin, I didn't even get to see
Ji Hyo and So Min.
Exactly.
But it doesn't feel so good.
- I know. It's disappointing, right?
- I mean...
Besides...
You will leave the show soon.
I can't believe...
They can't do this.
This is driving me nuts.
Oh, Suk Jin is actually at home.
I'm at home.
Are you really going home?
Suk Jin, I'm feeling so weird.
I shouldn't have chanted
"Feeling! Intuition! Cross!"
I got a little emotional
when we chanted together.
Me too. I got emotional too.
- Right?
- I genuinely felt sad.
I genuinely felt sad too.
I didn't expect that.
It's okay. We'll get to chant
two more times.
That's right.
(It's okay. We'll get to chant
2 more times.)
- See you later.
- See you. I'll call you again.
Okay.
Can you make a little detour?
(Can you make a little detour?)
This isn't right.
- Can't I be around the set?
- No.
Let me just watch.
I don't mind if I won't be filmed.
- Can't I just watch?
- No. You should go home.
Thank you.
(At 12:10 p.m., he finally got home
after a meaningless detour.)
Did I do something wrong?
(Did I do something wrong?)
Go on in. Why aren't you going in?
Go home.
(At 12:11 p.m., the 2nd member to leave
arrived home.)
Okay. Goodbye.
(Bowing)
(The staff members are going back
to the filming set afterward.)
Why are you sitting there
instead of going home?
- Are you serious?
- Yes. We should go now.
(His body refuses to go home.)
We can leave now, sir.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
Go home now. We're not joking.
(The staff members left him
on the street.)
We've arrived at the location.
- Yes!
- Great.
- What is that?
- What is it?
We should try, you punk.
The Read the Room Race.
The first Read the Room Race.
Could the race have an architect?
Of course.
Maybe someone made the rules.
Ji Hyo's here.
- Hello.
- Ginger hair Ji Hyo.
Suk Jin went home.
- He was given two on our end.
- Thanks.
Kwang Soo also went home.
Kwang Soo went home.
- In the van.
- Did you pick up the pouch?
This is where the first
Read the Room Race will be hosted.
Surprisingly enough,
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
already went home...
- after collecting 50 coins.
- Exactly.
- I'm jealous.
- That was fast.
- I envy them.
- Lucky them.
Here's your first mission
of the day.
You must pop the balloons
with all your might...
in this game of Pop the Balloon.
You'll pop the 20 balloons
with your fist in the given time...
and win coins afterward.
- Really?
- The order you play is up to you.
With our fist?
- Balloons...
- This I can't do.
Maybe the colors mean something.
- We need to read the game.
- Just a second.
They're all the same size.
Do you need any help?
Maybe it's this.
No?
Are you trying to receive coins?
I just want to know
how you can get more.
How do you get more coins?
- It's random.
- Let me help.
Gosh, let me help.
I'll take that. Let me.
(Is this not it either?)
Why are the water bottles
only half full?
(Detective Kook notices the bottles
that are only half full.)
- There's no need for that.
- And this game...
- Why can't they be full?
- Don't you think...
that this game lacks finesse?
- It's odd.
- Hold on.
- I find this weird.
- Me too.
Something's odd about this game.
A lot about this game feels odd.
Maybe it was Suk Jin
and Kwang Soo...
who designed this game?
If you think about it...
Let me see. I'll check it out.
Things felt odd
the moment I stepped inside.
The moment I stepped inside.
(Jong Kook heads toward the staff
where the water bottles are.)
What's going on?
- It's weird.
- This is odd.
- This feels odd.
- Just odd.
(Out of the bottles
in front of the staff,)
(only one has a red sticker
on the cap.)
- These...
- But...
It won't pop.
(Jong Kook heads back
with questions looming in his head.)
- It won't pop.
- Let us begin.
Should we be filling up the bottles?
Wait, check this out.
This game must have
its own set of rules.
- I think so.
- Right.
Kwang Soo earned five coins...
just by mentioning the nice weather.
Let's try Kwang Soo.
- The nice weather?
- Call Kwang Soo.
Hold on. What could this be?
(Hold on. What's going on?)
(Is there something in the bottle?)
Kwang Soo earned five coins...
just by mentioning the nice weather.
(The bottle with the red sticker
on the cap.)
Hold on. What could this be?
(Just then, the whistle blows.)
What's going on?
(The sudden whistle...)
(Jong Kook freezes
with the bottle in his hand.)
- What's going on?
- Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook...)
Jong Kook declared
the end of the race.
(The end of the race?)
- What?
- The first...
- Read the Room Race is now over.
- What?
What are you talking about?
(The first Read the Room Race
is over.)
(It ended just because
Jong Kook picked up a water bottle.)
What are you talking about?
Out of all the water bottles,
only one of them
had a red sticker on the cap.
(Only one of the bottles
had a red sticker on the cap.)
(Picking up that bottle...)
It would declare
the end of the race.
What?
Thanks to Jong Kook figuring it out,
the first Read the Room Race
has come to an end.
(Jong Kook picked up the bottle
which ended the race.)
- What?
- The episode ended?
- Do we go home then?
I only reacted
when I saw the red sticker.
The first Read the Room Race
is over.
And now, the quick-witted
will get to earn more coins...
in the second Read the Room Race.
(The 2nd Read the Room Race)
(The 1st race is over,
and now the 2nd race begins.)
Are you kidding me?
Are you all right up there?
- Look.
- Seriously?
- What's going on?
- What is this?
- What is all this?
- What are you playing at?
I mean... Hold on.
(A new banner is hung
to celebrate the 2nd race.)
(Flapping)
We're moving to
a specific rule today.
(The race has been designed
to follow a specific rule.)
What is all this?
The second race has begun.
You've got to be kidding me.
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
are running late,
so we'll begin the race
when they get here.
They have to come back!
(They couldn't fully comprehend
what was going on.)
(A revelation)
I see.
Please call them over.
- Is this the second race?
- They must come back.
The 1st race is over,
and now it's the 2nd race.
Is this the second race?
Call them over here.
- I'll call them.
- The first race is over.
I didn't quite get it.
Why are they running so late?
- Do a video call.
- Sure.
- Here.
- The two are resting at home,
- but they must...
- Suk Jin!
Change this to a video call.
- A video call?
- I thought...
that we should only be popping
the red balloons.
Suk Jin,
you have to come back here.
- You're lying.
- We're not.
The 1st race ended,
and now we must begin the 2nd race.
- The second race!
- This isn't a joke.
Take a look yourself.
We've been waiting around for you.
This isn't a joke?
A second race?
He already changed into home wear.
He changed already.
The second race has begun,
and you must get here.
This is no joke.
You must be deadly serious.
(Calling Suk Jin back
finally makes it real.)
You... You do know...
that you're not right
in the head, right?
- Are you kidding me?
- Hurry over here.
Suk Jin, are you crazy?
Why are you still home
when it's the day of filming?
Suk Jin, hurry.
We're all waiting for you here.
Hurry over here!
Is this for real?
Hurry back here!
I knew something like this
would happen!
Are you kidding me?
Hurry on over.
This is the second race.
(Suk Jin gets angry
when he's the one running late.)
My wife and I were about
to go to a food court.
A food court?
Now's not the time for that.
Bring your wife with you.
Text me the address.
My manager's in Songpa-gu.
(Text me the address.
My manager's in Songpa-gu.)
- What?
- Hyung In is downstairs.
Hyung In is downstairs,
so hurry on down.
Is this for real?
- Yes, Hyung In is downstairs.
- It's for real.
Are you kidding me?
Hurry on over.
Get here in 30 minutes.
(Se Chan calls Kwang Soo
who's also late to the set.)
- Check out Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- What are you up to?
- What are you doing?
Filming will begin once again.
Get over here!
- What do you think you're doing?
- That was the first face.
- The second race.
- The second race has begun.
- The filming for it has begun.
- Hurry over here.
- Where do I go?
- The first race is over.
Just get over here.
(He is being told to hurry
to an unknown location.)
What are you doing
on the day of filming?
Honestly, you should shave.
It's a weird look on you.
You look like Woong's Father.
- Why is the camera at an odd angle?
- Hurry over!
You're drunk, aren't you?
Hey!
Are you kidding me?
The rest of the members await you.
- What?
- You shouldn't be late to work.
You've got to be kidding me.
I was told to relax for the day,
and I almost took a shower.
You must've been waiting for me
ever since you dropped me off.
You guys are unbelievable.
My wife and I were about
to go out for lunch.
(Suk Jin gets in the van
instead of going to the food court.)
(Kwang Soo heads to work too.)
Hello.
(He's leaving the house
an hour after coming home.)
Shouldn't you be at work today?
(He gets himself a weapon.)
The others are all gathered.
(The others are all gathered.)
The first Read the Room Race
has ended,
and the second Read the Room Race
has begun.
(An angry slap)
What the...
(Mr. Lee, are you heading to work?)
Yes, but this isn't
my first time today.
- Was this planned?
- No.
She's asking for real?
It's my second time
going to work today.
Bye.
Goodness.
All right.
In the second Read the Room Race,
you will also play games
to win coins.
Win 70,
and you'll head home for the day.
- 70 coins?
- 70.
They're trying to keep us here.
Do we start with the coins we have?
I don't want to go
since we'll have to come back.
Right. It's better to stay here.
- It's better to stay here.
- Exactly.
- There could be a third race.
- I'm guessing...
Is there an end
to this series of races?
You have
an ending planned out, right?
A certain move will unlock that.
How many races do you have planned?
I can't tell you that.
Why not? How long will this go on?
For the second race,
you'll change into...
the team uniforms from our sponsor.
- He must be crazy.
- This is reckless.
- He...
- What is he doing?
We have team uniforms?
Please go and change.
Chan Hee, I'll get going then.
What was that?
Good job, everyone.
- Good job, guys.
- You're the best.
We'll be right back.
- Good job on the first race.
- Thank you.
- We'll be right back.
- Should we clean this up?
(Those who were on time
go to change into team uniforms.)
This is where
you'll keep your coins.
Am I out of coins?
You used them all earlier...
to excuse yourself
from the first race.
Seriously?
I want to comment on that,
but all I can think of
are profanities.
I knew something was up
which is why I kept asking,
but you said it was for real.
How can one think
that there will be a new race?
Suk Jin's here!
He's here!
- He's in his own clothes.
- He's wearing his own clothes.
Isn't he the worst dresser?
- Is he a carrot?
- A carrot?
Turn him upside down.
- You're right.
- An orange.
You should've known better
than to have gone home.
Why did you go home?
You have no idea
how many times I asked.
I asked numerous times,
but I was told it was okay.
Did you cancel your reservation
at the food court?
Who makes reservations
at a food court?
- You just go to one.
- Is that so?
My wife was changing when...
(He was summoned back to work
without eating a proper meal.)
Do you know
what was more surprising?
My cameraman must not have known...
because he was beaming...
when I told him to have a good day.
- Because he was heading home?
- He was like this.
Later on, I asked...
if he didn't know.
(Nodding)
How can you fool my cameraman too?
We had to keep it confidential.
Kwang Soo's here.
Kwang Soo, you can't lose
your focus on set like this.
- What?
- Where was your focus?
- It's not over until it's over.
- How can you be this dense?
How can you be this dense?
What's happening?
- I actually talked to him...
- What's going on?
on the phone earlier. I said,
"Kwang Soo,
you'll be quitting the show soon,"
"so I don't think this is right."
When I told him that,
he said,
"I know. I was a little upset."
They won't just let you go
like that.
This is the second race.
- I need to get changed again.
- Go and put on our uniform.
- I'll give you the first mission.
- What is it?
It's called Foot Volleyball of Wits.
- Foot Volleyball of Wits?
- We're playing foot volleyball?
We'll let you choose
one or the other...
based on your preference.
Those who choose the same option
will be on the same team.
Then you'll play a game
of foot volleyball for five points.
Each player will earn points
through the game.
You'll then change the team.
(They'll play another game
of foot volleyball...)
(after changing the team.)
If someone reaches 15 points,
then the mission will be over.
Coins will be given to three people
with the highest points.
If you choose your team well,
you can earn many points.
- Okay!
- Okay, got it.
- It's a random game.
- Let's move to the court now.
You'll win
if you have good teammates.
Let's divide into teams
after the practice round.
- Okay!
- Yes!
You can do it. You can really do it.
Wait for it. There. It's here.
It's here. So Min, kick it softly.
There you go.
(She walks to the ball
looking determined,)
(but she ends up hurting herself.)
(So Min's slapstick comedy
makes the guys burst into laughter.)
Hey!
Hey, that was
a typical slapstick comedy.
- Well done.
- A fool's slapstick comedy.
- That was funny.
- It's...
It's not easy to pull off.
- Everyone, please gather around.
- Okay.
Listen to the options I give you,
and you'll be split into teams
by sitting or standing.
- Okay!
You can't study the room
and pick the option accordingly.
- Of course not!
- No, we won't!
If anyone hesitates,
then we should do it again.
Stand in a line.
- Director.
- Yes?
What if we're divided into
teams of 5 and 3?
- We'll just play with those teams.
- Oh, really?
- Really?
- Even if it's 6 to 2?
Yes, we'll just go with the result.
Don't read the room and copy others.
- We should turn around randomly.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Okay, then you should turn around.
- You should turn around.
- Okay. Turn around.
- Do we have to go this far?
Se Chan, you should turn around.
Choose the person you want to visit
on your day off.
Sit down if you want to go
to Jong Kook's place...
and remain standing
if you want to go to Jae Suk's.
(Sit down if you want to go to
Jong Kook's place.)
(Remain standing
if you want to go to Jae Suk's.)
- 1, 2, 3.
- What about me and Jae Suk?
The same goes for you two.
All right,
the teams have been decided.
- Okay!
- All right!
- All right! Who's on our team?
Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Haha,
and Se Chan are on one team.
What's this?
It's because he lives alone,
but Jae Suk has a family.
So it'd be uncomfortable
to hang out there.
That's right.
- My place is more comfortable.
- We can drink at his place.
My place is more comfortable.
Thank you for choosing
to come to my place though.
It's uncomfortable
because Jae Suk has a family.
Thank you for choosing
to come to my place.
(The host takes care
of the visitors.)
I actually wanted to choose
Jong Kook's place.
But it's your place.
All right! Let's do this!
How are we supposed to play
against them?
Ji Hyo and So Min
can use your hands.
Okay. Let's do this.
- Do we serve first?
- Yes.
Okay. I'll kick it.
(Kwang Soo serves first.)
- Has it started?
- Are you going to kick it?
Okay, there you go.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry.
- All right!
(The ball doesn't go over the net.)
(Se Chan makes an absurd mistake.)
You don't know who'll win!
- We got it!
- You don't know who'll win!
Everyone on Team Jae Suk
gets a point.
No, we need to decide
who serves first!
- We need to decide who serves!
- But you agreed to it earlier.
- We need to decide on it first!
- Mister, you agreed to it earlier.
- You can't do that!
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- You agreed to it earlier.
We'll let them serve first.
- Mister, you agreed to it earlier.
- No, we need to decide first.
- Why did you serve first?
- You agreed to it earlier!
- Then why did you agree to it?
Explain it to me.
Tell me the reason.
They chose to hang out at my place!
What about these guys?
These kids chose
to hang out at my place!
- Yes, you're one of us.
- They chose my place!
- "These kids"?
- Yes, you're one of us.
- Did he just refer to me as a kid?
- Hey, we...
I'll let it go
since we're on the same team.
- Let's play.
- You can play with your hands too,
so don't get flustered.
- Just hit it with your hand!
- Don't try to use your foot.
My ball!
- That's good!
- You called for it! Hurry!
That's good!
- He just passed it over the net.
- Take it easy.
- Here it is.
- He just passed it over the net.
- Take it easy.
- Here it is.
- Should I kick it?
- No. Good job.
- My ball!
- Take it easy.
My ball!
- Okay, good job.
- Kick it.
- Wait, wait.
- Just pass it over.
- Just pass it over!
- No!
- Nice. It's out!
- Out!
- I told you to just pass it over.
- It was an easy ball though.
- You could've just passed it over.
- I could've done it.
- You never know who'll win!
- All right!
Kwang Soo, good job!
- It's okay.
- Let's do this!
- They're nothing.
- Let's smile now.
Hold on! Haha.
Those who say "Let's smile"
get three coins.
- Why?
- Really?
The one who says "Let's smile"
gets three coins.
(Really?)
- Let's smile.
What did he say?
(The one who says "Let's smile"
or "This is fun" first...)
(gets 3 coins.)
Let's smile!
(Laughing)
- What was that?
- Look at him.
- Let's cheer up!
- Let's do this!
Let's cheer up!
- Let's beat them all!
- What was that?
Let's bet our lives on it!
- We can do this.
- Let's cheer up.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- We got this.
- Let's do our best!
- Hey, it's okay.
Let's play until the end
even if we lose!
- Hey!
- Pump it up! Pump it up!
- That was incredible.
Hey! You're like ginseng!
"Ginseng"?
What do you mean?
You're like ginseng to me.
- You're like ginseng.
- Let's cheer up.
There was a rule to give
three coins to the one who says...
- "Let's smile" or "This is fun."
- This is driving me crazy.
This is driving me crazy.
- 8012!
- Let's play.
We're winning by two points.
- Let's play!
- 8012! We're one!
- Yes, we are!
- Okay.
- Let's smile!
8012, 8012.
(The game resumes
with Kwang Soo's serve.)
- That was good.
- Suk Jin, it's yours.
- Well done, Kwang Soo.
- That's good.
- Nice!
- All right!
(They make another absurd mistake.)
- Nice!
- All right!
- You're good!
- You never know who'll win.
- I'm so happy...
- All right!
I'm so happy to have you on my team.
I'm so happy too!
- I love it.
- I'm so happy.
- You're indispensable.
- You're the best!
- We're going to smile for real now.
- You're the best player.
- Let's smile for real.
- You're so good.
- Let's smile.
- He's the best player.
- It's okay.
- He's an indispensable player.
- Suk Jin!
It's okay. It's really okay.
- That can happen.
- There's no winner or loser...
in this game.
- Let's do this!
- We can do it.
- Okay!
(They play for the match point
without getting extra coins.)
That was a good one, Kwang Soo.
Nice serve.
- Get it. There you go.
- Okay.
- Pass it to Suk Jin.
- Take it easy.
- Use your head.
- What was that?
- I said use your head!
- Use your head.
(He kicks it straight in the net.)
- I said use your head!
- What was that?
- What's wrong with him?
- It's okay.
It's okay.
How come they're so bad at it?
- Well done, everyone!
- It's over!
- All right!
- I can't believe our team won.
The members on Team Jae Suk
win four points,
and the members on Team Jong Kook
win one point.
- All right!
- I told you to use your head.
- My head?
We kept shouting to you.
- Sorry about that.
- Let me massage you.
I'll remember these members!
- That was great!
- Let's play one more time.
We'll play another round.
Please line up.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- Half of you should turn around.
- Okay.
You should turn around.
Pick the person
you'll hang out with...
after the shoot.
Sit down if you want to hang out
with Ji Hyo,
and remain standing if it's So Min.
1, 2, 3!
Oh, no.
(Everyone chose Ji Hyo.)
This is crazy.
(Disappointed)
All right.
It'll be a game of 6 against 2.
I have no idea how it turned out.
How did it go?
I sat down.
6 against 2?
It's 6 against 2?
She took off her microphone.
- Ji Hyo.
- She took off her microphone.
(She takes off her microphone
to protest.)
- She took off her microphone.
- I'll quit the show.
- Goodbye.
- That's not it!
- I really contemplated.
- Please come back, So Min!
What's worse is that no one
is stopping her from leaving.
- I didn't know.
- It'd be too tiring, that's why.
- Let's smile! This is fun!
- Let's smile!
- This is so therapeutic!
So Min, this isn't...
This is so therapeutic and nice.
So Min,
please don't get the wrong idea.
Okay? Okay.
- Okay, okay.
- It's after the shoot.
- Right? You get me, right?
- It'd be too tiring.
Everyone!
We'll give 3 coins to the 6 of you.
- Why?
- Why? What was it about?
- Why are you giving them to us?
- Why?
- Why not us?
Why aren't you giving us any?
Why can't we get coins?
- Why? What's the reason?
- What about Ji Hyo and me?
- What's the reason?
- We can't tell you the reason.
Are we getting the coins
because we have more members?
But you didn't give them
to us earlier.
- It was 4 to 4.
- Oh, so it's different.
That was another mission.
What about Ji Hyo and me?
Why aren't we getting one?
There's a reason for giving them,
so we'll tell you that later.
- Why? What is this about?
- What's the reason?
- What could it be?
- Let's just enjoy it.
Let's go, let's go!
- Ji Hyo, Let's do this.
- We can do this.
- Let's do this.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- Let's go!
- We can do it!
This is exciting! This is fun!
Hey, hey.
All right. Let's go!
- Let's huddle up!
- All right!
(Cheering)
- Let's do this.
- Let's go!
Why is he suddenly dancing?
- We'll only use our heads.
- Let's do that.
Let's win all five points.
- Let's win all five points.
- I can do it! Bring it on!
- Let's go!
Bring it on!
- Here it goes.
- Okay.
(The game starts
with Ji Hyo's serve.)
- All right!
- We got one point.
- We got one point!
- It's okay, it's okay.
- It's okay.
- You did well.
- Get the ball.
We can do this.
(Kwang Soo serves next.)
- Hey, hey.
- What are you doing?
(Another absurd serve)
- Hey, what was that about?
- Give me your coins.
- The ground...
- What's wrong with him?
It's okay, Kwang Soo.
8012, 8012!
Well done, Kwang Soo. Well done.
(Two of them cheer Kwang Soo up
without even looking at him,)
(and this guy is serious
about the game.)
He's just playing as he pleases
now that he's quitting.
- Jong Kook...
- You're doing as you please!
Did you hear him? He said...
Kwang Soo is playing as he pleases
now that he's quitting.
- It wasn't like that.
- You should think about us!
We're okay!
Kwang Soo, you're so cool!
You did well!
- That was good.
- You can throw it.
Just throw it.
(She changes her strategy
and throws the ball.)
- She's stepping way over the line.
- That was a good throw.
- Hey. Darn it!
- Hey!
- All right!
- What's wrong with you?
(This time, he makes a mistake
in receiving the ball.)
(The ball falls helplessly
in front of the net.)
- What's wrong with you?
- It's just that...
You're so cool!
- Hey!
- This can happen, you know?
Are you an attention seeker?
- What's wrong with him?
- This happens a lot, doesn't it?
- What's wrong with you, Kwang Soo?
- Are you an attention seeker?
- You should pass the ball to us.
- What was that about?
- What's wrong with you?
- Well done, Kwang Soo.
- It's okay, Kwang Soo.
- What's wrong with him?
- You don't mean it.
- Kwang Soo, well done.
I'll never do that again.
I'll do better from now on.
(The game turned around
because of Kwang Soo.)
- You can serve now.
- Here it goes.
You need to go behind that line.
He won't go easy on her anymore.
He won't go easy on her anymore
because we're losing.
- It's okay. You can do it!
- Think positively!
Think positively!
You should think positively
just like me.
- He won't go easy on her for real.
- Okay, okay.
There you go.
- Let's play!
- You can't throw it, can you?
- It's out.
- Okay!
- It's out, Ji Hyo.
- It's out.
Okay, we got two points!
(Kim Positive became positive again
after earning a point.)
- This is...
- Move!
Here it comes! Kick the ball.
- It's out.
- What do you mean?
Ji Hyo! Hit it!
(She received it!)
- Hit it!
- Okay!
- Two! You should hit it!
- Okay, we won!
(But they end up
letting their chance go to waste.)
(Okay, we won!)
- All right!
Darn it!
This is not foot volleyball!
- What is this?
- Hey! This is not foot volleyball!
(They don't care.)
(They're fully enjoying their win.)
(They're ecstatic when they won
against them with 6 members.)
- I'm sorry, but we won!
- I feel bad for them.
(Thud)
Why would you throw that at me?
So now...
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk
are in first place.
All right!
- Please line up again.
- Okay.
I'll start while I'm seated.
You need to choose one penalty.
If you want Se Chan's finger flick,
please sit down.
If you want to be flogged
by Kwang Soo, remain standing.
1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook, Haha, and So Min
chose to sit down.)
Jong Kook, Haha, and So Min
are in one team.
- Oh, no.
- All right!
- That's good!
- It's worth a try.
Yes, it's worth a try.
We'll win for sure.
- Yes, we can win this.
- Let's win.
You and I will play freely.
Everyone!
We'll give three coins
to this team's members.
- Why is that?
- Did they practice?
- We'll give you three each.
- Why?
Hey, it must be related
to the court.
Teams on this side of the court
get the coins.
Oh, you're right.
- That must be it.
- Oh, really?
- But we didn't get it the 1st time.
- We didn't get it the 1st time.
Is it because
they're being considerate of So Min?
Are they being considerate
of So Min?
But we were considerate
of Ji Hyo too.
(So it was because
we were considerate of So Min?)
So Min.
(Forcing himself to pat her)
- So Min.
- Don't do it.
- Are you sweating?
- Here, wipe your sweat.
- Ji Hyo, get on my back.
- But just now...
Get on my back, Ji Hyo.
She's on his back now.
Ji Hyo said her legs hurt.
- So we... Are you okay, Ji Hyo?
- Let's rub her shoulders.
- Ji Hyo, are you okay?
- Yes, Jae Suk.
Thank you, Jae Suk.
Blow your nose, Ji Hyo. Blow it!
It's okay.
- There you go.
- Relax your body.
Ji Hyo, you're so light.
Did something happen?
Don't you lie.
Your face is so red.
Your legs are shaking.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
Why did you lose so much weight?
No, Jae Suk.
(While they're pretending
to be nice to each other...)
Gosh, this is so funny.
(He found something.)
(He found makeup tools
on the table.)
- Hey, come here.
- I have no idea.
If you draw something...
- Will they give us more coins?
- Draw something on your face.
- Really?
- Do you want me to draw for you?
(They catch on fast
and quickly put on makeup.)
Are you sure about it?
(What are they doing?)
- Bo Pil!
- Let's do this!
- We can do it!
- Bo Pil, will you look at us?
(Will they give us coins
if we put on makeup?)
There were some tools there,
so I drew something...
as an entertainer!
They are giving him coins.
- They're giving out coins for real?
- Okay!
They're giving them out for real?
We got five coins each!
How many did they give you?
(They get busy after seeing Haha
and So Min getting coins.)
- This is...
- Wow.
- They got five coins?
- Bo Pil!
"Bo Pil".
(How do I look?)
Bo Pil. Thank you.
- Bo Pil!
- Isn't this too normal?
- It's not good enough.
- Is it?
(He gets rejected.)
They'll reject you
if it's not good enough.
You need to draw more!
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo set out.)
No, that's mine!
(Title,
Looking dejected with dark circles)
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Let's smile!
(She earns coins
for excellent makeup and acting.)
- Thank you.
- Let's smile!
Let's smile.
(Kwang Soo looks like
the cymbal-banging monkey.)
Let's smile!
Bo Pil!
(He gives it another try
after drawing on some glasses.)
How's this? Do you not like it?
Tell me fast!
The first five people...
who put on makeup
using the makeup tools on site...
earn five coins.
- They only give up to 5 people.
- 5 people?
- You're the 6th. That was so close.
- I almost didn't get them.
I even drew on glasses.
- It's for five people only?
- I even drew snot.
We talked fiercely
about what to draw there.
It's over.
- It's over.
- It's okay!
- Darn it.
- Let's smile.
- Let's try smiling.
- Who's going to serve first?
- You can serve first.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- Shall we serve first?
- No.
- No, you can't.
- Sorry?
- We'll serve first.
- Why?
You can serve first.
- No, you can serve first.
- You can serve first.
Oh, no. Are you okay?
No, you can serve first.
(Hitting the target)
(The ball hits him
right on the back of his head.)
- Are you okay?
- Jong Kook.
Wait a minute. Jong Kook.
I swear! I swear to the Almighty.
- I didn't throw it at you.
- Hey.
Jong Kook, I saw your eyes.
No, no.
- I saw your eyes.
- That's not true.
- Jong Kook...
- It's okay.
- It can't be helped.
- You just need to win against him.
We can do it. It's okay.
- Your eyes...
- I can't...
I can't throw the ball like this
and hit the back of his head.
I turned around
because I heard a loud thud.
But it really hit the spot.
- It hit right on his head.
- I swear.
You know, right?
I really didn't mean it.
- It was a mistake, right?
- Yes, it was.
- Right. It's okay.
- I didn't mean to hit you.
- Of course.
- I could never hit you like that.
- Suk Jin, just laugh it off!
- Okay.
- Who are you talking to?
- Let's smile!
- Who are you saying that to?
- Give them the ball.
- I think this is how you get coins.
- Let's play!
- Okay.
- Nice serve!
- I got it.
- Haha. Haha.
- That was a stable serve.
- Jong Kook.
- Give it to her.
- Head.
- Use your hand!
(Smashing)
- There you go!
- Wait.
- There you go.
- You can hit harder than that,
- So Min.
- Pass the ball.
- Ji Hyo! Use your hand!
- Ji Hyo!
Pass it over.
There you go!
No, we won.
- No, it was correct.
- No, we won, didn't we?
- No!
- How many times did they bounce it?
- Four times.
- It doesn't matter.
That's not it!
There's a rule
we need to follow, right?
(Suddenly becoming gentle)
Haha, do you want your coins
taken away?
- Take his coins!
- Do you want your coins taken away?
- No. Listen.
- No, that's not it.
- Do you want to go home?
- They bounced it more than 3 times.
- Are you upset?
- Do you want to go home?
- Did you get mad?
- No, no.
They bounced the ball
more than three times!
It's okay if they bounce it
more than three times...
- on a variety show.
- He said it's okay.
- But you didn't tell us that.
- They should've told us before.
Then this shouldn't count.
- It's a rule. Let's not count it.
- Let's not count this.
- Come on. You can't count this.
- You should've told us.
(Acting cute)
- So...
- Bo Pil, listen.
Okay, since we didn't know,
- let's not count it.
- Thank you.
You should say thank you.
It's so nice
to have everyone smile a lot.
It's a therapeutic show.
Jong Kook, kick it now. Kick it now.
- Hey, hey.
- Suk Jin!
- We got this.
Darn it.
Suk Jin!
(He kicks the ball wrong
and hits his own hand.)
That was so funny.
- It's over, right?
- This is so fun!
- It's over, right? 5 to 1.
- It is fun, actually.
Isn't it 4 to 1?
- It's the last round.
- It could be the last round.
Sit down if you want to be reborn
with Jae Suk's looks.
Remain standing if you want
to be reborn with Se Chan's looks.
Sit down if you choose Jae Suk.
Keep standing if you choose Se Chan.
I don't want to play it.
It's only about their looks. One...
- If we choose Jae Suk, we sit.
- You should sit down.
- This is crazy. I can't pick one.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Only 2 people chose Jae Suk.)
All right. Six people for Se Chan.
Obviously!
- How can you live with this face?
- Ji Hyo.
I can't live with his face.
Se Chan looks okay with his mask on.
This is nonsense.
I can't believe it.
- I chose you.
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
(I'm sorry, Jae Suk.)
- I can't believe it.
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
Ji Hyo,
did you misunderstand the rules?
Ji Hyo, come to my team.
Oh, right.
- Why would you follow them?
- Ji Hyo.
You sat down because you thought
you were choosing Se Chan, right?
- Yes.
- You had to remain standing.
- Come here.
- We could've made Jae Suk...
play by himself.
We need to earn at least one point.
We're in trouble.
- Let's do this!
You can do it!
- Haha!
- Use your head.
- Haha.
(After barely receiving
the ball with his head...)
- This isn't allowed.
- Why not? It's a variety show!
(This isn't allowed.)
(Why not? It's a variety show!)
- This isn't allowed.
- Why not? It's a variety show.
Don't get upset!
But it's a variety show.
Why isn't it allowed?
(He reads the room
and manages to come to his senses.)
- Why not? It's a variety show.
- That's allowed, but this isn't?
- Please!
- It'd be funny...
if I head the ball 100 times.
- It didn't fall on the ground.
- That's allowed, but this isn't?
- Bo Pil, this is a variety show.
- Are the rules up to you?
When is it allowed?
You should give us the rules
in advance.
- Aren't you Ms. Kim Ok Jung?
- I mean...
Ms. Kim Ok Jung.
"Get lucky this year."
- Can't we hit the ball twice?
- Of course not.
- Why not?
- This is a variety show.
- I thought it was allowed.
- Seriously.
- What isn't allowed?
Give us a list
of what is or isn't allowed.
Are you complaining?
You shouldn't have touched
that ball.
(Jae Suk's team wins despite having
only 2 members!)
Why did you touch it?
You shouldn't have touched
that ball.
We won!
(They gathered points diligently.)
- Jae Suk is 1st place.
- I got 15 points, right?
- Yes, you did.
- He won.
The results are out.
The first place is Jae Suk.
(The 1st place, Jae Suk)
Really?
In second place...
are Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
- Am I second place?
- Yes.
In third place are Ji Hyo,
So Min, and Jong Kook.
All right.
How many coins do you need now?
I think I will go home
after this game.
I know. I think you will go home.
(Will they be able to go home
for real this time?)
In the second mission,
you need to hinder the others
in order to go home.
The game is
Bend Over and Touch with Your Mouth.
(Bend Over
and Touch with Your Mouth)
There will be 1-on-1 matches.
Sit facing each other
with your hands behind your back.
Bend over and move the snacks
with your mouth only.
The winners will receive coins.
(The ones who move more snacks
will receive coins.)
You need to move the snacks
to your tray.
You don't eat them.
There are people
who are close to going home.
- You are right.
- Right?
Let's wrap things up.
How will we decide on
the list of matches?
Suk Jin and I will go
against each other.
- Otherwise,
- This is...
Kwang Soo could decide...
- since he will leave the show soon.
- What are you talking about?
Kwang Soo,
decide the matches one last time.
- What are you talking about?
- That's a good idea.
- I am for it.
- One last time?
- He will leave the show soon,
- I feel sad.
so we should give him that choice.
- It's time for us
- To say goodbye
What are you doing?
(They repeatedly prepare
for a parting.)
- Why are you singing that song?
- Bye.
I will go against Suk Jin.
Let's go.
Shall we start
with Haha and Se Chan?
- Okay.
All right.
- Let's put our heads together.
- Get ready.
- What are they doing?
- Set...
(They support each other
by putting their heads together.)
- Set,
- Are they working together?
go.
- It's not a bad idea.
- I know.
- That won't work.
- They are sharing the weight.
- What?
- I knew it wouldn't work.
- It's not a bad idea.
- I know.
- That won't work.
- They are sharing the weight.
What?
I can't do it. I can't do it.
What was that?
Hey.
He is bad at it.
Se Chan is bad at it.
I see that there is something
Se Chan is bad at.
I can't do it.
- Haha is good at it.
- How is he so good at it?
Hey, how will you win that way?
My goodness.
Se Chan,
why are you putting your face in it?
Hey.
I can't do it.
Se Chan, you got cream
all over your face.
(He is putting it on his skin.)
Se Chan, hold yourself back.
- Hold yourself back.
- Se Chan has thick legs.
- That's why he can't do it.
- You are right.
- I can't do it.
- What is going on?
I can't do it.
I can't move any snacks.
Time's up.
- He can't do it.
- I can't do it.
Haha got five snacks.
Okay!
- He will go home soon.
- I can't do it.
The second match is...
- between Jong Kook and Jae Suk.
- Really?
Get ready. Set, go.
Jae Suk only needs ten coins
to go home.
My goodness. My goodness.
Set, go.
Jae Suk only needs ten coins
to go home.
(Here is another man
with a protruding mouth.)
He is bowing nicely.
My goodness.
(It isn't easy
for Jong Kook either.)
Hold on. Hold on.
This is impossible.
- How did Haha do it?
- How did he do it?
Jong Kook can't reach it.
My goodness.
- Come on.
- He is leaning.
Jong Kook is holding out.
How did Haha do it?
(Jong Kook holds out with his legs,
but he fails soon.)
How did Haha do it?
(There is something
Jong Kook can't do with his body.)
Even Jong Kook can't do it.
How did I do it?
- This is fun.
- How am I good at it?
How are you good at it?
- You must be flexible.
- How did you do this?
The one in the middle
is easier to get.
Let's do this.
I will win if I get one.
Jae Suk will plant his face again.
He will plant his face again.
Dear viewers, hello.
(Pressing)
He is using Jae Suk's head.
For goodness' sake.
He is using his head for support.
(Biting)
(While Jae Suk was enjoying
the sweetness,)
(Jong Kook spotted the snack
on his forehead.)
(He quickly stole it.)
He stole the snack
that was on your forehead.
Time's up. Jong Kook won.
Jong Kook did it.
I am so annoyed.
(He only showed politeness.)
Jong Kook,
you will receive the coins.
Let's go.
You need to wipe your face.
Thank you.
I have a long way to go.
Here.
We should wipe each other's faces.
Hey!
Why did you take out
so many wet wipes?
Se Chan, you will get five coins.
- Why?
- Se Chan, you will get five coins.
Why?
(Did I need to read the room again?)
You got wet wipes
for your colleagues.
(Five coins)
You got wet wipes
for your colleagues.
Listen.
Thank you.
I am the one
who is covered in cream.
Didn't you see me...
give him a snack?
(He feels victimized.)
You shouldn't use
too many wet wipes.
Don't we get coins for frugality?
- What?
- Frugality.
- Stop it.
(Suk Jin belatedly tries
to help him.)
- What is wrong with you?
- Wipe your face.
My goodness.
Jae Suk.
For goodness' sake.
(They care a lot about each other
at times like this.)
For goodness' sake.
Se Chan, how many coins do you have?
Hold on. I have close to 70 coins.
- Did Se Chan get 5 coins?
- You have 70 coins.
Se Chan, how many coins do you have?
Will Se Chan go home?
I think there will be a third race.
- The second race won't be the last.
- No way.
You are set. Give them the coins.
(He turns in the coins
despite people's jealousy.)
You are set.
You have more than 70 coins.
- I think you are set, Se Chan.
- I think I am set.
Will Se Chan go home?
- He needs 70 coins.
- Will Se Chan go home?
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
How many coins do I have?
Can I go home?
Se Chan has...
- 73 coins.
- He can go home.
Se Chan, the second
Read the Room Race is over for you.
- You can go home.
- Thank you.
- That's incredible.
- Is it over?
There might be a third race.
This is the second race.
Since this is the 2nd race,
there might be a 3rd race.
No, it's over.
(Will he really get to go home
this time?)
- That's incredible.
- Is it over?
I think I will go home for real.
- I doubt he will get called back.
- There might be a third race.
Se Chan, congratulations.
Please go home.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- That's incredible.
- I think this is real.
I will go home without looking back.
See you soon.
I bet you will come back.
No, this is real.
Work hard. Bye.
See you soon.
(Will Se Chan go home for real?)
Can I really go home?
I should go and wash up.
Hye Jin, let's go.
Mi Rae, let's go.
Turn off your phones.
I will go home.
(There is a van
that will take him home.)
Se Chan left.
The third match.
It's So Min versus Ji Hyo.
Set...
Set, go.
(As soon as they begin,
they succeed.)
- What?
- They are good.
- They can do it.
Why is that?
They can do it so easily.
- They can do it so easily.
- Why is that?
- I don't know.
- What's the reason?
- Is it easy?
- I don't understand.
- So Min.
- She was good at foot volleyball.
Stop it. Stop it.
Will she take two at a time?
- Are you comfortable?
- You will save time that way.
My goodness.
You will save time that way.
- My goodness.
- She pushed So Min.
She headbutted So Min.
- That's it.
- The match began in earnest.
Time's up.
Who has more snacks?
So Min does.
So Min won.
- She got so many snacks.
- Is she close to going home?
- I don't feel good.
- She has a long way to go.
- So this is meaningless.
- I am nearly done.
What?
I have 65 or 67 coins.
So Min.
(Covered in cream,
So Min receives the coins!)
Let me wipe your hair.
(Running over)
Are you okay?
(Fake good-doers
smelled a chance to earn coins.)
- All right.
- I will wipe your face.
Haha.
- Gosh.
- Why?
- It was planned.
- You helped your colleague first.
That wasn't my intention.
I didn't do it for the coins.
I helped too.
- You were late.
- My goodness.
- Listen.
- You were late.
- You should give me a memo...
- in advance.
- Listen.
I had everything set up.
How could you award Haha...
when he snatched the wet wipe
from me?
Everyone.
We counted Haha's coins.
- He has exactly 70 coins.
- Really?
That means he can go home.
However...
However,
at this point,
we will wrap up
the second Read the Room Race.
- What?
- Is there another one?
- The second Read the Room Race.
- What?
Is there another one?
We will reveal the secrets
of this race.
- What?
- They will reveal the secrets.
- What happens to me?
- What are the secrets?
You will find out
once we reveal them.
- Are there secrets?
- What are they?
What are they?
(They will reveal the secrets
of the Read the Room Race.)
For your information,
the actions you must carry out...
in the Games of Wits
are decided by specific conditions.
(The specific conditions
weren't revealed.)
(They had to choose
between forks and chopsticks.)
(A comment about smiling
got them R coins.)
(Everyone was curious about
the conditions.)
They're giving them out for real?
(There must be secrets
behind the conditions!)
(Se Chan thought
someone could be behind this.)
("Specific conditions"
were stressed.)
(The secrets behind the conditions
will be revealed now!)
You gave coins to people
who said that the weather is nice.
We will introduce
the hero of the day...
who came up with the conditions.
- What?
- Is there a hero?
- Who is it?
Who came up with the conditions?
Is it Se Chan?
I don't think
it's one of the members.
Who is it? It must be Se Chan.
It must be Se Chan.
- Is it Se Chan?
- It's a gift-wrapped car.
It can't be Se Chan.
If Se Chan gets out of the car,
it won't be a gift.
Is Se Chan the architect?
(Se Chan went home the fastest.)
It isn't Se Chan, is it?
- Is it Se Chan?
- No way.
It would be funny if it's Se Chan.
No. That's not Se Chan's hand.
- Isn't it Ms. Choi Young In?
- What?
Ms. Choi?
- Someone is getting out.
- No. That's not Se Chan's hand.
Who is that?
(A young boy gets out of the car.)
Who came up with the conditions?
Dream!
Dad!
(Dream?)
What? Ms. Choi?
(Dream, what are you doing here?)
- Is that Dream?
- Really?
- Dream!
- What are you doing here?
(Haha's oldest son, Dream?)
Dream!
Is that Dream?
(Is Dream the architect?)
- What is Dream doing here?
- Dream.
I got goosebumps. What is going on?
Dream, what are you doing here?
What is going on?
You should have told me.
Hold on. How... Dream.
(1 day before the shoot)
(The production crew had a meeting
with the architect secretly.)
Hello. I am Ha Dream.
(Ha Dream,
the representative of young viewers)
- Ha Dream, it's nice to meet you.
- Thanks.
We asked to see you
because we need help from you,
an avid fan of Running Man.
The race we prepared
for the shoot is...
the Read the Room Race.
You will be the architect
of the Games of Wits.
You will decide
which actions of the members...
will give or take the coins.
The person with the fewest coins
can't go home right away.
He or she will go home
after carrying out the penalty.
If they order a dish
that isn't on the menu,
they should lose five coins.
Is there a dish you don't like?
I don't like abalone rice porridge.
(The dish Dream dislikes,
abalone rice porridge)
I will have abalone rice porridge.
(That was why the 3 who ordered
abalone rice porridge...)
(got 5 coins taken away.)
(The reason why they had to choose
the chopsticks...)
(instead of the forks...)
If they choose chopsticks,
they should earn coins.
(When someone dropped coins)
If they keep the coins
someone dropped,
they should return them.
If they return them to the producer,
they should get to keep them.
(Dream designed the game
so that honesty could earn coins.)
But I think Dad, Uncle Se Chan,
Uncle Jae Suk,
and Uncle Kwang Soo...
will charge at the coins...
like a pack of hyenas
no matter what.
- Are you including your dad?
- Yes.
(Dream knows his dad well.)
Give coins to people...
who team up with Dad.
(Haha is Dream's favorite person.)
(That was the reason why
Haha's teammates received coins!)
Dream,
what should happen to those...
who politely greet others
at the restaurant?
Let's give them five coins.
Shall we do that?
- Goodbye. I'll come again.
- Thank you. Goodbye.
- Thank you.
If they tell the others
to put on the seatbelt in the car,
they should get five coins.
Let's say
the R coins that are smaller...
than the regular R coins
are worth ten.
Can't we make my dad win...
even if he does badly?
(This architect has
so much filial love.)
Do you want him to win
even if he doesn't have coins?
Yes.
(Dream wants to see his dad win.)
Thank you for choosing me
to represent the young viewers.
Eun Jae, are you watching this?
I am on SBS' Running Man.
(Dream kept it a secret
even from his dad.)
Dream, what happened?
Dream is here.
- Dream.
- Dream, hello.
Dream.
- What brings you here?
- What happened?
- Dream, you are polite.
Dream, what brings you here?
- Dream, what brings you here?
- Dream.
- He is cute.
- What happened?
- Dream, what happened?
I had a preliminary shoot on Sunday.
You had a preliminary shoot
on Sunday.
- With today's shoot,
- What?
we celebrated Children's Day,
which is the day after tomorrow.
An avid viewer of Running Man,
Ha Dream came up...
with the conditions
of the Games of Wits.
All the coin-related missions
of the day...
- came from us and Ha Dream.
- That's incredible.
Dream.
Haha had no idea.
Dream, did you come up
with the chopsticks and forks?
He picked them.
I wondered why we had to choose
between the forks and chopsticks.
Seriously.
- Did you keep it a secret from Dad?
- Yes.
- Gosh, you are tight-lipped.
- How could you do that to me?
You made the shoot interesting.
Dream, will you replace
Uncle Kwang Soo?
Jae Suk!
(He tries to recruit a new member.)
That would be nice.
He grew up a lot.
- He grew up a lot, right?
- Yes.
Dream said
on Haha's YouTube channel...
that he wants to design the games
for Running Man.
That's right.
- He said that once.
- He did well.
You were little when we met,
so you might not recognize me.
- I was so flustered.
- Dream, take this.
What are you doing?
- Kids like R coins.
- For goodness' sake.
- It's not even real money.
- Gosh,
- you are too much.
- Seriously.
You are too much.
Dream, you wanted to try ripping off
the name tags.
- Yes.
- Do you want to try it?
- Whose name tag?
Whose name tag
do you want to rip off?
I heard that there is an uncle
Dream is scared of.
- Who is that?
- Among us?
(Which uncle is he scared of?)
No way.
(Dream is too polite
to voice his thoughts.)
- No way.
- The uncle Dream is scared of.
There is no way he is scared of me.
Do some action moves
before you let him rip it off.
Hold on. I guess he doesn't know
that I bought him many toys.
- What should I do, Dream?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
(It's Dream's dream to rip off
the scary uncle's name tag.)
- It's your last chance.
- Dream, let's go!
(Despite being scared,
Dream approaches him.)
- It's your last chance.
- Dream, let's go!
- Dream, a bit more.
- Dream, you can do it!
(After a fierce struggle,)
(his hand touches the name tag.)
- Dream, a bit more.
- Dream, you can do it!
A bit more.
(Who will be the winner?)
Okay.
(Dream ripped off the name tag!)
(Jong Kook is out!)
(The scary uncle lost!)
You are good.
- He is cute.
- Dream.
Okay.
We have presents for Dream.
- These are...
- Are those games?
game packs.
Dream, here are your presents.
(Dream loves game packs.)
- Say, "Thank you." Bow.
- Thank you.
Dream didn't get to see
Uncle Se Chan.
- Seriously.
- Did Se Chan just go home?
I guess so.
We are still filming him.
He is doubtful.
- He doesn't know about this.
- Really?
- No.
He will watch the episode
when it airs.
Sir, where are you taking me?
Please stop the car.
I don't want to go back and forth.
You are going home.
Thus, we will now finish the race
that Ha Dream designed,
the Read the Room Race.
All right.
- There is something I want to say.
- What?
There is something he wants to say.
- I will whisper it.
- Go ahead.
(Whispering)
(What does Dream want to say?)
- I see.
- What did he say?
Kwang Soo will leave the show soon,
so he wants me
to cut other members off...
as I did with Kwang Soo.
You like it
when I cut Kwang Soo off.
He likes it.
- Who will be the next one?
- All right, Dream.
- I will do it.
- All right.
Don't worry. It's my specialty.
You should do it to Suk Jin.
Dream, I will continue
to cut people off.
- Hold the name tag like this.
- That's right.
1, 2, 3.
(We thank Ha Dream
for designing a fun race.)
(I'm planning a new show.)
(They'll prepare all three meals
of the day for me.)
(Three Meals for Jae Suk)
Hey, it's 12 o'clock.
(Make three meals
for Lord Jae Suk!)
(He enjoys his favorite dish.)
Let's go out.
(As he pleases,)
(he brandishes his power
over the servants.)
(The servants take action.)
(Let's turn things upside down.)
(I can't live in a world like this.)
Hear our words, Lord Yu.
(Did the servants revolt?)
(A match between those
who want to be a nobleman...)
(and a man
who wants to defend his position)
(What will be the fate
of this village?)
(Three Meals for Jae Suk)