(One late summer,
at an exhibit hall in Paju)
(Various artworks are exhibited here.)
(A doll exhibition signboard is placed.)
(The artist of the doll exhibition is...)
(Kim So Hee,
the pride of the Korean doll industry)
(Won the silver prize
at the 27th Korean Youth Doll Competition)
(Won the silver prize at the 56th National
Prettiest Doll Contest)
(Won the gold prize
at the 32nd Asia Doll Exhibition)
(Even among famous artists
around the world,)
(Artist Kim So Hee shines
with her unrivaled artistry.)
(Her dolls have been shrouded
in mystery for a very long time.)
(Artist Kim's masterpieces
are finally opened to the public.)
(Welcome to
Artist Kim's VIP Doll Exhibition.)
Because I'm a fool
(The first guest arrives while humming.)
(Kim So Hee VIP Doll Exhibition)
Hello.
Hello. Welcome.
- Who are you?
- Welcome to Artist Kim So Hee's...
(Hello. Welcome.)
Welcome to
Artist Kim So Hee's VIP Doll Exhibition.
- VIP Doll Exhibition?
- That's right.
First, please sanitize your hands
before entering.
- Oh, is that so?
- After you enter,
you can freely check out the artwork.
I love exhibitions.
A doll exhibition?
(Dolls are displayed in each section.)
Artist Kim So Hee?
"VIP Doll Exhibition."
"The VIPs who have come
to the exhibition..."
"will be given Artist Kim's
limited edition doll as a gift."
So I can take one of them?
I love free stuff.
Oh, one of these? There's 2, 4...
I can take one of them?
(Including the most expensive doll,
7 dolls are displayed side by side.)
They are handmade dolls.
(Her style ranges from fancy to simple.)
These dolls are of high quality.
Whose is this?
Is this also by Artist Kim?
(Her world of art shows off
a wide spectrum.)
My, this looks expensive.
How much is this?
(Which doll is the most expensive one?)
Which one should I pick?
I can take one of them.
The first one is a bit...
It's a bit scary. I don't know why.
There's no male doll.
No, there's just one.
Should I take the male doll?
It's cute.
This is the only male doll.
All right, I'll take...
the male doll.
Oh, I can just take it out.
I'll take this.
Hey, Eddy.
Your name is Eddy.
This is really high quality.
- What's going on?
- Hello.
- What's this?
- Hello. Welcome.
- It's a doll exhibition.
- He's so cute.
You're so cute. Who are you?
- You're so cute.
- Welcome...
to Artist Kim So Hee's
VIP Doll Exhibition.
- Kim So Hee?
- Kim So Hee? Who is So Hee?
A doll exhibition?
I guess we have a guest today.
- But from the beginning...
- Let's go in.
Who is Kim So Hee?
Is she an actress?
Kim So Hee.
Here they are.
Oh, one of them...
is the most expensive doll
that Artist Kim made?
I like this one.
How cute is that? Look.
- Number seven.
- Look at this. It's...
The other dolls look scary.
- This one is the cutest.
- I like number seven.
Come here, you punk.
(Jong Kook chooses doll number 2.)
Yes, this one is the cutest.
- The other dolls look scary.
- I like dolls like this.
- I'll take number seven.
- I like the color.
- You're taking that?
- Isn't it cute?
- My gosh.
- Wait a minute.
- What is it?
- It's pretty.
- Right.
(Doll lookism)
- Do you like pretty dolls?
- Yes, I do.
- Is that so?
- I don't like ugly dolls.
All right. Where should we go next?
- Is that so?
- Upstairs?
So Min, which one do you want?
Gosh, So Min.
So Min, that one looks scary.
You picked a doll that looks like a ghost.
It's because...
Because it looks scary,
I thought it'd be less significant.
Who is Artist Kim So Hee?
(Jae Suk enters next.)
You thought it through
before making your choice, right?
- I knew it.
- I knew you'd pick that.
I knew you'd like the doll
with two braids.
You picked a mischievous-looking one
just like you.
- We have similar taste.
- You picked a mischievous one.
- He picked one that looks like him.
I picked the only male doll.
- "What are you saying?"
- What are you doing?
- I like dolls like this.
- "What are you doing, mister?"
- Your doll...
- His name is Eddy.
Call him Eddy.
"Eddy, my foot."
What's her name? Clara?
"Hi, Clara."
I like dolls that look like dolls.
- These look like a person.
- Right, it's better than these.
It's scary. I was thinking of
picking either of these two.
This style is my favorite.
Since when did you two get along so well?
- They're close.
- Since when?
If they stick together,
things will go crazy.
- It's too much to handle.
- Ever since...
"Three Meals for Jae Suk,"
they've become closer.
- I'll pick this one.
- This one? Then I'll pick this.
I don't have bangs,
so I want one with bangs.
It's so cute.
- It's so pretty.
- Right, Ji Hyo?
The one that Ji Hyo picked is cuter.
- This one's really cute.
- You picked a male doll?
- Yes.
- Yours is so pretty.
- Aren't they cute?
- Yes, they are.
I've never held a doll like this
for so long in my entire life.
I've never wanted a doll.
When were you born?
I was born 55 years ago.
- No, it's been 56 years.
- You're right.
Didn't they make dolls
with straw back in your day?
- It was...
- Like a cursed doll.
- I know.
- With straw?
Like back in the Joseon Dynasty?
- That puppy is still there.
- I want to know who he is.
- Who is that puppy?
- Artist Kim So Hee...
isn't a real figure, is she?
- I have no idea.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Everyone.
Hello. As you already know,
Artist Kim So Hee...
has won so many awards
in various competitions.
She's a star artist who's known
as a master of handmade dolls.
- That's right.
- Oh, she's a star artist?
Let me tell you about the dolls
you're holding.
Ms. Kim rejected all the invitations
from prestigious art galleries...
and focused on her artworks only.
After putting in a great deal
of effort, she made these dolls,
which are limited editions.
Yes! Limited editions!
One of the seven dolls...
is the most expensive doll
that Ms. Kim has ever made.
Among these?
One of you...
is holding the most expensive doll,
and I can't wait to find out who that is.
The next segment we've prepared for you...
is a meeting with Artist Kim.
- Artist Kim So Hee?
- I can't wait to see who she is.
Please welcome Artist Kim
with a big round of applause.
Who could it be?
(Curious)
- Hello.
(Artist Kim So Hee,
the master of handmade dolls)
- Is she a real artist?
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- I'm Artist Kim So Hee.
- Is she a real artist?
- My, hello.
- I'm Artist Kim So Hee.
Thank you so much for coming
to my VIP doll exhibition.
- Thank you.
- Of course we should come.
- Don't say something ridiculous.
- I know. What's wrong with you?
- Your ad-libs are horrible.
- I know.
- They can't even be aired.
- Just stay quiet.
You've all selected my dolls.
Let me introduce the dolls you're holding.
The doll you're holding...
was made with inspiration...
from Gaudi's architecture that I saw
when I was in Barcelona.
- Gaudi?
- Oh, I know who he is.
- "Gaori?"
- Gaudi.
- I got inspired...
- I know who Gaudi is.
- by his work and made this doll.
- You were inspired by his work?
- Yes.
When I look at this doll,
I can feel the sunlight...
- of Barcelona from that time.
- You can feel the sunlight?
That must be why
Suk Jin picked this doll.
- Because he was inspired.
- You can feel the sunlight?
What about the others?
You picked the doll
I put the most effort into.
- Oh, this one?
- Yes.
- What did she say?
- For this doll,
I got the material myself,
which is only provided...
to the Italian designer brands.
- I put my heart into every stitch.
- It looks that way.
(Now that you mention it)
And this doll...
(And this doll...)
Wait. Why are you...
- What's wrong?
- Artist Kim!
- What just happened?
- "Why are you?"
(Artist Kim was introducing
the doll Ji Hyo was holding.)
(Wait. Why are you...)
(With a mysterious remark,
Artist Kim collapsed.)
- What's wrong?
- Artist Kim!
- What just happened?
- "Why are you?"
Did she mean you?
No, she was talking about the doll.
- Maybe she had thrown it away.
- She was talking about the doll.
Artist Kim!
This is a VIP emergency! Paramedics!
Paramedics, please hurry over!
The paramedics are here.
It's so scary.
It's a horror special.
- The one she threw out is here.
- Is she okay?
Ms. Kim!
- But wait.
- She's rolling.
She's rolling on her own!
(She rolls onto the stretcher
as though it was scripted.)
- She's getting on it herself.
- She rolled on her own.
His butt is too close.
- Excuse me.
- You should face her.
Can't you do a better job, Hyung Gu?
- You're so clumsy.
- Didn't Hyung Gu practice?
- Carry her!
- Put her on the stretcher.
- There you go. Watch her arms!
- Be careful.
- Watch her arms.
- Here he goes again.
Just leave already! Watch her head.
You should go down a little.
Be careful.
- Is she okay?
- Her skirt!
Shouldn't she turn over?
She has passed away.
- What did you say?
- She has passed away.
- All of a sudden?
- She rolled herself...
onto the stretcher!
What do you mean she's dead?
- She's still alive!
- Hey.
How can you be so indifferent
when she's dead?
We'll take her to the funeral home.
But she's holding onto the pole.
(Artist Kim So Hee
suddenly died mysteriously.)
- They're going to the funeral home?
- The funeral home?
What number is on your doll, Ji Hyo?
- It's number 5.
- Hers is number 5.
She said that to Ji Hyo's doll.
She was looking at that doll,
and said, "Why are you?"
Ji Hyo.
- Why did you choose this?
- But this is...
(What's the secret
behind Artist Kim's death?)
- It looks like you too.
- It's scary.
The puppy is back.
Everyone.
I'm sure you're all surprised.
Let me clarify what just happened.
- Okay.
Due to the arduous effort
she put into her artworks,
she suffered from
visual and auditory hallucinations.
(Artist Kim suffered from
visual and auditory hallucinations.)
Sadly, today,
Artist Kim passed away.
- My goodness.
- She's dead?
(Artist Kim So Hee is dead.)
- The prices must spike.
What do we do?
Artist Kim...
prepared for her own sudden death.
She told me the procedures
I must take after her death...
- and entrusted her will to me.
- What?
Let me read her will out loud.
- Okay.
- Sure. Go ahead.
She must've left something.
This is the late Artist Kim So Hee's will.
First.
"Whenever, wherever, and however
I, Kim So Hee, die,"
"I will pass the ownership
and all of my assets..."
"to the person selected
by the procedures."
- That's what her will says.
- She must've left something.
Second.
"In accordance with her will
and the prepared plans for today,"
"the person who finds and attains
the most expensive doll by 8 p.m..."
"will inherit the ownership
of the doll and all her assets."
We haven't played
this kind of game in a while.
And lastly,
we're going to carry out a test...
to see if you deserve
to inherit all the assets.
"Those who place 1st and 2nd
on the test..."
"will be given a hint
on the most expensive doll."
"You need to do your best
if you want to inherit."
- Okay.
- All right, now.
We'll start the test now.
- Okay.
- All right.
The dolls suddenly look scary.
- Are we drawing the dolls?
- All of a sudden?
(How are the dolls
related to the artist's death?)
- Why did Artist Kim suddenly...
- Artist Kim...
Why did she die so suddenly?
- She looked at your doll...
- Why was she surprised by my doll?
(Artist Kim suddenly collapsed
after seeing Ji Hyo's doll.)
It's really pretty though.
(Is there a secret behind this doll?)
- All right.
- Please go ahead.
Artist Kim...
wanted to give the most expensive doll...
to the person who is sharp-eyed
and observant.
So here's the test we have prepared.
It's called Draw Using Your Memory.
- Draw Using Your Memory?
- Yes.
Using my memory?
Listen to the name of the brand
we often see...
and draw its logo using your memory.
(They're to draw the logo
of a brand that they remember.)
Two people who score the highest...
will be given a hint.
I must win this.
Everyone.
Please do your best
to win the most expensive doll.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
Bye.
According to Artist Kim So Hee's
last will and testament,
the first qualification test will be
carried out.
(It's time for the qualification test.)
You just have to draw the logo
of the brand I tell you.
- Really?
- Okay.
If the brand name is written on it,
you must spell it correctly too.
We have to spell the brand name too?
If it's necessary, yes.
There's another game inside the game.
- Here's your first question.
- Okay.
The international coffee brand, S coffee.
Oh, I see. Really?
S coffee.
How do I draw that logo?
- That's too difficult.
- How do I draw it?
Please draw the logo of S coffee.
- The one with "Star" in its name?
- Yes.
- First...
- Seriously?
- Their logo has a color.
- Hold on a second.
I'm holding it now.
We all picked this color.
- I wish I could drink it.
- Oh, I found the right color.
- I'll go with this color.
- This is too difficult...
- to draw.
- Jong Kook was holding the cup.
Exactly. I was holding it earlier.
- Wait.
- It's hard to draw that angel.
Oh, boy. Was it Medusa?
- Am I right?
- Yes, it looks like Medusa.
It's something like Medusa, right?
I have no idea how to draw it.
I have the image in my head, but...
All right. I'm done.
- Good. It looks just like the logo.
- Let's move on quickly.
Five, four, three,
- What's this? Look.
- two, one. Time's up.
All right.
Gosh. What's that?
(He turned it
into an aliens' beverage company.)
Hey, what's that?
- I couldn't remember the details.
- My goodness.
- So Min.
- Gosh. Is it a witch or something?
- Hers reminds me of Ninja Turtles.
- Isn't this it?
- There's a queen in the center.
- What's that?
Jong Kook, what did you draw?
- Jong Kook, that's Mr. Man.
- Why did you draw Mr. Man?
- Hey.
- I drew...
- Hey, Jong Kook.
It looks similar if you look at it
with your eyes half open.
- Doesn't it?
- What's that?
Ji Hyo, don't you know
the brand logo at all?
- There's a lady with...
- You don't know?
A lady...
Do you?
- This is it. It's almost the same.
- Okay. Next.
- This is it. There's...
- What's this?
There's the brand name
written around the drawing.
- I'm asking who this is.
- Oh, this...
- Who is this lady here?
- She...
She gained some weight.
- Gosh, seriously.
- She ate a lot and gained weight.
You should've made it look stylish.
This is it. I drew all the details nicely.
- Pardon?
- That's...
- Isn't that Zeus?
- What's that?
- That looks just like Zeus.
- Gosh. I think...
It has similar facial features.
- It'd be a great composite sketch.
- My drawing is the best.
- I drew it better.
- This is more accurate.
- The overall look is...
- Really?
It's obvious who is at the bottom.
- Why?
- What did you draw?
- What is this?
- It's the one on the cupholder.
- Hey.
- On the cupholder...
That's you when you dressed up
as a green onion.
That's ridiculous.
You've never tried their coffee, have you?
This is the drawing on the cupholder.
- We'll reveal the logo now.
- Okay.
- This is the correct answer.
- I'm sure I did the best.
(The correct answer is revealed.)
- It's a mermaid. See?
- Right. Look at her arms.
- I drew her arms right here.
- Look at her hair.
- I drew her curly hair.
- He drew her arms too.
- Right. I drew the arms right.
- Now...
- I drew her arms here.
- They're tails, not arms.
- Now...
- The brand name is written on it.
The winner that was chosen
by the staff members is Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- What?
- He's the winner?
- That?
- How can that be the best one?
- I'm the winner.
- He drew a mermaid at least.
- I knew it was a mermaid.
Oh, I see.
- But I did well too.
- It was hard to draw, right?
- I couldn't remember the logo.
- Okay.
The test result came out.
The person in first place is...
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk is in first place.)
- Jae Suk is good at these games.
- I'm sure I'm not at the bottom.
You guys lacked understanding
of the logo in the first place.
- You see, they...
- Just because you won. That's mean.
- You guys didn't know what it was.
- I can't believe him.
Artist Kim So Hee wouldn't want to
give you any hits.
- Seriously, it's so difficult.
- I'm so upset.
- I thought I could draw it.
- I couldn't remember the details.
I couldn't remember it.
The person in second place is...
Haha.
(Haha is in second place.)
Haha is in second place?
The two of you will be given a hint
on the most expensive doll.
- I'm jealous.
- Read it without showing anyone.
- Haha.
- I'm not allowed to share it?
- No, don't show it to anyone else.
- He said I shouldn't share it.
- Can't he share it with us?
- No.
You and I have known each other
for decades.
They gave me two envelopes.
(Jae Suk and Haha received
two hint envelopes.)
Check the cue card first.
- You mean this?
- Yes.
(They open the first envelope
and read the hint.)
He looks worried.
What? Why?
The first hint must be ambiguous.
But this is...
(What is it?)
There's a weird tension in the air.
(So the hint remains a secret
between them.)
Now, we're going to move
to the next spot of the tour.
(Let's go to the next spot!)
- We're leaving, everyone.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- That puppy is still here.
- Thank you.
(The puppy is standing
in front of the tour bus.)
- I think we'll get instructions.
- What?
Now, you're going to visit
the school Artist Kim went to.
- The school she went to?
- I see.
- If you look around the school,
- Yes.
you will find some hints
on the most expensive doll.
Use those hints to find
the most expensive doll.
And the person who has it
in his or her possession...
at 8 p.m. when the tour ends will
inherit the ownership...
and Artist Kim's assets.
(The person who finds
the most expensive doll wins.)
You can exchange your dolls...
- by mutual consent.
- Yes.
You can also exchange dolls
without consent...
by ripping off the doll owner's name tag.
Without consent?
Then we can get any doll we want.
- However...
- Understood. Thank you, sir.
Since you need to find hints
as quickly as possible,
the order in which you get off the bus
is very important.
- The order we get off?
- Yes.
While moving to the next location,
the order will be decided...
through a simple test.
Don't ever miss this chance.
- Got it.
- Then good luck, everyone.
I understand, sir.
I think there's something going on.
- It's suspicious.
- Exactly.
Why does the puppy keep showing up?
(The puppy with a weird vibe
sees them off as they leave.)
By the way, we can exchange dolls
by ripping off someone's name tag,
- Yes.
- but we can't take one from others.
- What's important is...
- Yes.
- that this doll...
- Do we need two dolls at the end?
- That may be right.
- I agree.
We'll probably need another doll.
Suk Jin, why would you twist
its neck like that? Gosh.
- Look. Its head is turned.
- Gosh.
Turn it back.
(Big Nose is having fun with his doll.)
He has never played with a doll.
He only played traditional games
like jwibulnori.
- Or biseokchigi.
- Or jachigi.
- Yes, jachigi.
- He only played such games.
- He has never played with a doll.
- Or throwing arrows in a bucket.
- He's never done it before.
- Or catching frogs.
(The traditional game lover is excited.)
- He went through a famine too.
- That reminds me of a song.
(Child, do not run)
(It will make you feel hungry)
What's that song?
- "Period of Spring Poverty."
- It's Jin Sung's song.
Oh, I see.
- Why don't you know the song?
- Suk Jin is...
Tell me why I should know that song.
He's one year younger than you.
That's not true.
My parents watched
our show yesterday and said...
- that you don't look well lately.
- Why?
- I don't know. You looked unwell.
- In that episode?
- Really?
- I guess I had some worries.
- So Min.
- I don't remember though.
- Ask your parents...
when he ever looked cheery.
Since they've never seen Suk Jin
look cheery before,
- they must've been worried.
- So Min.
- Brother seems to worry about me.
- Indeed.
- Who is "Brother?"
- Right?
- That kid's father.
- He calls my dad "Brother."
- Just call him "Mr. Jeon."
- Suk Jin.
- "That kid's father?"
- Why would you call him "Brother?"
- What was that?
- He's old enough to be my brother.
How much older is he than you?
- I think he's about...
- My dad was born in 1960.
- They have a six-year age gap.
- Young enough to be my big brother.
- Suk Jin, that sounded so cold.
- That's unbelievable.
- My dad was born in 1960.
- A much older brother.
(Their age gap is small enough
for them to be more friendly.)
My dad calls Suk Jin affectionately
while watching our show.
- "My dear Suk Jin."
- You see,
- That's funny.
- although I've never met him,
- I feel affectionate toward him.
- How they call each other is funny.
You can visit her parents' house...
- even when So Min isn't home.
- Absolutely.
I'd say to her mother,
"Hello, my sister-in-law."
- That's cute.
- They have a small age gap.
- When you look around the school,
- Yes.
the earlier you get out of the bus,
the better chance you'll get.
- We'll play a game to decide that.
- Okay.
- Great.
- All right.
- We can do that.
- Now...
This next test that will decide
the order you get off is...
Admit It to Get Out.
- Okay!
- "Admit It to Get Out?"
- I'd admit to anything.
- I admit things easily.
- I admit.
The first player can attack
one of the two people...
- sitting next to you.
- I see.
For example, tap one of the people
sitting next to you,
and say a sentence like,
"You're doing this now."
For example,
"You want to go number two now."
Or something else.
Anything would do.
- Okay. Got it.
- Then the person you attacked...
has to repeat what you said.
"I am doing it."
- Like this.
- I see.
- You respect me.
- That's good.
- Then you say...
- I respect you.
- Then you attack someone else.
- You like So Min.
- Then I say, "I like So Min."
- Correct.
- That's how you play the game.
- I see.
If you hesitate or fail to say it,
you lose one point.
- Got it.
- We'll have to admit what's false.
- Ready? Who wants to go first?
- Yes.
- Let's have Suk Jin go first.
- Let's do that.
- You should say something baffling.
- That's right.
You're looking at So Min.
(Attack, "You're looking at So Min.")
What was that?
I am looking at So Min.
(Se Chan blocked the weak attack.)
You don't love your family.
(Attack, "You don't love your family.")
(Taken aback)
You don't love your family.
- Go.
- He's hesitating.
I don't love my family.
(Defense, "I don't love my family.")
(He traded his love for his family
just for one point.)
- I can't believe he just said that.
- Did he just say that?
- Just to get off the bust first.
- I can't believe this.
- Suk Jin, how could you do that?
- You...
regret marrying your wife.
(Attack, "You regret marrying your wife.")
I...
I regret marrying my wife.
(Defense, "I regret marrying my wife.")
(The breaking celebrity news
keep pouring out.)
But...
You are thinking about Yoon Eun Hye.
Enough!
(Defense, "Enough!")
Enough is enough! Just stop it!
(Jong Kook is hitting Jae Suk
ruthlessly with his doll.)
- Stop it.
- Why...
- Eun Hye, come on the show.
- That's enough.
- "Running Man" is waiting for you.
- Enough. Gosh, seriously.
- I haven't seen you in ten years.
- You drive me crazy.
- I mean...
- She's practically a member.
- Eun Hye, I miss you.
- Please come on our show.
- Don't bring her up every time.
- Eun Hye, you're one of us.
- Eun Hye from Baby V.O.X,
- Why would you...
- we're all waiting for you...
- Stop it. That's enough.
- Don't let it continue.
- I mean this is just a game.
- Even so...
- This is just a game.
- Never bring her up in any case.
- Jong Kook, you lost one point.
- Never bring her up again.
- He lost a point.
- He lost one point. Okay.
- Promise me, okay?
- You lost one point.
- All right. That's okay.
- It ends right here.
- All right. I heard you.
- He can't seem to let it slide.
- It's just a game.
- Don't do that again.
- Jong Kook, you go first.
- Pick either person next to you.
- That was hilarious.
Okay. You may begin.
You want to be alone for three days.
(Attack, "You want to
be alone for three days.)
I bet he actually wants that.
- I want to be alone for three days.
- He means that.
- That's why he doesn't feel bad.
- Exactly.
("Mr. Yoo Demands Additional
Three Days for Quarantine")
You are thinking about your ex-lover.
(Attack, "You are thinking
about your ex-lover.")
- Oh, my gosh.
- The one that I know?
- Is it her?
- Suk Jin, don't do that.
Keep the peace in your family, Suk Jin.
You lost one point.
(He failed to admit it
and lost one point.)
- Darn.
- Why did you hesitate?
- Gosh.
- You could've just said it.
- You know... Hey.
- You could've just repeated it.
- You should've said it.
- I never thought about my ex-lover.
- Then why didn't you repeat it?
- It wasn't like that.
- You should've just repeated it.
- It was so unexpected.
You could've done it.
By the way, why is it only us
that play the game?
- Let them play too.
- Let's go that way.
- I'm so relaxed.
- I should repeat whatever it is.
- Let's start with Haha this time.
- Okay.
Great. Let's go.
You...
have dated Jong Kook.
(Attack, "You have dated Jong Kook.")
That's a hard one.
- What?
- That's a difficult one.
I have dated Jong Kook.
- I knew it.
- He said, "I knew it."
- We all knew that.
- Okay.
You...
still think of me.
What? Is this a love triangle or what?
But he's married.
- You're married. Will you say it?
- That was unexpected.
(When he was single, he said,
"Will Ji Hyo fall for me in ten seconds?")
(You want to go crazy today?)
(Should I hit on her?)
(There were times when he wouldn't
stop flirting with her.)
(Could Haha admit
his embarrassing moments?)
- You'll admit it?
- But this is just a game.
I still think of you.
Good.
That was good.
You...
were at Jong Kook's house yesterday.
(Attack, "You were
at Jong Kook's house yesterday.")
- Great.
- Fine.
I was at Jong Kook's house.
I knew it.
Oh, I see. Okay.
You...
thought of me yesterday too.
(Haha burst out laughing and failed.)
Haha got excited.
He's lost his touch.
Haha lost one point.
- He lost one point.
- He got taken aback.
I think it brought him back old memories.
I guess it reminded him of the days...
- when he was wild.
- There's romance for a change.
- Haha lost a point.
- By the way,
Haha looks like the coach
of the national archery team.
- "Let's go!"
- He looks like the coach...
- of the national archery team.
- Indeed.
- He's shooting an arrow. Good.
- Yes.
He looks like
the national archery team coach.
My gosh. I couldn't admit that.
- Let's start with So Min this time.
- This is fun.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Go Eun, I'm sorry.
- So Min will go first.
So Min will go first.
Why are you staring at me?
I have nothing to do with you.
(Tapping)
- You should look at me.
- Okay.
Look at me while I'm saying.
- Don't ask him out suddenly.
- Exactly.
You...
- love me with all your heart.
- Oh, man.
(Attack, "You love me
with all your heart.")
- Hey, you'll lose only one point.
- Oh, my.
It's only one point.
Keep your pride.
I...
- love you with all my heart.
- Okay.
(Defense, "I love you with all my heart.")
Hey, what was that?
I said you'd lose only one point.
- Why would you hit me?
- Go on.
- Why are you taking it out on me?
- You...
You...
love So Min with all your heart.
(Attack, "You love So Min
with all your heart.")
(Defense)
I...
(Laughing)
(He laughs while repeating it.)
I love So Min with all my heart.
Yes, I do.
(The extreme job)
- As a co-worker.
- Okay. Let's go.
You want to be alone for a month.
For a month?
I want to be alone for a month.
(Defense, "I want to be alone
for a month.")
- You're bad at improvising.
- Yes?
(Attack, "You're bad at improvising.")
(Clenching his teeth)
(They're laughing
as they know how he must feel.)
- That was good.
- Great job.
- My goodness.
- Hey.
I'm not bad at it!
- He wasn't teasing you.
- I'm not bad at improvising.
- He took it seriously.
- Exactly.
There must be a reason why I still
work in this industry!
- That was the hardest one so far.
- There must be a reason.
- Right?
- My goodness.
- "You're bad at improvising."
- People go crazy about me.
- This is a weekend variety show.
- You're bad at improvising.
- That's true.
- That was so hilarious.
- All right.
- Who wants to go first this time?
How about Jong Kook?
Okay. Let's start with Jong Kook.
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm curious about what he'll say.
You...
hate Director Choi Young In.
(Choi Young In, the director
of SBS variety show department)
(Fully satisfied)
(Actually, the two of them...)
(complimented each other
at an award ceremony as well.)
Oh, my. Will he meet her again after this?
I...
hate Director Choi Young In.
Oh, gosh. He just said it.
- Of course, I said it.
- I wouldn't have if I were you.
- Of course, I should. It's a game.
- I respect you, Ms. Choi.
- Okay.
- You...
- are not funny these days.
- Why do you attack only me?
(Attack, "You're not funny these days.")
(Laughing)
Don't laugh, you guys.
- He just said the same thing.
- It's not the same.
- Don't get mad.
- Don't be mad.
- It's the same as the previous one.
- That's not true.
- Repeat it for now.
- Repeat it.
- Everyone says I'm funny.
- Say it.
- What's with your reaction?
- It's the situation that's funny.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- It's not like we think it's true.
- That's right.
- That's not what I mean.
- Just repeat it.
- Why would you laugh at it?
- Why are you being sulky?
- You lost one point.
- Just say it.
- That's it. Gosh.
- But he made me angry.
- You hesitated too long.
- I mean...
- Is that what this game is about?
I didn't say it
because I actually hate Ms. Choi.
- Because it's just a game.
- I said it because it's a game.
Suk Jin, you go first.
Let's start with So Min.
She didn't get many chances.
- Have you run out of ideas?
- That's right.
I'm too angry to think of any.
- "Have you run out of ideas?"
- I ran out of ideas.
- Hey.
- He ran out of ideas.
- My, that's so funny.
- He's run out of ideas.
- Hey. Got a death wish?
- That's funny.
I'm just worried. That's all.
- He'll call the staff later...
- "Have you run out of ideas?"
to ask them to make him look funny
when they edit this.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Let's start with So Min.
- Me?
- Yes.
(It's So Min's turn.)
- It's you, Haha.
- That was cute.
You didn't go home last night.
I didn't go home last night.
(Haha repeated it.)
You...
are ugly.
I know that.
(So Min got upset.)
- So Min, come on.
- She admitted it though.
- She failed.
- Didn't she just admit it?
- Of course.
- No. I didn't fail.
- I was going to repeat it.
- She was going to.
- Why did you take it seriously?
- I was...
- going to repeat it.
- You should've said, "I'm ugly."
- I was going to...
- If you get upset...
- Exactly. You shouldn't get upset.
- I was going to repeat it.
- You lost one point. It's over.
- You shouldn't get upset.
- Exactly.
- The game ended.
- I'll tally the score and tell you.
- You...
- You're uglier than Se Chan.
- Stop it.
No, I'm not!
When we get there, you'll get out
in this order.
- Got it. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Why am I in sixth place?
- One, two, three.
This is the school
that Artist Kim went to.
- Yes.
- Where are we?
The person who is holding
the most expensive doll...
at 8 p.m. when the game ends...
gets the prize money
and inherits Artist Kim's assets.
- I see.
- As you were informed earlier,
- there are hints hidden throughout here.
- Yes.
Based on the hints you find,
guess the most expensive doll,
and exchange dolls with someone else
or take it from the person.
- This place is a little eerie.
- Indeed.
I'm a little scared.
This is really scary.
I have a bad feeling about this.
It looks creepy.
I feel like there's something in here.
- It's suspicious.
- Exactly.
(What do the hidden hints
tell about the most expensive doll?)
Now, the person who came in first
in the game...
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- You may go now.
- Okay.
- Take off your seat belt.
- Go, Se Chan.
I'll see you guys later.
I'm off.
(He got out of the bus
while holding his doll.)
All right.
Where should I check first?
I should find hints.
Oh, my. What's that?
Why are there dolls here and there?
I see dolls all over the place.
(In the stairways and classrooms...)
I wonder why there are dolls
here and there.
(Mysterious dolls are placed
here and there.)
(There's an eerie tension in the air.)
This place is so scary.
This isn't a horror special, is it?
(Something about this school
doesn't feel right.)
I'm scared.
I'm curious about So Min's doll.
(Se Chan wants So Min's doll.)
I'm going to rip off her name tag.
- So Min, yours is the scariest.
- There must be something.
There must be something else.
- Mine is so cute.
- It looks like a nine-tailed fox.
- My baby.
- If you think about it,
Artist Kim explained to us...
about only these two dolls
before she died.
- She didn't tell us about the others.
- That's right. Also,
she was startled when she saw this doll.
(Earlier on, at the exhibition...)
(She said that Suk Jin's doll is
a great doll.)
(Then she told them
about Jae Suk's doll too.)
And this one is...
(When she saw Ji Hyo's doll,
she collapsed and died.)
The dolls that she didn't tell us about...
- Ji Hyo, you may leave now.
- Okay.
- Go on, Ji Hyo.
- My gosh.
- Good luck.
- All right. Go on.
I'll get going.
(The doll in Ji Hyo's hand is
the mysterious doll number five.)
Wait. The hint...
(Wait. The hint...)
Are those dolls hints?
I see a lot of dolls around here.
(She picks the doll up
and continues moving.)
- Jae Suk, it's your turn.
- Yes!
- Okay.
- See you later.
Bye.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry.
- See you later.
(Jae Suk stepped on his foot.)
Why would you step on my foot?
- I'm sorry.
- Did he step on your foot?
- I doubt it.
- I didn't see it.
- Why did you put it in the path?
- That's why it happened.
- Why did you put it out there?
- Then where else should I put it?
- Come on. Don't do that.
- Why would you put your foot there?
- Gosh. You'll be in trouble.
- I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
(He gets out
after the half-hearted apology.)
(Then he checks something out.)
(What he took out as soon as
he got out of the bus was...)
(the hint envelope that was given
only to the top two earlier.)
- Why?
- But this is...
There's a weird tension in the air.
The cursed doll is the most expensive.
(Please head to Room 203
of Building A and play the video.)
(The most expensive doll is
a cursed doll?)
(They chose the dolls at random
while thinking that they're cute.)
(But out of the 7 dolls...)
(There's a cursed doll among them?)
(The cursed doll is the most expensive.)
(If you wish to know the full story,)
(please head to Room 203
of Building A and play the video.)
(Only Jae Suk and Haha...)
(know the secret
to the most expensive doll.)
I think it's this building.
(He must head to Room 203 to learn more.)
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
It started to rain all of a sudden.
(He bumped into Ji Hyo
on his way up the stairs.)
Jae Suk,
what was the clue you were given?
- I can't share that information.
- Got it.
- If I figure it out, we'll talk.
If I find out what the clue is,
we'll share ideas.
I'll put it down here for now.
What's with all the mosquitoes?
- Are there mosquitoes around?
- Yes.
(It's the room Jae Suk must go into
to watch the video.)
(He watches Ji Hyo's actions
and heads to the room.)
(He goes inside.)
Shouldn't I close the door?
(Nervous)
It won't lock.
My gosh.
(You startled me.)
That was terrifying, you know.
What are you up to?
- What...
- You scared me.
- That's why you locked the door?
- Yes.
(He blabbers nonsense
with a suspicious look on his face.)
- You startled me.
- I thought you had found something.
I didn't.
- What...
- You found something, didn't you?
I didn't.
I think you did.
I really didn't.
(Haha now gets off the bus.)
(He reads the clue like Jae Suk did.)
I must find the videotape.
(The cursed doll is the most expensive.)
(He heads to Room 303 of Building B
to look for the videotape.)
Let me see.
(He must find the videotape first.)
Is it here?
(Jae Suk managed to ditch Ji Hyo.)
(He searches for the videotape too.)
I think something could be here.
(I think something could be here.)
(Huh?)
I found it.
(It's the videotape.)
(He puts it in the VCR.)
It's been a while since I saw a VHS tape.
(The video plays.)
(What is recorded on the videotape?)
Welcome.
My gosh!
(He freezes on the spot.)
That startled me.
As a reward for finding me,
I will tell you a jaw-dropping story.
(I will tell you a jaw-dropping story.)
You're looking for
the most expensive doll So Hee made.
(You're looking for the most
expensive doll So Hee made.)
I am.
Do you believe...
that the doll you're currently holding...
is the most expensive one?
If so, be aware.
Because the most expensive doll...
has been cursed by a ghost.
(The most expensive doll
is in fact cursed.)
My gosh. Did I frighten you?
But that's not all.
The ghost that cursed the doll...
and killed Kim So Hee...
is among you.
(The killer is among you.)
(The ghost...)
(is among us?)
(One of them is the ghost
who murdered So Hee.)
And that ghost...
will be after you next.
(One of the dolls is cursed...)
(and the ghost
will now come after the living.)
Do you wish to live?
Your chances are slim,
but I'll still lay out an option.
(The way the living can survive)
Out of the seven dolls,
find the one that's cursed...
and cut it open by the belly.
(Cutting open the cursed doll
will eliminate the ghost.)
(The ghost will be eliminated.)
But be careful...
because the names of the living...
are written inside the other six dolls.
(The names of the living
are in the other 6 dolls.)
If you cut open a doll that isn't cursed,
the name in it
will point to who's eliminated.
(If you find a name in the doll,
that person will be eliminated.)
(Cutting the wrong doll will result
in the elimination of a human.)
(Their names are written
inside each doll.)
(Not knowing this,
they chose the one they liked.)
(The dolls aren't in the hands
of their respective owners.)
(No one's aware of whose doll they have.)
(To stay alive,)
(you must find the doll
that has your name in it.)
At 7 p.m.,
at 7:30 p.m.,
and at 8 p.m., head to the doll house...
to win the chance to stay alive.
(Every 30 minutes, they will
be given the chance to stay alive.)
Until 8 p.m., find the doll
that has your name inside.
(Winning conditions for humans)
Or find the cursed doll
and cut open its belly.
(Winning conditions for humans)
This is how you find
the dolls that belong to you.
Find the envelopes
hidden within the school...
and choose two of the dolls
from the photos inside.
Write down your name or
the name of the one you suspect...
and place it in the mailbox.
At the doll theater,
you'll be able to see...
if that person's doll is the right one.
(Write down a name
along with photos of 2 dolls.)
(Confirm your suspicions
at the doll theater.)
(The second envelope he was given...)
(has the photos of the dolls.)
I'm supposed to choose two.
(Confirm your suspicions
by choosing photos of two dolls.)
I hope you find the cursed doll
and stay alive.
Poor you.
(Poor you.)
(Horrified)
Do not...
trust anyone.
(He yells in anger
at the sudden bloody tears.)
That was scary.
(That was so scary.)
(One must secure his own doll
and find the cursed doll to win.)
(Who could be the ghost
that lurks among them?)
I bet the others first went that way.
However, I'm getting
a vibe from this place.
Wait. Here's a doll.
(Behind it...)
Why hasn't anyone...
See? No one has been here.
It's still here.
Hold on.
(He finds the photos of the dolls...)
(that'll lead him to the rightful owners.)
I'll check these later.
They don't seem to be in the right order.
(While Jong Kook finds the photos...)
(Like Jae Suk,
Haha figures out the rules.)
My gosh.
This is kind of scary.
(What's this sound?)
(Rattle)
What's this?
(Startled)
Hey!
- Welcome.
- Why is the door locked?
- This is odd.
- As a reward for finding me...
(Detective Kook knows something is up.)
Haha!
- I will tell you...
- Who are you with?
(What's that sound?)
(Behind locked doors...)
Write down your name...
(Haha finds out the scary truth.)
(What's scarier is Detective Kook
listening from the outside.)
Okay, I heard everything.
I heard it all.
Now I know why these photos were there.
(He figures out what the photos are for.)
- Gosh.
- Come on out already.
Why didn't you lower the volume?
I heard everything.
I heard it all.
The volume can't be turned down.
(The volume can't be turned down.)
- Why did you lock the door?
- What?
- It's nice to share.
- I was scared.
It's all the more reason
to have me with you.
I mean...
I don't know what I just saw.
Watch it yourself.
- I heard everything.
- It's like I've been possessed.
- Hey.
- I'm terrified right now.
(Haha talks in circles
and avoids Jong Kook.)
How will he...
(What is this?
He's being suspicious.)
Can anyone watch this?
- The video.
- That?
You have to fit the requirements, but...
I told you I heard everything.
Don't try to hide things from me.
- I'm not hiding anything.
- I'm going to cut that open.
- What?
- I'm going to cut open your doll.
Don't do that.
It's really scary today.
(Haha runs away as soon as possible
to escape Jong Kook's questions.)
- Today, my...
- You're too weak for this mission.
My brain is working really fast today.
I think I can do something today.
Turn on the lights.
I have good eyesight,
so I can see in the dark.
You can't see anything in
this pitch black room.
Hey.
What?
Stop kidding.
You're acting.
Did you think I'd fall?
"Did you think I'd fall?"
What does that even mean?
Just pretend to understand it.
Accept it as it is.
What does that mean?
Just accept it.
I mean,
"Did you think I'd fall for that?"
Hey!
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
I didn't know you'd scream.
(Laughing)
I didn't know you'd keep going.
(He's done teasing
and starts looking for hints.)
You know something, don't you?
Of course.
You're going to win anyway.
- Then I'll tell you something.
- Guys!
(Surprised)
- My gosh!
- Goodness.
Can you be quieter?
- My gosh. You scared me.
- Gosh!
You're usually so quiet.
What's with you today?
- Why are you...
- Because...
- you guys were whispering, so...
- You really surprised us.
You scared me.
There's something here. What is it?
(Jong Kook knows all the rules...)
Mine is important.
Mine.
(He plans to put in the photo
to find his doll.)
Mine.
Number two.
Mine and...
(The one Jong Kook has,
The one Suk Jin has)
Okay.
(He puts his name
on dolls number 2 and 4.)
Finding mine is most important.
Should I go to the doll theater?
I'm doing all sorts of things.
(He can find out if one of these
is his at the doll theater.)
Okay. Let's go.
(He can find out if one of these
is his at the theater.)
(So Min appears.)
Jong Kook.
Did you find any hints?
- I found about two...
- No, I didn't.
Did you go to the doll theater?
No. I'm going to go now.
That place is weird too. There are
dolls with our names on them.
- Really?
- So I thought there might be a spy.
There are dolls with our names on them?
Yes.
Let's go check it out.
- The doll theater is leery.
- Here?
- The doll theater is here.
- Okay.
It's at the end? The left end?
Here. Over here.
- It's here?
- Over here.
(So Min doesn't know anything yet.)
I'm pretty sure there's
something here, but... What is this?
- Why is Kim Jong Kook making an X?
- What's wrong?
- What?
- Why is it holding up its hands?
(Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook,
Haha, Song Ji Hyo)
What is it? Do you know what this means?
- It wasn't like this...
- So that's what it means...
Okay. I get it.
I have no idea what this is.
I just knew where this was.
What is it?
Okay. We have to move quickly.
I have to move fast.
- I have to reduce the probability.
- What is it?
- Okay.
- Why is yours an X?
(So Min doesn't get what's going on.)
- I should go over there.
- What's this? Are you leaving?
(Haha knows the rule,
and he's looking for hints.)
What are you doing?
(Surprised)
(After watching the video, he was
scared, but this made it worse.)
What is it? What's wrong?
Gosh, my neck.
Everyone is scared
out of their minds right now.
Okay.
My gosh!
Why are you so scared?
I have something to tell you.
- I found something.
- What is it?
- A photo.
- Right.
What do we do with it?
Did you find any hints?
- Hold onto it,
- Hold onto it.
and look at me. Maybe I should...
just share everything I have with you.
- Go ahead. What is it?
- Come with me.
Come with me.
(He can't make progress alone, so he
takes Se Chan to the video room.)
Do you see my goosebumps?
What is this? What's wrong?
- I'm not lying...
- Did you find something?
(He makes a fuss as he shares the video.)
I'll share it with him because
I think he's going to die early.
You think I'm going to die early?
Close the door.
(Se Chan finds out the truth
through the video.)
Jae Suk.
Can you share a hint with me?
Right. Can you tell us something?
Did you find that?
- This is...
- Let me see it.
(Like Haha, Jae Suk decides that
this is too hard to do alone.)
- What is that?
- Did you watch the video?
(He shares it with Ji Hyo and Suk Jin.)
- The two of you can go watch it.
- Let's go watch it.
Where do we have to go?
Do you remember the room I was in?
- Go watch it.
- Let's go.
Hurry.
(They find out everything
thanks to Jae Suk's help.)
- We can write two at a time, right?
- Yes.
I'll write 4 and 5.
We must write the name of the person
we want to find out, right?
(Haha uses the photos he got earlier now.)
The person who's been acting weird.
(Ji Suk Jin)
(Ji Suk Jin?)
Numbers 4 and 5.
(Haha wrote Ji Suk Jin down
for numbers 4 and 5.)
I just have a hunch.
Which one is mine?
(If Suk Jin's the ghost, the number
of his doll is important.)
(Ji Suk Jin)
(What is the result?)
(Suk Jin's doll isn't 4 or 5.)
(Sighing)
I need to watch what I say.
Okay.
(Ji Hyo begins searching
after watching the video.)
(Is there something inside these dolls?)
(Beep!)
So Hee hasn't been getting along
with her homeroom teacher.
That teacher has a brother.
"That teacher has a brother?"
(She found out there's
a voice message hint by chance.)
(It's a message that seems to be
pointing at someone.)
(Jae Suk is searching another room.)
My gosh.
So Hee was jealous of the student
in first place,
and their birthday was
in the spring or summer.
But So Hee forgot,
so they got into a fight.
So Hee was jealous of the student
in first place...
(It seems to be about Kim So Hee,
the artist he saw during the day.)
(Jae Suk looks nervous.)
(He hurries to the mailbox.)
- I can try it right now, right?
- Yes.
I need to find mine first.
(Despite the unusual situation,
he decides to find his doll first.)
Numbers 1 and 3.
(Jae Suk writes his name down
for 1 and 3.)
I'm going to find out if
one of these is mine.
- Where do I need to go?
- The first floor...
Okay.
(He can find out the results
in the doll theater.)
Gosh, this is scary.
This is really scary.
(What are the results?)
What?
What is this?
(The doll is making a circle.)
(That means Jae Suk's doll is
number 1 or 3.)
So my doll is either number 1 or 3?
- Did you put it in?
- What?
- Did you put yours in?
- Yes.
I put two in,
and the doll with my name was
making a circle.
- Really?
- I put in 1 and 3.
That means number 1 or 3 is yours.
My doll is either number 1 or 3.
- Right.
- It's 1 or 3.
It's either that doll or this doll.
- Right. You're right.
- One of these is mine.
- You guessed well.
- I did, didn't I?
- It worked out perfectly.
- Yes.
(As a result, the probability of
finding Jae Suk's doll got higher.)
I wonder where mine is.
(But they haven't found the real
owners of the other dolls.)
The first judgment stand
is about to start.
Please gather in the doll house.
(The doll house judgment stand they
heard about in the video is open.)
- It's on the second floor.
- Wait for me.
- Okay.
- I'm scared.
Isn't this place scary?
Want to trade with me?
- Okay. We can trade.
- Okay.
Why am I the only one in the dark?
There's something here.
Where is it?
Where's the judgment stand?
(The 1st judgment stand has opened.)
There is one ghost. Who is it?
What is this?
Oh, my.
- What is this?
- What's that doll? Is that Chucky?
(They walk towards it as if possessed.)
- What is this?
- What is that?
What is this?
(The doll display cabinet
is completely empty.)
- What is this?
- What is it?
What is that?
This is incredible.
So this is the story?
Suk Jin's reaction was weird.
I agree.
He's been like that from the start.
- What is it?
- Right.
"So this is the story?"
The video was so scary.
So Min.
(Surprised)
(Laughing)
(They suddenly hear someone laughing.)
I guess you want to avoid being cursed.
Then you came to the right place.
Welcome to the doll house,
the only place you can avoid being cursed.
(The place where you avoid
the curse, the doll house)
There are three judgments
to avoid the curse.
You must succeed before
the last judgment...
that will be held at 8 p.m.
This is driving me crazy.
What happens if you fail?
(What happens if you fail?)
The six humans will receive
a horrible penalty...
due to the doll's curse.
I'll give you your first chance now.
The three people who are sure
which dolls are theirs...
can place them on the top floor
with their names on them.
Then put the remaining four dolls
on the lower floor.
Once you close the door,
the judgment will start.
If the three dolls found
their rightful owners,
the humans will win right away.
- All three must be correct.
- However,
if even one of them is wrong,
you would have foolishly lost your chance.
Okay.
Okay. Put in your dolls right now.
The game will start now.
Let's start the first game.
- Is that yours?
- It's not that...
Yours is either 1 or 3,
- Right.
- so you can put yours in.
- But it's number four.
- I'll put mine in.
Yours is one of these, so put it in.
Yours is either 1 or 3.
(He puts number 3, the doll he was
holding, on the judgment stand.)
Next...
- Did anyone put my name in?
- I didn't put yours in.
- Then why was there an X?
- Why was yours an X?
I put in my name for these two.
- Which numbers?
- These two.
I got rid of two from
the list of possibilities.
So mine is among the remaining ones.
We have to guess for this round.
- We do.
- Put it in.
- This one's scary.
- Go with number one.
- Number one?
- We won't get it right. Put it in.
We won't get it right. Just guess.
Both numbers 1 and 3 belong...
to Jae Suk anyway.
That's right. Number one probably
belongs to Jae Suk...
Let's choose number seven then.
- That's right.
- Let's choose between 6 or 7.
Do you want to try So Min's doll?
- I like pink.
- Choose pink then.
- Pink?
- The pink doll might be right.
Se Chan, didn't you try my doll?
No, I didn't.
What number is your doll?
Me?
This one probably isn't it.
- It's not my doll?
- It's not.
- Why?
- I'll tell you later.
Are you going to tell me later?
Wait, this isn't it.
- Try this. Try number seven.
- He thinks this isn't it.
- Haha can't tell us anything,
- Let's just try putting this in.
but he thinks this isn't it.
- But seriously, are you...
- Wait a minute!
- Why is he doing this to me?
- You're lying, aren't you?
- I might be lying.
- Wait a minute.
Hey, he might be lying.
I might be lying, but trust me.
- For about 4 or 5 times, he...
- He told me quietly.
"Jong Kook,
I don't think it's number six."
Ask me in the next game.
- The ghost...
- Yes.
- that's in here...
- He just wrote it down.
will surely try to confuse us.
That's right.
- We need to find the doll.
- I think it's my doll.
Let's put it in.
(But Haha already checked
Suk Jin's doll.)
(Haha was suspicious of Suk Jin
and wrote his name for 4 and 5.)
(Suk Jin's doll wasn't among...)
(doll number 4 and doll number 5.)
(Even after checking that,)
(he didn't say anything.)
- Suk Jin, put it in.
- Hey.
- One person should put it in.
- Let Suk Jin put it in.
- Will you put it in?
- But this is...
- You will get an "X."
- The odds are against us right now.
Realistically, it is difficult.
We can't get it on the first try, right?
If Suk Jin is right,
- Haha is strange.
- his doll will be the answer.
- That's right.
- But all three of them must be...
- right for us to know it's right.
- That's right.
They won't tell us
whether each one is right or not.
They won't tell us one by one, right?
Actually, this is...
Have you made your choice?
- Yes.
I hope everyone won't regret this choice.
We will start judging now.
What will happen?
To be honest, the odds are very low.
Yes, very low.
(Will there be another plot twist?)
Okay, the judging has ended.
Let's see what the result is.
- It must be wrong.
- Jae Suk.
Open the door immediately
and check the result.
- Take a look.
- It's definitely wrong.
Could it be right?
(What's the result of their first choice?)
That's right.
- Here.
- That surprised me!
- We failed.
- It's wrong.
- That's right then.
- We can't do much now.
- They won't tell us how many dolls.
Kim Jong Kook, out.
- He's out?
(Why is Jong Kook suddenly out?)
- Why?
- Doll number five is broken.
- What is happening?
- It was Jong Kook's doll.
- Why?
- Did someone do it?
- Where did doll number five go?
- Doll number five got broken.
- Think about it.
- Someone did it.
- Why?
- My doll was number five.
Hurry up and think!
- Why is Kim Jong Kook out?
- Why is he out?
- Hurry up and think!
- Am I out?
Wait. No!
(They failed the first judgment.)
- Were you surprised to see...
- Who cut up the belly of the doll?
the ripped doll?
The ghost did this then.
Whenever you fail each judgment,
someone's doll designated by
the ghost will be torn to pieces.
So if we get it wrong...
If you don't want to be eliminated,
choose very carefully from now on.
Jong Kook's doll was doll number five.
I found all of them out.
I know the numbers now.
If we go there, we will know the answer.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Yes?
- You're acting strange.
- Se Chan is acting kind of strange.
- Come here.
- This is driving me insane.
- Tell me.
- It's not Se Chan.
- I'm telling the truth.
- Both of you are acting strange.
- They're really acting strange.
- Haha is acting strange.
- Haha.
- No, both of you are.
- It's either one of them.
- Okay.
- Okay, way to corner people.
- Both of them are acting strange.
- Eliminating Jong Kook...
- Yes?
means that this person is weak.
The ghost, I mean.
- That's right.
- Yes.
But everyone is weak except Jong Kook.
- Isn't that right?
- That's right.
So the ghost is among the six of us.
That's obvious.
- You sold Jong Kook out.
- Hey.
- That's obvious.
- I explained it to you.
If you don't have any hints,
it will be no use now.
- Let's go. Spread out.
- Yes.
We don't have time.
- Dolls number 6 and 7...
- We don't have time.
Jae Suk,
I should find your doll, right?
- Make sure you find mine.
- Your odds will become higher...
- that way.
- Make sure you find mine.
I should find your doll, right?
- Haha, isn't that right?
- It's not doll number 5 or 6.
I have a bad feeling about today.
I think we should definitely
put in doll numbers 6 and 1.
Sure, put those two in then.
If I do and I get an "O,"
Jae Suk's doll will definitely be
doll number one.
- It definitely will be.
- That's right.
Jae Suk's doll will probably be
doll number one.
Your doll and mine won't be number one.
That's not right. We don't know yet.
What if I put in numbers 6 and 1
and it says I'm wrong?
This is right. Just go.
Are you the ghost?
Just go.
- Are you the ghost?
- Why are you suddenly suspicious?
You keep confusing me.
It's strange that you showed me
the video over there.
You're not the ghost, are you?
Please make it clear.
- What do you mean?
- Gosh.
You're joking. I'm going to
put in doll numbers 6 and 1.
- Okay, numbers 6 and 1.
- Jae Suk for 6 and 1.
After that, let's have a meeting
and put in my numbers.
Here.
Let's go.
(The two of them head
to the doll theater.)
(If they get an "O,"
Jae Suk will be doll number 1.)
(If they get an "X,"
Jae Suk will be doll number 3.)
We will get an "O."
- Isn't it right?
- It's an "O."
See?
(The doll is making an "O" sign.)
(They're sure
which doll is Jae Suk's now.)
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk's doll is definitely
doll number 1.)
I'm scared.
(He's looking for hints,
not knowing they found his doll.)
I told you.
Why are you getting angry?
So Hee was jealous of
the top student in school.
I don't think the top student
will run a personal video channel...
even if it becomes popular.
(Not running a personal video
channel means that...)
It's either Ji Hyo, So Min, or me.
(It's either Ji Hyo, So Min, or me.)
(What?)
I got goosebumps.
(With this single hint,)
(the possibilities get narrowed down
by a lot.)
(Besides those who have YouTube channels,)
(who's left out of these 7?)
(Jae Suk, So Min, Ji Hyo)
(Are one of these three the ghost?)
- Gosh!
- Why?
(He runs quickly because it seems
like Jae Suk found something out.)
- Where are you?
- Jae Suk, where are you?
No, it's nothing.
- What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
Where is Jae Suk?
(Quiet)
Jae Suk...
Jae Suk, what is it?
It's nothing.
I need to find my doll.
I don't understand the rules right now.
(Fortunately, Ji Hyo went on her way
without being suspicious.)
Let's find the envelopes first.
(According to his hint,
one of these three is the ghost.)
- Let's see what you found.
- Gosh.
- Why?
- People get surprised...
whenever I say, "What are you doing?"
That's not it. I have many hints,
but I don't have any photos.
- We don't have any photos.
- Tell me then.
- Haha.
- Gather around.
I have so many hints,
but I don't have any photos.
- What kind of hints do you have?
- Let's have a meeting together.
I also have two hints.
Let me see.
The ghost is doll number one.
- What?
- The ghost is doll number one.
- What did you say?
The ghost is doll number one.
That's not true.
The hints aren't like that.
- No, they're like that.
- The ghost is doll number one?
No way, he's acting strange.
(It must be different
from what So Min had heard.)
- I'm not going to talk to him.
- It's doll number one.
- I'm not going to talk to you.
- What are your hints?
- Are you doll number one?
- The hints aren't like that.
You're doll number one.
- You're doll number one, right?
Doll number one?
Number one?
The ghost is doll number one.
- The hints aren't like that.
- They are.
They're described in detail.
I know because I tried it.
Yes, so did I.
They aren't like that.
They're like "So Hee's something..."
- I know another one.
- The hints aren't like that.
(The hints aren't like that?)
Why are you running away
as soon as I said that?
I think I know who it is.
Who is it?
Don't you think it's Jae Suk?
I think it's either Jae Suk or Ji Hyo.
Yes, it's either one of them.
They kept driving us into a corner.
What about So Hee's boyfriend?
He likes soccer.
- So Hee's boyfriend likes soccer?
- Yes.
(So Hee had a boyfriend?)
(So Hee has a boyfriend.)
(Recently, their relationship went sour.)
(The first hint So Min found was
a hint about So Hee's boyfriend.)
(So Hee's best friend...)
(had a hard time trying to please
So Hee who is very sensitive.)
(Soon after that, she found a hint
about So Hee's best friend.)
(Jae Suk's hint was about a friend
who is the top student in school.)
(Boyfriend, best friend,
a friend who is the top student)
(All of the hints weren't pointing
to one person.)
I don't know what the connection is.
What's the connection
between her boyfriend, friend,
- and the friend she was jealous of.
- What?
What's the connection
between the people around So Hee?
So Hee has a boyfriend.
Her boyfriend really likes soccer,
so she didn't like the fact...
that he didn't spend time with her
during lunch.
A boyfriend?
(A boyfriend who likes soccer?)
(Jae Suk is also confused
by the appearance of a new person.)
I thought it was either Ji Hyo or So Min.
(Jae Suk is also confused
by the appearance of a new person.)
So Hee had a very bad relationship
with her homeroom teacher.
That homeroom teacher wears glasses
and he's quite conservative.
(Homeroom teacher?)
Take a look now.
Homeroom teacher, best friend,
boyfriend, and the friend who is
always the top student in school.
Did someone among these four kill So Hee?
(Among these people, they must find
the ghost who killed So Hee.)
(Each of these people is
one of So Hee's acquaintances.)
(The ghost is among them!)
(They gather around to share
the hints they each found.)
- You're gathering hints, right?
- You startled me.
- I think it's Haha.
- Jae Suk.
- Come here.
- I think it's Haha.
Right now, people are...
The ghost is right here.
- There's a ghost here.
- The ghost is right here.
- A ghost is definitely here.
- Yes, definitely. Who is it?
According to the hint I found...
and the information I gathered,
I think the ghost is
either So Min or Ji Hyo.
It could also be Suk Jin or Jae Suk.
Me?
- That's what I got.
- I have no idea.
Does anyone have a photo envelope?
- No.
- No one has it, right?
Then let's cut one open.
- Here?
- Yes.
- What?
- A doll?
- Let's cut one open.
- It's not a bad idea.
We can exclude the dolls
we are certain about.
- Shall we cut that doll open?
- I want to cut that doll open.
- Good idea.
- That doll.
Why this one?
Are you nervous because you are the ghost?
- No, I'm not the ghost.
- Then it shouldn't be a problem.
My name might be inside.
Then it can't be helped.
(Haha doesn't want to cut open his doll.)
My name might be inside.
I am suspicious about one doll.
I want to cut open doll number one.
(Don't they know for sure
that doll number 1 is Jae Suk?)
- No.
- Then I will be eliminated.
It needs to be 1 of the 3 dolls
in the judgment stand.
- You punk.
- All right.
- You are suspicious.
You are of no help to us humans.
- Shall I cut mine open?
- Go ahead.
(Haha gets cornered
in his attempt to corner Jae Suk.)
- Cut it open.
- The judgment stand has opened.
Isn't the timing so suspicious?
The judgment stand has opened.
- Isn't the timing so suspicious?
- It's suspicious.
(The 2nd judgment stand opens
when Haha gets cornered.)
- It's suspicious.
- I told you that it isn't me.
- It's not me.
The judgment stand opened
when we tried to cut his doll open.
You are framing me.
Since the judgment stand opened,
someone will get eliminated.
(They need to put 3 dolls
in the judgment stand.)
- My doll goes in no matter what.
- That's right.
- How about Suk Jin's?
- Let's put mine in as well.
All right.
My doll is the only one we are sure about.
(Number 1, Jae Suk's doll,
goes into the judgment stand.)
I will try this one.
I know it's among numbers 2, 3, 6, and 7.
Choose among numbers 2, 3, 6, and 7.
(Number 1, Jae Suk)
(Number 7, Suk Jin)
Let's say...
- Haha, which doll is yours?
- This is scary.
Number three?
Let's put in Haha's doll.
- Okay.
- Put in number three.
(Haha's doll goes
into the judgment stand as well.)
- Okay.
- Put in number three.
Other dolls go in the bottom.
Haha, Suk Jin, and I put in our dolls.
(Number 1 belongs to Jae Suk.)
If we think about...
- the probability...
- Someone will die.
That's right.
But I doubt you will die.
It will be a disaster if Jae Suk dies.
- Number one is Jae Suk's doll.
- I think Jae Suk will die.
I think Jae Suk will die.
- He knows so much.
- You know,
there must be rules
behind the elimination process.
- They won't just kill anyone.
- The ghost decided on the order.
(The ghost decided on the order.)
Have you made your choice?
- Yes.
I hope everyone won't regret this choice.
(I hope everyone won't regret
this choice.)
We will start judging now.
- This is so scary.
- I know.
This is so scary.
(If all 3 dolls have the rightful owners,)
(the humans will win.)
(The ghost must be watching anxiously.)
Okay, the judging has ended.
Let's see what the result is.
- Someone got eliminated.
- Please.
Open the door immediately
and check the result.
(Did the three of them choose
the right doll?)
Who is it? Who died?
Which doll is on the floor?
(They failed.)
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
- Yoo Jae Suk, out.
- See? Jae Suk died.
See?
I told you that number one is Jae Suk.
- The ghost is someone weak.
- I knew it.
The ghost is someone weak.
This happened because I know the most.
- Right now...
- Hey.
- Find the ghost no matter what.
- Okay.
Do it for the humans.
- Only the weak ones remain.
- The ghost must be someone weak.
You wasted your second chance as well.
You must be quite stupid.
The last judgment remains,
so please take caution.
(There is 1 judgment
and 5 dolls remaining.)
(There are 4 normal dolls
and 1 cursed doll.)
(The humans are at a disadvantage
since the Grand Award Duo is out.)
- It's Haha.
- Find the ghost no matter what.
Okay.
- Do it for the humans.
- Only the weak ones remain.
The ghost must be someone weak.
Jong Kook and Jae Suk are out.
(Haha is suspected of being the ghost.)
Me?
Let's cut a doll open.
Let's do it.
- I can't believe Haha.
- Come on.
- Let's cut a doll open!
- Do it.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
and cut the loser's doll open.
- Cut your doll open.
- It might contain your name,
not mine.
This doll might not belong to Haha.
- It might belong to you.
- Cut it open.
- I am okay.
- It should be okay with you.
Really? Then I will cut it open.
- A human might die.
- It might not belong to you.
Let's cut it open.
- Let's cut number three open.
- You didn't trust me.
You cornered me until the end.
Come here.
- Cut it open.
- Let's do it.
- We have no choice.
- Really?
- I am sorry.
- I can't watch it.
If this doll belongs to the ghost,
the humans will win.
(If number 3 belongs to the ghost,
the humans will win.)
- It's out.
- Really? Whose name is it?
(Does number 3 contain
the ghost's name tag?)
If this doll belongs to the ghost,
the humans will win.
(Does number 3 contain
the ghost's name tag?)
- It's out.
- Really? Whose name is it?
- Suk Jin.
(The name tag belongs to Suk Jin.)
(Me?)
That's so funny.
Suk Jin, I am sorry.
Ji Suk Jin, out.
(The announcement
drives a nail in his coffin.)
(Suk Jin eliminated himself.)
That's so funny.
- I cut myself open.
- This is ridiculous.
I cut myself open.
(Suk Jin Scissorhands is devastated.)
How did this happen to us?
- Here it is.
- Give us the doll.
- Hey!
- Throw it.
I sacrificed myself,
so hurry up and find the ghost!
He picked up the scissors and cut open...
his own doll.
- For goodness' sake.
- What?
Did you cut a doll open?
The doll I cut open happened to be mine.
- It was number three, right?
- Yes.
I cut number three open.
- Suk Jin.
- I did it with scissors.
The older ones got eliminated.
- You are right.
- Are they having a party...
- without us?
- Seriously.
- They are by themselves.
- The older ones.
(Only 4 dolls remain.)
I have an idea.
The ghost is among us, right?
Come on.
You're the ghost.
- It has to be Haha.
- I think you are the ghost.
This is insane.
We just need to find our dolls.
Let's find our dolls.
We will win if we find our dolls
and put them in the judgment stand.
They made the decision without me.
- Se Chan.
- Haha.
- Let's look for them.
- I am sorry, Haha.
- Give us proof if you are human.
- Come here.
Come here!
(Who is the ghost that killed So Hee
and cursed a doll?)
How is it that I didn't find
a single photo envelope?
(The members disperse
in search of a photo envelope.)
(Surprised)
(For the first time,)
I found it.
(Ji Hyo found a photo envelope.)
(Among numbers 2, 4, 6, and 7
is Ji Hyo's doll.)
Numbers 4 and 6.
(She chose numbers 4 and 6.)
(Is Ji Hyo's doll among numbers 4 or 6?)
What?
(The doll's answer is "O.")
Either number 4 or 6 is...
my doll.
(Either number 4 or 6 is Ji Hyo's doll.)
Se Chan, I wish I could find
a photo envelope.
I just can't find it.
Both Ji Hyo and I
haven't been able to check...
since we never found any.
Do you know about anyone else's doll...
- other than Jae Suk's?
- No.
Do you have any idea
which doll might be yours?
(So Min keeps fishing for information.)
But the current situation...
(Ji Hyo doesn't make an effort
to share information.)
(She is searching fearlessly on her own.)
(She goes through the documents
in the principal's office.)
I used to be really good at finding hints.
(She complains that she can't seem
to find hints.)
These days, my skills...
My skills...
(She found something.)
What is this?
"The list of award winners
in Running High School?"
(The list of award winners
in Running High School)
(It's a list of award winners
in Running High School.)
(The record shows students
who won an award from 2000 to 2005.)
Third place.
Participation award.
(She looks for information
that could offer a hint.)
Kim So Hee?
(Kim So Hee is on the list.)
(She found a record of Kim So Hee.)
(What secret is hidden here?)
I am scared.
(To find a hint,
Haha came to the doll club room.)
(He searches the club room.)
Haha, we found a hint.
What hint?
- You are the ghost for sure.
- Why?
(You are the ghost for sure.)
(Is Haha the ghost?)
(Which hint is hidden
in the doll So Min brought?)
Haha is the ghost.
(Haha is the ghost.)
(For goodness' sake.)
What?
- Haha.
- Are you my fan?
- It's a hint.
Haha is the ghost.
- See?
- That's your voice.
(She made a hint to tease Haha.)
(A moment ago)
(Recording)
(She expertly created a fake hint.)
Haha, we found a hint.
So Min is a fool.
- It's you. A hint told me...
- What is this?
- What is it?
- That startled me.
(Haha found something!)
I just found it.
(A red diary?)
It's a diary.
- No way.
- How did you find it?
- Over there...
- I can't believe it.
So you aren't the ghost?
Once we read the diary...
- Prove that you aren't the ghost.
- Go away. You might be it.
- I'm not the ghost.
- I'm not the ghost either.
(Does the diary contain a hint
on the ghost's identity?)
"I stayed up for three nights
to prepare..."
"for the National Doll Olympics
that will take place in two weeks."
"I stayed up for three nights
to prepare..."
"for the National Doll Olympics
that will take place in two weeks."
"Because of that person,
I always missed the Gold Prize."
"But that person was sick
and couldn't prepare much."
(I have a feeling
that I will win the Gold Prize.)
"Let's go! Let's work hard
for another night."
(Let's go! Let's work hard
for another night.)
"It's the Silver Prize again."
"My friends whisper
about how I always come in second."
(My friends whisper
about how I always come in second.)
I feel even more pathetic...
because you consoled me and said
that second place is good too.
If it weren't for you,
I would have come in first.
I have a hint about the first place.
This is about the first place.
So Hee was...
No. It was written by the second place.
- It's the second place's diary.
- It's So Hee's diary.
(It's So Hee's diary.)
(The master of handmade dolls,
Kim So Hee died due to a curse.)
(In 2002, she won the Silver Prize
in the National Doll Olympics.)
(A long time ago)
(So Hee was a member
of the doll club back in school.)
(The red diary contains accounts
from her school days.)
(They hurriedly read the next page.)
May 5, 2003. Monday.
It wasn't a school day,
but I went because I felt trapped.
That person was making a doll.
Even from a distance,
the doll looked perfect.
"Even from a distance,
the doll looked perfect."
"And that person looked ecstatic."
"I really wanted that doll."
I really wanted that doll.
So I acted without thinking.
(So I acted without thinking.)
I hit that person's head
and brought the doll.
(I hit that person's head
and brought the doll.)
If that person dies,
can I keep the doll?
(So Hee killed the person
who always took 1st place.)
"That person died.
There were no witnesses."
"I don't need to return the doll."
"I went through that person's locker..."
"and found a notebook containing
doll designs."
And found a notebook containing
doll designs.
These poor things lost their owner.
I will turn them into dolls.
She stole the designs.
(She stole the designs.)
May 9, 2003. Friday.
I submitted that person's doll.
I am already excited because I think
I will win the Gold Prize.
May 19, 2003. Monday.
Gold Prize! It's the Gold Prize!
I finally did it!
"It's the Gold Prize!
I finally did it!"
(The Gold Prize winner of 2003?)
(Kim So Hee VIP Doll Exhibition)
(Kim So Hee, the pride
of the Korean doll industry)
(2003, Gold Prize winner
of the 32nd Asia Doll Fair)
(2000, Silver Prize)
(2002, Silver Prize)
(Until 2002,
So Hee only won the Silver Prize.)
(After she killed the 1st place in 2003)
(At the 32nd Asia Doll Fair,
Kim So Hee Wins the Gold Prize.)
(At the Dollmaker Contest of 2004,
(At the World Doll Expo of 2007,
Kim So Hee Wins the Gold Prize.)
(At the World Doll Expo of 2008,
(So Hee stole the 1st place's ideas
to become a master dollmaker.)
(So Hee was the jealous 2nd place
who killed the 1st place.)
(So Hee's collection was made
of stolen ideas.)
(So Hee's diary continues.)
- "To celebrate Children's Day..."
- "I went to my school..."
"for a talent donation."
"When I entered the classroom
full of memories,"
"that person was standing there
with a bloodied face."
That person appeared as a ghost.
To celebrate Children's Day,
I went to my school...
for a talent donation.
"When I entered the classroom
full of memories,"
(In the classroom full of memories)
that person was standing there...
with a bloodied face.
I was fine all along.
Why is this happening now?
I keep hearing that person's voice.
No, these are my dolls.
You went ahead and died.
Stop it already.
You are dead anyway.
Stop tormenting me.
(Guilt brought on
visual and auditory hallucinations.)
(In the end, she died
because of the 1st place's ghost.)
(That's the last entry in the diary.)
What? That's the last one.
You startled me.
What are you doing?
The first place died and became the ghost.
(So Hee's 1st place friend was the ghost.)
Haha, the first place doesn't have
a YouTube channel.
(Haha, the first place doesn't have
a YouTube channel.)
(Jae Suk found a hint
about the 1st place.)
(The 1st place won't run
a YouTube channel.)
(So Min found a hint about the 1st place.)
(The 1st place's name had a letter S.)
The first place So Hee was jealous of...
(The 1st place was born
in spring or summer.)
(If you exclude Jae Suk,)
(Ji Hyo or So Min is
the 1st place and the ghost.)
(Ghost candidate 1, Jeon So Min)
(Suspicion 1. She kept acting like
she didn't know the rules.)
(Did she feign ignorance
to avoid suspicion?)
(Suspicion 2. She kept
grilling people for information.)
(Suspicion 3. She suspected
one member with enthusiasm.)
(Ghost candidate 2, Song Ji Hyo)
(Suspicion 1. She followed
the members around.)
(Ji Hyo lingered
when Jae Suk tried to be alone.)
(She even eavesdropped on the members.)
(She was more intent
on checking everyone's location.)
(Suspicion 2. So Hee died
upon seeing Ji Hyo.)
(So Hee said something mysterious
as she pointed toward Ji Hyo.)
Haha, So Hee died
right after she saw Ji Hyo.
Isn't it strange?
Maybe this hint is fake.
The first place's name has the letter S.
Jeon So Min. It isn't Ji Hyo.
Song Ji Hyo.
- Her name has an S.
- Jeon So Min and Song Ji Hyo.
- You pieced everything together.
- Good job.
- I am sorry. You aren't the ghost.
- No, I'm not.
Why did you kill So Hee?
- Why did you kill her?
Start talking.
It isn't me.
- No way.
- Let's go upstairs.
- This is our last chance.
- I know.
That's So Min's handwriting.
(Which one of them is the 1st place
So Hee was jealous of?)
Listen to me.
Sit down.
In conclusion, So Hee was the culprit.
She was the killer.
- What?
- Here she comes.
She is bringing something.
- What is that? Let's see it.
- It's a list of award winners.
Is it a decisive hint?
Let's see it together.
Hold on. Let's analyze this first.
- This is...
- Math, art, art, PE,
music, track...
How did Lee Kwang Soo win
the Gold Prize in math?
- No way. It's a lie.
- This is false information.
- Seriously.
(He can barely memorize the times table.)
- Math, art, art, PE,
- Check out the next page.
track, music...
I see "Dollmaking."
Gold Prize, Kim So Hee. Here it is.
I saw the name too.
(Kim So Hee won the Gold Prize in 2003.)
What?
Gold Prize, Kim So Hee.
It's the Silver Prize again.
It's what we read in the diary.
The first place must be Jin Sung.
Here it is.
She won the Silver Prize then.
This kid kept winning
the Gold Prize. It's this kid.
- Jin Sung.
- Yoon Jin Sung is the ghost.
She must have won the Silver Prize before.
(From 2003 on, So Hee won the Gold Prize.)
(But Yoon Jin Sung won
the Gold Prize before then.)
(Because of that person,
I always missed the Gold Prize.)
(She was incredibly jealous
of that person.)
(Gold Prize, Yoon Jin Sung)
- Jin Sung.
- Yoon Jin Sung is the ghost.
There must be something about the name.
Yoon Jin Sung. Jeon So Min.
Yoon Jin Sung.
(The unfamiliar name
leaves them flustered.)
(Between So Min and Ji Hyo,
who is Yoon Jin Sung?)
Hurry up.
(They have ten minutes
until the last judgment.)
Four dolls remain. Among them...
(They don't know
who these dolls belong to.)
This is complicated.
(They have used
all the easily hidden envelopes.)
I want to find a photo envelope.
I want to try putting them in.
(With all three older members out,
Haha has a big responsibility.)
(He uses his short stature
to search everywhere.)
What?
(He finds a hidden folder.)
(Movie synopsis collection)
Pandora, Na'vi...
(It's a collection of synopses
the movie club used.)
Then came "Avatar."
("Ode to My Father")
"Ode to My Father."
What?
This is so scary.
This is incredible.
(He hears the announcement
of the last judgment.)
This is your last chance.
(The last judgment stand has opened.)
I hope you succeed and catch the ghost.
Shall we begin the final selection?
Are you the ghost or not?
I am not the ghost.
(Haha picks Ji Hyo.)
What is it?
Why don't you just show me?
- What is it?
- All right.
- It was torn.
("Ode to My Father," Synopsis)
(A synopsis that's torn?)
"So Hee, the top student
of the department of dance,"
(So Hee?)
"is loved by everyone
in her department..."
"due to her outstanding talent
and kind heart."
"On the other hand,
So Hee's best friend, Jin Sung..."
(Jin Sung?)
"makes a wish to let her enter
the competition on the stairs..."
"where a legend says that
if the 29th stair appears,"
"her wish will come true."
(Jin Sung climbs the stairs
while making a wish.)
This is the synopsis of "Wishing Stairs."
(This is the synopsis
of "Wishing Stairs.")
(They look up the movie right away.)
The actress who plays Jin Sung.
Who is it? Did you play Jin Sung?
(Song Ji Hyo as Jin Sung?)
("Whispering Corridors 3, Wishing Stairs")
(Director, Cast)
(Song Ji Hyo as Jin Sung)
(Who is it? Did you play Jin Sung?)
Who is it? Did you play Jin Sung?
(Yoon Jin Sung,)
(the person the humans
have been desperately looking for)
(Song Ji Hyo)
- My gosh.
- It must be her.
- I got goosebumps.
- That must be why...
(A movie where the 29th stair
grants a wish)
("Whispering Corridors 3, Wishing Stairs")
(And its main character, Yoon Jin Sung)
I used to be really good at finding hints.
Maybe it's because I became a ghost.
(Maybe it's because I became a ghost.)
(May 2003)
(The master of handmade dolls of
Running High School, Yoon Jin Sung)
(Kim So Hee was always in her shadow
as the forever runner-up.)
(An accident caused
by her sense of inferiority)
(The forever runner-up, So Hee,
ended up killing Jin Sung.)
(So Hee took...)
(all of Jin Sung's dolls.)
(Jin Sung who was wrongfully killed
became a ghost...)
(and cursed the dolls she made.)
(And Artist Kim So Hee...)
(who suffered from hallucinations
all her life ever since then...)
(saw Yoon Jin Sung.)
(Jin Sung got a chance
to take back the dolls she made.)
(She started to confuse the humans
who got in her way during the race.)
(When someone puts in the photo envelope,)
(she handed in new photos
in a new envelope...)
(using that person's name,
causing confusion.)
(She's been handing in
the envelopes with different names.)
(And the secret behind the order
of people who were eliminated)
(The 29th stair from the movie...)
(that makes your wish come true)
(Jin Sung could stick
the figure of her next target...)
(on the 29th stair.)
I should eliminate
the two most annoying ones.
Who do I think is the ghost?
Song Ji Hyo?
(Song Ji Hyo?)
(The ghost's identity
is finally revealed.)
(Song Ji Hyo was Yoon Jin Sung.)
(But it's not the humans' victory yet.)
It's either number 4 or 6.
- I know. We need to cut one open.
- Which one is it?
(They can only win
if they open Ji Hyo's doll.)
- Hold on. I'm so dizzy.
- Which one is it?
I'm so dizzy.
You wrote either number 4 or 6, right?
- But I could've made that up.
- Before that...
It depends on whether
she's telling a lie or not.
There could be a twist.
- Do we have any more hints?
- No, that's all we have.
Why didn't I find more hints?
So what if I'm the ghost?
That's right.
It's better just to cut one open.
We have a 50-percent chance.
If we put in all 3,
we'll have only a 30-percent chance.
Since I'm holding doll number six,
I'll cut open this one. Okay?
- Okay.
- If Ji Hyo's name is in there,
- then we'll win.
- We'll win.
- Let's do it.
- Cut it open.
- Then cut open number 6.
- I'll just cut open number 6.
- It's better to cut it open.
- That's right. Let's cut it open.
- I'm sure it's number six.
- Hurry up and cut it open.
- Hurry up. Cut it open.
- Cut it open.
- Look at her. She's so scary.
- She's so scary.
She is Jin Sung, right?
She is. I just got the chills.
When I looked it up...
Cut it open.
We should cut number six open.
(They start cutting open doll number 6.)
(And Ji Hyo has a mysterious look
on her face.)
(Whose doll is doll number 6?)
- I got her!
- I told you!
It's hers, right?
(Song Ji Hyo)
Oh, no. The humans made it.
(The humans made it.)
(The humans take the victory.)
- You're so scary.
- You said you're not the ghost!
(The Empty Head Mystery Club
caught the ghost in the end.)
(Running High School's
master of handmade dolls,)
(Yoon Jin Sung loses to the humans.)
- Everyone, today's race...
- It's so scary.
is about Jin Sung
who was wrongfully killed by So Hee.
The ghost of Jin Sung
wanted to curse the humans too.
Jin Sung was the role Ji Hyo played
in "Wishing Stairs."
- It's Jin Sung?
- Yes.
Didn't we sing Jin Sung's song
on the bus earlier?
- Oh, my.
- What?
"Child, don't run."
- Me too.
- We sang Jin Sung's song.
(While teasing Suk Jin on the bus,)
(they sang along to Jin Sung's song
by chance.)
What's that song?
(Jin Sung!)
(The real Jin Sung was nervous
by this unbelievable coincidence.)
(They sing Jin Sung's song
to celebrate their win.)
We were all surprised...
- because you sang Jin Sung's song.
- Right?
Because you talked about a period
of poverty, we sang that song.
Exactly.
(This is all thanks to Suk Jin
who mentioned a period of poverty.)
Ji Hyo was really scary earlier.
She was sitting on the bed
without even turning on the lights.
She was really scary
when she stared at you...
before cutting open your doll.
Oh, really?
It was as if she was saying,
"I'd love to see you try."
Her eyes were really scary. Right?
The last three remaining humans
realized the ghost was Song Ji Hyo.
They were inferring which doll was hers,
and they randomly cut open a doll,
and it happened to be Ji Hyo's.
(Simply put,
they won because they got lucky.)
Ji Hyo will receive the penalty...
of making a handmade doll
before going home today.
- I'm so jealous.
- A handmade doll?
- It's the worst.
- It really is the worst.
I'm supposed to make a doll?
(Just like that, after a long while...)
Why did she have to be so jealous
of Jin Sung?
It's okay to be a runner-up.
How could she kill her friend
just because she was a runner-up?
Just wait.
I'll be able to finish it today.
(But the master of handmade dolls
seems quite slow.)
Do you want to go home first?
(Do you want to go home first?)
It's not so easy to make a doll.
I'm done. I need to stitch this part
and tie a knot.
- I'm done!
- Please show it to us.
Ji Hyo, you cleared your penalty.
Good work.
(These guests are back after a long time.)
(Yoon Si Yoon, Hani, Park Ki Woong)
(Today is a couples' race.)
(The unchosen ones
will join Team Jae Suk.)
(He'll be Dr. Yoo who helps
improve their self-esteem.)
(The unchosen ones, come to me.)
He's a doctor?
The rest of you, come over here!
(Rebuilding their mentality)
I'll pick Jong Kook.
(The couple who decided to admit
their romance from today...)
(to the ones who can't admit it)
- You remember me, right?
- Yes.
(Next to the lovey-dovey couples,)
(Team Dr. Yoo seeks a chance
to turn the tables.)
(Can we switch partners?)
(I pick Si Yoon.)
(I'll trade Suk Jin with Si Yoon.)
(Their lives changed a little
with Dr. Yoo.)
(Will Dr. Yoo be able to give them
a new life?)
(Couples' Race, You Raise a Man Up)