(Summer has already arrived.)
I came out of the house after a long time.
(And there's a girl
who doesn't seem easy to deal with.)
I had cup noodles
before going to sleep last night.
So Min, you're the president
of the Running Game Club.
Today is the first get-together
of the game club.
You will open a group chat room...
and invite the members
to the get-together.
First, I'll meet the members...
of the club.
(Killer So Min has joined the chat.)
(Kwang Soo Is No Fool has joined the chat)
There's a nickname,
"Kwang Soo Is No Fool."
(Kwang Soo Is No Fool has joined the chat)
Who's that?
(Hurry and join the chat.)
Killing So Min?
(Dark Tornado has joined the chat.)
Who's Dark Tornado?
(I hate the nickname, "Dark Tornado.")
Dark Tornado?
He says he hates it. Has it begun?
(Push Ahead No Matter What
has joined the chat.)
Who's Push Ahead No Matter What?
That's just lame.
(Hello.)
(Kwang Soo Is No Fool,
you might be in trouble.)
Dark Tornado?
Kwang Soo Is No Fool.
Who's Pink Princess?
Who is Pink Princess?
Pink...
Hey, guys.
Let's meet in person.
(Hey, guys. Let's meet in person.)
Meet in person.
(ID, Pink Princess)
In person...
(Mustache Bomber has joined the chat.)
Mustache Bomber? It must be Haha.
I'm sure it's Haha.
Okay. I did it.
Hi.
(ID, Mustache Bomber)
Kwang Soo Is No Fool? Who's that?
(Guys, calm down.)
(I'm quite tough.)
(The 6 members of Running Game Club
have joined the chat.)
(But there's one member missing.)
(The last member is coming
with an extraordinary aura.)
Hello.
(Giggling)
So cute.
What's that thing?
This is my friend, Kwang Jjang.
I miss my friend, Kwang Jjang.
(The stuffed doll in the giraffe
costume is Kwang Jjang.)
Kwang Jjang.
What's this?
This is my friend, Kwang Jjang.
Say hello, Kwang Jjang.
Hello.
He's so cute.
I bet he's a close friend
if you brought him here.
But I lost my friend.
So I brought someone else
who's Kwang Jjang.
Right, Kwang Jjang?
(While a member has gone insane
after losing his friend...)
(All right.)
(Hello, guys.)
(I'm the president.)
Who's Touch and Explode?
(Touch and Explode has joined the chat.)
(Touch and Explode,
I really want to make you explode.)
(You're going to explode,
Touch and Explode.)
Explode?
(Let's meet in person,
Touch and Explode.)
They say I'll explode.
(All 7 members have joined the chat.)
(These are crocodile tears.)
(They suddenly start
criticizing each other.)
(He's a crybaby.)
(He goes around weeping.)
(Dark Tornado was born in 1966.)
What? It's up.
"Everyone, before our get-together..."
(Everyone, before our get-together,
we should be divided into teams.)
(Meet up with the members
you want as your teammates...)
(and come to the meeting place.)
Select the members you want
by chatting with them.
(They must choose the members
they want as teammates...)
(and begin the get-together.)
(Kwang Soo Is No Fool,
where are you now?)
(Who wants to team up with me?
Dark Tornado, you shouldn't cry.)
(I'm curious about the crybaby.
Let's meet in person.)
(I want you to use honorifics
and not ask common-sense questions.)
(They should team up with members
they like before the get-together.)
I'm curious about the other members.
I'm finally meeting with the members.
This is our first get-together.
I've never done this before.
I want to meet everyone.
Pink Princess,
Kwang Soo Is No Fool, and Dark Tornado...
I want to meet them.
I'm excited.
What would they be like?
(Even Dark Tornado is excited
to attend the meeting.)
Fasten your seat belt, Kwang Jjang.
Kwang Jjang.
Done. Let's go.
I don't know how they look.
I'm nervous to see
what they would be like.
(The meeting place is full
of board games...)
(loved by a lot of game fans.)
(ID, Dark Tornado,
ID, Push Ahead No Matter What)
- Let's sit.
- Are we the first ones to arrive?
- Have a seat.
- Push Ahead No Matter What.
Dark Tornado.
I'm so excited to meet the other members.
This is our first get-together, isn't it?
Yes. This is our first time.
(He's too into his stuffed doll.)
- I guess someone's coming.
- I heard something.
This is our first meeting,
so we should greet them standing up.
- Stay quiet.
- Welcome.
Did you open a cafe here?
No.
- Are you Pink Princess?
- Pink Princess?
I'm Pink Princess.
Yes, hello.
I'm Push Ahead No Matter What.
You are nothing like what I expected.
- You think?
- Yes.
The thing is, he used to be a gangster.
What do you mean, a gangster?
Are you from "Countryside Diary" then?
- Me?
- It looks like "Countryside Diary."
- I know.
- You're not sophisticated at all.
The way you're dressed.
Why are you holding that?
- It's his friend.
- This is my family.
- Seriously?
- This is my younger brother.
- Don't be afraid, Mini.
- Really?
It's all right.
They are good people.
If you do that for weeks,
you'll end up on "What on Earth."
You should change your hair color.
- Change it to yellow.
- If you...
- do this for weeks...
- Mini, don't be upset. It's okay.
Keep doing this for weeks
and give them a call.
- Then they will want to meet you.
- Right.
They are not bad guys.
They're just saying that.
It's all right.
- Hello.
- What?
You guys are wearing glasses.
- Are you Dirty Mustache?
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, hey.
- Hello.
(Trying to figure out what's going on)
- Are you Touch and Explode?
- Yes.
Yes. If you touch me, I'll explode.
Hello.
He's a bit sensitive,
so you shouldn't stare at him
for over three seconds.
- You should be careful.
- Wait. Look.
Those who are weak use intense nicknames.
(Dark Tornado, Touch and Explode,
Mustache Bomber)
- Think about that.
- You're right.
Strong guys use nicknames like this.
Look at the weak guys.
They have nicknames...
- like exploding and dynamite.
- And bomber.
Should I come up with something stronger?
What's Push Ahead No Matter What?
- He's on my team.
- That's right.
Is he your right-hand man?
Pink Princess,
are you his right-hand man?
I'm his left-hand man.
I'm on the left.
Excuse me. Are you his minion?
- Minion?
- Yes.
- Look.
- Pink Princess.
- Teach them a lesson.
- Okay.
Gosh, Pink Princess...
(He steps up to discipline them.)
Gosh, what's that? What is going on?
Isn't this "Three Meals for Jae Suk?"
- Pink Princess, talk to them.
- Look at you.
- You guys...
- Can you do that?
What? Let's just have a seat.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
What do you guys do for a living?
- Do you even have jobs?
- I do.
Touch and Explode can't look me
in the eyes for over three seconds.
Right. I can't look people
- If I do...
- What will happen then?
- Will you explode?
- What happens?
- Three seconds.
(As Dark Tornado looks
at his eyes for 3 seconds,)
(Touch and Explode explodes.)
I said 3 seconds. Only 3 seconds.
(He's punished right away.)
He has anger management issues.
- I see.
- Gosh, I'm sorry.
- My apologies.
- I see.
He was just fine.
- But if you stare for too long,
- I'm fine...
- he explodes.
- until I lose my temper.
The thing is,
now that Kwang Soo isn't here,
- you're playing his role.
- That's what we said.
- They're sharing his roles.
- That's what they're doing.
Right. I'm playing his role.
Everyone seems scary.
Today is...
the first get-together...
of the famous game club,
Running Game Club.
And you will win points
from two different games.
The two members with
the highest points will get prizes.
And the two with the lowest points
will get a penalty.
- All right.
- Two people?
The club president, Killer So Min,
will get the first game.
Please read it for us.
All right. We will be divided
into three teams...
to play Option Snake Ladders.
To play Option Snake Ladders,
you will start at the end
of the snake tail.
And the first team to reach
the snakehead wins the game.
Each team will spin the roulette
to move your pieces.
But you can...
lie about the numbers
you get from the roulette.
For example, you can say your
number is 7 when it's actually 1.
But if the other teams...
catch you in a lie,
your piece will go back
to the starting point.
If the other teams accuse you
of lying when you told the truth,
you get to spin
the roulette one more time.
So you should try reading
your opponents' minds...
and use it against them.
What if the roulette stops at "lie?"
In that case, you must lie.
- We lie?
- Yes.
There's more.
While you play this game,
if you use English words,
your piece goes
back to the starting point.
- English words?
- Yes.
We use quite a lot of English words.
I've done this before.
That's not fair for someone from abroad.
Jackson? Are you Jackson?
What about our nicknames?
Do words like Tornado and Pink count?
- We shouldn't call them.
- You shouldn't call them.
Just don't call them.
Or we can make the names short.
- Like DT.
- You can do that.
Each team should get a roulette.
I'm glad that our team doesn't
have English nicknames.
- Good.
- We don't know English words.
We don't know any, so we don't use it.
Those who don't speak English...
- use a lot of English words.
- Right.
- This team will go first.
- Okay.
The rest of you should close
your eyes then.
- Okay.
- All right.
Show us the roulette.
It's not easy to get "lie" from the start.
(What's the first number?)
- Nice!
- Okay.
He said "nice."
You didn't move your piece yet,
so it's okay.
What?
Don't say that.
Why do you speak English?
I'm sorry.
- I...
- Use a Korean word.
- That's my habit.
- Great.
- See?
Those who don't speak English
use a lot of English words.
Hang on.
- I got a call from Kwang Soo.
- Really?
- Answer it.
- Tell him to come right away.
- Kwang Soo.
- Hello, Jae Suk.
We're filming right now,
so I'm hanging up.
(He manages to cut Kwang Soo off again.)
I thought he wouldn't get
to cut Kwang Soo off again,
but he's doing it over the phone.
- I'm working now.
- That's unbelievable.
You're working?
You can announce the number now.
We got...
- 6.
(Team Haha's number is 6.)
- It's perfect.
- Gosh, this is...
They got six?
- I'm moving our piece. Be careful.
- Go ahead.
- They're...
- Move it to number 11.
- Look at that.
- To number 11?
It's perfect.
- Gosh, this is...
- Hang on.
It's strange, isn't it?
Move it.
That's the best...
- We should catch him.
- You want?
- Let's catch them.
- Catch them.
1, 2, 3.
- It's a lie.
All right.
The fact that they got six...
(What's the real number
Team Haha got from the roulette?)
was true.
(True)
- One more time!
- Okay!
He just said "okay."
You just said "okay,"
so you will go back to the starting point.
Hey, TE!
My gosh.
- You don't even speak English.
- Did you say an English word?
- Did I say that?
- Was it you?
I said that. I'm sorry.
My gosh.
- You don't even speak English.
- This is crazy.
- Just say great.
- Did I say that?
Okay. I'm sorry.
- Great.
- Darn.
Good.
Here we go. Close your eyes.
(Next up is Team Jae Suk.)
You shouldn't say okay.
Good.
(The number from the roulette is...)
(6.)
(Trying to keep a straight face)
This is tricky.
(They expect Team Jae Suk to lie.)
All right.
- Good.
- Make sure not to speak in English.
- I bet they got something bad.
- Good.
- It's 6.
- 6.
Six?
(Did they get 6 again?)
- It's a lie.
- It must be a lie.
- Is it six again?
- It's a lie.
- I bet they're lying.
It's a lie.
1, 2, 3.
- It's a lie.
- Good.
It's true...
- they got six.
- Good!
Good.
The thing is,
my talk is so limited.
I can't believe this.
(My talk is limited.)
Darn it!
(He can't help but use English words.)
What should I say then?
- What else could I say?
- Use a Korean word.
Use a Korean word.
Don't even say "comment."
(Okay.)
- All right.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- This is crazy.
- This is driving me crazy.
- What do we do now?
Okay. Let's go!
I shouldn't say anything.
Why do you use English words?
I shouldn't talk at all.
Let's go.
(Team Suk Jin has seen
a lot of bad examples.)
I don't think this game will end.
(They must lie this time.)
Put it down.
Announce the number now.
(Pushing)
(Pushing and pulling)
(The team is fighting a war of nerves.)
It's a war of nerves.
Why would you...
This is true, and that's false.
One is telling the truth,
and the other is lying.
True or false?
It's a lie!
True and false.
True or false?
I can't be on the same team as him.
- Gosh, DT.
- We need to talk.
Are you ready?
Do as you want.
- Shall we go?
- Move the piece.
(She moves her piece 2 spaces
when she has to lie.)
- Let's move on.
- Okay.
- Leave it be.
- Just move on.
Even if it's a lie,
we should leave it there.
- That was a lie.
- I see.
- Just leave it there.
- 1 and 2...
- Is it our turn?
- Yes.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
- We don't have any pieces yet.
- Okay.
- Great.
- Okay. We're playing board games.
Cameras.
There are cameras.
- This is SBS.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk will speak in English.
- Come on.
- You really use a lot of English.
Close your eyes.
Let me spin it.
(What's the number from the roulette?)
(It's 7.)
- Good.
- What color is our piece?
- Yellow.
- 1, 2,
- 3, 4, 5...
- Is it 7?
- It's 7.
I'll give you three seconds.
- This is...
- Don't say anything.
- Why not?
- Don't say a word.
Stay quiet.
- I can't keep my mouth shut.
- Stay quiet.
I bet it's true. 1, 2, 3.
- True.
All right. It's true.
I knew it.
Close your eyes.
I bet he will get seven.
(It's Team Jae Suk's turn.)
I bet the team will use
an English word at the end...
What did you say?
- I heard it.
- What did you say?
Move your piece back.
Go back. Go ahead.
- All right.
- I shouldn't talk.
- Go back.
- Darn it.
Move it.
- Move it back.
- That's why you shouldn't talk.
I shouldn't say anything. I'm sorry.
We got a number.
- Announce your number.
- 1, 2, 3.
- 6.
- This is...
- What?
- Let's go with a lie.
- It's a lie.
- He keeps lying.
- We should catch them.
Is it a lie?
But... PP.
Look at his eyes.
- Let's not talk.
- Who said that?
Who said the number six?
Then shall we say it's a lie...
and give them another chance?
They will speak English after all.
- No.
- I bet they will speak English.
We will never do that.
If he speaks English,
I'll beat him to death.
- We will say it's true.
- This guy can rip...
a cell phone apart.
I saw him rip it apart.
- Lie?
- True?
What is it?
- Let's go with truth.
- Truth.
- It's true.
(It's true that they got 6.)
- Who's next?
- I'll do it.
Spin it.
(Team Suk Jin's roulette...)
(shows number 3.)
(They will lie and say they got 4.)
- Are you ready?
- Yes. We're ready.
- Let's go.
- Catch them.
Let's go.
Okay. This is what we got.
- It's a lie.
- What?
Okay. This is what we got.
- It's a lie.
- What? He said that.
Okay.
(Team Suk Jin is going through
the worst time.)
- He got it.
- Good.
The word "okay" is driving me crazy.
What's wrong with me?
- Is there any tape?
- We shouldn't be like him.
- Good.
- Here we go.
Let's go.
It's okay to say that.
We don't have pieces on the board.
Good.
(The roulette shows 5.)
This is hard.
I'm so mad.
All right. Here we go.
- Good.
- Go.
1, 2,
3, 4,
- 5.
- 5?
It should go all the way up.
Then we will get to number 33.
It should go up.
(They take a shortcut to number 33.)
Can you believe this?
- Good.
- Nice.
Why aren't you talking?
You're being too quiet.
So Min just spun it.
And we got five.
Please save your breath.
Isn't that amazing?
- Right?
- But...
Should we give them a chance?
- This is too good though.
- We should risk it.
- Shall we?
- We have to say it's a lie.
Because there's a snake?
Even if they spin it again,
they might get the snake
and fall back down.
Right?
If they get the snake,
they will lie again.
1, 2, 3.
- It's a lie.
- Lie.
1, 2, 3.
- It's true.
I knew it was true.
I thought it was true.
Since it was true,
you get to spin it again.
Close your eyes.
You just spin it.
When they are watching?
You just spin the roulette
in the extra round.
But that's disadvantageous to us.
We have our patterns.
There are a lot of snakes.
We have to lie.
(We have our patterns.)
(I'm doomed.)
(Despite Haha's efforts...)
Did you say an English word?
What did you say?
- What did you say?
- What did he say?
See?
- What did you say?
- I'm sorry.
"We have our patterns."
(We have our patterns.)
I don't even know...
many English words.
How dare you!
Good.
- Well done.
- I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
- I only know a few words.
(He's going to say
all the English words he knows.)
- This is it.
- This is...
- what I want.
- What I want.
- If they don't speak English...
- Good.
- Let's never use any English words.
- Okay.
(I'll teach you a lesson!)
I don't even know how to spell
the word "pattern."
- Nice!
- I'm sorry.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- Let's...
- Let's start over again.
- We got this.
- Let's start over. I'm sorry.
- This is great.
- Let it slide just this once.
- Gosh. I'm so angry.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- They were almost there.
This is what I'm talking about.
Why did you say the word "pattern?"
- Gosh. Why did I do that?
- Close your eyes.
The roulette...
(Next up is Team Jae Suk,
the current winning team.)
It must be a small number.
Could it be a small number?
Are you done?
Can we open our eyes now?
- All right.
- Yes.
One.
- Pardon?
- One.
- One?
- Hold on.
They might have gotten two...
but said it was one
not to go back down here.
- Okay, okay.
- Right? Look here.
- Okay! I agree.
- Okay!
(Dark Tornado's theory sounds plausible.)
(It's hard to read
Jae Suk and Jong Kook's faces.)
(Did they say the truth or a lie?)
- Am I right?
- Let's conclude that they lied.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- It's a lie!
Okay. We caught them.
- All right.
- I can't trust him.
2, 3.
- It's the truth.
(They told the truth.)
- What?
- It's okay. It's only one time.
- Right. It's okay.
- Okay.
- Please go ahead.
- I will...
- You can speak English now.
- spin it.
- That's right.
- I hope they get one.
- What could it be?
- Three?
- Oh, gosh.
- That's nice.
- Is it three?
- 1, 2, 3. What?
- That's nice.
- Oh, wow.
- Shout "Good!" Or "Nice!"
- Shout "Nice!"
- Okay!
- This is it!
- This is what we wanted.
- Right.
That team is doing so well.
They have great teamwork, right?
Let's move on.
- Please close your eyes, everyone.
- That's...
- a really good strategy.
- As you all must know,
- you can lie to move far at once.
- Okay.
Aren't we allowed to tell a lie
only when it stops on "lie?"
- You're wrong.
- We can lie whenever we want...
- It doesn't matter?
- I didn't know that.
- It doesn't matter.
Jae Suk, you can lie any time you want.
- Don't say any English words.
- I won't.
- Let's catch them lying.
- Any time we want? Okay.
(Team Suk Jin, which is still
at the starting point, got 6.)
- Are you done?
- Okay. We'll move.
Let's just let them go.
We'll be okay.
Let's let them go for now.
That's a lie.
- 1, 2, 3. It's a lie!
- It's a lie!
(They suspect it's a lie.)
Since I said we should let them go,
he thought we would actually let them go.
- All right.
- Oh, yes!
It's the truth.
- Great job.
- We told the truth.
- By the way...
- Really?
- By the way, he just said...
- Is it not?
- An exclamation like that is okay.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- That's a universal exclamation.
- It's not exactly an English word.
- Dark Tornado...
- But...
- To be exact,
- it's an English expression.
- We're just letting this slide.
- What do you mean by that?
- You know that, right?
- Thank you.
- Is that even possible?
We're letting it slide.
- Stop it.
- I mean...
Just apologize to him right now.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- He said "Okay."
- "Okay."
- Great!
(Okay. We got him!)
(Team Suk Jin is devastated
while the other teams are happy.)
Okay!
- That was good.
- We all say "okay" so often.
- I told you not to speak at all!
- That was good.
Jae Suk, good job.
- What's wrong with me?
- That was good.
- Good job.
- Nice tiki-taka.
I must have lost my mind.
What is wrong with me?
He's dancing. Why are you dancing?
Are you in a good mood?
- What is that?
- Don't act up.
Don't act up.
Are you very happy?
- Don't act up.
- I'm really...
- Are you very happy?
- I am very happy.
- They'll win at this rate.
- No. We should stop them.
- I'll spin it. Close your eyes.
- Close your eyes.
- Okay.
(It's Team Haha's turn.)
If we push ahead...
We're going to say the truth.
(They got 7.)
- Move it, So Min.
- Go with the truth.
Let's stick to the truth.
(They moved 7 spaces.)
(Now they look suspicious
whatever they do.)
- It's okay.
- I think...
- We have no problem.
- Oh, my.
In this case... Since they're
near the starting point,
- Right.
- let's stop them.
- Let them be.
- Really?
- Should we stop them?
- I think we should...
- Okay. 1, 2, 3.
- Even if they move again...
- It's a lie.
- Do they have no say in it?
- That's right.
Who are you guys?
- We are...
- They got them.
- a special investigation team.
- What?
What did you say
after "special investigation?"
(He said "team" in English.)
(What?)
Oh, right.
(Jong Kook finally realized
what Jae Suk did wrong.)
- He said "team," right?
- This won't end.
This won't end.
- Gosh, that was funny.
- This won't end.
- "A special investigation..."
- I don't think...
- this game will ever end.
- Hey, come with me.
Come with me.
I can't.
- No! No!
- He said "team."
A special investigation team!
- SBS!
- This is driving me nuts.
He's driving me crazy.
Today is Monday!
- We said the truth.
- We even said...
- the truth!
- The truth!
One more time!
It's never-ending.
Seven!
Seven.
- Go, go.
- We can catch them.
- We need four.
- Yes, then we can catch them.
We can catch them if we get four.
(Team Jae Suk got 3.)
Can we open our eyes now?
- Are you done?
- Four.
Sorry?
(You got 4?)
- Is he lying?
- I said, four.
- It's 4.
- Is it 4, really?
(It's the best scenario
where they can catch Team Haha.)
- We were so surprised.
- What?
- We'll catch them.
- You'll catch us?
- Yes.
- Then will they go back?
We'll let you decide.
- We should stop them.
- Definitely.
- 1, 2, 3. It's a lie.
- It's a lie.
(They suspect it's a lie.)
- It was a lie.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- That was good.
- Good.
- It was good.
- Indeed. Okay.
He lied as soon as he learned
about the rules.
- Even if we get caught, it's okay.
- We should keep moving.
- I mean...
- That's enough.
We might get into trouble.
(Se Chan said "rule" in English.)
I would've lied every time.
Se Chan, what did you just say?
- What did you say? Come here.
- What did he say?
- You can't do this.
- He's impossible.
- What did you say?
- What did you say? Tell us!
- I said that Jae Suk lied...
- What did you say?
as soon as he learned the rules.
- I said "rule" in English.
- Hey!
- I mean...
- He can't seem to fix it.
You stone gold!
What's "stone gold?"
- Doesn't it mean "stupid?"
- You mean, stone head.
Oh, I should've said "stone head."
- They haven't moved in an hour.
- This is not acceptable.
- I'll leave.
- You have to start over again.
It's been an hour, and they're still here.
- That was funny.
- Why?
Don't use any English words.
- Never do that again.
- I didn't know they'd hear it.
I told you not to speak at all.
Exactly. Why did you...
It's not like you use
some difficult English words.
I don't even know how to spell
the words I said.
But you know what?
We made it this far...
- because Kwang Soo isn't here.
- True.
We couldn't have continued
if Kwang Soo was here.
- Gosh, I'm so frustrated.
- We'll spin it.
Please close your eyes.
(All teams are starting over again.
What number will Team Suk Jin get?)
- I think they spun it twice.
- Exactly.
The blue one is ours, right?
Here we go.
(They took the shortcut
and moved straight to 14.)
- Ji Hyo?
- They're talking too much.
- But Ji Hyo...
- 1, 2, 3.
- It's a lie.
We said the truth.
It's the truth.
- Let's move on.
- I didn't...
(Team Suk Jin got 2 this time
and moved to 16!)
- Hurry up.
- Hurry.
- We need 4.
- We should get 4 no matter what.
- Okay. Let's go with this number.
- This number?
(Team Haha got 7.)
(They're moving to 7
pretending they're lying.)
Yes. Right. Wait, no.
- Okay. Good.
- Yes. That's it.
- It's a lie.
- 1, 2, 3.
- It's the truth!
- Really?
- I knew it.
- Why did you do that?
I knew it was the truth.
- I thought it was the truth.
- I'll do it.
Four. That's good.
(Only they're at the starting point
when they don't have much time.)
If we get lucky, we can go
straight there with 4 and then 1.
- We need 4 and then 1.
- Or we can catch them with 6.
Or we can catch them with six.
Right? We have many options.
- Close your eyes.
- Don't say a word.
- Close your eyes!
Close your eyes!
That team is angry.
It'd be awesome if we get this number.
(Se Chan said "team" in English.)
- What did you just say?
- Hey!
- He did it again.
- What did he say?
He said "team"
when he said, "That team is angry."
- Come on.
- Gosh, you stupid punk!
My gosh. I'm so furious right now.
Get out, you punk!
- Leave!
- I'm sorry.
- I said, leave!
- Close your eyes!
- Darn it.
- Close your eyes.
- Why did I say that?
- I'm sorry.
Close your eyes!
Okay. It's four.
Wait.
- What?
- 1, 2, 3.
- It's a lie.
(They suspect it's a lie
as they took the shortcut.)
- It's a lie.
- You're right.
Come with me.
Hold on.
Come out.
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
I can't believe this. Hold on.
I'm sorry, sir! I'm sorry.
- I mean...
- I apologize!
This is driving me nuts. I mean...
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry, sir!
- We got five.
- Five moves are not so bad...
- I was wrong.
If we moved five spaces,
we would've been safe...
- I mean, we don't have much time.
- I'm sorry. I was wrong.
I'm sorry, PP.
Or you could've lied it was six.
- I'm sorry.
- Why would you say it was four?
- We'll be in 2nd place.
- Since we have 3 minutes left,
we'll end the game
after just one more round.
(They'll end the game after this round.)
- Good.
- Let's win this game.
- Now...
- We can do this.
- Suk Jin.
- I will be careful.
- Suk Jin, bite this.
- I think...
I will do that.
Gosh, I'm so angry.
(Suk Jin is biting his name tag
to be careful.)
We were almost there.
(They got the biggest number 7.)
- Then we can move...
- We should...
move at the right time.
You got seven?
- Suk Jin, did you get seven?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
2, 3.
- It's a lie.
- It's a lie?
- We should stop them.
- We should say it's a lie.
- We should say it no matter what.
- Got it.
- We actually got...
- Is it the truth?
(They get to spin the roulette again
because it's the truth!)
- Suk Jin, they want...
- Just hurry up.
Suk Jin, the cameraman wants you...
to count down from three
before you spin it.
- What do you want me to say?
- "3, 2, 1."
You little...
Hey, I'm not stupid.
- Gosh, that made me so upset.
- Say, "3, 2, 1."
- We'll make sure to win.
- Hurry up and spin it.
- Go ahead.
- Okay!
- All right.
- Wait.
- Go ahead.
- Okay!
- All right.
- He said "okay."
- We did it! We did it!
- Good job!
- We did it!
- Yes!
- It was recorded!
- All right. Okay.
Let's keep going.
- We did it.
Okay!
- Fine. Go ahead.
- Good!
- We did it.
- Okay. This is great.
- How did you make him say that?
- Okay!
- We stopped them.
- We'll push ahead no matter what.
They really are investigators.
They caught him.
We did it.
Okay!
How could you distract me
when my team was doing well?
- Okay, okay.
- I can't believe this.
- Okay. That was great.
- Okay.
Let's just play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Here we go, here we go
- Okay.
- Let's sit down.
- Let's give it a try.
- Okay.
- He got excited to speak freely.
Here we go
- Okay!
- Here we go
- He got excited to speak freely.
- Okay.
Here we go
- He's usually such a cheerful man,
- Let's go!
- but Ji Hyo wouldn't let him speak.
- I wanted to say "okay" so much.
- He says that all the time.
- Yes, we're back at the start.
Each team has one more chance
from now on, right?
Only these two teams. They're over.
- They're over?
- Okay. They're over.
- Be careful not to say "okay."
- I knew it this time.
- Yes. Yes. That's right.
- Okay. Let's go.
Please close your eyes.
- Okay. Good.
- Good.
(What number will Team Haha get
on their last attempt?)
(The highest number 7)
Go with the number.
3, 4, 5, 6. Yes.
- Yes. Good.
- They moved too far.
- How many moves?
- That's...
- We got 7.
- We moved 7 spaces.
Don't you think they moved too far?
- Shall we?
- You got seven?
- 1, 2, 3. It's a lie.
- It's a lie.
- 1, 2, 3. It's the truth.
- It's the truth.
- Go ahead and spin it.
- One more time.
- Haha.
- This could be better.
- I know! Don't speak!
- Be quiet.
- It's awesome.
- Shut it.
Can you turn off Se Chan's mic...
- It's okay.
- We can catch them with six.
So Min.
- What did she say?
- Did she say something?
What did she say?
She said "mic" when she asked us
to turn off his mic.
Darn it. Hey!
Hey, why...
- I won't play this game anymore.
- Haha.
- Move!
- Come back, please.
- I'm not doing this.
- Mustache Bomber, please.
- I won't do this! Let go of me.
- Come on.
- Please come back. Just this once.
- What is going on?
- Having many members isn't good.
- Exactly.
- Please sit down.
- There's a lot of pressure on him.
Mustache Bomber, we're really sorry.
My goodness.
- I'm sorry, Mustache Bomber.
- I'm sorry.
- This is unbelievable.
- We're almost there.
- It's the truth.
Now, the game is over.
Team Jae Suk wins.
Okay!
- Okay!
- Okay, we won!
- Okay. Nice!
The team that gets a bigger number
will be in second place.
- I hope they get a small number.
- Seven.
- Okay.
- Oh, no.
- The winning team gets five points.
- Great.
The team in 2nd place gets 3 points.
The team in 3rd place gets 1 point.
One point? Okay. That's not bad.
So Min, as the president,
please explain the next game.
- President Jeon.
- I get no benefits.
- The president gets no benefits.
- What could that be?
(What game could be in this box?)
(You've been invited
to the gangsters' world.)
(Jump together hand in hand
to enter the place.)
Everyone, please gather around
and hold each other's hands.
- What? Why?
- Hold each other's hands.
Do we need to jump?
Yes, we're going to jump together.
- Then we'll be there?
- Like what we did back in the day?
- Yes. Let's begin. 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Jumping)
Why didn't you jump?
We need to jump at once.
Jong Kook, grab his hand tightly.
- Gosh, he drives me crazy.
- Break his fingers.
- Ready. 1, 2, 3.
- Jump.
What? What is this?
What's with our clothes?
- Where are we?
- We're gunmen. Bang, bang, bang.
(The members entered
the real-life version of a game.)
- Bang, bang, bang.
- Oh, my.
- We all look so cool.
- Somehow...
- You look great in the costume.
- I know.
- Smoke keeps coming out of there.
- Why is there smoke here?
(The world that they entered is...)
This place is so cool.
- Hey, stop talking and sit down.
- Oh, my.
(A large budget was spent
to build the studio.)
- That's state-of-the-art.
- Great.
(The wild west gangsters will fight
one another here.)
Oh, my. It's sophisticated.
- It's fabulous.
- It's so cool.
- I see you spent a lot of money.
- Exactly.
That's funny.
Suk Jin,
Bo Pil didn't spend his own money.
"You spent a lot of money."
- He doesn't use his own money.
- Anyway...
- He's the one who gets approval.
- Choose your words carefully.
- People might get the wrong idea.
- Suk Jin.
They spent the money
they would've paid Kwang Soo with.
- Was he paid that much?
- He must've been paid a lot.
- As Kwang Soo left the show...
Now that Kwang Soo left the show...
- They got a bigger budget.
- I can see that we have more money.
I see that.
We filled Kwang Soo's absence
with a nicer filming set.
- Kwang Soo, thank you.
- Kwang Soo!
- Bang, bang, bang!
- There it is.
Thanks to you, we're shooting
on such a sophisticated set.
This is nice.
From now on, you are...
seven gangsters who must complete
the missions given by the boss.
- Are we gangsters?
- We're gangsters.
- That's cool.
If you get the items
written on the letter of request...
from the boss before the others do,
you will get points.
The top two will get a prize.
And the bottom two will get a penalty.
I just have to avoid a penalty.
- Good. I'll just avoid a penalty.
- Yes.
In this game, you have to bring
the items that the boss requested.
If you look at the board,
in order to get ten points,
you need 3 bottles of drink, 2 gems,
- and two dollars.
- Okay.
You get it, right?
Now I'll tell you how you get these items.
At the beginning of each round,
we'll randomly pick one of you
to be the police officer.
The chosen person will be
the police officer in that round...
whereas the other six are gangsters.
When the game begins...
There are rooms
numbered from 1 to 5 in the back,
and there are different items
in each of those rooms.
In rooms numbered 1 to 4,
you can get a different number
of bottles and gems.
But room number five is a pawn shop
where you can exchange...
the item you have with the item you want.
You will enter the room
of your choice and wait there.
All six gangsters go into a room.
- And then the police officer...
- The police officer will enter too.
gets to search only two rooms
for gangsters.
- Two rooms?
- Yes.
- It'll be easy to catch gangsters.
- Two rooms?
Gangsters will get caught so easily.
The gangsters who didn't get caught
by the police officer...
- share all the items in the room.
- They get the items in there.
Yes. But...
every gangster gets as many bottles
and gems as they find in the room.
(They get all the bottles and gems.)
But they have to divide the money equally.
(They have to divide the money equally.)
It's important to choose a room
where there aren't many gangsters.
That's important too.
Do the ones who get caught...
lose their items?
The gangster who gets caught
while being alone in the room...
doesn't get any items,
and on top of that,
loses all the items he or she has.
If there is more than one gangster
in the room...
Do you see the cards with "silence,"
"snitch," and "bribe" on them?
- Yes.
You have to decide
whether you will stay silent,
snitch, or bribe the officer.
If all the gangsters choose
to stay silent,
the police officer will leave
without getting anything,
and the gangsters will share
the items in the room.
Sounds good.
But if some of them choose to snitch,
the ones who snitched can get
all the items...
whereas the ones who stayed silent
lose all they have.
- Of course.
- Yes.
- It's all about snitching.
- It's a psychological game.
However, if all the gangsters choose
to snitch,
the police officer will take
all the items...
that belong to the gangsters in the room.
If you choose to bribe the officer,
regardless of the result,
you have to give one bottle
to the police officer...
and leave the room.
- You don't lose much.
- I don't get any items.
- What do I lose?
- I guess I can keep what I have.
You just have to give one bottle
to the officer.
- It's just a small loss.
- I don't lose it all?
Exactly. It's just a small loss.
- It's a small loss.
- It's like a tax.
- Yes. You can say that.
- That sounds reasonable.
- You can keep your gems.
- It costs you only one bottle.
- That won't be a bad choice.
- Right.
- But the other gangsters...
- Okay!
may get all the items in the room.
Do we get any items before we begin?
There are 1 gem, 1 bottle,
and 1 dollar in your bag.
- 1 of each? I get it.
- 1 of each.
We're not allowed to steal items
from other gangsters, right?
That's not allowed.
Hey, he left, you know.
Still, many of us would choose to snitch.
The one in the end and...
- Not if we come to an agreement.
- I wouldn't do that either.
The police officer will be changed
in every other round.
Do you want to practice first
or just begin the game?
- Let's begin right away.
- Okay then.
- Pick the police officer.
- Let's get it started now.
Bang, bang. I'll catch them all.
All right.
The first police officer is...
(Who could be the 1st police officer
to set the mood?)
The first police officer is...
(Who could be the 1st police officer
to set the mood?)
- Se Chan.
- Oh, my.
(It's Se Chan!)
- It doesn't suit him.
- Bang!
- Bang, bang.
- Yang Ssaebssaeb?
Please choose a room 1 by 1...
starting from the ones
on the police officer's right side.
- Okay. Then...
- Gosh, seriously.
- I'll go first.
- Go ahead.
(He can get different items in each room.)
(From the left, room numbers 1 to 5)
(Room number 5,
they can exchange their items here.)
You can see that there's a lot
of items in room number one, right?
I hope at least one of you goes
into that room.
- I promise I won't enter that room.
- Are you serious?
I won't enter room number one.
He might not choose the room
thinking many of us would go there.
I won't choose room number one.
You can trust me.
(Room number 1)
(Jae Suk is hesitating
in front of room number 1.)
Wait. I can exchange...
what I have with anything I want, right?
(Room number 4, room number 5)
Okay.
(Jae Suk picked room number 4!)
(Room number 4)
Oh, there's a lot of food in here.
(The hungry gangster
with a protruding mouth...)
(starts to steal food.)
(He chose room number 4...)
(with only a few items in it
that not many would choose.)
Next up is Suk Jin.
Please choose a room.
- Okay. I'll go.
- I won't go into room number one.
I bet Suk Jin will choose that room
because of what he said.
No, I won't. I'm off.
That's not the entrance.
He's so bad at role-playing.
- Please close the curtain.
- Close it.
- Close the other one too.
- Make sure you don't see.
(He's enjoying the solo shot on camera.)
Which room did Jae Suk choose?
I have to enter a different room.
(It'll get complicated
if another gangster is in the room.)
(Jae Suk is staying alert
while eating hardtack.)
I wonder which of the five rooms
he went into.
(Jae Suk is in room number 4.
Which room did Suk Jin choose?)
I bet So Min will choose room number one.
Me? Do you think I'm stupid?
"Do you think I'm stupid?"
You don't think...
that I can seduce a police officer
with my beauty?
I'm married.
- Since when?
- Next up is So Min.
(So Min, who got rejected
by the officer, will choose a room.)
(She chooses carefully.)
(And the room she chose is...)
(room number 4 where Jae Suk is.)
Why did you come here?
Why are you here?
- Why are you here?
- Why did you choose this room?
Why did you choose this one of all rooms?
It's because we're both timid.
- We're both timid.
- That's not the case.
(Suk Jin silently hides
in one of the rooms.)
- This isn't easy.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Se Chan thinks way too much.
- I do.
As you all know,
I stick to the basics.
There are many items
to share in room number one,
so that will probably be
one of the rooms I choose.
I must, you know.
I can't risk anyone getting those goods.
If the gangsters in room number one
choose to be silent,
- they'll keep the goods.
- You're right.
- If they all choose to stay quiet?
- Of course.
It's not a bad deal then.
- Then at first...
- It's not a bad choice then.
If the gangsters in room number one...
- agree to stay silent.
- Yes, exactly.
- Can you trust anyone though?
- For everyone to be silent?
The next gangster will enter.
- I already have a plan.
- Okay.
Go ahead.
- Sure.
- We can go into any room.
(Ji Hyo's next to choose a room.)
I already have a bottle.
I'll give you one right now...
if you promise
not to enter room number one.
I won't go in there.
(Whispering)
Jong Kook.
Hear me out.
I'll promise not to go in there...
if you give me a bottle each.
- I won't go in there.
- One each.
- Do you promise?
- Yes.
What if you turn on us?
I stay true to my word.
I'll hit you for real.
- What?
- That's a given.
- Right?
- Of course.
- Will you do that for a bottle?
- Must you even ask?
I won't go in there.
- Are you sure?
- For a bottle each?
(The two gangsters
bribe the police officer.)
Okay, Haha, you're next.
Do you promise?
I already did. Now, hand it over.
Then...
I won't go in there.
For two bottles.
- So...
- Haha?
Hold on a second.
Once I go in, they might...
- What?
- I'm worried...
that he'll change his mind.
It's why I don't want to leave this room.
(Even in the wild west,
they highly doubt each other.)
- Here I go.
- It's only the first round.
- You...
- All right.
- Yes, I hear you.
You've already crossed me many times.
Don't point it at me like that.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Get going or the others might hear you.
(Haha and Jong Kook bribe
the officer with a bottle each.)
- Don't you dare.
- I won't.
Let's trust him this once.
- Trust me this once.
- We have a long way to go anyway.
- I won't.
- Don't you dare.
(Haha heads to the rooms
with doubt in his mind.)
What will you do?
Are you really going to keep your word?
(Are you really not going to enter
room number one?)
(Winking)
(The dirty cop is willing
to go against his word.)
(He gives the muscular gangster
his bottle back.)
(Got you!)
(The pathological doubter
catches the police red-handed.)
- Why?
- What's wrong?
What's the matter with you?
- Why?
- What is it?
We were keeping quiet.
I'm seriously angry right now.
Don't you like
that we're keeping our silence?
- Just get going.
- I meant it.
- I won't go in that room.
- Why...
Haha, you can't come back out here.
- Just go.
- You can't come back out here.
(I have a bad feeling about this.)
The worst scenario for me
is when the gangsters keep quiet.
(He puts his trust in Detective Yang
and enters room number one.)
(Hi!)
(In room number 1 filled with items,)
(he's greeted by Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.)
If we all stay quiet
even after we're caught,
- we'll keep all the items.
- Right.
I don't know what I should do.
I have a plan though.
I have one in mind.
- Why here?
- Did you have to choose this room?
- I heard a sound.
- I thought you'd go...
into the next room.
- Why this room?
- I knew I heard something.
(A few gangsters
have gathered in room number 4.)
- Jong Kook...
- Why did you choose this room...
when there's nothing in here?
- That's exactly the reason.
- You two...
always go big, so...
(The siren wails to signal that
the officer is making his move.)
The search has begun.
All right.
How dare you steal what's mine.
Let me see.
(The gangsters are
in rooms number 1 and 4.)
Maybe you're in room number four...
which you swore that had nothing to take.
There's only one bottle.
(Room number 4)
Or maybe you went for the gems.
Or maybe...
you went for the 2 gems and 2 bottles...
to turn the tables of this game.
(Room number 1)
(There are 5 rooms and he can search 2.)
Here I go.
(The gangsters hold their breaths
as they wait.)
(Which room will Detective Yang search?)
Got you!
(Startled!)
Get over here.
(Yang Se Chan, darn you!)
There were three of you here.
(Those in room number 4
live to fight another day.)
- Ouch.
- I can't believe you.
How can you go back on your word?
Unbelievable.
(Detective Yang broke his promise
even after taking the bribe.)
You've got to be kidding me.
- What you are is a thug.
- I'm done talking to you.
Don't you dare speak like that
to the police.
Get over here.
Unbelievable.
(The 3 arrested will shortly choose
to stay quiet, snitch, or bribe.)
Get over here.
Unbelievable.
- Silence is our only way out.
- Watch your heads.
- Get out here.
- Don't touch me.
- You...
- Seriously?
Why can't any of you
think outside the box?
You can now choose
the second room to search.
- Right away?
- Yes.
Se Chan...
Okay, fine. Just see what I do.
- You'll pay for this.
- Okay.
You obviously...
can't keep your "world."
His world?
What's that supposed to mean?
- His world?
As if that makes any sense.
(Suk Jin's too stunned
to even speak properly.)
You went back on your word.
(Detective Yang
conducts his second search.)
Will it be 2 gems and 2 bottles?
Or will you safely take
just a bottle each?
My second search.
- Here I go.
- Sure thing.
(I'll catch you during my second search!)
(Will he be able to catch
the gangsters in room number 4?)
Got you!
No one's here.
(He failed to catch the gangsters.)
Okay. That concludes round one.
- No one was there.
- No one?
- That was close.
- I almost went in there.
Jae Suk, where were you?
- Was he in room four?
- Yes.
Was no one in room two?
(Jae Suk, So Min, Jong Kook)
No one was in room 2 or 3.
Hold on a second.
I apprehended three gangsters.
If you think about it,
- it's all about working as a team.
- Right.
Let's begin the round like this.
We agreed not to play tricks
in the first round.
- I can't believe what he did.
- Look at his face.
- His expression.
- Wait.
- He's that upset.
- Haha.
- We have to stay silent.
- Only a fool wouldn't.
- Round one has ended.
- Got you!
The three gangsters will decide...
whether to stay silent,
snitch, or bribe the officer.
Hold up your choice on the count of three.
Someone will definitely snitch.
Snitching is how you'll win this game.
If all three choose to stay silent,
you'll share the items in room one.
If one of you decides to snitch,
the items will be that person's to take.
Those who stay silent
will lose their share.
If all three snitch,
you'll all lose your items.
(Police, Se Chan)
If you would like to play it safe,
you can bribe the officer
with a bottle and keep the rest.
(Police, Se Chan)
I think all three
will choose to stay silent.
- Only a fool wouldn't stay silent.
- Exactly.
- Have you made up your minds?
- Yes.
Let's start with some items in our bags.
All three of us.
- That's better.
- Let's please do that.
That's exactly what I want.
- All right.
- Please...
- One.
- Haha.
- Make it fun.
- Please.
- One...
- Ji Hyo, please.
- Hold them up simultaneously.
- Kwang Soo would betray us, but...
I can be trusted, but not you two.
- No way.
- Why won't you trust me?
Only a fool wouldn't stay silent.
Isn't that obvious?
- Let me get So Min and Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Okay, let's stay silent.
- Stay silent.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Of course.
I'll stay silent!
(He snitches.)
- They snitched.
- They all snitched.
- Unbelievable.
- Those three.
That gave me goosebumps!
A chill was sent down my spine.
All three of you...
will lose your gems and bottles,
but not your money.
- Haha, that was solid acting.
- What did I tell you?
Don't I get anything?
You'll be confiscating what they have.
Right. They're mine to keep.
No way.
Gems and bottles.
He already took my bottle.
- What if he doesn't have any?
- Then there's nothing to give you.
- Shouldn't he give me one later?
- Only give what you have.
- What?
- You know...
- Come on.
- This is why I didn't choose to...
This was pretty obvious.
This is why I didn't choose to stay quiet.
We'll now begin the second round.
Off you go.
You play the cop for two rounds.
- Am I the cop again?
- Yes.
Choose your rooms!
Please note...
that there's a dollar more in each room.
(There's a dollar more in each room.)
Off you go.
Suk Jin will go first.
All right.
I don't know what to choose,
so I'll let the stars decide.
I'll enter the room my gun points at.
(Suk Jin chooses the room
the gun points at.)
Who's next?
- Jae Suk will go next.
- Okay!
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Can you give me one last chance?
If I betray you,
you can cut me from your life.
You said that the last time
and then betrayed me.
I mean it this time.
I'll choose room number one...
- and stay silent.
- Okay, I'll take that deal.
Okay, then I promise...
not to enter room number one.
(Seriously?)
Please don't throw that at me.
Haha almost...
To me, Se Chan is...
I won't go in there.
Not room number one.
Jong Kook, you and me.
Sounds good.
Who's next?
(Jong Kook's next.)
(Room number 4?)
This? Really?
(The alliance agrees on room number 4.)
So Min.
How about we join forces?
Call.
That offer...
I'll accept that offer.
(Acting cool
as if they're in a cowboy movie)
- Do you mean it?
- Yes.
You actually spilled it on you.
(Playing cowboy using a miniature bottle)
It's water.
So Min will enter first.
- Why?
- Go in, So Min.
(So Min enters as per Se Chan's order...)
(to room number 1
that has the most stuff.)
This is driving me crazy.
(Jae Suk is in the room again?)
(The tiger moth siblings
are on the same level.)
Why are you in here?
My gosh, seriously.
Jae Suk, why are you in here?
(The two of them are drawn
to each other like magnets.)
Why are you here?
See you in there if we can.
(Ji Hyo is next to go.)
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook
agreed to meet in room number 4.)
I have nothing in my hands.
(Room number 4)
(It's packed with Jong Kook and Suk Jin.)
Come here. Let's just hope
that no one else comes in.
Let's decide on what to do.
- There are three of us here.
- Let's hope no one else comes in.
No one will come in anymore.
(No one should come in
for them to earn a dollar each.)
(Haha chose room number 4 too.)
What's wrong with you?
(Room number 1, number 4)
(The 6 gangsters are gathered
in rooms number 1 and 4.)
You punks!
The search has begun.
(Will he succeed in rounding up
all the gangsters?)
Those punks.
(Will he succeed in rounding up
all the gangsters?)
These punks must be hiding well.
I can tell they tried so hard to run.
All right, then!
You're taking a bottle each again?
That's so predictable.
I'll go to room number four.
Or...
All right.
(The cop seems to have made up his mind.)
(He slowly approaches.)
You punk!
(He chose an empty room.)
(There's no one in here.)
(He has only one chance left.)
(If they don't get caught,
they can win all the items.)
I can smell people trembling in fear.
The rooms are reeking of sweat.
That means someone is nervous.
I should go easy on them this time.
Tip-tap, tip-tap.
Not a chance!
(Right then)
(Se Chan suddenly raids room number 1.)
I got you, you punks.
Come here!
- This is driving me crazy.
- Come here.
I got you.
(We're safe.)
- Here you go.
- My gosh.
We're getting everything.
We're not getting any money.
Otherwise, more people would've come in.
Why did you choose this room?
(They can't win the money
since they can't divide it evenly.)
- Why can't we take the money?
- We need to survive.
Because there's only three dollars.
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Officer Yang successfully arrests
gangsters in both rounds.)
Here's the result of Round Two.
Jae Suk and So Min, who were
in room number one, were arrested.
- It'll be fun to watch.
- They need to decide.
Jae Suk, I'm in last place.
- I'm in last place.
- This is...
This doesn't go the way you want it to.
(Will they choose to stay quiet,
snitch, or bribe?)
Your heart tells you to stay quiet.
You're not going to bribe?
No, I won't.
- She doesn't even need that card.
- I really don't.
We need just one of the two.
(Jae Suk also throws away
the bribe card.)
I'm going to throw away the snitch card.
(He threw both cards away?)
I'm showing how determined I am
to stay quiet.
I threw away the bribe and snitch cards.
This is...
- Okay.
- They're pretty intense.
All right, then.
Lift your card on the count of three.
1, 2...
(If they choose to remain quiet,
they'll earn a bottle and 2 gems.)
Three!
(Snitch?)
(And she chose to bribe.)
- Snitch and bribe. Jae Suk...
- I knew you'd do this.
(Jae Suk is the only one
who snitched on So Min.)
(All his belongings will be confiscated.)
- At least I chose to bribe.
- Jae Suk...
I handed him my card,
and he accepted it without hesitating.
You're unbelievable.
He and I had a connection.
(Se Chan offered his snitch card
to Jae Suk.)
I'm going to throw away the snitch card.
(He threw away his snitch card
and took Se Chan's.)
- At least I chose to bribe.
- That was wise of you, So Min.
That was a good choice.
At least bribing is better
than losing everything.
- It's way better.
- So Min, turn in one bottle.
Jae Suk, you need to turn in
everything except for the money.
- To me?
- I'm so relieved.
- We...
- Bring them to me.
We weren't born to stay quiet.
I didn't take anything.
You're supposed to hand in everything.
My gosh, this is harsh.
- He even had gems?
- We have one less competitor now.
You can buy stuff now if you want to.
- Now?
- Yes, you can buy them if you want.
I'll buy some first then.
(The Boss's Request)
- That way, they can't be taken.
- That's right.
You can take them after paying.
Ten points?
Three bottles.
Two gems.
Wait, I don't have money.
- Did you put in yours?
- I don't have money.
How dumb of me.
I don't have money.
How come I have just one dollar?
You need money too?
I'm sorry.
I have plenty of bottles and gems,
but I have no money.
That's because you took bribes
so many times!
I don't have money.
- You don't?
- No.
Then Se Chan is definitely going to
take the money.
We'll draw a ball to decide
who'll play the cop.
My goodness.
He'll go into room number five.
- Please pick me.
- All right.
- The second person to play cop...
- Please...
Haha.
(Who will be the second member
to play cop?)
Jae Suk.
(The 2nd cop is Jae Suk.)
It's Jae Suk.
(I'm in trouble.)
(They can't help but sigh
as Jae Suk is more oppressive.)
But I think it's better
to play cop second.
All right, then. Firstly,
Suk Jin...
Am I going first again?
All right.
- It doesn't matter.
- Right.
Let's go!
He uses so much English
if you listen to him.
Hang on. Come back, Suk Jin.
- What is it?
- I changed my mind.
He changed his mind.
- Haha, you go in first.
- He's so mischievous.
- Why are you doing this?
- I changed my mind.
It was as if he was
waiting for this moment.
He's so mischievous.
- Haha, you go first.
- This is...
Sit down.
The Shooter of Mapo.
(The Shooter of Mapo
leaves while acting cool.)
- The Mapo Cowboy.
- Which room are you choosing?
The Mapo Cowboy.
(Each room has 1 more dollar now.)
(Room number 5,
they can exchange their items here.)
(He chose room number 5
where he can exchange items.)
Jong Kook.
Which room are you going to?
(Room number 1)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo agree to meet
in room number 1 with hand signals.)
If I get caught this time,
I'll be destroyed.
It's okay.
I have a bad feeling.
If I get caught alone...
I can picture Jae Suk staring at me.
It's terrifying.
- But if you...
- If I'm alone in the room...
If you're alone in the room,
you'll need to hand in everything.
So I need to...
Gosh, you startled me!
You startled me!
Officer, please don't kill me.
You must go to a room...
- with many people.
- I should.
(So Min tries to become allies
with Suk Jin.)
I need to go to a room with many people.
(So Min tries to become allies
with Suk Jin.)
- Here.
- Gosh, that startled me.
(Suk Jin gets scared
when he knows what's coming.)
Please pick the next person.
So Min will go next.
You're incredible.
(So Min goes into the room
she promised with Suk Jin.)
You can go next, old man.
Who are you calling an old man?
TikTok Grandpa.
Even foreigners write comments
on my posts.
- Saying what?
- "Nice, TikTok Grandpa."
It's driving me crazy.
"Nice, TikTok Grandpa?"
Why would you call me that?
- I'm not...
- "Grandpa."
I'm not that old.
- "TikTok Grandpa."
- It's driving me crazy.
- You!
- It's funny.
- Nice.
- It is funny.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
I'm a loyal man.
I made a promise to someone.
I'm running toward that person!
And that person is her!
(Shouting loudly)
- He's not good at skits.
- Indeed.
He was scolded a lot for that.
He doesn't sound like a pro comedian.
(As soon as Suk Jin leaves,
they talk about skits.)
There's a certain tone
that comedians use for skits.
(As soon as Suk Jin leaves,
they talk about skits.)
I'm bribing you in advance.
(His fellow comedian
secretly hands him a gem.)
I'll go to room number one,
so don't come into that room.
If I earn two gems,
I'll give you one later.
We have another chance to go in anyway.
You got it, right?
If you decline,
I won't be giving you any gems next time.
- Off you go.
- You got it, right?
- Okay, go now.
- I'm going to room number one.
- But...
- I heard a loud noise just now.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
There's a lot of stuff...
in here.
Don't take them.
I'll give them to you later.
- Just give me one more.
- No.
Give me a bottle and a gem. Okay?
You're just robbing me.
Jae Suk, if you...
Haha tricked me using the same way.
Those with protruding mouths
are like that.
- Go now.
- Okay.
I won't go into that room.
(The gangster with a protruding mouth...)
(enters the room after making a promise.)
(He carefully enters room number 1.)
(Room number 1)
(It's already filled with people.)
(Everyone except Haha
is gathered in this room.)
(Suk Jin, So Min, Jong Kook,
and Ji Hyo all decided...)
(to gather in room number 1.)
- Listen. I told him...
- Suk Jin.
(Number 1 is a popular spot
as there are many items.)
The search has begun.
(Thanks to Se Chan who bribed him,
they might not be caught.)
(The search begins.)
I'll start arresting them now.
(Vocalizing)
(He enjoys playing
an outlaw of the Wild West.)
(Showing how a comedy skit is done)
(The 6 gangsters are more nervous
after hearing Jae Suk singing.)
You punks!
Why is no one in here?
(He fails to catch them
in his 1st attempt.)
Please begin your second search.
(There are 4 rooms left
for him to search.)
(He promised to not enter
room number 1 after getting bribed.)
(He's left with rooms number 2, 4, and 5.)
(He has only one chance left.)
(Which room will the comedian cop pick?)
There you are!
- Darn it!
- Everyone's gathered here!
Darn you!
(Officer Yoo manages to arrest
5 people in room number 1.)
- All right!
- Too bad.
I got you all.
- Darn it.
- Officer!
- What?
- Are you serious?
I got nothing from the first room I chose.
Okay, okay.
(Room number 5,
they can exchange their items here.)
Where did Haha go?
(Haha survived alone
and took 4 dollars for himself.)
Haha went to room number five alone,
so you can exchange your items.
I'll exchange my money for a gem.
Money for a gem?
- Are you going to snitch?
- No, I am...
(The rest of them need to pick
a card to play.)
Who got caught?
Everyone except you.
- All 5 of them.
- All 5?
We were in the same room.
- Room number one?
- Yes.
- I'll stay quiet.
- Okay.
Do you really want to try that?
- No, no.
- Staying quiet.
(Staying quiet together)
(No, no.)
(No.)
(He has no intention of trusting anyone.)
If you choose to stay quiet,
- we can get the gems and bottles.
- No, no.
No, I'm never going to choose
to stay quiet.
He's ridiculous.
- What did you say?
- Besides,
- I'm sure you...
- Can't you use your head?
You'll choose to snitch for sure.
I said I'll choose to stay quiet.
All right. Make your decisions now.
(Which card will the 5 gangsters choose?)
- Let's do it.
- Se Chan.
- I'm staying quiet.
- Do you agree to stay quiet?
- Ji Hyo, you agree to stay quiet?
- Yes.
I'll stay quiet.
(If anyone snitches, those who chose
to stay quiet will suffer losses.)
Two...
(If anyone snitches, those who chose
to stay quiet will suffer losses.)
(They're done choosing their cards.)
- Snitch.
- That's bribing.
Two chose to snitch
and three chose to bribe.
Those who chose to bribe
will give their bottles away.
The two of you need to turn in everything.
(Only these two will have
their belongings confiscated.)
Oh, I forgot that bribing is an option.
My goodness.
This is quite a gain.
- You see? We...
- This is quite a gain.
- Give them to me.
- I mean...
- You learn from your experience.
- This is quite a gain.
If I told you to stay quiet,
- you should've all stayed quiet.
- All right now.
By now,
we'll be happily going home...
- with 2 gems and 2 bottles!
- Give them to me.
We still have another round to play.
- Give me everything you've got.
- This is frustrating!
Give them to me.
Choose the person who'll go first
for the next round.
- Jong Kook should go first.
- Me?
Next. Ji Hyo.
Mr. Officer.
(Mr. Officer.)
Is there anything I can do for you?
(Is there anything I can do for you?)
(Haha tries to make a deal
when there are fewer people.)
I promise not to go into the room
you choose.
- Please, I beg of you.
- You should go ahead.
(He sends Se Chan first.)
I'll trust you one last time.
Tell me the room you'll go into.
(Their negotiation starts
when there's no one around.)
I won't go into the room you're in
if you give me a dollar.
All right now.
Which room are you going to?
Okay. I won't go into room number two.
Please keep your promise.
- I won't go into room number two.
- I'll trust you.
- Please keep your promise.
- Okay.
Can't you trust me?
You already earned so much.
Okay.
Please go in now.
(Quietly and quickly, they strike a deal.)
(The last person,
Haha, enters a room.)
Mr. Officer.
(The last person,
Haha, enters a room.)
("Infinite Challenge")
(Haha asks for his help
for old times' sake.)
Barely.
(That won't work on me.)
I won't go into room number two.
I promise you.
(Haha went straight into room number 2.)
I...
I bribed Jae Suk.
- The search has begun.
- He won't come into this room.
(Meanwhile, the rest of them
are gathered in room number 1.)
(The search begins.)
Should I pick a small store
or a pawn shop?
(Room number 1
where 4 of them are gathered)
(Room number 2 where Haha
bribed Jae Suk not to come in)
Despite all that,
the tiger moths gathered here.
(Despite all that,
the tiger moths gathered here.)
Goodness. Why is no one here?
(His 1st search fails.)
I cleared one room.
(The room is full of tension
after the 1st crisis.)
I'll pick the next room.
(The room is full of tension
after the 1st crisis.)
(Did you bribe him not to come in?)
(I see.)
Darn you! You fraud!
(Officer Yoo betrayed them again.)
- You fraud!
- Come here!
- Come out here!
Don't talk back.
- I thought Haha bribed you.
- You fraud.
(Haha only ended up losing his gem.)
I thought Haha bribed you.
- Let's see how it'll turn out.
- Yes!
Have a seat. Have a seat.
The cop is clearly at an advantage.
Those who were in room number one...
get 2 bottles, 2 gems, and a dollar each.
- My gosh.
- I wasn't in that room.
2 bottles, 2 gems
Next, Haha and Suk Jin
will pick their cards.
- Let's throw one to the center.
- Okay.
(It's time for Haha and Suk Jin
to pick their cards.)
- One...
- Wait a minute. Suk Jin...
Why are you laughing?
I'm not concerned about them.
(Officer Yoo is looking forward
to collecting more items from them.)
- Get up.
- I'm not concerned about them.
Please count to three.
1, 2...
(They'll choose their cards right away.)
Three!
- What?
- What is it?
(Haha chose to stay quiet,
and Suk Jin's card is facing down.)
(If Suk Jin chose to stay quiet,
they can earn all the items.)
(What did Suk Jin choose?)
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
(What did Suk Jin choose?)
Yes!
(He chose to stay quiet!)
(It's the first time
they all chose to stay quiet.)
- We got it.
- We needed this.
They're advancing ahead of us.
My goodness.
(When Suk Jin and Haha were arrested...)
- If you don't stay quiet...
- Let's both stay quiet.
- I can't... What will you choose?
- Okay, okay.
You should swear on Dream.
- "Dream, I won't betray your dad."
- Dream.
Dream, if I betray your dad,
I won't be able to face you.
I promise you.
You promise Hyun Woo too.
- Promise Hyun Woo.
- Hyun Woo, if I betray your dad,
you don't need to call me uncle,
and I won't go near your house.
- But...
- Dream, I promise to stay quiet.
- Hyun Woo, you got it, right?
- Dream, I promise you.
- Married men, cross!
(Married men, cross!)
(Their loyalty came to fruition.)
(Officer Yoo gains nothing,
and Round 4 ends.)
I should buy some items too.
I'll exchange these.
(Officer Yoo buys points.)
That's seven points.
- Here you go.
- Haha, you should...
My gosh.
(If someone buys off points,
a new card takes its place.)
I'm going to buy ten points.
There you go.
(Jong Kook buys off 10 points,
and the card is replaced.)
Se Chan.
(Se Chan buys off points too.)
(The three of them take the lead.)
I'll pick a new ball now.
(They draw a new ball to pick a new cop.)
(Haha)
- It's me.
- Haha.
(The 3rd cop is Haha.)
Thank goodness.
I used all of my items.
Here you go.
(Haha got a golden opportunity.)
Please decide the order.
Ji Hyo should go first.
(The 6 gangsters entered the rooms.)
(Haha begins the search.)
2 bottles and 6 dollars.
(Haha contemplated a lot.)
Get out, you punks!
(He manages to catch 4 gangsters.)
(Room number 5,
they can exchange their items here.)
No one was in room number 1.
No one goes in there.
(After Round 5,
only So Min and Jae Suk remain.)
(They finally get a chance
to take the items.)
My gosh, this is...
(Despite that,
Officer Haha seems relaxed.)
Let's pick one, everyone.
We can choose to stay quiet.
But Se Chan could choose to snitch.
- No, he won't.
- I...
- It's because...
- I have too many bottles.
He has too many bottles.
- I'll choose to bribe.
- Okay, you should do that.
Those who are going to bribe can do that.
Let's go with either bribing
or staying silent.
- Go.
- One,
two,
(Not many rounds remain now.)
three.
(Which gangsters will acquire the items?)
Show your card.
Snitch, snitch, bribe.
(Snitch, snitch, snitch)
Now,
the three members who snitched
will lose all their belongings.
(The three members who snitched
lost all their belongings.)
I knew it.
What?
The three members who snitched
will lose all their belongings.
The member who bribed the officer
will turn in one bottle.
(Jong Kook avoids the situation
by turning in one bottle.)
I am rich!
(I am rich!)
- I am rich!
- That's unbelievable.
- I knew it.
- They will lose all the gems.
My goodness.
- Give me everything you've got.
- Here is my bribe.
All right.
Can't you stay silent?
I lost everything.
This is incredible!
(Officer Haha goes around
to collect the items.)
The next officer...
should get ready to accept bribes from me.
(The next officer should get ready
to accept bribes from me.)
I will be able to sell these bottles
and construct a building.
(Suk Jin)
- We don't lose the dollars, right?
- That's right.
For goodness' sake.
Why did I take a risk?
(Ji Hyo)
- It's best...
- I am no longer at the bottom.
to be the officer.
Choose the next order.
It's Round Six.
- This time...
- He is finally smiling.
- Jae Suk, go in first.
- Okay.
Officer Haha finally smiles
after getting conned twice.
I confiscated so much.
I tasted sweet success.
We gave you that success.
(Officer Haha smiles from ear to ear.)
(He displays his items
as he breathes heavily.)
(My goodness.)
You have everything.
- Officer Haha, are you happy?
- Yes.
Pick the next person.
Anyone can go.
I must be at the bottom.
(The gangster
who lost everything is bitter.)
- Go, Se Chan.
- I will go next.
So Min, go.
(The gangsters begin to enter.)
I will go next.
(After deciding the order,)
You found composure.
(he enjoys some free time with a snack.)
You designed this game so well.
It's so much fun.
I am so absorbed.
Is it room number four?
(Officer Haha begins
to search the rooms excitedly.)
Is it?
Shall I enter?
Shall I?
Shall I open the curtain?
(He is overly absorbed.)
(Officer Haha's voice becomes loud
after tasting success.)
Come on out!
(He barges into room number two.)
For goodness' sake!
(For goodness' sake!)
(Suk Jin gets apprehended.)
Why did you come to this room?
(He gets apprehended in a 1-dollar room.)
Hey.
Why did you check the room
with so few items?
I thought no one would enter
a one-dollar room.
(The poor gangster doesn't have
anything to turn in.)
Come on out! Gosh, it's empty.
The room is completely empty.
(He checks room number 3,
but fails to apprehend more people.)
(Jae Suk and So Min
can't divide 1 dollar.)
(Room number 5,
they can exchange their items here.)
(The 3 members in room number 4 get
1 bottle and 2 dollars each.)
All right.
Haha, you can buy what you want.
Haha will get many points.
- Haha will get many points.
- Seriously.
- Haha is excited right now.
- 2, 3.
Now, two rounds remain.
In the last two rounds,
all the rewards are doubled.
- That's incredible.
- Increase the rewards.
The gems and bottles will be doubled...
and two dollars will be added
to each room.
- We can turn the tables.
- Rounds 7 and 8...
will each have different officers.
Let's turn the tables.
The officer for Round Seven is...
- Let me be the officer.
- I want to be the officer.
Let me be the officer.
(Who will be the officer
for this important round?)
Suk Jin.
So Min.
- All right.
- Can we see the current scores?
We need to do well in this round.
I am at the bottom.
You don't need to be wary of me.
- Okay.
- I am at the bottom.
So Min, I am at the bottom.
I am the third from the bottom.
My ranking is pretty low.
Ji Hyo, go first.
You are sending the bottom ones first.
I will send the bottom ones first.
In every single round,
I was apprehended.
What could be the reason?
What's the reason?
It's not like I entered
room number one all the time.
I tried entering the room
with the smallest reward.
- Do you breathe loudly?
- What could be the reason?
- You must breathe loudly.
Do I breathe loudly?
Please send the next person.
I need to do well.
I know which rooms
the gangsters will enter.
(It's Officer Jeon's turn.)
The search has begun.
(She begins the search
as she pretends to be cool.)
(Let's see here.)
I will catch them without hesitation.
(Which rooms will So Min choose?)
I will choose...
these rooms.
These rooms.
(She chooses rooms number 1 and 5.)
(Will there be gangsters
inside the rooms So Min chose?)
(She checks room number 1.)
(She apprehends
Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo.)
I got you, you punks.
And I will go to...
(She walks over to room number 5.)
(Suk Jin gets apprehended again.)
I got Suk Jin!
Why did she enter this room?
He got apprehended again!
Suk Jin, come on out.
- What?
- I can't believe it.
Hey.
Room number five never got checked before.
Did he get caught again?
- Did he get caught again?
- Hey.
- You entered that room!
- Of course.
- That room...
- Why did you enter that room?
I felt like someone would be inside.
How did I get caught in room number five?
Where are Se Chan and Jong Kook?
They were in that room.
In room number one were...
three people, Ji Hyo, Haha, and Jae Suk.
(Haha, Jae Suk, and Ji Hyo
got apprehended.)
- Please decide.
- How many rounds remain?
One round remains after this one.
- It will be the last round.
- That's right.
Then Ji Hyo has no reason to snitch.
She needs items to buy points.
- Of course.
- She will go silent.
That's what I have been telling you.
You have no reason to snitch either.
- You have many points.
- I am holding the card.
Please help me out, just this once.
We should stay silent for Ji Hyo.
All right. One,
(Then Ji Hyo won't be at the bottom.)
two,
three.
(What will be the three member's choices?)
(Both Jae Suk and Ji Hyo
decided to snitch.)
Look at that.
(What is Haha's card?)
I knew this would happen.
(Bribe!)
- Haha is good.
- I knew this would happen.
- I chose to bribe her.
- Jae Suk.
- Ji Hyo!
- I knew this would happen.
- What happened?
I can't believe you.
Jae Suk,
I told you I'm at the bottom.
I couldn't let So Min confiscate
my belongings.
- I had too much to lose.
- Put them in here.
Here is one bottle.
I don't have any items.
- Gosh.
- Why don't you have more?
I will give you a bribe.
I will be at the bottom anyway.
Is there a chance to turn the tables?
I will choose the last officer,
which will give you a chance
to turn the tables.
(Please let me be an officer this time.)
- Here it comes.
- Okay.
(Who will be the last officer?)
Ji Hyo.
(The last officer is Ji Hyo!)
- Oh, no.
- Gosh!
Let's go.
I am so absorbed in the game.
Hey, that's because
things are going well for you.
I am so bored right now.
I get caught in every room.
No one goes silent.
- You know,
- I lose everything when I snitch.
you are just bad at the game.
I have no items for a bribe.
(He gets apprehended
100 percent of the time.)
Six points.
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, room number 5
lets you do a 1-on-1 exchange.
You should turn in your glasses and hat...
for items.
I could get ten points.
- Hey.
- What? Excuse me!
Would you give me a chance...
to enter room number five by myself?
- Sure.
- Room number five?
- Yes.
- Will that help you?
I could get ten points.
Okay, okay.
But you can't buy 10 points.
Is that your plan?
- Why are you sharing your plan?
- Well, no matter what I do,
- I get apprehended anyway.
- You have nothing.
Even when I don't share my plan,
I get caught.
- All right.
- What choice do I have?
I will enter room number five...
- if no one wants to enter it.
- I won't enter it.
- I can't divide the money.
- Ji Hyo is sitting right here.
She will do what she wants.
You won't enter room number five, right?
- Room number 5? Okay.
- Room number 5.
- That room has a small reward.
- Okay.
You don't need to come, okay?
I'm off.
Keep your promise, guys.
Who is next?
Please pick the next person.
- Shall I go next?
- Yes.
I will go in search of Suk Jin.
He should be in room number 1 or 5.
- Room number 1 or 5.
- Yes.
(Will Jae Suk enter room number 5
after Suk Jin?)
He is a hunter.
- A hunter for Suk Jin.
Let's catch Suk Jin
Yes, yes, yes
- Yes, yes, yes
In which room is Suk Jin?
Room number five!
Is he in room number one?
(Where is Suk Jin?)
It won't be good for you
to choose a room with one person.
You should catch someone with items.
You should catch Haha.
No, Haha...
- You are right.
- You just need his belongings.
(For Ji Hyo to avoid being the bottom,)
For goodness' sake.
This is a tricky situation.
(she needs to catch Haha,
the member with lots of items!)
(Haha chose room number 4.)
The search has begun.
(For Ji Hyo to beat So Min and Suk Jin,)
(she needs to apprehend Haha,
the member who has the most stuff!)
(The one who must avoid the search)
If it were me...
I will put myself in his shoes.
(The one who must catch the gangster)
If it were me...
(She puts herself in Haha's shoes.)
(Haha is in room number 4.)
Room number four.
(Oh, no.)
Room number three.
Room number two. Hold on.
(What will be Ji Hyo's first choice?)
You are here!
For goodness' sake.
(But Jae Suk doesn't have any items.)
Apprehending me
would be meaningless for you.
For goodness' sake.
You need someone with items.
You need to catch Haha.
You need to catch Haha, Ji Hyo.
Haha.
(Is she heading to room number 4?)
Room number four.
(A fierce game of wits
between the chaser and the chased)
There you are!
(Who will be the winner?)
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Se Chan
get apprehended.)
There you are!
(I'm safe!)
(Haha gets 2 bottles and 5 dollars!)
All right.
(So Min gets an exchange card
and 5 dollars.)
I was so scared that you would come.
- Were you in room number 5?
- Haha was in room number 4.
Which rooms did you check?
I have nothing to give you.
Jae Suk, do you have any belongings?
No, I don't.
- Jong Kook and Se Chan.
- Yes?
This is a good time for us
to come together.
It's only a matter of obtaining
a few more dollars.
What's the point of snitching
to obtain a few more dollars?
Let's think about the rankings then.
What will happen?
For example,
Jong Kook could be in first place.
I could beat the two of them...
and be in fifth place.
- It's plausible.
- Really?
- That's a big reward.
- With those goods,
- I could win so many points.
- There are dollars too.
I could buy over ten... Ten points.
(His voice cracks.)
- Dr. Hwang Soo Kwan.
- What's up with your voice?
- "I could buy over ten points."
- Dr. Hwang Soo Kwan.
Over ten points.
I could buy over ten points.
What's up with your voice?
- He is flustered.
- I could buy...
17 to 18 points.
He is nervous.
I need to stay silent
if I want to place second.
- Will you stay silent?
- I will stay silent.
I will stay silent.
It's meaningless for me to snitch.
Why... Do you believe Suk Jin?
You can believe me.
I have no reason to snitch.
Even if you snitch...
It won't do me any good...
because your belongings will go to Ji Hyo.
It won't do me any good. I can't snitch.
I can't snitch even if it's entertaining.
Then you won't be entertaining today.
- No. It's unfortunate.
- It's unfortunate.
Think about it.
- Please make up your mind.
- It won't do me any good...
to give items to my competitor, Ji Hyo.
I have no interest in beating you guys.
I have an interest
in beating the two of them.
Let's go. It's a competition.
I have no interest in beating you guys.
I have an interest
in beating the two of them.
(Suk Jin must beat So Min
and Ji Hyo to avoid the penalty.)
One,
two,
- three.
- Did someone snitch?
What?
(Jong Kook chose to be silent!)
- Did someone snitch?
- What?
(Suk Jin chose to be silent too!)
(Se Chan chose to snitch!)
- Hey.
- He snitched.
(Se Chan chose to snitch!)
(Upset)
Okay. That's it.
(Se Chan, in 4th place,
suddenly snitched.)
Hey, you...
This is how I become second place!
- Hey.
- He is in second place.
I saw the possibility.
(There is a reason
why Se Chan snitched in the end.)
Snitch, snitch.
(Se Chan had given up on winning
after Haha took all of his items.)
(No, you can take 2nd place.)
(He belatedly realized
that he can take 2nd place.)
(He saw the possibility of taking
2nd place,)
(but he feigned ignorance
to catch Suk Jin off guard.)
(He took all the items,
thanks to his poker face.)
We don't know the result yet. Let's see.
It was a mistake to trust you.
For goodness' sake.
(Se Chan ripped off Suk Jin.)
Until the end...
I had no intention
to enter room number one.
I had my hopes up until the end.
Why did you trust Ssaebssaeb?
Jong Kook and Suk Jin,
give all of your belongings...
except for the money to Ji Hyo.
Se Chan will receive seven dollars...
as well as 4 gems and 4 bottles.
- That's incredible.
- He will be in second place.
Thank you.
(Heavy)
- I shouldn't have...
- Justice lives!
- "Justice lives?"
(He thinks it's justice when he wins.)
It's time for the final purchase.
Ji Hyo can go first.
Shall I purchase ten points?
Don't I have enough items?
- Both?
- Yes.
(Which gangsters will win the prizes?)
I will reveal the prizes.
It's the luxurious tomahawk steak.
What is that?
- The second place will get melons.
- I love melons.
I will reveal the final scores.
Okay.
1st place has 39 points.
It's Haha.
2nd place has 35 points. It's Se Chan.
Is it me? Okay!
Bang, bang, bang!
3rd place is Jae Suk with 23 points.
4th place is Jong Kook with 22 points.
Fifth place is...
(Only one of them will avoid the penalty!)
So Min with 20 points.
- 20 points.
- Thank goodness.
6th place is Ji Hyo with 10 points.
7th place is Suk Jin with 4 points.
- What did you do today?
- Four points?
- Four points!
- What did you do today?
- That's too much.
- Four points?
Didn't you work today?
- What did you do?
- How did you get four points?
How did you get four points?
That's so funny. What a cute score.
The officer followed me
every time I entered a room.
Suk Jin with four points.
I will now reveal the penalty.
Give us something easy.
A single decision will change your fate...
in the Random Gun Game.
One water gun has ink
and the other one has water.
That's nice. It's a doable penalty.
Okay.
Have your backs against each other.
(They have a cute water gun match
on an expensive set.)
(There is no special equipment.)
It's cool. It's like a music video.
(Cameraman Kang Chan Hee moves
the camera himself.)
(Too much money was spent on the set
to borrow special equipment.)
One.
(Since there is no special equipment,)
- 2.
(their steps create tension.)
Three.
(Which gangster will get hit with ink?)
Turn around and shoot.
(She gets covered in ink.)
Bye, Suk Jin.
Don't come near me.
- Suk Jin won.
- I can't believe I won.
(Thus, the outlaws of the Wild West...)
(remained in that world.)
(The 7 members' 1st vacation
and the 2 energetic girls)
(Han Chae Young and Hur Young Ji)
- It's a creek.
- It has been a while.
(They enjoy delicious food in nature,)
(but right then...)
(The vacation turns unpleasant.)
(You are so unpleasant.)
How am I unpleasant?
(The high level of discomfort...)
(makes the members sensitive.)
(You are bound to be voted
Unpleasant Man today.)
(Unpleasant Man ruins the vacation.)
(Despite the presence of Unpleasant Man,)
(they must have fun.)
(Somewhere between unpleasantness
and pleasantness...)
(lies their vacation of 2021.)
- I am so upset.
- You are upset, right?
- How about you?
- I am upset.
- I am happy.
(How will the vacation
of the energetic 9 turn out?)
(The Delightful Men and Women's Vacation)