(A tile-roofed house
with the charm of a Hanok)
All right. Let's go.
- Oh, dear.
- Hello.
- Hello, guys.
- All right.
Good morning.
Hello.
- We're...
- Where's Lord Yu?
Why won't Lord Yoo pay us
our salaries?
- Actually,
- Salaries?
everyone feels pressure
for different reasons.
My gosh.
We all have different reasons.
Let's get it started.
(Running Man prepared
a coffee truck...)
(to celebrate the 30th anniversary
of Jae Suk's debut.)
(And the message on the cup sleeve
caught people's eyes.)
Jae Suk.
A few decades ago,
I was just like an immature child.
But now, we're already middle-aged.
And he...
(But he suddenly burst into tears.)
He seemed so happy.
(And he cited famous sayings
out of the blue.)
Actually, everyone feels pressure
for different reasons.
(This is where Haha quoted it from.)
(Actually, everyone feels pressure
for different reasons.)
I bet everyone does.
(Pressure ASMR)
(Big Nose celebrated
Jae Suk's 30th year with tears.)
(Deeply ashamed)
- I'm under a lot of pressure.
- Hey.
Gosh, I got goosebumps.
What's that thing on your forehead?
I needed something to cover my hair.
- Hey, why did you put it on there?
- What's wrong?
Suk Jin, what did your tears mean?
- I've thought about it,
- It's not like that.
and I should stop
making fun of him now.
- No, that's not it. It's okay.
- He might burst into tears.
- He's such a crybaby.
- No, I'm not.
- What a crybaby.
- What was with your glasses?
You kept touching your glasses
trying to hold back tears.
He was trying to hold it back.
He stared at the camera crying.
Actually, I didn't want to say
anything when they asked me to.
We've had a lot of sad occasions
on Running Man so far.
You didn't even cry
when Gary left our show.
(The last episode
that featured Gary)
(Calm and impassive)
You will have to wail
when Kwang Soo leaves.
- You should weep aloud.
- It's not like that.
Are you ready to wail?
- I got goosebumps.
- It's not something I can prepare.
I was just in tears
before I knew it.
- What's that car?
- That's a car only for big stars.
- Really?
- Gosh, what's that?
The car looks so pretty.
(A car pulls into the old house,
transcending space and time.)
- It's really pretty.
- That's a car only for big stars.
- What?
- Today's guest must be a big star.
- This is really cool.
- It's so pretty.
- Look at the car.
- It looks comfortable.
(Bling-bling)
- This is something you can find...
- He's a big star.
at a motor show.
- Right.
- Look at the color.
- I bet the trunk is spacious.
- It will make you a star.
There's a star.
- There's a big star.
- Lord Yu.
(The servants are
crawling to Lord Yu.)
Oh, dear.
Please get off.
- Yoo Yaho.
- Why are you in the car?
Okay. I'm here.
Be careful.
- Star Yu.
- Jae Suk is the lord.
- Right.
- Why did you make him cry?
Please step on her back.
Hey, the time has changed.
Move over.
- Is that So Min?
- She's So Min.
- Move over.
- I thought it was Kwang Soo.
- Me too.
- I also thought it was me.
- Thank you for coming so early.
- Lord Yu.
- You need a shave.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- All right.
Hey. Good morning.
What's that thing on your head?
- I decorated it a little.
- Okay.
Aren't you going to pay us?
- What did you say?
- We haven't been paid for months.
You will lose your teeth.
Don't do that.
Don't be like that to Suk Jin.
- He might cry.
- Why did you make him cry?
- Don't cry.
- I'm not crying.
Why would you make a scene
at my workplace?
I didn't mean it.
Why... Why did you weep?
- It's not like that.
- Why did you do that?
- I tried to hold it back.
- Why did he weep there?
- He's a crybaby.
- No, I'm not.
Don't be like that.
Actually, everyone feels pressure
for different reasons.
Stop it!
- That's enough.
- Stop saying that.
Enough is enough.
I can't take this anymore.
- I mean...
- I can't stand it.
He says he has no tears.
- That's black tears.
- Crocodile tears.
- Crocodile tears. It's fake.
- It's fake.
- I know.
- So what are we doing today?
- Why are we dressed like this?
Why am I a lord?
Is this to celebrate
the 30th anniversary of his debut?
This is
the Three Meals for Jae Suk Race.
(Three Meals for Jae Suk)
- Three Meals for Jae Suk?
- That's...
Jae Suk talked about it before.
- They're doing it for real.
- Right. Three Meals for Jae Suk.
That's what I said.
Why are we doing it here?
That's right.
It's the Three Meals for Jae Suk.
(I'm planning a new show.)
(Jae Suk talked about the show
with some sauce on his lips.)
(It's a show where his close friends
cook three meals for Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk will be the only one
to dress as a nobleman.)
(The crew members carried out
his plan right away.)
I said I was planning a show,
and they carried it out.
I thought we should do it
before your favorite servant leaves.
Oh, right. Kwang Soo is leaving.
Gosh, this is a mess.
He cried on another show,
and he's leaving our show.
- This is a mess.
- It's a total disaster.
I can't believe
how things are going here.
Don't be like that. Actually,
everyone feels pressure
for different reasons.
He tried his best.
- Right.
- My goodness.
He was under a lot of pressure.
By the way, Servant Se Chan is...
He's a mere servant,
but he made a hole in one.
Why would you say that now?
Why would you bring that up?
- A hole in one?
- That's amazing.
- On a real golf course?
- And you should stop...
hanging out with the members
of "2 Days and 1 Night 4."
Members of "2 Days and 1 Night 4?"
You mean DinDin.
Right.
- Hey.
- How dare you...
Just make sure to take
care of JinJin.
(JinJin, a servant with 12 years
of experience)
Take good care of JinJin.
I'm sorry.
Stop worrying about DinDin...
- and take good care of JinJin.
- Excuse me.
- Okay?
- You can call me JinJin,
but I'm not Jing Jing.
- Just care about JinJin.
- I will take good care of him.
So this is
the Three Meals for Jae Suk Race.
The servants should cook
three meals for Lord Yu.
Once Lord Yoo finishes
his three meals,
the race is over.
- Really?
- He's not doing anything today.
However,
each servant has a penalty stick...
that has their names on it.
A stick will be drawn
at the end of the race,
and the member whose name
is on the stick will get a penalty.
Only one member
will get a penalty for now.
And regardless of the penalty,
Lord Yoo can pick one member
to get a prize with.
(Lord Yoo can pick a member
to get a prize.)
- Lord Yoo will pick one?
- Yes.
I'm sure...
he will pick Suk Jin.
So you will need to get
more sticks for other members...
to reduce your chance
of getting picked for a penalty.
I'll tell you how you can get
more penalty sticks.
Lord Yoo will start the race
with 100 nyang.
- 100 nyang?
- Yes.
With the coins,
you can make servants...
buy ingredients...
or pay them for their labor.
- I can pay them.
- And the servants...
should save the coins.
You can buy a penalty stick
for another member with five nyang.
With 15 nyang, you can buy
a penalty stick for Lord Yu.
We can buy one for Lord Yu.
But we can't do that to Lord Yu.
And...
Lord Yoo can't buy anything himself.
- Really?
- If he wants to buy something,
he should find a servant
whom he can trust...
and make the servant buy
what he needs.
And if Lord Yoo gets
three penalty sticks,
you will elect a new lord.
- A new lord?
- That's nice.
(If Lord Yoo gets 3 penalty sticks,
there will be a new lord.)
(There's a glimmer of hope
for the servants.)
- Jae Suk's eyes are shaking.
- Seriously?
- He's nervous.
- Jae Suk's eyes are shaking.
We should get a new lord.
- I'll survive no matter what.
- That's not bad.
So if two members each pay
15 nyang...
to buy two penalty sticks
for Lord Yu,
one of you will become
the new lord by drawing lots.
Gosh, this is serious.
- I have to stay a lord.
- We can change the lord.
- We can do this.
- It will be tough.
But every time the lord changes,
the number of members to get
the penalty will increase by one.
So you will need
to make careful decisions.
(Every time the lord changes,
more members get the penalty.)
So we can change the lord.
- But 15 nyang is a lot.
- We can't do that to Lord Yu.
- It's three times as much.
- If we do that to Lord Yu,
- Suk Jin will blame us.
- He will cry.
- Oh dear.
- My gosh.
- This year...
- He's like Jae Suk's right hand.
I'll give him a hard time.
- We should do it behind his back.
- You'll see.
So this is the first meal
Lord Yoo will have today.
Should we cook it for him?
- Do we have to?
- Of course.
How would we do that?
Why are your toes sticking out?
I'm not wearing socks.
- Is this...
- Galbijjim and jeon?
(The first meal, galbijjim and jeon)
- Are we supposed to make it?
- Are we cooking?
To make the dishes,
you should get coins from Lord Yu
to buy ingredients...
and cook as much as you want.
Really?
Prices are high here.
Lord Yoo has a lot of money.
- I bet he's rich.
- Right.
Gosh, Lord Yu.
Please be generous.
All right then. I appreciate...
that you're working hard for me
so early in the morning.
- Lord Yoo is the best.
- I see.
- He's so sweet.
- So...
- He's open-minded.
- It was inconceivable...
in the Joseon Dynasty.
- He's a real nobleman.
- I'm...
We don't need a new lord.
I'm not like other lords.
You guys...
- Hang on.
- Yes, Lord Yu.
How dare a servant sit...
- with his legs crossed?
- Who?
Who's the disrespectful...
I straightened out my legs.
- My gosh.
- It's not like that.
I didn't know we started the shoot.
- You crossed your legs?
- This isn't about the shoot.
We're in a hierarchical society now.
Exactly.
Do you not know what it is like
to be in the Joseon Dynasty?
Not really.
I can't believe this.
- He needs a good scolding.
- Hang on a second.
- Wait. I can't take this anymore.
- Coins.
I'm not so strict.
(He takes out his 100 nyang.)
Gosh, Lord Yu.
- Coins...
- He's being generous.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Coins...
- He's being generous.
(What about me?)
You'd need some money...
- My gosh.
- to do your job.
Thank you.
- I mean, this is...
- Thank you.
- You can't work for nothing.
- Thank you, sir.
You should get paid.
Will you keep discriminating
against me?
- You're the best, Lord Yu.
- Hang on.
What did you just say, Seok Sam?
"Will you keep discriminating
against me?"
- What was that?
- How could you...
- Why would you say that?
- I was flustered.
He just learned the Korean alphabet.
- But why am I...
- I told you.
That's because
you're being disrespectful.
He's disrespectful indeed.
- My gosh.
- I told you.
Unlike the other servants,
you're just nasty.
- You're being ridiculous.
- Ridiculous?
I can't take this anymore.
- He can't stand it.
- All right.
Show him some respect.
- Hey.
- I mean...
- Here.
- Again? Thank you.
- All right.
- Thank you, sir!
All right.
- You should be...
- How dare you...
Hey, that's enough.
Stop it.
Anyway,
you guys should cook my first meal.
- Count off.
- One.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
- 7. End of count.
Are we soldiers or what?
- I mean...
- I don't think...
they did this in the Joseon Dynasty.
- Just stay quiet.
- This is ridiculous.
- What's wrong with you?
Do you want to work lying down?
(He's a loyal servant.)
(Servant Kim is serious
about being a servant.)
- Hey.
- Do you pay him a lot?
- Jong Kook.
- How much do you pay him?
I appreciate your loyalty,
but he needs to work.
So don't hit his legs.
- Okay. I won't hit his legs.
- Okay?
- Can we get married?
- What?
Can servants get married?
- With each other?
- Yes.
- In-house romance is forbidden.
- Okay.
Do you understand?
But I'm married.
- What did you say?
- I have a wife at home.
She shouldn't stay at home.
Bring her!
She has to work.
- No.
- Why would she stay at home?
- It's not like that.
- Bring her.
You should bring your wife.
- Your whole family should work.
- We're not a double-income family.
Where's your punk son?
- His punk son?
- Bring him as well.
How dare you...
- Jong Kook.
- He's a slave.
My punk son?
- You should bring your punk son.
- Gosh, this is scary.
Am I supposed to let this slide?
You should bring
your punk kid as well.
- Listen.
- I don't think JinJin knows...
what things are like here.
Have a seat.
- JinJin.
- Yes?
It was a hierarchical society
in the Joseon Dynasty.
- This isn't about hierarchy.
- And it is passed down.
It's passed down the family line.
If you're married,
Ms. Ryu Su Jung should be here
as well.
- Sure.
- For me...
She should sweep the yard.
You know him. He's a slave hunter.
I go after runaway slaves...
as a side job.
- He's a famous slave hunter.
- Really?
- My friend...
- Servant Kim...
- is just happy to be here.
- Exactly.
- Anyway, I need to eat breakfast.
- Okay.
You should go to the market...
and buy ingredients
for galbijjim and jeon.
Okay.
(Lord Yoo can't buy things himself.)
(He should give money
to a servant he can trust.)
(And servants can pocket the money.)
Like I said before,
you don't have to spend
a lot of money.
Make sure to buy things
at reasonable prices.
We will be sure to do that.
Like I said before,
I want Jong Kook to do this.
- Do you want me to go? Okay.
- Jong Kook, you're on it.
- And Long Legs.
- Yes, sir.
- I want to go.
- Okay. Ji Hyo, you're going too.
Okay. We're leaving now.
- Let's go.
- We should check the prices.
We didn't get the money.
We just need to check the prices.
- The servants...
- We can just take it.
The two meals...
- My gosh.
- He found one.
(The servants are picking up
lucky bags.)
There are...
coins and penalty sticks
hidden everywhere.
If you find one, you can keep it.
All right. Hurry and make a fire.
The weather is cool today.
Yes, sir.
(Wielding an ax)
Hey, what are you doing?
- Are you hammering or what?
- This is strange.
- Why is this...
- What was that?
Are you carving in your name?
This is... Watch out.
Hit it in the middle.
Move over.
I don't think I'll get hurt.
You did it. It worked.
See?
My goodness.
(Servant Ji hasn't gotten
any better for the past 11 years.)
- This is it.
- My gosh.
(It's the Ingredient Store
that sells cooking ingredients.)
(They don't have fixed prices.)
- Hello.
- They have all the ingredients.
- This place looks nice.
- How much are these?
- Let's see.
The meat is five nyang.
And a squid is three nyang.
Scallions are one nyang.
(They need about 15 to 20 nyang
to cook galbijjim and jeon.)
My gosh.
It's three nyang.
(They can save some money
if they give up ingredients.)
We should pocket some money.
(The slave hunter has decided
to embezzle some money.)
Gosh, what should we do now?
(The three servants have decided
to cheat Lord Yoo out of his money.)
15?
- 10.
- 10?
(They go back home
discussing the fake prices.)
How much is the meat?
Meat is 10 nyang.
Meat is 10 nyang. And...
the other ingredients
cost three nyang each.
And squid is five nyang.
Do they have squid?
Then you should give them the money.
Right.
- Once you give us the money...
- We can't cook without the money.
So the meat is...
What do we need? Meat is 10 nyang.
10 nyang.
We need 13 nyang.
So we need about 30 nyang in total.
In total.
For the flour to make jeon...
(Kwang Soo inflated the prices
even more to 30 nyang.)
Tell me the prices again.
(He sensed that
something's not right.)
So the meat is 10 nyang.
10 nyang.
- And?
- Squid is five nyang.
- And the other ingredients...
- are all 3 nyang.
- All the others are 3 nyang.
Then I guess 20 nyang should be
enough for all ingredients we need.
I agree.
- But you asked me for 30 nyang.
- Right.
- What I'm saying is...
- Hey.
Hey, he said 18 nyang is enough.
Why did you ask me for 30 nyang?
I mean, we need
some other ingredients as well.
- Like what?
- Like green onion...
- They sell vegetables there too.
- Oh, right.
But we'll make jeon as well,
so we need more than 25 nyang...
Here's 20 nyang.
- 20 nyang? Okay then.
- 20 nyang?
Let's shop within our budget.
- You should do that.
- Green onion... And what else?
- Ji Hyo, take 20 nyang...
- Yes? 20 nyang.
- With that money...
- We'll spend it wisely.
- Spend it wisely.
- We'll make it work.
Good.
Let's make it work.
Let's do our best.
- But 20 nyang is...
- Hey, let's make it work.
- Wait. Hey, Long Legs, stay here.
- Let's make it work.
(Pardon?)
Okay. Long Legs will stay.
Let's go without Long Legs.
(Heartless)
It's not like that.
- You made the right decision.
- Let's go without Long Legs.
- Why?
- He always tries to pocket money.
- No, I mean...
We still received more money
than we actually need.
We should ask for a discount.
Then we can save some more money.
(They're going
to the store cheerfully.)
You can find dishware
on the way to the vegetable garden.
Oh, right. We have to pay
for the dishware too.
No, it's provided free.
- Gosh, you punk.
- Hey.
Why would you tell such a lie
when we were all informed?
Lord Yu! Lord Yu!
(Servant Ha is entering hastily.)
I found this...
- at the vegetable garden.
- What is it?
That punk...
(Servant Ha tries to frame Kwang Soo
with the pouch he found.)
- Search his bag.
- No. Don't do that.
- I didn't do that!
- How dare you?
- For each coin...
- You filthy jerk!
- This punk did it.
- I found another one.
- He had these pouches.
- Look at that.
- How dare you?
- It's not like that.
- Get on your knees, you punk.
- How dare you?
This isn't fair!
- My gosh.
- You were supposed to work.
- Trust me. I didn't do anything.
- Punish him right now.
- No! It wasn't me!
- You punk.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- Bring it here.
- You must know...
- It's not true. Ouch!
It hurts so much.
- You must know...
- It's not true. Ouch!
(Ouch! It hurts so much!)
What was that?
How could you
actually twist my legs?
- Why did you do that?
- That sly jerk...
How dare you to try to ruin
everything...
- before you leave the show?
- It's true.
My lord, I've been working for you
like a loyal dog...
for more than 43 years.
Please give me just one nyang.
I can't give you any more than that.
Understood?
But hey, I brought you the evidence.
- Hang on. Did you just say, "hey?"
- Right?
- Let's punish him.
- How dare you...
- talk down to him?
- Come with us.
- How could you...
- You shouldn't do that.
- I didn't mean to.
- Let's punish him.
- Hey.
- Let go of me, you punks!
Hey. Hey.
He and I worked together
for 20 years as slaves.
(Double punishment)
Stop it! Stop!
(Both of them were punished
at the same time unintentionally.)
Why did you sit there?
- You fool.
- You should have avoided my legs.
You should've twisted only his legs.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
came back from the store.)
- They're back.
- Oh, gosh.
- Look at this.
- Did you get meat?
Listen. We got all this...
- at a big discount.
- Really?
- I thought of beating him up too.
- I see.
Then there won't be much money
left for us.
We'll buy some more food later.
You get to live.
Wouldn't that matter?
- I got a discount eventually.
- You negotiated the price.
- Good job.
- Thank goodness you didn't hit him.
- Hey, by the way,
- Yes, I negotiated the price. Yes?
Stop fighting with others.
- Okay?
- Understood.
Hurry up and start cooking.
- How should we cook pork ribs?
- Exactly.
- Hey, Long Legs.
- Yes, my lord.
- Come and fan the fire.
- Where are the vegetables?
- Come on. Move faster.
It's almost noon.
I need to eat something!
- We have to cook...
- He's upset.
Lord Yoo is angry!
(Lord Yoo yelled in a vulgar manner.)
- What's with his tone?
- Hey!
Let's change the lord
as soon as we can. This is too much.
Green onion jeon.
(The discontent among the servants
is growing.)
There's a frying pan, and there are
all sorts of condiments.
- Wait. Hold on.
- We should start...
- Seok Sam,
- Yes?
- Ssaebssaeb,
and the two of you
including Long Legs,
carry my litter,
so I can go downtown.
Hang on a second.
- My lord.
- Didn't you just get here?
Why do you keep giving me
physically taxing jobs?
Why would you ride a litter?
- Do we actually have a litter?
- Do we? What's that?
All right.
- We should carry this?
- I mean...
- Now...
- Where did you say you're going?
(The 100 percent
human-powered vehicle)
- All right.
- It'll be easier to carry the back.
Haha.
- It's better to carry the back.
- I think it's carried by two men.
Lift the front.
2 in the front and 2 at the back.
- Can't you just walk?
- How dare you?
- It's right there.
- Both of your legs are fine.
- Why must we carry this?
- It's only five steps away.
(As the servants are complaining...)
- It's right in front of the house.
- Lift me up now!
- This is too harsh.
- Come on.
1, 2, 3.
- Oh, gosh.
- Good.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Yes?
- It's slanted!
- That's weird. Why is it slanted?
It's tilting toward Haha. Seriously.
I think I shouldn't carry this.
- It's because I'm taller than them.
- Put me down.
- It's hard to balance it.
- The positions may be wrong.
- Hey.
- You go to the front.
- Hold it properly, will you?
- To the front.
- Okay.
- Come here.
- Hey, hold it properly, will you?
- I did, but I couldn't help it.
- Listen to me.
- Come over here.
Do you want to be in trouble
right before you leave the show?
- No. I held it properly.
- Do you? Hey.
- Hey, hey.
- You stand here.
Gosh, seriously.
- Hey, stop complaining!
- Let's lift it up.
Wait. Hold on.
Move the litter as smoothly as
the car we were provided with...
for the indirect advertisement,
okay?
- Yes, my lord.
- That elegantly?
Exactly.
- That's impossible.
- You should move it...
as elegantly and safely as the car.
By any chance, will you ride it
with your entire family?
- Okay.
- On the count of three. Get ready.
You look like a top star
on the litter.
- Let's go.
- Hold it.
Lift it up. 1, 2, 3.
- Okay. Let's go.
- That's good.
- That was smooth.
- Move forward.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- 1, 2.
- Let's have a tour.
- Hey, move aside.
- What's that?
We're almost there already.
- Keep going.
- This is ridiculous.
Hey, you can just walk there.
- "Hey?" How dare you?
- It's right over there.
- Keep going. I'm a nobleman.
- Why would you...
This is what a nobleman does.
It caught fire so quickly.
Really?
- Well...
- How is galbijjim usually made?
Since it's pork, not beef,
I think we can just add that sauce,
and put in some vegetables...
Put everything in the pot
and boil them together. That'll do.
(Ji Hyo started preparing
the ingredients for galbijjim.)
I must say, Ji Hyo works really hard
and does it well.
- I do my work quietly.
- Yes, you're good at that.
Se Chan, yalbijjim...
I mean, galbijjim...
So Min is a great cook.
I should make green onion jeon.
(So Min is preparing the ingredients
for green onion jeon.)
- Is it for green onion jeon?
- Yes.
Marinate the meat
with the sauce first.
Okay.
Jong Kook is unexpectedly good
at cooking.
We can't ruin any piece.
Shall I bring another one?
We have one more spatula.
To make jeon.
It's so nice
to watch you guys working.
- We'll have a party, my lord.
- That's great.
- All the dishes look quite good.
- Ji Hyo.
I'm a little hungry.
My lord, it will be ready soon.
- Don't boil it down.
- I know.
Hey, hey, Long Legs.
- Yes?
- You seem free. Come over here.
That's not true. I was...
- preparing to cook...
- Come over here.
Let's go over there.
(Hopping)
What...
My lord, who is going to carry you
on his back from next week?
- Exactly.
- None of us is as tall as he is.
I won't get to ride on his back
anymore.
(Lord Yoo is enjoying
riding on the tall servant.)
You'll get a lower ride.
- Put me down here.
- Yes, my lord.
He rode on his back
just to come here?
This is crazy.
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
- That looks good.
- Why would he make me...
You should boil it for a long time.
- It looks delicious.
- Kwang Soo, come with me.
Here. You can have this.
Why?
For no reason. Today is
your last day on the show.
Gosh. I told you
not to act like this.
- Take it.
- Why would you give me a coin?
- Just take it.
- Why are you doing this?
- Just take it. What's the point...
- Listen to me.
It's my coin.
I want to give it to him.
- Hold on.
- Why would you give me your coin?
Don't go easy on me.
Well, I'll just put it here.
Gosh. Just keep it.
(He put bait to lure Long Legs
who is crazy about coins.)
Keep it.
Then give it to me instead.
Are you not going to be
on the show next week?
- Next week...
- You'll keep being on the show.
- That's true.
- He won't be here next week.
- Is that why you want to give him?
- Yes. It'll be pointless to win.
- I think the food is ready.
- Yes.
Scoop out the rice.
- And set the table here.
- Yes.
Yes, my lord.
Seok Sam, hold this janggu.
- And play it for me.
- Me?
I've never played it before.
I have never played it before.
But I'll do it since you told me to.
(With a nervous look on his face,)
(he started playing it carefully.)
It feels good, let's have some fun
- We cooked
- Wait...
- Wait until the food is served.
- It feels good, let's have some fun
- Start playing when the food is...
- Today, we'll have a party
It feels good, let's have some fun
We have galbijjim
and green onion jeon
It feels good, let's have some fun
Cabbage jeon is tasty too,
it feels good, let's have some fun
Lord Yoo is as stubborn as a mule,
I can't stand him anymore,
it feels good, let's have some fun
Let us all work together
- It feels good, let's have some fun
Everyone feels pressure
for different reasons
It feels good, let's have some fun
(He overcame the pressure
and sang the entire work song.)
I'll bring you the other dishes.
This looks so delicious.
Ji Hyo did an amazing job.
We made cabbage jeon as well
since you like it.
So Min did a great job.
- Ji Hyo did an amazing job.
- We made cabbage jeon as well...
(He's having a big bite
of crispy jeon.)
- How do you like it?
- She made cabbage jeon?
- Do you like it?
- Is it okay?
- Really?
- It's good.
I'm finally getting a coin.
It's so hard to make him
spend money.
He's finally taking a coin out.
- So Min.
- Yes, my lord.
- I'll give you three nyang.
- Oh, my.
We made it together, my lord.
- Thank you.
- Hey, we made it together.
Just give me one nyang.
- Did you scoop it out?
- It looks delicious.
Shouldn't you put some more
in the bowl?
Scoop out some more.
That looks good.
Jae Suk is actually eating alone
over there.
I can't believe him.
He must think he's really a lord.
He didn't even offer us a bite.
- Isn't he too mean?
- Is it good?
My lord, here's galbijjim.
- Please try it.
- Please try a bite.
The table is too small.
- Let me taste it.
- Let's bring another table.
(I eat alone.)
There's not much left.
Give him a bite.
- He did it on another show.
- Gosh, look at him.
We cooked it in an iron pot,
my lord.
(Standing in line)
(Seok Sam seems dazed
because he's hungry.)
That kimchi smelled so good too.
- Watching Lord Yoo enjoying it...
- Everything looks so good.
- makes me feel great.
- Indeed.
- But he can't finish all that.
- It makes me happy.
Can we... Can we eat some too?
You can eat some
if Lord Yoo lets you.
We only have a few potatoes left.
My lord, can we eat a little too?
How about just one of us eats?
(Shaking his head)
- Gosh, seriously.
- Is that a no?
I can't believe him.
Why can't we eat?
- Let's change the lord. I'm angry.
- What's wrong with him?
Let's all pitch in
to change the lord.
- I think we should.
- That's so mean.
What do you say? Are you in?
Lord Yoo is so kind and generous
to us.
We don't have to think
about doing anything.
Hey, you guys, do you like
living in this world?
- Let's turn the world upside down,
- That's why you're always a slave.
and make it a world that we rule.
That's why you can't be freed
from slavery.
Why won't they try to be freed?
- Just the two of us?
- Let's make a new world.
- We need 15 coins, right?
- Yes.
(What they have is far from enough.)
- If we collect 15 coins...
- Right. Let's go.
(They plan to go outside
to find more coins.)
There's another one.
Oh, my. I found another pouch.
(Kwang Soo found a pouch,
and there's a penalty stick in it!)
Hey. I found it too.
What's this?
We can write a name on it
and turn it in.
Write a name on it and turn it in?
Do we write a name on this
and turn it in?
Suk Jin, we can collect 15 of these
and turn them in.
Do we write a name on this
and turn it in?
Yes, but you're not allowed to write
the lord's name on it.
- We can do it by ourselves.
- Let's hold on to it for now.
(They can buy a penalty stick
with coins.)
(The penalty stick they can write
a lord's name on is marked red!)
(They need 3
of Lord Yu's penalty sticks...)
(to change the lord!)
(Will Seok Sam and Long Legs
succeed in changing the lord?)
- How many coins do you have?
- I have three.
I think I have 5 coins.
No, I have 4.
- That's not enough.
- We have only seven coins.
- We need 15 nyang.
- Let's find 8 more coins.
There's a lot of pouches
hidden in different places.
You have one, right?
Let's turn in our penalty sticks.
Let's not write each other's names.
I'll write Se Chan's name on it.
He's so cheeky.
- I choose Jong Kook.
- Here you go.
- It's good.
- Lord Yoo is so nice.
He's not a bad person.
- Hey, where did Seok Sam...
- Here.
and Long Legs go?
Long Legs? He must've gone out
to find more pouches.
I think he did too.
- Everyone, let's eat.
- Let's eat here.
- Se Chan, here you go.
- Thank you.
Eat as much as you want
since you worked hard to cook.
- Let's sit down here.
- Thank you, my lord.
We should go and get food.
- My, it's so delicious.
- It's really good.
I feel like a slave.
I feel like a real slave.
I really feel like
a slave right now.
It's as if war just broke out.
We wouldn't dare
to sit there with him.
What are you doing?
Come over here
so Lord Yoo can eat comfortably.
Okay.
You can come and eat here.
- Can we, really?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- When could we...
- You look like a real servant.
- Se Chan is...
- It's so realistic.
- I'm just acting.
- He looks so natural, right?
- You're not just acting.
- I'm acting.
- Se Chan, eat some jeon too.
- That looks so good.
- Right?
- Yes.
- It's so good.
- Do you like it?
Eat up.
- It's so good.
- Give some to Ji Hyo too.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's so tasty.
- So Min, this is amazing.
- It's good, right?
(He's into his character
even when eating.)
- It's good.
- I mean...
You seemed to make it so easy
and yet it's so good.
- It's really tasty.
- It's delicious.
(While they're impressed
by the effect of an iron pot...)
- Are you eating?
- What?
Did you all finish your food?
- Yes, my lord.
- We enjoyed it.
- Wait. We didn't...
- Then...
We're starving.
You weren't here when we had food.
Did you make bibimbap?
A store-bought sauce is the best.
It's hard to believe
that you made this so quickly.
(Seok Sam and Long Legs are
finally trying the food.)
Did we really make this?
It's so delicious.
He said "we."
What do you mean by that?
- You didn't...
- All you did was play the janggu.
You didn't cook.
Hey, are you on our side
or his side?
Don't try to divide us into teams.
Shouldn't we be grateful
for food and a place to sleep?
- Look how you guys are eating.
- You all look so happy.
Why would you make a fuss about it?
You're sitting next to Lord Yu.
- Sitting on this bench...
- It makes us feel...
as if we moved up in social class.
- Now stand in line.
- Yes, my lord.
Stand in line.
- Stand in line.
In the order of seniority.
- Hey, who do you think you are?
- All right.
- Jong Kook, lead the group.
- Get in the back of the line.
- Yes, my lord!
- Seok Sam, get in the back.
- Starting from Seok Sam, count off.
- Seok Sam.
- 1.
- 2.
- 3. 4.
- 5.
- 6.
- 7. End of the number.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Yes.
- Jong Kook probably won't change.
- Jong Kook is unbelievable.
Why is Jong Kook...
- so obedient?
- Let's go.
Also, do you know this?
That I will choose one of you...
to receive a prize along with me.
- Oh, right.
- Okay!
Yes, my lord.
Stand in your position!
(Stand in your position!)
You just sound like a gangster.
Have you decided
to stick to that image?
- He looks like...
- Stand in line!
- Is he a gangster or what?
- What was that?
- He acts like a gangster.
- I mean...
If you don't obey me,
I'll put a brand on your body.
Why is he acting like that?
(As if I burnt my heart)
Why is he so loyal to Jae Suk?
Was he always that obedient to him?
Jong Kook, step forward.
Here.
- I'll give you one nyang.
- Thank you, my lord.
- You look like a pet dog.
- Good.
- I can always trust you.
- Of course.
Why is he so loyal to Jae Suk?
You should never forget
that you're a slave.
What's with his tone?
- I don't understand.
- Calm down.
Calm down. You are right.
- My gosh.
- He's such a loyal servant.
He's just a bully.
- We were born slaves.
- Why are you...
- You're right.
- so loyal to him?
- We were born slaves.
- He changed his attitude...
just for coins.
- If we put our coins together...
- I'll put a brand on your body.
- It's possible.
- We have enough money.
We need to go...
to the bank to turn in our coins.
We have eight coins. Give me yours.
Who is whispering?
- I'm sorry.
- Stop it.
- Hey.
- Who is still whispering?
I heard Haha saying that we should
collect 15 coins...
and do voting over there.
I didn't say that.
- It's true!
- I didn't say that.
- I'm innocent.
- Take a step forward.
- That's a false accusation.
- Se Chan asked us to vote for him.
- There's no way I said that.
- I'm innocent.
- You know I wouldn't do that.
- Come forward.
- These two planned it.
- I would never do that.
- We would never do that.
- Why don't I break their wrists...
- so they can't cast a vote?
- That's okay.
- Gosh, seriously.
- What's wrong with him?
What's his problem?
- Why is he so loyal to Lord Yu?
- He's Lord Yu's bodyguard.
- It's a false accusation.
- Be careful.
- Yes, my lord.
Quite a lot of penalty sticks
have been added...
- in the servant room.
- Really?
Someone will very likely receive
a penalty.
(The servants gave one another
a penalty stick.)
You don't have to turn in 15 nyang
all at once to drag Lord Yoo down.
You can turn in a little at a time,
and it will be saved.
Like an installment savings plan?
- The coins can be accumulated?
- That's right.
I'll turn in all five coins I have.
The first mission...
requires a good strategy and wit.
- It's Galbijjim of Fear.
- What is it?
- Galbijjim?
It's a different version
of tonkatsu game.
- Oh, I see.
- Oh, tonkatsu game?
Start outside the circle.
Shout "Gal" and step
inside the circle with one foot.
Then shout "Bijjim,"
jump out of the circle,
and land on both feet.
The next players will continue
in the same way.
If you step on the foot
of someone who jumped before you,
you can draw on his or her face.
- I see.
- Got it.
And those who already jumped
can avoid it,
but they can move only one foot.
You have to go back
inside the circle on your turn.
If you fail to do so,
you get eliminated.
Each of the final 5 members
will get 5 nyang.
- Got it.
- Okay.
We can get a lot of coins
in this game.
Can you all step back?
I'll show you how to play the game.
Yes, please demonstrate
for us, my lord.
- Watch me.
- What's wrong with him?
- He drives me crazy.
- What's wrong with you?
I haven't seen anyone
who butters up others like he does.
- What if we change the lord?
- He's determined...
to be Lord Yu's servant.
If you're far away from the circle,
and failed to go back
inside the circle, you're out.
- That's right.
- If you fail to come back.
- You have to consider coming back.
If you fail to come back,
you're out.
- We shouldn't go too far.
- You should jump at once.
- Here are makeup tools.
- Okay.
- Going first is a disadvantage.
- Thank you.
Lord Yu, please decide the order.
- Going first is a disadvantage.
- Okay.
- No.
- Is it a disadvantage?
You should attack and defend.
How about we play
rock-paper-scissors?
I think it will be fair.
Seok Sam goes first.
(Seok Sam has been chosen
to be the 1st to go.)
Okay.
- He goes first.
- We shouldn't jump too far.
- We shouldn't.
- Going first is not good.
- Okay.
- It's not good.
I'm at a disadvantage,
but life is all about
overcoming difficulties.
- I don't think...
- We should overcome it.
- Don't you agree? We can do this!
- Right.
Don't look at me.
Chant "Feeling! Intuition! Cross!"
You just want to chant it.
Don't try too hard...
- to make it look natural.
- Why would we do that again?
- Feel!
- Why would we...
Why should we do that
all of a sudden?
- Feel!
- Intuition!
- Cross!
Suk Jin seems happy.
He's crying. Don't cry, Suk Jin.
Lee Ji Brothers
- Go ahead. Go.
- Let's go.
Here I go. I won't go too far.
Galbijjim.
- You're out if you fall down.
- I won't fall.
We shouted the chant together.
Galbijjim.
- He stepped on Suk Jin's foot.
- Galbijjim.
(He stepped on Suk Jin's foot.)
- He stepped on Suk Jin's foot.
- Draw on his face.
Keep your foot on his foot.
(Servant Ji got stepped on his foot
on his 1st turn.)
(Kwang Soo drew snot on his face.)
(Se Chan is up next.)
Galbijjim.
(He dodged it.)
You dodged it?
Ready, go.
(Haha is up next.)
Galbijjim.
That's a smart move.
He has a different strategy.
Is it my turn?
- Yes.
- Galbijjim.
- She stepped on his foot.
(Kwang Soo got stepped on his foot!)
Ji Hyo, draw something on his face.
(She will draw on his face
as he couldn't dodge it.)
- Close your eyes.
- Rather than...
(Rubbing)
(What's that?)
(He looks as if he got
flour bombed.)
That's good.
- Who's up next?
- Next.
- I'm up next, right?
- Yes.
- I can dodge it, right?
(Here comes Bodyguard Kook.)
It must hurt
if he steps on the foot.
He has the scary look
on his face again.
Jong Kook is about to start.
Take it easy, will you?
Why are you being this loyal to him?
I'll get rid of at least three.
Sounds good. Go ahead.
Don't think about cheating.
Galbijjim.
I don't think Jong Kook
can make it back.
How can we head back?
You won't be able to.
I can make it though.
So Min, you're up next.
All right.
Which way?
Galbijjim.
It's peaceful over there.
This is how it is usually done.
Will Lord Yoo take a gamble?
Go ahead.
Here he comes.
Galbijjim!
(He just jumps to them
without any planning.)
(It hurts...)
How did you see the opening?
How did you manage that?
Did he step on Suk Jin's foot?
That must've really hurt.
Why didn't you move out of the way?
How did he manage
to stomp on Suk Jin's feet?
Why didn't you move out of the way?
You flew like a butterfly just now.
Okay.
Suk Jin must go back now.
- Can we push one another?
- I didn't touch you.
We must stay still.
- I'm standing still.
- This is cruel.
My hands are in one place.
All I have to do
is step inside that circle.
I feel bad for him.
Suk Jin, are you feeling pressured?
- No.
- Can you manage to get back?
- Of course.
- Is there any pressure?
- There's no pressure.
- Show some tears first.
You're cruel, you know that?
What if Suk Jin...
is targeted all day?
Why did I have to go first?
He didn't get to jump
on anyone else.
- Here I go.
- I'm standing still.
- You should stand still.
- Of course.
We won't do anything.
- Don't grab me.
- We won't.
Say "Gal."
- Gal...
- He's out.
bijjim.
(He managed to make it out
despite the pressure.)
Kwang Soo's next.
- It's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo's next.
He won't be able to make it.
There's no chance.
(Jong Kook's legs
make it harder for him.)
Gal...
(Gal...)
You're out.
- You're out.
- Isn't he out?
- Am I out?
- Okay.
- Does that mean I'm out?
- Yes.
- Of course.
- Next!
- Who's next?
- Se Chan.
- Is it Se Chan?
Who should I attack?
Galbijjim! I stepped on your foot.
(He targets So Min.)
All right. Draw on So Min's face.
- Is it me?
- What's going on over there?
We're too close, aren't we?
Sorry about that.
- What on earth?
- I'm sorry.
- What's going on?
- What is this?
- I...
- What's the meaning of this?
- I'm really sorry.
- Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you kidding me?
- I was just playing the game.
- What do you think you're doing?
This with a flower in your hair?
Why are you two enjoying this?
I said I didn't want
to see things like this.
What do you think you're doing?
We're too close, aren't we?
Se Chan...
You two.
- Stop it.
- This is public indecency.
This is your workplace.
No relationships
are allowed at work.
Turn toward me.
Unbelievable.
You two seem close.
Seriously?
Hi, Yondu.
- Keep Yondu locked down.
- Yondu's back.
- Why did it have to be Se Chan?
- I knew it.
Look at you, Yondu.
Did you think
we wouldn't recognize you?
There you go.
Who's next?
- Isn't it me?
- Okay.
(Glancing)
- Look at his gaze.
- I'm putting my trust in you.
What do you think you're doing?
Look at his gaze.
His eyes were sparkling just now.
- Unbelievable.
- He's saying it's his turn.
He swears to give it his all.
He looks like a loyal servant.
Why is he being this loyal?
Gal...
- Jong Kook will crush him down.
- bijjim!
It hurts me to just look at him.
He stepped on Suk Jin's foot.
- Nicely done.
- I stepped on your foot.
His foot will be bruised.
(Seok Sam has sore feet and
a face that's been scribbled on.)
Is So Min next?
- Yes, it's me.
- She can't make it.
That means you're out of the game.
Gal...
She stepped on the line.
- But...
- She's out.
- Out.
- You're out.
Round one will end
if another is eliminated.
- Will it be over then?
- Who's next?
Go ahead.
- It's Lord Yu.
- Jae Suk, you're up.
- Is it my turn?
- It's Lord Yu's turn.
It's too far away.
Let me see.
(Which group will he target?)
- Lord Yu, he won't be able to...
- Gal...
bijjim.
- Lord Yu, he won't be able to...
- Gal...
bijjim.
- He can't move.
- Did you step on his foot?
- No.
- Suk Jin, you're next.
- Me?
- Yes.
His leg...
How can he move
when Jong Kook's foot is on his?
- You can do it.
- I feel bad for him.
- Go ahead.
- Go.
I'll move out of the way.
- He...
- He did it.
You have to free your other foot.
I'll move out of the way.
(One foot made it to the circle!)
You have to free your other foot.
I can't believe he made it.
He has to free his other foot.
You're out if you can't make it.
I'm getting a cramp.
Wait, Bi...
(He struggles to free his foot,)
(but he falls to the side
with a scream.)
How could you press down that hard?
- You all won.
- Nice!
Okay, let's do this.
Five nyang will be given to those...
- who survived the game.
- Nice.
- Really?
- Five nyang?
That's generous of you.
You get five nyang each?
Thank you.
- Let's play just one more round.
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
- The order seems to be important.
- All right. Then...
- He's right.
Let's play a game
to decide the order.
- Sure.
- Sounds good!
Then,
since we're all here,
let's play the Game of Wits.
- 1.
- 2.
- 3.
- Who sat down first?
I did.
You'll be first to jump.
Hold on a second.
- Okay.
- Are you kidding me, Lord Yu?
There's nothing I can do about it.
You said it was the Game of Wits.
Just jump!
- Do as you are told.
- You ungrateful brat.
Seriously?
- Look here, shorty.
- Mind your manners.
- How dare you.
- What did I do?
Are you glaring at your master?
- Just do as you are told.
- Wait...
Jong Kook.
You shouldn't be this way.
You're one of us, aren't you?
- Are you defying him?
- Wait.
Insolent brat.
(After disciplining Haha,
he returns with a smile.)
Here you go.
Did you give him money?
Let's not be this way.
- Seriously?
- Are you kidding me?
I like your constantly
positive attitude.
- Learn from him.
- Exactly.
Having a positive attitude...
- I'll go first then.
- No, I will.
Se Chan will go first.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
- We should spread out.
- Right.
What's the best move?
- Should we go further out?
- Coming back should be the goal.
Galbijjim.
- Just don't be stepped on.
- Galbijjim.
- That's it.
- Go further out.
Galbijjim.
- Good.
- Things have taken a fun turn.
Good job, guys.
This is how it's done.
(Jong Kook's next.)
How about you go that way?
- From here to there?
- Yes.
The one up next
gets the first choice then.
(Jong Kook could
split them into four groups.)
Galbijjim.
(He ambushes Kwang Soo.)
He made his choice.
(It hurts!)
(His heavy weight
lands on Kwang Soo's foot.)
It serves you right for spacing out.
He said he was going that way!
- You should've been focused.
- Okay.
You already have a beard anyway.
(He gets a mustache
on top of white eye-shadow.)
Ji Hyo.
- Galbijjim!
- She stepped on his foot.
(Is she hugging him from behind?)
- What on earth?
- What is this?
Why are you hugging him from behind?
- I...
- Hold on a second.
Ji Hyo, why did you
hug him from behind?
You didn't step on my feet.
Jae Suk, I'm just playing a game.
- Did you step on his foot?
- I did.
- On his heel.
- She did.
- Did she?
- Wait.
Then...
(She draws on Jong Kook's face.)
Now I'm scared. It's Rambo.
It's Rambo!
- It's Rambo!
- What is this?
Rambo!
Must it be this random?
Hey there, Rambo.
You could've drawn it
across my cheeks.
It's Rambo.
When did Rambo get here?
I'm a huge fan.
All he needs
is for the bandana to be red.
They're all going that way now.
They will easily make it back.
The first one to play
gets to come back first.
Gal...
bijjim!
Okay, good.
Is Haha aiming for this opening?
- Get over here.
- Galbijjim.
- Okay.
- I have no choice, Lord Yu.
I can't believe
you stepped on Lord Yu's foot.
- What on earth is that?
- He looks cool though.
- You look great.
- Rambo!
It's Rambo.
He truly looks like Rambo.
He looks determined.
The first master and special agent.
(The first master and special agent)
Call me Lord Rambo.
- Lord Rambo.
- I'm Lord Rambo.
- Who's next?
- It's me.
- There's no chance he can make it.
- No way.
- Go ahead.
- He'll never make it.
- Go on.
- He can't move.
(He tries to cheat his way out.)
Are you out of your mind?
You must jump from your spot,
and you can't hold onto anyone.
(He must get past 7 people.)
Gal...
- You're out.
- He's out.
Is it me?
Oh, it's Jong Kook.
All right.
- Where is it?
- Right here.
He won't be able to make it.
Can you?
- He can't make it.
- How...
Gal...
(Gal...)
- What?
- Bijjim.
He actually made it.
He made it through!
- What was that?
- Are you kidding me?
Can you push past people like that?
Is this a joke?
- That's your move?
- What's wrong?
- Okay, fine.
- All right!
- Nicely done.
- Gal...
I like your gung-ho attitude.
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm next.
- Ji Hyo will be out.
- Go ahead.
Gal...
Out! You stepped on the line.
That's too bad.
Suk Jin will make it back.
(It doesn't seem easy
with Haha blocking his way.)
Gal...
(Take that.)
Suk Jin got poked in the butt.
That should be a world record.
Getting poked in the butt...
The oldest person
to get poked in the butt.
The pants are too thin, so...
(Humiliated)
It's been about 45 years
since I was goosed.
It's a world record!
(It's his turn to attack.)
Bijjim!
(Just the one foot?)
What on earth was that?
You're out.
(Suk Jin's out.)
- You're out.
- Both feet should've made it out.
- Both feet.
- Of course.
- We've played many times already.
- They did go out later.
- Stop it.
- My gosh.
I was so upset
when he poked my butt.
I was so upset.
- I won this round.
- Me too.
- This guy is...
- Thank you.
Okay.
I collected a few already.
(They were able to collect
lots of coins through this mission.)
- I'm going to get the sticks.
- Me too.
I'm going to kick Lord Yoo out.
(The tall servant puts his thoughts
into action first.)
(He arrived at the servant room.)
I'm going to use
all the coins I have.
(He uses 6 nyang
to kick Lord Yoo out.)
Let's go to the servant room.
I think we should.
Let's go to the servant room
and change our lord.
So this is it.
I've never been to this place.
I'm going to kick Lord Yoo out.
Hello.
(To dethrone Lord Yu,
Se Chan uses all his coins too.)
Two more penalty sticks
of Lord Yoo have been added.
It's done, right?
- You can change the lord.
- Really?
I used all of my coins.
- Well done.
- And read this out loud for him.
Well done.
How did it go?
- We can change the lord.
- I used all of my coins.
(The servants succeed
in their uprising...)
(behind Lord Yu's back.)
- We can change the lord.
- How do we do it?
- Gosh, he startled me.
- What are you guys up to?
- Nothing.
- It's nothing, Lord Yu.
What are you guys up to?
Let's walk faster now.
Hurry up!
(Come quickly, Lord Yu.)
(Those arrogant servants...)
I have a big announcement to make!
What is it?
I received a note.
- Read it out loud.
- This doesn't suit you.
"Hear this, Lord Yu."
"The servants succeeded
in their uprising."
"You are no longer a lord.
You have been degraded..."
- "to a servant."
- Hey!
(He falls in status.)
(Getting back at him)
Kneel before us!
Kneel!
- Stay still!
- How dare you!
- "How dare you?"
- How is this happening?
- You.
(The former lord keeps treating
the servants rudely.)
- Stop right there.
- Already?
- Of course.
- Shall we torture him?
"You will now pick a new lord..."
"among the servants who contributed
to the uprising."
Let's go over there.
(The miserable end of Lord Yu
who made people suffer)
The two servants who contributed
to kicking Lord Yoo out...
are Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
Their names are written here.
We'll pick one name randomly,
and the winner will be the new lord.
Please pick one.
All right. Pick a name.
- Hey, you. Keep quiet.
- Watch your tone.
(Watch what you say.)
- Keep quiet.
- You...
- Look at him.
- Don't say anything.
- Hey, you.
- You should get changed now!
- Get changed!
- You changed your stance so fast.
- My goodness.
- I'm dumbfounded.
- My gosh, look at his face.
- I'm really dumbfounded.
- You should go ahead!
- My gosh.
How about letting Lord Yoo pick it?
- Lord Yu?
- Who is Lord Yu?
- I mean Servant Yu.
- It's Servant Yu.
Take off your robe.
Why are you still wearing it?
Although I am descending...
- Shut it.
- Be quiet.
(Hitting his mouth)
- Who are you to say that?
(As soon as he steps down,
he's getting hit by everyone.)
This is so upsetting.
- Whose name are you picking?
- It's over already.
I pick this.
(Who will become the new lord?)
- It's Kwang Soo.
- Yes!
(Kwang Soo got picked.)
- It's Kwang Soo.
- Yes!
(We have a new lord, Lord Lee.)
- Lord Lee! Let me carry you!
- Yes!
Enjoy it.
Lord Yu, you'll give all your money
to Lord Lee.
- I'm getting the money too?
- He's getting the money too?
You can give out coins using those.
We're in big trouble.
He's worse than Jae Suk.
- We're in trouble. It'll be harder.
- I'm worried already.
Hurry up. 10, 9, 8, 7...
- Take off your robe.
- Hey.
(Lord Yoo is stripped of his power,
wealth, and silk clothes.)
Gosh, this is infuriating.
Get changed now.
He's like a faithful dog.
How dare you talk casually
to Lord Lee?
Don't talk about the past!
- Give me some.
- What?
Don't talk about the past!
(Approaching Kwang Soo)
- Give me some.
- What?
Move!
What do you think you are doing?
(Satisfied)
- This is why I like you.
- How dare you?
(This bodyguard is only kind
to the man with power.)
- You're a faithful dog indeed.
- Okay!
While Lord Lee gets changed,
you need to send someone out
to get ingredients for hotteok.
The second dish is hotteok.
The ingredients for hotteok.
- Ingredients?
- The second dish is hotteok.
Gosh, there's no one to send out.
Lord Lee, please trust me.
- Lord Lee.
- Then I'll pick the man I trust,
- Jong Kook.
- Me?
All right. I'll go with him.
No, I will go.
You should get ready
to lift the palanquin.
(Lord Lee pays back
for how he was treated.)
- This is so upsetting.
- Jong Kook...
- and Suk Jin should go.
- Okay!
I like Suk Jin.
- This is great.
- This is so upsetting.
Let's go find out the prices.
(The two servants set out
to get the ingredients.)
Gosh, this man...
You brat! Sweep the garden!
I can't stand the sight of you.
That punk. I knew this would happen.
(The former lord
is treated with contempt.)
I'm a man of low status.
From now, I am...
I'm the first special agent
among servants.
- So you should...
- Don't be ridiculous.
I'm the first special agent
among servants.
(In your dreams!)
(Servant Yoo still can't get over
his role-playing.)
- He's being ridiculous.
- This is so upsetting.
- Lord Lee.
- Lord Lee, I'll perform for you.
- That's...
- what Servant Ji likes!
- So give me some money.
Give me some money.
Things are so expensive these days.
- We're not even kidding.
- Really?
How much do they cost?
- They're so expensive.
- Hotteok is...
The flour is 20 nyang.
And the sugar you put inside...
- is 10 nyang.
- So a total of 30 nyang.
He became a pushover now.
Lord Lee became a pushover.
Then should I trust them
and give them the money?
- We're serious.
- We're serious. We're not kidding.
- Do you want to see for yourself?
- If you give me the money,
I'll be sure to buy them
at the right price.
- Lord Lee, don't you trust us?
- I'm serious.
- I'll do it.
- Please let me go.
- Give me 15 nyang.
- 10...
- I'll go get them at 15 nyang.
- 15 nyang?
- Yes.
- I'll use mine if it's not enough.
- They said they'll take 15 only.
- I'll use my own money too.
- No one's going lower than that?
- Yes, 15 nyang.
If you fail,
I'll take all your money.
- Okay.
- Okay, got it.
Make sure to get all the ingredients
with 15 nyang.
Okay, okay.
- Let's follow them.
- Let's do that.
(Haha and Suk Jin also set off.)
- Sweep the garden!
- Hey, make a fire.
- Hey.
- Make a fire.
Come here. Get down.
(While Lord Lee becomes
more ruthless...)
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
(Somebody moans in pain.)
- Lord Lee!
- Something bad happened!
- What is it? What happened?
- We met...
- We met bandits on our way!
(Bandits in the middle of a city?)
- We lost all of our money!
- Lord Lee!
- We barely...
- My goodness.
- We barely made it out alive.
- We almost died!
- Please forgive us!
We almost died!
- We're serious!
- They hit us and threatened us!
- I'm so sorry!
- It's all my fault!
I was so scared!
They threatened us with a knife!
We almost died!
- What happened?
- I barely saved them!
- Lord Lee.
- If you give us 15 nyang,
- we'll get the ingredients.
- Seriously. Lord Lee!
- You should punish them.
- Can I check your bag?
No, you can't!
- I really don't have it.
- No need to go through their bags.
- I think they hid it somewhere.
What's that?
"Hear this, offender Lord Lee."
"The servants succeeded
in their uprising."
"You are no longer a lord."
"You have been degraded
to a servant."
You punk!
- They used that money.
- "You will now pick a new lord..."
"among the servants who contributed
to the uprising."
- Hey, hey. Move!
- We have a new lord!
Let's go right now.
We can change the lord right away.
We can change the lord right now.
Let's change the lord right away.
(They headed straight
to the servant room instead.)
- That brat...
- That rude brat!
- That rude brat.
- I got 15 nyang.
- 15 nyang?
- I got 15 too. Put them together.
(They used the money from Lord Lee
to bring him down.)
- They used that money?
- Did they really?
- You thoughtless brat!
- How dare you!
- Take off your robe.
- Take off your robe now!
- Put the palanquin away.
There are
Jae Suk, Haha, and So Min.
You should pick one.
Pick one.
- Pick one.
- So Min would be funny.
- I want to try it too.
- I want So Min to become one.
You want to do it, right?
- All right.
- I picked it.
Help So Min become one.
But I think
she'd be really annoying.
It'd be best
if I become the lord again.
If Jae Suk
becomes the lord again...
- Let us see.
- It's Jae Suk.
Give that to me!
(The 3 servants rose up in revolt
and brought down Lord Lee.)
(Who will become the new lord
among them?)
- It's Jae Suk.
- Give that to me!
Is it really Jae Suk?
"Yoo Jae Suk."
(Jae Suk has become
the lord again!)
(Lord Rambo is back.)
I knew it.
Take it off right now.
Lord Yu!
(He was degraded to a servant
and had miserable days.)
- Shut it.
- Be quiet.
(He was slapped and humiliated.)
(They made fun of him
playing Lord Rambo.)
(A glorious return of Lord Yu)
- Look at Jong Kook.
- I knew it.
Jong Kook is at it again.
I knew it.
I knew it!
- Take it off right now.
- I knew it.
He'll get up there again.
We used the money you gave us
in the servant room.
That darn boy.
We were short of exactly 15 nyang.
- Thank you for that.
- We used your money.
(Donation angel)
What did he do as a lord?
I just had the robe on briefly.
It's like a fashion show.
- I knew it!
- Take it off right now!
Jae Suk needs to be the lord.
- Is he getting it again?
- Lord Yu.
(Singing celebratory song)
(A parade to celebrate
the return of Lord Yu)
(Lord Rambo leads the parade.)
(And the servants
follow behind him.)
(Even the dancer
from the cultural center joins in.)
(The celebration
reaches its climax.)
(Gosh, I don't want to do it.)
(Servant Lee,
who used to be a clown,)
(twirls a baton to celebrate.)
(The parade ends.)
- Well, Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- Start the count off.
- Okay, My Lord.
- There he goes again.
- He's at it again.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I'm so sick of it.
- Please.
- Come on.
- We're doing it again?
- Count off!
- Do it properly!
- This is driving me crazy.
Let's start with Kwang Soo. Start!
- 1.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
Seven. End of count.
- I'm going to the village,
- This is exhausting.
- so bring the palanquin.
- Palanquin!
- Palanquin...
- Who is carrying it?
- Tell us.
- Carry it!
- Carry it.
- You...
- You should carry it too.
- and you.
Lord Yu, when will we get
the ingredients for hotteok?
- What?
- Lord Yu, while traveling,
pick the servant you want,
and you can relax
in a luxurious SUV.
I wanted to ride it.
Then can't I join in
on the product placement?
- Okay, now...
- Pick me.
You all saw how it was
when Lord Lee was in charge.
- Right.
- Now.
- I will...
- I'm finally in the right place.
Be quiet. Be quiet!
(Be quiet!)
How dare you open your mouth?
- He's having so much fun.
- Who said you could talk?
Who said you could talk?
Earlier, he said...
- Did I?
- No, My Lord.
He called himself
a special agent earlier.
Se Chan, you should come with me.
- Him?
- Thank you.
- I'll take him.
- Because he's comfortable.
I think
he's going to scheme against me.
- Oh, right.
- Come here.
- You should go.
- Sure.
I'll go and take a break.
Lord Yu, you made the right choice.
Right you are.
(Lord Yoo and Servant Yang arrive
at a place where they get to rest.)
- Please get in.
- Shall I?
(Let me...)
Only Lord Yoo can get in the car.
Darn it! This is...
Then what am I supposed to do?
You can wait outside
and open the door for him.
- Hey, hey.
- What is this?
Then where can I stay?
Just stand right there.
You want me to just wait here?
The inside is really spacious.
Gosh, this is nice.
(The VJ goes inside
to shoot Lord Yu.)
He can get in but I can't?
Director, I'll shoot him myself.
Actually,
you don't need me here.
You're only shooting the inside.
Was this one of their conditions?
One of us standing outside?
(Even the product placement
discriminates based on his status.)
How many coins do you have?
- Gosh, he's so annoying today.
- I should choose him this time.
- He's just...
- He crossed the line.
- He's so annoying.
- I know. It's killing me.
- I used all of my coins already.
- Me too.
Let's choose Jong Kook then.
- Gosh, he's so annoying today.
- I should choose him this time.
- He's just...
- He crossed the line.
- He's so annoying.
- I know. It's killing me.
Welcome.
How much are the ingredients
of hotteok?
Flour costs 12 nyang,
and sugar costs 8 nyang.
Then just give us the flour.
(Then just give us the flour.)
- You only need this?
- Yes.
(What about sugar?)
- You're not adding sugar?
- It's okay.
We're only going to make it
with flour.
- Here you go.
- Okay, then...
(They used 12 nyang
to get flour only.)
I got 12 nyang.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- I'm putting in 5 nyang.
- Who will you pick?
- No, I'm paying to change the lord.
- Lord Yu?
How come you took Se Chan?
Haha and I...
bought the sticks to make you
the new lord.
Keep quiet and bring yakgwa.
You're upsetting me.
(Lord Yu
has anger management issues.)
We won't be able to
see them together anymore.
- Is he being hysterical or what?
- My gosh.
All the lords are sensitive.
I preferred having Lord Lee...
because he gave us more money.
Don't you think?
It was way better
when we had Lord Lee.
- Right. He even paid us more.
- I'm so angry.
Hurry up and make hotteok. Hey!
You. Come here.
"You. Come here?"
- Come here.
- Why?
Come here.
(Look at his face.)
Look at his makeup.
You know you have snot
on your face, right?
(He looks even more pitiful
with the snot makeup.)
Hey, only these guys are working.
- Why aren't you working?
- I'm hungry.
Who cares if you're hungry?
Everyone here is hungry.
Where did you hit?
I heard a loud snap.
I mean,
he's slacking off for so long.
Why aren't you working?
- I mean...
- Tell me.
I had to go to the store
so I couldn't eat.
My goodness.
(Lord Yoo can't stand his servants
being idle.)
I got so upset earlier.
I think it's a good idea
to press with this.
- I think it'll be really spicy.
- Who adds chilis in hotteok?
It's a fusion dish.
Who adds chilis in hotteok?
Just let her be.
- Wait and see.
- You're complaining...
when you're not even helping her.
Gosh, seriously.
Hold on.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes, My Lord!
- Leave Ji Hyo, Se Chan,
- Okay.
- and So Min here,
and let the rest
run laps around here.
You should take them and...
- What are you talking about?
- It's not like we're dogs!
- Until where?
- To the stairs, and come back.
- Why would we run?
- Okay.
Why would he let us run...
- out of nowhere?
- Line up!
- Line up now!
- Haha, you can stay.
Just us two?
Line up and start the count off.
- 1.
- 2.
- Three. End of count.
- All right. Good.
I'll be behind you.
We're taking a big lap around here.
- Ready. Start with your left foot.
- What is this?
Left, left, left.
Why are we doing this?
- What is this?
- Start counting!
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 1, 2, 3...
- 1, 2, 3.
- They're back.
- 1, 2,
- 3, 4.
- This is nice.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- That's good.
- This is nice.
- They all look so tired.
- 3, 4.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Halt.
- 1, 2.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes, My Lord.
- Did they run well?
- They really worked out.
- Yes, they listened to me well.
- Look at them sweating.
You should report to me now.
- We had no renegades.
- That's good. Well done.
- Mr. Kim, you're so...
- He's all smiles.
- You're really good with this.
- Jong Kook is all smiles.
- Here. Good work.
- Thank you, My Lord.
I don't want to live like him.
At ease. You're dismissed.
You're dismissed!
- You're dismissed.
- What is this?
He made you run.
- We're not getting any?
- You're not giving us any?
He made you run so that
you don't scheme against him.
If they stay together,
they keep plotting things.
Lord Yu, please sit down.
My, look at this.
This looks amazing.
(He greedily eats it alone.)
(I hope it's to his liking.)
Oh, really?
Spicy, salty,
and sweet ingredients go well.
- Right. It's sweet and salty.
- Also,
because of Cheongyang chili,
- it's not greasy.
- You see?
You see? I told you we should add
Cheongyang chili.
My gosh, it's so good.
He really finished the whole thing.
Lord Yoo finished it.
- I'm happy that he finished it.
- I'm happy too.
All right, everyone!
Put your arms around each other.
Come! Put your arms
around each other.
- Come.
- My gosh.
- Why...
- Why are we doing this?
Why does he make us do
so many things?
- What are we doing next?
- Let's...
thank each other for making
the delicious hotteok...
that we all enjoyed.
(The cheering
that only Jae Suk wants)
(I really don't want to do this.)
(Lord Yoo loves having
a family-like relationship...)
(with his servants.)
- To the front.
- Let's go.
- Put your hands together.
- Put them together!
All right now.
- Let's...
- Yes!
wish everyone good health.
- Doesn't this house...
- Let's cheer for each other.
- let the servants take a break?
- No.
Why is he so full of energy all day?
Say "let's go"
on the count of 3. 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go!
That was nice! Let's go!
I can't even go against him
because I have no money.
- This is driving me crazy.
- You're all dismissed!
- Dismissed!
- Let's take a break.
- You're all dismissed!
- You can take a break.
- Come to the servant room.
Come to the servant room.
- Is there something?
- There are two.
- Let's gather all our coins.
- Okay.
(They take a short break
after working hard.)
I should lie down.
I'm so tired.
(Seok Sam found the perfect spot
to rest while the staff have lunch.)
This is nice.
(He lies down as he groans.)
It's so nice to lie down.
(Servant Ji uses a book
as his pillow and lies down.)
(He then fell asleep
in the same position.)
(Right then, the staff spotted
Servant Ji who's deeply asleep.)
(He's deep in sleep
without knowing what's going on.)
- He's sleeping.
- Quiet.
- He's really sleeping.
- Let's begin.
Suk Jin is sleeping.
(Let's begin. Suk Jin is sleeping.)
(Even the staff get ready to shoot
to play a joke on Seok Sam.)
- Did you all sleep well?
- Yes, My Lord.
- Did you have a good rest?
What do you want us to do now?
- We'll do anything for you.
- Now...
- Hold on. Jong Kook.
- Yes, My Lord.
Shall we start the count off?
- Let's begin with you.
- One.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
Six. End of count.
- What?
- There's only six of us?
- This is...
- There's only six of you?
Where did the other one go?
- I'll get ready to chase him down!
- Where did he go?
- I'll chase him down!
Where did one go?
- Where did one go?
- The slave hunter will find him.
The slave hunter will find him.
For goodness' sake.
(Seok Sam is startled awake
upon the news of slave hunters.)
For goodness' sake.
(Peeking)
- Look at his face.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- What is up with his face?
- For a second...
- You punk.
I was told I could rest
while the staff members were eating.
Come back to your senses.
- Why are you staggering?
- Hey.
- Suddenly...
- For goodness' sake.
How did his face become so puffy
in such a short amount of time?
You punk.
- Why didn't you wake me up?
- Hey.
How could you use books as a pillow?
(How could you use books
as a pillow?)
Hey.
- I mean...
- How could you do that?
I guess he was cold.
- He must feel chilly.
- It's cold.
- I had a good nap.
Gosh, it's very refreshing.
Are you healthy?
I am healthy.
Are you okay?
- I am healthy.
- He is healthy!
- I am jealous of Suk Jin.
- He came alive.
(Cold water helped Seok Sam
find his vigor.)
- I am healthy.
- He is healthy.
Suk Jin is back.
I am healthy.
- I am healthy.
- Seok Sam, are you okay?
- I am okay.
- Did you recover?
- It's time for a meal.
- We need to eat.
- Let's prepare the third meal.
- "We need to eat."
- Seok Sam, go.
- You are the healthy one.
See how much the ingredients are.
For goodness' sake.
Why are they making me work so much?
Patbingsu.
I am here
for the patbingsu ingredients.
They are here.
- Do we need to crush the ice?
- Yes.
All the ingredients cost two nyang.
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7.
14 nyang.
(Buying all the ingredients
would cost 14 nyang.)
All right.
Shall I go for a walk?
Are you going for a walk?
Lord Yu...
is going for a walk.
All right.
Shall I go for a walk?
(Lord Yoo goes on a short walk
by himself.)
Lord Yu...
is going for a walk.
How many coins do you have?
- How many...
- We should go...
- and get the number.
- Does anyone have three?
We need to get the number.
- I have many coins.
- I will use mine then.
- I have two coins.
- I have some coins too.
- Don't buy a penalty stick for me.
- Okay.
(They leave as they check
the number of their coins.)
It's over there.
(Jong Kook calls the servants
to the servant room.)
Let's go inside.
Where did you guys go?
Hey.
Everyone is here.
(Everyone gathers around.)
We have enough!
Let's change the lord!
(Let's change the lord!)
(The servants
want to change the lord again.)
- I will chip in one coin.
- Shall I do that?
- Three coins.
- Let's gather them around.
All right.
- Let's go.
Please take the scroll and read it.
Everyone chipped in
except for Jae Suk.
The new lord will be decided
by drawing lots.
Let's go for the prize.
(Every servant worked
to change the lord.)
All right.
All right!
I will make another announcement.
(All right!
I will make another announcement.)
(Again?)
"Hear this, Lord Yu."
"The servants succeeded
in their uprising."
"You are no longer a lord.
You have been degraded..."
"to a servant."
- Take it off.
- "You will now pick a new lord..."
"among the servants..."
- "who contributed to the uprising."
- For goodness' sake.
Good work, everyone.
- All right.
- I don't care who becomes the lord.
For goodness' sake.
- This is too much.
- Pick the new lord.
We all have equal chances.
- Let me be the new lord.
- Seriously.
- Let it be me just once.
- Let me be the new lord...
- just once.
- Will it be the last change?
We don't have the money...
- to change the lord again.
- Jae Suk.
- It will be the last change.
- That's right.
There are a lot of coins inside.
Let's help each other.
- He picked one.
He picked one.
If the new lord
doesn't get changed again,
he or she will receive a prize
and pick another member.
(The last lord will receive a prize
and pick another member.)
- He picked one.
- Who will it be?
(Who will be the lucky 4th lord?)
Me.
It's me, you punks!
(Haha.)
(The new lord is Haha.)
For goodness' sake.
I have no luck whatsoever.
Why can't I become the lord
just once?
- Seriously.
- I turned in so many coins.
For goodness' sake.
I have no luck whatsoever.
- I knew you had the lord's voice.
- Lord Ha.
Lord Ha,
you know how things work, right?
You should help a fellow servant.
(Lord Ha!)
Who is this?
Judging by the thickness...
- Haha got picked.
- I got the position.
I got the position.
- He will win the prize.
- I got it.
He will win the prize
no matter what.
I said repeatedly
that he has a lord's voice.
Help him get dressed, you punk.
- Servant Yu.
- Help him get dressed.
- Hey.
- Why are you... You, you!
Why are you so insolent?
Why is he so insolent?
He glared at me earlier.
The outfit suits him perfectly.
He finally found the outfit
that suits him perfectly.
- He looks so cute.
- "He looks so cute."
- You look so cute.
- All right.
- We will eat patbingsu now.
- Okay.
I am getting a prize.
You are right.
And one of you will win the prize
with me.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Raise your hand
if you have beef with it.
- We don't.
- "Have beef?"
It looks like you have beef.
No, Lord Ha.
I love your choice of words.
- I love your raw choice of words.
- Lord Ha,
I guess you didn't read many books.
Lord Ha!
I can bring back the ingredients
if you give me ten coins.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I am sure.
I will go.
I can bring back the ingredients
if you give me ten coins.
(He doesn't stop chattering.)
Don't do that.
He will run into a bandit.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Make him run a lap.
- Okay.
Come here.
You don't need to go.
- Get ready.
- Let's hear it.
- Okay!
In place, double time.
Left, left,
- left... Left!
- He is bad at it.
- Again.
- Set, go.
- He is nervous.
- Left, left.
- Come on.
March as you say the number.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Make sure we hear it.
We can't hear you!
Say it loud again.
- March as you say the number.
- 1, 2,
3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 4.
For goodness' sake.
(He stops
as soon as he is out of sight.)
I need to find some money.
(I need to find some money.)
(How many coins does he have?)
Six coins.
I can't hear you!
Shall I go and get him?
Someone will need to go and get him.
All right.
- Jong Kook, go and get him.
- Okay.
I will go.
- I can go.
- Please let me do it.
- Lee Ji Brothers will go.
- Don't cry.
(He suddenly makes an offer.)
- Feeling and Intuition should go.
- Yes.
(Feeling and Intuition should go.)
- Come on.
- Don't make it emotional.
Don't send me away like that.
Feeling!
- Intuition! Cross!
- Cross!
- Let's go.
- Why...
The rest of you should clean up.
Okay.
Clean up the place.
We finished cleaning up.
- The three of you, follow me.
- Why?
What is going on?
Lord Ha, it's an emergency.
My goodness.
- Doctor!
- My goodness.
- Lord Ha!
- Suk Jin, please.
Seok Sam, please wake up.
Lord Ha, it's an emergency.
- My goodness.
- Doctor!
- I knew it.
- Suk Jin, please.
Seok Sam, please wake up.
What happened?
- Lord Ha!
- Suk Jin, please.
Seok Sam, please wake up.
He was on his way
to buy the ingredients.
- Please wake up.
- Listen.
- I mean...
- Those jerks.
It happened when I was looking away
for a second.
I am so upset.
- He got robbed.
- When I was looking away,
- he got robbed.
- It was a pickpocket.
Seriously.
You know,
- I was too focused on the road.
- We even met a tiger.
A tiger!
What happened?
- You jerk.
- I was too focused on the road.
"Hear this, insolent Lord Ha."
You punk!
"The servants succeeded
in their uprising."
"You are no longer a lord."
"You have been degraded
to a servant."
- Isn't this too much?
- "You will now pick a new lord..."
"among the servants who contributed
to the uprising."
You know, I have been a lord...
for less than five minutes.
This is too much.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
He was a lord for five minutes.
In the neighborhood,
- there are so many bandits.
- Seriously.
- We really ran out of money.
- We ran out of money.
The next lord will be the last one.
- My goodness.
- The next lord will win.
- Seriously.
- Please let it be me.
Please.
- Pick one without looking.
- No matter who becomes a lord...
- Go ahead.
It will be incredible
if I become a lord this time.
Pick one.
Please, please.
Let me be a lord this once.
This is the last chance.
Please, please.
I will make a peaceful village.
I just hope it isn't him.
- I won't say anything.
- I just hope it isn't him.
Who is it? Jong Kook?
- It has to be me.
- You never know.
(Who is it among Jae Suk,
Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo?)
- Can I pick again?
- Why?
- Is it Jae Suk again?
- Is it Jae Suk?
- No way.
- Can I pick again?
- Come on.
Who is it?
Is it Jong Kook?
Gosh!
It's Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook becomes a lord.)
Kim Jong Kook!
For goodness' sake.
I can't believe it. Okay.
(Here is the thing
about Servant Kim.)
(The endless roll calls
didn't tire him out.)
(He was a faithful dog
who collected coins diligently.)
(He relieved his work stress
by splitting firewood.)
Let go of me. Just let go of me.
- All right. Let go of me.
- I support you.
- Lord Kim.
- Give me the hat.
- Give him the outfit.
- Lord Kim.
He said he wants to pick again.
- Who?
- He did.
- Do you want to pick again?
- No, no.
Shall I take this off?
Lord Kim.
Please send us home.
- All right.
- Can we go home soon?
- For goodness' sake.
- Forget it.
We are getting so many patients.
Who is tired?
We would have gone home
had we just eaten patbingsu.
We are getting so many patients.
We would have been done
had we just eaten patbingsu.
- Patbingsu.
- It's another patient.
- Hey, hey.
- Patbingsu.
- Hey.
- What is up with him?
- Stand in a double file.
Who do you think you are?
- What is up with her?
- Who do you think you are?
What is up with her?
- Don't bother with her.
- Who do you think you are?
Lord Kim gave me instructions.
- You were in the special forces.
- Yes, sir.
You were in the special forces.
- Line them up.
- That's ridiculous.
- Stand in a double file.
Stand in a double file.
- Fall into two lines.
- I can't help...
- but follow the orders.
- Fall into two lines.
Count off.
- 1.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
Say, "End of count."
- You are seven.
- Say your number.
Who do you think you are?
Does he think
he is in a position of power?
He should be tortured.
- I mean...
- Say your number.
- Yes, sir! Yes, sir! Okay, sir!
- Got it?
- Again.
Without saying his number, he went,
"Why are there six servants?"
All right.
Who will go and buy
the ingredients for patbingsu?
I will do it.
- Do you have money?
- No.
Steal the ingredients.
- What?
- What kind of lord...
- makes his servants steal?
- Steal?
Yes.
There is a lot of money
in the servant room.
- Is that so?
- Shall we go over there?
Shall we go over there
and steal money?
I should receive money
since I became a lord, right?
I will give you six nyang.
- All right.
- Red bean paste and ice?
Red bean paste, ice, and rice cake.
He is good at running errands.
It's like a regular errand.
Ice, red bean paste, rice cake.
What? What?
It's the end.
Let's eat it quickly
and get the shoot over with.
Can we change the lord?
No. We don't have enough coins.
- We don't have the money.
- Seriously.
- All right.
- Where did Jae Suk go?
- What?
- Where did he go?
(Lord Kim finds out
that Servant Yoo is missing.)
He is scheming something.
Shall we go after him?
Where did Jae Suk go?
(Lord Kim will surely ask
where he has been.)
(Servant suddenly puts
an A-frame on his back.)
- He is back.
- What?
(Why is he carrying an A-frame?)
- An A-frame?
- What kind of setup is this?
Let's hear it.
- Let's hear what he has to say.
- What happened?
Let's hear it.
Let's hear what he has to say.
What happened?
Will he be able
to convince Lord Kim?
Lord Kim,
I buried Seok Sam
in a nice plot of land.
(Lord Kim, I buried Seok Sam
in a nice plot of land.)
(I buried Seok Sam
No!
- Seok Sam!
- No!
Seok Sam!
- Overcome it!
- My goodness.
You promised to be healthy!
He couldn't even eat patbingsu.
Seok Sam.
We were almost done.
He became the crows' meal.
It's good
that there's one less mouth to feed.
It's better to have
fewer mouths to feed.
- It's for the best.
- Yes, it's better this way.
That's right. Good job.
For goodness' sake.
He and I shouted,
"Feeling! Intuition! Cross!"
- He left before you.
He left before you.
Okay. All right.
- Can we sit down?
- What?
- Sit in a single row.
Let's sit in a single row.
(They overcome their sadness
and return to their daily lives.)
- Is it mine?
- Yes.
- Seok Sam.
- Okay. Good job.
Servant Song, go and balance...
- the penalty sticks.
- Okay.
Sit down.
- Hey.
- What do you have?
Seok Sam. It's Seok Sam.
- Seok Sam came back.
- Seok Sam.
- Seok Sam came back to life.
- What? It's a ghost!
- Seok Sam.
- You aren't Seok Sam, are you?
- It's a ghost!
- What? It's a ghost!
- Seok Sam.
(How did Seok Sam come back
to life?)
- What?
- Seok Sam is dead!
- Seok Sam.
- What is going on?
- I died?
- My goodness.
- I can't touch him.
- Seok Sam.
- Why did I... Why?
- What's going on with the story?
- Please move on to the afterlife!
Seok Sam.
(Please move on to the afterlife!)
We will resolve your resentment.
Please go.
What's going on with the story?
(The story changed a lot
while he was on an errand.)
(Move on?)
- Seok Sam, you are dead.
- Dead?
- What's going on with the story?
- Stop it.
Stop it.
Seok Sam, where is the rice cake?
- What?
- Rice cake.
- It's here.
- Lord Kim.
- Is it underneath?
- It's too little.
How did you get rice cake?
Of course I got rice cake.
Here is the machine.
Bring it here.
- Spin it.
- Watch your hands.
The ice is getting crushed.
- It's working.
- You are doing well.
- Add the red bean paste.
- Add it.
Okay. Put it here.
(They put the patbingsu
in front of Lord Kim.)
- My goodness.
- I went and got the ingredients.
(The last meal of the day
is patbingsu.)
- It looks delicious.
- Seriously.
I really want to eat it.
- The texture must be different.
- I am thirsty.
- Is it tasty?
- The texture must be different.
He used the old-fashioned machine.
Are you okay?
- I know that feeling.
- He has brain-freeze.
He has brain-freeze.
Is it tasty?
(Lord Kim's review)
I see that condensed milk is a must.
(They finished serving
the last meal.)
It's a must.
You finished all three meals.
The lord changed four times
in total.
(More people will receive
the penalty.)
Thus, five penalty sticks
will be picked.
- 5?
Practically everyone will receive
the penalty.
Why don't I give the prize first?
Lord Kim.
The prize is Korean beef.
It looks delicious.
Pick a servant who will receive
the same prize.
(Lord Kim and the servant he picks
will receive the Korean beef.)
Look at the color.
(Who will Lord Kim choose?)
(Handing it over)
Why would you give it to me?
Don't pretend to cry.
- Hey.
- Don't give it to me.
Take it, you punk.
- Take it.
- Why would you give it to me?
Take it. You will be gone soon.
It doesn't mean
you should give it to me.
- Good job.
- Why would you give it to me?
- It doesn't suit you.
- Don't pretend to cry.
(Whispering)
- What?
- Sell it to me for a cheap price.
Sell it to you for a cheap price?
(A dealer tries to take the prize.)
Now, I will reveal the penalty.
The penalty for the lord
and the servants' will be...
doing the dirty dishes.
- That's such a hassle.
The batter has hardened.
I don't like doing dishes.
It will take 15 minutes
just to soak the dishes.
That's such a hassle.
You also need to carry the dishes
to a different location.
Do we need to carry them?
It's a big hassle.
- It's the worst penalty.
- This is driving me crazy.
I will reveal how many
penalty sticks each member has.
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
and Haha...
each have five.
Ji Hyo has one.
So Min has two.
Se Chan has six.
- 6?
- How do I have 6?
Kwang Soo has eight.
Eight?
(The final count of penalty sticks)
Please pick five penalty sticks.
The names on the five penalty sticks
can overlap, right?
That's right. One member
might carry out the penalty alone.
That would be the worst.
Please don't let it be me.
I have a high chance.
Let's go.
- Kwang Soo.
- So Min.
Don't pick mine.
I hope So Min and Ji Hyo
get included.
He picked one.
- The first one.
- What?
(Kwang Soo got picked.)
Gosh!
(He got picked right away
to carry out the penalty.)
Kwang Soo's penalties
will be forever!
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
One shot.
Here I go.
I mixed the sticks well.
No way.
What?
- What?
No way.
(It's Kwang Soo again!)
(The spirit of variety shows
has come down on Kwang Soo again.)
That's so funny.
Nice, nice!
Kwang Soo is the best for penalties!
Three more.
- Let's go.
- I will mix the sticks well.
This one won't be Kwang Soo's.
It's unbelievable.
If all five sticks are yours,
you shouldn't quit.
(Kwang Soo might be able
to monopolize the penalty.)
- He picked one.
- What?
What? Are you serious?
- Is it Kwang Soo again?
- Are you serious?
It's really Kwang Soo's!
Are you serious?
How is this possible?
It's really Kwang Soo's!
- It's really Kwang Soo's!
- It's really his!
(Everyone is surprised.)
(Even after 11 years,
they aren't used to his bad luck.)
- Come on.
- It's really his!
- No way.
- It's unbelievable.
How is this possible?
Two spots remain.
- Getting picked now is the worst.
- It's the worst.
- It must be Seok Sam.
- Please, please.
(He picks the fourth penalty stick.)
- Again?
- It must be Jong Kook's!
- Is it Jong Kook's?
(Gosh!)
(Lord Kim got picked.)
All right.
(Kwang Soo got someone
to do the dishes with.)
It's the last one.
The last one.
Please let me avoid it.
(It's time to pick
the last penalty stick.)
- The last one.
- Let's go.
- Please.
I really don't want to do this.
Let's go.
I hope Suk Jin gets picked.
Who is it?
Why? Who is it?
- Is it Kwang Soo?
- No way.
Is it you?
Me?
- No way.
- For real?
Give it to Suk Jin.
(Seok Sam got picked.)
- Yes!
- We did it!
(Seok Sam always gets picked
for things like this.)
It's beautiful.
Why did I have to pick mine?
- Do "Feeling and intuition."
- Feeling! Cross!
- Intuition! Cross!
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
There are so many dishes
with the batter.
We can finish it quickly.
How did I end up working
with servants?
Jong Kook, it's over.
I stooped to the servants' level.
We ate so much.
I don't want to do the dishes.
(Suk Jin takes the initiative
for the first time in a long while.)
Then you rinse it.
(They wash the dishes diligently.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
This might be your last penalty.
Seriously.
How many weeks remain?
I think this is his last penalty.
His last episode
might not have a penalty.
Kwang Soo,
this is your last penalty.
- Seriously.
- That might be the case.
- Really?
- I think this is his last penalty.
His last episode...
I doubt it would have a penalty.
Today's penalty...
makes me happy for some reason.
Don't say stuff like that.
Why are you making things awkward?
- It's nice...
- Don't say stuff like that.
to join Kwang Soo's last penalty.
(Without a word,)
(they carry on as if it's a part
of their daily lives.)
(11 years ago,)
- I don't know what to say.
- Hello.
I am Lee Kwang Soo.
I am 26 years old. I will work hard.
(Kwang Soo was in his mid-20s.)
(11 years have passed,)
(and he is now in his late-30s.)
Thank you so much.
(The last story...)
I am sorry.
(Kwang Soo wants to tell)
(Goodbye, Our Special Brother)