(The smell of fall is in the air
with a chilly wind.)
- Hello.
It's fall.
- In fall
(Fall is more precious
because it's short.)
Fall is in the air.
It's the season of the high sky
and plump horses.
But the trees are still green.
- I know.
- You're right.
- They should turn red.
- It suddenly became cold.
- My gosh.
- How did it change so soon?
I was wearing shorts
only three days ago.
- I wore short-sleeved shirts.
- He's still wearing shorts.
(He wears shorts
even when it's cold.)
- Shorts?
- What's wrong with that?
At least he's wearing long-sleeved
shirts because he's old now.
- Why would you say that?
- Now that he is in his 40s...
- I'm wearing two shirts now.
- He wasn't like that before.
He wore short-sleeved shirts
until the end of October.
This is too soon.
Right.
By the way,
you two are standing together again.
Actually, that's what I thought...
as I was walking in here.
"I think I picked the wrong spot."
(He's standing
right next to Ji Hyo.)
- If that's what you thought...
- You're being self-conscious.
If you felt that way,
- you should've moved...
- No.
- to another spot like this.
- That would've been strange.
- This happens a lot.
- It's strange.
I came in a little late today.
And you guys came in all together.
Actually, it's going crazy.
Some people want...
to cast Jong Kook
in my favorite drama,
"Princess Hours."
- "Princess Hours?"
- Jong Kook is the protagonist.
And it features Eun Hye and Ji Hyo.
My goodness. What?
I'll be the casting director.
- Like "Yoo's Princess Hours."
- Right.
That's what I'd like to watch.
It will get high viewer ratings.
- Thank you.
- Will you be in the drama too?
What? No, I'll just watch it.
- As a viewer,
- You just like it.
I like the cast.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
will be in the drama.
- You should produce a movie.
- All right.
- A blockbuster movie.
- I should make one.
- You should make it.
- For sure.
We can do that on Running Man.
- It will be fun.
- No, don't do it.
- We can make a drama here.
- Just don't.
- We can do it on Running Man.
- Suk Jin,
you won't be in the drama anyway.
Why not?
You should be in the drama
as Gung Ye.
- Gung Ye?
- That would be fun.
- As Jong Kook's spy.
- Ji Gung Ye.
- I can play Gung Ye.
Suk Jin, why don't you
change your hairstyle?
- Dye your hair.
- No.
- Why?
- It's always the same.
You know what? I've always wanted
to have dreadlocks.
Just do it. You can do it.
I want to try it at least once.
With your hair, you will get
only about three strands.
With your hair, you can make
only three strands of dreadlocks.
- Only three.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- How dare you...
- Why are you swearing?
- Three strands.
- I have thick hair.
Three dreadlocks.
Hey!
That's because dreadlocks are thick.
- My gosh.
- You...
He's right about that.
You will have to wear a queue.
I will try dreadlocks someday.
Give me a chance.
- Because Suk Jin...
- I'll do whatever I want.
Everything about Suk Jin is
fashionable except his hairstyle.
But his hairstyle is old-fashioned.
- This is just...
- He'd look good with bangs.
- Look.
- I have to go to a beauty shop.
This hairstyle is optimal
for Suk Jin's gesture.
How would he have
a different hairstyle?
This is what Suk Jin does
all the time.
- Let your hair grow longer.
- This is funny.
As you can see,
we will shoot today's episode
in a big mansion.
- This is cool.
- What is this building?
I didn't know there was
a place like this in Myeong-dong.
The owner of this mansion
invited you here.
- The owner?
- Who is it?
Please bring in
the owner of this mansion.
Is there someone?
(The owner is dressed
in flashy silver tails.)
(The frivolous fingers show
the dignity of the mansion owner.)
It must be someone rich.
Who is it? Are we having an actor?
(They burst into cheers...)
(and laughter.)
(The owner of the mansion...)
My goodness.
(The owner of the mansion,
Kim Joon Ho)
Is it a nouveau riche?
He's a nouveau riche.
He's just a puppet.
- Isn't he a butler?
- Seriously.
- Hello?
- Isn't he a butler?
What? A dolphin is stuck
in the drain? Pull it out.
A dolphin in the drain?
- All right.
- A butler.
Let Yoo Jae Suk
host the birthday party.
Welcome to my house.
- Hey, come on.
- Nice to meet you.
Hey, come on. Come on down, Joon Ho.
Welcome to Charlie's house.
- Charlie's house? Is that his name?
- By the way...
Obviously,
he rented the suit.
Isn't that his suit?
- I've always wanted to meet you.
- Hello.
Joon Ho, isn't this
your first time on Running Man?
Yes, it is.
- Is he the only guest?
- Hello.
Is Joon Ho the only guest for today?
- Only one?
- He's not that popular.
Joon Ho, is there someone else?
Is someone else coming?
He's not popular enough
to be a sole guest.
Seriously, did he come alone?
- We had many different plans,
- And?
but it happened this way.
I guess things got messed up.
Seriously, am I the only guest?
- Why is that?
- Joon Ho.
Since you're here,
I guess this is about a bet.
Don't say that.
That's your thing.
- Stop it.
- Let's call it promise.
- Promise?
- He calls it promise.
The promise special.
(He decided to become
the icon of promise.)
We are going to have a race
at Kim Joon Ho's house today.
- And it will be an individual game.
- Really?
The winner will be decided by
the number of chocolates you have.
Now you will pick the chocolates
that you will start the race with.
Please bring in the bags.
- That's right.
- The numbers of chocolates...
You're not supposed to touch them.
The bags have different numbers
of chocolates...
from 20 to 6.
- That's what we do?
- The difference is too big.
You can't tell how many there are.
The one that looks small
might have many chocolates.
You can put your name
on a bag you want.
- Let's pick one each.
- Okay.
- Joon Ho, you go first.
- Me?
Charlie.
Joon Ho has a pretty nose.
- But he has grey nose hair.
- What?
You're right. He has grey nose hair.
His nose hair is grey.
Why is he pretending not to hear us?
- Am I supposed to pick one?
- He can't hear you.
- His nose hair is grey.
- Joon Ho.
Your nose hair is grey.
My nose hair? Is it sticking out?
- No, it's grey.
- It's grey over here.
Excuse me.
(He apologizes for his grey
nose hair like a gentleman.)
It's all right.
I'm serious. It's true.
I understand.
- Don't pull it out. You might die.
- It's all right.
My ears are turning red.
Your ears?
Your ears are red.
I'm sorry.
I don't care about the men though.
I have manners.
All right then.
Ji Hyo, you go next.
I'll be the last one.
- I want number two.
- All right.
- We will open the bags all at once.
- Okay.
- I want number two.
- I want number three.
- This one is heavy.
- Okay. Number seven.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- Open your bag and show us.
- Se Chan, what's your number?
It has 20 chocolates at most.
- How many...
- Number three!
- What? Why?
- Why?
(Jae Suk picked number 3.)
- Is it 20 pieces?
- Jae Suk picked 20 chocolates.
- Are these 20 pieces?
- Yes.
Number 3 has 20 chocolates.
I have quite a lot.
- It's 12.
- That's good.
I...
- It's 16.
- I have 16.
I have 18.
That's good.
I have ten.
- So Min has 10.
- I have 14.
I have only 8. I wanted number 2.
Why did I pick this? It's only six.
What's with me?
How is this possible?
- How many for Jae Suk? Is it 20?
- I have 20.
The penalty will be decided
by the number of chocolates.
So you should take
good care of them.
- I have only six.
- Okay.
Today,
you will have
the Mansion of Misfortune Race.
The owner of this mansion...
and the icon of misfortune,
Kim Joon Ho...
invited you guys over
to get good energy from Running Man.
You should share your good luck
with Joon Ho...
to help him make it into top ranks.
Are we supposed to help him?
It will be an individual game today.
Those who make it
into the top four will get prizes.
And Joon Ho's rank will decide
who will get the penalty.
(His rank will decide the number
of members to get the penalty.)
You should protect me.
If Joon Ho makes it
into the top four,
among the members
who are ranked below Joon Ho,
one person picked by Joon Ho
will get the penalty.
- One person?
- If Joon Ho is in the top four.
If Joon Ho is in third place,
he will pick one from number 4 to 8.
(Joon Ho will pick one
from number 4 to 8.)
If Joon Ho fails to make it
into the top four,
all the members ranked below Joon Ho
including him will get the penalty.
(The members ranked below Joon Ho
including him will get the penalty.)
If Joon Ho is in fifth place,
number 5 to 8 will get the penalty.
Okay, I get it.
If he's number 6, number 6, 7,
and 8 will get the penalty.
If he's number 7,
number 7 and 8 will get the penalty.
If he's number eight,
all of you will get the penalty.
- He shouldn't be number 8.
- We can't make him number 8.
He shouldn't be number eight.
It's the best
to make him number four.
So you should help Joon Ho...
while staying
in a higher rank than him.
As I said, the winner will be
decided by the number of chocolates.
You will get more chocolates
after each mission.
And after each mission,
you can get extra chocolates
by playing One or the Other.
That sounds good.
And we will reveal...
Joon Ho's rank after each mission.
Number 1 and 2 will get to know
their ranks as well.
(Number 1 and 2 will get to know
their ranks as well.)
You will go get changed
and start the first mission then.
- Okay.
- Yes!
(They will get changed
and move to the first venue.)
This place reeks of alcohol.
- Wine.
- This is pretty.
Joon Ho is very successful.
- I prepared this for you.
- The crew members prepared it.
- Gosh, Joon Ho.
- You're successful.
You look even worse
in a casual outfit.
(Laughing)
I thought you were
talking about the wine.
(He has a mysterious body
that looks horrible in any outfit.)
Joon Ho, you look even worse
in a casual outfit.
Joon Ho is...
sitting here like that,
but he's a CEO.
- We know.
- Really?
He's a CEO.
- You know what?
- With Dae Hee...
Other comedians respect him a lot.
- Right.
- He's like their godfather.
Totally.
He's the father of comedians.
- The beggar of comedians?
- No, not a beggar.
Stubborn?
- No, the father.
- I said the father.
The father of comedians.
I'm not a beggar.
He says the beggar of comedians.
- The father of comedians.
- I'm embarrassed to say that.
- It's so cool.
Jae Suk is the father of comedians.
- No.
- He's the king.
The king?
- The king of comedians?
- The king.
- The king of comedians.
He's the king.
He's Mr. Comedian.
Mr. Comedian.
- Just a comedian?
- What am I?
- What does that mean?
- Just a comedian.
(Just a comedian.)
- How dare you...
- Like Mr. Ji Suk Jin.
Hey, Mr. Comedian.
He's the father of comedians,
and he's the king of comedians.
Hey, Mr. Comedian.
(The famous comedians
are gathered together here.)
All right. I'll tell you
about the mission then.
In the first mission, you work with
your team to get more chocolates.
It's called Shout at the Same Time.
- I see.
- Shout at the Same Time.
- Show us how you say it.
- That's your thing.
- You should say it right.
Shout at the Same Time.
This is how Cho Hye Lyun says it.
She keeps saying
that I stole her catchphrase.
- But mine is different.
- Like how?
Shout at the Same Time.
It's different, isn't it?
It sounds different.
- He's good.
- That's really nice.
You will play it in teams of two.
A team of two members
will wear headsets...
and play Cry in Silence
for three minutes.
But this isn't a game
with general rules.
Each member gets different words.
So the two members will
explain different words.
It will be confusing
because you can't hear each other.
And the number of correct answers
you give will be your points.
Even in the same team, the one
who gets more correct answers...
will be ranked higher.
(The one who gets more correct
answers will be ranked higher.)
Let's say
your team took first place.
If you get more correct answers
than your partner,
you'll be ranked higher.
In my team.
So you're playing it as a team,
but you still need to get
more correct answers.
Joon Ho, explain the rules.
- How is it going?
- So...
- This is like "Family Arcade."
- Right. This is Cry in Silence.
So we should shout.
- Right. Like how?
- What do we shout?
There are rules.
They are a little complicated.
Well...
Joon Ho,
you weren't listening, were you?
No.
I don't know
what he's talking about.
You'll see once you play it.
- I have no idea.
- You'll...
You'll see once it begins.
Okay.
You should pick teams first.
To pick a team,
you will choose a partner you want
all at the same time.
Those who choose each other
will be ruled out.
- Okay.
- Pointing at each other.
Send a signal.
Are you two going to be a team?
No.
They won't do that.
It's not going to happen.
Ji Hyo.
- If you keep choosing her,
- Good.
- you might become her partner.
- Right.
- They might become a team.
- Sure.
Let's do this.
- All right.
- He seems to like it.
- Let's begin.
- One.
One, two, and three.
See?
It's done.
Those who are paired up
should be out.
All right. Joon Ho and me.
(Joon Ho and Jae Suk
are on the same team.)
(Suk Jin and So Min,
and Se Chan and Haha are paired up.)
Who's left?
Okay.
- This is spontaneous.
- Okay.
All right.
- This is spontaneous.
Let's...
make things awkward.
- Okay.
- All right.
So Min and Suk Jin.
I can't hear anything.
This is what Suk Jin did today.
We talked about brand names earlier.
Se Chan said...
he liked to show
the brand names of his clothes.
- I like it.
- And Suk Jin said,
"Hey."
"That's what novices do."
"Those who don't know fashion
like to show brand names."
And look at his pants.
(His outfit is covered
with its brand name.)
- He's a novice.
- He knows nothing.
(He didn't hear it because
of the song "Ring Ding Dong.")
(Excited)
All right. You have three minutes.
Start.
- They get different words.
- What?
(The word Suk Jin explains
to So Min: Squid Game)
- It's a drama.
- It stinks.
(The word So Min explains
to Suk Jin: Stinky tofu)
- A drama.
- It stinks.
- No gesture.
- The smell.
- Squid.
Don't use your hands.
No gesture.
It's a drama. No?
No. You can only talk.
- It's a drama.
- Fold your hands behind your back.
- Square, triangle,
- Title?
and circle.
- They both should answer.
- It's a drama.
Square, triangle, and circle.
- This is what we do.
- A drama.
Green light, red light
I can't hear you.
- Green light, red light
- Light...
- Red light...
You know this.
You know what it is.
- Green light, red light
- Hatching?
- Green light.
- Hatching.
- My goodness.
- Hatching?
She knows it.
Are you crazy?
It's a famous drama.
Why are you yelling at me?
- Netflix!
- Don't get mad at me.
- He's throwing a tantrum.
- Hatching?
- He's upset.
- Why is he throwing a tantrum?
- I can't hear you.
- You die if you lose.
- I can't hear you!
- Read my lips.
- Explain to him.
- You go ahead now.
- Read my lips...
- It's a smelly food.
(So Min describes "stinky tofu.")
- A smelly food?
- It's a smelly food.
- No. "Green light, red light."
- A smelly food.
- You really can't hear me? Gosh.
- Try to guess the word.
- I mean...
He won't even try to listen to her.
- They should... Exactly.
- He's only talking to her.
Teamwork is important in this game.
- Hey!
- A smelly food.
A smelly food?
Oh, I get it. Stinky tofu.
- Correct.
- Stinky tofu.
(Finally, they succeed
and get the right answer.)
- What?
- It's in the bathroom.
- Okay. Keep going.
- Did you say "cookie stew?"
- When you...
- Cookie stew in the bathroom?
Open your mouth wide.
(Frustrated and upset)
- I can't hear him at all.
- They're running out of time.
- It's over.
- Time's up.
- You got only "stinky tofu" right.
- Hey.
- I couldn't hear him at all.
- I said, "green light, red light."
Your pronunciation wasn't right.
I couldn't read your lips.
- Right. Pronunciation is important.
- But...
You just kept
swearing and yelling at me.
No. I also said,
"square, triangle, and circle."
I couldn't hear you. You should've shaped
your mouth more clearly.
- You know "Green light, red light."
- I know that game and the drama.
But I couldn't hear you.
- Please stop arguing.
- Hey.
- That's enough, you guys.
- I'll never team up with him again.
I won't either.
- Give me your chocolate.
- You played dumb on purpose.
- That's ridiculous. Try it.
- Let's take turns.
- I know it was intentional.
- I couldn't hear you.
- Stop it, So Min.
- I have only six chocolates.
- You know that.
- I couldn't even hear you.
- Give me one chocolate.
- Give me one too.
- I'll never team up with you again.
- Help me out.
- I won't team up with you either.
- You have more chocolates.
What?
You have more chocolates than I do.
Ready. Go.
(Se Chan to Haha, nose hair,
Haha to Se Chan, parvenu)
Haha, what's in Joon Ho's nose?
Gosh.
It's in Joon Ho's nose. Two words.
In his nose.
(Something in his nose?)
- Nostrils.
- No.
- Nose hair.
- Yes, that's correct.
Correct.
- Hey.
- Haha.
What do people put on
when they go out these days?
Hey.
- Wait.
- Joon Ho...
- Joon Ho.
- Joon Ho?
- Joon Ho...
- Nose hair. Grey nose hair.
It stinks.
- A rich man...
- A rich man?
who became rich all of a sudden.
- Parvenu.
- Yes.
- It's my turn. When you go out,
- When I go out...
what do you put on?
- A mask.
- Correct.
(They get 3 answers right in a row.)
(Haha to Se Chan, gyeonggeomangdong)
(A Chinese idiom shows up.)
It's a Chinese idiom.
He doesn't know any Chinese idioms.
A Chinese idiom.
Gagyageogyeo?
- It's a Chinese idiom.
- King Sejong?
(He's getting
stiff shoulders already.)
A Chinese idiom.
A Chinese idiom?
Yes. Look at my lips.
You...
He doesn't know the meaning of it.
I...
You act...
like this.
A lunatic.
- You go like this.
- A Chinese idiom?
He doesn't know the meaning
of the idiom.
Pass.
- Hey.
- Haha, it's my turn now.
Glass slippers.
Glass slippers?
Who wears them?
(Se Chan to Haha, Cinderella)
A fairy tale.
- Glass slippers.
- A fairy tale.
- He doesn't know?
- A girl.
- Snow White.
- Yes. What?
- Yes.
(Snow White wears glass slippers?)
He said "Snow White."
No.
You idiot. Look at my lips.
(You idiot. Look at my lips.)
Snow White meets the seven dwarfs.
Oh, I know. An apple, right?
Yes.
Who eats the apple?
- An apple?
- Who eats the apple?
- That's not it.
- No.
- The apple...
- That's still Snow White.
- The apple.
- The apple. Snow White.
- The apple. Yes.
- She eats it and falls asleep.
- He got it all wrong.
- The seven dwarfs?
- He got confused.
- No. She eats the apple...
- She eats the apple.
and falls asleep.
- He suddenly got confused.
- She wears glass slippers.
- Yes.
- Who is she?
- No, listen. She eats the apple...
- She eats the apple...
- Cinderella doesn't eat an apple.
- and wears glass slippers. Who?
- It's Snow White who eats an apple.
- Snow White.
No.
- Glass slippers.
- No?
You said "apple."
She eats an apple...
- That must be...
- It has four syllables.
Yes, it has four syllables.
S-now-whi-te.
- No.
- The apple. Right?
- Glass slippers.
- Yes, she wears glass slippers...
- She wears glass slippers.
- and eats an apple.
- She eats an apple.
Who is she?
(Cinderella in the story Haha knows
eats an apple as well.)
- Who is she?
- No?
Gosh, that idiot.
- Come on. Who wears glass slippers?
- She doesn't...
She doesn't eat an apple.
She wears glass slippers
and eats an apple.
- She falls asleep after that.
- But the prince kisses her.
- Yes.
- My gosh. This is frustrating.
It has four syllables.
Does she turn into a frog?
(It's getting weirder.)
- Four syllables.
- Pumpkin carriage.
- Unbelievable.
- Seriously.
That's Snow White, right?
- Why...
- Another princess.
- What's wrong with them?
- My goodness.
- He's the problem.
- Hey.
- Cinderella doesn't eat an apple.
Why would she eat an apple?
- That's Snow White.
- See?
- It's Snow White who eats an apple.
- Yes.
- Who wears glass slippers?
- It's Cinderella who wears them.
- It's not Snow White.
- She wears them and eats an apple.
- Exactly. Right?
- No.
- She wears glass slippers... No?
- They both got it wrong.
- That's ridiculous.
- Am I wrong?
- Cinderella...
- Hey.
- After midnight...
- It turns back into a pumpkin.
- Cinderella goes home at midnight.
- That's right.
What a shame.
I did explain well, but...
- Hold on a second.
- Joon Ho.
- We combined those two stories.
- Yes.
- Cinderella and Snow White...
- You guys combined those stories.
- Your hand is so sweaty.
- I know.
- You got three questions right.
- Joon Ho, you get it now, right?
- We'll go first.
- Use simple words.
- It's our turn.
- We'll go first.
Oh, you two will go first?
- Yes, we'll go first.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- You can't. You have a small mouth.
- This means two syllables.
And this means three syllables.
- Come on. Don't cheat.
- Two syllables.
- Stop.
- Three syllables.
- He...
- Gosh.
- What are you doing?
- That's just disgusting.
He went like this.
"This means three syllables."
(He came up with a cheating skill.)
Two syllables, and three syllables.
Joon Ho,
I'll say a few keywords, okay?
There's no point in saying it loudly
since you can't hear anything.
Oh, my. I can't hear anything.
Let me get it straight.
Snow White's story...
- is similar to the story...
- Ring, ding, dong
- of Kong Jwi and Pat Jwi, right?
Ready. Here's your question. Go.
- Glass slippers...
- You get this as you age... Wait, no.
- Hands at the back.
- You...
(He's using his face
instead of his hands.)
What's that? What does that mean?
- This right here.
- What is it?
A double chin?
This. What you're seeing now.
You get this when you get old.
You're going...
You get this on your face
when you get old.
You're going...
- That's close.
- You're going...
- You get this on your face...
You go...
- You...
- What's he doing? Speak.
- Describe it.
- Let me answer. Goby.
Hands at the back.
You get this on your face.
(Goby uses his facial expressions
as he's not good with words.)
A monster?
Pass.
- It's really frustrating.
- Is it my turn?
You were on this.
- That's too easy.
- The TV show you appeared on.
(Jae Suk to Joon Ho,
"2 Days 1 Night")
Upper limit.
Upper limit and lower limit.
- Upper limit. Lower limit.
- Jerk?
Jerk?
- Upper limit. Lower limit.
- Is it...
Jerk?
- You get stuck on a certain word.
- What?
Jerk?
It...
(Gibberish)
What did you say?
- Describe the word.
- You go first.
I'll describe mine.
- The TV show...
- TV show?
that you appeared on.
"2 Days 1 Night."
Too loud.
The upstairs neighbors are too loud.
Three words.
Noise between floors?
- Correct.
- Great job.
- Keep going. You're good at this.
- Jae Suk is good at this.
They got easy questions.
Why didn't you say anything?
I'm not good at games like this.
You two got three questions right.
Since Jae Suk described them all,
he wins.
I win?
- I can't hear anything.
- Indeed.
Oh, my. I really can't hear at all.
Ready. Go.
(Jong Kook to Ji Hyo,
blind date for marriage)
What is it? Can we start? Okay.
Say, "love."
- Jong Kook.
- Say, "I like you."
- Four words.
- "Let us start dating."
- Stock investment.
- "My heart for you."
- Four words.
- Four words?
"Honey. Darling."
- A man.
- "I really like you."
A fan.
- A woman.
A man and a woman...
- meet each other.
- The opposite sex? Okay.
- They meet each other.
- "Let's get married."
They might end up...
- "Let's get married?"
- They talk about marriage.
(Let's get married.)
- "Let's get married?"
- They talk about marriage.
- "How about we get married?"
- Will you marry me?
A man and a woman...
- He said, "You and I..."
- meet up...
- to get married.
- To get married?
- Someone sets them up.
- Dating.
Someone sets them up. Four words.
- Jo...
- Someone sets them up.
Joraengi rice cake?
She said, "joraengi rice cake."
- Someone sets them up.
- "Joraengi rice cake?"
Speak more loudly.
- A man...
- A man.
- and a woman...
- A woman.
- meet up...
- They meet up.
to be introduced to each other.
A blind date.
No. Four words.
She doesn't know.
Arrangement.
It's for people who are not
so young anymore.
It's not that she doesn't know
the answer, right?
Four words.
I'm starting to think
that she might not know it.
- I bet she doesn't know.
- A group blind date?
See? She doesn't know the answer.
Not a group blind date.
- It's not a normal blind date.
- It's a Korean word.
- It's not a normal blind date?
- Add more words to that.
- You know...
- Picking up a girl in public.
What is it?
She doesn't know.
- Dating.
- No.
Jong Kook keeps smiling
unlike how he usually reacts.
A blind date for marriage.
(She finally got it right!)
- A blind date for marriage.
- Correct? Okay.
It's your turn.
Jong Kook.
- Say, "I love you."
- Gambling.
- "Gumbling?"
- Money.
- What?
Money.
- Mo...
- I want to edit this part...
- to make this look romantic.
- How many words?
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Lee Kwang Soo?
- His movie.
- They look so affectionate.
His movie? "Collective Invention?"
- This is so romantic.
- They're deeply in love.
- Two words.
- They're like Romeo and Juliet.
Two words?
(It makes
the love story lovers happy.)
- "I'm sorry."
- Gambling.
- My goodness.
Kwang Soo's gambling movie.
Kwang Soo's gangster movie?
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks."
- Two words. Correct.
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks."
(A perfect question for them
shows up.)
(Cheering)
(Ji Hyo to Jong Kook, cutie)
- Jong Kook.
- I...
- You.
- "I like you."
- It's a five-letter word.
It's a five-letter word.
What did you say?
- Five letters.
- Five letters? Okay.
- Come on.
- A cute gesture?
- Cutie.
- That's correct.
- That's impressive.
- Cutie.
- He sees it every day.
- Right.
- He's used to it.
- I bet he saw it yesterday too.
- Keep going.
- Time's up.
- It's over.
- Was "Cutie" the correct answer?
- Yes, it was.
- Really?
- We all feel the same way.
- I guess I did a good job.
- They did really well.
(The cutie shows up again.)
- She's acting cute again.
- I think I did a good job.
- I didn't expect that question.
- She's so cute.
They came in first place
with their fantastic teamwork.
- Really?
- That's amazing.
We can't defeat a couple
in a game like this.
Jong Kook described more words
to Ji Hyo.
- Really? I did?
- Yes.
Ji Hyo got 3 questions right.
So Ji Hyo is in 2nd place.
Se Chan is in 3rd place.
- He gets clumsy sometimes.
- He's so cute.
Jae Suk is in 5th place,
and Joon Ho is in 6th place.
So Min is in 7th place,
and Suk Jin is in 8th place.
We'll give you chocolates
according to your rankings.
- Really?
- We'll give you chocolates now.
- Oh, my.
- That's a lot.
- He got so many chocolates.
- Indeed.
- How many did he get?
- He got 20 chocolates.
- It's Se Chan.
- Se Chan, here you go.
- Thank you.
- That's a lot.
- How many did he get?
- He got 20.
- How many will I receive then?
- Twenty?
- Yes.
- And...
Currently, Joon Ho is ranked...
fifth out of all of you.
That's not bad.
- No. He should move up.
- He should be ranked fourth.
But it's a good start.
If he remains in fifth place
until the end,
those who are ranked from 5th to 8th
will get a penalty...
because Joon Ho is not
in the top four.
We can give some of our chocolates
to Joon Ho later.
True. But if you do,
it'd be a loss for you...
since you'd go down in the ranking.
And the top two, I'll tell you
your rankings in private.
Please come forward.
- Really? Will you tell us that?
- Yes.
No. I have
fewer chocolates than you.
- I don't have many.
- Now...
If you go two floors up,
you'll see three rooms
where you can play One or the Other.
You can enter any of those rooms.
You'll be given only five minutes.
You can gain more chocolates there.
We're here.
We're on the second floor.
I see numbers 1 and 2.
(Contemplating)
- One or the Other?
- It seems to me...
Oh, it's hard to decide.
- I'll go into the last room.
- What's this?
- Should we choose the room too?
- Joon Ho, you'll go in now, right?
- Kid, come on in.
- All right.
The game you will play
in this room is...
Russian roulette.
(Russian roulette)
- What's this?
- Take turns shooting each other.
The winner gets double
the amount he betted.
(The first one to pop the balloon
gets double the amount he betted.)
You have to place your bet first...
Regardless of the result
of the game,
I'm just excited
to get to point a gun at him.
(It's a good chance to get on
Jong Kook's nerves all he wants.)
Why don't we bet five chocolates?
Gosh. Fine. Let's bet five each.
It's up to luck,
and I have no choice but to do this.
Which one of you will shoot first?
- Who should go first?
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Wait.
The order is important
in this game too.
- If he goes first...
- It could pop in the first shot.
- You don't know either, right?
- That's correct.
- Did you shuffle it?
- Go ahead. You go first.
I think I should go first.
(Haha will go first.)
If the balloon pops,
Jong Kook loses.
Got it.
Go ahead.
(The business partners meet
at the worst place.)
(The two tycoons are fighting
over their stakes in a restaurant.)
(He who was a business partner
turns into an enemy.)
You haven't even gotten married yet.
I'm sorry.
(He acted cool but fails.)
- I think...
- Hold still.
Maybe it was supposed to pop
but it didn't.
No, I don't think so.
You should pull it all the way.
I pulled it all the way.
Then I guess you failed.
(He already got scared.)
(Breathing out heavily)
He's acting like an assassin.
(The assassin of the wilderness,
Muscle Gunman, shows up.)
(The latest movie, "Protein Pistol")
Don't move.
I said, stay put, you punk.
(Evil laughter)
Please spare me.
I'm begging you. Spare me.
- You punk.
- I have a wife and kids.
- You have a wife and kids? Right.
- A wife and kids?
- Please.
Okay. One.
(Could Muscle Gunman punish Haha?)
Two.
(He failed.)
(Little Gunman is back.)
How many bullets are there in it?
Hey, the first one to start is
at an advantage in this game.
I know that.
Why didn't you go first?
I always imagined this moment
behind your back.
What game are they playing?
(Screaming)
(The 2 gunmen in their 40s are lost
in playing cowboys.)
What's this game?
- You're out if it pops.
- Do you know what this is?
You startled me. What is it?
Get out.
You can't...
Wait, that's not how it's done.
- That's not how this works.
- Don't ruin the game.
Is that so?
(He's pointing the gun at Jong Kook
for the third time.)
Just get it over with.
(What could be
Muscle Gunman's fate?)
Shoot.
Does it pop when the bullet is shot?
- Sit down.
- If it pops, you lose.
- If it doesn't go off...
- Hey.
- Please. I'm begging you.
- What are you talking about?
- Please. Just this once.
- What are you begging for?
- Just one week.
Please give me just one week.
- Please.
- What's going on in here?
What game are you playing?
- Are you still playing the game?
- Get out.
- You're not done yet?
- Get out, old man.
- You're still playing it?
- "Get out, old man."
The old man
with three strands of hair.
I have a feeling
that it'll pop this time.
Say your last words.
Go ahead.
Shoot!
Hey, get it together, will you?
Focus, all right?
Please.
(Five chocolates are at stake.
How will their fate turn out?)
(Popping)
(Muscle Gunman beats Little Gunman
and wins five chocolates.)
Okay.
- Hello.
- I came with Joon Ho.
- Can we sit down right away?
- Yes, please sit.
The game you'll play in this room is
TMI Choice.
You'll be given a question
about the cast members.
If you get the question right,
we'll give you a double amount
of chocolates you betted.
I see.
Do we get to play once?
Yes, you have only one chance.
Where was Haha born?
(Stuttgart or Saint Petersburg)
Stuttgart or Saint Petersburg?
Where are those regions?
- Where?
- Germany.
Is Haha German?
- He was born in Germany.
- Stuttgart is on this side.
Saint Petersburg is the other side.
Please bet your chocolates.
That's all I know.
- You don't know the region?
- Stuttgart or Saint Petersburg?
(Ji Hyo betted one chocolate
on Stuttgart.)
Stutt... Shugart. Schubert.
Where is Schubert from?
Schubert.
(He talked nonsense
while contemplating for a while.)
Wait, Joon Ho.
- You shouldn't do this.
- It's okay.
- You shouldn't bet all you have.
- Don't worry.
Trust me. I'm telling you...
You decided to start anew.
- It's okay. These are chocolates.
- Come on.
- Don't do this, Joon Ho.
- What are you thinking?
You really shouldn't bet them all.
- Done.
- How many did you bet?
- I betted 27 chocolates.
- I see.
- And you betted three, right?
- Yes.
Joon Ho.
- I trust you.
- All right.
(What could be the answer?)
The answer is...
- Stuttgart.
- Yes!
(Stuttgart)
- Stuttgart.
- Yes!
(I hit the jackpot.)
Here. Have one.
- Have one.
- Give me one too, please.
Sure. Here you go.
Wait. This won't help me
create a good image.
My gosh.
- I'll give all of you...
- Are you done? Come on out.
Joon Ho, I see you won a lot.
- Yes, I did.
- Ji Hyo, how many did you win?
I betted three.
What game do we play here?
- What are the rules?
- The game you'll play here is...
- TMI Choice.
- I see.
You will be given a question
about one of the cast members.
- If you get it right,
- That's what we did this morning.
you'll get a double amount
of what you betted.
- We can double the amount?
- Here's your question.
Did Se Chan wash his feet...
while showering this morning?
(Yes or no)
I know the answer.
You mean if he rubbed his feet
with a bath towel, right?
Yes. Put them on this side
if you think he washed his feet...
I bet he didn't wash his feet.
I'm all in.
Se Chan always rinses his feet
with water.
He never uses soap to wash his feet.
I remember...
that he said it during a shoot.
I think he rubs down to his ankles
with a bath towel.
Right?
I betted all the 13 chocolates
I had.
Okay. He didn't wash his feet.
What? Why did you bet
on the same thing?
- He didn't wash his feet.
- How many are these?
They're 31.
- Okay.
- That's a lot.
- You bet he didn't wash his feet.
- Yes. We're all in.
- I hope he didn't wash his feet.
- Please.
- I really hope so.
- I'll be disappointed if he did.
- Please.
- That's not like him.
- The answer is...
- He didn't wash his feet.
- Okay.
You're rich now.
- While showering this morning,
- Yes?
did you wash your feet or not?
Actually, I recently changed...
my shower routine.
I rub my feet as well
with a bath ball now.
So I've been
scrubbing my feet these days.
Did you scrub them today?
No, not today.
(No, not today.)
I only scrub them at night
and not in the morning.
I'm trying to make it a habit
of scrubbing them at night,
so I didn't scrub them this morning.
(Thanks to Se Chan,
they both hit the jackpot.)
We scored big.
That's 30.
I'll take 31, please.
Jae Suk, you're rich.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You should have one.
- I should.
I should have one as well.
(A banquet hall
is prepared at the mansion.)
(2. Yang Se Chan, 3. Ji Suk Jin)
(8 nameplates with their names are
on an individual stand.)
- What's this?
- What's going on?
What is this for?
- What's this?
- One, two.
(They each find their stands.)
One, two, three.
- It's like...
- What is this for?
- What is this?
- It's like a presidential debate.
- It must be a debate.
- A debate?
I need to win a lot of chocolate...
and increase the number
in the next game.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
By being logical
and speaking eloquently,
you are to persuade
the staff of Running Man.
This is the Running Man
Election Debate.
- An election debate?
- This is out of the blue.
(Running Man Election Debate)
- I'm not good at debates.
- Neither am I.
You all entered the election
as celebrities...
who will have
a more promising year in 2022.
- All of us?
- Next year?
You had a good year in 2021,
but next year will be even better.
I like how that sounds.
You will each get
three minutes to speak.
Then we'll move on to a debate
where one takes initiative.
When the debate is over,
staff members will vote.
- You'll actually vote?
- Yes.
The chocolate you receive
will depend on your ranking.
During the debate, you will vote...
for the worst candidate among you.
That person will receive a penalty.
The worst candidate?
We should choose our words wisely.
I can't afford to get on
anyone's bad side.
In a minute,
starting with So Min,
you will get a minute
to appeal to the others.
- To gather votes?
- Exactly.
Take this time
to think about what you'll say.
(It's their first chance
to win over the staff.)
- This isn't easy.
- It's quite tricky.
What can I say?
Show us how valuable you are.
- Our value?
- In 2022.
I wonder what I should say.
Suk Jin...
What was that word again?
Together...
- This year...
- Suk Jin.
The word for when
two candidates come together.
- A partnership.
- Not a merger but...
What's the word?
- When two candidates...
- A unification.
Yes, a unification.
- I thought it was a merger.
Seriously?
I can't believe I forgot.
Haha, how about we put up
a unified front?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk's done
with his speech.)
Okay, I'm ready.
(Glancing)
Are you copying my words?
Why would you copy mine?
I wanted to know
how successful people speak.
Unbelievable.
You haven't changed a bit, have you?
Just so you know,
there are about 80 voters here.
They won't vote for you
if you sound snobby.
Not being greedy
can lead to good results.
All right. I'm good.
I'm ready.
(1. Jeon So Min, 2. Yang Se Chan,
3. Ji Suk Jin, 4. Yoo Jae Suk)
All right, we'll begin.
Jeon So Min will be
the first to speak.
Hello, everyone.
I am candidate number one
Jeon So Min.
It's good to meet you all.
There's a good reason...
why you can look forward to me
in the year to come.
I recovered from
being sick last year.
And like a frog
coming out of hibernation,
I've been taking on
more and more projects.
As you all know,
I haven't been able
to act in the past few months,
and Running Man was
the one and only project I was in.
However, this year,
I have two dramas coming up,
and another has been set
to air next year.
For me, the year 2022
is looking to be one...
where I enjoy the second surge
of great luck in life.
(1. Jeon So Min)
Hello?
- "Hello?"
- It's over.
- What was with the "Hello?"
- What was that?
Let's not be rude.
- Wait.
- Seriously?
Are we on limited time
like an actual debate?
- That was too short.
- Watch your language.
- Seriously.
- Come on!
- This is ridiculous.
- Hello.
I am Yang Se Chan,
the celebrity set to have...
a better year in 2022.
I'd appreciate a round of applause.
(2. Yang Se Chan)
(He made a request
in a cheesy voice,)
(but his shy fans
applaud with courage.)
Thank you.
His voice...
- You lost ten seconds.
- Thank you.
You see, next year...
- is the year of the tiger.
- What?
I was born in 1986
which is the year of the tiger.
What does that
have to do with anything?
It goes to show
that it could be my year.
Weren't you born
in the year of the vole?
That doesn't even exist.
You can say
that I'm still quite young as well.
Anything Running Man wants,
I can deliver.
A love connection too...
Enjoy it on your own.
We don't expect much
from you next year.
- Why not?
- Forget it.
I'm looking forward to
a love connection with a guest.
- We don't have many these days.
- With a guest?
They will. Also...
(His minute is over.)
See?
Hey, mic testing.
It's too short.
(Next is Mr. Ji,
the former event host)
Hello, everyone.
(Plucked)
(The event host makes his entrance.)
- The celebrity who...
- Is this an event?
- Hi, I'm Ji Suk Jin.
First of all,
I'd like to inform you
of my unrivaled quality.
I am the only
male celebrity in his 50s...
who is a regular
on a weekend variety show.
As you all know,
MSG Wannabe shocked the world.
It all goes to prove
my future value.
- Jae Suk made it happen.
- Also,
many projects are being
offered to me again.
That also proves
the future value I possess.
There you have it.
Aren't you looking forward
to how 2022 will turn out for me?
He fumbled just now.
I'm Ji Suk Jin.
Thank you!
(He wasted his time
by repeating himself.)
Hello, everyone.
Like this year...
and last year,
- next year...
- He's so serious.
You can put your faith in me.
- What a joke.
- We must first...
go over the basics.
- The Winter Olympics...
- He's so succinct.
and the World Cup.
International sports events...
will be held for us to enjoy.
When there are events
that steal most of our attention,
we must come up
with special episodes of our own.
So let me tell you this.
(Candidate Yoo is planning
a special episode.)
Next year, I will make sure that
Yoon Eun Hye appears on the show.
(I will make sure that
Yoon Eun Hye appears on the show.)
I second that!
(He promises to get
Yoon Eun Hye on the show.)
(The voters cheer.)
I will make that happen.
- Are you insane?
- One should make...
the grand events and surprises
that people look forward to happen.
- He's crazy.
- You know that.
- Seriously?
- Unbelievable.
- He went off the rails.
As you know,
I'm putting my life on the line.
My life is at risk
every time I mention her.
Anyway, please look forward
to me next year.
My cheekiness...
will continue next year.
(His time ends as he leaves
what could be a will.)
- Next year...
- Your time is up.
- Enough.
- That's enough!
Your minute is up.
That's too bad.
I had more to say, you know.
You'll have to speak faster.
Hello, everyone. I'm the cheeky...
(Hello, everyone. I'm the cheeky...)
I'm the cheeky chipmunk.
- This is the worst.
- Back when I was younger,
I flew around like
a chipmunk with wings.
However, I then became
the icon of self-reflection...
and became known as a failure.
My life was filled with bitterness.
I've already hit rock bottom...
which means a simple jump
can make me relevant again.
Jae Suk is at the top
which means...
Hello, I'm Kim Jong Kook...
and 2022 will be a better year
than 2021 was for me.
But you already knew this.
I began a new project
by opening my YouTube channel.
His YouTube channel!
- That's close to cheating.
- Come on.
That's like cheating.
Well...
Most importantly though,
for ten years, I wasn't able
to cash in the investment I made.
However, Haha promised
to free up my money for me.
- Finally?
- That's right.
- Will you get your money back?
- In any way he can.
He finally gave me hope that
I could make money with it again.
If that money gets freed up,
there will be nothing left
to hold me back.
You can probably tell yourselves,
but I have all the potential...
- in the world. Thank you.
- That's enough.
Okay.
I'm Haha, the celebrity
who will shine more in 2022.
I will be selling
my business next year.
(Okay!)
You must be aware
that I'm a kingmaker.
Kim Jong Kook is proof of that.
- I...
- A kingmaker?
He won the Grand Award at all
three major broadcasting stations.
Thanks to my help,
he also won the Grand Award
at the Entertainment Awards.
He was given the endorsement deal
to promote my business...
which helped reshape his image
from being like a thug.
After I dissolve
my business next year,
I will launch my new project
to become a rich man.
As long as I'm your leader,
you won't have
to pay for team dinners.
I am Song Ji Hyo,
the celebrity
who will shine brighter next year.
I'm candidate number eight.
I'm genuinely excited
for Ji Hyo though.
I believe...
that a career is built,
not earned by a lucky strike.
(A career is built,
not earned by a lucky strike.)
- That's a nice way to put it.
- Up until now,
I put up a wall around me.
However, I've been breaking it down.
- It has been coming down.
- She's not wrong.
In 2022,
I will be looking for love...
and seeking out
a better career path.
You'll be looking
for love next year?
I'm saying I'll be in love.
- I see.
- I'll be in love.
We heard what you all had to say.
Now, we will begin
the initiative debate.
- What's that?
- In the initiative debate,
the one in charge
will get three minutes.
Using that authority,
he or she will ask
any question they want.
- Got it.
- Who'd like to go first?
Suk Jin, go ahead.
(Candidate Ji raises his hand.)
Your three minutes begin now.
- My question is for Jae Suk.
- Sure.
How long do you expect
to be popular?
I'm not one to have
thought of that in particular.
Of course you haven't.
- The way I see it though...
- Yes?
I believe you're at your peak...
- and that you'll go downhill...
- I don't know how you'll take this,
but a fortune-teller
I met on another show said...
that I was in for
great luck next year.
That great luck refers to
your luck in real estate.
- Real estate?
- I'm sure that's what he meant.
Are we going to reveal
our economic conditions?
I don't know about that.
- Should I talk about yours too?
- I know that you don't own...
that many buildings.
Should I bring up the land
you bought in Paju?
- The land in Paju?
- Yes.
I've revealed it on a show before.
I've shared that already.
- Excuse me. This is my turn.
- All right.
Until when... I think...
your popularity reached its peak
this year.
"How Do You Play?" was a big hit.
This may be another topic,
but during the 11 years
of Running Man,
you remained obscure for nine years.
(Jae Suk's counterattack)
- Yes. He only got popular recently.
- It's seven years.
I helped you become popular
through MSG Wannabe.
I practically raised him.
- You really did.
- Right.
You should send Jae Suk
some gifts during the holidays.
- I don't do that.
- He should do that,
- but I don't...
- I can't do it because it's corny.
- When Ji Ho goes to college,
- But you...
I'll pay for his tuition.
Now that you put it that way...
Of course.
When Ji Ho goes to college,
I'll pay for his first tuition.
- Thank you.
- He will go to college, won't he?
- He will...
- Wait a minute.
(He will go to college, won't he?)
- Wait.
- Candidate number three.
- I meant...
- You attacked his family.
- That was a bit...
- I'm sorry.
I hope no one gets me wrong.
You never know what he wants.
Please don't get me wrong.
He might want to do something else
instead of going to college.
These days,
going to college is not a must.
- Of course not.
- Right, it's not.
- That's why I said that.
- All right.
- I apologize.
- I got your intention.
Thank you. Shall I go next?
- Okay.
- Sure.
Please turn on my mic. Thank you.
This is Yang Se Chan.
I want to ask a question
to candidate number seven, Haha.
You work really hard
on "How Do You Play?"
- but you slack off on our show.
- He does work really hard.
Right. Please tell us
which show you value more.
I've told you already.
I value Running Man more.
What about "How Do You Play?"
Are you ditching it?
I value that show as well.
If you were to choose between the two,
which one would you choose?
(A stress question to
choose between the two)
- Who are you to ask that?
- You need some time to think?
Who are you to ask that?
Last time,
you even dressed up on that show.
You dressed up for the opening.
But you don't do that here.
That's a misunderstanding.
You're saying that...
Thank you. That's all.
- I'll ask Mr. Ji a question now.
- Sure.
(Se Chan cuts him off and moves on.)
What's your secret to good health?
(What's your secret to good health?)
- That's random.
- Yes.
What's your secret to good health?
I think I'm healthier than you.
- In what ways?
- That's my secret.
Could you pay more respect...
- to your opposing candidate?
- I apologize.
The question was so poor that I...
What do you mean
the question was poor?
He suddenly asked
a random question...
when we're talking about celebrities
who will have a promising year.
- We're the same candidates.
- Why would you ask about my health?
- You should respect him.
- Please tell us your secret.
To stay healthy,
you need to eat small portions.
- And...
- Eat small portions?
Yes.
Didn't you stuff yourself
with the buckwheat crepe earlier?
I eat small portions intermittently.
I do that,
and I fight with my wife often.
- So I'm always tense.
- It invigorates you.
- That's my secret to good health.
- I see.
- My wife takes care of my health.
- All right.
Let me ask a question
to Mr. Kim Joon Ho this time.
Mr. Kim, how old are you?
You must think
you're a big star now.
Excuse me! How could he...
(You must think
you're a big star now, Se Chan.)
Why would he be mad?
As a fellow candidate...
Bo Pil!
- You should answer his question.
- Se Chan thinks he's a big star.
- What are you doing?
- You should answer his question.
He was just a little kid.
- He was just a kid.
- You should answer his question.
Why would you say that?
- Shall I take the initiative now?
- Sure.
Mr. Ji, how old are you?
I'm 56 this year.
- You'll turn 57 next year.
- That's right.
He's turning 57?
When do you plan to retire?
- Me?
- Yes.
I'll reveal that there.
- I'll retire when I turn 60.
- Really?
(I'll retire when I turn 60.)
Really?
That's only a few years away.
- It's only three years away.
- That's only a few years away.
That's only a few years away.
- You should make it clear.
- Make it clear.
Make it clear. When you turn...
I'll start my career again
when I turn 60.
I believe
my second heyday will come.
Then when are you planning
to retire?
When I can't walk on my own...
That's what you think.
But you never know what will happen.
You might get fired next week.
- That's true.
- Let's say...
- Of course.
- you got fired from Running Man.
Do you have a retirement plan?
I think Running Man
will be my last show.
Are you sure?
- Hold on.
- What about "Tteokbokki Brothers?"
What about "Tteokbokki Brothers?"
- All right.
- Okay.
I'll ask Mr. Kim Jong Kook...
- a question.
- Me? All right.
Do you actually...
Please answer it honestly.
If I succeed in inviting Eun Hye
to the show next year...
Hold on.
When you take the initiative,
you should ask questions
about the pledges...
and attack the opposing candidates.
I don't plan to do that at all.
I'm asking what you think
about my pledge.
Why would you get me involved
in your pledge?
You should ask a question about me.
I wanted to see
if you're willing to execute it.
- Execute it?
- If you can invite her.
Why would you ask me that?
You should ask her!
All right.
- He's full of anger.
- You're quite sensitive.
I mean, why would you ask me that?
I'm curious.
Why do you only ask his opinion?
(Why do you only ask his opinion?)
- All of a sudden?
- Doesn't my opinion matter too?
Is that so?
Hold on.
(Laughing)
- Hold on.
- Is that so?
- Why would you leave me out?
- Will you be okay with it?
I don't like the idea.
(I don't like the idea.)
Well done.
You don't like the idea
of inviting Eun Hye?
One of our members
is against the idea.
Then this makes...
But still,
even if she's against the idea,
people will be more interested
in it.
That's a good approach.
Anyway, I'll have to consider
various factors,
- but I'll proceed with the plan.
- That's great.
I promise to...
(He promises to keep his pledge.)
I haven't even begun.
- Let me take the initiative now.
- All right.
We're discussing
who would perform well next year,
but if you think about
the special talents of the members,
they're all lousy.
- Isn't yours the lousiest?
- We...
- His talent is old fashioned.
The one where he rolls his eyes.
- That's the lousiest one.
- It's the worst.
The one where he goes like this.
This is supposed to be my turn!
Starting with So Min,
you should all show
a new special talent.
- A new special talent?
- A new one?
So Min has the most special talents
among us.
She does.
- Can you impersonate Jeon Do Yeon?
- Jeon Do Yeon.
"Sung Tae! Hey, Gu Sung Tae."
- She's really good.
- Yes, So Min is good.
- She's good.
- She is.
- Can you do one, Se Chan?
- Shall I impersonate Kim Jung Min?
- Kim Jung Min?
- That's a good one.
- Kim Jung Min of...
- You mean the singer?
(Impersonating Kim Jung Min
of MSG Wannabe)
It'll be very brief.
(Come out)
(Let's go somewhere)
(Gosh, that startled me)
(There's a man)
Stop it. It's funny enough.
- What?
- Stop it since it's funny.
You told me to do it!
We all have special talents.
(Candidate Kim Joon Ho falls behind
his junior comedian.)
Do you have one, Suk Jin?
I'm a man
with excellent special talents.
But I haven't had a chance
to develop them.
- He will never develop them.
- He hasn't had a chance?
- I'll impersonate Lim Byung Soo.
- Until when are you going to...
- impersonate him?
- I'll impersonate Lim Byung Soo.
(The hit singer
of the 70s and 80s...)
(whose footage is difficult to find)
"Hello, everyone.
I'm Lim Byung Soo."
(Saying I love you)
(Is too common)
That's so old.
(His lousy special talent
with sweet voice)
We should be looking forward
to how 2022 will turn out.
I'll impersonate Baek Seol Hee now.
(My heart)
This is seriously old.
(Is beating)
He passed the comedian audition
with this.
He passed...
(It's a lousy special talent
from 30 years ago.)
Gosh, Father. You're doing so well.
This is just...
(Showing off his singing skill)
Isn't he just too much?
Take your initiative.
I asked him to show
a new special talent.
It's like his 60th birthday party.
Wasn't that hilarious?
He's been doing this
since his debut.
He's seriously incredible.
The young writers of the show
don't even know who they are.
- It's funny though.
- He's horrible.
Wasn't it fun to watch
even if you didn't know them?
It was fun to watch, right?
Mr. Yoo Jae Suk, you should
come up with a new special talent.
Let me impersonate Jong Kook.
It's been a while since I did.
- Sorry?
- Jong Kook?
- You'll impersonate me?
- I don't do it often.
A few of us know
that I sound exactly like him.
We do.
- I'll sing "One Man."
- "One Man?"
(There is a man)
(This man sounds super petty.)
He's making fun of you!
- You're taunting him.
- You should punch him for it.
- He made fun of you!
- No.
- That's not it.
- He's making fun of you.
How could he do that?
(I'm always in the same place)
My voice isn't working well today.
(Brazen)
(Right then,
the fake singer steps forward.)
Usually, my voice
is in good condition.
(There is a man)
What was that?
(He starts the second part
of his dinner show.)
- I'll show you my special talent.
- What was that?
- Which one?
- I'll show you my special talent.
(Twisting joints)
- That must hurt.
- What do you think?
That was my special talent.
- Gosh, he twisted my arm.
- That must've hurt.
He almost tore off my muscles.
That was my special talent.
Is it still my turn?
- I'll ask Haha a question.
- Your turn is over.
- It's over?
- Yes.
Gosh, I wasted my turn
on the lousy special talents.
(The end of a lousy talent show
that hasn't improved for 20 years)
It's been 20 years
since I last developed one.
Now, we'll do a mid-checkup.
Based on what you learned
through the debate,
write down the name of the person
you're not looking forward to.
- The one I don't look forward to?
Yes, pick the worst one
and submit it later.
Whom should I pick?
In one...
Gosh, whom should I pick?
Two,
three!
(The mid-checkup results
will be revealed soon.)
One vote for Haha,
one vote for Jong Kook,
three votes for Joon Ho,
and three votes for Suk Jin.
Joon Ho and Suk Jin were picked
as the worst candidates.
(Mid-checkup, Worst candidates,
Kim Joon Ho, Ji Suk Jin)
- Who voted for me?
- For the two of you...
- This is great.
- The members next to them...
will put makeup on them
before the final appeal.
- They'll put on makeup?
- Yes.
- On Suk Jin?
Wait. For Joon Ho...
He can handle
pretty much everything.
- I've done it a lot.
- He can handle everything.
- Nothing will be that bad.
- It won't be bad.
His plain face itself
is the funniest.
- I'm handsome for a comedian.
- You're funny as is.
(The youngest members help
with Candidate Ji's makeup.)
- He's bleeding.
- It won't be fun if it's too much.
(Putting on a straight face)
He's telling us not to put a lot...
- because it won't be fun.
- He just yelled at us.
We can't help with his makeup
because he's disheartening us.
- He won't let us!
- He's complaining.
Let us do it however we want.
Se Chan, you should make
his eyebrows droopy.
Yes, they should be.
- Make them droopy.
- You're making me look like a fool.
If you add too much,
it won't be fun.
What are you putting on my ear?
It won't be seen anyway.
- I'm coloring it.
- Hey.
Just let me do it!
- Suk Jin.
- His ear...
- So Min, that's a bit...
- His ear is bleeding.
- It can't be seen anyway.
- No, it will be.
- It's hard to erase it.
- So Min, that's too much.
That's too much.
- You're cute.
- He's cute.
- It's hilarious.
- Only my right side is red.
(They look more sallow
because of their red ears.)
That's the end of the debate.
You call that a debate?
What does that make us?
- Sorry?
- What does that make us?
They put makeup on you so that
you can raise their expectations.
Oh, is that so?
You keep...
- It doesn't mean anything.
- It's okay.
- That's it? We just put on makeup?
- Or the two of them...
- There was no reason.
- Just randomly?
Those who just tuned in
might wonder what we are.
All right, now.
Every staff member
is holding a ballot.
Everyone, please take a look
at my pledges.
- Everyone, let's become rich.
- Everyone.
Keep up with the trend.
They're not meaningless.
- You should read the trend.
- I'm the kingmaker.
Everyone.
(Ji Suk Jin,
"Old ways are the best.")
(Yoo Jae Suk, "I'll keep the pledge
that will draw attention.")
(Song Ji Hyo, "I'll communicate
with the world.")
(After each candidate's
last remark,)
(the staff members
carefully cast their votes.)
(Who will they pick
as the celebrity...)
(who has the most promising year
in 2022?)
- Everyone, we have the results.
- All right.
I'd be grateful if just one of you
voted for me.
- I don't think I'd get one.
- Let's just hit the average.
The total number of votes is 97.
Ninety-seven votes? That's a lot.
All right, now.
There were some who wrote
their reasons.
- Oh, really?
- I'll read them to you.
- Reasons?
- This person picked Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- They wrote only one thing.
- What does it say?
- "Yoon Eun Hye."
(The reason they voted for Jae Suk
was Yoon Eun Hye.)
- My gosh.
- That was his pledge.
- I knew my pledge was strong.
- It's one of the production crew.
Another person
who picked Jae Suk...
said, "I'm in charge of him,
so he needs to do well."
("I'm in charge of him,
so he needs to do well.")
I can tell who wrote that.
(Jae Suk's cameraman
played favorites with him.)
- Next is So Min.
- Someone picked me?
- "Let's go, the Year of the Tiger."
- Who wrote that?
I was also born in the Year of
the Tiger. Why didn't you pick me?
- Who wrote it?
- I'm in the Year of the Tiger too.
You see? You were born
in the Year of the Rat.
- Let me announce the results.
- The Year of the Rat?
Okay.
(Announcing the final results)
- First place...
- It must be Jae Suk.
won 25 votes.
(1st place, 25 votes)
(First-place candidate
won 25 votes out of 97.)
- It must be Jae Suk.
I'd be glad if I got just one vote.
(1st place, 25 votes)
It's Ji Suk Jin.
What?
(Ji Suk Jin won 1st place
in the list of a celebrity...)
(that will have a promising year
in 2022.)
Thank you so much, everyone!
- What's so promising about him?
- I'll work hard.
- Everyone!
I'm sorry that
I don't recognize you sometimes.
Earlier, he showed
an old-fashioned special talent.
I'm always grateful.
What is this?
(An encore stage
to celebrate his win)
(His sweet voice melted
the hearts of staff members.)
(A shoulder dance is a must
at a party.)
(They can't help but get excited.)
- You're doing well.
- All right!
Good job.
That suits him well.
- That was hilarious.
- How did Suk Jin win first place?
I know. Thank you so much.
Next is second place.
(2nd place)
Second place won seventeen votes.
(2nd place, 17 votes)
- It's Yang Se Chan.
- What?
(2nd place, 17 votes, Yang Se Chan)
It's Se Chan?
Thank you so much!
(He puts on an encore performance
right away.)
(Gosh, that startled me)
They voted for me?
Thank you so much.
(Se Chan gets 18 chocolates
for winning 2nd place.)
Thank you, everyone.
Gosh, I need to come in
fourth place, at least.
Next is third place.
Third place won fifteen votes.
(3rd place, 15 votes)
It's Yoo Jae Suk.
- As expected.
- He can't get better than this.
Please look forward to
my performance next year.
- You can do it!
- Shouldn't Joon Ho...
come in fourth place?
If you don't put me in fourth place,
- you'll all get penalties.
- You're right.
You should've encouraged me.
- I forgot about that.
- Seeing how things are going,
I think you'll win fourth place.
- I forgot about that.
All right. Fourth place...
- won 13 votes.
- Kim Joon Ho.
It's Kim Jong Kook.
- Joon Ho won fourth place?
- No, Jong Kook did.
- It's me?
- It's Jong Kook?
- It's me.
- Gosh, seriously.
Goodness.
- Jong Kook...
- He should be in fourth place.
Fifth place won ten votes.
It's Song Ji Hyo.
- What happened, Joon Ho?
- Joon Ho...
Why is he even here?
Sixth place won nine votes.
It's Jeon So Min.
- What's wrong with him?
- This is...
Next is seventh place.
Seventh place won six votes.
It's Kim Joon Ho.
- I'm in seventh place?
- What? I'm in last place?
- Kim Joon Ho.
- I'm in seventh place?
Haha, you're in last place.
You won three votes.
Three votes?
Go and get more votes
from "How Do You Play?"
No one will vote for you here!
Go and get more votes
from "How Do You Play?"
You should just join
"How Do You Play?"
Why do you keep bringing that up?
- I mean...
- Don't mention that show here.
Many of our staff members
felt betrayed.
That's not true! Don't be like this.
I value Running Man more!
Thank you, anyway.
(Thank you, anyway.)
(At least Haha
won Jae Suk's heart.)
I'll tell you Joon Ho's ranking
according to the results.
Joon Ho got 8 chocolates
because he's in 7th place.
(Joon Ho got only 8 chocolates
for winning 7th place.)
- And?
- But...
he's in second place.
- I'm in second place?
- He must have a lot.
He increased the number
through betting.
He earned more chocolates
- He was betting separately.
- Don't make bets!
He was betting separately.
- You should promise me.
- He did what?
- Seriously?
- Why would you do that on our show?
- Stop betting, Joon Ho.
- Why would you keep betting them?
Why would you do that on our show?
I only tried to win some chocolates.
Suk Jin and Se Chan who won
1st and 2nd place,
I'll tell you your ranking.
Please come forward.
- They'll only share it with us.
- All right.
Joon Ho must be in fourth place
at least.
- Yes, he must.
- Right?
(Sharing his ranking)
Did I hear that right?
I won 1st place this time,
but I'm in 8th place overall?
I'm in 8th place out of 8?
(Despite getting 20 chocolates,
he's in last place.)
Let's move on to the room
where you can play One or the Other.
- All right.
- Which room should I pick?
- Oh, gosh.
What is this? I haven't played it.
- It's Russian roulette.
- I see.
- You two should play.
- I'm betting everything I got.
- You're betting the whole thing?
- Yes.
- I'll bet everything.
- You shouldn't...
- You shouldn't bet like this.
- You shouldn't do this.
No, I'll give it a try.
- No, this is...
- You shouldn't bet everything.
I'm infuriated
because I lost earlier.
- I'll bet six.
- But you should be...
in fourth place, at least.
It's go big or go home.
It has a 50-50 chance.
- It has a 50-50 chance.
- Here's my bet.
If the balloon pops,
- then Suk Jin will be eliminated.
- How many times can he...
What if it pops on the last bullet?
(Will he be able to break the jinx?)
(Popping)
(Unlike everyone's expectation,
he popped the balloon at once.)
- I told you I'd bet more!
- You were right.
- Goodness.
- Darn it.
- I'll double the amount you bet.
- All right. Thank you.
(Joon Ho wins
a total of 48 chocolates.)
That's a lot.
I won 48 chocolates.
- Are you joining this room?
- You can go in there.
- What are we playing?
- The game you'll be playing...
is Dial Tone Odd or Even.
- Sorry?
- You'll have to choose...
whether your friend
will pick up the call...
after it rings in odd numbers
or even numbers.
If your guess is right, you'll get
double the amount you bet.
Gosh, this is the difficult part.
How do we know
when they'll pick up?
I'll bet ten.
(Haha bets 10 chocolates.)
Which one?
- I bet on odd numbers.
- You bet ten on odd numbers.
I'll bet ten on even numbers.
You bet ten on even numbers.
I'm calling Geun Sik.
- That's one.
- One.
- Who are you calling?
- I'm calling Geun Sik.
(It rings once.)
Two. That's an even number.
Pick it up!
- Pick it up!
- Hey, Haha.
Geun Sik, I love you.
I'm shooting Running Man right now.
You're indeed my best friend.
Thanks a lot!
Since you succeeded,
I'll give you 20 chocolates.
Gosh, what do I do?
I can watch how she does, right?
I'll call my mom.
(So Min, who bet on even numbers,
decides to call her mom.)
- Odd.
- That's one.
(It rings once.)
(So Min bet on even numbers.)
Even.
(She picked up at an even number!)
Mom, I love you.
(Mom, I love you.
I'll call you later.)
I'm in the middle of a shoot.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
She's not surprised at all.
(So Min, who bet on even numbers,
wins 20 chocolates.)
- That was incredible.
- Haha.
I'll never come back to this room.
- I won't come back either.
- This room...
- It's not to my liking.
- It's too difficult.
Let's go to the other room.
The TMI Room.
I'll ask you TMI questions
about the members.
(Jae Suk entered the TMI Room.)
What's Se Chan's body secret?
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
on the mole on his butt.
The question repulses me.
(The question repulses me.)
(What's Se Chan's body secret?)
It repulses so much.
It's the TMI that he shared himself.
Gosh, this is...
What did you say?
What about his nipple?
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
(She fails to hold her laughter.)
(The TMI makes
the staff laugh as well.)
His hair grows
on the mole on his butt.
(The TMI makes
the staff laugh as well.)
The hair is supposedly very long.
His hair grows
on the left nipple only?
(Laughing)
Let's go. Why can't I?
- You can play with him.
- All right.
I'll tell you the question.
(He joins Jae Suk
without knowing what it is.)
- By the way...
- This is TMI Choice.
Did you earn some?
No, I lost them.
This is TMI Choice.
What's Se Chan's body secret?
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
on the mole on his butt.
The question is so repulsive.
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
on the mole on his butt.
- On the mole on his butt?
- On the mole on his butt. Yes.
(Sighing)
Can the hair grow
on the left nipple only?
I can't believe
I have to think about this.
This is driving me crazy.
Do I need to worry about this?
It's impossible to have hair grow
on the left nipple only.
You could have hair grow on a mole.
But how does he know
he has a mole on his butt?
I am not sure about this.
- Nipple.
- I will go with the nipple too.
(Jae Suk bets 1 chocolate
on the nipple.)
Please place your bet.
Does anyone grow hair
on the left nipple only?
I don't even know.
(Suk Jin bets 2 chocolates
on the nipple.)
What's the answer?
- I am so curious.
- Se Chan's body secret is...
(Is it about the left nipple
or the mole on the butt?)
(They have seen Se Chan's nipples
and butt in the past 5 years.)
What's the answer?
- I am so curious.
- Se Chan's body secret is...
that his hair grows
on the left nipple only.
I should have bet
all the chocolates.
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
(Both of them are correct.)
He wouldn't have known
about hair on his butt.
For goodness' sake.
(They didn't win much since they bet
only a few chocolates.)
I heard that you have a body secret.
Please reveal what it is.
I don't know
if it's exactly a body secret.
Hair grows...
around my left nipple.
(He readily agreed to show it.)
- All right, We will film it.
- It's right here.
(Surprisingly,
he was telling the truth.)
Why does he have hair
on his left nipple only?
How annoying! It makes no sense.
He would be
the most annoyed about it.
- He would be the most annoyed.
- That's right.
- Hair on the left nipple only.
- Why does it grow there only?
- The left nipple.
- Is it the same for his armpit?
They wouldn't know.
How would Hyung In know that?
Maybe his body hair grows
on the left side only.
- Let's have another one.
I can give you a question
about someone else.
- Really?
- Let's have another one.
This is the most interesting.
You want to bet all chocolates.
Please give us another one.
(The production crew
provides an additional question.)
- Jong Kook has a mole on his neck.
- Okay.
Is it on his left or right side?
I know this.
(Is Jong Kook's neck mole
on his left side or right side?)
Is it on his left or right side?
Isn't it on his right side?
I think it's on his right side.
How about you, Jong Kook?
- I am from Anyang.
- Yes.
(He saw Jong Kook's neck mole
every week for the past 11 years.)
(He definitely saw it.)
My goodness.
Which side is which?
- The left side and right side.
- I will choose the right side.
- Did you bet everything?
- I bet everything.
I don't know.
How many chocolates are there?
There are 71 chocolates.
You bet 71 chocolates.
- I will bet all chocolates too.
- You will bet on the right side.
- Yes.
- There are 71 chocolates.
(Both of them went all in
on the right side.)
Jong Kook's neck mole is...
(What will be the answer?)
on his left side.
(The left side)
I am sorry.
- Why did you ask about the number?
- Hyung In.
Seriously.
- Why did you ask about the number?
- Hyung In.
(The production crew takes
all the chocolates.)
What a strange producer!
- Why did you ask?
I was curious.
For goodness' sake.
You can leave now.
Are you telling us to get lost?
(They lose all the chocolates
they collected during the day.)
Suk Jin. I was waiting for my turn.
- Why did you cut in line?
- Jong Kook.
Your mole is
really on the left side.
(He cries blood.)
It's on the left side.
(They hear a cheer
from the neighboring room.)
(The icon of promise won big
from playing Russian roulette.)
(He won 96 chocolates!)
(He became rich in chocolates.)
You won 96 chocolates.
That's great.
Joon Ho, kids watch this show.
Kids love this show.
If you show
that kind of a reaction...
Hey, these are chocolates.
I should make another call.
- Does it pay well?
- I will bet everything.
This is the last one.
(He enters the TMI Room
as haughty as ever.)
This is your last chance.
I have too many chocolates.
That's insane.
What's Se Chan's body secret?
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
on the mole on his butt.
- That's disgusting.
- I saw it.
Seriously.
(Everyone reacts the same way
to the question.)
I saw it.
It's strange...
that hair grows
on only one of the nipples.
I think I heard about it.
I think he got drunk and
told me about it tearfully.
Please place your bet.
The chest.
- Eight, ten...
- Joon Ho.
Let's bet on the same thing.
- Two, one.
- A mole on the butt is strange too.
- What is up with you?
- I hit the jackpot.
(Heavy)
I hit the jackpot over there.
I went all in and hit the jackpot.
(She hit the jackpot
and became a new-rich.)
(Did she hit the jackpot?)
Shall we go?
What will it be?
Three, two...
I choose the nipple.
(Joon Ho suddenly opens his bag.)
How about you, Joon Ho?
Will you go all in?
The butt.
(He bets everything on the butt.)
(The icon of promise
was motivated by So Min.)
So Min motivated me.
Se Chan's body secret is...
I chose the nipple
and Joon Ho chose the butt.
(Haha bet on the nipple
and Joon Ho bet on the butt.)
I chose the nipple
and Joon Ho chose the butt.
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
(The answer is the left nipple.)
His hair grows
on the left nipple only.
(His eyes become unfocused.)
I will give you ten chocolates.
It's So Min's fault.
Why did she have to enter
and run her mouth?
Please move on to the next mission.
Use this for transportation.
- Forget it.
- Use this for transportation.
Give me five chocolates.
Eat gukbap too.
Five chocolates.
- Don't walk home, okay?
- For goodness' sake.
(The icon of promise
sacrificed himself for a lesson.)
I shouldn't have entered this room.
What a lousy room.
(Thus, his life turned bitter.)
For goodness' sake.
(The second One or the Other ends.)
- We will now have the last mission.
- Okay.
We have to point out...
that Joon Ho...
He is a fool.
How many times
did I tell you not to do that?
Gosh, that really hurt.
I told you...
not to do that.
I told you to stop
when you won chocolates.
- I told you not to do that.
- So Min bragged about her winnings.
Why did you bet recklessly
just because she won chocolates?
We need to make him number four.
- He needs to move up the ranks.
- Seriously.
I will explain the last mission.
In the last mission, you will see...
the difference between Joon Ho,
the easy Kim Grand Award,
and Jong Kook,
the scary Kim Grand Award.
It's Green Light, Red Light
with Kim Grand Award.
What?
The two Kim Grand Awards
will take turns...
being the traffic cop.
Unlike the traditional version,
everyone will disperse in a minute
before the game starts.
The traffic cop will walk around...
and say "Green light, red light"
with the walkie-talkie.
The seven members...
will have a bell on their shoes.
While the traffic cop
does the chant,
they will search the place
for the four-leaf clover cards.
A lot of cards are hidden.
While the traffic cop chants,
"Green light, red light,"
- the rest of the members can move.
- Okay.
When the chant ends,
both the traffic cop...
and other members can't move.
But if you aren't
in his line of sight,
you can search freely.
- I see.
- Do you understand?
Let's say the chant ended...
and the traffic cop
caught you moving.
- Then you are out.
- Yes.
Do the traffic cops get chocolates
for catching people?
Each person you catch will count
as 3 4-leaf clover cards.
(Each person they catch will count
as 3 4-leaf clover cards.)
Okay.
It will be hard. Isn't that right?
Round One's traffic cop is...
- Jong Kook.
- It will be hard.
You have a minute to hide.
- A minute.
- Then the game will begin...
- with the chant.
- I bet the cards are outside.
Once you go up,
you won't be able to come back down.
All right.
(Go to a place where you can find
the four-leaf clover cards!)
All right. Get ready.
Your one minute begins now.
Find many four-leaf clovers
in order to win.
Many people are going up the stairs.
(Kim Grand Award listens
to figure out their locations.)
Find many four-leaf clovers
in order to win.
(Joon Ho and Jae Suk go
to the 2nd floor.)
Where are the four-leaf clovers?
(Where are the four-leaf clovers?)
(Searching)
Okay. Here is one.
(It's a four-leaf clover!)
A four-leaf clover.
Okay. It was here.
I found one.
(The number of four-leaf clovers
will determine the ranking.)
(Se Chan found
a four-leaf clover as well.)
Here.
(1 card)
(2 cards)
This is great. I found two.
(Everyone is absorbed in the search
for four-leaf clovers.)
You have 20 seconds.
(20 seconds left.)
There are no cards here.
Do we have 20 seconds left?
I need to hide now.
(The members become nervous
with 20 seconds remaining.)
Where should I hide? Oh, no.
Oh, no.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan
go up to the 2nd floor.)
(Suk Jin also
goes up to the 2nd floor.)
Green light...
(Jong Kook sets off.)
(He is on the move.)
Red...
(So Min is the only one
who is still outside.)
The game has begun.
(The rest of the timid members...)
(are on the 2nd floor of the house.)
(They hear Jong Kook's voice.)
(But they don't know where he is.)
(Please.)
(Where will Jong Kook head?)
Light...
(He heads to the 2nd floor.)
Red...
(6 members
are searching the 2nd floor.)
(He storms the 2nd floor.)
Light.
(He spots Suk Jin
as he says the last word!)
Green light, red light.
(Jong Kook takes steps toward him.)
Green light...
(He charges at the target.)
Light...
(He passes by a weak member!)
Red light.
(Suk Jin quickly runs away.)
Green light,
red light.
(The tense atmosphere
makes the members hide hurriedly.)
(Haha spots Jong Kook.)
Red light.
Green light, red...
(Green light, red...)
Light.
Green light, red light.
Haha is out.
(Haha ran fast,)
(but he couldn't stop at "Light!")
(Haha is out.)
I am so annoyed.
(News of the first elimination...)
(makes everyone
even more nervous.)
(Ji Hyo)
(Will the members
on the 2nd floor be safe?)
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk came outside.)
(Walking stealthily)
Green light, red light.
(He finds a four-leaf clover.)
(Ji Hyo is also searching
with bated breath.)
Green light...
Green light, red...
(Suk Jin runs into Jong Kook
again.)
(He runs into Jong Kook
at every turn.)
light.
Green light, red light.
Where is everyone?
What am I going to do?
Green light, red light.
Don't come here. Go away.
Go away.
Go away, Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk joins her
against her wish.)
Hey.
Did you find the clovers?
What do they look like?
- Did you find the clovers?
- They are in envelopes.
Green light, red light.
Where is Jong Kook?
(It's Jong Kook.)
(Chuckling)
Green light, red light.
(The two targets are on his radar.)
Oh, no.
Green light...
(Jong Kook is watching.)
Red light.
(He will be eliminated
if he moves an inch.)
Green light, red light.
(So Min couldn't stop at "Light.")
- So Min, you are out.
- I didn't hear it.
(So Min is out.)
The sound broke off.
I am out.
I couldn't find any clovers.
(She gets eliminated
without finding any clovers.)
Green light, red light.
(Jong Kook moves.)
(He runs to a place
where Jong Kook can't see him.)
Green light...
(He moves as his heart pounds.)
Red light.
(My goodness.)
Green light, red light.
(His heart pounds.)
Red light.
(Peek-a-boo.)
Green light, red light.
(Even when Jong Kook attacks
suddenly,)
(Jae Suk remains frozen.)
Green light, red light.
(The target holds out,
but Jong Kook is persistent.)
Green light, red light.
(Suk Jin enters the house.)
- Look under the wine.
- Books.
Check the green books.
- Look under the wine.
- It's next to that green book.
I want you to do well, Suk Jin.
It's at the top.
- It's over there.
- There is another one at the top.
- Green light,
- Why can't you see it?
- red light.
- Look under the wine.
(The survivors move
while the focus is on Jae Suk.)
Green light, red light.
(Jae Suk runs away.)
(I barely managed to survive.)
Green light, red light.
(He runs away
from Jong Kook's gaze.)
Green...
Red light.
(Jong Kook appears again!)
Green light, red light.
(Freezing)
(Chuckling)
(Kim Grand Award is a scary hunter.)
Green light, red light.
You have one minute.
(Jae Suk needs a lot of clovers.)
Green light, red light.
For goodness' sake.
(Running at full speed)
(Jae Suk gives his last spurt
away from Jong Kook.)
Green light, red light.
(Jong Kook chases after him.)
(A scary hide-and-seek)
Green light, red light.
(Will Jae Suk get caught
in 1 minute?)
Green light, red light.
(Joon Ho was on the 2nd floor.)
(He looks for four-leaf clovers.)
(You can see Jong Kook
in the mirror!)
(After pretending to leave,
he looks in the mirror.)
Green light, red light.
(He moved.)
(Jong Kook caught him
by looking in the mirror.)
You moved.
Joon Ho is out.
- You moved.
- You can't use a mirror.
You can't use a mirror.
- Yes, I can.
- Does it count?
I can't believe it counts.
This time, Joon Ho is
the traffic cop.
Green...
(Joon Ho needs to catch many people
in order to be in the top 4.)
light...
Green light, red light.
(No matter how much he runs,)
I can't catch a single person.
(he can't catch a single person.)
(Since this Kim Grand Award
is slow,)
There it is.
(they find many four-leaf clovers!)
(The members collect
a lot of four-leaf clovers.)
Green light, red light.
(He misses the member
who was behind him.)
Where did they go?
They are so fast.
This really is Running Man.
Joon Ho, look over there.
Joon Ho, here.
(Some members try to bump up
Joon Ho's rank.)
I caught you.
I let you catch me.
Is that so?
- I let you catch me.
- Okay. Good.
Time's up. Please gather around.
I found nine.
- Ten.
- How did you find so many?
How did you find so many?
(Joon Ho caught two members!)
- I did this in my childhood.
- Suk Jin found so many.
How many did you find?
I couldn't find them.
- You found a lot.
- Where did you find them?
I couldn't spot them.
I only found three.
- How many did you find?
- Zero.
What will happen?
Can his rank be the fourth?
My goodness.
This is bad.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
The result is out.
This is bad.
I will announce Joon Ho's rank first
since it's the most important.
I think I am the fourth.
If Joon Ho is in the top four,
only one of the lower ranks
will receive the penalty.
He needs to be the fourth.
If Joon Ho's rank is
the fifth or lower,
everyone below him
will receive the penalty with him.
If Joon Ho's rank is the last,
everyone will receive the penalty.
- This is scary.
- Kim Joon Ho's final rank is...
Joon Ho.
He's got nine chocolates.
(Kim Joon Ho's final rank is...)
- He's in sixth place.
- Why?
(6th place)
- You are not good at calculations.
You should've made me the fourth.
- And...
- My goodness.
Then who's ranked below me?
And there are two members
who took seventh place.
What happened?
My goodness.
That can't be me.
The two members who took seventh
place are Se Chan and Jae Suk.
(In 7th place, Se Chan and Jae Suk)
(They will get the penalty
with 7 chocolates.)
So the members
to get the penalty today...
are Joon Ho, Jae Suk, and Se Chan.
My gosh. Really?
Oh, dear.
- The prize is...
- Do we have a prize?
It's the symbol of good luck.
It's Korean pork.
- My gosh.
- Really?
It's pork.
(1st place So Min, 2nd place Ji Hyo,
3rd place Jong Kook and Haha)
The four of you will get the pork.
I'll reveal today's penalty.
- What is it?
- The penalty.
The penalty is...
- Is it something tiresome?
- We will give you...
Something tiresome.
a storybook which you will read
and write a book report on.
- My gosh.
- I hate that.
- That's good.
- I'm not good at it.
It's really tiresome.
That's the worst.
- What?
- I'd rather get doused in water.
You should read a children's book
we give you...
- Good.
- and write...
a book report of 400 letters.
- Gosh, seriously...
- My goodness.
I can't believe this.
I'll read "Cinderella."
Let me see.
(Se Chan wants to read "Cinderella"
which he didn't know earlier.)
I'll read
"The Emperor's New Clothes."
Can I write it right away?
Yes. Read the book first.
We will post it
on Running Man's social media.
Gosh, please.
I'll read
"Aladdin's Wonderful Lamp."
I don't know how to write
a book report.
- Can I start by saying hello?
- No.
- What do I do then?
- "Today, I..."
Read the book
and write about how you feel.
How about "I read a book today?"
- That's a journal.
- Really?
"Let me tell you about how I feel."
Then what am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
Aladdin in Persia...
But Cinderella... Joon Ho.
Her shoe size is 260mm.
- You have only one shot in life.
- Only one shot in life.
Actually, Aladdin has
the same message.
"I read the book again
after a long time."
(Jae Suk starts writing
his book report first.)
"It made me think of many things."
I can't finish the sentence here.
Can I write it on the next line?
- The sentence is cut here. Then...
- Move onto the next line.
I want to say, "It was touching."
But there's no space.
Should I change it to "Touching?"
You can continue the sentence
on the next line.
"Then,"
"will I..."
This is so embarrassing.
"By any chance..."
"Someone else..."
You can't copy mine.
You have a different book.
I can say,
"It made me think of many things."
- I'll say the same thing.
- Hey.
- "It was very touching."
- My goodness.
"Pretty and nice..."
"Cinderella..."
"I should live
with an honest heart."
Should I finish this?
I'm done.
- Do you want me to read it?
- Read it for us.
(Joon Ho finishes his report first
and reads it out loud.)
"I read 'Aladdin's Wonderful Lamp',
and thought of many things."
"It made me wonder
if I ever hesitated..."
"due to other people's gaze."
What does that mean?
Hey, you copied mine.
(Hey, you copied mine.)
I read it first.
- I read it first.
- It's the same as mine.
What did you write?
"I thought of many things
after reading this book."
"It made me wonder
if I ever said..."
"what I didn't really mean
due to other people's attention."
You can't copy mine.
"It made me wonder if I hesitated
due to other people's gaze."
What does this have to do
with Aladdin?
This is for
"The Emperor's New Clothes."
It's for
- Hey.
- It's just the beginning.
"If I had a magic lamp,
what wish would I make?"
"My first wish is to become rich."
"The second is to make people laugh
on variety shows."
"The third is to make
another three wishes."
"If I keep making that wish,"
"I will be able to have
all of my wishes granted for life."
"Aladdin is so stupid."
(Aladdin is so stupid.)
(He ruins childhood innocence.)
"I should be smart."
Is that how I should
write a book report?
"You should use your brain
when you make wishes."
This is a real book report.
This is just pretense.
Why would you live
with an honest heart again?
You're right. But this is
what a book report should look like.
- My gosh.
- This is difficult.
You basically just wrote a summary.
- We're done.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for today.
(Read their special book reports
on Running Man's social media.)
The weather is nice.
It's a perfect day for hiking.
(The 1st get-together
of Running Man Alpine Club)
(The two old members
don't act their age.)
(There's a lady
on the campaign trail.)
(We're getting to know each other.
What's your name?)
(The couples
get to know each other.)
- Hey, Hyuk. Come with me.
- Hyuk?
(Jang Hyuk, 44 years old,
a new member)
(They are getting to know
each other too.)
(It didn't even take an hour
from Seoul,)
(but this place has a fine view.)
(They have fun looking around...)
(and get carried away.)
(Why do you keep taking photos?)
(She suddenly wants
to take photos with us.)
- I know.
- We should make them spend money.
(Someone's making them spend money.)
(If they don't spend money,)
(you will be eliminated.)
(The alpine club is in crisis.)
(Will they stay together
until the end?)
(The Race to Get To Know Each Other,
My Money and My Alpine Club)