(It's the last day
of the Lunar New Year holidays.)
Hello.
(There will be Running Man
Neighborhood Athletic Meet.)
Hello.
- Ha Do Kwon is here again.
- Right.
- Really?
- I saw Do Kwon...
wandering around outside.
He's dressed like a bully
not to lose again today.
He's dressed all in black.
I'm in charge of the cast.
I pick them up.
And I bring them again
if I like them.
- Cool.
- This is exciting.
How much would I suffer today?
(How much would I suffer today?)
Gosh, Do Kwon is such
a troublesome guest.
- He doesn't want to lose.
- And we don't need to ask...
how he's been doing.
We should skip it.
I'm tired of seeing Do Kwon.
- I know.
- All right.
- Do we start right away?
- It's Suk Jin.
(The prankster mode is on.)
It's begun.
He started teasing Suk Jin.
Are we shooting it already?
What? What's going on?
(Suk Jin is denied from entering.)
I can't believe this. Hey!
Hello?
You can use
the other gate, Suk Jin.
(Thanks to the prankster,
he's come a long way.)
- Good.
- Hey.
What are you doing
from the beginning?
Gosh, he fell for that anyway.
Is it that you're not strong
enough to open it?
I didn't open it on purpose.
I don't want him to get hurt.
- Who'd get hurt?
- If I pulled it, you'd get hurt.
- No, I wouldn't.
- Yes, you would.
- That's not true.
- You would if I forced it open.
You couldn't come in
because you're weak.
I'm at least stronger than you.
- It's just that you're weak.
- I'm not as weak as you.
He's weak. He's so feeble.
Hello.
- Detective, we're here.
- Kwang Soo.
You're here to find the culprit.
- Detective Lee.
- Detective Macgyver.
I just got in here.
- You shouldn't be late.
- Am I late?
- Yes, you are.
- You're late.
- Chan Hee is waiting here.
- Hello.
Chan Hee was in captions...
- of TV shows from the 1980s.
- Really?
As Cameraman Kang Chan Hee.
Really? From the 1980s?
- Did anyone of you work in the 80s?
- No.
Do you even check captions?
I saw Chan Hee's name...
- when the credits rolled.
- Why do you check the credits?
Where did you see it?
I saw his name
on "Humor, 1st Avenue".
- It's a very old show.
- "Humor, 1st Avenue"?
- My gosh.
- Do you still watch it?
I understand
you watched "Humor, 1st Avenue".
But why did you check the credits?
I should check the credits.
I tried to find Chan Hee's name,
- and it was right there.
- He must've been the youngest one.
He needs some hobbies.
- I think so.
- He has nothing to do.
- I'm enjoying my hobby in TV shows.
- What is it?
- You two.
- Is it what you're doing now?
I play tricks on you two.
That's my hobby.
- My goodness.
- Teasing Suk Jin.
I'm doing it right now.
- Hello.
- Okay.
- You're here.
They are Jong Kook and his gang.
You look taller.
Hello.
I'm wearing dress shoes today.
My goodness.
As I always say,
I rarely find a woman cheesy.
- But she's...
- Is she being cheesy again?
Gosh, So Min was like...
"Hello, Jae Suk."
(She said hello to Jae Suk...)
(and made a 180-degree turn.)
So Min is the first woman
whom I find cheesy.
- So Min, you look great today.
- Do I?
- I'm gaining weight these days.
- You look good.
I'm gaining weight too.
It's driving me crazy.
Why?
I... I...
- What's wrong?
- I've gained 4kg.
- Seriously?
- You gained a lot of weight.
Why are you being like that?
This is adorable.
- So cute.
- I'm serious.
You look cute, Haha.
Your shoulders should be broader.
But they look narrower.
They are slanting.
Your face is getting bigger.
You need some safety pins.
Your shirt would slip down.
- Be confident.
- I think we're done.
It's done.
(He's done talking.)
- I'm so into at-home exercise now.
- Really?
It's crazy.
- I can't see it though.
- Have you been working out?
My muscles are so...
My gosh. Show me your hand.
My goodness.
- What was that?
- Hey.
What is he doing?
I didn't know he'd hit me.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't do that to him.
- He's almost 60.
I'm so sorry, Suk Jin.
- Hey, don't say that.
- Hey.
- Stop it.
- He's almost 60.
- Stop saying that.
- People would believe that.
- I'm sorry.
I really mean it.
I just did it instinctively.
He's a living legend
of variety shows.
- He's 60.
- He will be 60 soon.
- We have only four years left.
- My gosh.
- We should throw him a party.
- This is crazy.
- It's really good.
- We don't usually...
see our guests in the parking lot.
But Do Kwon kept walking around...
- with his hands in his pockets.
- I know.
He tried to show that he's here.
It feels like he's our member.
Today, to celebrate
Lunar New Year's Day,
we will have 2021 Running Man
Neighborhood Athletic Meet.
And we have...
special guests
from "The Penthouse"...
who're here to participate
in the athletic meet.
Please come on in.
- It's Do Kwon.
- Who are they?
(More heroes
from "The Penthouse")
(Yoon Jong Hun,
Ha Do Kwon, Park Eun Seok)
(Yoon Jong Hun is the new icon
of sickly sexy charm.)
(He married Cheon Seo Jin
for money and power.)
(He showed the best performance
of his career playing Ha Yoon Chul.)
(He brought chaos to everyone
playing a double role.)
(Park Eun Seok played
a rustic PE teacher, Gu Ho Dong...)
(and an American
millionaire, Logan Lee.)
(An immoral music teacher
who would do anything...)
(for money and power,
Ha Do Kwon)
(You don't know your place,
and you're fearless.)
(He didn't know his place,
and he was fearless last time.)
(He got knocked out right away.)
(Do Kwon got
his shirt ripped off...)
(and suffered a humiliating defeat.)
(Then he came back with
the 3 actresses of "The Penthouse".)
(He challenged Jong Kook
face-to-face.)
(He fought
Jong Kook face-to-face...)
(and got knocked out again.)
(He was even defeated by Kwang Soo,
the assassin on the chin-up bar.)
(Do Kwon is officially
Running Man's clumsy guest.)
- Hello.
- Do Kwon.
- Hey.
You've lost weight.
Hey, Jong Hun.
Jong Hun, stand in the middle.
Nice to meet you.
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
- Hello.
(Ha Do Kwon, Park Eun Seok,
Yoon Jong Hun)
Hey, Do Kwon.
"The Penthouse" is...
the only drama I watched
in the past five years.
- What?
- I watched all the episodes.
- You watched "Sky Castle" too.
- You watched "Sky Castle".
- What about "Sky Castle"?
- Stop it.
It's been more than
five years, right?
- No.
- It hasn't been five years.
And you recently watched "Voice".
- I watched "Voice".
- You watched a lot of dramas.
You also watched
"The Uncanny Counter".
Right. He watched
- There are a lot.
- You have a lot of free time.
- Why is he lying?
- I stopped watching it.
But I watched all the episodes
of "The Penthouse".
As Suk Jin grows older,
he says more lies.
- My gosh.
- He's becoming good at it.
- He's improving a lot.
- He's still improving.
We can't talk about anything
without Suk Jin.
It seems like you're
acquainted with Ji Hyo.
How do you know each other?
- Did you do a drama together?
- Has it been about seven years?
14 years?
- It's been longer than that.
- You know what?
Those who are acquainted
with Ji Hyo look...
- They feel awkward.
- They look really awkward.
She's really cold.
It'd be better for him
to pretend not to know her.
And to be honest,
Jong Hun seems to know Ji Hyo,
but Ji Hyo doesn't seem
to remember him.
- Isn't that it?
- No. I know him.
What happened seven years ago?
When guests ask her...
about when they first met,
Ji Hyo just stands still.
It seems like
she can't hear anything.
She doesn't remember anything.
By the way,
I was surprised
to see Eun Seok's age.
Are you 38?
- Yes. We are the same age.
- He's older than me.
- Jong Hun is also older than me.
- Right.
- Eun Seok...
- Are they older than me?
They look so young.
I almost made a mistake again.
I was going to ask
how old they were.
He almost made a mistake.
He often makes mistakes.
- It's okay. Do as you please.
- I'm sorry.
Suk Jin.
Eun Seok is the one
who looks young for his age.
I didn't say
I look young for my age.
- I was being quiet.
- Don't be upset.
Suk Jin, don't sulk.
He always says...
- people think he's in his 30s.
- He only...
dresses like a young man.
Only his outfit.
- Hey.
- But inside the outfit...
- Only his outfit is young.
- I'm still fresh.
Only his outfit.
Do Kwon brought his friends today.
He's so determined to win.
Why is he determined?
- Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon...
- brought his friends who are tough.
- Do Kwon.
Are you here
to defeat Jong Kook again?
I don't want anything today.
I really don't.
- I'm here to defeat Se Chan.
- Why me?
- He's lowered his goal.
- It's a lot lower.
He brought down the goal.
He brought it down.
I won't stay still.
Do Kwon is here...
as our guest today,
- but he's like our member.
- He's like our family.
He was here with So Yeon
and other actresses last time.
Are you here as a link...
between "The Penthouse"
and our show?
I'm like your guide.
(Call me a guide.)
- Like an agency.
- It's an agency.
- This time...
- He's an agency.
He's doing this
to get some commission.
- He's dressed like an agent today.
- Right.
- I'm like their guardian.
- Okay.
Did you know that Do Kwon
isn't his real name?
- What?
- It's not his real name.
- What are you talking about?
- His real name is...
- His real name is Kim Yong Gu.
- What?
- Yong Gu?
- Yong Gu.
Yong Gu sounds a lot better.
- Yong Gu?
- Yong Gu sounds perfect.
It sounds perfect for you.
- I like the name.
- Yong Gu sounds good.
Yong Gu sounds
better than Ha Do Kwon.
- Yong Gu is better.
- I agree.
I thought...
his name didn't sound right.
Yong Gu is better.
If we went to school together,
I would've called him Young Gu.
(Disappointed)
Yong Gu.
Is your family name Kim?
- He's Kim.
- He likes it.
- And he lives in Anyang.
He likes it.
- He's like your immediate family.
- Immediate family?
- That sounds nice.
Today, to celebrate
Lunar New Year's Day,
we will have 2021 Running Man...
Athletic Meet with the athletes
from each neighborhood.
And you guys are great athletes
who represent your neighborhood.
The three athletes with the most
trophy stamps will win the prizes.
And the one
with the fewest stamps...
and a person
selected by the last...
will get a penalty.
The last gets to pick
one person again.
I should be nice to the last then.
You will be doing
missions in three teams.
And each team has...
a member of lightweight,
middleweight, and heavyweight each.
Since this is the athletic meet,
each team is named...
after the hometown
of their lightweight member.
The lightweight member?
First, the lightweight member
of Team Gyeongsang.
Song Ji Hyo, the daughter of Pohang.
(The lightweight member
of Team Gyeongsang is Ji Hyo.)
She's in Team Gyeongsang.
What's that dance?
Is she doing it right?
And...
the lightweight member
of Team Gyeonggi.
Jeon So Min, the flower of Goyang.
(The lightweight member
of Team Gyeonggi is So Min.)
She's so cheesy.
(She likes the nickname,
the flower of Goyang.)
So Min is...
After a long time...
What?
- Just say I'm pretty.
- Is she cheesy?
- I can't bring myself to say that.
- Why not?
- Isn't it what you want to say?
- He forced himself to say that.
I just can't say it.
The lightweight member
of Team Gangwon.
Ji Suk Jin, the son of Jeongseon.
Is he from Gangwon Province?
People in Jeongseon
don't know him though.
I know. He doesn't seem
like a person from Jeongseon.
His profile on a portal says
he's from Gangwon Province.
I'm the son of Jeongseon.
But people in Jeongseon
have no idea.
I think they just pretend
not to know him.
I came to Seoul when I was three.
(Lightweight, Team Gyeongsang,
Team Gyeonggi, Team Gangwon)
Now I'll name the middleweight
members of each team.
Yang Se Chan of Team Gyeongsang.
I'm from Dongducheon.
- You just belong to the team.
- Is that my team?
- You're like a mercenary.
- I'm a mercenary.
Haha of Team Gyeonggi.
Yes!
You should look at me.
Why aren't you looking at me?
- I was confused.
- You should look at me.
The next member of Team Gangwon
is Jae Suk.
I'm on Team Gangwon?
- Team Gangwon.
- Come here.
I'm from Seoul.
(Middleweight: Yang Se Chan,
Haha, Yoo Jae Suk)
Gosh, I don't like this.
Next up is Kwang Soo
on Team Gyeongsang.
(Kwang Soo is the heavyweight
player on Team Gyeongsang.)
- Do Kwon is on Team Gyeonggi.
- Team Gyeonggi?
- Jong Kook is on Team Gangwon.
- Me?
- Hey, Jong Kook!
- I'm on that team?
- It's game over.
- Jong Kook, come join us.
- My gosh.
- All right.
- Hey.
- Come with me.
- Hey, it's game over.
- We'll win.
- That team is too strong.
- It's game over.
- Yes, we'll definitely win.
- We'll definitely win.
- I'll go through a hard time.
- Who is on our team again?
- We'll win.
- On Team Gyeongsang? Gosh.
- This team?
(Heavyweight: Lee Kwang Soo
on Team Gyeongsang)
(Ha Do Kwon on Team Gyeonggi)
(Kim Jong Kook on Team Gangwon)
- Okay. That's good.
- What about them?
What about those two?
Eun Seok and Jong Hun
who do not belong...
- to any of the teams...
- What happens to them?
are hooligans whose abilities
haven't been verified...
on Running Man
and who are aiming to win.
- "Hooligans"?
- As hooligans, you two...
get to choose which team to join...
and carry out the missions
on the team of your choice.
However, the teams
with these two hooligans...
will have a disadvantage.
Regardless of the rankings,
one of the members of the team
won't get any trophy stamps.
- 1 of the team members?
- Just 1 member?
For example, Jong Hun joins
your team,
only 3 of you get stamps
while 1 of you can't get any.
- It's the same for Eun Seok.
- It's a double-edged sword.
Meanwhile, the team with no hooligan
will obtain double stamps.
- It's better without a hooligan.
- Exactly.
However, you can send the hooligan
to another team after a mission.
The hooligans can appoint
someone else as a hooligan...
and become a member of the team...
after each mission.
In short, after each mission,
the hooligans can change,
- and the team members can change.
- We may become a hooligan?
Yes, that's possible.
Now, Eun Seok and Jong Hun,
please choose a team
to join for the first mission.
Can you give us a hint
about the mission?
A hint about the mission.
It requires strength, knowledge,
and speed.
We need knowledge too?
This is an athletic meet.
- Knowledge?
- We have a chance to win.
- Listen.
- We're all airheads.
- I'm serious.
- All three of us are.
- No. We can win this.
- They have no hope.
- They're hopeless.
- How could you say that?
- But they...
They're just like you guys.
Do Kwon completes the team.
- The team became complete...
- Hey, he graduated from SNU.
- as he joined it.
- Oh, right. He went to SNU.
- He went to SNU.
- Okay.
- Jong Hun, choose your team.
Since I've met him before,
- I'll join Jae Suk's team.
- Okay!
- Hold on. You've met Ji Hyo too.
- That doesn't even count?
- He's met both of them.
- Did you two really meet?
- He's met...
both of them.
But he told us about how he met
Ji Hyo seven years ago.
- Jong Hun, welcome to my team.
- I bet it's because of Jong Kook.
- It's not like that.
- He made his own choice.
- We starred on "Busted!" as well.
- That's right.
- Come here. We worked together.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- But... Ji Hyo, you should get mad.
- No.
Eun Seok, choose your team.
Hey, it's been a long time.
Come on. All right.
(He tried to attract him
with his poor English.)
- Let's have a bowl of gukbap.
- Please join our team.
(He chose Team Gyeonggi
despite Se chan's effort.)
This is great.
- Really?
- Okay.
- All right. Bring it on.
- It's okay.
- We'll get double stamps if we win.
- It's a good thing. Double stamps.
We'll win the first game
no matter what.
Let's do some quizzes
in the first game.
Now, we'll move to
the first mission location.
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Come on.
(They'll move to the 1st mission
location!)
You're all full of energy as always.
(The 1st venue of 2021 Running
Man Neighborhood Athletic Meet)
What's that?
What are "Combat" and "Answer"?
I guess we'll do
some quizzes as well.
You think?
Do Kwon, you're not on our team.
I want to stay close
to the powerful men.
(He figured out who had power
after 3 appearances on the show.)
I heard that you've been
shooting the drama.
- "The Penthouse".
- Yes, the second season.
("'The Penthouse' Season 2
to Premiere on February 19")
You must be excited.
(To the halfhearted comment,)
Yes, I am.
(he gave a halfhearted reply.)
It must be nice to get to play
in another season without a break.
- Of course, it's nice.
- It's the best in this era.
You see, I appeared in a drama
written by Writer Kim Soon Ok too.
- You said you got a compliment too.
- You know that, right?
Of course.
- Say hello to her for me.
- In what drama?
In what drama did you appear?
"My Daughter Geum Sa Wol".
- Oh, right. I remember that.
- Yes.
I played a cameo role.
The writer complimented me
for my performance.
(He's bragging about
getting a compliment from her.)
I'm sure she complimented you
as she would never see you again.
- Hey.
- That's what people do.
Do you want me to talk about
"The Producers"?
- You want me to talk about it?
- I got a compliment too.
I stopped by there.
It's so cold.
- Suk Jin, what's wrong?
- Nothing. I was joking around.
- What did you do?
- I don't know.
I tried to tap her on the head,
but failed.
- You failed to pull a prank on her?
- I meant to tap here. Yes.
- Because I sat down?
- Yes.
You felt that a little bit, right?
- Suk Jin, your fists are so soft.
- What?
Suk Jin, why would you
act so tough?
(He's picking a fight with So Min
who's an easy target.)
He does that only to me.
He can't do it to anyone else.
(The 2 of them are equally weak.)
I'll explain the rules now.
Through the first mission,
we'll find the best person
in each weight class.
It's Quiz for Each Class.
- We'll do a quiz from the start?
- Quiz for Each Class.
(A quiz from the beginning?)
- Okay. Here go the airheads.
- Look at her face.
- Ji Hyo seems worried again.
- Oh, my.
- The airhead trio.
- Don't worry, Ji Hyo.
- Let's give it a try.
- Ji Hyo will get a lot of air time.
You will have a match against
the other teams' members...
in the same weight class as you,
and the hooligans will have a match
against each other.
- You have to solve quizzes.
- Okay.
The first person who presses
the buzzer gets to answer.
If you get it right in 5 seconds,
you win 5 points.
But if you say a wrong answer,
you lose one point.
Then we shouldn't press it
unless we're sure.
- Exactly. You may lose one point.
- We'd better not press it.
- But you may also win 5 points.
- 5 points.
If you're not sure about the answer,
press the buzzer
and when your turn comes,
you can choose "Combat".
- "Combat"?
- Yes.
After you pick up the combat picket,
as soon as another person...
picks up the combat picket,
the three players start
Name Tag Elimination.
(Once another person chooses it,
Name Tag Elimination begins.)
- Name Tag Elimination?
- It begins right away?
Yes, right away. In other words,
when 2 of the 3 players...
give up on the quiz...
- and choose "Combat",
- We can choose the game.
you'll hear the bell ringing.
Then you may begin the game.
You will win two points
for each name tag you rip off.
- For each name tag?
- Yes.
I bet there will only be combats
to the end.
- I guess...
- Combat is the only way.
we'll continue fighting
all day long.
There will be only combats
and no answers.
Ji Hyo, let's just
rip off their name tags.
Right away.
The hooligans will have a match
against each other...
- and one member of Team Gyeongsang.
- I see.
- The hooligans and one of them.
- Okay.
- The first round...
- Let's start with the lightweight.
Go, So Min!
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- Go, Suk Jin!
By the way, I got lucky
to have a match with them.
Exactly. You got so lucky.
I feel so confident. I can take off
their name tags easily.
- They might join their forces.
- Then it won't be easy.
You can work with Ji Hyo
to rip off his name tag first.
They can't do that
even if they join their forces.
- Are you sure?
- I've been working out at home.
Go, Song Jeoktoma! Pick up Combat
unless you're confident.
Put "Answer" down.
Why would you even hold it?
Ji Hyo, hold only "Combat",
not "Answer".
- Don't worry about the rules.
- Are you sure?
- They just do whatever they want.
- I see.
Oh, my. Do Kwon just told
Eun Seok...
not to worry about the rules
saying we do whatever we want.
- Do Kwon, we do have rules.
- We follow the rules.
- You crossed the line.
- We have our own rules.
I believed what he said
without a doubt. "Oh, I see."
(The cast members of Running Man
do follow the rules.)
- Here's your first question.
- Okay.
The first question is
regarding sports.
- That's nice.
- Oh, no.
- This is perfect for us to win.
- This is good for us.
- Good.
- I should be there instead of him.
(He seems confident.)
Oh, no. I know nothing about sports.
We're allowed to tell her
the answer, right?
No. We're not allowed to do that.
- We shouldn't tell her?
- Of course, we shouldn't.
- He's acting like he knows all.
- Why?
He said, "We can just
tell her the answer."
What kind of rule is that?
- You can't tell her the answer.
- Of course, you can't.
I was saying that we're not
allowed to do it.
If you tell your team member
the answer, your team loses a point.
Of course, it's not allowed.
Worry about yourself, will you?
Here goes the first question.
- In basketball,
- Basketball?
what is the best bench player
called?
You don't know the answer?
- If you don't know this...
- Gosh. How...
Press the buzzer
if you know the answer.
- A sixth man.
- Oh, right.
(The answer is "sixth man".)
(She has never heard of it.)
Press the buzzer
if you know the answer.
- Pick up "Answer".
- Go ahead.
- An ace.
- Gosh.
You lost one point.
Is there a points deduction too?
- Why don't they know this?
- Yes.
- Oh, right.
- Go ahead.
- A bench ace.
- Gosh.
You lost one point.
In basketball?
(In that case...)
An ace bench.
"Ace bench"?
(No one has ever heard
the expression "ace bench".)
- "Ace bench"?
- Ji Hyo.
This is frustrating.
(So Min raised "Combat"!)
So Min raised "Combat".
If one of them chooses it too...
(If 1 more person chooses it, they
can start Name Tag Elimination.)
(If 2 of the 3 raise "Combat",
Name Tag Elimination begins.)
If one of them chooses it too...
(Ji Hyo chose to combat.)
(Name Tag Elimination begins.)
(What? Wait.)
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- Rip it off!
Ji Hyo, don't let her rip it off.
(Screaming)
(Because of
the unexpectedly exciting fight,)
(some people in the audience
are about to faint.)
You should be the one to rip it off!
- They're so scary.
- Don't let her do that!
You should be the one to rip it off!
- Gosh, no.
(Both ripped his name tag off.)
(Ji Hyo ripped it off
before So Min did!)
- That doesn't count.
- What's this?
- You two should keep fighting.
- We won two points!
- It's not over yet.
- Ji Hyo.
- Why do I have two name tags?
- Rip So Min's off too.
- Rip So Min's name tag off now.
- Rip it off!
- It's "sixth man".
- Oh, is that the answer?
- It's not over yet.
- Ji Hyo.
Rip So Min's name tag off.
- Should I...
- Rip her name tag off.
- You can do this!
- We'll win four points.
(It's a match
between Ji Hyo and So Min!)
(Precious Sisters haven't had
a match in a long time.)
Go, So Min!
(Ji Hyo will win 4 points if she
rips So Min's name tag off too.)
You can do this, So Min!
Hey, what's the matter? So Min!
- Hey, So Min!
- Ji Hyo, let's go!
(While they were waiting for
a chance, So Min attacked first!)
- Put them under the armpits.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
I said, put them under the armpits.
Song Jeoktoma, show us
what you can do!
(It's becoming even more exciting
after Suk Jin got eliminated.)
(He got eliminated a while ago.)
Gosh. They're unbelievable.
Push her hands away first.
Rip it off no matter what.
That's good!
(Ji Hyo grabbed
So Min's name tag first!)
(But So Min grabbed Ji Hyo's
shortly after that.)
(They're grabbing
each other's name tag!)
(Who will be the winner
of the match?)
(Ji Hyo wins.)
- That's good.
- Oh, my.
- Nice, four points.
- When did you rip that off?
(That was so close.)
- Team Gyeongsang won four points.
- Song Jeoktoma is the best!
(Team Gyeongsang gained 4 points
as Ji Hyo won.)
- She's so good at this.
- She practically played with her.
So Min, when can I see you
defeat her?
At least once before I die.
The answer was sixth man.
It was easy.
- Did you know the answer?
- That doesn't matter.
- Everyone in the world knows it.
- I didn't know.
- Why didn't you know sixth man?
You should get the right answer.
Or else, you can't win.
Earn your keep, will you?
All right. I heard you.
Seriously, I was... Hey!
I declare hard on you.
"I declare hard on you"?
(I declare hard on you?)
What was that?
- You mean, you declare war on her.
- What does that even mean?
- I'll explain what he meant.
- Hey, I will...
It's when a person who went through
hard times declares war...
- on someone else.
- Exactly.
- Correct.
- That's what it means.
So Min, I won't go easy on you
anymore.
Suk Jin, please don't
go easy on me.
Here goes your second question.
This is used as an indicator of...
- a country's standard of living...
- Let me answer.
Go ahead.
(Suk Jin pressed the buzzer
even before the question ended.)
- Engel's coefficient.
- Good.
It's called Engel's coefficient.
(It's called Engel's coefficient.)
(That wasn't the question.)
Don't be flippant!
- Don't be a know-it-all.
- What was that?
- That wasn't the question.
- You didn't know.
- Why were you being so flippant?
- It wasn't like that.
- Gosh. Don't be so flippant.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Why were you being so flippant?
It wasn't the answer?
Don't be so arrogant.
Don't be a know-it-all.
- I can't believe him.
- I thought I got it right.
Okay. Continue.
Only So Min and Ji Hyo get to
press the buzzer now.
Why would you do that?
Engel's coefficient is...
the proportion of this...
to the total expenditure.
- Let me answer.
- They get to do it first.
You don't have a chance now.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Gosh.
What is this?
I'm so frustrated. Gosh.
(Frustrated)
"The cost of something"?
They said it's GOP.
Or is it GDP? GDP?
Ji Hyo, the answer is GDP.
- GOP or GDP.
- It's GDP.
Trust me.
So it's what people spend
the most money on...
It's the cost of something.
(The answer is
the cost of something.)
- "A cost"?
- Yes. The cost of something.
It's an English word, right?
Isn't it an abbreviation?
I mean, the first letters...
- It's the cost of something.
- "The cost of something"?
Oh, this is...
So Min, it's what you think is
the most important thing in life.
- The largest proportion...
- Go ahead.
The cost of love.
(The cost of love?)
- What?
- All you care about is love?
- He said it's my favorite thing.
- I can answer now, right?
- My favorite thing...
- Ji Hyo...
Challenge them to combat.
You can choose combat
if you don't know the answer.
- Choose combat.
- Five.
(Song Jeoktoma chose combat.)
(So Min chose combat too.)
(The combat begins!)
(Suk Jin is targeting only So Min.)
Come here.
Wait. Wait a second.
Ji Hyo, wait there.
Suk Jin, why are you
targeting So Min?
Ji Hyo, help her
rip his name tag off.
- Wait there.
- Ji Hyo.
- Rip it off.
- Wait.
- Ji Hyo, help her out.
- Just wait there.
- Wait over there, Ji Hyo.
- But...
- That's ridiculous.
- Why should I?
That's ridiculous.
He's on my team, but I must say,
he's playing so dirty.
You stay here.
Wait just for a while.
- Look at him.
- Wait over there.
- He's playing dirty.
- Ji Hyo, hold him.
- Okay. Let's take a break.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Ji Hyo, I'll give you my name tag.
- Okay.
- You'll give her yours?
- Yes. Ji Hyo, I'll give you mine.
He gets intimidated by Ji Hyo.
He's doing his best right now.
He's not pretending.
(Ji Hyo is still too intimidating
for Ji-rasoni.)
(He's trying to attack So Min,
the easiest target, again.)
He just hit me. He hit me.
- No!
- He's serious about this.
- He seems so enthusiastic.
- Suk Jin is serious about this.
Suk Jin is serious.
Suk Jin is actually trying to win.
His face turned red too.
He's attacking her
with all his might.
- Suk Jin seems so serious.
- My gosh.
I've never seen him
that enthusiastic before.
(He's trying his best
to take So Min's name tag off.)
Ji Hyo seems so relaxed.
Suk Jin's top ripped.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
He gave up.
- Ji Hyo, start attacking her now.
- Attack her.
Wait. Give me a second.
So Min, don't waste your energy.
Let's get more points.
- This is so funny.
- Give it a try.
- My, she's so good at this.
- This won't work.
Give it a try. Why?
- This is your chance, Ji Hyo.
- Go and attack her.
So Min, you should put on your mic.
There's nothing to record anyway.
I'll only scream, don't you think?
(There's nothing to record anyway.
I'll only scream, don't you think?)
(The sound engineer says,
"That's true.")
That's true.
Rip her name tag off!
- Rip one more name tag off, So Min.
- You can do this.
So Min, give it a try.
- She's so scary.
- Oh, gosh.
Let's do a common knowledge quiz.
- Let's do a quiz instead.
- Ji Hyo, you should get mad.
Ji Hyo, don't listen to her.
- You have no common knowledge.
- She's looking down on you.
- Common knowledge, my foot.
- Song Jeoktoma, come on.
(Song Jeoktoma got angry
when she heard "common knowledge".)
She's angry. Ji Hyo got mad.
She got upset
because So Min suggested a quiz.
(How dare you talk about
common knowledge in front of me?)
- It's the word Ji Hyo hates most.
- Rip it off!
- That word is taboo on Running Man.
- Help me.
Help me. Can anyone help me?
(Ripping)
Nice! That was funny.
- Good job.
- It wasn't easy.
- It was so intense.
- Ji Hyo won all the points.
It was a quiz, but you guys didn't
get any questions right, did you?
Next up is the middleweight class.
- It's my turn?
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
- I'm sure the others will...
- You should be quick.
- They'll choose combat.
- You should get the answer quickly.
- I should press the buzzer quickly.
Oh, man. Jae Suk is
in the middleweight class too.
(Jae Suk is the best at quizzes
while the others are the worst.)
When you hear the bell ringing,
run to Haha no matter what.
- Got it.
- Se Chan.
- You know, right?
- What do you mean?
If I raise Combat...
- Oh, okay.
- We'll fight together, okay?
- I can get the right answer first.
- Of course.
- Right.
- You can just get it right.
I can get it right.
The first question is regarding
current affairs.
- We're in trouble.
- Raise Combat.
This is a Danish word
that means "coziness".
- A Danish word?
- Go ahead.
(He didn't even hear the question
to the end.)
Hygge.
(Correct)
(He got the right answer quickly
and won 5 points!)
- Hygge!
Hygge!
(Hygge is a Danish word that means
warmth and coziness.)
- Hygge!
- Hold on. Jae Suk.
- I got it right. Okay.
- Hey.
I said "Engel's coefficient"
just like he said the answer.
But it wasn't the correct answer.
- Did he say the correct answer?
- Hygge.
You should've let us say
some wrong answers that are funny...
like "hyvaa" or "hwitturu matturu".
Why did you answer it right away?
- You should've given us a chance...
- I think...
he's been studying at a library.
- "Hygge" is not a word!
- Exactly.
It's either "hyvaa"
or "hwitturu matturu".
- I promise...
- This is ridiculous.
I'll end this before you get
a chance to raise Combat.
That was like a real quiz.
(It was like a real quiz
for a change.)
I should get
the right answer quickly.
Hey, Haha.
Don't even think you might know it.
Put Combat in front of you.
- We have no chance.
- Let's give it a try.
- It might be an easy one.
- Now...
Wait. Hold on a second.
I just saw Kwang Soo taking this
out of Se Chan's bag.
Are we allowed to steal
others' stamps?
- I swear...
- Hey, hey, hey.
I tried to steal his stamps,
but there aren't any in here.
Gosh, seriously.
- I found no stamps here.
- Right.
- I knew it, so I put them here.
- Put it back in his bag.
- You call this a team?
- I put them in my pocket.
- He's incredible.
- Don't try to steal mine.
It already began.
Make sure to keep your bag safe.
- They're so sly.
- They might steal yours.
- Give me my bag over there.
- I didn't think...
I didn't know you could steal them.
I bet Suk Jin will try it.
- I never even imagined.
- You can't do that.
This is an unusual
consumption pattern...
during economic recessions.
Hey, raise it now. Hurry.
- Go ahead.
- You should get the right answer.
- Revenge spending.
- Wait. Jae Suk.
(What is the increase in consumption
of affordable luxuries called?)
(Could he get the correct answer...)
(so quickly that the others don't
get to raise Combat once again?)
- He was wrong.
- What did you say?
- I'll hear the question to the end.
- I'll hear the rest.
Give us some time.
This is an unusual consumption
pattern during recessions.
What is the increase
in consumption...
of affordable luxuries called?
- C brand effect.
- "Affordable..."
- An effect?
- C brand effect.
Kwang Soo said "C brand effect".
Cheap stuff effect.
(Cheap stuff effect)
(The empty-headed duo frustrates
everyone just like a traffic jam.)
It might be similar to the answer.
- "Cheap stuff effect"?
- What was it called?
Okay!
Buy-1-get-1-free effect.
(Buy-1-get-1-free effect)
(Buy 1 Empty Head and get 1 free.)
- It's funny because he's serious.
- You're laughing?
- How dare you laugh?
- Does Jae Suk know the answer?
- That was a good one.
- You don't know either?
It sounded like a correct answer.
The only effect I can think of is
a placebo effect.
And a butterfly effect.
You know, Ji Hyo said...
I expected something like
a placebo effect.
Do you know what she said?
She said, "saving pennies effect".
(Do you know what she said?
She said, "saving pennies effect".)
- My gosh.
- I couldn't play along with it.
(This is the class
of the queen of airheads.)
- "Saving pennies effect".
- Yes, that's what I said.
- All right.
- Raise Combat. Why won't you?
Go ahead.
(Se Chan raised Combat.)
- Press it. What are you doing?
- It's a combat.
- Let's attack Jae Suk first.
(Unlike Suk Jin, Jae Suk quickly
gets ready for the combat.)
- Let's attack Jae Suk.
- Go for it.
- Haha, you have a chance.
- I'll hold him.
Hold him.
- Okay. Good.
- He'll lose shortly.
Rip it off.
They did it.
- They're fighting with each other.
- What a shame.
- Go, Haha!
- That won't work.
- Move fast.
- Oh, my. This is exciting.
Haha won't let him win.
Go, Mr. Dirty Mustache!
- You can do it!
- Their pride is on the line.
(They have pride when it comes to
Name Tag Elimination.)
- Good! Grab it!
- Oh, wow.
One has 11 years of experience
and the other has 4.
You can do it! All right!
One has 11 years of experience
and the other has 4.
(The man with 11 years of experience
slapped him in the face.)
(Ripping)
(He won with his experience
as a dirty player.)
- All right!
- He...
- He slapped me in the face.
- Haha wins!
- Haha, you're so cool.
- Good job.
He suddenly looks much younger.
- 11 years of experience!
- Haha, that was so cool.
- You were so nimble.
- I knew it.
He slapped me in the face.
- Isn't it the same thing?
- What is the correct answer?
- The lipstick effect.
- Oh, that. I know that term.
(A situation where people buy more
small luxuries during recessions)
- I've heard of it.
- Oh, the lipstick effect?
- Oh, that was the answer?
- It disappears like lipstick.
(Both of them must not know
what it means.)
It disappears when you use it up.
Isn't it because people try to
buy lipstick for less?
Kwang Soo, you seem so upset.
- I wasn't so sure about it.
- Right?
It's now time for
the hooligan match.
- One of you will play again.
- Go, Eun Seok.
- Kwang Soo's joining the game.
- Kwang Soo?
- The category is sports.
- Nice.
- All right.
- That's a good one.
After originating from Scotland,
curling went on to being...
an official event
in the winter Olympics.
What are curling stones made out of?
Marble.
(The answer is marble.)
(Spoken like the main member
of the Airhead Squad.)
That's what it looks like though.
- What stone is it made out of?
- Request a combat.
Think of what it can be.
- Yes?
- Cement.
- That's not it.
- My gosh.
That's not it!
Are you okay?
Cement. Seriously?
- I can't believe it.
- Can cement be this smooth?
Name one that no one would think of.
- Name any stone you know.
- Bricks.
- Should I?
- Yes.
- Basalt.
- What...
But basalt has holes in them!
How can it be used to play curling?
Jong Hun, please.
Didn't you think it through?
Basalt has holes in them.
It's a three-syllable word, right?
It's very well-known.
It's obvious.
Granite.
See what I mean?
- Granite!
- That's what I said.
The well-known rock.
- I don't know the names of rocks.
- Unbelievable.
- Okay!
They don't seem to be knowledgeable.
Neither of them is
on the clever side.
Kwang Soo has found confidence.
British economist
William Henry Beveridge...
Beverly Hills?
He published a report regarding
issues of social welfare.
In this report,
he named society's five giant evils.
Name one of them.
A giant evil? Isn't it Kwang Soo?
- The 5 giant evils of society.
- 5 giant evils.
Jong Hun, just say anything.
- Just say what comes to mind.
- Whatever sounds evil.
Extravagance.
(Extravagance is incorrect.)
Desire.
No, something else.
Robbery.
What is it?
A giant evil of society?
Betrayal.
(They keep losing points
for giving wrong answers.)
Kwang Soo...
Wouldn't it be better
to just request a combat?
If you think about it...
Please press the buzzer.
Eun Seok requested a combat.
Kwang Soo has the upper hand here.
Yes, that's why
you should attack him first.
Right, take out Kwang Soo first.
Take him out first.
- He's already getting ready.
- Look.
He's getting ready.
Why are you taking off
your shoes though?
Wait!
- I don't trust him.
- I'll take it instead.
- I don't trust you either.
- Let me take it.
- But I didn't do anything.
- A combat.
- Hey!
- Hold on.
- Team up first.
- You two should team up.
- Take out Kwang Soo first.
- Eliminate Kwang Soo first.
- Right.
Take out Kwang Soo first.
Take off your satchels.
No, wait!
Hold on a second.
(Eun Seok runs forward
to get his satchel back.)
No, wait!
Don't let him!
(Don't let Kwang Soo
rip off your name tag!)
(The penthouse residents
aren't seeing straight.)
Rip his name tag off.
Hold on!
(He loses his vest
in a matter of seconds.)
Rip his name tag off. Hold on.
Get his name tag!
- Rip his name tag off.
- Wait.
Get his name tag first.
(Kwang Soo sees red
after being humiliated.)
Rip it off.
- Get it.
- Good job.
He ripped off his own name tag!
(Kwang Soo ripped
a name tag off but...)
It's his.
(It was his own name tag!)
Jong Hun, good job.
Jong Hun, nicely done.
Why did you rip yours off?
Why would you
rip off your own name tag?
Get Jong Hun's next!
Jong Hun, be careful.
- Jong Hun!
- Get Eun Seok's name tag.
(Jong Hun and Eun Seok
go head to head.)
Hold on.
I need my satchel back though.
- It's all right.
- I got it.
Nice!
(Eun Seok scores 2 points for
ripping Jong Hun's name tag off.)
Jong Hun, are you kidding me?
To keep things fair,
Kwang Soo will have
two points deducted...
- since he ripped his own name tag.
- Right.
Jong Hun gets 0 points
while Eun Seok gets 2.
- Nice!
- Okay, good.
I was only trying to steal it back.
Let me tell you what the answer is.
The answer is this.
- Want.
- Disease.
Ignorance.
- Ignorance?
- Is that a giant evil?
- There's a great evil right here.
I'm a great evil?
Being ignorant
makes him a great evil.
Squalor and idleness.
- Idleness.
Right, of course.
They are words we all know.
- One should never be idle.
- Idleness.
They are words we know.
Here's the next question.
What is the word...
that explains a government
failing to pay back...
all or some of the loan...
it took out from other nations
within a designated time limit?
- Don't you know this?
- Are you saying you do?
Right, go ahead.
IMF!
IMF. Oh, that's not it.
That's what I thought it was.
You got it wrong just as he did.
That's what popped into my head too.
- IMF?
- International Monetary Fund.
International Monetary Fund.
Still, it shows...
that you picked up a few things.
International Monetary Fund.
This...
- Does this call for another combat?
- The government can't repay a debt.
- It's an English word.
- What?
- An English word?
There's no way you can get
this right. Request a combat.
You'll never get this right.
- Right.
- You know...
(Can the New Yorker save face?)
Taxation.
(Taxation is incorrect.)
- What's that?
- What's taxation?
- The levying of the tax.
- Oh, tax.
The levying of additional tax.
Like tax-free?
Tax-free?
Can you believe it?
- Tax-free...
- That's the exemption of tax.
- I see.
- Jong Hun.
- Gosh.
- I don't remember.
- Stop repenting.
Jong Hun, if you don't know
the answer, request a combat.
It's okay not to know.
- Of course.
- This...
- It's okay.
- Who would know this anyway?
- He stands no chance in a combat.
- Request a combat.
You worked out, didn't you?
You look the same as
Jae Suk and Suk Jin from behind.
The silhouette from behind
is the same.
Jong Hun, come on!
It starts with a D
and ends with a T.
He gave you everything.
- Descent.
- Figure out the middle letters.
- Shouldn't Logan Lee know this?
- De-fact.
- No.
- What on earth?
I'm now doubting Logan Lee.
Are you sure your name is Logan?
You've been losing points, you know.
- We've been losing points.
- It's all right.
- Have I been losing points?
- Yes.
It's only one point anyway,
He got the F right.
F. He got the F right.
- De-fant.
- No way!
- Jong Hun.
- Come on!
- Just say something.
- He got the F right.
- D, F, and T.
- Just throw about any word.
No, don't.
- Just request a combat.
- Combat!
Let's wrestle it out.
You've got to be kidding me.
A combat is on.
They were so close.
It's a combat.
My name tag
was already ripped off once.
That doesn't mean
you can skip this round out.
We're from Team Penthouse, so...
Due to his long arms,
you'll lose in a 1-on-1 match
with Kwang Soo.
- Right, you'll lose.
- Eliminate him first.
- Eliminate him together.
- Take him out first.
This is fun to watch.
Logan, get in there!
Shouldn't you eliminate Logan first?
Jong Hun, join in!
(Kwang Soo goes wild.)
- Go for it!
- Grab him!
Jong Hun!
(Eun Seok takes off his sweater
to play defense.)
Yes, you've got it.
- Nice!
- Good job.
(Jong Hun joins in
and eliminates Kwang Soo!)
Are you allowed
to take off your clothes?
You held out well.
Are you allowed
to take off your clothes?
You held out well.
Are you allowed
to take off your clothes?
(The dirty player from New York)
He took off his sweater!
- Put on your sweater first.
- Go ahead and get dressed.
How can one play this game
if he takes off his sweater?
- You're the one who took it off.
- Move!
- But...
- Get out of the frame.
- I would've just gone naked!
- Move.
Let us keep filming.
He said he'd go naked
if that was allowed.
(The loser was forced
out of the ring.)
- Goodness.
- They go head to head.
It's Eun Seok versus Jong Hun.
Jong Hun, that's good.
(Only the two
penthouse residents remain.)
(Even in the drama series,
they went head to head.)
(Who will win
the Name Tag Elimination?)
("Don't be mistaken.
I'm done getting trampled on.")
(The betrayal fuels
Jong Hun's revenge.)
("Don't you dare!")
("You'll get a taste
of your own medicine!")
(The dirty player from New York
goes for the win.)
Rip his name tag off!
(Immersed)
Rip his name tag off.
(Neither are backing off.)
- Is this a fight scene?
- I got it.
It's like a fight scene.
- They're practicing a fight scene.
- That's right.
What is that?
(Logan Lee wins!)
It wouldn't come off.
It's all right.
Jong Hun, it's fine.
You at least got one.
(You gave it your all!)
Nice.
(Their battle will continue in
the 2nd season of "The Penthouse".)
Lastly, the heavyweight class
will compete.
- Are you all right?
- You did great.
The heavyweight class will compete.
Still...
- We've got this.
- The heavyweight class.
Go, Kim Yong Gu!
- Good luck!
- Do Kwon's up.
I didn't have to go this far.
- It won't be easy.
- We're relying on you.
- Okay, don't worry.
- We're reassured.
- The heavyweight class.
It's the heavyweight class.
Go, Kim Yong Gu.
(He was humiliated in the past...)
(from having his clothes ripped
and getting kicked in the stomach.)
Let's just answer the quiz.
- Go, Kim Yong Gu!
- All right.
Good luck.
(He gets ready for the game.)
Hold on a second.
Who did this?
(Who did this?)
- It wasn't me.
- Hold on.
- Let me see.
- It really wasn't me, Eun Seok.
I wouldn't do that to you.
- What is it?
- Are they missing?
They're all gone!
Please refrain from stealing.
Eun Seok's entire batch is missing.
- Whose batch?
- Eun Seok's.
Eun Seok, here it is.
How could you accuse me of stealing?
- It's right here.
- It's here.
- I'm sorry about this.
- Hold on a second.
Why were you over on our side?
- Wait.
- Why were you over here?
Why were you wandering around me?
- Wait.
- I felt your presence, but...
- It's a misunderstanding.
- I didn't want to believe it.
Eun Seok, it's upsetting, you know.
It was as if a fly
was flying around me.
It's a misunderstanding!
Being a rich boy in the show
doesn't mean you can...
Wait. Someone...
But they're really not here!
Gosh, who took them?
- Gosh, who took them?
- What?
(Clean)
- Who took them?
- Really?
(Who took them?)
Who was it?
- You. Give them back.
- It's not me.
- Hey.
I played the game with him.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I played the game with him.
- Who took them?
- It's not me.
- It's Jeon So Min. I can tell.
- It's really not me.
- Hold on.
- It's really not me!
- We need to...
- I'm sure she took them!
I think we need to check
everyone's bag.
- It's So Min for sure.
- It's not me.
- I can tell from her look.
- They're really not here.
I think it's you, So Min.
- No, it's not me.
- But her face says she took them.
- It's really not me. Look.
- So Min.
They told you to give them back.
Give them back to him, So Min.
Haha, give them back.
- Is it you?
- Give them back.
- It's not me!
- Give them to me right now.
- Give them to me.
- Jae Suk.
- It's not me.
- Let me check just once.
Eun Seok, it's him.
- Haha took them.
- I'm disappointed by him.
I was looking for his stamps,
and he came up to me,
saying, "Give them back."
- Eun Seok. It's him.
- I'm suspicious of everyone.
It'll be embarrassing,
so just put them back later, okay?
- Okay, when everyone's not looking.
- It's really not me.
- Put it there.
- I swear, it's not me.
- They can put them back.
- It'll be embarrassing.
Just put them back later.
It's here. Put them back
whenever you can.
You know, children love our show.
We can't be stealing anymore.
This is driving me crazy.
You guys are so mean.
- Put it there.
- They'll put them back.
- Okay, okay.
- They'll put them back for you.
Let's start now.
Let's go!
(Sighing)
Do Kwon, you can relax.
- No, I'm not...
- Take it easy, Do Kwon.
Do Kwon, are you here
to get Jong Kook?
No, I'm not.
I'm not after anyone today.
What do you call a person...
who guides the visitors
in a museum or an art gallery...
- Curator.
- That's right.
- That's correct.
- That's the answer.
- It's slightly different.
- It's wrong?
Curatration.
(Wrong)
- I'll hear out the question.
- It's clearly wrong.
What do you call a person
who guides the visitors...
in a museum or an art gallery
with knowledge about...
the exhibition? It's a person
who leads guided tours.
No, that's not it.
There's another term for it.
- Another term?
- It's not curator?
There's another term for it.
That's right.
It starts with a D.
- D?
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, give it a go.
A DJ.
Are you kidding me?
I know it's not a DJ.
I'm actually offended.
It's DJ.
Five,
four,
- three,
- I knew the term.
- two...
- I think I know what it is.
Combat. He requested combat.
- He pressed the buzzer.
- Let's go, Do Kwon!
(Name tag elimination starts.)
You need to stick with Kwang Soo.
- Jong Kook...
- Don't trust Kwang Soo.
He'll try to win two points.
- Get those two points, Kwang Soo.
- Don't ever trust Kwang Soo.
They've ripped off my name tag
before, so I don't trust anyone.
- It really is a heavyweight.
- Do Kwon looks small.
(Swift)
He's good.
- He's in trouble.
- Will the members join forces?
- Will they fight against the guest?
- You're wearing knee pads!
- Are you Lee Duke Jean?
- Gosh, I'm not!
Are you Lee Duke Jean?
(Lee Duke Jean's fan appears
in a pressing situation.)
You flustered me.
- It's not him?
- Lee Duke Jean.
He really looks like Lee Duke Jean.
What are you doing?
- Look, he's doing steps.
- Yong Gu!
- Yong Gu.
- Why does Do Kwon look so slow?
(Frivolous)
- You said you're not after him.
- Kim Yong Gu!
- Yong Gu!
(Swift)
(Yong Gu's steps are pretty swift.)
- He's pretty fast.
- Don't get caught.
Follow, follow me.
(Suddenly hitting the brakes)
- What are you doing?
- Don't get caught.
(His steps get messed up
while trying to look swift.)
(The assassin kicks his knee first.)
- Why are you doing this to me?
- What's wrong with him?
What are you doing?
(He got eliminated after
showing his dance moves.)
He's eliminated.
(I've only waited for this day.)
(He's dumbfounded.)
(Now it's a one-on-one match
between Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.)
Go easy on him.
- Kwang Soo is all serious.
- We must watch this.
(We must watch this!)
- Kwang Soo is all serious.
- We must watch this.
(Ripping)
Impressive, Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo ripped off
Jong Kook's name tag!)
(Amazing)
Why did you do that?
I cared too much
about his hair. Okay.
Jong Kook!
Gosh, this is frustrating.
- It's okay.
- I fell down.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm never cutting my mullet.
He kept letting me go
when he grabbed my mullet.
Nice one.
- Okay. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- Just get the questions right.
- Okay, okay. I got it.
- It's okay.
- Get the questions.
- This is worth only two points.
- Okay.
- Get the questions right.
- Kwang Soo, let's do this.
(They're about to restart the game.)
- You have to stop Jong Kook.
- We don't know yet, right?
- I got the stamps back.
- You did?
- She's the one who took them.
- You got them back?
- They're back.
- They are?
(His 5 stamps are back
without him knowing.)
You really are amazing.
Haha, when did you put them back?
- Kwang Soo is acting...
- It's really not me.
- It's giving me chills.
- You're amazing.
(The suspects are impressed
by each other.)
- That's amazing!
- You're the best.
(He yells out "That's amazing"
to divert attention.)
(Then he stealthily opens
Eun Seok's stamp book.)
(Putting back the stamps)
You really are amazing.
(He follows the rule
and puts back what he stole.)
- It's giving me chills.
- You're amazing.
Eun Seok is a bit clumsy too.
Actually, he's very clumsy.
We have the result.
(Announcing the final rankings)
In last place is Team Gyeonggi
with two points.
Team Gyeonggi got two points.
- Why are we in last place?
- Did they...
- We're in last place?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- You had a lot of wrong answers.
- Wrong answers?
- Gosh, seriously.
(Eun Seok answered wrong
the most.)
- We actually have a shot.
- We do.
If we're in first place,
we can get double the amount, right?
The difference in score
is just two points.
(They're only 2 points apart.)
The 2 teams won
10 points and 8 points respectively.
The team that won 10 points...
(Which team will win 1st place
and take 10 stamps each?)
Team Gangwon.
- is Team Gangwon.
- Yes!
(Team Gangwon won.)
- Okay, we did it.
- We did it.
What a relief.
- We did well.
- Only if we didn't get two wrong.
The team in 1st place
gets 10 stamps each.
The team in 2nd place gets 7,
and the team in 3rd place gets 5.
- And?
- Since this team gets double,
- they get 14 stamps.
- Okay!
(Team Gyeongsang gets 14 stamps
as they don't have hooligans.)
That's right.
Because there's no hooligan
on their team.
Then one of us can't get the stamps.
That's right, one of you can't.
- We can't?
- No.
Let's draw lots first.
Let's start with Team Gangwon.
Having a hooligan
is a big disadvantage.
- Pick one.
- Okay.
- Shall I pick first?
- Please, please!
- Do I pick one?
- I'm really unlucky.
I always become it.
(Only 1 of them will get a dud.)
- What's the mark?
- Is it the one with a mark?
(Sighing)
I saw his even before checking mine.
- My gosh.
- It's an O?
How did he...
It's you.
Jae Suk won't bet getting
any stamps.
The next team.
- You're not getting any stamps?
- Well done, Jae Suk.
We won thanks to you.
Well done.
(Team Gyeonggi starts drawing.)
I think Eun Seok got it. Did he not?
Is it you, Do Kwon?
- Nothing is working out today.
- Yes!
- That's great.
- My gosh.
I don't think I'm cut out
for Running Man.
Today is total chaos.
Seriously...
It's not easy to be this unlucky.
We get 10 each.
Nice.
Everyone, it's time to kick out
the hooligans.
Oh, the hooligans.
The teams with hooligans,
Eun Seok and Jong Hun,
can decide to kick out, keep,
or switch them.
It will be between the hooligan
and the rest of the team.
Write down the number of stamps
with someone's name in secret.
And the hooligan will write down
the number he can afford.
And when they lay the cards...
If the numbers are the same,
the hooligan will remain
on the team.
If the hooligan's number
is bigger than the members',
then the hooligan can appoint
one of the members as a hooligan...
and send them away
to the other team.
Oh, we can change the hooligan.
But if the hooligan's number
is smaller,
(Rules of play)
they'll leave the team for good.
It sounds complicated.
- We need to make the number big.
- We need to use a lot of stamps.
Oh, do the hooligans leave the team
for good?
The other hooligans
could join the team.
So if you want to kick out
the hooligan, use a lot of stamps.
If the hooligan doesn't want to
be one, use a lot of stamps.
- Is there a maximum number?
- There isn't.
- Do we get the stamps back later?
- No, you don't. They'll be gone.
It's nice to double the numbers.
This is quite difficult though.
(To which team will the hooligans
be sent to?)
Are you all done
writing down the numbers?
Okay, okay.
Team Gyeonggi will go first.
The stamp owner
will reveal the numbers.
I lost at rock-paper-scissors,
so we're using my stickers.
- How many are you spending?
- I got none.
Five stamps.
- You must use the five stamps.
- Okay.
(If Eun Seok wrote more than 5,
he'll remain on the team,)
(and the new hooligan
will be kicked out.)
Next, Eun Seok. Please reveal yours.
What did you write down?
I only have five.
- He wrote five!
- It's a tie.
- Then he'll remain on the team.
- He's staying!
(As they bet the same amount,
Eun Seok remains on the team.)
They'll have to
give back the stamps.
Give us back the stamps.
- He's staying?
- We can't kick him out?
Okay!
(It's the best outcome
for the other teams.)
Then this is... We're only using
all of our stamps?
- You should've bet more stamps.
- You're staying!
I can't believe they got a tie.
- They actually got a tie.
- Next.
- Suk Jin.
- Can I change the number?
- No.
- I can't?
- The number isn't that big though.
- Let me tell you this first.
No one on our team
is of high caliber.
That means they're all timid.
- We are all just...
- That's not true.
- We read the others first.
- We only bet moderate amounts.
- That's right. Only moderately.
- We don't go big.
We're not that ambitious.
No, we're not.
That's the biggest we can bet.
(The highest number they can
bet is 3.)
Oh, it's yours.
You're betting three stamps?
Next is Jong Hun.
- I don't think he wrote any.
- You can turn the tables later.
- You can turn the game around.
- You didn't write anything, right?
- No, no.
- He must've bet a lot.
You didn't write anything, right?
(If he bet less than 2, he'll be
kicked out to Team Gyeongsang.)
- He must've bet a lot.
- How many did you bet?
(How many did Jong Hun bet?)
- He must've bet a lot.
- How many did you bet?
- I bet five.
- He must've bet a lot.
(He bet 5 stamps.)
(As the hooligan's number is bigger,
they'll pick a new hooligan.)
- Now, Jong Hun...
- He's not the hooligan anymore?
will pick one of them as a hooligan,
and he will move to the other team.
The newly picked one
will join our team?
Yes, because there's only
three people on your team.
I'm staying on this team?
Yes, you'll remain
as an ordinary player.
So you're no longer a hooligan.
Then this team
will be free of hooligans.
But you can become one
and get kicked out.
That's... No, that's not true.
I'm sure that won't happen.
- So who's leaving?
- You are leaving, Suk Jin.
No... Don't be like that.
So who's leaving?
(You should leave, Suk Jin.)
(Don't be like that.)
(Hooligan Jong Hun picks Suk Jin.)
- But why?
- We'll accept him!
Please think it over just once.
- Well done, Jong Hun.
- Well done.
- It's good that you're staying.
- It's so much better for us.
- Our team will be stronger.
- It's so much better.
Why don't we play
rock-paper-scissors?
- We can play that.
- No, no. You did well, Jong Hun.
Wait, he didn't officially say it.
Jong Hun.
- Is it...
- Yes, it's you. You can leave.
- Mr. Hooligan.
- Gosh.
- Welcome.
- Nice!
- Now even Jong Hun...
- Mr. Ji!
Congratulations once again.
Everyone bet it all
so early in the game.
I thought they'd overturn the game.
- The fish cake is so good.
- The soup...
is very spicy.
- It's really good.
- The tteokbokki is amazing.
Wow, it looks so good.
It is good.
It's so good.
It tastes even better
after winning first place.
My gosh.
You can listen to the rules
while eating.
The second mission...
is a combination of foot volleyball
and table tennis.
It's an alteration
of the new sport, teqball.
It's called
the Birth of Foot Table Tennis.
- Foot table tennis?
- We're good at both.
Foot table tennis.
A team of two
will compete against another team.
So there will be two teams
within your current team.
Using all body parts
besides your hands,
bounce the ball to the other side.
You can touch the ball three times
before passing it to the other side.
You have to return the ball
within three times.
You can bounce the ball on
your table or the ground only once.
(You can't bounce the ball twice.)
You can't bounce the ball
on the table or the ground twice.
(You can't bounce the ball twice.)
The team that scores
11 points first wins.
The rankings will be decided
by the number of points you get.
- Okay.
- Sounds fun.
You need to divide into two teams
within your current team.
That means 1 member has to play
twice for the team with 3 members.
Jong Kook will play twice for us.
(Smiling)
We can divide into Team Jong Kook A
and Team Jong Kook B.
Can I play twice?
Because the two players there
are easy to beat.
Jong Hun wants to go twice.
- Oh, really? Okay, he can do that.
- Yes.
(The passionate man
gladly gives his permission.)
If you don't play well,
brace yourself for a scolding.
I'm in trouble.
- Jong Kook has a clear rule.
- I do.
- If you want to, you can play.
- That's right.
But you'll get a scolding
if you're bad at it.
What he means by a scolding
isn't appropriate to broadcast.
He means a really harsh scolding.
He's not kidding.
(What will become of Jong Hun
who volunteered to play twice?)
Just keep that in mind, Jong Hun.
Tell us how you divided your teams.
The first team to go
is Jong Hun and me.
The first match,
Jae Suk and Jong Hun
versus Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
Let's go! I think we're going to
win this round as well.
- You can serve, Jong Hun.
- Not yet.
- You do it.
- Let's go!
This is just the beginning.
(The game starts.)
- There it goes.
- He's good.
He's pretty good.
- He's pretty good.
Take it slow.
- Hey.
- I got it. Pass it over.
(Kicking the air)
(Luckily, Se Chan passed the ball.)
- It's on the other side.
- We got it.
- Okay!
- I should've hit it.
(The ball hit the table,)
(and Jong Hun kicks it
out of the line.)
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- That was good.
- Okay.
- Good job!
- You can do this.
That was good.
(Ssaebssaeb played
a remarkable part.)
He's good.
Okay.
(Team Gangwon 0,
Team Gyeongsang 1)
That was good. Okay.
It's 0 to 1.
- That was good.
- Go back up.
Oh, no. That was...
(A sudden slapstick)
- You should've been careful.
- Be careful.
- You should be careful.
- Isn't it your turn to serve?
- Oh, that's right.
- It's our serve? Okay.
(The slapstick during the interval
makes the audience happy.)
- I thought it was their turn.
- I see.
- I thought it was theirs.
- Let's play.
That was a good one.
- He's really good.
- That was funny.
He's good.
Do you want to serve? You can serve.
- It's our turn?
- That was a good one.
You can serve.
- You should watch out!
- I'm so sorry.
- I wanted to kick it hard.
- Be careful.
- I wanted to kick hard.
- You did?
- They're good.
- Be careful, guys.
Don't turn this
into "Comedy Big League".
I think it's good enough
for "Comedy Big League".
- Right?
- You two make a great team.
- Isn't he good?
- They do make a good team.
Let's get on the table
as soon as you serve.
No, you serve. I'll go up.
- I will... Shall we do that?
- Yes.
Kick it high.
- Make sure to kick it high.
- Okay.
Isn't he really ugly?
We got it.
Pass it to me.
(Their strategy is to minimize
their moving range.)
(Jong Hun calmly receives the ball.)
- Good. Receive it.
- Block with your head!
- Okay.
- It didn't hit them.
- Nice one!
- That was great.
- Let's stick to this strategy.
Okay.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- It didn't hit them.
(Jong Hun is bright
although they lost a point.)
- It didn't hit them?
- It's okay.
You're doing great!
This is really fun.
Good, I have to stay far back?
- This is really fun.
- Let's play!
It's like volleyball.
- Go up!
- You have to receive the ball.
(Team Gyeongsang
goes up to the table again.)
Hit them.
- Okay!
- Yes!
Is passing the ball between
the legs allowed?
- This won't do.
- One of us must stay on the ground.
You have to make the ball
touch their body.
(An in-between-the-legs shot)
(The ball passed through
Se Chan's short legs.)
One of us must stay on the ground.
- That was impressive.
- We're doing great.
He's proud of himself now.
It's a neck-and-neck match.
Let's play it well.
(Sighing)
Okay. Wait a minute.
Why did you burp facing me?
- Why did you do that?
- Come on, you guys.
I mean, he attacked
his own team member.
- Come on.
- I couldn't stop.
It's like a self-destruct.
(A biological attack
that stimulates the sense of smell)
I couldn't stop. I'm sorry.
- You should face the other side.
- I couldn't...
We all had tteokbokki together.
You did, didn't you?
But that didn't smell
like tteokbokki.
It is from the tteokbokki.
(They even take care of
each other's gut health.)
Gosh, it's getting digested.
Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- It'll be out if it hits the net.
- Be cunning, that's it.
(Be cunning?)
- Are you doing commentary?
- That's it. Will it be this side...
or that side?
Will it be this side or that side?
- Are you doing commentary?
- Will it be this side or that side?
(Commentator Ji Suk Jin)
Will it be this side or that side?
No one knows! There you go!
- Yes!
- All right!
No one knows! There you go!
(He scores a point cunningly.)
- Good job.
- That was...
(Team Gangwon
was thrown into confusion)
That was impressive, Kwang Soo.
(His mullet flaps even more
because he's excited.)
You're the best, Kwang Soo!
Let me throw it this time.
(After playing the game using
all sorts of cunning tricks...)
It's a match point.
- You serve, Kwang Soo.
- It's a match point.
(Team Gyeongsang will win
if they win 1 more point.)
It's hard to pass it gently.
It's not easy.
Will it be this side or that side?
You might've thought it's this side,
but it was that side.
- Will it be this side or that side?
(A rubber ball windmill
on a roll)
(Dizzy)
Will it be this side?
It's that side.
(He finally serves.)
- Okay!
- Nice serve.
(The ball hit the table
and went out.)
(Team Gyeongsang takes 1 win.)
That was a match point.
Well done!
Will it be this side?
It's that side.
- Okay!
- Nice serve.
But that was too...
You can't call that a serve.
(After throwing them into confusion,
Team Gyeongsang takes a point.)
- Good job.
- The serve was...
The table is too high.
The final round,
Haha and Eun Seok
versus Jong Hun and Jong Kook.
It's our turn? We can still play?
Let's play.
Give me the ball, please.
Let's do this. Let's do it.
- Hey, don't serve nicely.
- Jong Kook is bad at ball games.
Jong Kook is bad at ball games.
Let's play. It's a combination
of sports I'm good at.
Can we play a practice round?
Let's practice first.
- He's pretty good.
- He's good.
(He heads the ball downward.)
(He does it again.)
(The seal show with a bouncy ball)
He is good.
- Yes!
- Good job.
- He is good.
- Jong Hun can receive the ball.
- Good job.
(Which team will win the match?)
Let's begin the match.
- Serve.
- This is the real deal.
It's okay.
Okay.
He is good.
(Okay.)
(Jong Kook sends over the ball
Haha headed.)
- Okay.
- It's out.
- It's hard to be at the front.
- You need to kick gently.
Since it's a bouncy ball,
you need to kick gently.
Okay, okay.
Just put your foot against it.
Jong Kook is too muscular
to be good at it.
Jong Kook, I am a big fan!
- Okay, okay.
- I am a big fan of Jong Kook.
- Just put your foot against it.
- Team Gangwon needs to win.
Okay. Receive it.
- Okay, okay.
- That's good.
Okay.
(Jong Kook jumps up instantly.)
Out.
- Spike it.
Jong Kook, spike it.
- Jong Kook, spike it.
- Okay. I will try again.
(That's so funny.)
(The funny sight
makes them stifle their laughter.)
(Eun Seok serves again.)
Again. One more time.
Send it over.
(He spikes the bouncy ball.)
There you go.
(Jong Kook manages to save it.)
- You can bounce it once more.
- Okay.
- Can we bounce it twice?
(Jong Kook messes up
3 times in a row.)
- Okay.
- Can we bounce it twice?
(Out)
- You are the best.
- He is so good.
I was sleeping behind you.
- Eun Seok is no joke.
- How is he so good at this?
This is a game for Eun Seok.
- He is like a seal.
- He moves so fast.
- He is good.
Let's resume.
- Jong Kook.
- Bounce it.
Yes!
(He charged forward for no reason.)
I should have gone up sooner.
Jong Kook.
Is this how you play it?
(The audience is forced
to stifle their laughter.)
My goodness. My goodness.
I can't watch this.
Eun Seok is so fast.
- Jong Kook is angry.
- I didn't expect him to do well.
Jong Kook is angry.
That's short.
(My goodness.)
Our team is better than this.
- It's okay. You did well.
- Jong Kook is angry.
Jong Kook is angry.
- It's okay. You did well.
- Jong Kook is angry.
Jong Kook is forcing a smile.
He began to show a fake smile.
- Jong Kook is angry right now.
- That's not true.
All right. It's okay.
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- Look at Jong Kook.
- Eun Seok, just do it.
- He became wary of Jong Kook.
- It's okay.
- Can you handle the consequences?
- Look at Jong Kook.
Are you okay?
- I am okay.
(I am okay.)
Go. We need to get used to this.
Eun Seok is like a seal.
He is good at this game.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
(Eun Seok serves again.)
He can handle the ball really well.
Attack.
(Nice heading)
- How are they so good at it?
- Save it.
There you go.
What is going on?
He is like a national team member.
There you go.
(The ball went back and forth.)
What is going on?
He is like a national team member.
(Slipping)
What are you doing?
- I...
- You should have received it.
- For goodness' sake.
- They have bad teamwork.
- It's okay. What's the score?
- I didn't expect it.
- It's 6 to 1.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- They are really good.
This is fun.
- Unbelievable.
- This is so much fun.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
Haha.
(Running over)
He is lucky too.
(The master of the foot table tennis
is lucky too.)
- Okay, okay.
- We will do anything we can.
- You can't win against them.
- Seriously.
- Eun Seok is really good.
- That team is really good.
- Eun Seok is no joke.
- How is he so good at it?
This is Eun Seok's game.
Jong Hun won't look
in Jong Kook's direction.
It's okay.
We aren't kids.
Why would we play
with a bouncy ball? We aren't kids.
All right. Match point. Match point.
Jong Hun is all the way in the back.
(It's the match point
for Team Gyeonggi.)
We aren't used to the game yet.
(Jong Hun kicks the ball upward.)
- You can kick it.
(Seeing the ball touch the table
makes Jong Hun halt.)
- You can save it.
You can kick it.
(With the other team's permission,)
(he saves the bouncy ball.)
For goodness' sake.
I mean...
(A home run sends the ball
to the crowd.)
(Jong Kook launched
the bouncy ball rocket.)
I mean...
My goodness.
What was that?
(Even their teammate
bursts out laughing.)
What was that?
That happened because of the slope.
Didn't you know about the slope?
- I can't do this.
- Jong Kook.
I can't do this.
(This tall member is drunk
on utmost happiness.)
(He swings his arms
to ridicule Jong Kook.)
- I can't do this.
- Jong Kook.
I can't do this.
- I can't even laugh.
- How is Eun Seok so good at this?
- Didn't you know about the slope?
- I can't even laugh.
It's over.
Eun Seok is incredible.
- Gosh, that's too bad.
- Eun Seok toyed with them.
- Seriously.
- That was incredible.
(Team Gyeonggi placed 1st.)
- We placed first.
- You did an amazing job.
Hey.
If there is the World Cup for it,
he will join the national team.
Touch Jong Kook's back. It's wet.
He played really diligently.
- Jong Kook.
- It's not like that.
It happened because of the heat.
That's right.
Why is your back so hot?
It's too hot in here.
Kwang Soo, you should be careful...
since Jong Kook is mad at you.
- Why me?
- I didn't say anything.
You might not be able
to go home today.
- You are having too much fun.
- You too.
You too.
- Me? Why me?
- You should be careful too.
- I didn't do anything.
- Jong Kook is angry.
- Don't be flippant.
Don't be so proud of being good
at a child's ball game.
- Okay?
- Calm down, Jong Kook.
Do you want to have a go
on the field?
I am too scared to play.
What is this?
Why is he intimidating us?
Don't be so proud of being good
at a child's play.
- Jong Kook is...
- Stop bragging.
- Jong Kook is a person.
- Seriously.
Your endless teasing made him
very angry.
For goodness' sake.
But it was funny.
- Okay?
- Keep it down.
Jong Kook said he will play twice
in the beginning.
Does the team at the bottom receive
zero stamps?
- Does the team receive some stamps?
- Yes.
- It's twice the number, right?
- The first place.
Pick a member
who won't receive any stamps.
This step. This step again.
(Team Gyeonggi members will receive
10 stamps each except for 1.)
- Show the inside of the spoon.
- I need stamps.
1, 2, 3.
This is... This is ridiculous.
(Do Kwon receives 0 stamps again.)
(Other Team Gyeonggi members
receive 10 stamps.)
I have no luck.
He doesn't have any stamps.
- It's twice the number, right?
- Yes.
You will receive 10 stamps each.
(They receive 10 stamps each.)
- Hey.
We didn't do anything.
(Smiling)
We didn't do anything,
but we still received 10 stamps.
1, 2, 3.
- Okay!
- Okay.
(Team Gyeongsang members receive
7 stamps each except for Se Chan.)
Okay.
- Seven stamps each.
- Okay.
Gosh, Se Chan won't receive
a single stamp.
Hooligans
and the rest of the members...
need to write down the number.
Because Suk Jin is wearing
a hooligan's uniform,
the hooligans look so weak.
Should I leave or stay on the team?
- Share your opinions.
- You are...
- currently a hooligan.
- Should I leave?
- Make someone else a hooligan.
- Would that be better?
- So I should write a big number.
- Then you can stay on the team.
If you make someone else a hooligan,
you will get to join
a three-member team for sure.
- Will that happen for sure?
- Yes.
That team will receive
twice the number of stamps.
- Suk Jin, it's better to stay.
- What?
- It's better to stay.
- Is it better?
It's better to save up the stamps
for the last round.
- You don't need to switch teams.
- Seriously.
- Save up the stamps...
- That's right.
for the last round.
Look at their facial expressions.
Both sides make sense.
The two of them are really evil
when they are together.
This is confusing.
- Suk Jin, you should stay.
- Stay?
- You should stay.
- It's better to stay.
- Save up the stamps.
- I wrote down a number.
(Suk Jin listens to their words
and finishes betting.)
Suk Jin is determined.
- All right.
- Suk Jin made the right choice.
Suk Jin, reveal your number.
- 6.
- 6 stamps.
- Isn't that 9?
- It's 6.
6. 6.
Kwang Soo, reveal your number.
What is it?
I knew he wouldn't bet many stamps.
- I knew it.
- Good job.
Now, use 6 stamps and 1 stamp
respectively.
If you pick someone as a hooligan,
he or she will join Team Gangwon.
Who will it be?
(Suk Jin, pick Ji Hyo!)
(Glancing over)
(Suk Jin sees Se Chan's signal.)
I will send Ji Hyo to that team.
(Ji Hyo gets kicked out
of Team Gyeongsang!)
- Ji Hyo.
- You made the right choice.
- Come here.
Our team has three members.
Three members. That's great.
Six stamps.
I don't know. I don't know.
- It's good news for us.
Good job. It's okay.
- Ji Hyo, we will treat you well.
- That's right.
- Six stamps.
- Eun Seok, reveal your number.
One.
- 0.
Eun Seok wrote down the best number.
If you pick 1 of the 3 members
as a hooligan,
- he or she will go to that team.
- Our team?
- Why?
That's ridiculous.
Hold on.
I told you that it isn't over.
- Eun Seok.
- What I did...
was meaningless.
You should have told us.
I celebrated for no reason.
- This is ridiculous.
- I should have bet more stamps.
(What remains is Eun Seok's choice!)
(Who will become a hooligan
and get kicked out of the team?)
I am sorry.
(So Min gets sent
to Team Gyeongsang!)
So Min, Haha planned everything.
(Haha burst out laughing
as if he knew what would happen.)
I didn't plan anything.
(Yong Gu looks apologetic.)
(Eun Seok, pick So Min!)
(Haha is always one step
ahead of So Min.)
They made me do it.
- I had no choice.
- "They"? I didn't say anything.
(Ji Hyo and So Min are
the hooligans!)
(2021 Running Man
Neighborhood Athletic Meet)
What is this for?
(This is where they will play
the last game.)
(It's time to have a match
of strength and speed.)
I can already tell...
- It will be intense.
- It will be fierce.
(The last game will test
the teamwork and physical skills.)
All right. We developed
the last mission...
from World Chase Tag, a new sport...
- that combines parkour...
- It sounds hard.
and a game of tag.
It's Catch Me If You Can.
I know what it is.
There will be two taggers.
Other teams will send in
two members each.
Thus, six members in total
will play the game.
Four members will run away
and protect their balloons.
The two taggers...
will try to pop as many balloons
as possible in two minutes.
(The team that popped the most
number of balloons will win.)
All teams will each play defense
and offense once...
- Yes.
- to decide the winning team.
For your understanding,
- we prepared a video.
- I have seen it.
- These people are professionals.
- That's right.
- They jump.
- It will be hard.
The taggers chase
after other players.
It's a match of stamina.
- It's like a game of tag.
- Then you are out.
The bag...
Hold on.
Should I ignore what's happening?
Just laugh it off.
(They finish watching the video.)
For the first round, the taggers
will be from Team Yellow.
Our team? Okay.
(The lineup of Round 1,
offense and defense)
- Get ready.
- Let's go.
It's a matter of how many balloons
each team pops.
We should plan well.
Protecting the balloon...
- Hurry up.
- Over here.
(They chase after Haha
as soon as they begin.)
- They are chasing after one member.
- I got him.
(They caught him!)
(But Haha keeps his balloon
out of their reach.)
- Jae Suk.
- Get it.
Hold on.
(When Haha drops the balloon,
they pop it!)
(As soon as Haha's balloon pops...)
He came to them.
Why did you do that?
Hold out as much as you can.
- Pass it.
- Jae Suk.
- I got it.
- Did you get it?
- Gosh, Eun Seok.
- There you go.
He ran away.
- Gosh, Eun Seok.
- There you go.
(He is still running.)
Hold out until the end.
(He holds out...)
(and overpowers Jae Suk.)
- Hold out until the end.
- Come on.
Drag it out as long as you can.
Nice, nice.
Go, go.
(Kwang Soo's statue of liberty)
(He began climbing
as soon as the game started.)
(Even when Haha was getting caught
and backed into a corner...)
(and Eun Seok was holding out
with all his might,)
(he stood tall
in order to survive by himself.)
Go, go.
(They run over to Kwang Soo
because he is an eyesore.)
(Screaming)
(Popping)
(He used his height to put himself
at an advantage,)
(but he ends up self-destructing.)
(Kwang Soo's comedy skit
isn't over.)
Good job.
Seriously.
I mean...
(It's so hilarious.)
(Thanks to Kwang Soo,
they popped 3 balloons.)
Eun Seok.
(Everyone is out
except for Se Chan!)
(They run toward Se Chan.)
(Se Chan gets caught
since his mouth isn't aerodynamic.)
- Hold out until the end.
- Hold out.
Hold out.
We need to save one balloon.
(He gives out orders
after popping his own balloon.)
This is sad.
(They pop the last balloon!)
- Okay.
- Nice.
1 minute and 14 seconds.
(Team Gangwon's record is
1 minute and 14 seconds.)
For the second round, the taggers
will be from Team Red.
The other teams can send in
two members each.
What? Team Red?
The taggers.
We are the taggers.
- So Min.
- The taggers.
- What are we going to do?
- We are the taggers.
- So Min.
- What are we going to do?
- Are the two of them the taggers?
- The taggers.
- Yes.
- Really?
- You can't play twice.
- You should have told us.
- Can't we be the taggers?
Fools!
- Suk Jin.
- We are in trouble.
So Min and I are the taggers.
- Show us what you can do.
- The game won't end.
- We didn't plan this right.
- Seriously.
We are done for.
- Are you a tagger?
- Yes.
For goodness' sake.
- Let's go.
- Are the two of you taggers?
(It will take them all day.)
I am sorry, but would you give them
two more minutes?
- Slow! Cross!
- Clumsy!
- We weren't in sync.
- Let's try it again.
- Slow! Cross!
- Clumsy! Cross!
(They barely manage to do it.)
(There is no tension whatsoever.)
Ready.
- Get set...
- Let's go after one.
Go after Ji Hyo first.
(They attack Ji Hyo first since
she is relatively weak.)
Corner her. So Min, corner her.
(The two weakest members
corner her.)
(Did he catch her?)
(After cornering her,)
(he lets her go.)
Why are you guys so slow?
This is fun.
(Ji Hyo is a good girl
who helps her grandpa work out.)
Stop playing with the grandpa!
(Suk Jin is too old to catch up
to his granddaughter.)
(He finally manages
to hold her one hand.)
So Min, hurry up.
(This sitcom is so funny.)
(But they can't even touch
the balloon.)
Don't try to catch the balloon.
(Hitting)
What is this?
What are you doing?
- Catch it!
- This is so boring!
- What is wrong with you?
- Come and chase after us.
What is this?
Go after someone else.
- Pop it.
- Hold her arm.
- What is this?
Hold one arm each.
There it is. They did it.
- We did it.
- Okay.
(For goodness' sake.)
(He got slapped by the balloon.)
What was that?
(He eats a piece of the balloon
for energy.)
(The tearful balloon slap show
satisfied the audience.)
What is wrong with him?
(A balloon is enough
to make his fragile body sway.)
I think the Ji Suk Jin Show is
the most entertaining.
Suk Jin, pick a member
to chase after.
There you go. Corner him.
(He takes light steps.)
(He escapes easily.)
(Gosh, my right atrium.)
Why didn't you plan better?
They had to be the taggers.
I mean...
I didn't even break into a sweat!
So Min, get in there.
Do Kwon, you look really cool
right now.
(Do Kwon runs across the stadium
as if he is taking a stroll.)
What am I going to do?
Are the two of you walking
or running?
(They pick up an obstacle
out of frustration.)
- Suk Jin.
- What are you doing?
Catch someone.
Suk Jin, stop resting and run!
Suk Jin, run!
Catch Jong Kook.
Catch someone.
Corner him.
- Corner him.
- I will give you stickers.
Do Kwon. I will give you stickers.
Why are you carrying that?
- I will give you a sticker.
- No, thank you.
Stop taking out your anger
and just pop the balloons.
Do Kwon. I will give you stickers.
- How many?
- Three.
Work together and corner someone.
What are the two of you doing?
Suk Jin!
So Min, here.
- I look really cool, right?
- Catch him.
I am so fast.
(He has no problem escaping
even if he goes between them.)
(Exhausted)
What is this?
How did he escape that way?
Why can't you catch him
when he is running so slowly?
- He is slow.
- This is no fun.
Haha is doing better than the people
in the video we watched.
Good luck.
(3 minutes, time over)
Okay.
What was that?
It was fun.
- It was fun.
- It wasn't fun.
What was that?
The balloon slap was
so painful earlier.
- We got one.
(Round 3 begins with taggers
from Team Gyeonggi.)
(They attack Se Chan
from the start.)
- Gosh!
- Throw him down.
That's teamwork.
(Se Chan is out right away.)
That's incredible.
The left.
They are fast.
The right.
- They are incredible.
- Take one each.
(Each of them takes on a member.)
- That's good.
- Eun Seok is fast.
Kick his belly!
(It's his chance to take revenge
for the past humiliation.)
Throw him down to the ground.
(He pops the balloon
by kicking it!)
Help him!
Help him.
(Jae Suk is the only one left!)
He is on the ground.
(They pop the last balloon.)
Good job.
That was a work of art.
We didn't plan this right.
- They are so fast.
- Why...
- This won't do.
- That was a work of art.
For goodness' sake.
(2021 Running Man
Neighborhood Athletic Meet)
- Suk Jin.
- We won!
- Our plan was the worst.
- We failed.
We didn't think about the taggers.
Team Blue with a record
of 42 seconds.
(Team Gyeonggi is placed 1st.)
You get 20 stamps each.
- 20 stamps.
- 20 stamps?
Did they pop all the balloons
in 42 seconds?
That's insane.
Then comes Team Yellow with a record
of 1 minute and 14 seconds.
- It was our big break.
- Seriously.
- Life is all about the big break.
- Okay.
Suk Jin.
- Let's see the prizes first.
- The prizes.
(The special prizes
for the Lunar New Year)
It looks delicious.
- It looks delicious.
- It's beef.
2021 Running Man Neighborhood
Athletic Meet's gold medal goes...
(Who will win the gold medal
and the Korean beef set?)
to Haha.
(The gold medal goes to Haha.)
Really?
The gold medal doesn't suit him.
(He wins the gold medal
with 37 trophy stamps.)
That's incredible.
(Dream, Daddy won the gold medal!)
The silver medal goes to Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo wins the silver medal
with 34 trophy stamps.)
Mapo-gu!
- Mapo-gu!
- The bronze medal, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook wins the bronze medal
with 32 trophy stamps.)
Wasn't there someone else
with more stamps than me?
The penalty goes to Suk Jin
with 14 trophy stamps.
14?
- You always get the penalty.
- How many weeks is that now?
This is nothing new.
I think we can establish that fact
before the shoot.
The games must be fair...
- because he places last every time.
- It's not like that.
- Right? The games must be fair.
When you bet stamps to decide
who the hooligans will be...
Don't think about the past.
You didn't bet stamps.
Suk Jin, you can pick a member
to receive the penalty with you.
Really? What did you say?
(The tables have turned.)
I think I saw you do this.
I said that they should get rid
of these games.
Didn't you do this just now?
- Seriously.
- No way.
I did this.
Jae Suk became polite.
- Look at Jae Suk.
- He brought his hands together.
He is ridiculous.
You should pick someone
who hates the penalty.
- That's right.
- Who hates it the most?
It should be someone like Kwang Soo.
- That's true.
- I don't mind the penalty.
You don't mind it?
- I mean...
- I choose Kwang Soo.
Are you serious?
I choose Kwang Soo.
I wonder what the penalty will be.
- Kwang Soo is cool about it.
- That's right.
- You are amazing.
- I didn't know you would accept.
Kwang Soo, you changed a lot.
You are cool.
- Is that the final decision?
- Yes.
- I chose you.
- Really?
- It's you.
- What's the penalty.
I'll tell you what it is.
- It's Lunar New Year's Day.
- Right.
This will remind you of the Lunar
New Year's Days of your childhood.
- Dumplings?
- It's kite-flying.
- Kite-flying?
- Wow, kite-flying?
You can go home after flying a kite.
This is easy.
I've never tried it before.
- Bye.
How did they think of kite-flying?
Gosh, how...
This place looks nice. Okay. Good.
I'm doing it now.
(Kwang Soo has no idea
how to fly a kite.)
It's about to fly.
He's such a fool.
That fool. I'm flying it.
I'm not like that fool. It's flying.
(Meanwhile, the fool's kite is...)
It's flying.
There's no wind at all.
What should I do to fly it?
Good. It's time.
I should fly it now.
Okay.
It's done, right?
(The kite is flying stably.)
It's flying.
How did he do that?
Suk Jin, you completed the mission.
(Suk Jin's penalty is over
only after 18 minutes.)
- How did you fly it?
- What?
(Suk Jin's penalty is over
only after 18 minutes.)
I'm going home.
(Big Nose can get off work now.)
My gosh.
Bye, Kwang Soo.
See you, Kwang Soo.
- Help me.
- Bye.
I'm not supposed to get the penalty.
Bye. See you.
You should help me with this.
Hang on. It's time.
It's flying.
(It's flying!)
What should I do?
There's no wind.
It's flying.
(Making a fuss)
What is it doing? What's wrong?
(An unexpected
stunt-flying performance)
What's wrong with this?
(Kwang Soo's mind is
spinning like his kite.)
Why is it... Darn it.
What should I do? Suk Jin!
Super ultra-small investors.
(A big investor is here.)
(A good chance to make money,
stock investment)
This one.
(To make a fortune,)
(the Running Investors
invest their money.)
- I'm really nervous now.
- Please. Just this once.
(The new market is open.)
(Joy)
(Sorrow)
(Joy and sorrow alternate
in the room.)
(As their opponents show
a high return on investment,)
(they decide to wait patiently.)
(They need information
for higher rates of return.)
I don't make any moves
before I get information.
- What information can I get?
- Will it rise?
("Tazza: One Eyed Jack"
will be released soon.)
It's "go big or go home".
You told me to keep it.
(But not all the information
is accurate.)
What's there to life?
(They start risky investments
relying only on information.)
(Who wouldn't know this?)
(Everyone in the world knows this.)
Life has its ups and downs.
(Running Man Investment Contest:
Genius Investors)