- Hello.
- What is this?
- Is it our breakfast?
- Hello.
- I guess we get to pick something.
I pick number three.
- I'll go with number 8.
- I want number 3.
- All right.
- I'll pick number three.
I want number four.
Why do you like
number eight so much?
Eight is my favorite number.
I think Haha is doing
some mission alone.
He's wearing modernized hanbok.
Do you want to introduce
Korean culture to the world?
Haha. Your fashion is...
quite rambling these days.
When you wear hanbok like that,
you should change your hairstyle...
like an aristocrat.
It looks better now.
- Lord Haha.
- His hat...
- Hey.
- All right.
"Is anyone there?"
- Good.
- Like an aristocrat.
He's a dad and 42 years old now.
And this is what he's doing.
I'm 43.
- Are you 43?
- That's better.
Jae Suk, we have to
talk about this. Look.
He dyed his mullet.
- Will you let it slide?
- What?
- He dyed his hair here.
- No.
Will you let it slide or what?
- I did it just a little.
- Will you let it go?
It turns out his new movie
was just an excuse.
He actually thinks this looks cool.
I just became
attached to it over time.
- I just tried it before I cut it.
- This isn't right.
He dyed his hair for real.
It's so annoying.
You should wear it in a pigtail.
- What?
- Wear it in a pigtail.
I'm so disappointed
that you said that.
I'm really happy.
You just said
you liked my hair in the car.
You should wear my pants
and a pigtail together.
Gosh, I hate it.
- We're done.
Today,
to celebrate midwinter,
we got you a little something.
- I'm nervous though.
- I hope it's a good thing.
- It won't be fun if you all get it.
- Only two?
Six of them have
different gifts in them.
But two of them are duds.
Really?
I want you to stand
behind the table.
And you all will open
your gifts together.
- Okay.
- I will...
- I'll pick what's left.
- I pick number three.
- I want number eight.
- I'll have what's left.
- I'll just get what's left.
- I want number four.
- Number two.
- I'll get what's left.
- No.
- Then I'll go with number one.
- What do you want?
- I'll pick number two.
- I want number 4.
- I pick number 7.
Se Chan likes number eight.
Please open your gifts
on the count of three.
- All right.
- One.
(They can predict their luck
for today with the gifts.)
Two.
Three.
(Who will get the two duds?)
(Kwang Soo and So Min
lost the draw.)
(It's a 100 manual squirt gun.)
This is my favorite, hotteok.
I'm so lucky.
All right.
- This is amazing.
- All right.
(She got into trouble after
stealing Se Chan's choice.)
- Look at you.
- This is amazing.
I knew you would pick number eight.
I didn't know they would
squirt water guns from in there.
- Hyeong Gu.
- Hey.
Don't pull his hair.
(He tries to punish him
for squirting a water gun.)
(He pulls out his head...)
(and slaps him in the face.)
(Hyeong Gu, playing multiple roles,
he's in charge of water guns today.)
(He's getting slapped
after squirting a water gun.)
Hyeong Gu.
That's enough.
You're doing all sorts of things.
I didn't know number eight
would be a dud.
The gift we prepared for you is
six kinds of snacks for winter.
Yes! It's hotteok.
- It's still steaming.
- Right.
It's still warm.
- Look at this.
- This is warm too.
Please listen to the rules
while enjoying the snacks.
Today, we will have a New Year
Driving Out Bad Luck Race...
with a horrible penalty.
- What is the penalty now?
- I'm curious what it is.
Those who just picked duds
have been...
- selected as Penalty Men.
- Okay.
And there will be more
Penalty Men after the missions.
Is it settled already?
From the beginning?
It's not decided yet, but you are
highly likely to get a penalty.
Can I just get the penalty
and go home?
I woke up two hours early
to go to a hair salon this morning.
(Pleased)
We will have three guests soon.
- Do we have guests today?
- They don't know...
we picked the first Penalty Men
during the opening.
They just think they'll be picking
team members as a team leader.
Do you see the chairs
for the king over there?
We will have these chairs for them.
And the one on the right
will fall apart.
The guest who picks this chair
will start as a Penalty Man.
This is fun.
Can't you tell it's a dud?
You can't tell. It must be fun.
Then we will bring in the guests.
Yes!
Hello.
- He's Lee Sang Yi.
- Sang Yi.
(He was the baseball coach
in "When the Camellia Blooms".)
(He caught people's eye
playing a comedic role.)
(And he became the nation's beloved
brother-in-law in "Once Again".)
(Lee Sang Yi even won
the Best Male Rookie Award.)
- Hello, Eun Jin.
- Hello.
(She was a 2nd-year resident
in "Hospital Playlist".)
(With her great acting skills
from plays and musicals,)
(Ahn Eun Jin shows
her strong presence.)
And we have Yoon Kyung here.
(Bae Yoon Kyung)
(She was the most talked-about
cast member...)
(in "Heart Signal Season 1".)
(And now she's establishing
her presence as an actress.)
(She did many dramas like
"Record of Youth"...)
(and "Hi Bye, Mama!".)
They are Bae Yoon Kyung,
Ahn Eun Jin, and Lee Sang Yi.
- Great.
- Hello.
(The 3 rising stars have come to
visit a variety show.)
So, Sang Yi.
Jong Kook would be
excited to hear this.
- Why?
- He's from Anyang.
(Thrilled)
- Anyang?
(Befuddled)
- Come here.
- Is that true? Welcome.
(He greets a friend from Anyang
with a big hug.)
Is he from Anyang?
Congratulations.
- This is great.
- Congratulations.
(Guests from Anyang get
the highest power in Running Man.)
Things will be easy for him today.
- My gosh.
- Regionalism and school relations.
This darn world runs on
school relations and regionalism.
We have to get rid
of the bad custom.
He's really happy to hear that.
He always cares about
regionalism and school relations.
And he's not ashamed of it at all.
And he cares about
regionalism the most.
I thought he seemed
somewhat familiar.
I kept saying that, right?
"He seems familiar."
Actually, Jong Kook was
eating sweet potatoes.
(Before he found out
that Sang Yi is from Anyang,)
(he only cared
about his sweet potatoes.)
(As soon as he says
he's from Anyang,)
(he became Jong Kook's favorite.)
(Anyang cartel)
- He's even blushing.
- Anyang is the best.
Like I said before,
Jong Kook cares...
- a lot about regionalism.
- Exactly.
He really does.
Although this is his first time
on Running Man,
Sang Yi is fitting in well already.
Congratulations.
- You're in Jong Kook's arms.
- Congratulations.
Seriously.
Things will be easy for you.
- Anyang.
- He's got the face of Anyang.
Anyang.
Sang Yi is also a musical actor.
He must have a lot of talents.
We have to hear him sing.
- I watched his performance.
- What?
- Really?
Sang Yi performed
at MONNI's concert.
- I watched it.
- Really?
- In Samseong-dong?
- Yes.
Do you know the members of MONNI?
Yes. I know the drummer.
(I know the drummer.)
(Laughing)
She knows a lot of musicians.
I see.
She knows a lot of band members.
(She's got the sensitivity
of a band member.)
She knows a lot of musicians.
She's intimate with many musicians.
So Min is acquainted with
a lot of musicians.
I did a musical with Ahn Eun Jin.
Eun Jin? What was the musical?
- They are acquainted.
- We did a musical together.
- He's a friend from college.
- We went to the same college.
I see.
(As she saw Sang Yi get cheers
just because he's from Anyang...)
Isn't he amazing?
He's my friend from college.
Are you two close?
We went to college together.
He really is amazing.
Sang Yi prepared a song
and will play the acoustic guitar.
- I want to watch it.
- That's what So Min likes.
I want to hear him sing.
He sings really well.
- He plays the guitar?
- Sang Yi was...
the winner of a YouTube Star
UCC contest.
- What?
- UCC?
It's "Rainism"
of Anyang Arts High School.
- He was the winner.
- "Rainism"?
Sang Yi was quite popular.
He's amazing. And he was
the student representative.
The student representative?
- The student representative?
- He was a UCC star.
So Min is taking
a few steps forward.
- All of a sudden.
- She's revving up.
- She keeps coming closer.
- Because...
- This is what So Min likes.
- So Min likes stuff like this.
This is her favorite.
I love it.
I'll sing a little.
Okay.
(How are Sang Yi's
singing and guitar skills?)
1, 2, 3, and go.
(Excited)
- He's got great skills.
- This is nice.
He's got a sweet voice.
(Skillful guitar-playing
with a baritone voice)
This is my gift for you
This is like "K-Pop Star".
Please accept it
(He's a student representative
playing the guitar.)
(They feel like
they are on a school trip.)
2 times 1 is 2, 2 times 2 is 4,
2 times 4 is 8
- 2 times 2 is 4, 2 times 4 is 8
- He's singing "Iguana".
This is "Iguana".
You should go close to him.
(She loves the song,
so she approaches him slowly.)
- 2 times 1 is 2, 2 times 2 is 4
- This is fun.
- 2 times 4 is 8
- She likes it.
- This is her favorite.
- 2 times 5 is 10
(She moves her limbs to the rhythm
of the acoustic guitar.)
Iguana
(Despite her dance,
he shows off his singing skills.)
Yes!
(Despite her dance,
he shows off his singing skills.)
I've never heard this song before.
It's "Iguana". He sang "Iguana"!
- I can't believe it.
- How do you know this song?
I listened to "Iguana"
on my way here today.
- Today?
- Yes.
You think you two
are meant for each other, right?
- It's just a coincidence.
- Right.
- Yes, it's a coincidence.
- So just calm down.
He sounded great...
- but her weird dance ruined it.
- Yes, she danced like this.
- What's wrong with your dance?
- What?
I just think the lyrics are cute.
It was just like Eun Jin said.
- Yes.
- He was popular back then, right?
Yes, he was very popular.
He really is talented.
- I saw him play for about 10 years.
- Is that so?
- You mean this pattern?
- Yes.
- I see.
- So I'm familiar with his pattern.
It's good to see various
performances for the opening...
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry.
Well, excuse me.
Are you his ex-girlfriend?
(Suddenly curious because
she knows many details about him)
I think it's possible.
- You know too much about him.
- Things are cool between them.
- Did you date each other?
- No.
It's just because
we went to the same school.
- We practically grew up together.
- We were close.
We know everything about each other.
- Sadly, yes.
- Seriously.
We were in the same class
and we even performed together.
- We're kind of tired of each other.
- I see.
So we've learned...
a lot about Lee Sang Yi.
No guest ever played the guitar
and sang for the opening before.
I'm sure he would've felt sad
if you hadn't asked him to do it.
See? She knows too much.
- You're right.
- Close enough to be his ex.
- You two went out, didn't you?
- I'm sure of it.
I'm sure they dated.
You two went out, right?
Yes, they're close.
- What did I tell you?
- She knows too much.
It's so obvious, right?
- I'll ask you this.
- Okay.
- I didn't think you did.
- But...
- I'm sorry.
Are you trying to support him
as his ex-girlfriend?
- That's right.
- I knew it.
- She said yes.
- So she wants to support him.
- She's a supporter.
She's supporting him
as his ex-girlfriend.
I didn't plan to, but it happened.
- Please give him a big hand.
- Yes.
(Sang Yi's introduction based on
regionalism and school relations)
He's very charming.
Next is Bae Yoon Kyung.
(Introducing Yoon Kyung after
Sang Yi's remarkable introduction)
(She saw how glad they were
because Sang Yi is from Anyang.)
(She's just confused
with all the complicated thoughts.)
(She even saw their strange
school connection.)
(So she thought carefully if she
has any connection with anyone.)
So Yoon Kyung.
Do you personally know anyone here?
Have you ever bumped
into anyone before?
(Who will have
a special connection with her?)
I've been to
Kwang Soo's movie preview.
- You have?
- Which movie?
"Inseparable Bros".
- Really?
- Right.
- We've been to that one.
- Yes, we have.
We've been there too.
Right, "Inseparable Bros".
I left in the middle
because of a soccer game.
- Right, you did.
- So I don't know how it ends.
- That's why I don't know the end.
- Right.
(Kwang Soo feels bad.)
He really left in the middle.
Did you watch it later?
No, I didn't.
I tried to send him a thank you
message after the premiere.
But then I saw a picture of him
playing soccer on his Instagram.
So I knew he went to play soccer.
I saw him at the premiere
but he went to play soccer.
So schedule the premiere
earlier next time.
Because I have soccer games
at that time.
I actually saw Ji Hyo too.
- Where did you see Ji Hyo?
- Me?
At Ms. Hong Da's wedding.
- Who?
- In Jeonju?
- Yes, in Jeonju.
- You saw her in Jeonju?
- Is that so?
- Who is she?
She's my hairdresser.
Ji Hyo hosted the wedding
for her hairdresser.
- Yes, I hosted the wedding.
- Ji Hyo hosted the wedding?
Oh, really?
- Yes, I hosted the wedding.
- Ji Hyo hosted the wedding?
Seriously?
Gosh.
Ji Hyo, you hosted the wedding?
- You did?
- Seriously?
- My goodness.
- You?
- I can't believe it.
- Why?
- She hosted the wedding?
- You did?
How did that happen?
Why didn't you tell us about it?
So how did it go?
It went well.
I've never heard that
Ji Hyo hosted someone's wedding.
- I can't believe it.
- Amazing.
You host weddings too?
Gosh, you're so cool.
Okay, it was Yoon Kyung.
Next is Ahn Eun Jin.
(Everyone calms down
to introduce Eun Jin!)
Hello, everyone.
So you went to the same college
as Sang Yi, right?
Did she have a nickname in college?
It was "Angel Eun Duin".
She wanted everyone
to call her "Angel".
- No.
- She called herself "Angel"?
- That's not true.
- You called yourself "Angel"?
- No, no.
- You called yourself that?
It was my Buddy Buddy ID.
That's why they called me that.
Gosh, Buddy Buddy.
- I haven't heard it in a long time.
- We're from the same generation.
- Gosh, Buddy Buddy.
- That's why...
they called me "Angel Eun Duin".
- So it was your ID.
- Yes.
Come on. It wasn't like that.
- How was it like then?
- You were like this.
You said, "I'm an angel.
So call me Angel Eun Duin."
I was that cute in college?
- Yes.
- So I was cute.
What is this?
- My goodness.
- I think...
- these two were...
- Yes.
not really that close.
Maybe something
went on between them.
- Maybe a little.
- Actually, I wasn't...
a very good student in college.
But he was the class rep so
he always told me to join things.
He was
our first class representative.
He wanted us to be
in all the meetings.
- He always called.
- He was passionate.
So he sent you messages
to attend the meetings?
I'm sure you're the only one
who got those messages.
My goodness.
- I told you they didn't date.
- Are you sure about that?
She said no.
Come on.
I love what you're insinuating.
It's like a teen drama.
So he sent her a message
pretending everyone else got it.
- Right.
- And he waited with flowers.
Yes, with the guitar.
I love the story.
- Yes, ready to sing "Iguana".
- I love the story.
Don't you think you're too excited?
- I love this story.
- You do, don't you?
Then he says, "You're the only one
I asked to come."
So that's what happened.
- He waited alone.
- Right.
Do you know what Eun Jin said?
"So that's what happened."
Give them a big hand, everyone.
(Their introductions are over
with many special connections!)
Before we start the race,
we'll divide you into teams.
Three guests will be the leaders
in the first round.
(The special rule
the guests don't know)
(Among the three chairs,)
(the one on the very right
will fall apart.)
(The guest who chooses the chair
will be a Penalty Man...)
(with Kwang Soo and So Min.)
(They don't know
about the special rule.)
So all three of you should
sit in these chairs for the leaders.
Please.
(After the introduction,
they're being guided to the game)
You can choose the one you want.
Should we sit down?
Yes, Yoon Kyung, Sang Yi,
and Eun Jin. Have a seat.
(Who will have the honor
of becoming a Penalty Man?)
(It's Sang Yi.)
(He confidently took a seat
as the team leader.)
My goodness.
(Everything he built on connections
and singing has been ruined.)
So we're starting the game now?
It's already started?
(The class representative's
friendly slapstick comedy)
All right.
(The class representative's
friendly slapstick comedy)
So the game has already started?
The game has already started?
How could you
fall on your back like that?
So is this what this place is like?
- This wasn't that bad.
- Okay.
I guess Sang Yi was quite surprised.
It's 2021 New Year
Driving Out Bad Luck Race,
Take My Bad Luck Away.
Today, we'll let you know
what the penalty is in advance.
Okay, what is it?
Like in the old days,
you'll go through a race
under a large scale water bomb.
(They had the large scale
water bomb specially made.)
- My goodness.
- I really hate this.
Why is it always cold
when we do something like this?
- Yes, it's cold.
- It's so cold today.
The three chosen Penalty Men
are on one team.
And the rest of you
will be divided into two teams.
So a total of three teams
will compete in the race.
After each mission,
one member of the losing team
will be chosen...
to be sent to Team Penalty.
(Team Penalty can bring one from
the losing team after each mission.)
And at the final race,
Team Penalty will compete...
against the rest of the members.
So they'll get more members.
Through the races, Penalty Men will
be able to switch teams.
Penalty Men will move around
but at the last round,
the team with more Penalty Men
will lose the race.
And Penalty Men in the losing team
will get the penalty.
(Penalty Men in the losing team
will get the penalty as well.)
And there's a separate rule...
of penalty tickets.
Every member will get
12 penalty tickets.
You've just received the tickets.
So you have 4 numbers
from 1 to 4 in the first digit...
and 4 numbers
from 1 to 4 in the second digit.
Which means you have
16 tickets in total.
And through the missions,
we will give you mission funds
according to the ranking.
You may use the funds
to get rid of your penalty tickets.
(Everyone starts with 16 tickets but
they can remove them with the fund.)
Also, we will draw lots.
If you have the number
we pick, you'll get the penalty.
All right.
(Every member who has the chosen
number will get the penalty.)
(Penalty Men in the losing team
and the members...)
(who have the number that has been
drawn will get the penalty.)
I should get rid of
all the tickets then.
You're right.
Getting rid of the tickets is good?
Three Penalty Men...
will divide the rest into two teams.
(Team Penalty Men, Team Eun Jin,
and Team Yoon Kyung)
Each team will take a picture
with their members.
A group picture?
Gosh, I wanted to use this.
Does each team get one?
2, 3.
(They'll do anything
for the production cost.)
Here we go. 1, 2.
Let's see. See more.
(Aiming for her one shot)
Portrait mode.
(Testing the functions for selfies)
There are so many functions.
I'll lower it.
Here it is. Gosh.
- You lowered it?
- Check this out.
The background gets darker
if I do this.
- It's amazing.
- It looks edited.
If you're done,
you may change your clothes.
- Haha, I'll take your picture.
- Okay.
- Why don't you sit over there?
- All right.
That's it.
Wait.
Ready?
Yellow.
- That's it.
- How is it?
Check this out.
I zoomed in 30 times.
Hey.
- What's this?
- Just look.
My mustache really looks dirty.
This one is really nice.
(Now let's go get
some mission funds!)
Why isn't Suk Jin coming?
He's busy doing product placement.
But it won't help
to promote the product at all.
I guess they're taking a risk.
Actually...
Suk Jin is using the product.
But he's not using the camera.
Why are you taking it from far away?
(He is in the group picture.)
- Suk Jin.
- Hey!
- Jong Kook.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Taking a picture from far away)
Even if it's far,
pretty people will look pretty
in the picture.
(Editing Suk Jin out)
- Did you only get them in the shot?
- No.
But the camera is facing that way.
How can I only get them in the shot
when I'm so far away?
Okay. Does it look good?
- Hey, you only got...
- It was very far.
But look how clear it is.
You only took a photo of them.
- 10 times?
- Yes, I zoomed in 10 times.
(While they work hard
doing product placement...)
Do you have rubber bands?
Thanks, Yoo Ri.
- It'll look okay with a trim.
- Pull it. It's fake.
I think it's a hairpiece.
- Wait, Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
(Playful Jae Suk is
tying Kwang Soo's hair back.)
- Wait.
- Can't believe it.
- Doesn't he look like...
- Don't make him look handsome.
I have to.
- Do I really look okay?
- Jae Suk cares for you.
He really looks nice.
He does, right?
- Seriously.
- But the side view doesn't.
- You look great.
- It's amazing.
- Really?
- Yes, you look great.
You look much better.
- Well, it feels cool.
- You look gross.
I look gross?
- Hey.
- Kwang Soo.
Isn't this nice?
- It's gross.
- You look great.
- Kwang Soo.
- Isn't this nice?
There's an emoticon like this.
- Right.
- What emoticon?
- You look really good.
- There's an emoticon like that.
Isn't that a wig he's wearing?
- He grew his hair.
- Really?
This is much better.
- They say you look cool.
- Look at them.
They are talking about you
in whispers. You're so popular.
Do you like my hair?
Yes. You look pretty.
He's popular again.
- My gosh.
- This is what happens all the time.
You're a star.
You should buy me a drink.
- It's always your best days.
- Last week,
- when Suk Jin...
- He's popular again.
He likes it.
That doesn't feel so bad.
- He should've done it sooner.
- It feels great.
Here's your first mission.
It's Need Communication...
where you need to communicate
with your team members.
Each team will
do the mission in turn.
All the team members will wear
headphones that play loud music.
One will give questions,
one will answer,
and the rest will sit under the
balloon that grows bigger over time.
Oh no.
So it's like Shout in Silence.
If you listen to the question
and answer it, you get one point.
If your team member gives
the correct answer or passes,
the players should switch seats.
(The players who give questions
should switch seats.)
We give questions in turn.
I shouldn't be sitting
under the balloon...
- at the last moment.
- And you'll be covered...
with flour once the balloon bursts.
Okay.
- The Penalty Men should go first.
- Do it with confidence.
Good.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Okay.
Make sure to explain it well.
- Ready.
- Let's do this.
We can do this.
Start.
(The balloon starts to be inflated.)
What?
(Confession)
(The first word is confession.)
I like you.
- You like me?
- Yes.
(I like you.)
(A word caught Love Frog's ear.)
- What is it called?
- She got it right away.
How could she hear that right away?
(She's good at listening tests
when it comes to love.)
It's a noun.
What? Do you like me?
- It's a noun.
- That's not it.
- You should answer it.
"I like you."
It's a noun.
- Proposal.
- It's something like that.
- Before a proposal...
- Propose.
Proposal?
- Proposal? Propose.
- Something before a proposal.
- Confession.
- Two syllables.
(She got the first word
right quite quickly.)
It was hard,
but she got it right anyway.
This is hard.
It's hard to explain.
(The second word is phone number.)
- Phone.
- Num.
- Ber.
(Is he just reading the word?)
You can't do that.
You should explain the word.
- You can't do that.
- Telephone.
- Correct.
- You can't do that.
The balloon is about to burst.
(Pad Thai)
Good.
- Vietnamese food.
- No.
(Vietnam?)
- Vietnam.
- It's Thai food.
- It's Thailand.
Whale?
(They got off on the wrong foot,
so they are just wasting time.)
Bow tie. Tie. Bow tie.
- Pass it!
- Tie.
Oh no.
(The balloon is
getting a lot bigger.)
Pass it!
- Tie.
- Pass it!
- It's a Vietnamese noodle dish.
- What?
A Vietnamese noodle dish.
- Pass it.
- A Vietnamese noodle dish.
- What?
- Pass it!
Pass the question!
Pass!
Pass it!
- What is it?
- Pass.
- No, I want to answer it.
You can't get it right.
No, I want to answer it.
- Pass it!
- He's such a fool.
- What a fool.
- Pass the question!
You don't know it. Pass it.
Do you not know
a Vietnamese noodle dish?
I don't know anything.
- I don't know. Let's just pass.
- I don't know?
(At the moment...)
- Pass it!
- Look at him.
Pass!
My goodness.
Pass.
This is too big.
(It finally bursts.)
(No one listened
to Kwang Soo's shout.)
It's too big.
(No one listened
to Kwang Soo's shout.)
(The boy with twin tails
has become a wreck.)
It looks like he got hit.
It was loud.
I mean, he didn't explain it well.
You should explain it in words.
You shouldn't make gestures.
You should only say words.
Guys, you should explain it
with your hands behind your back.
- Okay.
- Put your hands behind your back.
Ready. Start.
You can't make any gestures.
(Mouthwash)
(The first word is mouthwash.)
You gargle with this.
- Gargle?
- You eat something...
when your breath stinks.
- Eat it?
- You gargle and spit.
- Gargle?
- Your mouth...
Gargle.
- You gargle with this.
- Garglin.
- Garglin?
- You gargle with this.
It's a brand name.
What is it called?
- Gargle liquid?
- No.
- He doesn't know the word.
- He doesn't know.
He doesn't know the word.
No. What is it called
in a fancy word?
In a fancy word?
You gargle with this.
What is it called?
It's not fancy at all.
(Mouthwash is a fancy word
to Empty Head of Running Man.)
You gargle with this.
What is it called?
He's so ugly.
- What is he saying?
- You stupid punk.
(Extremely frustrated)
You gargle with it.
(He opens his heart taking advantage
of the silence from the headphone.)
You gargle with it.
No. You gargle like this.
What is it called?
- Hey, just pass it.
- What is this called?
It's a gargle.
Tell me how many syllables it has.
Sam.
Gam?
- Sam.
- Hap.
- Samhap?
- What's in samhap?
Skate.
- Right.
- Okay.
She's good.
(Scandal)
She's doing a good job.
(Jae Suk should explain
the word, "scandal".)
- Hey.
- What?
This is... Well...
(Clapping)
He can't explain the word.
He's stuck.
It's something between
a man and a woman.
What did you say?
- Well, the thing is...
- What?
That's what stars have.
What is he talking about?
- Stars have...
- What?
- When stars meet...
- He's really bad at this.
- They take pictures and...
- Gestures.
- No gestures.
- They do this thing.
- Don't make gestures.
- What are you talking about?
Suk Jin shouldn't see anyone now.
But he sees someone.
It's something like that.
Blind date.
Three syllables.
- He met someone?
- I mean, Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook?
- Jong Kook...
- Yoon Eun Hye.
- He has a girlfriend.
(He just says
the name automatically.)
- Pass. What are you talking about?
- This is frustrating.
- He can't explain the word.
- That's cheating.
Why can't you get it right?
What is this?
- He doesn't know what it means.
- It's a bad guy.
He's really...
(Ingratitude means bad.)
He's really mean.
I mean...
(He barely explains
the feeling of the word.)
- He doesn't know this word.
- I'm younger than you.
- You're younger.
I'm younger, but I call you stupid.
- Mutiny.
- I call you a fool.
I'm bad. I'm a jerk.
What is it called?
- Is that what it means?
- It's a Chinese idiom.
The younger one is mean
to the older one.
Oh, right. That's what you like.
What?
What's the word?
It's "Fruits of diligent study".
No.
"Fruits of diligent study"?
What does it have to do
with "Fruits of diligent study"?
What was that?
Is it nangjungjichu or something?
- This is crazy.
- You're so...
(Popping)
(Team Yoon Kyung gets 1 point.)
I'm startled.
I'll surprise you.
I'm going to surprise you.
Ready.
(Team Eun Jin took risks
and let Suk Jin answer questions.)
Start.
Suk Jin is answering.
(In-laws)
This is easy.
- I have a stomachache.
- When do we start?
If he buys land...
- Grab medicine?
- Buy land.
- Catch chicken?
- I get a stomachache.
- Stomach.
- It's done.
- Isn't it a cousin?
- Stomach.
I get a stomachache.
The saying says a cousin.
- If he buys land, I get jealous.
- Stomachache.
Jealous?
- In-laws.
- Right.
I get jealous
when my in-law buys land.
(And he got it right?)
He got it right.
He's supposed to say a cousin.
It's about a cousin.
The saying goes, "You get jealous
when your cousin buys land."
(Joe Biden)
- The US president.
- Soap.
- Jeoktoma.
- The US president.
- Soap.
- President?
- Yes.
- Soap president?
- The new president.
- Soap?
- US.
- Soap president?
- The US president, you fool.
Soap president?
- Soap?
- Start over.
Soap president?
Aekyung?
(Is the soap president Aekyung?)
What?
- Aekyung?
- Did he say Aekyung?
Because it's soap.
(He says all the companies he knows
to find the soap president.)
Aekyung?
Pass.
- What's the soap president?
- Why is it so hard?
Jong Kook is upset. He's mad.
I mean...
What on earth is the soap president?
(They've done only one word,
but they are getting really upset.)
(Pancake)
(Wiggling)
- Okay?
- Eun Jin tries to look nice.
What are you doing?
You should hurry.
Just hurry.
On a birthday.
- Birthday.
You eat this.
I eat this on my birthday?
Cake.
- And...
- Cake.
- There's one more syllable.
(Eun Jin keeps
wiggling her fingers.)
- Don't move your hands.
- Birthday.
- Birthday?
- You eat it on your birthday.
Cake.
- Eun Jin's face is really funny.
- In front of the word.
Something cake.
Suk Jin can't
get it right this way.
Happy birthday.
See? He doesn't know.
But it's something cake.
Eun Jin's face is really funny.
Cheesecake?
(Oh, cheesecake?)
I don't know how else to explain.
- Cheesecake?
- A plate to put it on.
- He thinks it's a type of cake.
- Pass.
- Oh, gosh. What do we do?
- Eun Jin is so funny.
That was hilarious.
- It's going to pop shortly.
- "Soap".
(Prima donna)
(A prima donna is the lead female
soprano singer of an opera.)
That's difficult.
How should he explain it?
Oh, boy. How will he explain it?
The US!
(The US!)
- Soap?
- No, no.
- Gosh, I'm so frustrated.
- "Soap" again?
- The US...
- He's already tired.
She sang "Like a Virgin"!
"It's raining"?
The female singer!
- "Fur leather"?
- From the US!
- "Tiger Mask"?
- "Like a Virgin"...
- Time's over.
- My, it's so loud.
How should I explain it?
I should've passed it.
- "Madonna".
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
Why couldn't you guess Joe Biden?
- Why? When did you...
- She said the US president.
The US president.
Why would you say
a soap brand name instead?
Why did you mishear "the US"
as "soap"?
Your lips and hers look different.
- Ji Hyo, how did say it? Show me.
- You kept saying...
"The US Ma..."
Darn it. I said "Madonna".
Just say "the US".
"The US president".
- Just say "the US".
- "The US".
(They suddenly started
reenacting the moment.)
(Just say "the US".)
- "The US".
- I said it more than 100 times.
- Did you pronounce it properly?
- He doesn't know anyway.
- I mean...
- Why are you getting upset at her?
- Stop fighting.
- Listen to me.
- There's no way of doing it well.
- You're being too sensitive.
- Why are you being so sensitive?
- Why couldn't you get it?
- Just say "the US".
- It wasn't like that.
I thought there's someone
called the soap president.
I'm not sure if I can explain well.
Hold on a second.
- It was difficult to explain.
- There you go.
- You can do it!
- Wait.
Must I let him do things like this
to me when he's younger than me?
"Ingratitude"!
You can do this, right?
You can do it!
(Everyone in here is so playful.)
Let's do this!
(Yoo Jae Suk)
This is hard to guess.
(The 1st word is Yoo Jae Suk.)
He's ugly!
(She shouted out loud
to let everyone know he's ugly.)
He's ugly!
Yoo Jae Suk!
(But Kwang Soo got it right!)
(He got the correct answer magically
from a single hint "ugly".)
(I'm ugly?)
(He got the answer right so fast
that her jaw dropped.)
- That was incredible.
- My goodness.
(That gave everyone goosebumps.)
- What just happened?
- How did he know?
- Gosh.
- That was so funny.
How did he know?
(The next question is
"unconcealable talent".)
- Fruits of diligent study!
- "Fruits of diligent study"?
Another expression other than that.
There are too many.
Fruits of late-night study?
(Team Penalty Men gained 1 point
in Round 2.)
To pee...
- "To pee"?
- Yes!
- Anywhere!
- Urinating in public!
Urinating in public.
Switch your seats quickly.
(Team Yoon Kyung also
gained 1 point in Round 2.)
- Let's do this.
- Here I go.
Let's do this properly.
- Jong Kook, look at us too.
- Turn it around.
- Let's go!
- Being in second place is good too.
- Ready. Go.
- Hasn't it begun yet?
- Not yet.
- Not yet?
- Go.
- Oh, no. It's difficult.
(The answer is
"The Way This Guy Lives".)
- It's a fast-tempo song.
- It's difficult.
What? Speak slowly.
(Singing)
(He suddenly started singing.)
- What is he doing?
- What is that?
- What's that? Are you singing?
- He could just...
That's not how the song goes.
- Is it a song?
- It's a song!
- He's singing "Barefooted Youth".
- That's ridiculous.
- That's "Barefooted Youth".
- He's singing the wrong song?
(He keeps singing the song
that's not related to the answer.)
(This won't work.)
That's not the song
he should sing.
- Is it a song?
- It's a song. It has five words.
- What song is it?
- What is he doing?
- I don't even know.
- That's not the song.
- I don't know! Pass it!
- Tell me if you don't know.
- You don't know? Okay.
- I don't know.
(They passed it in the end.)
- Isn't it SECHSKIES' song?
- Pass.
- I live and die by style
- What was that?
- Wasn't that "Barefooted Youth"?
- Yes.
- That's Buck's song.
- Gosh.
(Stock)
- Let's go. Let's go.
- What a shame.
- Samsung Elec...
- I should be guessing the answer.
El?
(Samsung Elec...)
(Sam!)
(Sung!)
(Samsung Elec...)
- What is she doing?
- Kakao.
- My gosh.
- What?
("Kakao")
Gosh. This is no joke.
You shouldn't explain it like that.
She's amazing.
- Te!
- "Te"?
(Te...)
Tesla.
- "Tae Jin Ah"?
- Te...
(She urgently said
the hottest blue-chip stock.)
"Tae Jin Ah"?
(He misheard it as "Tae Jin Ah".)
(She's trying to express
stock price increase.)
"Tae Jin Ah"?
Did you say "Tae Jin Ah"?
(It's going up.)
(The price of the stock I have
is staying the same.)
(The price of the stock
she's holding hasn't changed.)
My goodness. Eun Jin is so funny.
- Te...
- "Tae".
- S...
- "Jin".
- La.
- "Ah".
I bet Jong Kook can't even imagine
the correct answer.
- "Tae Jin Ah"!
- It's going up.
(Going up)
- "Tae Jin Ah"!
- It's going up.
Yes, Tesla.
- "Tae Jin Ah"!
- "Going up!"
(She uses her hands more and more.)
- Eun Jin is hilarious.
- I'm sure she invested in stocks.
- She's so funny.
- Definitely.
Tae Jin Ah is going up?
Oh, wait. Is it stock?
- Yes!
- That's amazing. He got it right.
What does Tae Jin Ah have to do
with stocks?
That's amazing.
(They barely got the correct answer
with company names and gestures.)
(If they get another one right,
they'll tie with Team Penalty Men.)
How many points did they score?
- That's difficult.
- We're doing well!
- Of course.
- It'd be even harder.
(Sweet potato)
(They must get the correct answer
before the balloon pops.)
- You...
- I...
- ate this...
- Haha?
- earlier in the morning.
- My business partner? At his house?
What?
You ate this. You ate it.
(The balloon is about to pop.)
What? At Haha's house?
(Pop)
- They got many answers right.
- I did what at Haha's house?
You ate it in the morning.
- Oh, sweet potato?
- Eun Jin did a great job.
(Team Penalty Men is
still in 1st place.)
Saying company names
was a good strategy.
- Why did you say "Tae Jin Ah"?
- It's been going up.
Suk Jin, can you sing
"The Way This Guy Lives" again?
No, that's...
(He's still singing the same song.)
("Barefooted Youth")
(Woo-ah! Woo-ah!)
- Oh, right.
- Why did you even sing?
Did you think he could
hear you sing?
I don't know many songs either.
He tried to make it easier
for him to guess.
He sang "Barefooted Youth".
(This is how
"The Way This Guy Lives" goes.)
- Oh, that's right.
- SECHSKIES.
- Darn it.
- As a result,
- Team Penalty Men came in first.
- Okay!
(Team Penalty Men came in 1st
with 3 points.)
Team Eun Jin is in 2nd place,
and Team Yoon Kyung is in 3rd place.
What a shame.
- I'm relieved.
- We did quite well.
I'm so relieved.
As I told you earlier,
the more mission fund you get,
the more penalty tickets...
- you can get rid of.
- Yes.
We'll give you the drawing board
for R money.
Each member of the teams
can pick...
1 out of 5 in the section
of your team ranking.
I haven't done this in a long time.
When I was a little boy,
- in front of schools,
- Team Penalty Men.
- kids would do this after school.
- Pick one.
- Each of us gets 1?
- Pick just 1.
- 2 of them will be left.
- Everyone gets 1?
Just pick one.
Okay. Pick one.
- You want this one?
- No.
Among those pieces of paper,
2 of them are 100 dollars,
the rest are 80, 60, and 0 dollars.
(How much did each of the team
members gain?)
- Zero.
- I think Kwang Soo picked zero.
Show us what you chose
starting with Kwang Soo.
- I think he chose zero.
- Zero?
I picked zero.
(Kwang Soo gained zero.)
(His team came in 1st,
but he gained no money.)
It's so hard to believe.
80 dollars.
(Sang Yi got 80 dollars.)
(So Min got 100 dollars.)
100 dollars?
- 80 dollars.
- What happens now?
That's the amount you have
individually.
This is an individual fund.
Eun Jin, what about you?
I got 60 dollars.
- How much?
- 60 dollars.
- 60 dollars? I got...
- Suk Jin.
50 dollars.
- 40 dollars.
- I see.
- Ji Hyo got 80 dollars.
- I must've picked zero.
I got 80 dollars.
I thought I got no money.
Both of you got 80 dollars.
- None of us picked zero.
- Exactly.
All right. Here we go!
Do not hesitate!
Your team can get 60, 60, 40, 20,
and 0 dollars.
- 90? Oh, 60 dollars.
- That's 60 dollars.
- You got lucky.
- I got 40 dollars.
- Did I get the most among us?
- Yes. I got 20 dollars.
What about you, Yoon Kyung?
- Zero.
- She got no money.
- I picked the highest amount.
- She's in trouble.
- Right.
- Yoon Kyung is in trouble.
60 dollars!
Is this an individual game?
- No, but you need...
- Next,
it's time for Team Penalty Men...
to recruit one person
from the bottom place team.
- They're in the last place, right?
- Yes.
Yoon Kyung is on our team too.
What do you mean, "I see"?
Yoon Kyung, you should stand
here with us.
- Who should we choose?
- They can choose anyone?
Just one person?
- Who?
- Yes.
We don't know what will happen
when we move to that team.
What will happen to
the chosen person?
If you join Team Penalty Men,
you'll have more chances
of getting a penalty at the end.
- Oh, I get it.
- We should avoid joining that team.
- It'll be someone on that team.
- Exactly.
- Have you guys made up your mind?
- Yes, we've made our decision.
Please announce it.
(Who could be the unlucky person
to join Team Penalty Men?)
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Okay.
(They chose Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk has been chosen
by his senior Penalty Men.)
Nice.
- Of course.
- Why me?
- Hey.
- You belong to that team.
- It feels right.
- You suit the team.
You're perfect for the team.
Gosh, seriously.
Now, we'll move
to the next location.
If we bring Jong Kook to our team,
it'll be game over.
(Everyone is getting on the bus
to move to the next location.)
Kwang Soo, I have something
to ask you about.
- When you look in the mirror...
- Do you think you look pretty?
- and check your hair...
- Do you feel pretty?
When you see your hair at the back,
does it make you want to go out?
- You... Hang on.
- Why?
- I don't mind if Jong Kook says it.
- But...
- Checking your hair in the mirror,
- I told you not to act up.
he'd say, "Good. Okay."
Is that how you react?
- That's...
- I'm just curious.
- We're just curious.
- He didn't have any intention,
- but you provoked him.
- That's not true.
How do you feel?
Who inspired you?
There must be the key point
of your style.
Kim Da Mi from "Itaewon Class".
(The crazy Da Mi)
(The story behind his hairstyle
has finally been revealed.)
Oh, okay. That makes sense now.
- It feels great to finally hear it.
- Indeed.
- Have you been hiding it?
- All right.
- Okay.
- You can tell us anything.
(The talk has been heated up
through the story of his hairstyle.)
Eun Jin did a great job
at explaining the word "stock".
- I bet she's investing in stocks.
- Are you, Eun Jin?
- I think so.
- It's not like that.
- "It's not like that."
- I know nothing about it.
- It's not like that.
I don't know stock trading any terms
like "Tae Jin Ah".
- It was "Tesla", not "Tae Jin Ah".
- Oh, right.
Sang Yi didn't seem to be so good
at playing games.
He was lousy at explaining.
It was unexpected.
Sang Yi and Eun Jin,
you two must've gone on
a group trip together.
- Yes, we did. Sang Yi...
- He's trying to put them together.
- Sang Yi arranged everything...
- as the student representative.
- Oh, I see.
- He rented a bus and everything.
- Really?
You normally play games
at these things.
- Of course.
- And have the orientation.
Then you split into groups...
- And talk.
- Yes, that's right.
You'll also have a few drinks and...
That's enough!
- Will you stop?
- Just stop.
How is it that everything
is spun that way?
- He's just lonely, that's all.
- Unbelievable.
- He's had that expression all day.
- Once...
you have a few drinks...
People like you
ruin brewing romances.
Right, you're only ruining it.
Did you ask her out
for some fresh air?
Yes or no? Answer me!
I want to feel the romance.
You want to what?
- He's hilarious.
- He wants to feel the romance.
It's only so that he can have fun.
- No way.
- I'm sick and tired of this.
What a pervert.
You probably ruined...
some relationships
of Jong Kook's too.
Although, I'm only speculating.
Jong Kook? Well, he's...
His wall is put up too high.
- There's no hope for him this year.
- He doesn't let anyone in.
He'll just stay a bachelor forever.
But...
We recently went by
Jong Kook's place.
- Yes.
- That's right.
It's been a while...
since I've been to a house that
felt more like a storage facility.
- Seriously?
- I mean...
This is what I said
after leaving his place.
After leaving his place,
I asked Jae Suk...
if it was only my feet
that were cold.
He was like, "No."
I thought I was
under the weather or something.
- My feet were freezing.
- How can...
your feet be freezing
when in a house?
He doesn't even turn on the lights.
It reminds you of hyeongseoljigong.
It's winter, so the sun sets
around 5 p.m., right?
- Where's the need?
- Why do you need lights?
You have to feel your way
to your own bathroom.
It's not like I'm going to read.
No way.
Yoon Kyung, were you...
not interested in joining
the entertainment industry?
Me? No, not at first.
- Not at all?
- No.
I see hints of Kim Min Jung
in your face.
- Thank you.
- You should know this in advance.
If you get to meet Suk Jin
some other time...
Let me say I'm sorry.
- He might not recognize you.
- I'll apologize in advance.
There's a high chance of that.
I don't pay attention to faces...
when I meet new people.
No, that's a lie.
He used to remember faces
like nobody's business.
- Only rich people.
- Yes, exactly.
He never forgets
the faces of rich people.
- When they buy meals.
- So get wealthier.
- What are you talking about?
- But it's true.
I'm good at remembering my seniors,
that's all.
You never forget
the 10-billion dollar guy.
- What?
- 10 billion...
- Oh, him.
- He's Chinese.
- He's younger than me.
- Is he?
But you addressed him
as someone older.
(Because he has 10 billion dollars?)
If they're rich,
he regards them as his elder.
It's money over age.
- I'm only joking.
- There's no need to say that.
He regards them as older
if they're rich.
It's only a joke.
- Let's not mention that.
- I only address him that way...
as a joke.
How can you not get the joke?
Don't humiliate Suk Jin like this.
A few years ago,
he called me for the first time...
to treat me to a meal.
- Really?
- I went out...
and he was with a group
of wealthy Chinese men.
- Really?
- And...
he was serving them.
(He was waiting on the rich men?)
I'm not making this up.
He didn't mention anything
but just offered to buy me dinner.
Don't you lie!
Don't you remember it?
- That's enough.
- Why would I have waited on them?
- But it's true.
- That's enough.
- Kwang Soo, that's enough.
- You were in a suit.
- That's enough.
- Don't you remember that?
Viewers, what he said is a lie.
I didn't wait on them.
- That's enough.
- I kept my pride, you know.
Anyway, we're going...
to play a mini-game
on our way there.
- Nice.
- Sounds good.
- Will we get to add another member?
- Yes.
- Oh, dear.
- Again?
- Yes, you can.
- After this game?
Jong Kook's not good
at games on buses.
We can add a member
to Team Penalty.
This game...
was created based on how Jae Suk
kept saying "What about apples?"...
during a game in a recent episode.
This is What About Apples.
What About Apples?
(Episode 539)
(Suk Jin started off
the strawberry game.)
(Why do you like them?)
(Jae Suk suddenly asked
an unrelated question.)
(He still answered.)
(What about apples?)
(The game was created
based on Jae Suk's ad-lib.)
It goes like this.
What about apples?
- What about apples?
- Go ahead.
- Suk Jin, four.
The first and last word
should be "apple,"
but the ones in between
should be "elppa."
(The words in between
should be said backwards.)
This is too tricky.
The weakest link
is appalled by the rules.
- What about when the number is 1?
- 1?
Apple
If it's two,
do you just say apple twice?
- Apple-apple
That's two.
- And if it's three.
- Elppa-elppa
- Apple-elppa-apple
If it's four...
- Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
Apple.
- Okay.
- Apple-elppa-apple
- Let's do this.
- What about apples?
- It's too fast.
- Kwang Soo, three.
Apple-elppa-apple
Jong Kook, four.
Apple-elppa-elppa-elppa
- Okay.
- Nice!
(The last word
should've been apple.)
Nicely done!
I knew you'd attack me first.
- Okay, let's go.
- Don't attack teammates.
- Let's go.
- Jong Kook's up first.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
- And go.
- What about apples?
- Kwang Soo, three.
- Apple-elppa-apple
Jong Kook, one.
Apple
Kwang Soo, two.
Apple-apple
Suk Jin, three.
Apple-elppa-apple
Hold on a second.
(The timing was off,
but not too much.)
- Wait.
- I did it correctly.
Are you sure?
- Really?
- I'm sure.
I was on beat.
- Jae Suk, four.
- Elppa-apple-elppa
(Off beat)
Elppa-apple-elppa
(Like always,
he chokes while playing the game.)
- Didn't I do all right?
- Absolutely.
- Apple, elppa...
- Yoon Kyung, go ahead.
- What about apples?
Jae Suk, four.
Apple-apple-elppa-app
("Jae Suk, four" works like magic.)
- He...
- Apple-elppa-apple
- Apple!
- You should've clapped.
- Didn't I?
- Apple!
- Didn't I do that?
- No.
"Jae Suk, four"
will work every time.
- What about apples?
Sang Yi, three.
Apple-elppa-apple
- Eun Jin, four.
- Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
- Haha, four.
- Jae Suk, three.
- Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
What now?
(Targeting Jae Suk
will guarantee a win.)
What's the matter with you?
- Wait.
- "Apple, apple."
Are we allowed to kick someone
off our team?
This game doesn't fit me well.
Jae Suk, just get off, will you?
- I...
- He keeps getting it wrong.
Just get off the bus.
- This game doesn't fit me well.
- We chose the wrong teammate.
- Unbelievable.
- Jae Suk...
- Can't we switch fruits?
- You can.
How about grapefruit?
- Plum.
- Yes, plum.
- Geobong.
- Watermelon.
- What about geobong?
Jae Suk, three.
Geobong-bonggeo-bonggeo-geobong
Seriously?
(His mouth protrudes even more
when he's flustered.)
Hold on a second.
Let's play without him.
- Jae Suk...
- Can we please play without him?
- Hey.
- We just can't get past him.
Please tell them
I'd rather take a break.
- Just for a moment.
- I'll take a break.
- Just for one round.
- This game doesn't suit me.
Got it?
The round always ends with him.
Geobong's a hard word.
Team Penalty
is currently in last place.
Okay, good.
- What word should I say?
- 5, 6, 7, 8
- What about belts?
Eun Jin, three.
- Belt-tleb-belt
- She's good.
Kwang Soo, two.
Belt-belt
Ji Hyo, four.
Belt-tleb-tleb-belt
Safety, two.
- What?
- Safety?
(Huh? Safety?)
Who's Safety?
Were you talking about safety belts?
- Were you?
- Unbelievable.
- That caught my attention.
- No way.
- This is what she saw.
- Safety?
- She must be our driver.
- Who's Safety?
- This is what she read.
- Ji Hyo, what was that?
(What she read
dominated her subconscious.)
- Who's Safety?
- Ji Hyo.
Is it Kim Safety or Choi Safety?
Who is it?
- Who were you calling?
- Mr. Safety.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Zoned-out Ji Hyo.
Let's end it with this round.
- We'll win anyway.
- If we win this round...
- Jae Suk.
- Good luck.
- Who's up?
- Yoon Kyung.
Pomegranate will be a hard one.
Then what is that backwards?
1, 2
- 1, 2, 3, 4
I like soy milk
- I like soy milk
Jae Suk, four.
Soy milk-milk soy-milk soy-milk soy
- Seriously?
- Unbelievable.
You know that word means
nipple in Korean, right?
Why do you have three nipples?
Well, I...
Must you repeat that word
so many times?
- I...
- We only have two nipples.
He said that word on purpose.
- Actually...
- Soy milk-milk soy-milk soy
Unbelievable.
I can't believe you did this.
The last one
should've been "soy milk."
(She shakes her head.)
Eun Jin back there was like this.
No, don't.
Gosh.
All right, good.
In first place...
- is Team Yoon Kyung.
- Okay.
- First place?
- Haha...
- We're on Yoon Kyung's team.
- Yes, us.
- Not you, Suk Jin.
- Aren't you on our team?
Can you please remember your team?
You're not on this team.
She's teamed up with Se Chan and...
Yoon Kyung, Haha, and Se Chan
are in first place.
We won the game.
- And in second place...
- It's us.
Eun Jin, Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo.
- I'm glad.
- At least we came in second.
You had 4, 5, 6 points respectively.
Is Team Penalty
in last place again?
- That was close.
- We didn't lose as a team.
Jae Suk lost it for us.
You keep making me play games
that I'm bad at.
It was wrong of you
to add Jae Suk to your team.
This game just isn't the one for me.
(They arrive where
the last mission will take place.)
Right.
I mean it today.
I mean it.
(He announces that
he'll be playing dirty.)
Kwang Soo's terrifying me today.
He'll be like a mad man
in this round.
His eyes seem determined.
We're in trouble today.
Our fates were sealed...
the moment he joined...
- Team Penalty.
- I'll be shooting.
- I'll shoot.
- He's only joking.
(He threatens others
with a bullet that has expired.)
- Guys.
- Yes?
Starting with the winning team,
you'll choose the money you earned.
All right, let's do this.
- It's us three, right?
- Right.
- Go ahead.
- Back in the day,
I used to play games
like this a lot.
Kwang Soo earned no money last time.
- 100 dollars!
- No way, I got 80 dollars.
- Nice.
- Unbelievable.
I have 60 dollars!
The money...
that you blindly selected
in both rounds...
- is your total amount.
- Got it.
Team Penalty
will choose another teammate.
We thought about this...
- and the team...
- That's right.
We can't have anyone
strong on this team.
- We'll be at a disadvantage.
- It won't be ideal for us.
So we should choose
from the weaker links.
(They need to choose
from the weaker links.)
How about Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin...
- Yes, Suk Jin.
(He's the number 1 choice
out of all the members?)
Wait a second.
You'll choose Suk Jin
over Ji Hyo and Eun Jin?
- He's the weakest link.
- That must be our choice.
- The weakest link.
- You see...
We must choose the weakest link.
The issue with Suk Jin is this.
He tries to trick
his own team members.
- So Eun Jin might be better.
- Right. Eun Jin would be better.
I think she would cause us
less trouble, don't you think?
- Absolutely.
- She must be honest and upright.
- We'd be at a disadvantage.
- Of course.
- I really hope they won't pick me.
- We should choose one of them.
Okay. 1, 2, 3.
(Out of Eun Jin and Suk Jin,
which one did Team Penalty choose?)
- Ahn Eun Jin.
- Eun Jin.
(Ahn Eun Jin has been chosen
as a new member!)
Go.
- Just like this?
- Eun Jin will be...
- a Penalty Man in this round.
- Okay.
- Eun Jin.
(Welcome to Penalty Men world.)
We can talk about the stock market
with her during the race.
(They picked Eun Jin thinking
she was an easy target.)
(But later on, in the race...)
(She'll tear off the most name tags
with her tenacity and strategies.)
(What change will Eun Jin make
as the blue-chip name tag taker?)
Through the final race, you can
change the team to get a penalty,
and gained extra mission funds.
It's Switch Penalty Men.
That's the worst.
You'll be divided into
Team Penalty and Team Non-penalty.
It'll be 5 members versus 6 members
at the beginning.
Each team will wear either red caps
or blue caps.
You can switch caps
and join the other team...
by taking off the name tag
of a member of that team.
You're allowed to take off
anyone's name tag.
(Team Penalty wears red caps,
and the other wears blue caps.)
(They can switch teams
by taking off a name tag.)
30 minutes after you begin the race,
the team with more Penalty Men
will lose.
The Penalty Men on the losing team
will get a penalty.
And the winning team will receive
extra mission funds.
The Penalty Men on the losing team
will get a penalty.
And the winning team will receive
extra mission funds.
If they join our team,
- we all have to move to that team.
- Exactly.
That's how you can calculate.
So people wearing the same color
caps don't have to fight.
Correct. Take off the name tags
of people in the other color.
You have to join the team
with fewer Penalty Men.
Also, we'll announce which team has
more Penalty Men...
every five minutes.
The result will be determined
in the last minute.
In the last minute.
Everyone, please leave me alone
just for today.
- We have to move to that team.
- I'm begging you.
Please leave me alone.
I want her cap.
I call dibs on her cap.
- Please leave me alone.
- She's the easiest target.
I can't predict the result
because of So Min.
Exactly. So Min will be
the largest variable.
Prepare 20 caps for So Min.
I don't know which team
So Min will end up on.
I started off on the wrong foot.
Also, we hid 10-dollar mission funds
in different places.
(It's also important
to find the hidden mission funds.)
- You can gain extra funds that way.
- Okay.
- Everyone, you may leave now.
- Let's go.
- This won't be easy.
- We must move to that team.
We have to try at least.
It will be an intense war of nerves.
(All members of Team Penalty
put on red caps!)
No one can predict...
what could turn the game around
at the end.
It's hard to predict.
I'll be tough today.
I'll run really fast too.
So please stay alert.
(He seems determined to act up
like crazy today.)
Kwang Soo said he'll be tough today.
So I'm going to be tough as well.
Let's save as much money
as possible for now.
I need money...
(Haha plans to save money
to get rid of penalty tickets.)
in order to get rid of
as many penalty tickets as I can.
I will never be hit by
water balloons in this cold weather.
(She looks unnecessarily serious.)
(She's full of enthusiasm.)
The race will begin shortly.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Race, start.
(Currently, all Penalty Men are
on Team Red.)
(They'd be at an advantage
if they move to Team Blue.)
I have no time for this.
I should take off a name tag first.
I should take off a name tag.
(Kwang Soo is going to move to
Team Blue that has no Penalty Men.)
(Jae Suk has the same plan.)
- Oh, my. Jae Suk.
- Hey, Sebastien.
Are you going to join Team Blue?
Well... I think...
I should move to your team
no matter what, right?
Yes. You need a good strategy.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
Wait. Just like this?
You're attacking me right away?
- You know I have no choice.
- Wait.
(He's taking off Se Chan's name tag
just like this?)
- I have no choice.
- Wait a second.
- You know... I should...
- My gosh.
- There must be some confrontation.
- That's unnecessary.
There's no need.
It hasn't even been 10 seconds
since the race began.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk...
- Already? We should run away.
- Let's hurry up.
We should run away from them.
- We should run away from them.
- They will probably...
(They're running away
from the Team Red members.)
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, come over here.
(Sang Yi found the weakest members
of Team Blue.)
Let's go.
- Why?
- Come over here.
(And Kwang Soo joined Sang Yi.)
(Penalty Men Kwang Soo and Sang Yi
want to move to Team Blue!)
Hey, stop it. What are you doing?
Take it off now. Hurry.
- Hey!
- Hurry up.
- Why are you wearing a blue cap?
- I took it off!
(Team Red had 4 Penalty Men,
Team Blue had 1 Penalty Man.)
All right.
(Kwang Soo took Ji Hyo's name tag
off and joined Team Blue!)
(Team Red has 3 Penalty Men,
and Team Blue has 2 now.)
Take it off! Take it off, Sang Yi!
Jae Suk, why are you wearing
a blue cap?
Why... Why is it blue?
- Listen.
- When did you join that team?
Right now...
You should take off the name tag
of anyone you see.
There he is.
(In front of Penalty Man Eun Jin,)
(the weakest member
of Team Blue showed up.)
- Oh, my. Hello.
- Hi.
I'm just so glad to see you here.
- Hi. Bye.
- Wait.
- Bye!
Stop!
Get him.
(Suk Jin has no choice but to run
to avoid joining Team Red.)
(But he got caught quickly due to
his poor cardiovascular endurance.)
Oh, my gosh.
Wait.
(Eun Jin got a chance
to join Team Blue.)
- Just for a moment. I'm so tired.
- You caught me,
so let's take a break.
- I'm really sorry.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
No way.
(After a quick apology,
she reached his name tag.)
No need to apologize
because you can't take it off.
You think?
Really? Are you sure?
(He's bluffing
when he can't do anything.)
Outer reaping throw!
Gosh. I'm running out of energy.
(After repeated attempts to perform
an outer reaping throw,)
(Eun Jin succeeded in
her 1st name tag hunt.)
(She successfully took off
the name tag of the easiest target.)
Well... I saw it coming.
(They're exchanging their caps
while catching their breath.)
Here you go.
(Team Red has 2 Penalty Men,
and Team Blue has 3.)
(As Eun Jin joins Team Blue,
Team Blue is now losing!)
I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- You have nothing to apologize for.
- I'm sorry.
Don't be.
(Team Red is winning
with 2 Penalty Men.)
Jae Suk, we have to
keep our caps blue.
- But...
- We don't know the exact numbers.
- We don't know yet.
- Right.
- It's pointless to take it off.
- It's pointless.
It's pointless right now.
Okay. Let's...
- You see, right now...
- Jae Suk, why...
Why are you wearing a blue cap?
As soon as he saw me,
he ripped my name tag off.
- He was so determined to do it.
- Hey.
As soon as he saw my blue cap,
he attacked me.
I'm relieved that you two are
on the same team. Let's go, Ji Hyo.
- We're on the same team now.
- Se Chan.
- Take Jae Suk's name tag off.
- Sorry?
Then hold him down.
Take it off! Take it off now!
(Ripping off)
- There's no point.
- I didn't know she'd take mine off.
- Gosh, you.
- There's no point.
You should've ripped off
only one of our name tags.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You should have...
Give it to me.
- Don't put it on like that.
- Put their name tags back on them.
(Penalty Men Kwang Soo and Jae Suk
are back on Team Red.)
- Se Chan, let's hurry up and go.
- Okay.
Why would you do that?
Run!
- Hey, we're back on Team Blue.
- Run!
(After moving the Penalty Men to
Team Red, they're running away.)
Let's go and find some money.
Oh, those mean people.
(Team Red has 4 Penalty Men,
and Team Blue has 1.)
(While running around, she met...)
I wish I could have a sip of water.
(The red cap duo)
(They need to move to Team Blue!)
- Eun Jin.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Wait.
- Eun Jin.
(She lied down to protect
her name tag.)
My gosh. This can't be happening.
Hey, wait. All right.
- Eun Jin.
- All right. Let me...
- I'll do it by myself. I don't...
- Come on.
Eun Jin, I'm sorry.
(Ripping off)
I'm sorry.
(Jae Suk moved to Team Blue alone
in the end.)
I can't stand this anymore.
This is ridiculous.
He's so sly.
- Eun Jin, here you go.
- Okay.
(Sang Yi was quietly watching them.)
- Jae Suk is on Team Blue now.
- Eun Jin, here you go.
(He's planning to move to Team Blue
by ripping Jae Suk's name tag off.)
Kwang Soo.
Which team has more Penalty Men?
(Passing him by quietly)
(I should run away now!)
(Peek-a-boo)
(Sang Yi succeeds in leaving
Team Red!)
- Gosh, seriously.
- Let's stop this.
- Gosh. I mean...
- That was so funny.
(The merciless Eun Jin takes off
even a passer-by's name tag.)
What was that?
Let me pass by, will you?
- Hey!
- Let me pass by, okay?
- Don't stretch your cap.
- I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Team Red has more Penalty Men?
- I'm on your team.
- He's on Team Red too.
- Oh, he's on Team Red too.
- Hey.
It makes me upset for no reason.
Check the color
before ripping the name tag off.
- Check the color first.
- How many Penalty Men are here?
I'll leave. Please give me a moment.
- Check the color first.
- How many Penalty Men are here?
Only two of you are Penalty Men.
Really?
- We might be at an advantage.
- That's possible.
- Let's keep it this way.
- We might have fewer Penalty Men.
- If we hide ourselves...
- So Min is the problem.
so no one can find us...
Let's hurry up and go.
All the four of us together.
- We should stick together.
- Let's not split up.
- We just have to keep this number.
- That's right.
I can't believe I'm on the team
with you guys out of all people.
- We're all so weak.
- What a band of misfits.
- Gosh.
And 2 of us are the bottom 2
in terms of appearance.
(The weakest and ugliest)
True.
I can't believe this.
- We must keep our caps.
- Yes, we must.
- Let the others fight in there.
- We have only 30 minutes.
- Why don't we...
- Okay.
- What is it?
- Hey, wait.
(As soon as Se Chan found
the mission fund envelope...)
- No. Wait, wait. No. Stop.
- You brat.
- Stop it.
- Hey.
Let's divide the money equally.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do that.
- Wait.
- Let's put it down for now.
- I found this.
- How can we work together?
- Let's put it down for now.
- Okay.
- Let's put it down.
- All right.
- But I'm the one who found it.
- Okay.
- Put it down. Come on.
- Put it down.
- Gosh. I can't believe you guys.
- Don't be like this.
- Seriously, they're so mean.
- Put your hand down.
- Put it down.
- Okay. Let's all put it down.
- Okay.
- Let it go on the count of three.
- This is what we'll do.
- It's torn into pieces.
- Let's put it down.
- Let's just divide it by four.
We'll play rock-paper-scissors
and let the winner have it all.
That'll sort this out.
Let's divide it by four.
(Under Suk Jin's leadership,
they're dividing the R money.)
- It's not valid without this piece.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- This is the most important piece.
- True.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors,
and let the winner take it all.
- Do we have to go this far?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- I won.
- Hold on.
- Gosh.
- Darn it.
(If I can't have it,
I'd rather swallow it.)
Let's get rid of it.
This never happened.
- It says 10 dollars here.
- It's written on that piece?
- It's written on mine too.
- Hang on.
Can you see?
Mine says 10 dollars.
- But it's torn in half.
- He swallowed it.
- And I even won.
- Make it a whole piece.
- It says 10 dollars.
- You have to have our pieces too.
That's impossible.
Let me tell you the current status.
There are more Penalty Men...
(On Team Red...)
on Team Red.
- Darn it.
- We should rip off a name tag.
(There are three Penalty Men
on Team Red.)
(Team Red is losing.)
(There are two Penalty Men
on Team Blue.)
(They run as fast as they can
to find the members of Team Blue.)
There are more Penalty Men
on Team Red.
(The rest of the members
heard the current status as well.)
You mean there are more Penalty Men
on Team Red?
(Let's switch to Team Blue.)
Who is that?
(The Penalty Men on Team Blue
are being chased.)
Rock-paper... Let's play it fair.
This way.
- Hang on!
- Suk Jin.
I'll lie on the floor.
- Be careful!
- I'm being serious.
Come on, Suk Jin!
(Big Nose mercilessly ripped off
Eun Jin's name tag.)
- I'm sorry.
- Switch your caps.
You have to keep moving.
(Big Brother Big Nose leaves
as soon as getting the blue cap.)
Hey, wait! You can't rip it off
right away!
It wasn't mine that got ripped off.
(Big Nose is back on Team Red
in less than 10 seconds.)
There are more Penalty Men
on Team Red now?
You have 10 seconds to run.
How many Penalty Men
are on Team Red now?
There are more Penalty Men
on Team Red.
If we just wait, there will be
lesser Penalty Men on Team Red.
(If we wait, there will be
lesser Penalty Men on Team Red.)
(Cool down.)
- Did you find any money?
- Is your heart okay?
I'm okay. I ran too hard.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
I think you should sit for a while.
I think they'll come for me
if I just stay in one place.
That's right. They'll just come.
(A sudden dance time
when they're losing)
I like this move.
(The tour bus dance move
Jae Suk fell for)
Your dance skills...
I like this move.
Where did you learn that?
I mean...
Where did you learn this move?
It's a move from
"Saturday Night Fever".
Oh, really?
(Being cute)
I think So Min found
her signature move.
This is not the time
to be playing around.
- Hey.
- If we just stay in one spot,
Over here!
- they'll come to us.
- I got Team Blue here!
(Eun Jin yields Haha
to So Min after catching him.)
I'll send you away... No, you can't!
I'm coming!
- The Penalty Man.
- Okay!
You're ripping it off now?
(Penalty Man So Min
is on Team Blue now.)
- So Min is on the other team now.
- The Penalty Man is gone.
- So Min is on the other team.
- All right.
We're winning.
Jae Suk, we're winning.
Keep it down.
- That fool.
- Keep it down.
What should I do now?
I should look for the money.
(So Min got fooled by Eun Jin.)
I have no idea what's going on.
Which team has more Penalty Men?
- All right. It's time.
- Eun Jin...
- Okay, tell us the status.
- Currently,
- Team Blue is losing.
- We got this.
(Currently, Team Blue is losing.)
- Then...
- We're all set, Jae Suk.
We're all set. They're losing.
You mean Team Blue
has more Penalty Men?
- Yes, they do.
- We got this.
We got this. Let's pause then.
Team Blue is losing.
Jae Suk, what's important is...
- The three of us...
- Sang Yi!
can follow So Min around.
- What?
- Just follow...
If we just follow So Min around,
we'll never lose.
- Sang Yi, come here.
- He's right.
We can be So Min's shadow.
- We should guard So Min.
- Then we'll never lose.
We should guard So Min.
(Right then, Sang Yi joined Team Red
after ripping Eun Jin's name tag.)
We should guard So Min.
- Kwang Soo is on Team Blue.
- Look at her.
She'll end up getting
the penalty, but she likes it.
Because she's getting
all the attention.
- Since we're guarding her.
- We're like your fan club.
- Jeon So Min!
- Jeon...
- Listen.
I won't get my name tag ripped,
so give me 10 dollars each.
- 10 dollars each?
- I won't get it ripped.
I'll make sure to guard it
and stick with you.
So Min, you don't have a choice.
In other words, you're our hostage.
(In other words,
you're our hostage.)
- So Min.
- What is she talking about?
- Someone is coming.
- But you can't...
Team Blue is losing.
(So Min is seeking a chance
to leave Team Blue.)
- How did you...
- If we stick to these members...
- Hey.
- Is she serious?
(Se Chan is giving So Min
a sideways glance.)
(There are two Penalty Men
on Team Red now.)
(If one more goes to Team Red...)
Help me. Help me now!
- Help me!
- He ripped off So Min's name tag.
But I almost got it!
I almost got it.
I grabbed the tip of his name tag.
Get ready to run, Kwang Soo.
Switch your cap with Sang Yi's.
- What's the status now?
- We're back to square one.
Back to square one.
Come on!
Wait a minute. I'm on the same team
as them again?
What color is my cap? Is it red?
There are three Penalty Men
on Team Red already.
- We have to run.
- They have more Penalty Men!
(Sang Yi and Se Chan
ditch the fan club and run.)
They have more Penalty Men now!
It hasn't been 10 seconds yet!
- It hasn't been 10 seconds yet!
- Yours wasn't ripped!
Hey, this is so tiring.
Who came up with this race?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Who did?
Hey! What happened?
- This is so exhausting!
- It's the three of us again?
(It's the three of us again?)
This is the worst race.
- This is the worst.
- You know,
I'll never be able to win
no matter what I do.
- We can just...
- But we can't be doing nothing.
make our moves a few minutes
before the race is over.
(They decide to use their energy
3 minutes before the race is over.)
(Right then, Eun Jin
from Team Blue appears.)
How do we find them?
(As soon as they heard
Eun Jin's voice...)
- I know.
- We can't find them anywhere.
(He goes at her right away.)
- He's not even human.
- What's...
(He goes at her
without even hesitating.)
- What's the current status?
- You're not even human.
What's the status?
Which team is losing?
- Why would you go after her?
- How can I...
- Where is the money?
- Which team has more Penalty Men?
- I have no idea.
- Did you find any, Eun Jin?
I found really little.
(Suk Jin loses his patience
and attacks Eun Jin.)
You can't rip off mine!
I'm on your team.
So now...
- What just happened?
- Let's recall what happened.
- The blue cap goes to him.
- Yes, it should.
Eun Jin's cap goes to Suk Jin.
- It's mine.
- And then...
- Watch.
- Then it goes to Kwang Soo.
- Why?
- Because he ripped off your name.
And then it comes to me.
(The blue cap goes to Jae Suk?)
You got it, right?
Then...
Then I'm going to run,
but you're a fool.
Why?
- Why?
(But Team Blue is winning.)
- You sent him away.
- That's right.
- That's right. Come here.
- We should go.
- What's happening?
- Which team is winning?
- We should go.
(Even Yoon Kyung and Jong Kook
who were passing by got confused.)
What's going on?
(Ripping)
- You ripped off his name tag?
- What was that?
(Yoon Kyung ripped off
Kwang Soo's name tag.)
Wait.
That's a good thing.
Team Red was winning.
Why? They said Team Blue
has more Penalty Men.
- No, that's not true.
- I know!
But you're not Penalty Man.
Can you put this back on?
We're totally safe. Follow me.
- Follow me. Hurry.
- We...
We're safe. We sent the Penalty Man
to Team Blue again.
- We are...
- What a relief.
Why did Yoon Kyung rip off
Kwang Soo's name tag?
Yoon Kyung ripped off my name tag.
Then we'll have more Penalty Men.
I know. If you just stay still...
Where did you find the money?
- Where was it?
- Jae Suk.
- Hey, give me 10 dollars.
- What? Don't be ridiculous.
- I gave out a lot.
You should look for the money.
There are more Penalty Men
on our team now.
Why did you have to go after her?
No, I got mine ripped off.
(I got mine ripped off.)
Will you please use your brain?
(Will you please use your brain?)
Think before you rip off
someone's name tag.
Running around like a headless
chicken won't get you a win.
- Jae Suk, you're...
- That's not how...
- the variety shows these days work.
- Jae Suk.
Think before you move.
Think about it.
- Okay? If you play like that,
- Jae Suk.
you'll always get the penalty.
I think...
you and I will be going home
completely wet.
- We're totally safe.
- We totally are.
They'll come rip our name tags off,
- so we should run away.
- Can't we rip off theirs?
But this is a dead-end.
Let's go back to the hallway.
- Assume that they're not there.
- But we are... We need...
two Penalty Men anyway.
- We'll be in trouble if we have...
- He's coming!
(He's coming!)
We should run to the other side!
(Kwang Soo is chasing them.)
Run away!
(When Kwang Soo chases after them,)
Hurry! Go!
(Suk Jin goes into the room
and Yoon Kyung stays in the hall.)
- Welcome.
- What?
(Welcome.)
Welcome.
What?
- Welcome.
- What... What is going on?
Come here.
Yoon Kyung.
(She tries to fight Jae Suk off.)
I need to rip off the name tag.
- Why?
- Come on.
- I will reach behind your neck.
- Walk away.
Over there,
- Suk Jin is in the room.
- Where?
(She gives him
her team member's location.)
- That room.
- You need to take me there.
- Over there.
- Where?
That room.
Once I see him,
- I will rip off his name tag.
- Really?
- Let's go.
- Then...
- I will take you to the room.
- Okay. Then I will let you go.
- Open the door, okay?
- Okay.
- Where is he?
- In there.
- Is he in "The Penthouse" room?
- Yes.
I am serious. He is hiding in there.
- I don't see him.
- He is hiding in there.
Open the door.
Bring Suk Jin out.
- Really?
- Yes.
(She enters the room
as if nothing has happened.)
(Suk Jin is here.)
What? Did you sell me out?
Did you sell me out?
- No.
- You were talking to someone.
- No, I wasn't.
- No?
- I...
- Jae Suk.
I was going to hide with you,
but I couldn't find you.
Where did Jae Suk go?
He was chasing after us.
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- He almost ripped off my name tag.
- Stay in here.
(Peek-a-boo)
Where are you going?
Hey.
Hey!
Yoon Kyung, please hold him.
What is going on?
Did you sell me out?
Come on.
I mean...
Yoon Kyung, just you wait.
(She runs away at full speed
while Suk Jin threatens her.)
This is nerve-wracking.
- Team Red.
- I need to go over there.
Yoon Kyung.
(He finds his target.)
- There are more on Team Blue.
- Jae Suk was...
on Team Red.
- He is a Penalty Man.
- Yes.
- Is he on Team Red?
There are members of Team Red.
I am Team Red, right?
Am I Team Blue?
(Am I Team Blue?)
(He attacks Yoon Kyung for revenge!)
What?
(He successfully takes his revenge.)
- How could you betray me?
- It's better to be...
on Team Red.
- It's better to be on Team Red.
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo spots So Min,
Team Red's Penalty Man.)
Team Blue has fewer Penalty Men.
- Really?
- Yes. We have fewer Penalty Men.
- We have fewer Penalty Men.
- Hold on.
Penalty Men!
(They spot Team Red's Penalty Men,
Jae Suk and Eun Jin!)
(So Min is on Team Red too.)
- Look at that.
- Team Red.
What?
Hey!
- We are Team Red. What is it?
- What is it?
Hurry up.
(Team Blue is winning.)
- Why are they running away?
- Kwang Soo. Hold on.
So Min is on Team Red.
That team has three Penalty Men.
We just need to protect ourselves.
Watch out for Jae Suk.
The Penalty Men must be
at each other's throats.
Gosh, how do you know
which side to join?
Haha!
(Haha!)
Haha, we are the only Penalty Men
on the team.
(Haha, we are the only Penalty Men
on the team.)
We just need to keep it this way.
- Our team has only two Penalty Men.
- Really? Are you sure?
The Penalty Men of that team have
no reason to rip off...
Team Blue's name tags.
Then Team Blue would have
more Penalty Men.
I need to rip off
Team Blue's name tag.
I think I should do that.
There they are.
Team Blue members
are gathered outside.
Then...
- I don't have anything.
- Hey, hold on.
I can't beat you guys...
in terms of speed or strength.
Both of you are Penalty Men, right?
(Sang Yi and Kwang Soo want
to keep the blue cap.)
(Hold on.)
(It's better to have
fewer Penalty Men on Team Blue.)
(In that case...)
(Suk Jin,
rip off Sang Yi's name tag.)
- You understood the rules, right?
- I...
You understood the rules, right?
I understood them perfectly.
Are you going to be this way?
Hold on.
(Ripping)
Okay. I did it.
- Let's go.
- We need to run away.
- Suk Jin, So Min is coming.
- 1, 2, 3,
4, 5...
We are safe. We are totally safe.
(Team Blue loses Sang Yi,
a Penalty Man.)
I am the only Penalty Man...
on Team Blue.
(Kwang Soo is the only Penalty Man
on Team Blue!)
- 7, 8,
- What's the current situation...
- nine,
- for Team Red?
- 10. Okay.
- What's the current situation?
How many Penalty Men are
on Team Red?
- Let's...
- Let's think.
- You and me.
- Kwang Soo is on Team Blue.
- Kwang Soo is the only one...
- There are five Penalty Men, right?
- Yes.
Kwang Soo is the only Penalty Man
on Team Blue.
- Jae Suk is on Team Red.
- The other four are on Team Red.
Then...
This is...
I figured this out
after running around for 10 minutes.
I trusted Kwang Soo.
Why did you trust Kwang Soo?
(My goodness.)
(Yoon Kyung, a Blue Team member,
is walking around by herself.)
(Hiding)
(She spots Jae Suk.)
Yoon Kyung.
What is going on?
(Yoon Kyung doesn't know
that Team Blue is winning.)
It's more advantageous for you
to join Team Red.
Why?
Team Blue currently has
more Penalty Men.
- So I will switch teams with you.
- Why would you do that?
- It's 3 versus 2,
- Okay.
so it doesn't affect me that much
to switch teams with you.
I will do it for you.
But we don't know...
the current situation.
That's why
I want to try switching teams.
It's a good idea.
Right? Let me rip off your name tag.
Or you can rip mine off.
You can rip off mine.
- I will rip off yours.
- Okay.
(Fooled by Jae Suk,
she reaches for his name tag.)
(Running away)
I have had it with you.
(Yoon Kyung suspects Jae Suk
and runs away.)
Listen.
What is your problem?
(Yoon Kyung tends to be suspicious.)
Why...
It's either you rip off my name tag
or I rip off yours. I have no time.
(But Jae Suk's lie continues.)
All right. Gosh, it's stiff.
- No one ripped it off before.
- Yes.
- The race ends in five minutes.
- Really?
Will you give us
the current situation now?
- Yes.
- Okay.
All right. Team Blue...
Team Blue is winning.
(Excuse me?)
(Laughing)
(You can sense her rage
from the back.)
Oh, that hurts!
He is too fast!
(The cheater runs away.)
(Crying)
He is too fast.
(Jae Suk manages to lose her.)
He fooled me.
(He fooled me.)
Team Red is losing.
This is driving me crazy.
What should I do?
Is there no way to win?
(Less than 5 minutes remain.)
I see Team Blue.
Someone is over there, right?
(Hitting)
Hey!
Team Blue... I am Team Blue, right?
Where is everyone hiding?
Everyone must be hiding.
If Team Blue members scatter,
we will win for sure.
30 seconds remain.
Run away, Team Blue!
(The last 30 seconds
to determine the result)
She is coming after us!
I need to keep this cap.
I need to keep this cap
no matter what.
15 seconds remain. 15 seconds.
(Kwang Soo in a blue cap
is looking for a place to hide.)
Jae Suk!
What? Why are you on Team Blue?
Why are you... Hold on!
(There are two blue caps.)
(Why is Sang Yi
in a blue cap as well?)
- Hold on! What?
- Hey!
- What is...
(At that moment,)
(Suk Jin appears in a red cap.)
- There are so many of them.
- What?
- Hey!
- What is going on?
(At this rate, Team Blue will lose.)
So Min!
Team Red has fewer Penalty Men.
Team Blue has more, right?
What is going on?
(Then their target is Suk Jin.)
(The last 5 seconds will determine
the result.)
- Three...
- Get him!
(If the race ends this way,)
(the Penalty Men
of Team Blue will lose.)
Get him!
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo ripped off
Suk Jin's name tag!)
(The race ends.)
(Each team currently has
2 Penalty Men.)
Please gather around.
Hey, Sang Yi is a Penalty Man!
What happened?
(The non-Penalty Men's cap colors
get revealed.)
What?
It's blue.
Did Team Blue win?
We don't know yet.
(Jong Kook and Eun Jin
will determine the result.)
Which color is Eun Jin's cap?
(Since Eun Jin is a Penalty Man,
her team will lose.)
(What are their cap colors?)
Hey.
Eun Jin is on Team Blue.
(Eun Jin is on Team Blue.)
(Eun Jin, a Penalty Man,
is wearing a blue cap.)
- We lost.
- Team Red won!
Team Red won.
Okay!
(Team Red won.)
At the last moment...
(We were winning.)
Kwang Soo came out of nowhere.
(Kwang Soo made the right choice
by ripping off Suk Jin's name tag!)
Team Red won!
What?
When did this happen?
Jong Kook is on Team Red.
(Jong Kook is wearing a red cap.)
What happened?
She is coming after us!
(Right before the race ended)
I got you, Muscle Monster!
It's better for me to rip off
the name tag.
It's better for me to switch teams.
(But both Ji Hyo and Yoon Kyung had
red caps.)
I should switch over to Team Red.
Okay.
(If 3 out of 5 members
are non-Penalty Men on Team Red...)
I should switch over to Team Red.
Rip it off.
(Thus, he gave up his blue cap!)
(He sent Eun Jin to Team Blue
and solidified his victory.)
Jong Kook, did you switch teams
at the last moment?
Jong Kook.
(Protein Monster
can strategize now.)
We lost because of Jong Kook.
- I did it.
- Jong Kook.
Let's move to the ending location.
Shall we go?
(They move to the ending location
for the final penalty!)
All right, everyone.
Thanks to Kwang Soo's buzzer-beater,
Team Blue lost.
(Team Red won!)
Thus, Team Blue's...
Eun Jin, Sang Yi, and Jae Suk...
will get the penalty.
- The decision is final.
- Yes.
Here is
what the rest of you will do.
the winning team...
will select the R money
one last time.
Really?
Pick one each.
Gosh, I picked 10 dollars.
Look at Ji Hyo.
Four dollars.
How about you, Yoon Kyung?
What's the number?
Is it zero?
(She got zero again.)
You got zero all day long.
- What is up with her today?
- We will get the penalty together.
She is really bad at games.
Before the penalty ticket lottery,
you can use the mission fund...
- to discard your penalty tickets.
- Okay.
You remember
the 16 penalty tickets, right?
- Yes.
You can discard 1 penalty ticket
for 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars?
- We can't discard that many.
Pay up and pick the numbers
you want to discard.
(Afterward, two numbers
will be chosen by lottery.)
Discard the number
you think will get chosen.
(The one who has the chosen number
will receive the penalty.)
(The final Penalty Men will be hit
with a strong water bomb!)
I don't know
which number will get chosen.
It's impossible to know.
There are so many.
It wasn't my goal
to rip off the name tags.
I will discard these tickets.
Okay. If you leave them there,
we will take them.
I have two tickets left.
I won't get chosen, right?
I bet you do.
I will pay up 320 dollars.
- 320 dollars.
- 320 dollars?
Yes. Count them.
Did he discard all the tickets?
- Did you discard all the tickets?
- Do you still have money left?
Yes, I do.
Jong Kook discarded all the tickets.
- I have 40 dollars left.
- What?
- You have to turn it in.
- Really?
(He turns in 40 dollars.)
- How did he do that?
- What?
He is so frugal.
Is he the production crew or what?
While you guys focused on the cap,
I searched for the R money.
People pretended not to see him
when they ran into him.
(Protein Monster,
we didn't see anything.)
- Seriously.
- He is too scary.
Did you acknowledge him?
I pretended not to see him.
Show us your tickets.
Please let the number be three.
- Please.
- Please let the number be three.
Kwang Soo has a high chance
of getting the penalty.
Why do I have
so many penalty tickets?
Hey, I have more.
I have the most number
of penalty tickets.
(Out of the 7 of them,
who will receive the penalty?)
I will pick the first digit.
- Please. The 1st digit.
- 3.
2 or 3.
(The first digit...)
(can increase or decrease
the chances of the penalty!)
All right. The first digit.
Please don't let it be one.
(What's the first digit?)
- Two.
- Okay!
(Okay!)
He is set.
I am set. I am safe.
- I have 2 numbers left.
- The 1st digit.
23 and 22.
Haha, you and I have
the same numbers.
- You and I have the same numbers.
- 21 and 22?
Please let it be 3 or 4.
- 3 or 4.
- My numbers are 21 and 22 too.
- Really?
- 3 or 4.
- My numbers are 21 and 22 too.
(Yoon Kyung's numbers are included.)
- 3 or 4.
- Kwang Soo.
Hey.
- No, no.
- You shouldn't celebrate yet.
I thought you were set.
- Okay, okay.
- 3 or 4.
- I picked it.
- Two.
3 or 4.
Please let it be four.
Then no one will be picked.
- 3 or 4.
- Two.
- Bo Pil!
All right.
22.
Kwang Soo is ruined!
(Congratulations on getting chosen.)
- That was quick.
- All right.
Okay, okay.
22.
(Yoon Kyung avoided getting picked
for the penalty!)
- That was quick.
- All right.
(Let's get the penalty together.)
Okay, okay.
- Did you pick it on purpose?
- No, I didn't.
Pick again.
This makes no sense.
- Yoon Kyung, how about you?
- I didn't get picked.
- She has so many tickets.
- Excuse me?
How did that happen?
How did she avoid getting picked?
She is good at games.
- She is the master.
- Yoon Kyung is good at games.
- Okay.
(This is fun.)
Everyone I had hoped for
will receive the penalty.
This makes no sense.
(Kwang Soo's prediction came true.)
2021 New Year
Driving Out Bad Luck Race.
Driving out bad luck.
(Se Chan got exempted
thanks to the Relief Chance.)
1, 2, 3.
(Staggering)
That was incredible.
(The water bomb hit them hard!)
(He looks ugly.)
That was incredible.
That's it!
(Highly satisfied)
(Dry heaving)
(They can't help
but feel overwhelmed.)
That's it.
- That's it.
- I just gargled.
- It was like a disaster movie.
- That's it.
- Thank you for your hard work.
(They drove out their bad luck
for 2021.)
(We thank Eun Jin, Sang Yi,
and Yoon Kyung...)
(for joining the 2021 New Year
Driving Out Bad Luck Race.)
(Running Gym)
(This is the home ground
of the most mischievous members.)
(Will the gym get new visitors?)
(3 guests from "The Penthouse")
(Yoon Jong Hun)
(Park Eun Seok)
(Ha Do Kwon)
(Do Kwon, are you here
to get Jong Kook?)
(I have no greed today.)
(Dual)
(He returns to being
the game-changer right away.)
I just heard
his switch getting flipped on.
(Running Man's
athletic meet starts!)
(Shouts...)
(and theft bombard them
as they get used to the show.)
(Running Man shows them
the harsh variety show environment.)
(The 3 guests go to the dark side.)
(They use upgraded fouls
and adjust to the show!)
(The determined trio...)
(and the mischievous members
of Running Man have a match!)
(Which team will win
the athletic meet?)
(2021 Running Man Neighborhood
Athletic Meet with "The Penthouse")