(A fall morning
with a refreshing breeze)
(Chairs neatly arranged in rows)
(And there's a whiteboard
in the middle.)
(The elevator is coming up
right at the moment.)
- We're here.
- Gosh, what's that?
What is this?
Is it started already?
- I guess we should talk right away.
- What's this?
- What?
- Gosh, what is this for?
Hello.
- This is...
- Should we start talking now?
- What is this?
- Is it started already?
- I want to go home.
- What are we doing?
- Hello.
- What should we do now?
- Hello. What's this?
- We don't have a studio?
By any chance,
is this for my doping test?
What are we doing today?
Is this a press conference or what?
- Hey, that's...
- Is this for my doping test?
- Jong Kook is now...
- It's no joke.
- He's busy taking doping tests.
- Why?
He's an artist.
- Why does he need a doping test?
- I was going to let it slide...
as if it was no big deal.
You know me. I'm going
to throw a big tantrum.
Right.
- We know what you're like.
- You know what?
- It's just that...
- I'll take this to the end.
he doesn't know
much about Jong Kook.
- He picked the wrong person.
- Seriously.
(The YouTuber who criticized
Kim Jong Kook finally apologized.)
(Greg Doucette ultimately takes down
all videos about Kim Jong Kook.)
By the way, Jong Kook, you...
- Stay quiet.
- I'm talking now.
(Let me talk.)
Stay quiet. We're not done yet.
- We need to talk.
- See?
We are still talking.
Just stay quiet.
(Slapping)
He's slapping him.
He probably needs a doping test.
- He needs one.
- He's acting strange.
Will you turn around
and take it off?
This one?
- What is this?
- This is how we begin.
(There's a mysterious whiteboard.)
- What's that?
- What?
(What does it say?)
What do you think of the penalties
on Running Man?
Penalties.
I guess they want an update.
I see.
Penalties on Running Man?
About penalties...
(The history of penalties
for the 11 years of Running Man)
(1st stage: The early years
since 2010)
(Cold and embarrassing
clothes like hot pants in winter)
- Let's go.
- Seriously, I can't.
(2nd stage: From 2015 to 2017)
(Terrifying and thrilling penalties
inside and outside of the country)
(3rd stage: From 2018 to 2019)
(The top 3 penalties including fresh
cream, water canon, and flogging.)
(4th stage: from 2020 until now)
(Tiresome penalties that they should
do after the shoot is over.)
- That sounds horrible.
- Gosh, it's so bothersome.
(For the members
who hate all those penalties...)
It's squeaking.
Penalties for the cast?
(The crew members prepared
this negotiation table.)
Penalties...
What Suk Jin and I did...
- last week...
- What?
It was the worst.
- What did you do?
- Honestly, it was the worst.
(The worst penalty
that Se Chan and Suk Jin got is...)
(Taking a photo of the signpost
that says Gangneung.)
(They had to find a signpost
of Gangneung in Yangpyeong.)
(They spent three hours,
but it was on TV for 3 minutes.)
(They spent a lot of time on it,
but it's not impressive at all.)
Including the time I spent
on my way home,
it took me four hours.
I didn't know what to do with it...
because we didn't know
where the signpost was.
If I was told to go to Gangneung,
I would've slept over.
But that wasn't the case.
Will you say something?
(Will you say something?)
(He forces Jae Suk
to say something.)
- Well...
- Aren't you ready...
Are you ready to listen yet?
Why is everyone
throwing a tantrum today?
- Why are you upset?
- What's wrong with you?
He's being really sensitive.
I can't say anything.
I'm just...
The thing is,
I'm listening to what you say.
You're not listening.
You are smacking your lips...
trying to get at me.
- I'm listening.
- You don't understand.
I think there are penalties...
that we hate...
and penalties that
our viewers want to see.
Exactly.
That's what we need to think about.
I'm sure the crew members
know exactly what we hate.
- They do.
- I hated the book report thing.
I know. It was so annoying.
- It was the worst.
- It's horrible.
I don't know what to write.
Anyway, we hate it
when we get to go home late.
I prefer things that end quickly.
Like a water canon.
Or something
that gives a little pain.
Fresh cream isn't so good.
- I got a text from Aiki earlier.
- What did she say?
That night, she couldn't get rid...
- of the smell of the shaving cream.
- Right.
- Did you get her number?
- I did.
(Ji Hyo got Aiki's number?)
- You did?
- Why?
We became intimate
as we showered together.
- Wow.
- Really?
- That rarely happens to her.
- Aiki's number?
Now you're trying
to start your social life.
- Ji Hyo.
- Finally.
Ji Hyo.
Why do you never shower with me?
- You?
- Why not me?
We showered together many times.
(We showered together many times.)
What kind of conversation is this?
What are they talking about?
Are you sad
that you didn't shower together?
Are you upset?
I see. It wasn't in the same room.
I thought they went
to a bathhouse together.
- It wasn't like that.
- We just washed off the cream.
You're not a man. Why do you want
to go to a bathhouse with her?
- Why are you sad about that?
- It will bring us closer together.
Why are you jealous?
- We can be more intimate.
- More intimate?
You should think about this
when we talk about penalties.
- What?
- If a penalty is too harsh,
we become too competitive...
- as we play games.
- It's not for fun.
It's not for fun.
We only care
about the result of the game.
- It can happen.
- He's right.
You know what I mean.
If we have a harsh penalty,
- We're already competitive.
- it might look...
- more thrilling,
- Right.
- but if it gets worse...
- We might get carried away.
In a word,
- the race itself won't be fun.
- That makes sense.
That's possible.
- Seriously...
- But if it's too soft,
- it's a little...
- It won't be intense.
We might not want to try hard...
when we play games or something.
We won't have a motivation.
When a penalty is too harsh,
- I can say, "Go easy on me."
- By the way,
I'm sorry to say this, but...
I know you're having a hard time
with the doping test, but...
- don't take this the wrong way.
- Okay.
Every time we have a harsh penalty,
the first person to respond is you.
You always say, "Okay."
"It's okay."
- "This isn't about the penalty."
- Exactly.
- "I can do this."
- I guess you're right.
- It can be a motivation.
- What about this?
Why don't we try
something that our viewers want...
It's too soon to propose a solution.
All right.
(It was too soon
to propose a solution.)
- Wait.
- What?
You are right.
Suk Jin talked
only for five seconds today.
Suk Jin, do you want
to switch seats with me?
- Hey.
- Just wait.
You know the process.
I need to hear what Ji Hyo thinks.
- She already spoke.
- No.
- We should go zigzag.
- I need their opinions.
You are taking his side.
What are you talking about?
We have a member who's
on another weekend variety show.
Where does "How Do You Play?"
stand on this issue?
- "How Do You Play?"?
- The opinion of "How Do You Play?"?
- The Saturday show?
- What is he talking about?
(Giggling)
We promised
that we wouldn't talk about it.
We need the opinion
of the Saturday show.
- What?
- He danced a lot...
- in the karaoke room.
- Does "How Do You Play?"...
He kept dancing without a break.
- He danced...
- He never stopped.
I just tried
what I did on Running Man.
You're supposed to do this
only on Running Man.
- Guys.
- Why did you do it on Saturday?
May I weigh in?
The thought of giving a penalty...
If you asked, "May I weigh in?",
then you should wait for our answer.
Exactly. You need our consent.
- Why did you not wait?
- All right.
We have something to talk about.
Do you think Suk Jin may speak?
- Hey, this...
- In three.
- One, two, three.
All right.
I'd like you to wait then.
(They all say no.)
What are you to say that?
He asked our opinions.
You asked it first.
- I did?
- It's you who asked it first.
You could've just said it.
Why did you ask?
I'm strong, you punk!
He's so childish.
The thing is,
I think the crew members are...
being obsessed with penalties.
Think of the episode
that was aired yesterday.
We enjoyed some free time
like a retreat.
With some short skits,
we had a lot of fun.
I don't think we need a penalty
in an episode like that.
It could've ended just like that.
Then are you saying
we shouldn't have a penalty?
- We need it.
- We need a penalty.
It's like sweet and salty food.
- Right.
- That's what I think.
- Sweet and salty?
- Sometimes it can be...
a special event.
- Sometimes, it can be huge.
- That's right.
- Or it can be trivial at times.
- Sure.
When we don't need a penalty,
- Exactly!
- we can skip it.
Only when it's useless.
I think the episode we shot
yesterday didn't need a penalty.
- Hang on. Jae Suk is talking.
- That's a bit...
Will you stay quiet?
Jong Kook, I'm not older than him.
Suk Jin is older.
I get it.
Suk Jin is older than me.
I mean, you were talking.
This isn't about age.
You were leading the conversation,
- but he butted in.
- But Suk Jin is older.
I hate Jong Kook even more.
(So they suggested
various opinions on penalties.)
- Guys.
- Yes.
I appreciate your opinions
on penalties.
Like you said, you've been
on Running Man for 11 years,
so you must have
diverse opinions about penalties.
The crew members also
have their opinions,
and our viewers have theirs.
In order to put the opinions
together, we will have...
2021 Running Man
Penalty Negotiation today.
- Negotiation?
- Negotiation.
- What do we do?
Eight years ago,
you negotiated
with the crew members...
about missions during
the Year-End Settlement Race.
- That's right.
- I remember.
The crew members won,
but they got splashed because of the
youngest producer's mistake.
Right. The water bomb.
That was a long time ago.
I'll show you the video.
- The video.
- What was his name?
- I remember that.
- Right.
I know what this is.
Who was the producer?
(Episode 178 aired in December 2013)
(The members negotiated with
the crew members about missions.)
(The members have a feeling
that they lost.)
(They make their last speech
under the water bomb.)
(The team
whose running ball is picked wins.)
(Who are the winners?)
(Team Crew Members wins.)
Team Crew Members.
My goodness.
I can't believe this.
We lost.
What?
The crew members got splashed.
They were happy, but...
Isn't this the best scene ever?
Why? Whose mistake was that?
- It was our producer.
- The youngest producer.
Our producer?
The one over there.
The team whose ball
is picked wins the race.
But when the crew members'
ball was picked,
- He thought...
- he thought they lost.
It was a miscommunication.
(The director splashed water
on the crew members by mistake.)
(The members
sang together with joy.)
Look at that.
He made a big mistake.
He splashed water
on the crew members.
They went through a lot.
So you will have a negotiation...
- like you did back then.
- With the production crew?
You will have a race
against the production crew...
- for the water bomb penalty.
- Really?
- My gosh.
- That sounds harsh.
The production crew
might get splashed today.
- Today?
- Yes.
- Really?
- It's cold today.
After each mission,
you will get the penalty balls
based on the results.
The team whose ball
is picked will lose.
- The team whose ball is picked.
- You need fewer balls.
It's the production crew versus us.
If you win,
the directors will get splashed.
Starting from next week's episode
and until the end of this year,
you will get to decide
the penalty of each week.
- Really?
- Do we get to decide?
- For ourselves?
- Yes.
- We can pick something simple.
- That's right.
- Something easy.
- We can do that.
And if we win,
you'll get splashed.
And we will decide penalties
for you until the end of this year.
So you should try to get...
fewer penalty balls today.
Here's the mission
to decide the number...
of the first penalty balls.
You will perform the mission,
and its result will decide
the number of penalty balls.
The first mission to decide
the crew members' penalty balls...
- is blowing out candles.
- What?
You will take turns to try it.
You're supposed...
to blow out only 7
out of 10 candles at one go.
If you each succeed, the staff
gets one ball for each success.
- How would we do that?
- So...
if 3 members succeed
in blowing out 7 candles,
- we will get three penalty balls.
- At one go?
- Yes.
- Seven candles?
- That sounds difficult.
- Seven is too much.
At one go?
It's so tempting...
that we can decide
a penalty for ourselves.
We can pick something simple.
- Do you want me to go first?
- Yes.
(Se Chan tries
blowing out 7 candles.)
So Min, can you put your hand
up here to see if I can reach it?
- This isn't easy.
- Over here.
- Next to the third candle.
- Only if it was just thin paper.
No, we have to do this.
I can feel it, but it's too weak.
You should aim at this candle.
It's too low now.
Here I go. I'm ready.
(Here I go. I'm ready.)
- What?
- Blow the candles, please.
It looks as if she's waiting
for her boyfriend.
(Her boyfriend with a pouty mouth
prepared a candle event.)
I'm ready. Here we go.
(Will he succeed in putting out
7 out of 10 candles?)
- What?
- That was too weak.
- Oh, no.
- I knew the flame would come back.
(It looked like he succeeded.)
(But he failed.)
- Fail.
- You should've blown harder.
- Who wants to go next?
- They looked like they were off.
I'll try it.
- What a shame.
- I thought they were off.
- How did the flame come back?
- Don't blow for long.
Just blow hard at once.
- I have a question.
- Don't blow for long.
The rule is to use the air I inhale
in one breath, right?
- I'll block my nose. In one breath.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, why don't you wait
until we all do?
Right. He'll probably do well.
(The active singer seems confident
in controlling exhaling.)
Take a long breath, Jong Kook.
Aim carefully. You might blow
below the flames.
- Wait. Do it in one breath...
- That's not...
- Jong Kook, stop.
- Hey.
Jong Kook, hold on.
(Exhaling repeatedly)
- Stop. We need a doping test.
- You should do it in one breath.
It's okay as long as I use the air
I inhale in one breath.
- You can exhale only one time.
- Oh, in one go?
- I was mistaken.
- Give him another chance.
I mean... Gosh, I'm dizzy.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- I thought...
- that I could...
- This isn't like you.
Wouldn't it be okay
as long as I don't inhale again?
- No, you should exhale only once.
- This isn't like you.
- You looked really sly.
- Jong Kook.
Taking a long breath helps
to blow out many candles.
Breathe longer than you think
you should.
(Spitting while blowing)
- That was just gross.
- Gosh, seriously.
Why would you spit?
Jong Kook, what's with you?
- He put out only 3 of them.
- He should've put out 7.
- What was that?
- Exactly.
- Why couldn't he blow harder?
- Oh, dear.
- Fail.
- So Min, you're up next.
- I tried to blow hard.
- I'll give it a try.
I used up all the air too quickly
because I blew hard.
- I think...
- Breathe out like the wind blows.
- that Se Chan's way was better.
- You shouldn't exhale quickly.
- Make sure to exhale hard.
- He's right. Exhale hard.
- You should do it in one breath.
- Blow at once like this.
- Blow at once.
- Right. I think that's better.
Don't get too close.
You might burn your nose hair.
Be careful. You might burn
your pleather jacket.
- You might burn another one.
- You don't want to burn it.
- I'm ready.
- Go ahead.
- I'll do my best.
- Don't get too close.
- Your hair might catch on fire.
- You might burn your nose hair.
- She failed. I get it now.
- Fail.
You should never slow down.
- You should keep blowing hard.
- Exactly.
- You shouldn't try to control it.
- I almost made it through.
I put out five candles.
- I'll go next. Gosh.
- You did a good job.
- Blow hard enough to put all out.
- So Min did a good job.
- I'll do it.
- Jae Suk, let me try this time.
- Sure. Go ahead.
- She wants to go first.
- She never volunteered to go first.
- Oh, my. I feel...
- Ji Hyo.
- Aim to put all out.
- I almost cried.
- Hey.
- She volunteered enthusiastically.
- Exactly.
She has never stopped me
to try something before me.
- Yes, this is her first time.
- She has changed.
Ji Hyo, I'm impressed.
- She's changed.
- Aim to blow out all ten of them.
(Ji Hyo volunteered to go next.
How many candles will she put out?)
- She made it!
- She put out seven of them!
(Ji Hyo succeeded in blowing out
7 candles.)
(Ji Hyo, great job!)
(Disappointed)
- Great job.
- What's wrong?
- Hey, you succeeded.
- You made it.
- You did well.
- You won.
I think she was going to
put all candles out.
- You made it.
- The goal is to put out seven.
- Really? Did I win?
- You made it.
- Oh, my. I made it.
- You succeeded.
- I thought I had to put all out.
- Did you think they were seven?
- Yes. That's what I thought.
- She was amazing.
She took us by surprise again.
- I guess...
- She pulled it off.
Ji Hyo, I see that you stopped me
for a reason.
- She's good at everything.
- That was amazing.
There's a lesson we should learn
from this.
Ji Hyo made it because she aimed
to put out all of them.
- One person succeeded so far.
- I thought I had to put all out.
- All of them, right?
- Ji Hyo, you're amazing.
It worked because she aimed
to put out all of them.
- Ji Hyo, great job.
- Yes? Thanks.
- Jae Suk, aim to put all out.
- She's incredible.
I'm sorry, but you already said it
several times.
- But it's important, you know.
- We all heard you.
Hey, don't forget to aim to put out
all of them.
See? You just repeated it again.
I wonder if it's hard for him
to aim properly.
- Maybe, because of his pouty mouth.
- Exactly.
- And his mouth is a bit crooked.
- Aim to put all out in one breath.
- I see that his mouth is crooked.
- Yes. Just a little bit.
- Shape your mouth like this.
- Jae Suk, blow them like this.
(Crooked)
(Slanted)
- Why?
- Because your mouth is crooked.
He has uneven teeth. That's all.
Uneven teeth won't affect
how I do this.
- Jae Suk, try this.
- I promise you.
He looks serious.
He acts so confidently,
but he's never
succeeded in the past 11 years.
- Am I not right?
- He acts like he knows everything.
- Right. He's so arrogant.
- Like an expert.
- "I'm a pro at this, you guys."
- Listen, guys. A game like this...
But once his turn comes,
he starts shaking.
He shakes like crazy.
- I saw him shaking there just now.
- He gets nervous.
Don't worry about it.
Just let it burn. What?
(He turned his cap around
like a cute little boy!)
- Just let it burn.
- Right.
- Jae Suk, get closer.
- That's enough.
- That's close enough.
- You can get closer than that.
(Will the playful Jae Suk succeed?)
- Yes!
- What's that?
- I can't believe this.
(Upset)
- What's that?
- I can't believe this.
- Look at this.
- That's impossible.
- What happened?
- It's because of your uneven teeth.
- It's because they're crooked.
- Right. Jae Suk.
- The air went around this one.
- Like a curveball.
- Then it hit the one behind it.
- Gosh.
- How come that one was skipped?
- The air curved around it.
- How did this happen?
- It can't be done.
I stopped breathing out
not to put out more than enough.
- It's because of his uneven teeth.
- This is unbelievable.
Hey, stop it already.
Jae Suk, shouldn't this
be considered a success?
Shouldn't this be considered
a success?
- You put out more than seven.
- That's right.
Gosh. What a shame.
He would've succeeded
had he had even teeth.
I almost succeeded.
Your mouth should be up here. Good.
Dong Hoon, get closer.
- That's good. Nice.
- Good.
Be careful not to burn
your mustache.
- Burn your mustache.
- I want him to burn it.
- Get closer and squat down.
- I'm telling you...
- One, two, three. Good. Closer.
- Haha.
If you slack off on this show,
I'll teach you a lesson.
He drives me crazy.
Gosh. I can't believe him.
- He must be so passionate there.
- Hey.
- He says the same thing there.
- Jae Suk.
He repeats the same thing
on both shows.
- I just warned him.
- I'm glad you did.
- He's on both shows just like me!
- Haha.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- I'll slap you in the face.
- Haha.
- Hey, Haha.
Haha, Mi Joo told me
that you had called her...
- to ask her to drink with you.
- That hurts my feelings.
- You never call us.
- You've never asked us that.
- It was a team dinner.
- We drank with the whole team.
- Was it a team dinner?
- We'll drink together tonight.
- Anyway, you called her...
- Was it really a team dinner?
Haha, you talk to her on the phone?
You never call me.
- Okay. I get it.
- You punk, we talked two days ago.
- He never calls you either, right?
- It's true.
- This is driving me nuts.
- What's wrong with you?
Did I call you or not?
- Focus on the game.
- Why would you yell at Se Chan?
What are you doing, old man?
(The old man who tried to do it
has been kicked out.)
Aim to put out all of them.
Get closer than that.
- I'm warning you. Stay focused.
- Get closer.
Get as close as you are
to "How Do You Play?".
- Get closer.
- As close as you are to MBC.
Get as close as you can.
- Get close, will you?
Go on. Closer.
- As close as you can get.
- Good.
If he were on "How Do You Play?",
he would put his lips on the flame.
(He would put his lips
on the flame.)
- You go first.
- Hey, stop.
- Haha, come back.
- What's the matter?
- Haha, stop.
- I can't put up with this anymore.
- Come on, Haha.
- Hey.
- It's okay.
- Let go of me!
- You can get through this.
- Go back there right now.
- You should overcome this.
- Be professional.
- What's the matter with you?
- What's wrong?
Overcome this.
- That wasn't professional. Okay?
- Get over it.
- That was hilarious.
- Gosh, that punk.
He's mentally weak.
- You can do this.
- Get close.
Good. That's perfect.
- Blow harder than you think.
- Exactly.
- Blow as hard as you can.
- Go ahead.
- I think he'll make it.
- Blow hard at once.
I wonder if he has
good lung capacity.
(He blew!)
- Oh, my.
- Great.
- Stop.
- Oh, I think...
(Did he succeed?)
(Did he fail?)
- Stop. Yes!
- Oh, I think...
(He succeeded in putting out
7 candles.)
(Shouting)
- Running Man!
- Good job.
Chief Director Choi Young In!
- Did you just drop the honorifics?
- Did you?
- Did he?
- Ma'am!
(I love SBS.)
- That was great. Good job.
- He made it.
- Great job.
- You made it.
Dong Hoon, you did a good job.
- That was great.
- My business partner, good job.
- Great job.
- He made it.
- You made it, Haha.
- That was good.
- Good job, Haha.
- That was funny.
- He proved us wrong.
- He did a great job.
By the way, I didn't think
I could make it.
- Under so much pressure...
- See?
- You made it as you stayed focused.
- You proved yourself.
He's the last one.
You obtained two so far.
(They got 2 penalty balls
thanks to Ji Hyo and Haha.)
- Great.
- What?
(And this is their last chance.
Will Suk Jin succeed?)
(He put out 8 candles!)
- You did great.
- He put out too many candles.
- But he did well.
- Yes.
- He put out eight candles.
- I see that he's very healthy.
- That was close.
- Oh, gosh.
- I almost made it.
- You did well.
- I guess I have bad lung capacity.
- Great job, Suk Jin.
As a result, the staff has
two penalty balls now.
Didn't we get three?
- Only two of us succeeded.
- Okay.
Now, you're going to play a game
to decide...
the number of penalty balls for you.
It'll probably be harder than this.
- I wish we'd gotten one more ball.
- Exactly.
The game you'll play to decide
your penalty balls is...
Tail Catching Game.
- What's that?
- Tail Catching Game?
- Whose tail do we catch?
- Starting here, the seven of you...
go in and come out of
the three waiting rooms.
- It's a simple game.
- Yes.
You have 30 seconds to finish.
- What? We have only 30 seconds?
- Before you leave,
the first one in the line
presses that button.
- It won't be easy.
- To start the stopwatch.
Then the 1st one opens the door,
and you all go into the 1st room.
The last one closes the door.
Next, you come back out of the room.
- And you move to the second room.
- I understand.
Close the door when all of you go in
and open it when you come out.
Then move to the third room.
When you come back here,
the last one...
stops the stopwatch.
That's how you measure time.
The first and the last ones play
the most important roles.
- I agree.
- The first and the last ones.
- I'm not confident.
- Everyone.
You can go ahead and look around
before we set up cameras.
- Look around the three rooms.
- Let's go.
I'm sure they made it hard
for us to move around in there.
- Wouldn't you agree?
- Of course.
- I think...
- By the way,
- do we have to hold one another?
- It's hard to finish in 30 seconds.
- We have only 30 seconds.
- Exactly. It'll be hard.
- We go into the room.
- We enter the room.
- Open the door. We all go in.
- All of us come in.
- Go on in, everyone.
- Close it when we're all in here.
- The last one comes in.
- How about we turn to the right?
- The last one.
- No, the first one should...
- stand here.
- Exactly. The first one stays here.
- The rest of us come in.
- Then the others come in.
The first one closes the door
and opens it right away.
The last one should close it
when we leave the room.
Like this.
You know what I mean, right?
- Got it.
- Okay. Stay close to one another.
- We don't have to close this door.
- You have to.
- Do we have to close it too?
- Yes, you have to close it too.
We have to close this door too?
- We have to close this door too.
- But have you tried this?
- Yes, we have.
- No way.
- And they shortened the time limit.
- How much time do we have?
- You have 30 seconds.
- We can do this.
If you succeed
at your first attempt,
- you won't get any penalty balls.
- Okay.
After your first try, you get
a penalty ball every time you fail.
- Okay.
- Remember who's in front of you.
Guys, let's succeed
at our first try.
- Let's finish it in one go.
- We've got this.
- This requires good teamwork.
- Okay.
We have to move fast.
Let's keep this door open.
- Let's show them what we've got.
- Here we go.
- Open it right away.
- Let's go.
- Get ready.
- Just a second.
Ready.
Suk Jin, you must run fast.
Don't push me, okay?
Push him. We need to move fast.
- One, two...
- Be careful not to fall down.
- We should run fast.
- Here we go. Ready. Get set.
(Go.)
- Let's go.
- Move. Hurry up.
Move fast.
- Let's go.
- Move. Hurry up.
- Move fast. Hurry.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Hurry up.
(Everyone entered the 1st room
in only 6 seconds.)
- Go on.
- Open the door.
(Jae Suk falls down.)
- Run.
- Get up. What are you doing?
- Come on. Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- Hurry up!
- I can't believe him.
- Where is he?
- Open the door!
(Time kept passing
until Jae Suk got back up.)
- Hurry up!
- Where are you?
- What are you doing? Run.
- Hurry up and come on in.
(They came out of the 2nd room,
and 20 seconds passed already.)
Hurry up. Move fast.
- Gosh.
- Run. Go.
- Keep going.
- I think we can make it.
- We can make it.
- Hurry.
Let's go.
- You should press the button.
- I know.
(They're moving from the 3rd room
to the finishing point.)
- You should press the button.
- Run. Hurry.
- Hurry up and come on in.
- Press it.
(Less than 1 second is remaining.)
(Jong Kook, the last runner, must
press the buzzer.)
- Hurry up and come on in.
- Press it.
(Their record is 29.61 seconds.)
(They succeeded
at their first attempt.)
- We made it.
- Why did you fall down?
- This is Running Man!
- Okay.
- We are Running Man!
- I'm excited.
- You know...
- I can't believe we did it.
- I even fell down once.
- We did it.
- I mean, Jong Kook wouldn't come.
- Amazing.
(Move fast. Hurry up.)
(Hurry up. Gosh.)
(Get up. What are you doing?)
(The average of the staff's records
was 33 seconds.)
(The cast members' record is
29.61 seconds.)
That was amazing.
- Awesome.
- We did a great job.
- That's how fast we are.
- With only 0.39 seconds remaining,
you barely made it.
- Yes!
- Okay!
Guys, we wouldn't have made it
if this was "How Do You Play?".
Great.
You did much better
than we expected.
We thought you'd fail
at least three times.
- We were so cool.
- We did an amazing job.
- Didn't we do well?
- Yes, you did.
Anyway, you didn't get
any penalty balls.
- I was so surprised.
- We did great. I was surprised too.
- Now...
we'll move to another location
for your first mission.
Before that,
I have a question for you guys.
- Go ahead.
- Which three of you...
do you think have
the most common knowledge?
- Jae Suk,
- Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin, and Jong Kook.
- Suk Jin and Jong Kook.
I wouldn't say I'm in the top three.
Then who is the ace among the rest?
- It's definitely me.
- I don't want to admit it,
- but it's Haha.
- Haha is the ace.
You can put it to a national vote.
- I agree. It wouldn't be me.
- I understand.
We'll prepare the first mission
based on your answers.
- Okay.
- Change your clothes and come back.
- Will it be a quiz game?
- Let's go.
(Running Study Room is waiting
for the cast members.)
I guess we're going to study again.
Look at that. My gosh.
I hated going to the library
when I was in school.
- It makes me feel sick.
- Gosh.
I feel sick already.
I can't do this.
- I can't breathe.
- I won't play this game.
It never affected my life...
- although I didn't study.
- I won't do it. We have four.
We have four aces. Don't worry.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
I see we'll study. I'm frustrated.
- I asked you a question earlier.
- Are we going to take an exam?
- Three, one, and three people.
- Yes.
- I think we'll have a match.
- In your first mission,
the empty heads have to do well...
to give the staff
more penalty balls.
It's Running Man Quiz Championship.
- I knew it.
- You're the ace.
- Did they leave us out?
- Thirty minutes later,
the three empty heads will
play a quiz game.
The staff will get a penalty ball
for each question they get right.
And you'll get a penalty ball
for each question they get wrong.
Only when they all get it right,
it counts as the correct answer.
- All three of them?
- Yes.
- That's too much.
- But...
We'll give them
elementary school level questions.
- Is it for fifth grade?
- I hated social studies.
I hated all subjects.
- Elementary school level questions?
- However,
since Haha is the ace
of the empty heads,
they can use the Haha chance card
three times.
(Haha with a master's degree,
the ace of empty heads)
Thank you, Haha. You're so cool.
- When the three empty heads...
- He's the ace.
request for the Haha chance card
after hearing the keyword,
or if Haha thinks he can get
a correct answer,
- Haha gets to answer the question.
- That's great.
Then what are we going to do?
I'm sure you don't know...
- where to start with the quiz.
- Indeed.
For the next 30 minutes,
these three members will...
- give you a 1 on 1 lesson.
- Oh, I see.
Teach them what's in the book...
and predict the questions for them.
This is great. I'm glad
you let us be their tutors.
- A quiz on a variety show...
- I'm worried.
- I mean, the way of studying...
- Is it different?
for a variety show is different.
Also, we made the questions
just as you see in the book.
- I want to study alone.
- Just as it is written in the book?
- I wonder which one will teach me.
- Can't you make it confusing?
In brief, we're going to be
their private tutors.
- That's right.
- Now, you have to...
- It's difficult.
- Indeed.
- I didn't study social studies.
- Do you know the five duties?
I gave up on the subject
when I was six.
Three of you, choose your tutors.
- It's not that difficult.
- Will one of us study alone?
- Haha will study alone.
- Oh, I see.
I don't think any of them can
teach me.
- Let's begin.
- I gave up on all subjects.
If only one of you fails to get
the correct answer, you all fail.
- We can't let that happen.
- They all should know the answers.
- All of you should study hard.
- Absolutely.
- Right.
- Before deciding, Suk Jin is...
(She can't seem to continue.)
- I'll be a kind tutor.
- I don't want him to be my tutor.
- Why?
- Of course.
- It's because...
- I'll be a kind tutor.
- What's the reason?
- I'm pretty sure he'll get angry...
- the entire time.
- I won't get upset.
I won't lose my temper.
- I think he'll get upset.
- I won't.
Whoever it may be,
- Your student?
- I promise...
- I'll tell you only the key points.
- Let's draw lots.
I prefer that way.
I can learn the key points.
- Only the key points.
- I don't need anything else.
- I can't even memorize them.
- Let's hear Mr. Gym out.
- Mr. Gym.
- I'll hit you while teaching you.
Would you hit one of the ladies too?
Of course not.
That's why I choose you.
- But you know...
- His teaching method suits me.
I made my choice.
I'll teach Se Chan.
Okay.
- Jong Kook, choose your student.
- Your method suits me.
- Me?
- He'll probably choose Ji Hyo.
My goodness.
All right. Let's go.
(He made a brief
but romantic comment.)
(Cheering passionately)
- Why would you be so excited?
- Then...
- It didn't mean anything.
- I mean...
- I'm just teaching her.
- Trust me.
- I didn't mean it like that.
- He'll help me study. That's all.
Did you see Ji Hyo's reaction
when he chose her?
(Smiling happily)
- My goodness.
- So Min.
- I won't get angry at you.
- You guys are so funny.
- I promise you.
- Suk Jin is So Min's tutor.
- Why do you think I'll do that?
- Okay.
- I'll be a kind tutor.
- Let's go.
- I'll be gentle.
- Where should we sit?
- Where is our desk?
- Let's sit down.
- This is my desk.
- Shall we begin?
Teacher, what should I begin with?
Come and sit down.
You have a lot to cover.
It's too much. Where should I begin?
That's why we need to cover
only the key points.
You know what "national territory"
means, right?
- The land owned by our country?
- Correct. It means...
- the land that belongs to a nation.
- Yes.
- What's this?
- Which one?
It says to find our country's
national territory.
- This is Asia.
- Yes.
- Korea is in the Asian continent.
Exactly where are we?
Did you guys hear what he said?
"This is Asia."
(This is Asia.)
(The first thing he taught Se Chan
was the location of Asia.)
- Se Chan, do you understand?
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- This is Asia.
- Asia.
What are continents?
(What are continents?)
"A large mass of land on earth..."
These are continents.
- The whole land?
- Yes.
What is a peninsula?
(What is a peninsula?)
- The ocean?
- Yes.
It's surrounded by the ocean
on three sides.
- On three sides?
- Look at this.
- Yes.
- Korea is a peninsula.
- It's called the Korean Peninsula.
- The Korean Peninsula.
- You can memorize it that way.
- I see.
- Okay.
- South Korea is here.
Correct. Since these are easy,
let's start with them.
Jong Kook, do you think
this will be in the quiz?
"Administrative Districts Puzzle"?
Tell me if I'm right. Seoul is...
- Seoul Special City.
- It's the capital Special city.
- Daegu Special City,
- Right.
Busan Special City,
Gwangju Special City...
Wait. Isn't Busan
a metropolitan city?
Oh, right. Seoul Special City,
Busan Metropolitan City,
Daegu Metropolitan City.
That's correct. You're doing great.
- Here are the duties.
- Sorry?
"Let's learn about the duties
of citizens in the constitution."
- "Tax liability".
- Wait. Hold on.
- Stop. Take it easy.
- "Basic education".
- Sorry?
- Tax liability.
TEW.
- "TEW"?
- Tax, education,
- and work.
- It's not TEW. It should be WET.
- "WET"?
- WET.
- "Work, educate, and tax."
- Duty to work.
WET. "Work, educate, and tax."
- The fundamental duties...
- Listen to me.
written in the constitution...
- I'm your tutor.
- There's military duty too.
- Listen to me.
- There are five of them.
- Hold on. I'll give you...
- Military duty.
- expected questions.
- Okay.
- This will be in the quiz for sure.
- What is it?
This will definitely be in the quiz.
- You see, the constitution...
- Check this out.
What is latitude?
- What's latitude?
- Sorry? North of the equator...
is called north latitude
and south of it is south latitude.
Oh, this is what latitude means.
Look, Suk Jin.
- This is the earth.
- Memorize "prime meridian".
- That's latitude. That's longitude.
- Yes.
You need to memorize
what will likely be in the quiz.
The questions won't be that simple.
Memorize "prime meridian".
"The reference line for longitude"?
- Which line is it?
- "Prime meridian".
It's called "prime meridian".
Just memorize it.
Study what could be in the quiz.
Suk Jin,
you're supposed to teach me,
- not to study yourself.
- I'm telling you what to memorize.
What was it again?
What is the reference line
for the longitude?
Prime medium.
It's "meridian", not "medium".
- "Meridian".
- Prime meridian.
- Good. "Meridian".
- "Meridian".
- Prime meridian.
See? I'm giving you
expected questions.
- You gave me two questions so far.
- Yes.
"My parents and my siblings..."
Hold on.
(Meanwhile,
Ace Empty Head is studying alone.)
(He uses a notepad as well.)
Gyeongpodae Pavilion... And azaleas.
Azaleas and the sound of cicadas.
I don't have to memorize the rest.
(He absorbed the knowledge.)
That's all I need to know.
- The thing is...
- Check this out.
The Asian Highway.
Are you going to ask about that?
The Asian Highway. Turkey and...
What is the line
that indicates the same temperature?
- An isotherm.
- That's right.
"Therm" in thermometer
and "therm" in isotherm.
- An isotherm.
My back is warm.
- The same temperature.
- An isotherm.
A line is drawn
to indicate the same temperature.
That is called an isotherm.
- This will surely be asked.
- What is it?
They will surely ask this.
High ground level house.
- What's that?
- Just look.
Why would a house
take on this shape?
- So that it won't be flooded?
- Exactly.
Compared to other areas...
- Because it rains in the summer?
- The house can be flooded.
- So on higher ground.
- Right. What is this called again?
A high ground level house.
What is the line that indicates...
the same temperature?
- An ondol?
- What is that line called?
The longitude?
- No, an isotherm.
- Oh, right.
(An isotherm)
- An isotherm.
- Right, an isotherm.
- That's right.
- An isotherm.
- Right.
- You know Bang Jeong Hwan, right?
- I don't.
(Admits proudly)
Bang Jeong Hwan. Who is he?
Please tell me.
He established Children's Day.
Mr. Bang Jeong Hwan.
Children's Day.
(May 5, Children's Day,
a day of innocent fun)
So that's his name. Children's Day.
Who wrote
"The Tale of Hong Gil Dong"?
(Who wrote
"The Tale of Hong Gil Dong"?)
- "The Tale of Hong Gil Dong".
- Hohyeonghoje.
(Hohyeonghoje!)
(Giggling)
Not being able to say
that his father is his father.
Was that what you were getting at?
That's not the case.
Hohyeonghoje means...
a close friendship.
That's what hohyeonghoje means.
- You know...
- Bang Jeong Hwan, Children's Day.
- "The Tale of Hong Gil Dong"...
- The writer.
Who wrote it?
- Heo Gyun.
- Right, Heo Gyun.
Heo Gyun. It's like Heo Jun, right?
Hey, an isotherm.
- What's that?
- It's this.
- The same temperature.
- The same temperature?
The prefix "iso" means equal.
- The same temperature...
- From 20 to 50 degrees.
- I'm explaining what it is.
- An isotherm.
The middle latitudes.
From 20 degrees to 50 degrees.
- You have three minutes left.
- Say that again?
- Three minutes.
- Hold on a second.
Crude oil.
Crude oil as in gasoline.
I don't think my brain
can process more.
No, don't think like that.
The heavy chemical industry.
I'm hungry.
How can you even
think that right now?
All three of them
must answer correctly.
That's the catch here.
- Those abandoned...
- Memorize what you wrote.
The 5 rights and 5 duties.
To be equal, to request...
- To be equal, to request...
- Keep memorizing that.
Please take your seats.
I had to brush up on everything.
Everybody...
including the tutors.
Your time is up.
Please take your seats.
- Sovereignty...
- Jong Kook!
- The land.
- That's it.
Promise me you'll do well.
My brain is packed with information.
Please take your seats.
- Your time is up.
- They'll ask what I didn't study.
You can't possibly know everything.
- However, you read the whole book.
- It would be impossible.
No one can know all this.
Article one.
The Republic of Korea
shall be a democratic republic.
The sovereignty of
the Republic of Korea...
shall reside in the people,
and all state authority
shall emanate from the people.
Do you even know what you recited?
I don't know.
Article one of the Constitution?
We're doomed since
all three must answer correctly.
Let your conscience
stop you from cheating.
All right.
I'll tell you the keyword first.
Upon hearing that,
Haha may use his chance cards
for 3 out of 15 questions.
I forgot it all.
- I forgot everything too.
- I...
The first category is...
Okay.
Map.
Yes, map. We studied a lot of them.
- You knew a lot of the basics.
- I didn't study though.
Here's the first question.
Ji Hyo has basic knowledge
when it comes to maps.
Her generation is used to maps.
- On a climatic map...
- What?
On a climatic map,
what is the line that indicates
the same temperature?
- We went over this!
- No clues are allowed.
What is the line that indicates
the same temperature?
We went over this!
No clues are allowed.
I'm sure they'll ask this.
A line that indicates
the same temperature.
- I said they'd ask this.
- What did you say?
- Am I a genius or what?
- On a climatic map,
what is the line that indicates
the same temperature?
What did I tell you?
- Can you please sit still?
- On a climatic map,
what is the line that indicates
the same temperature?
Toss it over to me
if you don't know.
They lost their chance to do that.
Can't they decide
after hearing the question?
No, only after hearing the keyword.
- Only So Min will know this.
- You'll get five seconds.
- Is this correct?
- Five seconds.
I reminded you...
- right before you sat down.
- Five,
- four...
- This was in the book.
- Three...
- This...
- Two...
- This one...
- You know what it is, right?
- One!
Please lift up your answers.
It's an isotherm of course.
- Please lift up your answers.
- An isotherm?
- It's an isotherm of course.
- That's right.
(Even Ssaebssaeb who was unsure
got it right.)
- Ji Hyo...
- An isotherm?
- Gosh.
- Ji Hyo wrote...
the equator which is wrong.
(Incorrect!)
Is isotherm the right answer?
- I reminded you before you sat.
- An isotherm!
- But she got it wrong.
- What did I tell you?
You didn't teach me this.
- Ji Hyo, why...
- You said it'd be easy.
We didn't go over the isotherm.
- Why not?
- We just didn't.
I didn't know.
- An isotherm...
- We had to rush past it.
But Mr. Gym...
- Seriously?
- Sorry.
- We didn't study that.
- How could you not?
- We didn't study it.
- It was the obvious choice.
I should've told you.
- Check it out.
- Good job.
- All right.
- I have isotherm written down.
- Stop it, will you?
- Exactly.
- Then...
- You're only a tutor for the day.
The next category...
is the law.
- The law?
- This I can answer.
- The law? You've got this.
- I can answer it too.
- You've got this,
- Ji Hyo.
- Hold on a second.
- Without interferences of others...
- This I know.
What do you call the authority
of a state to govern itself?
- This I know.
- We studied this.
Hold on a second.
The right to make your own choices.
- I kept telling you this.
- So Min,
- you kept mentioning this.
- We all did.
- Just a second.
- You can't give them clues.
We went over this.
- Just a second.
- You have five seconds!
- This kept coming up.
- So Min, you did this, remember?
It kept coming up.
- I said it earlier.
- The right.
I mentioned this.
- Two...
- This...
Just a second.
I'm sorry, but hold on.
- This is an easy one.
- You can't say it out loud.
- Three, two...
- Is this right?
- Is it?
- One.
- Lift up your answers.
- I taught her well.
- Seriously?
- My gosh!
- Lift up your answers.
- Restrictions?
- He's a great tutor.
- Seriously?
- Sovereignty.
- It's sovereignty.
A right. Sovereignty.
- Lift up your answers.
- Restrictions?
He's a great tutor.
- Seriously?
- My gosh!
A right. Sovereignty.
Sovereignty!
- Se Chan, we went over this.
- Why didn't you answer instead?
- You get three chances.
- Sovereignty!
This they should know.
How can they not know this?
- Se Chan, we went over this.
- I said it was a right.
- Unbelievable.
- Sovereignty?
- We went over it.
- But...
- I apologize.
- The sovereignty...
It's about time I intervened.
I was thinking of the word hinge.
The third category...
is famous people.
- I'm in!
- You've got this.
We three should at least
get one question right.
- Let's do this.
- You know the four names.
We went over them all.
Let it be those three.
You've got this.
I'm more worried about Se Chan.
- Let's do this.
- You know the four names.
- Let's answer this correctly.
- Here we go.
- Against race discrimination...
- Okay, this is a done deal.
(Okay!)
- Ji Hyo, you know this.
- Who gave a speech about...
humans having the same rights
regardless of skin color?
- You mentioned this.
- She knows this.
Martin Lucer King.
It's "th" not "c."
Martin Luther King.
(The answer: Martin Luther King)
- You said it yourself.
- I told you about this.
- You know this.
- That's right.
- We went over this.
Of course, they'd ask this.
- Se Chan, I told you about him.
- All right.
You even repeated the name.
- You said it yourself.
- Ji Hyo knows this.
- You're the best.
- What did I tell you?
- Of course, they'd ask about him.
Two, three.
- Martin Luther King.
- Nice!
- Three.
- Is it Martin Luther King?
- Nice!
- Nicely done!
(The Three Empty Heads
all answer correctly!)
(She remembered the "th" sound.)
- Martin Luther King.
- Okay.
So Min, how am I for a tutor?
- I guessed every single one.
- It's as you said.
- Right?
- Jae Suk guessed...
the questions correctly too.
Here's the next category.
We can't afford
any more penalty balls.
Here's the next question.
The category is...
index.
What's an index?
I studied this earlier.
(Even the category
has them baffled.)
- I think I can answer this.
- An index?
- I don't know.
- Could it be...
- Haha...
- He has better chances.
- Yes, you have better chances.
- I agree.
- You should answer this one.
- I'm pretty sure...
that one of them
will answer incorrectly.
Here we go.
We should use Haha wisely.
I knew all the answers up until now.
A number of people living
in a unit of area...
that measures its density.
- You know this.
- We studied this, remember?
One doesn't have to study
to know this.
- Exactly.
- You know what this is.
Use the words he just said.
- The answer lies in the question.
- Exactly.
Can you repeat the question?
- The answer lies in the question.
- Exactly.
- Can you repeat the question?
- The number of people...
What measures the density of people
in a unit?
- Haha, are you ready?
- Haha...
Okay, he knows this.
- It's hard to think of.
- But this...
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- Yes!
- That's the one!
That is correct.
(Haha gets it right.)
Who knew it'd be this easy?
- The answer was in the question.
- I'm glad we turned to Haha.
Here's the next question.
To prevent...
- houses from being flooded...
- I know this one.
due to summer rain,
this type of house was built
on higher ground.
- Hold on.
- I think I know.
- I wouldn't have known this.
- You studied this.
You memorized this earlier.
It's four syllables.
Give me a second.
- I'll give you five seconds.
- Hold on!
- It's four syllables.
- This is bad.
Can I stick to three syllables?
No, you should write down
the correct answer.
Just three syllables?
- If it's three syllables...
- Se Chan,
- you know this one.
- He should write down the answer.
I mentioned this.
"Can I stick to three syllables?"
- Then it wouldn't be the answer.
- I mentioned this.
- All right.
- Let me try again.
Don't you remember the photo?
The house is on higher ground.
- That's right.
- All right.
- You repeated this.
- Three.
Two...
(Will they all have
the correct answer again?)
One. Show us your answers.
Is it high ground level house?
(Se Chan got it right!)
High ground level house.
It's all right.
- High ground?
- You did well.
- That's where you build it.
- What's the answer?
Isn't it high ground level site?
Seriously?
The answer is
high ground level house.
(Only Se Chan gets it right
which means they fail.)
(Jae Suk couldn't be prouder.)
Is it a competition
between tutors too?
How did he memorize that?
- High ground level house...
- The tutors go head-to-head.
How did I remember this?
The tutors...
I couldn't remember
the first syllable.
(The tutors' moods shift
depending on the answers.)
(Jae Suk is really proud of him.)
It's okay. It's not the area
you focused on.
Mr. Gym.
Your student is falling behind.
No, she's not!
Your student got it wrong too!
No, at least she got
the first letter right.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Your student memorized it herself.
You managed to memorize it.
But this doesn't look like
a team game.
It looks like a battle
between the teachers.
- But it's...
- No, that's not it.
She learned it herself.
- Mr. Gym.
- You didn't teach her that.
It feels so rewarding
to be a teacher.
When your student does well,
- it makes me feel great.
- Why would you feel great?
- You can do it!
- All three of them should get it.
- He's doing so well.
- You're only thinking of him.
- Ji Hyo has her own strengths.
- My student...
My student memorized
the answer I told him.
- Let's do this!
- And he got the answer.
- Well done.
- I did memorize it.
- Ji Hyo, it's okay.
- I should stop my family...
from watching this episode.
This is driving me crazy.
Here's the sixth question.
- The keyword is geography.
- Geography?
- You're good with geography, right?
- You studied this area.
- Yes, I am.
- You're good with geography.
- Geography?
- She's good with geography.
Se Chan, you covered everything.
You went over it all.
- Geography? Bring it on.
- Let's do this.
Let's do it.
What is the highway that connects
Asia and Europe called?
- See? We covered this.
- You know the answer, right?
We covered it earlier.
(What is the highway that connects
Asia and Europe called?)
(Se Chan writes down the answer
as soon as he hears it.)
We covered it earlier!
- Se Chan! We covered this!
- We covered it earlier.
My gosh, quizzes are fun...
when you know the answer.
- He just realized it.
- Quizzes are fun!
- I mean...
- Hey.
Oh, it's called the Asian Highway?
- What's that?
- The Asian Highway.
The answer
is in the question itself.
- Can you repeat the question?
- Hold on.
What is the highway that connects
Asia and Europe called?
(The Asian Highway)
I repeatedly told her this.
- I kept telling this to her.
- She can't remember it.
My gosh, Se Chan. You might
make it to SNU at this rate.
- In 3, 2...
- What's the question again?
- It connects Asia and Europe.
- Open.
- No, that's not it.
- What was that?
- Hey!
What was that?
(So Min didn't write anything,
and Se Chan forgot to add an N.)
What was that?
(What did Ji Hyo write?)
- Ji Hyo.
- She wrote only highway.
There's another word before it.
- "High-pass"?
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. She's...
- I wrote "highway" at first!
- She got a lot funnier.
- What was that?
- "High-pass"?
- Hey!
- She got a lot funnier.
- What did she write?
- You became a lot funnier.
- The answer is the Asian Highway?
My gosh, she's...
But isn't "high-pass"
too far-fetched?
- Jong Kook.
- Wait.
- My gosh.
- She got a lot funnier.
- She's incredible.
- So is the answer "highway"?
- I was right.
- It is highway.
- I thought it was "Asia" highway.
- Oh, it's the Asian Highway?
Se Chan is better than the others.
It's my first time getting answers
quickly during a quiz.
I even wrote the answer before
he finished reading the question.
- Even before...
- Before the question ended.
- I got the answer right away.
- Se Chan, do you see it now?
- You wrote it like this.
- Do you see it now?
This is why we must learn
from the first-tier teacher!
- That's right.
- You remember the word "highway".
Yes, but that's
all I could remember.
But the answer is the Asian Highway.
I'll open a study room
for variety shows.
- You should!
- I'll open a study room.
All right, then.
The next keyword is geography.
- Geography?
- It's geography.
- Haha should answer it.
- Haha, go for it.
- All right.
- We need to get the right answer.
- You know the answer, right?
- That's it!
- Correct.
- All right!
- Good job.
(He got an easy question and
manages to act as the top student.)
- All right!
- That's not what I had in mind.
Haha, you're contributing a lot.
- Of course.
- You got most of the questions.
- This is great.
- Get another one.
It'll be great
if he gets one more question.
Why is it so nerve-racking?
Write down the five duties
of a citizen...
under the constitution.
- Ji Hyo, you got this.
- We covered the five duties.
- Not the rights but duties, right?
- The five duties we memorized.
- It's the duties, not rights.
- It's the duties.
- Se Chan, it's the duties.
My gosh, you're writing the answer
without hesitation.
- You're a genius!
- I wrote it down...
as soon as I heard the question.
You're amazing.
You're at the top of the class.
- Quizzes are so fun!
- You're the master of study.
I was indeed the master.
- You have the brain for it.
- I can't remember one.
- What? Why can't you remember one?
I helped you memorize...
the duties in order.
- I told you...
- You have to do this...
- this will come out for sure.
- after this.
Someone who does this
will have to do this too.
- Ji Hyo, remember the last one?
- Hold on.
I can't remember anything.
Why can't you remember it?
(He's also confronted
with teaching by rote.)
Why can't you remember it?
- You must remember it.
- It's easy once you understand it.
- It's the most basic thing.
- Right.
In 1, 2, 3. Open.
- Let's see.
- We talked about this earlier.
(Taxation, national defense,
education, protect environment...)
No, you don't get one's
money's worth with environment.
- In 1, 2, 3. Open. Let's see.
- We talked about this earlier.
(Taxation, national defense,
get one's money's worth with...)
"Get one's money's worth"?
No, you don't get one's
money's worth with environment.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry about that.
- That one is fine.
- She wrote it wrong.
- Please go back to your seat.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's "protection".
- I got it.
- How could you write that?
- I did well. I got it.
- Get one's money's worth?
- No, that's not it.
This is what happens
when you memorize the answers...
in a short amount of time.
You need to understand the question.
No, this is...
She couldn't go wrong with this.
She wrote it wrong.
- She wrote it wrong.
- Since it's a meaningful question,
we'll accept her answer.
- Yes!
- Of course.
Se Chan, you're incredible.
- You're pretty smart.
- You should compliment others too.
I should be...
- complimenting mine first.
- They all wrote the answer.
- Stop it, already!
- You should compliment everyone.
She wrote,
"get one's money's worth".
Compliment them too.
We're all in one team.
- Okay.
- We're all in one team.
- Yes, we are,
- That's right.
but he's admirable.
- Yes, he is, but...
- He knows...
the five duties of a citizen.
- She knows it too.
- I know.
She knows it too.
Se Chan knows the five duties.
Ji Hyo knows it too.
- So Min knows it too.
- So Min knows it.
- They all know.
- Right.
- You should be more understanding.
- They're so awesome.
They all know
the five duties of a citizen.
Now I finally understand how
my homeroom teacher must've felt.
- We got them wrong.
- Right.
Gosh, we got them wrong.
The next keyword is industry.
- I don't think...
- I don't think we covered it.
- we covered it.
- It's about industries.
- We didn't cover it either.
- We did cover it briefly.
- It's about industries.
- We covered it.
- The one I mentioned earlier!
- We did?
We talked about the industries
in each city.
(He remembers it.)
- We did, right?
- Yes.
- You remember it, right?
- Oh, this...
- Let's make Haha answer it.
- Like the industry...
Pohang is known for?
- Let's have Haha answer it.
- Haha should do it.
- We didn't cover this area.
- No, we didn't.
- I'm not so confident though.
- It's your third time, right?
- I think I know the question.
- It's an industry...
that makes heavy products...
or one that uses crude oil
to make various products.
- I memorized it.
- Crude oil?
(Industry that makes heavy products
or uses crude oil for many products)
The question has a hint
of the answer.
It says it makes heavy products.
(Industry that makes heavy products
or uses crude oil for many products)
- It makes heavy products.
- It uses Chinese characters.
- I'll give you three seconds.
- Then it must have "heavy" in it.
Heavy...
- Three...
- Hold on.
(The answer is
the heavy chemical industry.)
(Right then, Se Chan
remembered something.)
The heavy chemical industry.
Heavy chemical
as in "Chinese restaurants".
Yes, the heavy chemical industry.
Just remember that petroleum...
Jae Suk,
is it the heavy chemical industry?
You can do it, Haha.
The top student knows the answer.
- You know the answer?
- Don't you know the answer, Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo, you know the answer, right?
You know the answer?
I forgot. What is it?
(He confirms it.)
This is the basics!
My gosh.
- Se Chan knows it all.
- This is crazy.
I'm so proud of you.
Haha, I'll give you three seconds.
- Heavy... Darn it.
- Two, one. Time's up.
- Did you write your answer?
- Hey.
- What did you write?
- "Queen"?
- Doesn't it begin with "heavy"?
- Her Majesty the Queen?
- "Chinese restaurant".
- Let's see Se Chan's answer.
You brat!
(Chinese restaurant industry?)
- Hey.
- What's the answer?
- It's "heavy chemical"!
- Hey!
You shouldn't have acted
like you knew the answer.
- Isn't it correct?
- It's "heavy chemical"!
- I only memorized the first part.
- "Chinese restaurant".
- I only memorized that part.
Why did you mention
Chinese restaurant?
He called it
Chinese restaurant industry.
(The side effects of the mnemonics
that the top student has been using)
I only memorized the first part.
That's the funniest thing.
Chinese restaurant industry.
- He can only go so far.
- Oh, it's heavy chemical industry?
- Oh, it's heavy chemical industry.
I didn't memorize the latter part.
- I'm done with it, right?
- Yes.
The next keyword is law.
- Students, you can do it!
- Let's do it!
- Ji Hyo, you learned it.
- I got this.
The day the constitution
was promulgated.
(The day the constitution
was promulgated)
(The answer is Constitution Day.)
The day the constitution
was promulgated.
They knew the answer
before studying it.
The day the constitution
was promulgated.
You know the answer
even if you don't study it.
(Se Chan also learned it
from Jae Suk.)
The day the constitution
was promulgated.
The word itself means
they enacted the constitution.
- Oh, does it?
- Constitution Day.
(Anyone can get the answer
if they don't think deeply.)
This is... Hold on.
You even memorized it.
- This is...
- Three, two, one, open.
(Will they be able
to get the answer?)
Open.
- No, that's not it.
- No? Isn't it Constitutional Day?
(Constitutional Day,
the Day of Constitution)
(Ji Hyo and So Min
got the wrong answer.)
- No, that's not it.
- No? Isn't it Constitutional Day?
(What did Se Chan write?)
(Constitution Day)
He got the answer.
You got it?
(He's the only one
who got the right answer.)
It's Constitution Day, right?
He got the answer?
Jae Suk!
You got the answer?
- You must know this!
- You got the answer?
You got the answer?
The day the constitution
was enacted.
- It's Constitution Day!
- He got the answer!
- Dear viewers, he got the answer!
- But this is...
I wasn't sure of the answer.
- The day the constitution...
- I know.
This has nothing to do with studies.
- I really knew the answer.
- It's Constitution Day.
See? I even wrote the first letter.
- You did?
- You should've written it.
- I didn't think that'd be it.
It's a miracle, right?
- Yes, Mr. Yoo.
- Right.
Thank you so much.
What's with Constitutional Day?
Gosh.
- Will you stay quiet?
- But that's...
The Day of Constitution
isn't any better.
Is the Day of Constitution
isn't any better?
- What I'm saying is...
- Mr. Gym.
You can mock her only when
your student got the right answer.
- It's about the constitution, so...
- Sir.
This happens because you made them
memorize the answers...
in a short term.
You have to make them understand.
- They can't think of it.
- It's not about understanding them.
You always get a day off
on Constitution Day!
You must know
what Constitution Day is!
What's so great about him?
Look at him. He understood it.
That's how he remembered it.
What I'm saying is...
Right. I remember seeing teachers
fighting with each other.
- With each other?
- Yes.
They fight because they think
their students are better.
- How can they not know...
- You must know...
what Constitution Day is?
- what Constitution Day is.
- Exactly.
It's Constitution Day, of all days.
- The students...
- "Why are we getting a day off?"
- No.
- "Because it's Constitution Day."
It's Constitution Day.
"Why are we getting a day off?"
"Mom, why are we getting a day off?"
- "Because it's Constitution Day."
- What I'm saying is...
Mr. Gym.
The more you fight with each other,
- I know you're right, but...
- the more suffocated we feel!
You need to understand the question.
- Why must you understand it?
- You don't even know...
- what's in the constitution.
- Just forget it.
- Forget it!
- Hey, mister.
- Wait.
- Why are you assaulting a student?
- It's not like you know everything.
- Hey!
- Don't do this!
- What do you think you're doing?
- Don't do that to the students.
- Get this man out of here.
How are you any better than So Min?
What did you say?
He's really smart.
- What do you mean he's smart?
- Just go!
- Okay, let's sit down.
- Goodness.
- Please sit down.
- Give us the next question.
A teacher is tormenting a student.
- You need to calm down.
- Mr. Ji.
- Yes?
- Why do you keep pointing...
your finger at my student?
- It's because...
- I do that to everyone.
Why would you point your finger...
- at him?
- Look at this guy.
- Why would you point your finger?
- Why did you poke me?
Please don't fight!
(Please don't fight!)
- Please don't fight!
- How dare you?
- Wait a minute.
- How dare you poke a teacher?
Look at this guy.
- How dare you throw my cap off?
- What about it?
What's so great about him?
- I know.
- The kids are okay with it.
Why are you all making so much fuss?
(Why are you
all making so much fuss?)
Hold on. Who are you?
- I'm the top student.
- The top student?
What have you ever taught me?
- Hey.
- I did it all by myself!
What do you mean? You must've
gotten all three questions...
- if you're a top student.
- Gosh, seriously.
The next keyword
is general social studies.
Social studies?
It's the norm that all members
of a society...
must follow in conscience.
- Se Chan, you know this.
- This is...
(The answer is ethics.)
Se Chan, you know the answer.
It's the norm that all members
of a society...
must follow in conscience.
It's about conscience.
All right.
(Se Chan and So Min wrote down
the answer without hesitating.)
They must know the answer.
In three,
- two,
- You know the answer.
(Ji Hyo is also writing something.
Will they get it right this time?)
one. Open!
- Is this the answer?
- I'm not sure about it.
Ethics! It's correct!
- Ethics.
- Ethics!
- Legislation?
- What do you mean by legislation?
- Ethics.
- Ethics!
(Dropping his head)
- It's ethics!
- How can you write legislation?
- Well done!
- Was it supposed to be this one?
- It was really easy.
- I got it.
Yes! This is what I'm talking about.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- Our society is still ethical!
- This is it!
- This is what I'm talking about.
- It was nothing difficult.
- It's all my fault.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
So Min got the answer.
- I...
- They asked all the questions...
that Jae Suk picked.
It's okay. It can happen.
I understand.
Ji Hyo, your agency
must stop this episode...
from airing.
(Your agency must stop this episode
from airing.)
To improve the average grade,
To be honest...
the teachers must
pay more attention.
- That's not it.
- Are you a principal or something?
- She got the answers too.
- No, I'm not.
Why are you saying this
when she can hear it?
- I think...
- You're a teacher.
(Why are you saying this
when she can hear it?)
Why are the teachers fighting again?
We could go to the back
and talk quietly.
Or you could've texted me.
- Text?
- She could hear you.
How could you say that
in front of her?
- Did I mean to do that?
- I can't believe this guy.
- She could hear you.
- Did I mean to let her hear it?
She heard you.
- I...
- Toegye Yi Hwang once said...
you should watch what you say
because even cows can hear you.
- He told you to be careful,
- Hold on.
- but you were...
- Mr. Gym.
Ji Hyo is old enough.
She's not a kid.
That doesn't matter.
You shouldn't have said it...
in front of her.
We could've stepped outside.
Screw the education system of Korea!
(Screw the education system
of Korea!)
(A cry that echoed
through the classroom)
Why that little punk... Hey!
(They slowly get up on their desks.)
Everyone, get up!
(Everyone, get up!)
(The voices of the students...)
(that little Haha,
who's only 168cm tall, drew out.)
(Everyone, get up!)
Everyone, get up!
(What we want)
What we want
(The students deliver what they want
in harmony)
Nice.
(The teachers were awakened
by the students' performance.)
(Happiness doesn't come
from good grades.)
- It was like a movie.
- It's okay.
"Everyone, get up."
- We...
- I'm sorry, but...
We pushed the students to compete
in the college entrance exam.
- This is the last question.
- Okay.
Let's do this.
Here's the last question.
It's not easy
for all three of them...
- to get the answer.
- Of course.
What's the name
of the mountain range...
that blocks
the cold northwesterly winds?
- I don't know the answer.
- Hey!
(What's the name
of the mountain range...)
(that blocks
the cold northwesterly winds?)
(Se Chan quickly writes down
the answer.)
- Se Chan, we covered this.
- Look at him writing it down.
Se Chan, we covered this!
He writes it down
without any hesitation.
He doesn't hesitate at all.
It's like a movie.
- Hey, Se Chan!
- He doesn't hesitate at all.
- We covered this!
- What is it?
We...
- Hold on.
- I'll give you three seconds.
Hey, think carefully.
- The northwesterly winds?
- It...
It blocks the winds.
Think of it with common sense.
Think of it with common sense!
- It's common sense.
- You didn't cover this part,
- but you can do it, So Min.
- Se Chan.
(So Min is writing down something.)
What's the name
of the mountain range...
that blocks
the cold northwesterly winds?
- You can do it!
- Remember the mountain range?
- Just write one of the ranges.
- You can do it!
I told you that was why
that area is warm.
Ji Hyo, just write down
any mountain range you know.
- The one you know.
- I can't remember it.
- Just one of the mountain ranges.
- Mr. Gym.
- I think I saw it.
- Stay quiet.
Ji Hyo is getting pressured.
I'm just sitting still here.
But you're running your mouth.
That's why I'm saying this!
(What did you say?)
- Hold on.
- The teachers are fighting again.
- I apologize.
- My gosh.
I think I crossed the line.
The kids are at ease,
but the teachers are too worked up.
- All right, now. In 3, 2...
- Okay!
- One.
- Just write down one that you know.
- Open.
- All right.
Think of it. Think of one.
(Ji Hyo wrote
the Taebaek Mountain Range.)
- I don't think this is the answer.
- Think of it. Think of one.
- This is wrong, right?
- They got it.
Correct!
I told you! It's the mountain range
you know of!
(All 3 of them got it.)
- I didn't know.
- You did it!
- I wasn't sure.
I even wrote Hangyeryeong.
She almost wrote Hangyeryeong
for the answer.
I wrote the answer before he even
finished reading the question.
Mr. Yoo. I wrote it before he even
- You remembered it, right?
- I did.
So Min even drew the mountain range!
The only mountain range I know of
is Taebaek Mountain Range.
So Min even drew
the mountain range, everyone!
She drew the Taebaek Mountain Range.
- What's it called again?
- "Sky Castle".
She almost wrote Hangyeryeong
for the answer.
Gosh, my throat hurts.
She knows where it is.
- She even knows where it is.
- Ji Hyo even knows...
what Hangyeryeong is.
- She knows what Hangyeryeong is?
- Yes!
Well done!
- Good job, So Min.
- Well done, Empty Heads!
- We did pretty well.
- This wraps up the game.
- We lost, but we fought well.
- We did.
The cast gets 9 penalty balls,
and the staff gets 6 penalty balls.
- Well done.
- Well done, Ji Hyo.
We were going to lose anyway.
(Lunchtime)
Se Chan, please move
to the waiting room.
- The top student.
- I'll be tactful.
- Okay.
- He'd have gone to SNU...
if he put his mind to his studies.
It's not that easy to go to SNU.
I'm just saying.
What could it be?
(The new top student
carefully steps out of the room.)
(And the producer
is waiting for him.)
(What kind of mission awaits him?)
- All right.
- From now,
we'll check how well you can
communicate through telepathy.
Okay.
Pick a member whom you think
won't be chosen by anyone...
except for you.
Someone whom I think won't be
chosen by anyone except me?
You won't get additional
penalty balls...
if the members you pick
do not overlap.
- If they don't overlap?
- But...
we'll give you penalty balls
as many as the unchosen members.
You should pick a member
that only you will choose.
(Each member should pick different
members, so they don't overlap.)
(Se Chan, Jae Suk, Suk Jin,
Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Haha, So Min)
I'll pick...
Jae Suk.
- Do I take it with me?
- I'll pick this person.
- You picked Haha.
- Yes.
I'll pick her. Do I take it with me?
- Then I'll pick Jong Kook.
- Okay. Take that with you.
Of course, I'll pick Ji Hyo.
- You can take that with you.
- All right.
- I pick So Min.
- Take it with you.
I think somehow no one picked her.
Because So Min is going last...
- It's okay. You did well.
- That's why I picked her.
So far, it's good.
I thought you'd avoid choosing
members that everyone would choose,
so I picked one
that anyone would choose.
- That's good thinking.
- So who did you pick?
- You did well.
- I picked Suk Jin.
(She picked Suk Jin.)
(She avoided picking
an overlapping member.)
You did really well.
Well done.
Only one of us was overlapped.
Because you have a connection
with him...
- She did really well.
- Well done.
- Who did you pick?
Only one of us was overlapped.
What's the result?
- Only one member.
We're incredible.
- We did such a good job.
- We're good.
We have wonderful teamwork.
Our teamwork is really good.
The staff gets six penalty balls,
and the cast gets just one.
- What will you do?
- We should...
We should let them
experience the water bomb.
- Bring in their meal.
- We all picked different people.
It's incredible, isn't it?
I guess it's another PPL.
What's this? Thank you.
It's so neat.
- This is a meal box?
- It looks so good.
This is amazing.
- Look at the meat.
- It's solid.
- I guess we mix it with rice.
- There's a pile of meat.
We obviously
need to mix it with rice.
Meal boxes
usually aren't this solid.
There's wasabi too.
- It'll be nice for a photo too.
- It's incredible.
Is this even profitable?
(Is this even profitable?)
- Why would you worry about that?
- A PPL expert.
You don't even know how much it is.
(They caught the fraud red-handed.)
How is it?
You know how to cook.
It's perfect for me.
It'd be nice with octopus too.
The yolk is a game-changer.
It's so good.
We don't need any other side dishes.
It's our favorite.
- What's this?
- It's table tennis.
- Gosh, it's table tennis.
- Is it table tennis?
- We love table tennis.
- I know.
We love it.
Will we go against
the production crew? What?
I guess we will.
They took off their clothes.
(The production crew changed
into group uniform.)
Everyone,
this is the last mission.
The members and production crew
will compete against each other...
- to see who is better.
- Better?
It's the Variety Triathlon.
- What could it be?
- Variety Triathlon?
- The members...
- We will play foot volleyball too.
and production crew
will compete against each other.
- Okay.
- We will play your favorite sports,
table tennis,
badminton,
and foot volleyball.
- I see.
- Okay.
Se Chan plays badminton
on a show these days.
- "Racket Boys".
- Yes.
I will show you.
We need...
two members for table tennis,
two members for badminton,
and four members
for foot volleyball.
In short, only one member
will play twice.
- That's right.
- The players can't overlap.
The 1st team
to score 21 points wins.
But the score combines points
from all three events.
Once a team scores seven points,
the event will change.
(Once a team scores 7 points,
the event will change.)
The score will keep going.
If the 2nd team reaches 14 points,
you will move on
to the last event, foot volleyball.
Everyone needs to play.
Thus, the 1st team
to score 21 points wins.
The production team...
will be represented
by people you are familiar with.
They must have picked athletic ones.
As for So Min and Ji Hyo's event,
Seon Myung and Hyung In
will participate.
They are bad at sports. That's good.
- They are bad at sports.
- Thus,
the losing team...
will receive five penalty balls.
- That's good. Five. Come on.
- Okay.
I can take on Seon Myung.
Write down which members
will participate in each event.
Among the three, table tennis
would be the best for me.
- That's right. Play table tennis.
- Play table tennis.
I want to play table tennis too.
- Jong Kook and Suk Jin...
- I want to play table tennis too.
- are good at table tennis.
- Yes.
- Shall we play badminton?
- Badminton.
- I want to play badminton.
Can I use my private racket?
I have it in the car.
- You can bring it.
- Hey.
Jae Suk, I have a good racket.
- A good racket. It's light.
- Really?
Let's begin the first event,
- badminton.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's go.
You can do it, right?
Let's do well this time.
- Let's show them.
- I didn't see it coming.
Let's avoid the penalty.
- I don't want the penalty.
- Everyone.
From the production crew,
producer Kim Nam Joong
and cameraman Cho Sung Oh will play.
- Nam Joong?
- Sung Oh?
- They are good.
- Sung Oh is a professional.
- Sung Oh is good.
- Is he good?
Look at his body.
He looks like a table tennis player.
Nam Joong is relaxed.
Let's see how well they can play
before cameras.
Go ahead and play.
Let's begin a game
for the first serve.
A game for the first serve.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- I need to stand in the back.
My goodness.
- Let's go.
- I will move to the side.
- It's a game for the 1st serve.
- The 1st serve.
All right.
There you go. That's it.
- They are good.
- The sound is different.
There you go. That's it. Warm up.
- That's it.
- Okay.
- Serve first.
- Warm up.
(The production crew fails
to receive.)
- Serve first.
- Let's begin.
- Warm up.
- Hold on.
They aren't good.
Good job.
All right.
Seven points.
- The game begins now.
- Let's make the score 7 to 0.
- Play with seriousness.
- Okay.
Hit it.
- Gosh.
- It's okay.
(The production crew
succeeded in scoring first.)
- It's okay.
- Nice.
- Okay. It's okay.
- Okay.
- Play with seriousness.
Okay.
They look serious.
(Suk Jin succeeds in
receiving the ball.)
- Okay.
- Nice.
- They look serious.
- Okay.
- Nice.
One point.
Okay.
They are no match for us.
- They are no match for us.
- Play with seriousness.
(Which team will get ahead?)
- Okay.
(Sung Oh made a careless mistake.)
Let's go.
(Team Running Man: 2 points,
Team Production Crew: 1 point)
Feel the pressure.
Just get it over the net.
"Just get it over the net."
- Okay.
Nice.
(He suddenly plays baseball.)
- Hey.
- Let's go.
- We are doing so well.
You are sexy.
Sung Oh, what is going on?
Sung Oh is flustered.
Other people
who played against you...
couldn't receive your serve, right?
We can receive it.
- Okay.
- It's about the energy.
- The members have strong energy,
- Is it our turn?
so they are intimidated.
- My goodness.
- They are intimidated.
Production crew, please do better.
- Go ahead.
- They are intimidated.
My goodness.
- The tables have turned.
- I will receive it.
(He fails to make a serve
this time.)
- Okay.
- We won't go easy in you.
- Being in front of the cameras...
- makes you nervous, right?
- Let's go.
If you show us a specialty,
we will give you a point.
- A specialty.
- You don't even know the order.
- You are out of it.
- What is your problem?
We move on to the next event
once we have seven points, right?
- It's Suk Jin.
- The current score is 6 to 1.
Can't you beat Suk Jin?
My goodness.
Okay.
- Okay.
- That side.
(They already lost 6 points.)
(Will the production crew succeed in
turning the tables?)
That was good.
(Jong Kook smashes the ball!)
(Their play is weak until the end.)
(The members ridicule them.)
You are no match for us.
- You are no match for us.
- We are good.
The set has ended.
- Nice.
- The score is 7 to 1.
- What was that?
- That was easy.
The next event is badminton.
Okay. Badminton.
- Let's go.
- Jae Suk.
Let's go.
Na Dong Geun
of the operation team...
and Kim Hyun Gi
of the setup team will play.
They look like professionals.
- Good luck.
- We have to win.
- Guys.
Guys, we are cornered.
We have to win.
Please do well.
(Since the production crew is losing
with a score of 7 to 1,)
(this is an important game.)
Dong Geun.
(They have a practice match
to warm up.)
He is good.
- Everyone is good.
- Seriously.
I can't see the shuttlecock.
- Everyone is good.
- Seriously.
- He can use his wrist well.
- I can't see the shuttlecock.
He is good.
- He is really good.
- Look at Se Chan.
How is he so good?
- He is good.
You must have played
badminton often.
Let's go.
He must be in a badminton club.
He was in the production crew
for "Law of the Jungle".
He is really good.
Let's begin right away.
We scored seven points.
We are in the lead by many points.
Don't let them catch up.
Let's score seven points.
- Hey.
- Let's go.
His pose is different.
(The fateful game begins.)
- Se Chan is good.
- Here it comes.
He is really good.
He is good.
- He is good.
- What is Se Chan up to these days?
He is good.
- This is no joke.
- He is good.
I can't see the shuttlecock.
(They watch like meerkats.)
- This is no joke.
- He is good.
I can't see the shuttlecock.
For goodness' sake.
Good job.
(Nice!)
He raised it too fast.
- Good job.
- They are good.
- You warmed up.
- Good job.
You gave them a point, so it's okay.
It's okay.
I can't see the shuttlecock.
It's too fast.
You know,
- he has played it often.
- It seems that way.
Seriously.
(Smash)
(Racket Boy's non-spin smash)
Se Chan, that was great.
- Okay.
- You are good.
I see that you are smart
and athletic.
He is like a hero...
- in a comic book.
- He makes me jealous.
- Seriously.
- I am so jealous.
A hero in a comic book.
- I want to win.
- Se Chan.
- I lose all the time.
(Team Running Man: 8 points,
Team Production Crew: 3 points)
- Here I go.
- That's a proper pose.
Look at his pose. He is an expert.
(Racket Boy makes a mistake!)
They are so good.
(Cheering)
They are good.
Don't be so happy.
We went easy on you.
- For goodness' sake.
- We went easy on them many times.
How many times
do we need to do that?
That part will get edited out.
(The production crew
had to beg for a point.)
The production crew
will get the water bomb.
I know.
They might turn the tables here.
Jae Suk can't keep his eyes
on the shuttlecock.
Okay.
How did it happen
as soon as I said that?
- It's okay, right?
- Jae Suk.
Don't say something like that.
- Okay.
- He can't keep his eyes on it.
- Don't say that.
Look at that.
(A light tap)
(A sudden drop shot)
How could you be so sneaky?
Seriously.
You don't look that way.
- I expected better from you.
- You were so sneaky.
We need to win.
Hold on. Go and change your pants.
(So tight)
They are too revealing.
They should be illegal.
- They are building teamwork.
- They finished warming up.
You need to destroy them
before they do that.
(This is an important round.)
Okay.
(He fails to receive it.)
- That was fun.
- Dong Geun.
- Good job.
- Dong Geun, what was that?
- That was fun.
- Are you a spy?
This is fun.
- Go.
- What's the current score?
It's 13 to 8.
We have one point to go.
(If Team Running Man
scores another point,)
(they will switch over
to the next game.)
- We have one point to go.
- Yes.
(Team Production Crew is
on the edge of a cliff.)
Come on.
(Will the production crew be able
to overcome this crisis?)
Okay.
(Flailing)
(The 2nd event, badminton ends.)
- What was that?
- Nice.
The event ended
with a score of 14 to 8.
The next event is foot volleyball.
- Okay.
- That's good.
Let's finish them.
It's light, right?
- The next event is foot volleyball.
- Okay.
- Our players are Kang Chan Hee,
Lee Ju Yong, Choi Hyung In,
and Yoo Seon Myung.
- Ju Yong and Chan Hee...
- Ju Yong has long legs.
Ju Yong is good, right?
I think so.
(When the production crew had
a tug-of-war against the members,)
(Ju Yong showed
his exceptional athletic skills.)
The legend of the variety shows,
Kang Chan Hee will decide.
(The living legend of Korean
variety shows, Kang Chan Hee)
Seon Myung will play.
(The experts of editing,
Choi Hyung In and Yoo Seon Myung)
I won't joke around.
- I won't be funny
- I will play with seriousness.
- I will score right away.
- I won't be funny.
I won't be funny.
I can do better
than Seon Myung and Hyung In.
It feels different to play
in front of the camera.
- That's right.
- It feels different.
Did he do well on "2 Days and 1 Night"?
- We need to win this.
- Yes, he did.
I will send it upward.
Then you can kick it.
Who will receive it? Seon Myung.
- It's better to send it over there.
- Seon Myung.
There you go. Good job.
(She sends it to space.)
- We found one bad player.
- Okay.
- It's Hyung In.
Okay. We have a chance.
Seon Myung.
- There you go.
- Okay.
(So Min's producer
does the mask dance.)
We found another bad player.
We are set.
- We are set. I was started.
- That team has two So Mins.
- Two So Mins.
- I thought they were really good.
- I thought they were athletic.
- Thank you.
We are better.
We didn't choose them
by their athletic skills.
- Really?
- All right.
I don't think they have played
foot volleyball before.
Seon Myung.
They weren't chosen
by their athletic skills.
There you go.
- Seon Myung.
- There you go.
(She kicks the air.)
- Seon Myung.
- You guys are cute.
(Seon Myung is as bad as So Min.)
- Seon Myung is enthusiastic.
- You guys are cute.
- So Min.
- Head the ball.
- There you go.
- Good job.
- My goodness.
- You did well.
- How are you so good?
- You are good.
Come on.
Stay in the middle.
I will be all the way in the back.
(The practice game continues
to put the production crew on ease.)
All right.
What?
(A sudden attack)
What was that?
- Chan Hee.
- What was up with that cute foot?
- Hold on.
- What was that?
- Don't act cute.
- Seriously.
Don't intimidate them.
Don't act cute.
- Are you ready? Let's get started.
- Let's go.
- Make it funny.
You are doing well.
(The match starts
with Haha's serve.)
Haha is good at receiving.
Ju Yong.
Haha.
- You know...
- There you go.
Okay.
Hyung In, receive it. Let's go.
(Grunting)
(He painstakingly saved the ball.)
Haha is good at defense.
That's good.
(My goodness.)
Hold on.
(He headed the ball backward.)
- What was that?
- We will be funny, okay?
He doesn't have anything
other than the cute foot.
- You should have saved it.
- That was nice.
Are you ready?
All right.
(The production crew lost 1 point
with the slapstick comedy.)
Good job.
Send it over the net.
- Seon Myung.
Don't do it.
(She kicks the air.)
(Don't do it.)
- Who told her not to do it?
- Hey.
Why did you stop her?
- Why did you stop her?
- It was Seon Myung's ball.
Why didn't you kick the ball?
Seon Myung is charming.
The score is 15 to 8.
She was like Bbakgu.
I know.
Here I go. This time...
- Hyung In.
- Hyung In, receive the ball.
(They target the younger producers.)
Hyung In.
- Hyung In.
(Shouting)
(A knee kick)
What was that?
Was it a knee-jerk reaction?
- The ball hit your knee.
- You will hurt your knee.
You will hurt your knee.
She did this.
(Teasing)
Hyung In.
She is so funny.
- We can't have a rally.
- We are good.
- Here I go.
- Seriously.
- Let's go.
- Good.
That was a nice serve.
- Nice.
- Hyung In.
Send it over the net.
Receive it.
There you go. Good job.
(My goodness.)
- Hold on.
- Hyung In.
Why are two members playing
by themselves?
Your team is the same.
- Mine.
- Seon Myung.
Hyung In.
(My goodness.)
My goodness.
He learned slapstick comedy from us.
(Chan Hee showed
unexpected slapstick comedy.)
- This is fun.
- This is so much fun.
- Chan Hee.
- I am laughing so much.
- That was cute.
Suk Jin.
- Don't worry about comedy.
- You shouldn't laugh from now on.
If he hadn't been
the main cameraman,
- they would have dragged him out.
- Definitely.
- Seriously.
- Here I go.
Don't laugh
when Suk Jin does badly.
That was a nice serve.
- Seon Myung.
- Hold on.
Two touches.
- Seon Myung.
- Hold on.
(The ball hits her twice.)
We can't beat them
in terms of slapstick comedy.
- We can't beat them.
- How did you form the team?
(Their slapstick comedy beats
that of entertainers.)
It's so hard.
- It's okay.
- I practiced so hard.
Do you know what's scary?
Do you know what she said?
"I practiced so hard."
She practiced.
Hyung In,
why won't you receive the ball?
- Here I go.
- Seon Myung.
It's Seon Myung's ball.
Hyung In.
It's Hyung In's ball. Hyung In.
- Hyung In.
(Double slapstick comedy)
(The worst collaboration)
- My goodness.
- Chan Hee.
Hyung In was going to kick it.
Why did you do that?
They charge at the ball like a moth
when they hear their names.
Chan Hee went...
He charges at the ball
when he hears his name.
- Shall we change the players?
- Let's just keep going.
Shall we change the players?
We can switch a player
with Suk Jin.
I will play.
Can we do that?
We will have Suk Jin play.
I will play instead of Se Chan.
- Okay.
- All right.
- It's for balance.
- We still have an advantage.
- We are so much better.
- Let's go.
Why did they even challenge us?
Why did they even challenge us
to play these games?
The back...
- Chan Hee.
- They can switch the players.
- Will you get it?
- Yes.
- They can stand...
- Go ahead.
- and watch.
- There you go.
- Who will receive it?
- Nice.
Hyung In, come on out.
Go backward.
Receive it.
(It hits the net.)
Okay.
That was...
Did you become confident
upon seeing me enter the game?
You suddenly improved.
- The team seems easier now.
- Do we seem easier now?
There is a balance now.
- Seriously.
- There is finally a balance.
- You should relax now.
- Yes.
It's okay.
Send the ball to Seon Myung.
Is that a pass?
- Go.
- Ji Hyo.
- Did I say Ji Hyo?
- So Min.
(The ball hits the net again!)
- Did I say Ji Hyo?
- So Min.
(So Min, a bad player,
loses a point.)
I wanted to give you a chance
since we are leading.
You know, Suk Jin...
- Does he avoid the ball?
- He avoids the ball too much.
He gives me the ball
when it's impossible to receive it.
I will receive it this time.
(Suk Jin avoids the ball
if it's beyond his abilities.)
- Haha.
- That's a strong serve.
Haha is a great player.
- Go, So Min.
- So Min.
- He got it.
- Hey.
(Haha saved the ball
that was directed at the team!)
Seon Myung.
We won.
(The unbelievable rally)
(The slapstick comedy was
the grand finale.)
(I can't believe it.)
We won.
(So Min's hopeless heading
resulted in a point.)
What was that?
I can't believe it.
Did you guys plan it out?
- So Min.
- Did you guys plan it out?
Seon Myung, Ju Yong,
and So Min,
did you guys plan it out?
- The ball went from there...
- It was unbelievable.
What was that?
The back attack.
- Seriously.
- The back attack was amazing.
- Seon Myung, that was so funny.
- That was so funny.
That was unbelievably funny.
Here I go.
All right.
Wait.
Two points remain.
Hyung In.
Come on.
Get it.
Okay.
Good job, Old Man.
- All right.
- Go.
(The production crew
barely scored 1 point.)
- There you go.
- Receive it.
Suk Jin.
- Send it over the net.
- Head the ball.
- So Min.
- Hit it.
- There you go.
Okay.
Anything can happen.
- I mean...
- Okay.
(Anything can happen.)
Anything can happen.
- You need to pull yourself up.
- Let's go.
- There is a six-point difference.
- That's a big difference.
- Let's stop playing around.
Don't lose.
One person should receive it.
Let's go. All right.
(She touches the ball.)
(Go away.)
- Hey.
- That was too much.
- Why did you use your hand?
- You scored a point.
- What was that?
You shouldn't be like that.
Ju Yong.
- That was too much.
- I didn't mean to do that.
- I was too startled.
- Come on.
You lost all the points.
- Se Chan, go back in there.
- I was too startled.
- Can I go back in there?
- We will lose at this rate.
- Shouldn't he go back in there?
- I was too startled.
I was too startled.
Who will receive it?
- What was that?
- Why did you just stand there?
Send it over the net.
Okay.
It didn't touch. Ji Hyo.
Mine.
There you go. No!
- You should have left it.
- Seriously.
- I hit it.
Get a grip.
We will lose at this rate.
Seriously. We have to win.
- Just try to focus.
- All right.
Focus. Be serious.
- What's the score?
- You're three points ahead.
- Oh, no.
- Let's do this.
(They are in the lead
only by 3 points.)
- We can't make more mistakes.
- We might lose.
We need one person
to receive the ball.
- Stay calm.
- Calm?
Don't panic.
They seem motivated now.
(The members are about to snatch
defeat from the jaws of victory.)
Don't panic.
They seem motivated now.
(A strong service
in a tense atmosphere)
It's out. No.
- I'll do it.
- Send it over.
- Let me do it.
- Good. Just send it over.
Just end it.
Seon Myung, you do it.
- Out.
- It went out.
(He sent the ball to an empty spot,
but it went out.)
The director seems flustered.
Are they supposed to avoid the ball?
Can't they touch the ball?
- These two...
- It's our ball.
These two are playing dodgeball.
And the rest of them
are playing foot volleyball.
It must be fun.
You have one point left.
Don't do that. You need one person.
Haha should receive the ball.
This is no joke.
I'll send over the ball.
(This match will decide
who gets 5 penalty balls.)
Kick it high.
(The fatal match begins.)
Isn't it over?
- There you go.
- Send it over.
Catch it.
- All right.
- Seon Myung.
(Big Nose received the ball well.)
- Done.
- Okay.
- It's in.
- Nice.
Good.
- Good.
(Reflecting)
(The grand finale)
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
I wanted to try a back-header.
That was funny.
- I didn't do anything.
- My goodness.
That was hilarious.
I didn't even make you laugh.
What was that?
He's so good at variety shows.
He's a master of slapstick comedy.
Chan Hee showed
a lot of funny things today.
That was really fun.
- He's outstanding.
- That was hilarious.
- We're too good.
- We all are really good.
That was fun.
You guys are better than we thought.
Of course.
- We are really good.
- You don't sound serious.
So the production crew
got another five penalty balls.
- Yes.
- Here is the final result.
The cast has 10 balls,
and the staff has 19 balls.
- It's possible that we win.
- This isn't bad.
You have about a 30-percent chance.
- Okay. Let's be strict.
- All right.
- It's only once.
- Now we will draw the balls.
- Okay.
- It's worth a shot.
My goodness.
- I'm nervous.
- They have so many balls.
Seriously, if we lose here...
- If we lose...
- We can still lose.
There's Bo Pil.
(The crew members are gathered
together under the water bomb.)
Bo Pil, take off your watch.
- My goodness.
- Stand behind the line.
- Okay.
- Where?
- The line in the front.
- Step back a little.
Step back?
Do you see the red sticker?
- Of course.
- We will win anyway.
- Sure.
- We won't get splashed.
This isn't
our first time doing this.
We have an announcer here
to play fairly.
- Hello.
This is 2021 Running Man
Penalty Negotiation.
I'm here...
to draw balls
and decide the winners.
I'm the host, Lee In Kwon.
Nice to meet you.
- In Kwon!
- Hello.
He's an announcer.
I wonder how you are feeling today.
- Well...
- I guess we will get splashed.
- No, we won't.
- We won't.
We will go home dry and soft today.
I think they will make a mistake,
and we will get splashed.
- Right. Don't make a mistake.
- Don't try anything silly.
Don't make a mistake.
Mr. Announcer, you...
- What? Mr. Announcer?
- Mr. Announcer?
- What was that?
- Mister?
He's frowning.
The team whose ball is picked
will get splashed, right?
- Yes.
- The team with the selected ball.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Now I will announce
the result of today's race.
The number of
the production crew's balls is...
19 in total.
And the number of the Running Man
members is ten.
- It's good.
- We have a good chance to win.
- The odds are in our favor.
- Definitely.
Sure.
All right then. Now I will put
the penalty balls in the machine.
(Putting in the penalty balls)
- Let's go!
- Let us see it, Mr. Lee.
To make sure it's ten balls.
You're not adding
more balls, are you?
- They are ten balls.
- Okay.
- Ten balls for the members.
- Trust him.
(He starts putting
10 penalty balls in the machine.)
We can't lose here.
- I know.
- That would be horrible.
The odds are against them.
It can't be helped.
This is all about probability.
We can feel at ease.
But we had a loser
with only one ball before.
I lost when I had only two balls.
- Right.
- It was last week.
All right then.
Now I will...
Oh, dear.
pick a ball.
All right.
- Turn on the machine.
- Give it a good shuffle.
(10 balls versus 19 balls)
Let's do this.
(Things have been going well
for the members since the morning.)
(They messed up
the production crew's plans...)
(with the power of unity.)
(They were good at quizzes.)
(They were good
at exchanging telepathy.)
(The 7 members showed
outstanding teamwork.)
(The 7 members seemed clumsy,)
(but they were actually amazing.)
(It was a mistake
to underestimate them.)
(10 balls versus 19 balls)
We will probably get splashed.
- Because ten is a big number.
- It can happen.
This isn't easy.
(The balls will decide the result.)
(If there's someone
to control variety shows,)
(this is the time
when he should show up.)
- Did he open it already?
- No.
So soon?
- Is it open?
- Is it done?
Is it out?
In my hand...
All right. Good.
(It's finally selected.)
- He's good.
- Did you see the ball?
- It's okay.
- I didn't see it yet.
Good.
Take off your microphone
just in case.
- Take off your microphone.
- Okay.
- Take it off?
- Is it our ball?
Just in case. We don't know it yet.
- I guess they got a signal.
- Take this off?
Just in case.
Why do they want us
to take off the microphones?
Hang on. You're not
manipulating the result, are you?
(They suspect In Kwon is
manipulating the result.)
You're distracting us on purpose.
No.
I'm watching you.
It's not like that. I'm telling you.
He looks like a magician.
Aren't you Lee Eun Gyeol?
- You're Lee Eun Gyeol, right?
- No.
You look like him.
You have a dove
in your pocket, right?
- I think you do.
- You seem strange.
You don't have the hairstyle
of an announcer.
(It looks like he hid a dove
in his permed hair.)
Move a little forward.
Why?
- It's okay.
- I think it's us.
- Let's go.
- Don't worry.
All right. Now...
I will announce the result.
It can't be us.
The losing team...
- is...
- The production crew.
(The result is
about to be revealed.)
The production crew.
(The production crew loses.)
(We won!)
(Embarrassed)
We won!
See? I told you.
(They get splashed
by the 500kg water bomb.)
(Just like their colleagues
from 8 years ago,)
(a bunch of directors get soaked.)
(They are elated.)
(Tumbling)
(The magician is shocked
by the amount of water.)
- Yes!
- We won!
(The cast won 2021 Running Man
Penalty Negotiation.)
Dry and soft
(Dry and soft)
(We are going home
dry and soft today.)
(The playful members' song stabs
the crew members' hearts.)
You have good pronunciation.
He's an announcer.
I thought he was a magician.