(One sunny day with a blue sky)
- Hello.
(The three members show up
dressed like office workers.)
The weather is nice.
- It's really good.
- This place is nice.
- Are you today's guest singer?
- No.
Go this way. This is where we work.
- A guest singer should...
- Why are you laughing?
Why do you think...
an office worker should
be dressed like this?
I'm having a gathering
with my co-workers here.
- I'm an office worker too.
- Are you...
- the manager of this restaurant?
- Come on, Assistant Manager Ha.
- Assistant Manager Ha.
- The shop manager.
- Are you the manager here?
- I'm your co-worker.
I'm Chief Ji.
- Chief Ji?
- Yes.
- Do you have a sore throat?
- No.
It's fashion.
Why are you being like this?
Did you bleach
the back of your pants?
No.
You keep making jokes.
You keep making fun of his costume.
- Like ten jokes.
- I should keep being like this...
- Excuse me.
- to make him pull himself together.
- He's...
- I'm in my right mind now.
so into young fashion trends
these days.
It's not like that.
How would I bleach...
the back of my pants like this?
They're coming. We're here.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Guys, we have
something funny to show you.
- My goodness.
- He's a guest singer.
(They all burst
into laughter right away.)
- He's our guest singer.
- Think outside the box.
Sing a song for us.
You should see outside the box.
This is what Tae Jin Ah would wear.
- No.
- Suk Jin, why...
I'm too frustrated
to work with them.
- I'm really frustrated too.
- Why?
When our crew members tell you
to dress like an office worker,
you should dress accordingly.
They didn't tell me though.
- What?
- They told my stylist.
- Why are you upset?
- Don't yell at us.
Don't be so worked up
from the opening.
- Why are you upset?
- They talked to my stylist.
We're just talking. Don't be upset.
- I'm not upset.
- You're yelling.
- I'm not.
- We can't say anything.
We're so daunted
that we can't say anything.
Why are you so upset?
- It feels suffocating.
- I'm not upset.
Why are you putting your arms
around my shoulders?
He has no one...
- He has no one to count on.
- I need help.
- I need your help.
- Suk Jin.
He wants you to take his side.
- Good.
- Are you fighting again?
- I'm not fighting.
- Why do you keep fighting?
As you can see
from your employee cards,
you are employees...
of Married Corporation
and Single Dot-com.
We work at matchmaking companies.
Do I work with Suk Jin
at the same company?
This is crazy.
(For those who look for
their lifelong partner,)
(there are two
matchmaking companies.)
You guys are employees,
and your CEOs are on their way.
- Really?
(And the 2 CEOs are coming
to meet them.)
(Who are the CEOs
in the neat suits?)
(The car is pulling over
with the two CEOs.)
Is someone coming?
Someone's here.
- What is this car?
- What?
- I bet it belongs to a top star.
- That looks fancy.
- Are they here?
The top star is getting off.
- It has a sleek design.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- Who is he?
- He's...
(What? He is...)
Isn't that Yong Jin?
- Si Kyung?
- It's Si Kyung.
Hey, Si Kyung.
Yong Jin isn't a star.
- Hey, what is Si Kyung doing here?
- He's Sung Ballad.
What are Yong Jin
and Si Kyung doing here?
(His new album was released
after 10 years.)
(Sung Ballad is back with his sweet
dance song, "I Love U.")
What is Si Kyung doing here?
- Si Kyung?
- Yong Jin is Petty.
Hey. Isn't Yong Jin a secretary?
He's a petty star.
He's a secretary.
- He should get married himself.
- It's Sung Ballad.
- Hello.
- It's Si Kyung and his secretary.
- He brought his secretary?
- Why were you in the car for stars?
- It's not like that.
- Why would a secretary...
I was behind the cameras,
but you attacked me eight times.
- Of course.
- We have to.
- I was even behind the camera.
- He says we attacked him.
- Gosh, Si Kyung is...
- Si Kyung.
- Hey, Si Kyung.
- My gosh.
Yong Jin.
How have you been?
- Hey, Yong Jin.
- Yong Jin.
Hello.
- Hey.
- I heard...
Si Kyung is the CEO
of Single Dot-com.
- Yes. And Married Corporation.
- You're from Married Corporation.
Yong Jin is married.
I can't believe this.
Are you the CEOs?
I married 5,000 couples last month.
- 5,000 couples?
- Yes.
Then why are you still single?
You married 5,000 couples,
- but why are you single?
- Seriously, why is he single?
I'm just waiting.
Waiting for what?
Well, I'm...
the CEO of Married Corporation,
Lee Yong Jin.
Nice to meet you.
He looks shrewd.
I bet you've seen
the advertisement on buses.
Something Duo.
They are below us.
Our company is bigger than that.
Our market capitalization is
about 500,000 dollars higher.
Market capitalization?
The market capitalization
of only 500,000 dollars?
I mean we're rivals.
I mean we are rivals.
Do you even know
what market capitalization is?
Well... Isn't that money?
He doesn't know anything.
Isn't Duo the company name?
- Hey.
- Just let it go.
- He doesn't know anything.
- Dancing Duo.
- He's just bluffing.
- It's like saying Samsung.
- Just say "Du something."
- Du something.
- I see.
He meant Dancing Duo.
- Sure.
We haven't met Si Kyung
for a long time.
Is this your first time
on Running Man?
- No, it's his second time.
- I was here before.
By the way,
even the CEO dressed like this...
- Button up your shirt.
- Take your hands out.
You're not wearing a belt.
- He's the real CEO.
- Are you a gangster?
Who wears a belt these days?
- What?
- Why would I wear a belt?
He works in the field.
- Even the CEO...
- He works in the field.
What does he do in the field?
We can see people dressed like him
in political campaigns.
Are you a political gangster?
(Are you a political gangster?)
My gosh.
- We need an employee like me.
- What's that?
The CEOs of the two companies...
used to be the MCs
of relationship counseling TV shows.
- Oh, really?
- During the race today,
the CEOs can change
the positions of their employees...
using the position stickers
whenever they want.
- We have positions.
- I like stuff like this.
The CEOs may put the stickers
on each employee now.
- Then...
- My position?
When I watch a drama or a movie,
Lee Geung Young always plays...
the Senior Managing Director.
You're his age, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
They're friends from school.
He's about his age.
- Hey.
- Right.
- He's a lot older than me.
- They are similar in age.
"Move ahead with it."
First, the elite member should be...
- the Senior Managing Director.
- Right.
He's not an elite.
He didn't make his way up
through his connections.
I bet he did through his ability.
- You should be Manager.
- Manager?
I think that's perfect for you.
- Manager Ha sounds about right.
- I wanted to be an executive.
Just do it.
Think of Muhan Company.
You got promoted.
- What was your position?
- Back then,
you were just an employee.
That was a long time ago.
He says that again.
He's a manager now.
Haha was trying to do this.
He was doing this.
He didn't mean to shake hands.
He's not playing a game with you.
It's this hand gesture.
Why would you hold his hand?
Myung Soo keeps calling me.
He asks what is happening to us.
He feels nervous
since "How Do You Play?" is popular.
- The positions can change.
- I'm a manager. Okay.
You are supposed to wear a tie
with your shirt.
I just love fashion.
The jacket makes you
look like an intern.
Is this a fashion company?
- Hey, you...
- Is Suk Jin an intern?
There's a movie called
"The Intern," isn't there?
It features an old man.
It features a grandpa.
A grandpa works as an intern.
You're Robert De Niro.
- I'm not a grandpa.
- I like the movie.
Robert De Niro.
- But this is... Gosh.
- Old soldiers never die.
It's all right.
You can give us anything.
- You think?
- Anything would work.
- It's fun to go all the way up.
- Sure.
- It's fun to succeed.
- Give him the intern position.
- I'll...
- Gosh.
Assistant Manager?
It's a high position, right?
No, it's not high.
- It's right above employees.
- Really?
But Assistant Manager sounds
right for him.
- I agree.
- He's reckless, but he works hard.
He just can't get promoted.
Assistant Manager Lee.
- Kwang Soo, it's a good thing.
- Is it good?
He has the hairstyle of a manager.
- Gosh.
- Is Se Chan higher than me?
What's wrong with you?
- Why?
- It suits you.
You said we'd go up from the bottom.
You should use honorifics
when you speak to me, okay?
- It's not like that.
- Stay quiet. Use honorifics.
- Hey, he's an intern.
- He's an intern.
- An intern?
- Hey, he's an intern.
(Intern Kim Jong Kook)
An intern?
- Hey, you.
- Look at you.
- Come here.
- Be nice.
Now that I'm an intern,
I can just knock you down and quit.
Gosh, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, please.
- I'm just an intern.
You're right about that.
You should get promoted.
He's not dressed
like a full-time employee yet.
Today, you have two clients...
looking for their ideal types,
Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min.
(They will look for Ji Hyo
and So Min's ideal types.)
- I get it.
- Okay.
- They are our clients.
- I get it.
(Client Song Ji Hyo)
Sleep is a time just for myself
and for recharging my batteries.
(Sleep is a time just for myself
and for recharging my batteries.)
I had a good sleep.
(I had a good sleep.)
I'm feeling refreshed
after a good sleep.
(I'm feeling refreshed
after a good sleep.)
My ideal type?
My ideal type is... Well...
The shoot has begun.
We're starting now, Ji Hyo.
I want to meet a man who respects
and understands my lifestyle.
(I want to meet a man who respects
and understands my lifestyle.)
That's all I'm asking for.
(That's all I'm asking for.)
I like to read.
(I like to read.)
And I listen to music a lot.
What I like to listen to...
is exciting music.
And...
I'm always writing when I'm alone.
I want a man who'll read my writing
and relate to them.
They say beautiful people
like flowers.
I like flowers too.
I'm looking for a man
who will enjoy those things with me.
Is there anyone...
who can do that?
(The two extraordinary clients
are looking for their soulmates.)
It will be important
for both companies...
to find out what the clients like.
The two clients are not easy
to deal with.
They are polar opposites.
They are quite unusual.
They are completely different.
The two clients will rate...
their level of satisfaction
after each mission.
And they will give points
to the company...
that offered better service.
- It will be hard.
- The company with higher points...
will be the winner.
And the three employees
in the highest positions...
will get 3.75g of gold each.
- It's about 10g in total.
- Really?
10g of gold?
- My gosh.
- 10g of gold...
- It's quite good.
- It's not bad.
- All right.
- So...
you will need to work hard...
- to get on your boss's good side.
- Okay.
We will move to the next venue
and start the mission.
(Which company will get
10g of gold after the race?)
Gosh, the setting is a little...
This is like "Hot Brothers."
(The employees are gathered
in the next venue for the mission.)
What is this?
- It's like an avatar.
- Everyone.
Before we start the mission,
you will play Avatar Date...
to find out
the two clients' tastes...
and evaluate
the two companies' competence.
That sounds fun.
- We haven't done this for long.
- It will be fun.
Is this serious?
- Are we doing this seriously?
- Well...
(The two clients are waiting
in a fancy restaurant.)
Well...
(The two clients are waiting
in a fancy restaurant.)
Do people usually eat at restaurants
like this?
Sure, on a blind date.
- Really?
- Yes.
I've never been
on a blind date before.
So what do people usually talk about
on a blind date?
- What do you talk about?
- First, they usually...
I usually ask
about his blood type...
and about food,
movies, or music that he likes.
That's what I ask.
As soon as I sat here,
I wanted to go home.
- You've never done this before?
- No.
(The two clients are
polar opposites.)
- Not even once?
- No.
It feels so uncomfortable...
to be on a date like this.
We're here to get
to know each other.
- Right.
- That's the purpose.
The CEOs of each company...
who are not well-acquainted
with the clients,
Sung Si Kyung and Lee Yong Jin...
will go on the virtual date
with Ji Hyo and So Min...
getting orders from the members
through the radio.
It's a double date.
Each company will try
many different things...
and check the clients' responses.
And they will figure out
their ideal types.
After the date,
the clients will rate...
- the level of their satisfaction.
- That's the good part.
And the team with a higher score
will get points.
But our team is...
Si Kyung is single,
but our CEO is married.
We're in a disadvantageous position.
Why do you think so?
He's just an avatar.
It doesn't matter.
His looks are a lot worse
than our CEO's anyway.
- Excuse me, Employee Yang.
- Yes.
What do you mean
his looks are worse?
He's not an employee.
He's a manager.
- I'm a manager.
- What?
- I'm a senior managing director.
- Senior Managing Director Yu.
We work at different companies!
(He just realizes that
he doesn't need to bow to him.)
- I shouldn't have bowed to him.
- Mister.
Hey, mister.
- Hey.
- Hey, Intern.
- Sit down.
- Don't talk down to me.
- You're just an intern.
- How could you...
- How dare you talk down to me?
- Hey.
You're not even my colleague.
- Get your hands out of your pocket.
- Excuse me.
He's a grandpa.
Be polite.
He can't beat us
using his brainpower,
so he's using his strength.
I can't use my brainpower,
but I can use my physical power.
Show him.
He's serious.
Why are you being so edgy?
He used to be a political gangster.
A political gangster?
That's what he used to do.
He was in the political world.
He was a political gangster.
I think it'll be important
to form a connection.
It's like, "I feel the same way."
He does sound like a CEO.
Mr. Lee, you know what?
You should do this right.
- You're blocking the camera.
- Right.
- We don't need it.
- Move over.
- Don't worry about the camera.
- Just move over.
He's just an intern,
so he can't even check the cameras.
Mr. Lee, let me talk.
- I'm sorry,
- Mr. Lee.
but get us a steak.
I'm not a waiter,
Senior Managing Director Yu.
- I want a steak.
- It's not like that.
I'm your employee.
Our CEO is married,
so he has some dating experience.
- Your wife's name Bo A, right?
- Yes, but...
Are you just blurting it out? Yes.
(Surprised)
- He knows everything.
- Right. She's Bo A.
His wife is Na Kyung Eun,
and his wife is Ryu Su Jung.
My wife is Kim Go Eun.
- His wife is Kim Go Eun.
- Right.
And his wife is Yoon Eun Hye.
(And his wife is Yoon Eun Hye.)
Not anymore.
(It's a name from his memory
from 15 years ago.)
That was so sudden.
My gosh.
She's not your wife anymore.
Out of nowhere...
It was silent for half a second.
That was a long time ago.
(My goodness.)
- Not anymore.
- It's been years.
(Closing his ears)
- "Of course."
- That's right.
The CEOs should leave now.
And you'll see the date
on the monitor.
Good luck, Mr. Lee.
- Why am I feeling nervous?
- Good luck.
You don't need to feel nervous.
- Just be comfortable.
- Mr. Sung.
We will make you a gentleman.
- You don't have to worry.
- Okay.
- I'll do the basic things my way.
The rest of you should wear
the in-ear earphones...
- and talk through the radio.
- Okay.
(The two avatars come out
and put on the earphones.)
This is so fun.
The game might end quickly.
In So Min's case,
once she finds a guy she likes,
she only cares about him.
- Right.
- That's true.
- The beginning part is important.
- Right.
Yong Jin is in trouble.
So Min won't care about him.
But Mr. Lee is...
I went on some group dates
with him before.
- He's good.
- He's popular with girls.
- Girls like him a lot.
- Mr. Lee is popular.
He's good. He's funny and witty.
He was very popular.
He is still popular.
And he looks friendly.
- He's easy to grow attached to.
- Exactly.
(How will the blind date go with
Sung Ballad and Popular Yong Jin?)
(Surprised)
- Hello.
Hello.
(Which avatar will captivate
the clients' hearts?)
Where should we sit?
- Hello.
Hello.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Please have a seat.
He looks very confident.
- Look at his smile.
- Who's the petty guy behind him?
He's a smiling angel.
- That coward.
- Yong Jin looks...
- so pathetic.
- Yong Jin is really...
He looks so pathetic.
It's good that
our CEO came in first.
Please have a seat.
Did you hear that?
Our members would make a fuss.
But he said, "Please have a seat."
It sounded so calm.
It's something I've never heard.
- Please have a seat.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
(Laughing)
(She feels so excited
that she can't stop smiling.)
This feels strange.
It feels unfamiliar.
- It's strange.
- I know.
So Min is acting cute.
I hate that.
What's with her voice?
My gosh.
This is really nice, isn't it?
- Today, we're...
- You two are very beautiful.
Thank you.
So Min is serious. Look at her face.
- Look at So Min.
- Right?
But either So Min or Ji Hyo
could go out with him.
She's serious. Look at her face.
- You're right, Jong Kook.
- See?
Have you decided what to eat?
What should we eat?
Order whatever you want.
Isn't this a date?
You can do whatever you want.
What do you like to eat?
- Do you want to order one of each?
- Yes.
- That's good.
- One pasta.
- And one pizza.
- We can ask for a recommendation.
Excuse me.
Can we tell him what to do now?
Yes, you can.
- Tenderloin.
- One salmon salad, please.
One salmon salad, please.
And...
One steak, please.
- One steak, please.
- A steak.
And give me some pocket money.
And...
give me some pocket money.
Give me some pocket money.
(Giggling)
I'm afraid I can't.
(He asks for money
with a sweet voice.)
It worked.
- It worked!
- They like it.
Are they smiling for real?
It worked. I knew it.
They're smiling.
By the way, the way you talk...
Si Kyung is really...
That's not the voice I usually hear.
It's something
we can never hear here.
You have a calm and warm voice.
The thing is,
I've seen you a lot on TV.
- I grew up listening to your songs.
- I know.
Saying I love you
Why is she being like this
when she doesn't get any orders?
(So Min starts singing
without anyone's orders.)
I don't get any orders.
Look at So Min. This is crazy.
What's funny is...
Si Kyung is serious too.
He seems to enjoy this a lot.
Can you see what they're doing?
Look at So Min. Can you see that?
Mr. Sung, drink some water.
Gargle before you swallow the water.
You're right.
Then do you usually think...
(Gargling)
(The clear gargling sound
echoes through the room.)
He gargles all of a sudden.
(Oral hygiene is most important
in this day and age.)
Do you usually do that?
My father is
from Gyeongsang Province.
On his first date with Mom,
he had some coffee and...
Save your breath.
(What?)
(We didn't tell him to do that.)
He wasn't told to say that.
- Good.
- He wasn't even told to say that.
- Just say what you're told.
- That's what I'm told.
That's what I heard.
You'll see that on TV.
I'll watch it on TV.
(The mutinous AI
is working on its own.)
So what kind of man do you like?
- Me?
- Yes.
She likes to meet guys
in a natural way.
- Naturally?
- That's what she likes.
- This is her first time to do...
- Ji Hyo, do you need an ashtray?
Ji Hyo.
Do you need an ashtray?
(Ji Hyo, do you need an ashtray?)
Can you tell Kwang Soo
that I'm going to kill him?
She said she'll kill Kwang Soo.
What? She didn't laugh?
It was just a joke.
I thought she would respond
in a witty way.
Pretend that you're looking
for a cigarette in your pocket.
(The orders are
getting more difficult.)
Do you smoke cigars?
(He's doing as he was told.)
Give me one.
Oh, I'm sorry. I left my cigars
at home.
It was being charged.
I can't believe
that Ji Hyo played along with that.
She seems to like that joke.
- You must like jokes.
- You seem a little uncomfortable.
Yes, I feel uncomfortable
in a situation like this.
- Right?
- Yes. I feel so awkward...
If this was an actual blind date,
it would likely fail.
- I can tell you don't like this.
- Shut your dirty mouth.
Hey, shut your dirty mouth.
Don't do anything
you're not told to do.
That's not the case. I just...
- I might punch you.
- It wasn't like that.
(Si Kyung got mad
because of the rude comment.)
Si Kyung...
- looks so upset.
- Si Kyung is angry.
- He suddenly got upset.
- Why would he get upset?
He's getting angry at Yong Jin.
(The avatars have
a clear rank order.)
- Don't think...
- I just take orders.
Don't think that Jong Kook is
the only one who can hit you.
I just take orders. It's true.
That was so funny.
What are your hobbies?
I play tennis. I like sports.
But what I like to do most is
having a drink...
- with the people I like.
- Right. That's really fun.
- Having a glass with my friends.
- Of course.
- I got hooked on makgeolli.
- Makgeolli?
- I'm back on makgeolli too.
- You're back on it?
- So Min...
- She doesn't care about Yong Jin...
- only looks at Si Kyung.
- at all.
She won't give him a chance
to talk to her.
Yong Jin seems sulky.
I'd like to tell you something
about me. I also...
Si Kyung, eat the bread
without using your hand.
(Eat the bread
without using your hand.)
Let's eat. Shall we?
Flower petals...
(Biting)
(The ballad king's
hands-free eating habit)
(Well...)
That was too...
Hey, that was...
(Being an avatar is an extreme job.)
That's hilarious.
- The bread is warm and tasty.
- That's...
Yong Jin, say your catchphrase.
While giving the bread,
say, "You catch it and eat it."
Here. You can eat mine too.
You should catch it.
You can't catch it, can you?
Bread, bread.
(Looking serious again)
Nicely done. That was good.
- Great job.
- He made Ji Hyo laugh.
- Ji Hyo is laughing.
- I knew it.
That was funny.
You fool, you fool.
Ji Hyo doesn't know what that is.
She doesn't know his catchphrase.
If she doesn't know,
he must look like a crazy person.
(He only looks like a talented crook
to Ji Hyo.)
I didn't know that I would do this
after releasing a new album.
Yong Jin, you released a song album
with Se Chan, right?
- Yes, I did.
- I saw you rap in the music video.
(It would be nice)
(Breathing in)
(He's showing off his singing skills
in front of the original singer.)
That's good.
(If I was walking with you
along this street)
(Sniffling)
(He's eating snot and bread
at the same time.)
I used to listen to this song
very often especially in spring.
(Si Kyung is staying calm
while pouring everyone a glass.)
- "Thought It Would Be Nice."
- Do you...
Pour it on your bread and eat it.
(Pour it on your bread and eat it.)
(Sighing)
- Are you serious?
- Europeans do this these days.
(Ballad Sung, the king of mentality,
Europeans do this these days.)
Italians eat bread...
- soaked in a drink like this.
- Oh, my.
(Biting)
(The great ballad singer is
showcasing a great eating habit.)
- What's that?
- Look at Ji Hyo's face.
- Look at her face.
- Ji Hyo genuinely hates it.
- That's so funny.
- Thank you.
By the way, you both look great
in light colors.
You look even prettier
from this angle.
I like your hairstyle,
especially the color.
- My hair color? Thank you.
- Yes.
- Good. That's a necessary comment.
- Absolutely.
What are your thoughts on marriage?
(Serious)
I believe that marriage is not
just about romance, but reality.
People have high expectations
from their partners at first.
I think that most people
around my age have such thoughts.
Some of my friends are married,
and it's not like I have
no dating experience.
(No, no, no,
what's wrong with your age?)
(No, no, no)
(What's wrong with your age?)
He always sings like that.
(Here comes
the technically skilled singer.)
(He can sing any given songs
with great techniques.)
You're right. Age doesn't matter.
Age doesn't matter.
You did it so well. Great job.
- He even clinked glasses with her.
- He did a great job.
- He did really well.
- Indeed.
I have one more question.
You don't want...
a long-term relationship
before marriage, right?
Do you want to get married
soon after you meet someone?
No, I don't want marriage
to be my purpose of dating a man.
How would you two describe
a good man?
I want a man who knows
when to apologize.
Of course. That's important.
- I see.
- I'm so sorry
(I'm so sorry)
I like his singing voice.
(He started singing
as soon as he got inspiration.)
You're such a great singer.
- He's really good at singing.
- He has an attractive voice.
I like how he sang it.
That was good.
- He's so good at singing.
- Indeed.
(Meanwhile, the main dishes came!)
My, that looks delicious.
Hooray! The food is here.
(He sounds like a sly man
in front of someone higher in rank.)
I'm sorry. That came out wrong.
(Everyone is satisfied with the tone
that doesn't suit Si Kyung.)
Before you start eating,
say, "Hooray! It's pasta."
Hooray, it's pasta.
(Si Kyung is improving
his sly tone of voice.)
I guess you say "hooray" often.
Yes.
(Slurping)
(The advanced skill
of eating noodles without cutlery)
The way he eats pasta seems...
- I'll try it too.
- so fun.
It tastes better as it all comes
into my mouth at once.
I see.
- Ji Hyo is trying it too?
- They're both trying it.
When no one told her to do so.
Both of them are eating it that way.
(They're gobbling down the food
with their heads down.)
My, it's good.
(She does look adorable though.)
This is not a blind date.
This is a zoo tour,
not a blind date.
What do you find attractive
in women?
I like the type of woman
like my wife.
What do you like about her?
There must be things about her
that you found attractive.
First of all, she's much prettier
than you girls.
- First of all, my wife is...
- It's delicious.
much prettier than you girls.
(My wife is much prettier
than you girls.)
(He brags about his wife
regardless of the time and place.)
Why did he even go on a blind date
if he was going to be like that?
Hey, are you...
Are you trying to ruin everything?
That's so funny.
Hey, just do what you're told to do.
I was told to say it.
I'm having such a hard time
following their orders.
- Were you really told to say it?
- Yes, I was. Believe me.
Which one do you two prefer?
A good singer...
or a good dancer?
Which one do you two prefer?
A good singer...
or a good dancer?
- A good singer.
- Yong Jin is good at both.
I'm good at both
if I had to brag about myself.
- Being good at both is the best.
- Why don't I show you?
Why don't I show you?
- May I show you?
- Yes, please.
(How well could Yong Jin
sing and dance?)
I like singing rock songs,
but I like dancing to dance songs.
One day, I saw you
Crying
(He's the type that uses techniques
when dancing as well.)
I wanted to run to you
(Imitating a horse)
That's good.
(He imitated a horse neighing
at the end for no reason.)
Good job. That was really good.
You definitely impressed them.
(Yong Jin impressed
the girls greatly.)
- So Min, aren't you a good dancer?
- If there's something...
So Min, aren't you a good dancer?
- I do like dancing, but...
- I see.
If it's not too much to ask,
can you show us a little?
What kind of dance?
Or I can dance with you.
Without music?
I'll dance along with you.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(They started dancing without music
on a blind date.)
(The breathtaking couple dance)
- That's not a blind date.
- I'm impressed.
- What kind of blind date is this?
- Yong Jin is doing so well.
Yong Jin is doing so well.
Sing a song, Yong Jin.
(She dances in her own style,
and he dances with techniques.)
Yong Jin, sing a song.
(Scatting)
Look at Si Kyung's face.
What kind of blind date is this?
That was really great.
Ji Hyo, come out.
Next, Ji Hyo, can you come out?
(Ji Hyo, come out.)
(Me?)
There she comes.
- She's coming out.
I might have an upset stomach.
(What?)
- Sing a song.
- Yo, let's go
(Singing gibberish)
What was that?
(Ji Hyo started dancing
to the gibberish song.)
I really like Yong Jin's boldness.
That's one of my favorite songs.
(Standing up)
That's not a blind date.
(The natural-born dancer got excited
and joined them.)
You don't call that blind date.
(I don't want to hang out
with them.)
- That's okay.
- Si Kyung, come out.
Si Kyung, can you come out?
(The active dance singer has been
called out.)
All right! That's perfect!
That's great.
This is so fun to watch.
(Hesitating)
(I wanted to run to you)
(Sighing)
(They don't know how to react
unlike usual.)
(The employees of Single Dot-com are
satisfied.)
Si Kyung is upset. He's upset now.
I'd like to hear you sing too.
I released a song recently.
- Did you?
- Really?
- But it's a sad song. Is it okay?
- Of course.
(So Min collaborated with a singer
as a lyricist and a vocalist.)
("Reasons for Not Cutting Long Hair"
by Choi Botton and Jeon So Min)
(Love is the same)
(Love is like a poison)
Doze off. Doze off.
Love is like a flower
(Entering REM sleep)
Yong Jin, lie down and sleep.
Lie down on the floor and sleep.
(Yong Jin, lie down on the floor
and sleep.)
(The avatars are drunk
by the lullaby.)
What's going on? Where am I?
(So Min's singing voice is the best
for putting avatars to sleep.)
(Jeon So Min, the queen of lullaby)
(That's hilarious.)
Where am I?
(Where am I?)
That was good.
Apologize to her. Apologize first.
Apologize to her first.
- You should apologize to her.
- I'm sorry.
- You should keep good manners.
I haven't slept so soundly
in the past three years. Thank you.
- I'm sorry. And thank you.
- I know that it's... Yes?
I haven't slept so soundly
in the past three years. Thank you.
Seeing how quickly we fell asleep,
I think it's a great song.
Indeed. I was surprised.
I slept as if
I was under anesthesia.
As if you were under anesthesia?
(The song can make you feel like
you're under anesthesia.)
The song is not that boring.
I'm sorry to ask you for this,
but if it's not too much to ask,
can you sing your new song for us?
The song title "I Love U,"
which may sound cheesy.
"I Love U?"
(Si Kyung gladly sings his new song
upon the request of his client.)
It took me too long
- to tell you how I feel
- Doze off.
(He went under anesthesia
for the 2nd time.)
My gosh. What's going on?
- Just do what you're told to do.
- My gosh.
Oh, dear. My goodness.
Thank you so much.
Look at Si Kyung's face.
- Thank you so much.
- It's a great song.
I slept well thanks to you.
(Polite)
It's time to say goodbye.
You did a good job.
Yong Jin, be a gentleman
when you say goodbye to them.
Also, I'd like to thank you both...
for such a great time.
Although I did some rude things,
I did those only to figure out
your characteristics.
That's why I did those things.
- It was sort of a test.
- I had so much fun.
Although we were here as avatars,
I think we got to know you a little.
Like the different types you like,
your personalities,
and what you want from a man.
We'll split the bill, right?
How shall we pay for the food?
- Let's split the bill.
- What?
It's on me.
Hooray, I can save money.
(Hooray! I can save money!)
(The blind date ended
with the sly tone of his voice.)
"Hooray, I can save money."
Good job, you both.
Good job, Si Kyung and Yong Jin.
- That was so funny.
- Great job.
Good job, you guys.
- Sir.
- Good job, So Min.
- Please come in.
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
So Min, Si Kyung went on
about how cute you are.
- He's crazy about you.
- Yes, he is.
Have a seat, So Min.
(Stop it.)
Look at her.
- Jong Kook is not a detective.
- Come to the center.
The two clients, Ji Hyo and So Min,
finished evaluating...
both companies' services
based on the blind date.
Let's start with So Min.
So Min, please put a sticker...
on the board of the team
that you're more satisfied with.
- I evaluated objectively.
- You should be objective.
Of course. Since Yong Jin is
a very funny man...
When I was dancing,
- You seemed excited.
- to be honest,
I thought I could hear music.
- Really?
- Yes, he was so good...
I want to do it again. Can't you
do it again for me? Please?
Of course. No problem at all.
(He started singing right away.)
(She's dancing to the song
automatically.)
(Her body reacted first
to the familiar singing voice.)
- That was so good.
- What song was that?
- I can do an EDM song too.
- She's one cheery girl.
- An EDM song?
- Please do that.
(The human jukebox sings
an EDM song as well.)
(Let's dance to the EDM song!)
Scream!
(Scream!)
(They have perfect teamwork
as if they prepared this.)
(It was a successful collaboration.)
He's amazing.
He's as good as Jeong Jong Chul.
- That was so much fun.
- He's amazing.
- I really liked it so much.
- He has such a great voice.
- I liked it so much.
- He has a great voice.
I knew that Yong Jin was funny,
- but Si Kyung was so funny too.
- Really?
- When he ate the bread...
- I see why she liked it.
- That's what I like.
- Right.
It's because you didn't expect
to see him act like that.
(He lowered his head
with a little smile...)
(and had a bite.)
(She liked it so much.)
It's because I didn't expect him
to act like that.
- It was an unexpected charm.
- It really was unexpected.
And he said with his sweet voice
that I never hear on Running Man,
"Please have a seat.
What shall we order?"
I gave 13 points to this team
and 10 points to the other.
Great. We got three more points.
13 to 10.
- You can put it on here. Thank you.
- Ji Hyo might give us her sticker.
Thank you!
He was as funny as Yong Jin.
What I liked about Si Kyung was...
I liked how he kept looking me
in the eyes while talking to me.
Eye contact is important.
I liked it so much,
and I gave the team five points.
- We won.
- We won again.
We won again.
We won, we won again
- We won.
- Hooray! We won again.
- We lost.
- We won again.
- They got more points.
- We won
Then we'll move
to the next location.
- Yes!
- Okay.
The weather is so nice.
The weather is really nice.
(Under the clear blue sky,
food is served on the table.)
You can bond
with your team members...
and learn more about the ladies
while enjoying the food freely.
- Okay.
- Really?
- They ordered catering.
- We can just eat it?
We haven't eaten outside like this
in a long time, right?
- Oh, dear.
- They prepared delicious food.
- I'll drink a beverage later.
- Since we're all tired...
- I see a lot of chicken breasts.
- I should eat some Korean food.
I feel like I'm on a picnic.
- Look at that.
- It looks delicious.
Intern Ji, enjoy your meal.
- Are you talking to me?
- Yes.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Oh, I see. Thank you.
- Let's talk later.
- Oh, that?
Intern Ji, enjoy your meal.
- What did you just say?
- It's chili powder.
(He's an assistant manager
and Se Chan is a manager.)
- "What did you just say?"
- Oh, I see.
- I'm sorry.
- Who do you think you are?
- Let's talk later.
Two CEOs can change their
employees' positions at any time.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- By the way, Suk Jin,
- Yes.
I think I should change yours
as you have great passion.
Really?
- Yes.
- CEO Lee.
Thank you so much.
I'll change your sticker
with a new one.
- Is he still an intern?
- Yes.
You can put the new one
on top of it.
(He gave him a new sticker.)
- It does look shiny and nice.
- It looks nice.
- CEO Lee is so funny.
- CEO Lee.
- He has a good personality.
- Yes.
He's friendly too.
And I also found out...
- that he has no criminal records.
- Right.
- That's true.
- So...
- I have no criminal records.
- I'll promote you to an employee.
- Thank you. Okay!
- This is really nice.
(The thug got a promotion.)
Jong Kook is an employee now.
We're in trouble. He got promoted.
What? Jong Kook got promoted?
You should butter CEO Sung up
to make our company successful.
Don't you want to get a promotion,
Assistant Manager Lee?
(Assistant Manager Lee made up
his mind following his advice.)
- with strawberries in it.
- Go and butter him up.
CEO Sung, do you need anything more?
That's okay. I've eaten enough.
(- Do you need anything more?
- That's okay. I've eaten enough.)
- You don't have to do that.
- Pardon?
- Is there anything...
- Don't make him uncomfortable.
- It's not like that.
- Sir.
- You're trying to get a promotion.
- What's wrong with you?
- Sir.
- Yes?
- Can I talk to you briefly?
- Yes.
- Are you an assistant manager?
- It's rice cake.
- Can you drive my car...
Pardon me?
Can you drive my car to my house...
I'm not a chauffeur.
- I don't do things like that.
- You don't?
Sir, this is how people treat me
because I'm an assistant manager.
- You don't do that?
- They ask me to be their chauffeur.
I'm being mistreated.
- Work a little harder.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay. That happens.
- Okay.
- I was mistaken.
- You're very tall.
- Yes.
- You're so tall.
Can you put that light bulb
in your mouth?
(Can you put that light bulb
in your mouth?)
- I'm just curious.
- He's ridiculous.
(Can you put that light bulb
in your mouth?)
(I'm just curious
since you're tall.)
- He's the CEO of my company.
- I'm just curious since you are...
- really tall.
- I mean...
- He's my company's CEO.
- Why would I put it in my mouth?
- Try it, Mr. Lee.
- Don't be upset.
- It's understandable.
- I was just curious.
Can he put that light bulb
in his mouth?
- Wasn't that a ridiculous question?
- I think he can do it.
Here are some more.
(Oh, no!)
- Oh, no.
- I like rice cake.
- I know. Right? It's good.
- I think...
- I just spilled the juice.
- I like rice cake too...
But you didn't ask if I was okay
or try to help me.
Is this how you treat your clients?
- The glass made a loud noise,
- It wasn't like that.
but you were too busy
eating that rice cake...
Would you like one?
For that piece of rice cake...
You're pulling a power trip
because you're our client.
How could you say that?
I can't work with you.
He works at Yong Jin's company,
right?
- Married Corporation.
- You shouldn't raise your voice...
- at our client.
- Right.
- Yes.
- He's right.
Get on the ground
and do some push-ups.
(Get on the ground
and do some push-ups.)
- Do it.
- Do it now.
- Do as CEO Lee says.
- It's a company rule.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You should do it.
He might actually...
Right. Go on and do as he said.
Do it unless you want to get fired.
CEO Lee, if you really want me
to do it, I would...
- No, I didn't mean it like that.
- Are you sure?
I'm just saying
that you should be more careful.
I see. Of course, I'll be careful.
- That was so funny.
- That's too much.
- Did someone eat my rice cake?
- Yes.
Was it you?
What is this?
(At the next location...)
- I recognize this. The green light.
- What's this?
I saw it on the show
where CEO Sung...
- Quiet down, everyone!
- Okay.
My gosh.
- Don't you think...
- Well...
it was related to the context?
I really wanted to see that face.
I mean, where this red light...
Through this mission,
you can see what the clients think
about different situations.
- It's Turn on the Red Light.
- Turn on the Red Light.
As those who checked
our social media must know,
we received many love stories
from our viewers...
for four days through social media.
Among the 833 stories we received,
- we selected a few.
- Sounds great.
- Among so many stories...
- How did you select them?
Listen to the story...
and decide whether or not to turn on
the red light.
After a debate on all those stories,
Ji Hyo and So Min...
will give the members whose opinions
you agree with the most...
with three stars just as they want.
- We can get 3 stars?
- 3 stars?
- I'm confident.
- That's not all.
- Jong Kook is good at this game.
- They can give all 3 to 1 person...
or give each to a different member.
It's up to them.
I'm sure you guys know us well...
- Of course, we know you well.
- Of course.
By the way, Se Chan and Kwang Soo...
don't know much about dating.
Don't you think so?
- Exactly.
- But we all have experience.
- Kwang Soo is dating someone.
- I see.
But he doesn't seem to have
a girlfriend now.
- You mean Se Chan? Right.
- CEO Lee...
- knows all my dating history.
- You know him well.
- He could be dating someone.
- He's the type...
that lets his girlfriend control him
while crying like a baby.
- Are you kidding me?
- What?
You're one to talk.
Should I tell them about you?
- What about you?
- I'll talk, you know.
I'll tell them about you too.
- I will, you know.
- That's enough.
- I might even name names.
- Guys, that's enough.
I haven't so far
for your wife's sake.
CEO Sung, will you
read the first one?
His voice. I love his voice.
- You know...
- Right?
- CEO Sung.
- Yes?
Due to your last name being "Sung,"
it makes you sound
like the sex expert.
That's right, the sex expert.
- Right.
- You seem like one...
who is certified in that area.
CEO Sung, the sex expert.
The sex expert?
I did host a show
by the name of "Witch Hunt."
Yes, of course.
That's right.
He's the sex expert
among balladeers.
- It seems that way.
- Ballad Sung.
(The sex expert reads
the first one.)
Title. "Is That All I Meant to You?"
"Hello, I'm a 36-year-old woman
with a corporate job."
"I've been dating a man
3 years my senior for 100 days now."
I see.
They're in the honeymoon phase then.
"I'm one of those people
who need to see her boyfriend..."
"at least once a day
even if it's only for a minute."
"However, since we both
have corporate jobs..."
"and live about an hour apart,"
"we can't dream of
going out on a weekday."
"Since I missed him so much,"
"I suggested that we..."
"spend both Saturday
and Sunday together."
("Is That All I Meant to You?")
But for men...
- My gosh.
- She cut off his air supply.
I already feel smothered too.
- I hate it.
- "My boyfriend agreed to it,"
"and for three weeks..."
"on the weekend..."
Get me an oxygen tank!
It's like this.
(The air is being sucked
out of him.)
Don't!
Just don't.
Don't come any closer.
- Get over here.
- Don't come any closer.
(Spending the weekend together
is brutal for some people.)
- It's only been 100 days.
- Right, that's true.
- Yes, 100 days.
- Not 2 years,
- but 100 days.
- Yes, that's the honeymoon phase.
He's right.
"For three weeks,
we spent our weekends together."
"It washed away
the longing I'd been feeling."
"But as time went by,
my boyfriend started..."
"to push back the time we'd meet."
"From 11 a.m. to 1 p.m."
- "And then to 2 p.m."
- Of course.
"I first thought
it had to do with his work."
"But then,"
"after trying to find
the right moment, he said this."
"He didn't mind
being with me all weekend,"
"but he wanted at least
a day to himself too."
He got caught in the trap.
Oh, no.
(We all know deep down
what'll happen next.)
I don't know why I'm in tears.
You can relate to the story.
I'm in tears.
"I'd understand
if we were an old couple in a rut,"
"but we've only been dating
for about 100 days."
"Meeting other friends
and enjoying your time alone..."
"is something you can do
on a weekday after work."
Must you say it in that tone?
And what tone is that?
- I was trying to sound annoyed.
- It showed.
(Annoyed)
(He sounds exactly like
an annoyed girlfriend.)
(Professor Sung
can not only sing but also act.)
I'm in tears over here.
"Ever since then, we've been
meeting up only once a week."
"However, I still feel like
it's not enough."
"Would it be okay to ask..."
"that we spend
the entire weekend together again?"
"Or should I just accept
and respect his wishes?"
(More dating time versus
at least a day to himself)
Once a week
doesn't seem like enough though.
- They're a new couple.
- It's only been 100 days,
so a date once a week isn't enough.
- It's too short.
- But since it's the weekend...
The boyfriend being 39
should be considered too.
You see,
he's at an age where he needs
to focus on getting ahead in life.
- And he needs rest.
- Right.
- I'd like to say something too.
- Go ahead.
The girlfriend wouldn't
have written about it...
if this hadn't been
stressing her out.
The boyfriend should
understand that.
Of course.
This is how I see it.
If he truly loves his girlfriend,
he'll change his mind.
- Of course.
- He must be well past that stage.
How can you be so
emotionally stunted?
- What?
- Are you challenging us?
- I'd love nothing more.
Sounds good to me.
It brings joy to my ears.
- Hey.
- Sounds good.
(The CEO tries
to calm his employee.)
- You two...
- Why are you on your feet?
Are you his minions?
How about a fight
between minions then?
I see you're quite tall.
- I see you're quite tall.
- Right.
Can you stuff that projector
in your mouth?
Why do you keep asking me that?
Because you're tall, that's all.
(CEO Lee is the curious type.)
Why would one
shove that in his mouth?
- You see...
- Are you good?
This might sound drastic, but still.
What if the boyfriend
gives himself a nosebleed...
during one of their dates?
- On purpose?
- It's not like that.
Don't think of it as a hoax.
It'll benefit both of them.
What if he got sick?
- He could get sick.
- You know,
like this.
In my opinion, this isn't about
the number of dates,
but how they express
their feelings for one another.
Even though
they're not physically together,
saying things like
"I miss you and I love you..."
could comfort the girlfriend...
- and fill the obvious void.
- Right.
So what you're saying is this.
Whether they go on
one or two dates a week,
she needs to know that he loves her.
- He needs to express it.
- That's what you're saying.
In my opinion though,
one should be more attentive
during the early stages.
- He's right.
- Right.
In my case,
when I first started
to date my wife,
I was busy with work.
But I still went to see her
even though it was for five minutes.
- And that would be enough.
- But for how long?
- How sweet of you.
- It's enough to fill the void.
During the early stages,
I'd go running to her...
- on rainy days.
- Of course.
Whom did you go running to?
My current wife.
- We lived close by.
- When was it?
- What? Whom?
- We lived...
Take that, you jerk.
Your wife used to live close by?
What?
- You lived...
- That wasn't the case.
Were you lying?
She lived in Gangnam,
which was nowhere near your house.
I'm a guest on your show, you jerk.
- Help a brother out.
- What?
Why must you nitpick everything?
Your wife would be startled,
that's why.
So here's my suggestion.
- On a non-date day...
- A nosebleed?
"What are you up to?
I'm outside your house."
- "Can I see you?"
- An unexpected visit.
Show up with an IV drip...
(Outside the window)
(The nosebleed guy
now has an IV drip.)
An IV drip?
Just think about it.
With an IV drip...
(With an IV drip stuck to him,
he can greet her with a big smile.)
Look at it go back out.
(He makes himself look even sicker.)
- "I love you."
- Jae Suk, it's an act of love.
- Right?
- Totally.
"I'm good now!"
- "We can be apart for a month."
- Exactly.
- That's...
- Those actions are most important.
It's most important.
The people of that company...
What? What about us?
The losers are more...
- Losers?
- Seriously?
- Hold on.
- Must you speak so cruelly?
- I spoke cruelly?
How about I be cruel
in another way then?
Wait.
No, don't.
Get on your feet.
How about I make
something else go red?
(The political thug
shows his true colors.)
How old are you guys anyway?
- Should we get reinforcements?
- How old are you?
Should we get reinforcements?
Look. He's taller than
the air conditioner.
He's taller than
Wait a second.
Why does he keep
mentioning my height?
He's taller than
the air conditioner.
Why does he keep...
- mentioning my height?
- You're right.
You really are taller
than the air conditioner.
How can he be taller than that?
I was taken aback.
Anyway, what's important...
is that he shouldn't
make his girlfriend...
question his love...
- or their relationship.
- From what I can tell,
he probably didn't call often...
- and became different in a way.
- Exactly.
- It's why she's upset.
- Of course.
We also...
can't ignore their age.
- Absolutely.
- You see,
when you're in your 20s,
you use a joint bank account
for dating expenses,
- but when you're over 30...
- A bank account?
Did you have one
with your girlfriend?
- I mean...
- With which girlfriend?
- The one I know, right?
- Hey!
Take that! Stop it, will you?
- What did I do?
- Stop it already.
The girlfriends of yours I know...
I know a few.
- The one...
- It's the same as singing.
(CEO Lee becomes a different person
in Se Chan's presence.)
From what I can tell,
couples argue
even though they're compatible.
Right?
- Do you and your wife argue too?
- Of course.
- It doesn't seem that way.
- What?
- That doesn't seem like the case.
- We argue.
Let's say I want to open a window...
to cool down, but my wife is cold.
What should I do, right?
I suggest turning on the AC,
but she'd say
it's too early for that.
That's a possible scenario.
- How does it end though?
- What?
How does it end?
I'd open the door
and step outside...
to get some fresh air.
(He steps outside to enjoy
the right kind of temperature.)
So that's why
a lot of husbands and fathers...
can be seen
outside apartment buildings.
"Darn household."
That must be the reason.
In this case,
my wife is the boss of the house,
which is why I step outside.
- Right.
- That's why...
- And now...
- Should she bring it up or not?
Press the button if you think
she should bring it up again.
I don't think she should.
- Same here.
- But then they'd break up.
(They are to press the button...)
(if they think
she should bring it up again.)
1, 2, 3.
- No one.
- Not even one of us.
I think it's best
not to bring it back up.
She wants to though.
- Right.
- She must want to.
- I can relate to both parties.
- Me too.
Same here.
Now that you've heard
the two companies debate,
please give out the three stars...
to anyone you want.
It'll be a tough call.
(A total of 6 stars
are on the line.)
- They...
- To be honest,
I'd like to give the IV drip
all of my three stars.
Because seeing that IV drip...
would make me want to
give him a month off.
So here you go.
- Thank you.
- It's for the IV drip.
We finally scored a point.
Someone else also scratched
the necessary places.
It's Jong Kook.
Thank you.
This next one is a pity star.
Nice!
It sure is nice to be pitied.
A pity star.
(Ji Hyo's up next.)
The IV drip and nosebleed.
(The IV drip wins 2 stars.)
The IV drip and nosebleed
were solid ideas.
- This...
- It was the best.
Did he win two in total?
Two stars?
I'll lead my people better.
I'll encourage that with a star.
- That was close.
- We almost tanked this round.
We're neck and neck now.
Mr. Sung, good going.
- We're now tied.
- It's a tie.
- We're tied.
- We have the same score.
You were able to figure out...
the type of relationships
your clients prefer.
- Right.
- Okay.
In this next round,
you'll get to find out...
what they look for in an ideal man.
This is
the Relationship Balance Game.
The Relationship Balance Game.
In front of me...
are the names of men...
Ji Hyo and So Min
mentioned as their type...
along with the eight of your names.
When did they ever
mention those names?
- Quite often in So Min's case.
- Ji Hyo doesn't have one.
Ji Hyo doesn't have an ideal type.
She barely managed
to come up with one,
and we guessed some.
- She barely managed?
- She had to come up with one.
So you'll pick two balls
from the box...
and add all sorts of modifiers...
to the two people you picked.
Your job is to make it hard
for your client...
to pick one person by making
their conditions equally attractive.
I totally got it.
- For example...
- I get it.
Let's say Jae Suk impresses
his partner with surprise events.
But his opponent, Park Bo Gum,
forgets all the anniversaries
and makes his partner treat a meal.
It's something like this.
I get it.
- So that they can contemplate.
- Your job is...
to make their conditions balanced
so that your client...
can pick the person you want.
(Their job is to balance out
the conditions.)
You got it, right?
We'll pick the candidates...
for So Min first.
Let me tell you whom she picked...
aside from the eight people here.
Gong Myoung, Ahn Jae Hong,
- Kim Dong Jun, Lee Je Hoon,
- She's not shy about it.
Woo Do Hwan, Jinyoung of GOT7,
Did she mention
all the guests we had?
Ahn Bo Hyun, and Ha Suk Jin.
And the eight people here.
Those are the guys
that So Min likes.
- There's more, right?
- Did she mention Gong Myoung?
- There must be more.
- She did mention Gong Myoung.
- We need one of them to come.
Let me reveal Ji Hyo's list.
- Tom Hardy.
- Yes, Tom Hardy.
- Brad Pitt.
- She likes foreign actors.
So she likes foreign guys.
Optimus Prime.
- What?
- Optimus Prime?
("Song Ji Hyo's Ideal Type is
Optimus Prime of 'Transformers'")
- Come on!
- Really?
- Come on! That's nonsense.
- The robot?
- That's nonsense.
- Hey.
But it's easy to make modifiers
for Optimus Prime.
We could come up with something
like rusty Optimus Prime.
Optimus Prime that smells
like gasoline.
Let's start with So Min's.
We have a few experts on our team.
- We're experts.
- Let's start with So Min's.
(Who is the first person
to compete against her ideal type?)
The first one is Lee Je Hoon.
We know how to deal with him.
(The 1st candidate is Lee Je Hoon.)
- That's a strong candidate.
- We can write whatever we want.
Next is Se Chan.
(It's Se Chan.)
(Oh, gosh.)
You should describe Je Hoon
on one board,
and describe Se Chan
on the other one.
(Which modifiers
will they come up with?)
We should make something nice
for Se Chan.
How about just ordinary Je Hoon...
and Se Chan
who has ten million dollars?
Actually, I don't really care
about that.
- Really?
- Yes.
Do you want us
to make it more instinctive?
Se Chan who has one billion dollars.
(Hesitating)
That'd be more convincing.
Then why should I see So Min?
I wouldn't see her
if I had a billion dollars.
- I wouldn't see her.
- Oh, really? This isn't right.
How about a jobless Je Hoon
versus the head judge Se Chan?
You need to make him jobless now?
That's infuriating.
They're going
for something materialistic.
- We should...
- We need a different approach.
We're different.
We're going after So Min's emotions.
- Is that so?
- We're after her emotions.
Shall we check out the modifiers
that Single Dot-com wrote?
So Min, you should think through...
and choose the company that came up
with more difficult choices.
- Hey, hey!
- I'm so happy though.
Just the thought of it
makes me happy.
We'll reveal ours now.
- All right.
- First.
Se Chan who only loves So Min
all his life.
He doesn't love anyone else
- Never.
- That already makes my heart beat.
- What's with you?
- That one's okay.
- He has no one else.
- No one at all.
- And...
- This is driving me crazy.
It's time to describe Je Hoon.
- You're not exclusive with him.
- You don't know how it'll turn out.
You're seeing him nonexclusively.
- Hold on.
- It's not exclusive.
(Devoted Se Chan
versus nonexclusive Je Hoon)
I'm seeing Je Hoon?
- Yes, you're seeing him.
- But you'll only love me.
That's right.
- Wow, this is hard.
- She's actually contemplating.
I think I would too.
But you can lose Je Hoon anytime.
He could be seeing someone else
at the same time...
- since it's not exclusive.
- Let's be more specific.
He's dating you.
Does he pat me
on the head sometimes?
- Of course he does.
- Does he pat my head?
- And we text each other every hour?
- Totally.
- Of course.
- But you guys aren't exclusive.
- No, they're not.
- They're not.
This is actually hard.
Think about this.
Even when we're shooting this,
Je Hoon is constantly texting you.
(What are you up to, So Min?)
- Right now. "When does it end?"
- But Je Hoon is not guaranteed.
Se Chan is guaranteed
to love you all your life.
- He's guaranteed.
- He is.
So Min.
So Min, you're the love of my life.
Don't talk like a fool!
(He's used to acting like a fool.)
(This is not what we want!)
- That's not what we're going for.
- Don't talk like a fool!
This isn't what we want!
- That's not how you should talk.
- I'm rich too.
- Talk like a man.
- Okay.
Se Chan,
you can't change how you talk.
You shouldn't talk like that.
All right. Remember how you felt.
Now let's check out
Married Corporation's.
- Ours was intense.
- That was great.
So Min thought a lot.
I'm good at this.
We also prepared 2 options.
Let's check out the 1st one.
- Here.
- I'll cover it.
You're dating Je Hoon,
- but you can't meet him.
- You can't meet him.
He has to live
in Europe all his life.
You're dating Se Chan,
but you can't touch him.
But you can't touch him.
- How does it sound?
- She can't touch me?
- What do you think?
- It's hard to pick one, right?
- You're...
- Of course she'd pick Je Hoon.
They can't touch each other?
It's like Adam the cyber singer.
Of course she'd pick Je Hoon.
- But she can't meet him for life.
- Never in her life.
- Still...
- But they're seeing each other.
But they can't meet each other.
- Hang on.
- She can't touch him?
Then can I video chat with him?
- Yes, you can.
- You can do everything.
- He tells you he loves you.
- For all his life.
Je Hoon is crazy about you.
- He really loves you.
- But you can't meet him.
- He only loves you.
- What's this?
- You can't even eat with him.
Everyone in Korea knows
that you're his girlfriend.
- But they can't meet each other.
- That's right.
Let us give you an easier option.
- How's this?
- Je Hoon who is half animal...
- versus human Se Chan.
- You jerks!
(Half-animal Je Hoon...)
(versus human Se Chan)
- Are you kidding me?
- Je Hoon is half animal.
How could you compare an animal...
- So Min!
- to a human?
A centaur. He's a centaur.
- He walks like this.
- So Min.
- So the upper body...
- He's a centaur.
The upper body is Je Hoon,
but the lower body is a horse.
And he lives in a stable.
- And I'm a human?
- Yes, you are.
Why would you even think about it?
(Contemplating)
But Je Hoon calls So Min like this.
He calls her like this.
(He has to neigh
when he talks to So Min.)
- His lower body could be fish.
- That's possible.
- That's nonsense.
- I'll leave it to your imagination.
All right.
- I've made up my mind.
- Have you?
Pick a team that gave you
more difficult options.
Both teams gave me
difficult options,
but this team's options
were more difficult.
Yes!
(She picks Single Dot-com.)
- Yes, we were more convincing.
- They're trying too hard.
- This is not fair.
- It wasn't fun.
You should've made it
more realistic.
I'll pick Se Chan
from their options.
- What?
- I'd pick Se Chan.
- You'd pick Se Chan?
- Yes, I'd definitely pick Se Chan.
Of course you have to meet
each other.
You turned the innocent Je Hoon...
into a centaur.
- Come on.
- Who would you pick?
Seriously...
(Giving a point to Single Dot-com)
Next is Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
- It'll be fun.
- We need to know what she's after.
(Who will be the first
to be picked?)
- It's Jong Kook.
- That's great.
(Jong Kook is picked.)
- It's me?
- Jong Kook...
- That's great news.
They'll come up
with all sorts of horrible ideas.
It's Won Bin.
Jong Kook and Won Bin?
- We got this.
- It's worth trying.
- Let's just write down everything.
I suddenly got a surge of ideas.
- Won Bin.
- You need to know what exactly...
Ji Hyo wants in men.
- Right.
- But it must be a little difficult.
- I know.
- Right. She's difficult to guess.
Won Bin is too perfect...
to compare to anyone.
The Won Bin that we invented...
- can't be loved by anyone.
- Is that so?
- It's perfect for Ji Hyo.
- It's actually possible.
Ji Hyo would never meet this version
of Won Bin no matter what.
What could it be?
I can't wait to find out.
Shall we check out theirs first
this time?
- Married Corporation.
Here are our options.
A 60-year-old Jong Kook
who only loves Ji Hyo,
but he's a mama's boy.
He needs to get his mom's permission
for everything.
"Mom, can I eat?"
- He asks everything.
- "Mom, can I go to the bathroom?"
- When he's 60?
- But he loves Ji Hyo dearly.
And a pure 11-year-old boy
Won Bin...
- who only loves Ji Hyo.
- He's only 11 years old.
He's a baby. She needs to raise him.
She's supposed
to see an 11-year-old boy?
- But he only loves you.
- He's 11 years old?
That makes him a little kid.
- He's only in third grade.
- Yes, he's a kid.
But Jong Kook is really young
compared to his age.
He's really young,
- but he asks his mom everything.
- He's a mama's boy.
- "Mom, can I kiss Ji Hyo?"
- That's right.
- "Can I have pork cutlet with her?"
- This is...
- I ask her permission to kiss?
Yes, you do.
When he's about to kiss her,
he'd call his mom and ask,
"Mom, can I kiss Ji Hyo?"
- "Would that be okay?"
- "I think it's time I kiss her."
- When I'm 60?
- "Mom."
- Yes, you are.
- I'm 60.
That's just not right.
Then Won Bin is a better option.
He's so much better.
Okay, it seems like
you don't like it.
We have another option here.
- All right. Here it comes.
- Yes.
Jong Kook who only wears
a sleeveless shirt and slippers...
despite the weather and occasion,
versus Won Bin who is half animal.
(Jong Kook who only wears
a sleeveless shirt and slippers...)
(versus half-animal Won Bin)
- Why do you love centaurs so much?
- Why do you keep bringing that up?
- You're just...
- But that keeps the balance.
That's the only option
that keeps the balance.
- That keeps the balance.
Why do you compare us with centaurs?
We tried to use several options,
- And he's even faster than Je Hoon.
- but this is only right.
Why do they
keep bringing up centaurs?
Of course Jong Kook is better.
How dare you compare me to that?
I know it's Won Bin,
but it's still mean.
He's a centaur, but you can't tell
if he's seated.
- You won't be able to tell.
- Even if he's seated...
- You'd never know.
- What if he stands up?
What if he stands up?
And Won Bin cares for Ji Hyo a lot.
Why would you call it even
by making the centaur seated?
- That's not true.
- Don't be so serious.
- He looked so serious.
- How can he be always seated?
His lower body can turn into
any animals he wants.
- The upper body is Won Bin,
- That's right.
but the lower body is a bear.
That'd be really cool.
- That's not cool at all.
- You think a bear is cool?
He'd have no problem
being on social media.
On top of that, he's even faster
than cars when he runs.
That could be his strength.
Let's hear from Single Dot-com.
- I can't wait.
- We reflected...
- what Ji Hyo wants in men.
- Is that so?
We thought about what she despises.
- Won Bin...
- Here we go.
Won Bin who has a mouth
where moths keep coming out.
(Won Bin who has a mouth
where moths keep coming out?)
- From his mouth...
- Hey, hey!
- That's Sha Wujing.
- Hey.
(She shudders as she hates insects.)
Every time he talks, moths come out.
- "I'll destroy you all!"
- That's too much.
Ji Hyo, when he sneezes...
(When he opens his mouth,
an eclipse of moths comes out.)
- That's too much.
- "I'll destroy you all!"
You know the powder
from moths, right?
The moth powder.
You need to vacuum constantly.
- Moths come out of his mouth?
- They keep coming out.
- And?
- Next is Jong Kook.
Jong Kook who eats
cockroach protein every day.
Cockroach protein?
He eats it every day.
- That's not bad.
- It's not a bad thing.
It's not like he eats cockroaches.
He eats the protein.
- He eats cockroaches.
- He needs to grind them.
- He needs to grind cockroaches?
- He eats the ground cockroaches.
- That's right.
- And you can see their legs.
But you can still see the legs
between his teeth.
Ji Hyo hates insects.
- That's why you chose that.
- Right. She hates insects.
Even when Won Bin is sleeping...
(Moths come out of his mouth
even when he's sleeping.)
For Jong Kook...
When you're on a date with him,
- he'd go, "The feelers got stuck."
- Gross!
That's the worst.
I don't think she can choose one.
- It's too hard.
- And he only loves you.
A forever pure Won Bin
who is still a child.
How can she see him when he has
moths coming out of his mouth?
- Yes, moths come out of his mouth.
- Our options are more difficult.
They're both difficult.
- And he constantly...
- Cockroaches?
(Which team will she pick?)
I'll pick...
- Single Dot-com.
- All right!
(Won Bin with moths coming out
of his mouth)
(Single Dot-com
wins twice in a row.)
Yes. We know Ji Hyo so well.
- I knew it.
- It's So Min's turn again.
- It's Gong Myoung.
- This is...
Actually, the guy that So Min likes
the most...
She must like him the most.
- is Gong Myoung.
- Gong Myoung.
Gong Myoung goes to my gym.
Let me see.
- It's Jae Suk.
- We got this. All right.
- We got this.
- It's Jae Suk.
(Exclaiming)
- We got this.
- Let's make him a centaur.
Let's make him a centaur.
- We got this.
Let's say Jong Kook has eight...
- Mr. Lee.
- Yes?
- Isn't this...
- Show it to us. What is it?
- Isn't this too mean?
- I haven't made up my mind yet.
An ordinary grasshopper Jae Suk
who lives in a rice paddy.
(They can't make it a competition
between humans.)
- That's...
- Come on, Mr. Lee.
- But you look so kindhearted.
- Right next to marsh snails.
In peace.
- We...
- We came up with...
They both love So Min dearly.
- That's nice.
- They love her so much.
- She's finally found her love?
- He doesn't have moths either.
- That's good.
- We made it realistic.
- All right.
- Oh, gosh.
Gong Myoung is so busy
that you can only meet once a year.
But he loves So Min so much.
- That's nice.
- You can see him only once.
- Only once a year.
- Next is...
- It's not that bad.
You meet him every day,
but he nags you a lot.
- Jobless Jae Suk.
- He's jobless.
- He has no job?
- No, he doesn't.
- But this is...
- He's jobless.
- You don't know which she'll pick.
- I'd pick...
- Of course she'd pick Jae Suk.
- It's...
But...
But So Min hates it
when someone nags her.
But he doesn't work.
If Jae Suk is jobless...
- That's right.
- It's not the Jae Suk we know.
- It's not.
- He'd go, "Back in my heyday,"
- "I used to be on so many shows."
- Oh, gosh.
(She's tired of him already.)
"If you think back..."
What do you know about me?
You can't get mad.
- "Back in my day..."
- "You shouldn't live like this."
You're getting headaches, right?
Do you want to hear ours?
All right. Ours is very simple.
It's very intuitive.
- All right.
- We...
Jae Suk who has nipples
right next to his belly button,
My goodness.
versus Gong Myoung
who has eight nipples.
(Jae Suk who has nipples
right next to his belly button...)
(versus Gong Myoung
who has eight nipples)
- It's better to have 8 nipples!
- It's better to have eight nipples!
- Of course.
It's better to have more
than having them in the wrong place!
Of course it's better
to have eight nipples.
- Wait. His belly button...
- It's better to have eight nipples!
- But...
- Next to his belly button?
They're around here.
So they're a little lower
than where they are right now.
- You can't even see them.
- Then Gong Myoung is way better.
- No, it's because...
- Are they lined up in a row?
I think it'll be like this.
When I hug him like this,
he'd stop me.
He'd stop me
whenever I try to hug him...
because his nipples
are all over the place.
So Min, please pick one.
You can get them removed
with a laser.
Actually, they're both very hard
to choose from.
The one that's more difficult...
(Married Corporation's options)
(Jae Suk versus Gong Myoung
with 8 nipples)
(Single Dot-com's options)
(Gong Myoung she can meet only once
versus jobless and nagging Jae Suk)
The one that's more difficult...
- is Married Corporation's.
- Right?
(Married Corporation gets
their first win.)
- Right? It's hard, right?
- It's really hard.
It's definitely difficult to pick.
I think I can pick one
from their options.
- Nice.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn.
It's Brad Pitt.
- That's a strong opponent.
- It's hard.
(Who's going up against Brad Pitt?)
- He's a playboy.
- It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo got picked.)
(Bitter)
- What is it?
- Hold on.
- We don't need to...
- We already have an answer.
I'm sorry, but are you going to
make him a centaur again?
- No, we won't.
- You can't use that option again!
Wait. Isn't he already half-animal?
Are you calling me half-animal?
Aren't those giraffe legs?
- No, they're mine.
- Oh, really?
(Laughing)
This is the most difficult one
we've come up with.
- It's so funny.
- It's difficult?
- It's really difficult.
- It's really hard.
- This time...
- Let's see theirs first.
- Okay, we'll show ours first.
- It's too difficult.
- It's really difficult.
- Please help her pick one.
It's very difficult.
- It's Brad Pitt versus Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
- Brad Pitt who is 30cm tall.
- 30cm?
(Brad Pitt who is 30cm tall.)
- Brad Pitt.
- Then he's only this big.
- He's like an action figure.
- He's really cute.
- He's cute.
- He needs to be alive too.
He's small but really handsome.
Just as good-looking as he is.
He learned to speak Korean,
so you can communicate with him.
- And he's as rich as now.
- Next is...
- Kwang Soo.
- How tall will he be?
Kwang Soo who is 30m tall.
(A giant who is 30m tall)
(Brad Pitt who's 30cm tall
versus Kwang Soo who's 30m tall)
Why does he keep
exaggerating my height?
- What's wrong with it?
- Is he a skyscraper or something?
- What is he, a skyscraper?
- This is nonsense.
- He's 30m tall.
- Does that even make sense?
He'd get caught
between electric wires!
- I don't care about that.
- We don't care!
I don't care about that.
- Wow, this is really difficult.
- Right.
- Brad Pitt...
- Then Brad would be way better...
since he's only 30cm tall.
What use will he be
if he's 30m tall?
What? We don't care about that.
If he's 30cm tall,
you can at least talk to him.
We don't care about that.
I mean,
he can live on the first floor...
and hang his laundry on the rooftop.
Why would I hang my laundry
on the rooftop?
- Yes.
- This is really difficult.
- It is, right?
- You'll definitely pick us.
- All right.
- 30m?
He developed a symptom...
where he loses control at night.
Brad Pitt who wets his bed
every night.
But he pees a lot.
- Okay.
- It can't be covered with a diaper.
And Kwang Soo who is potty-trained.
(Brad Pitt who wets his bed
versus potty-trained Kwang Soo)
He's really well-trained.
I was going to make it
difficult for her to choose.
- But it's Kwang Soo.
- But this is...
This is me. I am well potty-trained.
I still don't like him.
- Bedwetter Brad Pitt.
- Yes, he's a bedwetter.
- But this is...
- Versus potty-trained Kwang Soo.
- I think we got an answer.
- It's really easy.
- I'd definitely pick Brad Pitt.
- And he's super rich.
I'd definitely pick Brad Pitt.
It's really easy.
But he wets his bed every day.
- He can wear diapers every day.
- He wets it twice a day.
Let's say he dozes off
while in the movies.
He doesn't fail to wet his pants.
- It doesn't matter where he is.
- Right.
- Once he falls asleep.
- He just wets his pants anywhere.
- Once he closes his eyes.
- That's right.
- I'm sure she'll still pick Brad.
- Of course.
When Kwang Soo is potty-trained?
He's normal. He's himself.
It's so offensive
that they even mentioned this.
It doesn't matter
whether you're potty-trained or not.
Ji Hyo, give it a serious thought.
- Be serious.
- Yes.
- Ours is difficult too.
- It's difficult.
- I know you contemplated.
- That's not hard at all.
Brat Pitt who's 30cm tall
and Kwang Soo who's 30m tall.
Being 30m tall doesn't make sense.
Don't our options
make you contemplate?
Right.
Ours is more difficult.
- You can't pick one.
- I've made up my mind.
I made up my mind
as soon as I saw their options
(Brad Pitt who wets his bed
versus potty-trained Kwang Soo)
(Brad Pitt who's 30cm tall
versus Kwang Soo who's 30m tall)
I'd pick Married Corporation.
(She picked Married Corporation.)
- Yes!
- Of course!
It made you contemplate, right?
- Really?
- Tell us why.
It made you contemplate?
She'd definitely pick Brad Pitt
for your options.
- She'd pick Brad Pitt.
It's really easy.
Of course I'd pick Brad Pitt.
But it's against Kwang Soo
who is normal.
Brad Pitt pees a lot.
- Still...
- Are you looking down on Kwang Soo?
Brad Pitt is rich,
- so he can take care of himself.
- Of course.
I make enough money too!
- But Kwang Soo is normal.
- So what if he's a bedwetter?
But is Kwang Soo
really potty-trained?
- What is he talking about?
- It leaks a little, actually.
Hey!
- It's true.
- It leaks a little.
Your underwear is a bit wet.
I don't have residual urine.
Are you saying
I have residual urine?
- Poor you.
- I'm not kidding.
- The normal Kwang Soo lost.
- She must really not like you.
The normal Kwang Soo lost.
When I'm well potty-trained.
No, Kwang Soo. I love you.
(Current number of stickers)
You're going to play
the final mission.
Here's how you'll choose
the company.
The clients have given situations...
where they determine
their ideal types.
You will have two minutes.
For two minutes,
become a client's ideal type.
A representative from each team
will play the role.
- It's about playing a role.
- That's right.
- Can it be any member of the team?
- From each team,
there should be 1 for So Min
and 1 for Ji Hyo.
That team has
both Si Kyung and Se Chan.
I will explain So Min's situation
for an ideal type.
You will go to a female friend
who is drinking after a breakup...
and confess your love.
In other words,
So Min is drinking...
after breaking up
with her boyfriend.
You will play a man who goes to her
and confesses his love.
- So the man is confessing to me?
- That's right.
You only saw him as a friend,
but he will confess his love
as an ideal type.
- So suddenly?
- So...
So Min is feeling sad...
when a friend visits,
and he confesses his love.
- Si Kyung should go.
- Okay.
All right.
Who will represent the team?
Yong Jin.
Please go in there...
and change into an outfit.
(What kind of a male friend
will they play?)
(They change into the outfit
the stylists prepared.)
We need to get changed...
for the date.
I would have gone, "Gosh, you fool."
"Why did you take a detour
before coming to me?"
Seriously.
Saying I love you
"Why did you take a detour?"
(Se Chan thinks about confessing
with background music.)
One sentence is enough.
He will look at me...
while I am drunk and go,
"Hey,"
"can I kiss you?"
(Kissing)
So Min, I am sorry,
- but...
- Should I stop?
don't live vicariously through us.
- "Don't live vicariously."
- I am happy.
- Are you happy?
I like this segment.
(The male friends arrive to make
So Min's heart flutter even more.)
Please stand over there.
Is that the boyfriend look?
(The male friends arrive to make
So Min's heart flutter even more.)
- That's the boyfriend look.
- The boyfriend look.
- They look different.
- They really dressed up.
(Her excitement level is
at its max already.)
(After a breakup,
So Min drinks alone at a cart bar.)
(Her male friend comes to her.)
So Min, you are here.
Hey,
why are you drinking alone?
Let's drink together.
- I don't even know.
- Hey.
- What? Give it to me.
- Give it to me.
- Gosh.
- I will pour it.
- What?
- What's wrong this time?
Did things end badly with him?
(The cringe-worthy drama
draws everyone in.)
You can tell me anything.
- Drink slowly.
- I mean...
Drink slowly.
I will pour it for you.
Why are you acting strange?
What's up with you?
What's up with you today?
You will get drunk.
Don't get drunk so quickly.
(Impressed)
(The cringe-worthy line is perfect
for So Min!)
It's like a youth drama.
(The cringe-worthy line
makes her grin from ear to ear.)
(Si Kyung feels pressured
about going next.)
It's not like that.
I want to get drunk today.
You shouldn't drink
on an empty stomach.
Please bring us
some tropical fruits.
(He picks tropical fruits
as a drinking snack.)
Hold on.
Where are they?
- Are they at a nightclub?
- Tropical fruits.
Why are you interrupting?
This is my style.
Tropical fruits.
My goodness.
He didn't ask
for some dried drinking snacks.
- Where are they?
- Tropical fruits.
(They try
to get back into character.)
- Well...
- Yong Jin.
- Tell me.
- Yong Jin is so funny.
- What's up with you?
- I am fine.
- Seeing you so upset...
- makes me upset.
- You weren't like this.
Why are you overreacting today?
- Tell me.
- What's up with you?
What happened?
Why did you guys break up?
He said he can't date me anymore
because we are too different.
So Min is so funny.
So Min is so into it.
I told you that there are
only a few people in the world...
who can deal with you.
It makes no sense
because we get along so well.
Hey, I think...
it would be great if we...
What?
It would be great if we...
(His confession of love
is barely heard.)
- What?
- What is he doing?
It would be great if we go out.
(He ventriloquizes
to confess his love shyly.)
I like it.
- It isn't half bad.
- It's nice.
- It's cute.
I mean...
Forget it. Keep drinking.
- Drink.
- Did you say "make ramyeon?"
No!
- It would be great if we...
- What is up with you?
He is spilling water
all over his chin.
- You are acting strange.
- Do you regret it?
Are you going to call him?
I called him, but he didn't pick up.
Then don't call him from now on.
How could I not? I miss him.
- I want us to get back together.
- Listen.
Whenever you miss someone...
or feel sad,
call me.
(Call me.)
(He delivers his sincerity
with half air and half sound.)
There are people just like him!
It's so true.
(The man who is going next
simply feels anxious.)
This is nice.
- What did you say?
- To be honest...
Call you?
Be quiet. I will do the talking now.
What are you saying?
What is up with you?
He is pretending to be manly.
Now that he gained confidence,
he is pretending to be manly.
So Min likes it.
- I told you this before.
- What?
I am the one
who understands you the best...
- since childhood.
- I know that, but...
- I watched over you for 20 years.
- I know that.
You dated countless men,
but I waited for you
without dating anyone.
Don't be ridiculous.
You dated Ji Hyo.
You dated Ji Hyo for three years.
Someday in the future
(The singer
with incredible techniques is back.)
What?
What is going on?
He didn't answer her.
- He is like a robot.
- If I wait endlessly
(His confession of love is strange,
but she is drawn to it.)
- There are words I haven't said
- It's nice.
- Yong Jin is doing well.
- In my heart
I love you
- What?
- I told you how I feel...
through a song.
I am not in the mood for a laugh.
It's not like that. How about me?
He is a lunatic.
A lunatic?
- He is a lunatic.
- A lunatic!
- Why? He was cool.
- Listen.
- He was cool.
- He is a lunatic.
- She was about to throw water.
- Good job. Yong Jin, it's over.
- He is a lunatic.
- He was cool.
- I showed my charismatic side.
- You were cool.
- He is a lunatic.
I would have found that charming.
I loved it.
I almost died when he sang.
- Right?
- It's Si Kyung's turn.
- I loved it.
- Here comes the real deal.
He will show you how it's done.
Yong Jin did everything funny.
My goodness.
You should keep it simple.
- You should keep it simple.
- Okay.
Keep it simple.
- You don't need to be funny.
- Keep it simple.
(Si Kyung visits her friend,
So Min.)
- Hey.
- Hey, you're here.
Why are you drinking alone?
I'm in a bad mood today.
Why? Did something happen?
My boyfriend and I broke up.
(He keeps his facial expression
utterly simple.)
(She becomes overly absorbed.)
She is absorbed.
All right.
I need a drink too. This won't do.
Why do you need a drink?
I am going to get drunk today,
so drop me off at home, okay?
Let me think after a drink.
(The talented balladeer shows
a luxurious way of drinking.)
(Kudos)
I can't believe...
I can't believe he did that.
You can't beat that.
You laughed!
(He succeeded to make her laugh.)
You can't beat
the repetition of the opening.
- I was forgetting it.
- He repeated it.
You can't beat
the repetition of the opening.
- Comedy is all about repetition.
- He is a professional.
That was...
You are the prettiest
when you smile.
What was that? Seriously.
Hey, why did you do that?
You made me laugh.
Seriously, you did.
- You made me laugh.
- Get started, Si Kyung.
I should have listened to you.
Get started, Si Kyung.
Someday in the future
You will look back at me
(His song knocks her out
right away.)
- If I wait endlessly
- Si Kyung, you're a good singer.
- Behind you
- It's nice.
- Gosh, he is good. It's game over.
- If I wait endlessly
(The married men are speechless.)
My goodness.
Today, I will sing for you...
and do other things.
So feel better.
Why didn't you stop me
when I began dating him?
That's because
you really seemed to like him.
It's a drama.
You should date someone you like.
Kiss her.
Don't interrupt! For goodness' sake!
- Don't get too into it!
- What?
This is the climax!
It was getting interesting!
Why did you do that?
- Are you insane?
- It's just that...
You got too into it, didn't you?
"Kiss her?"
- Let's end it here.
- Okay.
Si Kyung did pretty well too.
Si Kyung repeated a moment
from the opening.
There were a few great moments.
Seriously.
(How will So Min's heart decide?)
Firstly, Si Kyung...
really felt like a friend.
But Yong Jin's performance
was funny and sad.
It was funny and sad.
I almost became sad...
before I laughed.
- I have regrets now that it's over.
- It was embarrassing.
You are getting more ideas, right?
I should have acted drunk.
I should have drunk more.
Now comes Ji Hyo's situation.
She is sitting at a cafe...
when a man approaches
and makes a move on her.
- I know who will go.
- We have the perfect member.
We have...
a member...
who is like a secret weapon.
- I see.
- Suk Jin will go.
Suk Jin.
(Who will go against Suk Jin,
the cool married man?)
Who is it? Is it you?
(It's Se Chan, a single man.)
In this situation,
I would approach the woman
more playfully.
I wouldn't go,
"Excuse me.
You are exactly my type."
"Hey, what are you doing?"
What?
- Hey.
- I hate it.
It's the worst.
Isn't that a thug?
I mean...
"What a pretty picture you make!"
(He should be thankful
if she doesn't call the police.)
- Wouldn't that ease the tension?
- Se Chan, you will go first.
- Will Se Chan go first?
- Begin as soon as you enter.
Good luck.
- I am excited about this.
- This is a cafe, right?
- Se Chan.
(Ji Hyo is drinking coffee
at a cafe.)
Things like this don't happen
very often.
It depends on the person.
(A man musters up his courage
and approaches the beauty.)
Gosh.
(He has a clear concept.)
Gosh, the air is nice.
My goodness.
(His strong first impression
makes them look away.)
What are you looking at?
Am I a spectacle?
- Gosh, this is...
- Am I a spectacle?
You can't use a character like that.
Bring me a glass of beer.
Gosh, who is this?
This is insane.
I shouldn't have bought this.
(He means that she is more beautiful
than flowers.)
Take this.
(The straightforward man
hands over a bouquet right away.)
I fell for you at first sight.
Seriously.
Are you going to ignore my hand?
Take it.
Go ahead and take it. My goodness.
Ji Hyo looks a bit annoyed.
Is the seat empty?
- "Is the seat empty?"
- Yes.
Hurry up and bring me
a glass of beer!
Where is he from?
What is up with that accent?
(He has accents
from all over the nation.)
It's nice to meet you, gal.
(He is mixing up
all the accents he knows.)
- "Gal?"
- It's nice to meet you.
Why are you here alone?
I just felt like being alone today.
Do you have a boyfriend?
(Straightforward)
A boyfriend? Not yet.
Then you should have
a drink with me today.
That's the worst.
- What do you think?
- That's so rude.
- That's the worst.
- That's just wrong.
That's the worst.
- What do you think?
- I am becoming absorbed.
How can I drink with you
when I saw you for the first time?
- Seriously.
- I am a good man.
Here is the beer you ordered.
(A tall employee brings beer.)
Hold on.
Take this.
(He slaps him as a tip.)
(What?)
(The employee is confused
by the tip.)
There you go.
That's it.
(He succeeded to captivate
Ji Hyo's heart.)
That's the way to do it.
- Why is his hand wet?
- Go on your way.
- Go on your way, okay?
That's it. That's the way to do it.
That's the way to do it.
(The tall employee gets scolded
for no reason.)
(He is still confused
by the shocking tip.)
- Look at his face.
- Let's have a drink.
- The end.
Ji Hyo didn't say anything.
- It was hard.
- Good job.
It was fitting.
It was time for comedy.
- Kwang Soo went along with it.
- It was so funny.
- It was a comedy skit.
- Thank you.
It was a difficult fight.
It's too much.
Is Se Chan done?
(Will he be able to captivate
Ji Hyo's heart?)
- Is it my turn?
- Suk Jin has experience.
That's right.
Suk Jin
will probably keep it gentle.
It was so funny.
(Seok Sam appears.)
My goodness.
(What is that?)
- Oh, my goodness.
- He even has a tattoo.
It's a work of art.
Mom.
(Mama's boy, Seok Sam)
I am about to go crazy.
He started off wrong.
I had this thought.
"I will make a move
if I see someone I like."
He changed the concept.
(Laughing)
Seriously.
You like me, right?
(Charismatic man, Seok Sam)
- What?
- You like me, right?
"You like me, right?"
Ji Hyo, you are here.
(Se Chan comes to salvage
the situation.)
- Who are you?
- Who are you, you punk?
I should give you a tip.
(Happy ending)
(From a youth drama
to a comedy skit,)
(they tried various genres.)
It's time to announce
the final result.
You never know
what the result will be.
The score before this round was
6 to 6.
- Yes.
- 6 to 6.
This round will determine
the result,
so please talk among yourselves
and pick a team.
- All right.
- Okay.
Then put a sticker on the CEO.
As for me, both were the worst.
(Ji Hyo refuses to pick one.)
Which team should I pick?
(The team So Min chooses will win!)
(CEO Sung was like a real friend.)
(CEO Lee was funny and sad.)
We made up our minds.
You never know
what the result will be.
You never know.
- 6 to 6.
- Okay.
It's okay even if we lose.
- We choose this team.
- What?
(Their final choice is
Married Corporation.)
(Married Corporation wins!)
- We won.
- They didn't disappoint.
- Thank you.
- We did a good job.
I told you.
(He stayed by her side
like a friend...)
(and confessed his love
in a way that wasn't pushy.)
(He has enough good cheer
to dance with her without music.)
(He even showed his funny side
by using his vocal cords.)
(He is an eccentric man
with a charismatic side.)
- They didn't disappoint.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- I am disappointed.
(Ji Hyo couldn't find
her ideal type.)
I am so disappointed.
Thus, they finished their journey
of finding the ideal type.
Three people from the winning team
will receive 3.75g of gold each.
Thank you.
(CEO, Senior Managing Director,
and Director win the gold.)
(Manager Haha doesn't get any gold.)
How was it today?
It was my 1st time in 11 years
to be on Running Man.
So it was very meaningful.
Being an avatar was hard,
but I will be satisfied
if you laughed a lot. Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
(We thank Lee Yong Jin
and Sung Si Kyung.)
(10:08 a.m., Chinese restaurant)
- Cheers!
(10:13 a.m., Korean restaurant)
I lost.
(10:26 a.m., Chinese restaurant again)
You will receive five coins.
- Really?
- Why?
(10:27 a.m., Korean restaurant again)
You can go home right away.
(27 minutes into the shoot,
Suk Jin goes home.)
(11:04 a.m., In the car)
You can go home.
(Kwang Soo goes home
after 1 hour and 4 minutes.)
Is this for real?
(Some members get sent home
for real!)
- Come on.
- For real?
(11:10 a.m.)
(10:31 a.m.)
(11:24 a.m.)
(10:48 a.m.)
(11:31 a.m.)
(11:19 a.m.)
(11:44 a.m.)
(11:27 a.m.)
I will really go home. Bye.
(For the first time
in the history of Running Man,)
(some members go home for real
for no particular reason.)
(Going Home Race, Read the Room)