"Don't be friends with someone
who is not better than you."
Confucius said.
Today, the silly members are...
gathered together in Variety Village
to meet someone better than them.
(Perfect Partner Signal)
Man 1 and Man 2 are
the first ones to arrive.
(Sweet)
Hello.
- Hello.
What?
They have the rules
for Variety Village.
"The purpose
of Variety Village is to find..."
"a perfect partner to appear on
screen for a longer period of time."
"You may win your partner's heart
by any means necessary."
Three. A member
who fails to find a partner...
will get a harsh penalty.
Four. Whatever you do
in Variety Village will be aired...
without any omissions
or adjustments.
And all members are supposed
to keep trying...
to win the hearts of other members
even after finding a partner...
until the end in order to secure
the airtime and gold.
What is this? Perfect Partner?
(What is this? Perfect Partner?)
Perfect Partner?
- A partner who's right for you.
I see.
You mean someone
of the same mind as me.
Man Two is a little slow
of understanding.
Yes.
What's with your tone?
Do I know you?
You don't know me?
That's today's concept, right?
Why are you so tall
when we've just met?
- My gosh.
- I have to look up at your face.
Oh, dear.
(Chuckling)
- You should lower it a little.
- I haven't heard that in a while.
"Why are you so tall?"
I haven't heard it in a long time.
My gosh.
There's someone dawdling along.
Look.
Who on earth is he?
Why is he swaggering like that?
It says "Perfect Partner."
All right. Perfect Partner Signal.
Hey.
Nice to meet you.
(Man 4 Kim Jong Kook,
Man 3 Yang Se Chan)
- He's wearing shorts.
- Nice to meet you.
- He must be cold.
- I know. It's a little early.
- It's chilly today.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
How are you all?
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- All right.
- Gosh.
What do you think you're doing?
- Hello.
- Hello. Gosh.
- Why is he...
We've just met.
He's very vigorous.
The thing is...
We've just met here.
We're here together man to man.
What are you talking about?
So we're all men. But why are you...
Why are you swaggering?
Why are you swinging
your arms like this?
Why are you doing this?
I just want you to feel my energy.
You're right.
There's only one way
you can feel it.
(There's only one way
you can feel it.)
- Hey!
- What?
- Okay.
- Oh, dear.
(He shows off his strong grip
all of a sudden.)
- Come here.
- My goodness.
All right.
- Good.
- I can't believe this.
Man Four is rather violent.
He approaches the other members
the way he makes friends at a gym.
I made my palms callused on purpose.
- I see.
- Can you feel it?
Sure. I can totally feel it.
By the way, I guess he's
the owner of this place.
- What?
- There's a grandpa.
- He's the owner of this place.
- I see. He's the owner.
- He owns this place.
- Hello, sir.
(Man 5 Ji Suk Jin,
Man 6 Haha)
- He owns this place.
- Hello, sir.
- What?
- Is he wearing a crop top?
Please don't do this.
- What's with his pants?
- What's wrong with him?
- Who is that guy?
- This is crazy.
Is he in the fashion business?
- I got goosebumps.
- Hello.
- What's this?
- You're a man.
Why are you wearing women's clothes
when you're a man?
What's that thing on the sleeves?
Excessively rolled up cuffs
and lacy sleeves.
And a knitted crop top.
His fashion that reminds you
of a servant in medieval Europe...
throws Variety Village
into confusion.
I do like his outfit.
But I thought a woman
was walking in at first.
What's with the lacy sleeves?
I guess he's trying to draw
people's attention.
But he's totally mistaken.
Then what does Man Five
think of his fashion?
I think my outfit is outstanding
when it comes to fashion.
But it's also great
in terms of variety shows.
This is Variety Village.
The others should've cared
about their outfits too.
- Hello.
- Why are you wearing...
women's clothes when you're a man?
What's that thing on the sleeves?
I know there's
no boundary in fashion, but...
I'm very interested in fashion.
- Right.
- Hello.
- I'm serious.
Okay. Is it bad that
I'm interested in fashion?
- But the lace...
- What? This is...
- my tablecloth.
- Hello.
(Man 6 is being ostracized
because of Man 5's unique fashion.)
Man Six must be embarrassed.
- We can't see him because of Man 5.
- I know.
He's unnoticeable.
- My fashion...
- I just met him today.
But I was really embarrassed
on my way here.
I understand how you feel.
It's hard to set a new trend.
But, Man Five, on your way here,
you kept checking
your outfit like this.
(Man 5, you kept checking
your outfit like this.)
Like this.
- He wasn't sure.
- Did I do that?
- Yes.
- I didn't check how I looked.
I didn't get to check my outfit
before coming here.
At this rate,
you'll soon show up in a dress.
That's not true.
With no shame.
- That's enough.
- This is what you told me...
before coming in here.
When we just met.
"This is a little embarrassing."
You said that, didn't you?
Did you guys see me before?
- Do I know you?
- No.
As soon as you get here,
you're fighting against four people.
That's not true.
I'm just having a conversation.
As soon as you came in...
Since we've just met,
we will stop here.
- If we were friends...
- It would've been serious.
- You would've been doomed.
- I would've thrown this at him.
I had a lot of things to say.
You guys are mischievous.
I'm fine with that.
Man Five who seems
to take blows well...
has become the fashionista
of Variety Village.
Woman 1 and Woman 2
have just arrived.
- Really?
- Please greet them warmly.
I think I know who's coming.
They seem somewhat familiar.
Perfect Partner Signal?
(Woman 1 Song Ji Hyo,
Woman 2 Jeon So Min)
Perfect Partner Signal.
Men would usually go to them
and carry their bags.
Right.
We should skip that part.
- Well...
- We will skip it.
I can see them over there.
They are just good friends.
- Right.
- We know them.
Woman 1 and Woman 2
come to Variety Village every week.
There's no tension around them.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
Hello.
- Hello.
- They look good.
- You look great.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Man 1.
- Hello, Woman 2.
Hello.
Man One, why are you
flirting with them already?
No, I was just saying hello.
Why are you flirting with them?
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you doing this?
- What did I do?
- You just said you'd skip them.
I can't believe this.
Man One tries to impress the women
with his over-the-top kindness.
That draws unwelcome attention
from the other members.
(The silly members are
quarreling over nothing.)
(Staring)
- Come here.
- You want them to pick you.
Is that because of his outfit?
Why would you tell them
to stand next to you?
- Come over here.
- Why?
(Staring)
(Since they've just met,
she can't say anything mean.)
- Now...
- Look at them.
(Woman 1 and Woman 2 try to
hold back their laughter.)
- You both...
- What's wrong?
(What's wrong?)
He's Woman Five.
I thought you were Kim Jang Hoon.
(I thought you were Kim Jang Hoon.)
He's a great guy.
Where did your bag go?
- You should keep your bag with you.
- He was...
He was so flustered...
- With all the criticism...
- Man Five...
- He's out of his mind.
- doesn't know what to do now.
- That's not true.
- He forgot about his bag.
He put it here
as soon as he arrived.
And he said, "What? Why?"
He just walked
right into a battlefield like that.
That's not it. Usually...
Man Five is being quite bold today.
Would the women
appreciate his effort?
- Would they think he's trying?
- It's pretty...
They might feel that way.
- He's trying.
- I like that.
That's good.
- Someone's coming.
- What?
(Woman 3 shows up
right at that moment.)
(Woman 3 Seol In Ah)
(The actress with pure
and refreshing charm, Seol In Ah)
- Oh, hello.
- Who's coming?
- Who's she?
- Woman Three.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
(They seem a lot more excited than
when Woman 1 and Woman 2 showed up.)
- Hello.
- In Ah.
- Seol In Ah.
She's carrying her bag
instead of pulling it.
- She's strong.
- She's really strong.
She's strong.
In Ah, why are you carrying it?
I bet she's strong.
- Because it makes loud noises.
- In Ah, come here.
- Hello.
- She picked it up and carried it.
Like the one-arm dumbbell row.
- The one-arm dumbbell row?
- Yes.
Woman Three is really...
- Woman Three looks sophisticated.
- She's sophisticated.
She's wearing a jacket.
I know.
You guys look
a lot more excited now.
- Are we excited?
- That's because of his outfit.
- Right.
- Look at his outfit.
(The servant-style outfit
makes her clap like a seal.)
Woman Three, this isn't a penalty.
- Do you like this kind of fashion?
- It's not a penalty.
- Do you like my clothes?
- I like that.
- I knew it.
- He's in the fashion business.
I'm in the fashion business.
Even these three women are...
wearing simple outfits.
While everyone is frowning...
at Man Five's outfit,
Woman Four is coming in quietly.
(Woman 4 Jeong He In)
You're in danger now. You know that?
(Jeong He In,
a charismatic actress,)
(known for her short hair
and exotic charm)
- What?
- My gosh.
- Woman Four.
- Oh, dear.
- She's handsome...
- You look like someone.
You're really handsome.
- Thank you.
- Please come over here.
Woman Four, please come here.
She's wearing shorts like Jong Kook.
You're the most handsome one here.
- Hello.
- She looks like Terrius.
He In looks like...
- You're really tall.
- Right.
- I'm tall.
- By the way,
- you look like Hwang Shin Hye.
- That's right.
- I hear that a lot.
- I bet you do.
- You're right.
- She's like Hwang Shin Hye.
- She looks just like her.
- Thank you.
Right.
- You look great.
- Why are you laughing?
- Why?
- Who made you laugh?
- You look amazing.
- Is that because of his outfit?
- Is it his outfit?
You can laugh out loud.
We already did.
It's okay.
- It's hilarious.
- I don't mind.
- She bursts into laughter.
- The perfect outfit.
Woman Four is really...
She looks amazing.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo was here.
- What?
I just saw you now.
Did you not see him?
How could you not see
such a tall guy before?
- I couldn't see him...
- I kept talking to you.
because he was too tall.
What do you mean you didn't
see me because I'm too tall?
That's because of Man Five's outfit.
You can't cause me harm like that.
I didn't cause you harm.
Man Five is causing us
a lot of trouble.
I would've come naked then.
Why would you pick on me
for my outfit?
Woman Six is here.
- She's Woman 5.
- Woman 5.
What? Cho Hee?
It's Cho Hee.
(Woman 5 Lee Cho Hee)
Hello.
(Lee Cho Hee,
the romance fairy who won...)
(the Rookie of the Year Award
at the KBS Drama Awards in 2020)
- Hello.
- Cho Hee.
- Nice to meet you. This way.
- Please come this way.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Hello, Cho Hee.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
She says hello to everyone
with her eyes.
Hello.
(All the members are gathered
in Variety Village.)
Including Woman Five,
all the members have arrived
for Perfect Partner Signal.
Now they need some time
to get to know each other better.
Me?
All right. Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm working in the IT industry.
(Man 1 works in the IT industry,
which might be a video arcade.)
That's what I do.
And...
I have some stock options.
- What?
- What are stock options?
- Stock options?
- None of us understands that.
Say it in easy terms.
Do you not know about stock options?
You don't seem popular at all.
And I care a lot about my hobbies.
I think work and life balance...
is very important.
- Work and life balance.
- On weekends...
Are you saying
difficult words on purpose?
- I don't understand anything.
- What's work and life balance?
- I mean...
- You don't seem so smart.
Man One, why...
You're being weird.
- But...
- Don't say such difficult words.
I'm sorry,
but I'm not talking to you.
- What do you do in the IT industry?
- I guess he runs a video arcade.
I'm not sure if you knew this,
but I go water-skiing on weekends.
I just started
the one ski last week.
I just started the one ski.
I used only one ski last week.
- You guys...
- If you water-ski like that,
you will die.
You'll drown right away.
- You know the one ski, right?
- He will die.
Man One never listens to us.
Hey!
What? "Hey?"
Gosh, Man One.
- Why are you being like this?
- That's enough.
How could he do that to me?
By the way, I wasn't talking to you.
But I heard it too.
- He was talking to me.
- I wasn't talking to you.
You are short-tempered.
It's not that I'm short-tempered.
He's ridiculous.
- You're being rude.
- I wasn't talking to you.
Anyway, what's important is...
that we need
to find a perfect partner.
So you don't need to feel pressured.
- Of course not.
- All right?
Who's next?
Hello. I'm...
Hang on.
I'm sorry, but are you
making an announcement?
- Why do you sound so kind?
- That's what we do...
- But it was just too much.
- Just be natural.
- That's how I talk.
- It sounded awkward.
- You're making us uncomfortable.
- That's how I usually talk.
- Usually?
- Yes.
Hello.
(Hello.)
I'm inheriting my father's business.
It's just a small business.
Hey. Are you inheriting
your father's business?
I thought your father
was an office worker.
What I'm saying
doesn't have to be true.
All right.
They know so much about each other.
All I care about...
is honesty here.
Actually,
I'm inheriting my father's business,
but I don't care about that.
I'm inheriting my father's
small business now.
- What does he do?
- What?
It's a really small business.
(Maybe it's a mom-and-pop store.)
- It's really small.
- About this big.
- It's small.
- It's really tiny.
And I recently came back
after studying abroad.
- You studied abroad?
- Are you the son...
of S company?
S company? Really?
Samsung Dried Fish Store?
(Samsung Dried Fish Store?)
- No.
- He's a squid.
- You're a squid.
- It's you.
Mr. Squid.
Hello. I'm Man Two, Squid.
The dried fish store.
He's the son of the owner.
Samsung fish-shaped buns.
Gosh, it's so annoying.
(This isn't what I intended.)
All right. I'm Man Two.
Was the tall guy Man Two?
His face looked...
a little sly.
That's how I felt
when I saw his face.
I'm not that interested in him.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I've recently become
a nouveau riche.
I made a big fortune...
- on the stock market.
- He's rich.
Right. All I have is money.
If you want my money,
you should pick me.
- That's pathetic.
- What's wrong with being rich?
Man Five, why do you...
- keep meddling in?
- I know. He's jealous.
Why would you brag about your money?
Because I have to.
If I talk about my money,
you'll be in trouble.
- You should talk about your age.
- What?
You can talk about your age.
You're 56.
Tell them you're 56.
- Weren't you born in 1966?
- He'll turn 60 soon.
Weren't you born in 1966?
I was born in 1991.
- That's ridiculous.
- 1991.
- You're lying.
- I was born in 1991.
- In 1991?
- In the Year of the Sheep.
Anyway, all I have is money.
- Please pick me.
- You're young and rich.
Let's have fun.
I kind of...
liked Man Three.
I guess he has
an unpredictable charm.
That's the impression I got.
Hello. I'm a fitness trainer.
(I'm a fitness trainer.)
- I knew it.
- That sounds about right.
- I could tell.
- My gosh.
- A trainer.
- I'm running...
a small gym now.
I care a lot about health.
As soon as I saw him,
I thought he would be one of two.
And you're a trainer.
- A trainer or...
- What was the other thing?
Something in the dark world...
- A businessman.
- But you're a trainer.
- I'm a trainer.
- Okay.
That's what you should do.
Did you not hit the jing
in "Comedy Big League?"
- Are you that guy?
- I think I saw you.
- Was that you?
- You're him.
- I thought you looked familiar.
- You're the Jing Man.
I don't hit the jing.
I hit people.
You hit people?
You don't hit your friends, do you?
I don't hit my friends.
I guess it's my turn now.
Hello. I'm...
working in the fashion industry.
I run a small business.
He looks serious.
The focus of my business is export.
All right. Thank you.
(All right. Thank you.)
Hey.
Thank you.
You're rude.
I'm not rude.
- We all heard you.
- You should understand him.
This is just the beginning.
We all heard you.
- You didn't hear anything.
- They all heard you.
- You heard him, right?
- Yes.
In the fashion industry...
They're not interested.
Anyway, I'm Man Five.
All right. Man Five.
- I'm sorry, but are you single?
- Yes, I am.
- Are you sure?
- I'm single.
I wanted to get married, but...
That's not what we're here for.
What's your relationship
with Ms. Ryu Su Jung?
(What's your relationship
with Ms. Ryu Su Jung?)
What about Ms. Ryu Su Jung?
Why would he
talk about his real wife?
Ryu Su Jung?
She's a friend.
- She's just a friend.
- What about Ji Hyun Woo?
- Ji Hyun Woo.
- Who's Ji Hyun Woo?
He's my friend's son.
Your friend's son.
- Your friend's son.
- My friend's son.
- MFS.
- MFS?
Yes.
- That's right.
- Okay.
(Who's your least favorite?)
Well... Man number...
(Man number...)
Five.
(Man 5)
It's not that I don't like him.
I just feel a little
uncomfortable around him.
(I just feel a little
uncomfortable around him.)
The guy who runs
a fashion business...
(The guy who runs
a fashion business...)
Where is his fashion style from?
Where is he from?
I don't think...
I'll get along with him.
It's not that I hate him.
We're just not right for each other.
- Is it my turn?
- Man Six.
Hi.
What?
I don't like your character.
- I guess he studied abroad.
- He did?
I guess he's from abroad.
Speak in English.
I'm sorry I'm not using honorifics.
I just thought you guys
looked younger than me.
You guys can talk to me
in a casual way.
- Are you from abroad?
- Me?
Yes. I'm from abroad.
- Which country?
- Which part?
I just wandered from place to place.
I'll tell you
once we become friends.
Right. My dad failed his business.
- I...
- Is that why you came back?
I'm a self-made man.
- And...
- Do you even know what it means?
Doesn't that mean
I'm a successful man?
- Did you turn yourself in?
- I'm not sure.
Right. I don't speak Korean
very well.
Anyway, I'm not so good,
but I'd like you to be nice to me.
- And...
- You sound fluent though.
I like you.
(He just points
at the woman he likes.)
He's from abroad.
- My gosh.
- So he's straightforward.
I'm...
in between jobs right now.
- He has his charms.
- I know.
Who are you talking to?
- I want us to be friends.
- I can't see his eyes.
It was somewhere in the middle.
Not the ones on the sides.
- Not the ones on the sides.
- I agree.
- That's it.
- He sounds cool.
All right. Woman One,
please introduce yourself.
Hello.
My dream is to become
a good wife and mother.
- I thought I misheard you.
- What?
- Why?
- Let's get into our characters.
It's my dream.
I always laugh at others' jokes
and play along with them.
That's one of my strengths.
I want you all to know it.
- Really?
- Yes.
But I saw you earlier.
You didn't laugh at all
when he made jokes.
That's not true.
I laughed as hard as I could.
Oh, I see.
(Sniffling)
You have a runny nose.
- It's a bit chilly.
- I know.
May I ask what you do for a living?
- My occupation?
- Yes.
It's kind of a secret.
A secret?
- It's a secret?
- Why do you all use English words?
- She used an English word.
- I thought...
- That was sexy.
- Did she study abroad?
- I bet she studied abroad.
- Do you work at a national agency?
- Do you?
- I'll tell you when we get close.
Okay then.
Woman Two, it's your turn.
Hello, everyone. I run...
a small coffee shop.
Why?
- It suits you though.
- I know.
- It suits you.
- It does suit her.
Indeed. A small coffee shop owner.
- I'm a small coffee shop owner...
- Are you a certified barista?
- Pardon?
Yes, I brew coffee by myself.
- Where is your coffee shop?
- In which area?
- Where is it located?
- Well...
- Isn't it in Yongsan?
- It's in Goyang.
- Oh, Goyang?
- Yes.
- Oh, I see.
- We have our own parking spots.
And we also provide
a valet parking service if you want.
- A valet parking service too?
- Yes.
She has a lot of jobs.
I have to do everything on my own.
- It's a really small coffee shop.
- I see.
If I visit your coffee shop,
you won't be bothered
because I don't have a car.
(He suddenly confessed
that he doesn't own a car.)
But I have a bicycle.
- How thoughtful.
- Yes.
He's being very honest.
- Of course.
- I find it very attractive.
I know. I don't have a car.
How about you work
at my coffee shop?
- Pardon?
- At my coffee shop.
I told you earlier...
- that I work in the IT industry.
- Right.
- Yet you don't own a car.
- Pardon me?
- You don't own a car.
- Shut it.
- What's wrong with this man?
- What was that?
- That's rude. We just met.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
- How could he?
He and I had a little confrontation
in the beginning.
- With Man Two?
- Yes.
I'm here to find a variety partner
who can make people laugh.
That's great.
- Thank you.
- She looks like a good entertainer.
- I think she'll do well.
- She looks cheerful.
- Woman Three.
- Oh, okay.
- Did you call her "Ma'am?"
- "Ma'am?"
- I was surprised.
- I'm sorry. I was mistaken.
- "Ma'am?"
It sounded like "ma'am."
I was so surprised.
- Woman Three sounds similar to it.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Woman Three.
- Right.
I run a shop-in-shop.
(Woman Three runs a shop-in-shop.)
- What's a shop-in-shop?
- A small store within another.
Actually, I run a tanning salon
within your gym.
- But you didn't recognize me.
- A tanning salon?
(Woman Three opened her shop
in Man Four's gym.)
I think I know you.
- We know each other.
- Yes.
You're right.
Do you run a tanning salon
in his gym?
- Yes.
- It must be a very large gym.
I recommended her shop
to the members of my gym.
(It turns out that they are
quite closely acquainted.)
- You two know each other.
- Yes.
It made me realize
that we live in a small world.
We meet again here.
You're trying to win him over.
(He saw right through her.)
Woman Four, what about you?
I run a flower shop.
(Woman Four is running
a flower shop!)
- Do you actually run it?
- Yes.
- It sounds so realistic.
- They all thought hard.
- They all came up with ideas.
- She sounded so condescending.
That suits her well.
- She must've thought so hard.
- It suits her really well.
- They all run their own businesses.
- That's impressive.
- That's right.
- I may seem a little tough,
but I actually like
pretty, cute things.
- Oh, I see.
- It sounds real.
And my hobby is also water skiing.
- You water ski too?
- Yes.
- She water skis.
- I didn't know that.
I've been practicing
one-handed water skiing.
- That's amazing.
- One-handed water skiing?
One-handed? Really?
Do you even know what it means?
I don't think you do.
To water ski with one hand.
- Show us how to do it.
- Show us.
Show us. Demonstrate it.
- Come on. Show us.
- Show us.
- Mr. Bicycle, show us.
It means you water ski
with one hand.
- Correct.
- Like this.
- You'll die if you do it like this.
- You'll fall into the water.
Just shut it, will you?
- She has a lot of hobbies.
- Indeed.
Woman Five just said...
that she wanted to look rich.
She asked me for an idea.
Next up is Woman Five.
(Everyone else told
their dream jobs.)
I run a real estate agency.
- That suits you. I see.
- That suits you.
She must be rich.
(She carefully picked an occupation
that could make her look rich.)
Actually, this land is...
Do you own this property?
Yes.
- Really?
- Right here?
- This land?
- She's the owner of this property.
Why did you come on this show?
I just wanted to make people laugh.
- She wants to be funny.
- I already have a lot of money.
- Oh, she has a lot of money.
- Just for fun?
- Yes.
- She's charming.
It seems like we all caused
big trouble in the past...
and recently started a new life.
Right.
If this was a movie,
we all are con artists.
Exactly.
(Today, they will be legally lying
in the Variety Village.)
Today, it's Perfect Partner Signal,
Variety Village Race.
You are the male and female members
who came to the Variety Village...
to find a partner...
who would make a great duo
with you on a variety show.
You have a very simple mission
today.
Your goal is to promote yourselves
as much as you can...
and pair up with the opposite gender
at the end of the show.
At the end, you'll vote for the one
you want to pair up with.
The partners who chose each other...
will not get any penalty.
(The ones who choose each other
won't get a penalty.)
Those who failed to pair up
with anyone...
will receive a penalty
regardless of the number of them.
If we fail to pair up with anyone?
However, if you get
more than one vote,
you will receive gold as a prize...
regardless of whether you paired up
with someone or not.
(If you get more than one vote,
you will receive gold.)
We'll be at an advantage
if we're popular.
- That's unbelievable.
- Each one of you will receive...
points as a result of the mission
and the voting at the halfway point.
These points will be helpful...
at the final voting.
So try to get
as many points as you can.
- Oh, I get it.
- Rather than winning one over,
- We should win many over.
- you need to get many votes...
- to receive the prize.
- We should win over all of them.
It's not just us.
- The same goes for you five.
- Yes.
- You should win us over.
- Exactly.
Let's begin
the First Impression Poll...
where you can get some points.
- Right now?
- Based on what you've seen so far,
choose one person who you think
would be the best partner for you.
Then raise the penal all at once.
The number of votes you get is
the number of points you get.
The votes... I get it.
I need to get many votes.
Oh, boy.
- If I choose him...
- Which one should I pick?
Whom you will choose now
will affect how things go for you...
during the race.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I don't know whom I should choose.
Have you all made your decisions?
- I made up my mind.
- I chose one.
You can't change your vote.
Raise it at once
when I count to three.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- This is a hard choice.
- Ready?
One.
(This is an important first step
that will decide what happens next.)
- Two.
- The first voting has begun.
I wonder how their first impressions
of one another were.
Three.
(Who could be the most popular ones
to be a variety partner?)
- Now...
- What?
(Here's the result
of the male members' voting.)
(The Result
of the First Impression Poll)
Woman Four got 3 votes.
Woman Five got 2 votes,
and Woman Three got 1 vote.
Three.
(The most desirable variety partner
chosen by the female members is...)
(The Result
of the First Impression Poll)
- Now...
- What?
Man Five got 2 votes.
(With Ji Hyo and In Ah's votes,
Suk Jin gained two points.)
Man One, Man Two,
and Man Three got 1 vote.
Yes!
- Woman Four got 3 votes.
- Yes.
Woman Five got 2 votes,
and Woman Three got 1 vote.
- We checked your first impressions.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- We'll give you the points you got.
- All right.
- Okay.
You will change your clothes now
and then move to the first location.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Most of all, I prefer a tall guy...
because I'm very tall for a woman.
That's why he caught my eye
when I first met everyone.
(Why did you choose Man Two?)
Also, while we were talking,
he seemed to have
a good sense of humor.
I thought that strength of his could
offset my weakness,
and he'd be a great variety partner
for me.
That's why I chose him.
I didn't expect much on my way here.
I just told myself to be myself...
and to have a good time.
(You got a vote from Woman Four.
What do you think about it?)
I don't know if you saw it,
but Woman Four and I chose
each other.
That made me think...
that I might win this race.
(It made him think
he might win the race.)
What do you think about the future
of the dried seafood industry?
How would I know that?
I know nothing about that field.
I heard you started a business
related to it.
- I just inherited the business.
- I see.
I'm still a rookie in the industry.
(Man Two is still a rookie
in the dried seafood industry.)
(A word to Man Three
whom you voted for?)
Man Three.
I think we'll make a great team.
I hope we'll get along well.
(Woman Five feels...)
I'm embarrassed.
Well, I'm not sure
if I should reveal this now,
(How do you feel
now that you've met everyone?)
but there's someone
I'm interested in.
I'm sure we'll get along well.
The exploration for finding
a variety partner is over.
Some smiled and the other cried
at the First Impression Poll.
Finding the perfect partner will
officially begin now.
Hey, So Min.
If you and I keep pairing up,
we both will receive gold, right?
- Absolutely.
- Right?
I don't need anything else.
I just want to find...
someone who shares
a similar sense of humor with me.
- If that's what you want...
- Yes.
- I think you found the right man.
- I know.
You know... So Min.
- You like dancing like this.
- Yes, I love it.
I love it.
I know you like it.
- Absolutely.
- We'd be a perfect duo.
- I like it.
- Right.
- I really like it.
- We hit it off well.
- I like it so much.
- Here they go again.
Oh, right. Jae Suk,
- you dropped something back there.
- What is it?
- What is this?
- He dropped it earlier.
- What is it?
What is it?
It's a coffee shop coupon.
It has all ten stamps on it.
I can get a free cup of coffee.
- Is it free?
- Yes.
- I see. Thank you for this.
- You dropped it.
- Thank you.
- You're funny.
- I'll just keep doing this.
- Am I funny?
Man Six, you look like Lee Duk Hwa.
(He's dressed like
the fishing master.)
I knew he would say that.
Is it an homage
to "The Fishermen and the City?"
You're right.
(The unexpected comment made
the man from abroad feel dizzy.)
Show us how you catch a black porgy.
You must be a fan of the show.
Do you know the show? You might not
know it since you're from overseas.
Have you watched
"The Fishermen and the City?"
- "The Fashion and the City?"
- "The Fishermen and the City."
- "Fishermen."
- I don't know.
- "The Fishermen and the City."
In the first mission,
you will be divided
into three teams.
Woman Three, Woman Four,
and Woman Five...
will play a game
and choose their team members.
- We'll be divided into three teams.
- Sounds great.
- The three of them?
- Okay!
Woman 3, Woman 4, and Woman 5.
The game they will play is
Pulling Sideburns.
(They will play Pulling Sideburns.)
- Oh, boy.
- It hurts.
- It hurts so much.
- I hate that game.
I actually lost some sideburn hair
while playing this game.
The three of them will pull up
one another's sideburns.
The one who screams first will lose.
- The toughest one will win.
- Yes.
The winner will...
get to choose all three members
at once.
That's a great benefit.
Three of you, please come forward.
- In Ah, come forward.
- Go for it!
- It's not as easy as it seems.
- Just endure it.
- Right.
- Whom will I fight with?
- The three of you will compete.
- All together.
- Like this?
- You pull... Exactly.
Woman Three is already thinking of
fighting with the others.
Hold the others' sideburns
with both of your hands.
Are we pulling
one another's sideburns?
(They should do it even though
they met for the first time.)
But we met for the first time.
- Please sit on the floor.
- Okay.
- Grab one another's hair.
- Grab it.
If one of you makes a noise,
you can let her hair go.
Then the remaining two will
continue the game.
You can win this
if you don't make any noise.
Now, please grab each other's hair.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry in advance. I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
- It's just a game. Don't be sorry.
- It's just a game.
I'm not doing this
because I want to. You know, right?
- I'll wind it once.
- I don't want to do this.
(She's winding the hair
around her finger.)
Her hair is too thin.
You shouldn't pull it out.
Make sure not to pull it out.
- You just have to pull it up.
- Just pull it up lightly.
- You shouldn't pull it out.
- If you're ready...
- Ready.
- Please be quiet.
Set.
(They have to win this
to choose the ones they want.)
Go.
(They started pulling the hair
at the same time.)
They're just...
She pulled it up higher.
(The silent war for victory)
- She's moving upward.
- She's feeling it.
- She's moving upward. Right.
- She's moving upward.
- Cho Hee started to feel the pain.
- She's going up.
- I'm being pulled up too.
- In Ah... Oh, right.
- Pulling up higher.
(Once you make a noise, you're out.)
(Time is passing
as they endure the pain.)
(Groaning)
(She groaned unintentionally
as they pulled her hair harder.)
He In is out.
(The remaining two...)
Hey, if you pull only one side...
Her skin is being pulled up.
- Hey, In Ah.
- She's shaking.
Look at her skin.
- Your hair might get pulled out.
- The skin is being pulled up.
My gosh. They're pulling it so hard.
One of you should just give up.
I said your skin is being pulled up.
- Stop it.
- Throw in the towel.
Play rock-paper-scissors instead.
Your skin is being pulled up.
- Play rock-paper-scissors instead.
- Stop it.
- Call it a draw.
- Let's call it a draw.
- It's a draw.
Play rock-paper-scissors instead.
(They sacrificed their hair
for a variety show.)
- It hurts.
- Her skin was being pulled so hard.
It was scary.
- Wasn't it a friendly match?
- I heard something being torn off.
I know.
- They'll play rock-paper-scissors.
- That's a good idea.
I thought their faces would come off
like in "Mission Impossible."
- I'd be so upset if I lose...
- I thought it was happening.
- after enduring the pain.
- Exactly.
- They pulled it hard.
- He In pulled their hair up high.
All of your eyes looked like this.
(All three of them passed
the funny face test.)
That was so funny.
- That's how attractive we are.
- Good job.
That's how attractive we are.
The two of you will play
rock-paper-scissors.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- That's ridiculous.
(In Variety Village, you must
be polite but do your best to win.)
They're pretending to be nice.
Rock-paper-scissors
(In Ah wins, and Cho Hee loses.)
They were neck and neck once again.
In Ah, you're incredible.
- I'm sorry.
- She's amazing.
In Ah
- In Ah is here, baby
- Do you know what this is?
- In Ah, you're amazing.
- "Do you know what this is?"
- Do you?
- How does she know it?
- Okay.
In Ah, please choose three people
you want on your team.
- Go ahead.
- Three members at once?
It's only for this mission.
(Sending a signal)
(Chuckling)
(Choosing team members can also be
a Perfect Partner Signal.)
- Man Four.
- Okay.
Woman Two.
(Who could be the last one?)
And Man One.
(She chose Man One
who was staying still.)
You mean, Man One? Him?
- Yes.
- Man One?
- That's great.
- All right. Good.
- You chose great ones.
- This is good.
- But...
- That's a good choice.
- I gave her a signal.
- Can you make some room?
- Come and sit down.
- Okay.
- She wants to win.
- Good choice.
Next, Cho Hee, please choose
three members you want on your team.
(Snapping)
- I haven't done this in a while.
- It's been a long time.
- He hasn't done it in a while.
- Indeed.
Gosh. What was that?
- You looked like a lowlife.
- That brings back old memories.
- I choose Man Six.
- Okay!
She chose Man Six.
And Man Three.
- Man Three.
- And I choose...
Choose one more person.
I choose...
Woman One.
- Woman One.
- Nice.
Hold on. This could be...
- She chose the wrong ones.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm glad we're on the same team.
- It seems that we're going to...
- play a game while sitting.
- What?
- You're right. Hang on.
- Oh, right.
Jong Kook is right.
- I see a sketchbook...
- Okay.
- and a xylophone.
- It's a quiz.
- Hang on.
- You know, the three of them...
I'm worried.
The first mission will give you...
a chance to show off your teamwork.
It's Crazy Speed Quiz.
- Crazy Speed Quiz.
- What could that be?
- I'm fully confident.
- All members of the team will play.
The team with the highest score
will win.
Is it a quiz?
- But...
- We're done for.
- A quiz...
- Don't worry.
She said, "We're done for."
They're the three empty heads.
- I bet she didn't know.
- Woman Five...
- I feel bad for her.
- Woman Five.
Why did she choose them?
It's rare to see all three of us
on the same team, but today,
there might be four empty heads
on the same team.
It's a perfect team
for a variety show.
They'll be like
Running Man Avengers.
- A team of empty heads.
- Don't worry.
We're good at this.
The team members will take turns
answering questions.
You gain one point if you say a word
included in the given category...
in three seconds.
If you say the same answer
that someone else always said,
- you lose one point.
- I'm not good at things like this.
If you say a wrong answer
or can't say anything,
- you lose five points.
- It requires wit.
It's better to say the same answer
than saying nothing.
- Even if we lose one point.
- That's better.
- Okay. Let's do this!
- Yes.
I'm confident.
- It will continue without a break.
- Got it.
Don't be nervous.
Why are you getting so nervous?
I'm not good at things like this.
- He's shaking again.
- Look.
- He's fidgeting with his toes.
- He's shaking.
- This is my specialty.
- He's the first one to go.
Man One, your lips turned purple.
- What?
- You must be really nervous.
- This is my specialty.
- Why?
It's normal to get nervous...
- when it requires speed.
- It's my specialty.
Games that require speed.
- We'll begin with this team.
- Me?
The first round will be easy.
- Okay.
- That's great.
Countries in Europe. 1, 2, 3.
- France.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Italy.
- Denmark.
- 1, 2, 3.
- The UK.
- Denmark.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Switzerland.
- Turkey.
- 1, 2, 3.
- The Netherlands.
- Sweden.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Finland again.
- Prague.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Greece.
- Prague was incorrect.
- But...
- Come on.
So Min, please.
(The team lost a few points
as So Min said the same answers.)
There's a lot of countries
in Europe.
One of them couldn't even say
anything.
- I know.
- That's right.
- Excuse me. Our team is playing.
- Yes?
- Why do you keep interrupting?
- I'm sorry, but why did you do it?
- We must be accurate.
- Mister.
- Don't call me that.
- But you're a man.
That's true. But don't call me that.
- What else should I call you?
- Gosh, seriously.
- Call me "Man 5."
- Oh, "Man 5?"
- Yes. Don't call me "Mister."
- Okay.
- Man Five, why did you do that?
- You're so weird, mister.
Why did you call me that
when you asked me not to?
- That's it. He got caught.
- He got caught.
- Why are you speaking casually?
- You did the same thing earlier.
- So I tried it.
- Why are you speaking casually?
- I mean...
- Why did he sit there?
Don't forget to click "Like"
and subscribe to our channel.
- Are you going to punch me?
- What?
Are you going to punch me
in front of the camera?
Why would you speak casually to me?
- Stop arguing and sit here.
- Did you hear what he said?
- No. Stay here.
- Come over here.
He annoys me even more than you do.
- He's even worse.
- Stop it.
- He's even more annoying.
- Don't do that to my team member.
- My gosh.
- Stay there for now.
- Okay.
By the way, I think I know
the purpose of this game.
You're trying to make us
hate each other, right?
Do you see what I mean? Right?
- We see the worst in each other.
- I mean...
- The worst in us.
- It will only make us...
- We need to impress each other.
- This is not helping.
- No one will pick me.
- Exactly.
- Next up is this team.
- The Czech Republic.
- It'll be a disaster. Watch.
- Ready.
- Are you ready to laugh?
- Yes.
It'll be a mess.
Here's the category.
Capital cities
except for those of Asian countries.
(What does that mean?)
- What does that mean?
- One.
- We should...
- Luxemburg.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Jamaica... No.
- I mean, Kingston.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Kingston?
- What did he say? I didn't hear...
- I said the correct answer!
(The team of empty heads lost
many points from the beginning.)
- I said Kingston.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Well...
- 1, 2,
- Hungary.
- Three.
(He confidently said Hungary.)
(The first empty head thinks
Hungary is a city.)
- 1, 2, 3.
- London.
- Well...
- 1, 2, 3.
- London.
- Paris.
- Too late.
1, 2, 3.
(The spaced out one
next to the dumb one)
- Wait.
- 1, 2, 3.
- This is so great. Nice.
- You're doing great.
You said two correct answers.
(They said
only two correct answers.)
My gosh.
(The empty heads didn't let us down
as always.)
- Asian countries...
- Capital cities...
except for those of Asian countries.
- That team is unbelievable.
- Awesome.
- My goodness.
- We'll win.
- This is so nice.
- I'm having so much fun.
That was a disaster.
- Woman Five was an empty head too.
- That was so funny.
Woman Five is an empty head too.
I studied before the shoot.
I studied... Is it over?
- It's over.
- Your score is minus 63.
- What did you say?
- We did well.
Is it even possible
to get that score?
(Is getting that score possible?)
You got a higher score
than I thought it would be.
- You guys did well.
- Minus 63?
- He didn't understand the question.
- I didn't.
I know capital cities. Paris...
- and Washington, DC.
- Good.
I know all of them.
I could've said at least these two.
It would be minus 13
if they had said Prague 13 times.
Why did they confuse me
by saying something about Asia?
- That's why I missed the timing.
- There's Stockholm too.
You learned the capital city
of Argentina not long ago.
- Buenos Saires.
- He...
It's Buenos Aires.
Quiet down. Don't say anything.
I see that he already gave up.
I'm supposed to look charming
when I speak.
But whenever I speak,
I look less and less charming.
- He's a complete empty head.
- It's funny.
- You have great chemistry.
- I know.
- The answers were close enough.
- Saires?
- Brasilia.
- Buenos Saires?
Okay, good.
It seems like
they're all put off by us,
so let's team up within the group.
You can both pick me.
The others won't
be fond of us anyway.
- Within the group.
- Okay?
- Okay, got it.
- It's over for us.
We're done for.
- Yes, you're done.
- Okay.
(The round ends with them
putting the others off.)
Just saying the same answer
13 times...
will put us ahead of them.
- If you draw a blank...
- If you don't know the answer,
- just say what someone else said.
- Got it.
- It'll still put us in second.
- That's a good strategy.
Don't guess if you don't know.
Okay, here we go.
English words that start with an A.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Apple.
- 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Apple.
- 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Apple.
- 1, 2, 3.
Apple. Hold on a second.
- 2, 3.
- Are you kidding me?
(They had to use their strategy
a bit early in the game.)
- Again.
- 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- April.
- 1, 2, 3.
(They're no better
than the empty heads.)
- A...
- 1, 2, 3.
- Well...
Arab!
We'll count Arab.
- I mean...
- Is that the best you can do?
There are thousands of words
that start with A.
- You're better than this.
- It's...
There's AlphaGo.
- You're better than this.
- Armani.
- Hold on.
- You could've done better.
You went from countries
to capital cities to...
There are thousands of words
that start with an A.
- Are you kidding me?
- So Min...
- Do you know what she said?
- What?
"Jae Suk, there are thousands of
words starting with an A."
"Like Umbrella."
"Umbrella."
(Woman Two thought that
Umbrella began with an A.)
Seriously?
Jae Suk,
there are thousands of answers.
- Umbrella.
- That's enough.
Umbrella.
Umbrella begins with a U.
(She really didn't know
since she said it twice.)
(You're part of
the Empty Head Club!)
(Whoa!)
We're completely put off by you.
Get out of here.
A coffee shop owner
is not wanted either.
It begins with a U.
- Unbelievable.
- It begins with a U.
She...
Umbrella made me laugh so hard.
That was the best.
- Next...
- There's "ant" along with others.
- We're back to you guys.
- Can you...
have them name English words...
so that they can implode?
We're back to you guys.
- No more English words.
- Why not?
No more English words.
(His voice squeaks.)
(His voice squeaks
out of fear for English words.)
Did you hear that?
His voice squeaked.
- You must be feeling the pressure.
- Well...
- "No more English words."
- It had me worried.
You know what?
I found that quite charming.
- I won't go for English words.
- Okay.
It's doable then.
- Listen up for the question.
- That was hilarious.
Here we go.
Foreign painters.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- What?
- Vincent van Gogh.
- 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2...
- Paul Gauguin.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Leonardo da Vinci.
1, 2, 3.
- Mr. Chelly?
- 1, 2, 3.
- Vincent van Gogh.
- Picasso.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Vincent van Gogh.
Leonardo DiCaprio.
Hold on.
- Leonardo DiCaprio?
- 1, 2, 3.
- Go...
- Vincent van Gogh.
Vance Breck.
(Vance Breck, since 2021)
(Known for his piece
"The Empty Head")
Dance break, was it?
- Dance break?
- Dance break.
Even as a guy, I'm put off by him.
It's your turn now.
- We should switch seats.
- Why?
- There's really no difference.
- But Woman Four...
- It's making me dizzy.
- Is it?
- Then let me...
- Really?
- I'll take the middle seat.
- Thank you.
It's understandable.
Woman Four, you don't seem...
- to be that knowledgeable.
- I also...
don't think...
she's a fast thinker.
- Empty Head.
- All right.
Name the series and movies
Kwang Soo's been in.
- What?
- This isn't an easy one.
"Collective Invention."
(The filmography of
an actor of 14 years)
- "Collective Invention."
- 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- "Collective Invention."
- 1, 2, 3.
1, 2, 3.
- "Tazza One-Eyed Jacks."
- 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
"Tazza One-Eyed Jacks."
- Darn it!
- "Collective Invention."
(Darn it!)
(Whatever Kwang Soo says
comes back to him like an echo.)
- 1, 2, 3.
- "Live."
- In 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
- "Live."
- "Collective Invention."
- 1, 2, 3.
- I'm done.
(Kwang Soo announces
that he's quitting.)
- Hold on a second.
- Seriously?
(The Baeksang award winner
is more than just upset.)
Seriously?
It's...
- Do you even know who I am?
- I do.
Have you watched
at least one of them?
- I went to a premier,
- He was in many shows.
- but I don't remember which one.
- Right?
- Just pick one from the list!
- But...
Atka mackerel, halibut,
and frozen pollack.
I didn't mean
you should name fishes.
Anyway, here are the results.
In first place...
is Team Woman Three.
- Okay!
- Nice!
- Nice.
- Good one.
(They all receive 3 points each.)
In second place...
is Team Woman Four.
(They all get a point each.)
You have a total of minus 78 points.
(No one even comes close.)
Nicely done, guys.
It's all or nothing.
We can stick together though.
- Right.
- We'll partner up within the group.
- I have a feeling that'll happen.
- Exactly.
- They'll fall for each other.
- Right.
(The empty heads get absorbed
in each other's charms.)
- You must all be hungry.
- We are.
You'll take a step closer
to one another by partnering up...
in this round of Loving Lunch Box.
- A lunch box?
- Will we be sharing?
We're already choosing our partners?
The ladies will wait
in their designated spots.
The men will seek out
the woman they'd like...
to share their lunch with.
The points the women will receive...
depend on the number of men
that come looking for them.
(The ladies will receive points
every time someone comes to them.)
This...
- Hold on.
- After lunch,
the ladies...
will each choose one of the men.
That man will receive
the same number of points.
You can choose
whoever comes looking for you.
But if you don't like any of them...
and would rather show off your charm
to another man,
you can choose
to give them the points.
(They can choose anyone they want.)
- I wonder what'll happen.
- I'll receive a lot of points.
- This is a hard one.
- What will happen?
This is a little worrying.
It seems as though...
we should manage within this group.
We'll partner up within the group.
Be smart about this.
(We'll look forward
to their loyalty.)
There's something you should know.
We have the most points.
- Of course.
- Right.
- In Ah and I...
- She's right.
- We're aware of that.
- The ladies...
will head to their spots
with their packed lunches.
Go ahead.
Cho Hee, go ahead.
There's no need to worry.
But I don't have any points.
Opportunity will find
whoever takes a chance.
Who should I go to?
- Shall we?
- Sure.
Do we just take these?
- Do we take our lunch boxes?
- Sure.
(They take their designated seats.)
What if no one comes to me?
I'd like at least one
to come and find me.
To be honest,
I'm quite fond of Man Three.
He looks like
he'll be good at everything,
but he's a master of none.
It's why...
I feel like I should
care for him in some way.
I have a feeling that
Man Three will seek me out.
He showed how charming he is,
which has probably made him
popular with the ladies.
But when it comes
to who's funnier...
(You seem confident.)
I'm sure I have the advantage.
Man Three and Man Six
should be here for sure.
(Who do you think will come to you?)
That's what I believe.
My teammates are of
the Empty Head Club.
(They're all stupid.)
We were all just as stupid, right?
I mean...
Who else would they go to?
I'm their only option.
Who would accept them?
Surprisingly enough, Man Three
is popular with the ladies.
- Can I meet him outside?
- Sure.
Are Woman Four and Woman Five...
waiting for Man Three as well?
(Where will Man Three's heart
take him?)
Where will Man Three's heart...
take him?
- You eat with someone comfortable.
- Right.
I find So Min comfortable.
I agree,
but she has been buttering up
to just about anyone.
Exactly.
- She only means half her words.
- I know.
This is something I personally hate.
It's cheesy, isn't it?
Her choice of words
is always so cheesy.
(The IT expert hates paper coupons.)
It's why I made up my mind.
- Have you?
- Yes.
- Someone comfortable?
- I'd rather have lunch at ease.
- Hold on.
I'm not shy around strangers though.
I can eat just about anything too.
Even street food?
- You're not shy around strangers?
- Not at all.
I can be friendly with people
who I see for the first time.
Is that so?
I know you to be quite sensitive.
- That's hardly the case.
- Is that so?
You're one to eat food
in the most unappealing way.
- I know, but...
- Who should I choose?
Since I've been on He In's team,
maybe I should go
and talk to Cho Hee this time.
Cho Hee...
is the silliest.
- Is she?
- Yes.
- Really?
- She's the new Empty Head.
- She's...
- From what I could tell,
- she seemed fun to be around.
- Right.
She's funny.
- She's like sunshine too.
- I agree.
What if someone else
chooses the same partner?
- Do I eat with him?
- You'll all eat together.
You'll dine together.
But I don't want
to eat with Kwang Soo.
- Do you think that's a possibility?
- I do.
Who will you go to?
Tell us who your first choice is.
I'd like to know more about He In.
- He In?
- Yes.
She intrigues me.
- The way you put it is hilarious.
- You know,
Se Chan could really
be interested in her.
- It could be for real.
- Right.
- He's not like us.
- Of course not.
- This isn't serious for us.
- Right.
- But me...
- He could actually mean it.
I mean, Se Chan...
- Only me though.
- Right.
Only I can show interest
in Cho Hee and He In.
I really want to know them better.
- Then...
- Could it be too embarrassing?
Then let's allow Se Chan...
to have some alone time with He In.
- Just the two of them.
- Right.
- I'll go to her.
- You should.
So no one will join us? Okay.
Just the two of them.
Good.
After the meal,
she might be
put off by you completely.
That's the worst-case scenario.
He makes noises when he eats.
- You make noises?
- And he spills.
Some women hate that.
- It's all good.
- Women hate that, you know.
You're actually serious, aren't you?
Could you guys help me
just this once?
- Sure.
- I'm asking you.
- You know...
- We'll keep the possibilities open.
- You...
- can go to He In.
- Thanks.
- We'll make it happen for you.
- Right.
Just know this though.
You aren't compatible at all.
(You aren't compatible at all.)
I mean it.
Completely incompatible.
- You don't suit her.
- You're the worst.
- I like you, but...
- You look like her manager.
- It feels like...
- I'll see how compatible we are.
- "The Manager."
- Yes, let's see.
- Man One, you can set off now.
- I can?
- Man One, go ahead.
- Gosh.
- Oh, there's a map?
- We need to move strategically.
My goodness.
(Man 1 sets off first.)
Who's sitting there?
Oh, it's Cho Hee!
- Hi! Are you coming to me?
- You're sitting outside.
- Are you coming to me?
- Actually...
I didn't know you were here.
It's very close.
Yes. It's very close, isn't it?
Don't go somewhere far,
- and just come to me.
- Okay, okay. Hang on.
(Walking away)
- He's testing the waters.
- They're all waving at me.
Hey, So Min!
What do you mean? I'm not So Min!
Oh, you're In Ah. I'm sorry.
Do you have plenty of side dishes?
- Sorry?
- I have some meat for a side dish.
Oh, okay.
You came out this far to meet me?
Yes. You're going to look around
and come back, right?
Of course I will.
- Where are you going?
- Just hang in there.
- Man One!
- This is where you are. It's close.
(Woman 2 who has many petty talents
uses an echo to attract Man 1.)
Man One!
(Man 1 already burst into laughter.)
- You are...
- Over here!
She's indeed funny.
I missed you.
She's really funny.
Let's eat together!
I can dance for you...
the whole time while you're
having your lunch.
I can dance twice as fast.
I can do all types of dances.
What do you think?
- Really?
- There's a dance you like.
There's a dance you like.
There is.
Yes, I like that kind of dance.
(Woman 2 inspires
the dancer in Man 1.)
- She's such a good dancer.
- She's really funny.
Woman Two is funny.
Wait a minute. Where should I eat?
How are you?
(She asks how he is,
using the line from "Love Letter.")
Man One is flustered by all the love
he's getting for the first time.
Man One.
(She dances nonstop.)
She's incredible.
- So Min.
- She's funny.
- I give up.
- She's indeed funny.
- You got this.
- Woman Two is funny.
Wait a minute. I'll just...
(Will Man 1 have his lunch
with Woman 2?)
I'll have my lunch with Woman One.
(Shocked)
(The one who's chosen
is shocked too.)
- Really?
- Yes.
- It's because...
- Thank you.
I want to eat...
- You're not talkative, right?
- Of course not.
You need to eat comfortably.
- I love it.
- Man One!
I want to eat with...
Woman One who is
not the talkative type.
- You need to eat comfortably.
- Yes.
I want to eat comfortably.
- Good luck, Man Two.
- Thank you.
I'm not sure who I should pick.
(Man 2 sets off right after.)
Actually, at first,
He In picked me.
(Man 2 still hasn't decided.)
Nevertheless,
to win as many points as I can...
My gosh.
Young Master.
- My gosh, hello.
- Come this way.
(Woman 3 came to meet
the young master.)
But you didn't pick me
when we were picking team members.
Also, I just heard from somewhere...
that you said I look sly.
That wasn't me.
I heard the person who interviewed
before me said that.
- Oh, there was another interviewee?
- Yes.
Well, for me...
Oh, you chose your partner already?
Yes, I already picked mine.
(It's not you.)
Woman Three was rejected again.
I guess no one is coming this way.
(Smirking)
- May I come in?
- Hi.
Please come in, Man Two.
(You came to me!)
- Hello.
- My goodness.
What? You were there?
Yes, I'm stationed here.
(An unexpected love triangle)
- Oh, you were here, Woman Four.
- Yes.
There's lots of yellow dust today.
You should come inside.
- Wait, I need to...
- Come inside.
No, don't go.
Who are you looking at?
Didn't you come to see me, Man Two?
- Didn't you come to see me?
- No, I was...
This is driving me crazy.
This is so uncomfortable.
(He finds this sudden popularity
very uncomfortable.)
You should get back inside.
- No, I won't.
- Go back inside.
The weather is nice today, so...
Go back inside.
The weather is nice, I know.
Someone else is coming
for you, Woman Four.
I'll eat with Woman Five.
- Okay. Enjoy your lunch.
- Man Two, who was torn...
between the two, decided to
let Man Three take care of the rest.
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
Hello.
I won't end up eating alone, will I?
I'm sure I won't.
- Okay, I'll set off now.
- Man Three, it's your turn.
- Please be considerate.
- Okay.
- It's been a while.
- Man Three set off to...
find his love just in time.
It's been a while
since I've had such an experience.
- Sure.
- My goodness.
- It's exciting.
- I think he's serious.
- He's serious.
- He must not know...
they don't look good together.
(He can't help but smile
even when the others sneer at him.)
Where could she be?
My goodness. Ms. Song.
Our team has zero points, right?
That's true.
Please eat with me.
There's someone else coming.
I don't like it when people
act unnaturally.
(Reading a book under a tree)
Oh, you're here.
(Ms. Ambrella tries to appeal
with her intelligence.)
I'll go and look around.
- Your legs will hurt, Se Chan.
- I'll go and look around.
They said they'll support me,
so I'm going to meet
the woman of my life.
My gosh.
Gosh, I might as well
just sprinkle some salt.
- Are you done for today?
- Yes, I'm done.
I should just go home.
I'm losing money.
We should follow our strategy.
We have no other choice.
I have my own strategy too.
Gosh, Se Chan...
Why don't you go
and compete with him?
Why don't you go where Se Chan is...
You have to remember this.
Se Chan could be really shy
in front of her.
I could go and make things
easy for him.
(Se Chan could be shy, so I could go
and make things easy for him.)
But I want to see him being shy.
Man 5 is just envious of Man 3's...
infinite possibilities.
I can go and talk badly
about Se Chan.
"Do you still stay overnight
at someone else's place?"
You could do that.
But it could play against you.
- You think so?
- Because you never go home.
Se Chan will say this.
"You don't go home either."
- That's fine.
- He could say that.
- It's fine with you?
- My wife knows the truth.
- She might not know.
- You have a wife?
You have a wife?
- If you do, you can't be here.
- I'm sorry.
- I just...
- It's the rule of this place.
Please keep it a secret.
- You'll be in big trouble.
- The others won't find out.
It's okay as long as
the women don't know.
Our show will be ruined.
I'm sorry about that.
- Do you have kids also?
- You don't have a kid, do you?
I have a kid,
but I can't lie about it.
I feel so bad for my kid.
I feel bad if I say
that I don't have a kid.
- I feel bad for the kid.
- You have a kid too?
I do.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
If you two keep it a secret,
I'll edit the rest of the parts.
Many people have watched it already.
(Man 3 heads to the open door
without a doubt.)
All right.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- My gosh.
I came straight to you.
My, thank you for coming.
It's as though I'm attracted to you
like a magnet.
- Come, come.
- I came to you.
(Laughing awkwardly)
- How shall we sit?
- You can sit there.
- Sure.
- The left side of my face...
- is more handsome.
- Is that so?
- Yes, so I'll sit here.
- Okay.
My goodness. Thank you for coming.
Not at all.
(Laughing awkwardly)
My gosh. Were you perhaps
hoping for someone specific to come?
- Sorry? I wanted you to come.
- Did you want anyone...
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
I actually did an interview earlier.
They asked me if I wanted
anyone specific to come.
What did you say to that?
(In the interview earlier)
I want Man Five to come.
(Woman 4 hoped for Man 5 to come.)
At first, he seemed like too much,
but as we played games together
on the same team,
he took good care of me.
(She didn't even mention Man 3.
She's lying with an innocent face.)
- Sorry?
- What did you say to that?
- You said you wanted me to come?
- Yes.
So I said I want Man Three
to come to me.
You had me in mind
from the beginning?
(Coming up with an excuse
as Man Three is taking it seriously)
- When we were playing the quiz.
- Really?
Oh, when we played the quiz earlier?
Yes, I liked how humorous you are.
You seemed very pure.
(He's smiling widely
after hearing her compliment.)
- I thought you were very pure.
- My gosh.
I'm watching your drama,
"Sisyphus," these days.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- I really like it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Yes.
(He can't hide his excitement.)
(Has Man 3
finally found his other half?)
- See you later.
- Okay.
I can see them on my way.
I can see them.
Let me be honest with you, Man Five.
Yes. What is it?
I have something to tell you.
- I have kids too.
- Is that so?
I knew we had something in common.
(The father who lived abroad
plucked up his courage to confess.)
So the two of us have kids.
- I knew you had kids.
- I felt really uncomfortable.
I felt bad for my family.
- I have 3 kids.
- 3?
- I feel...
- You can't say you don't have kids.
I feel so much better now.
- You feel better, right?
- Yes.
I know. We can't lie.
It looks like you're having fun.
(Man 4 is patrolling the village
and checking on the others.)
Hang on.
What are you doing here?
I think no one will come to me.
Why... Why are you here?
(Woman 3 came to meet Man 4
with his name tag on her forehead.)
(Woman 3 who kept
getting rejected...)
- Woman 3 kept getting rejected,
- Seriously, I feel like...
so she decided to go after Man 4
who loves hearing compliments.
It's Man Four's turn, right?
Are you going to come this way
like a man?
But where are you supposed to be?
Over here.
I was going to go to you.
- Really?
- Why did you come all the way out?
- I was going to go to you. Sure.
- Really?
Of course.
With their effort to win affection
and some kind of deal,
Woman 2 and 3 got partners
to eat with.
I mean...
You two look very awkward.
First, if you...
- If you come,
- I will...
(The woman that Man 6 picks
takes 1st place and earns 2 points.)
I'll give a point
to Cho Hee for sure.
(The man Cho Hee picks
earns 2 points as well.)
You're trying to make me sit here.
I guess you're thinking
I'm an easy match to beat.
Not at all.
- What did you say?
- That's not true at all.
So Min seems to be
in good condition today.
But you've seen her a lot.
You're used to her ways.
That was nice. I like how you just
dropped the honorifics.
I really like it
when women do that too.
- Honestly, Haha can...
- Okay!
- Great!
- Okay.
Okay! Bring it on!
Yes!
(Woman 5 won 2 points. Which man
will win 2 points with her?)
- You're in first place.
- Yes, I am!
- That's true.
- Yes!
(Man 2 and Man 6 are with Woman 5.)
The female members need to pick
the male members...
they'll give points to
before they finish their meal.
- You made the right choice.
- Thank you.
Excuse me for asking,
but how old are you?
- Me? I'm 32.
- Yes.
Oh, really? I see.
I look older than that, don't I?
- No, no!
- Really?
I'm 36.
(Man 3 reacted awkwardly
after hearing her age.)
- You look younger than your age.
- Man Three.
- Sorry?
- Did you bring your apron?
What do you mean?
You usually spill food all the time
when you eat, so...
Excuse me, this is not the place
to say such things.
But don't you usually wear aprons
when you eat?
You should scram.
What on earth are you talking about?
We're having a nice talk,
- and you ruined...
- You usually spill food a lot.
- What do you mean?
- That's why you put on an apron.
I'll take small bites today.
What do you mean by an apron?
I just wanted to make sure
you had it.
(He became way more careful
in case he spills food.)
It's good.
(He became way more careful
in case he spills food.)
I love eating.
Really? But you're so skinny.
I love working out, that's why.
Do you work out a lot?
I'm doing a modern dance
called Tanzplay.
You're doing a modern dance?
Yes, I do it for fun,
but I'm quite good at it too.
- Oh, really?
- But I didn't major in it.
I do horseback riding too.
You do horseback riding?
(You do horseback riding?)
Where?
The riding ground I go to
is in Uijeongbu.
Oh, Uijeongbu? Really?
(He finally hears a word
he's familiar with.)
I live in Dongducheon.
I'm from Uijeongbu.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
(Man 3 finally gets to
smile broadly.)
- Oh, this regionalism...
- I finally found...
something we have in common.
- You're from Uijeongbu?
- Yes.
I went to elementary, middle,
and high school there.
Oh, really? I went to school
in Dongducheon.
- We lived so close by.
- I know.
- It was only 15 minutes away.
- No wonder.
(They didn't live in the same area,
but Se Chan insists that they did.)
Do you still live in Uijeongbu?
No, I live near Cheongdam-dong now.
- Oh, Cheongdam-dong? I see.
- Yes.
(Cheongdam-dong? I see.)
(Bursting into laughter)
That's funny.
I don't think we make a good couple.
Her life is very different
from mine.
I think this is as far as I can get
for today.
I should've said, "I think
jodhpurs will look good on you."
"Horseback riding sounds like fun."
But I reacted so poorly.
I don't think she'll write my name.
I'm done for.
The private lunch with her
was messed up.
(Shaking his head)
(Meanwhile, the three of them
are having lunch together.)
What are your hobbies, Cho Hee?
(What are your hobbies, Cho Hee?)
- Me?
- Shall we take a guess?
(What are Woman 5's hobbies?)
You're the active type, aren't you?
Me? Not at all.
No, she's a homebody.
(No, she's a homebody.)
Don't people call you sly?
What?
He doesn't know how to
read the room.
- They don't call me that.
- You're like a snake.
Me too.
- You're a homebody too?
- Totally.
Look how my arms have no muscles.
Actually, this is my first outing...
in eight years.
That's how much I love
staying at home.
I'm serious.
Oh, really? I can't believe it.
I hear your house is
actually a famous club.
- What are you talking about?
- Isn't that true?
Why would my house be a club?
I think I've seen you there.
I think you have a nice personality.
(I think you have
a nice personality.)
That was so random.
I mean it. When I'm with you...
How shall I put it?
I feel comfortable.
You can talk comfortably with me.
Sure. I just feel like
sharing all my secrets with you.
(Man 6 starts making a move
by talking nonsense.)
I think you're the type
who'll understand everything.
I feel like I'll cry if you just
listen to my stories.
Right. Having someone listen
to your story...
- could be really consoling.
- Right. I really mean it.
I'm talking
as if there are no cameras here.
I mean it. I feel like you'll
listen to my stories really well.
Wow, I can't believe
he's going this far.
(Wow, I can't believe
he's going this far.)
This is driving me crazy.
I mean it. I'm serious.
- All this for the points?
- You're serious?
I don't know.
I'm not used to life in Korea.
What's the time, Mr. Wolf?
But...
By the way, is it okay
if our voices overlap like this?
What's the time, Mr. Wolf?
(Woman 5 and Man 2 are busy
playing a game to put on a show.)
You just moved! You moved!
- No, I didn't!
- Yes, you did!
- And then...
- You're it.
- I feel like I made a new friend.
- I didn't move!
It was lonely living in Korea,
but I made a new friend.
I was really grateful for it.
I wanted to share
my secrets with her...
- What are you doing?
- and share my stories.
What are you doing?
That's who Woman Five is.
I also want to tell her...
that I have kids.
I think she'll forgive me.
By the way, before you set off,
you said you grew sick of her
after playing a game with her.
- I said that?
- Yes.
Do you believe such slander?
- No, that's... Wait.
- Are you that kind of person?
You can ask her.
It'd be brazen of me
to be sitting here.
Man Six's eyes seem sincere.
- Right?
- But...
Are you saying my eyes are...
Your eyes are a little...
Everyone is talking about it.
You're the one who called me sly,
aren't you?
(You're the one who called me sly,
aren't you?)
Wait a minute. Hey. I got you.
I heard that too.
I heard someone called me sly.
And it was you.
It's okay. I'll protect you.
If I pick someone else
besides you...
Everyone is done having their lunch.
Now it's time for the female members
to vote.
Give the points to me if you can.
It's over. I'm done today.
- There's nothing much to do today.
- This will end it.
I mean, earlier...
I wasn't accustomed
to life in Korea,
but you became a good friend.
Thank you.
I don't want to pressure you
with such talks.
I don't know much about Korea,
but I made a new friend.
(I don't know much about Korea,
but I made a new friend.)
And that's Cho Hee.
(And that's Cho Hee.)
I just want you to know how I feel.
I don't want to pressure you.
Choose whoever you want.
I'm being sincere.
You need to know who's being fake
and who's being sincere.
I've made up my mind.
The female members...
each gave their points
to only one male member.
- Who did the female members pick?
- What's this?
What could this be?
I hear that...
- Yes?
- Jong Kook...
is still chatting with In Ah.
- Oh, really?
- Even now?
That's strange.
- They're having a date.
- I know, right?
Do you work out every day?
I do. I don't take breaks.
Not even for a day.
- Why wouldn't you?
- That was his strategy?
- They're here.
- Why did you plan a strategy?
- What do you mean?
- Jong Kook,
everyone is talking about you here.
- What?
- What happened?
- I hear you two had a date.
- That's not true.
- You had a date?
- Why would you take so long?
- We talked about working out.
- You seem much happier now.
Not at all.
You look much happier
than before the meal.
- No, no.
- He seems brighter.
- Did something happen?
- That's not it.
- You guys must've clicked.
We talked about working out.
Because it was fun,
- They have something in common.
- so that relieved my stress.
Actually, there's someone...
who went to see a partner
for his life.
- What do you mean?
- Who?
- Se Chan.
- Man Three.
Oh, Se Chan?
That's not true.
- Man One.
- What are you? Man Three.
- Man 3 kept talking about...
- Man 1.
- You don't have to bring it up.
- How did it go?
- It's over.
- Why?
- It failed.
- You two don't get along?
- Not at all.
- They're not compatible.
I've never met anyone who does
horseback riding as a hobby.
So I couldn't go on.
- Is it really your hobby?
- Yes.
We have nothing in common.
- So it's over.
- Horseback riding?
- It's over.
- Does she enjoy horseback riding?
She enjoys horseback riding.
We tried to find something
we have in common,
- but there were none.
- So...
I gave up.
- You enjoy horseback riding.
- Yes.
- Is it your hobby?
In Ah, why did you have such
a long conversation with Jong Kook?
- How did you know?
- I guess there was a connection.
- Is it true?
- Look behind her cap.
- His tag is attached to her cap.
His tag is attached to her cap.
(It's the name tag of the man
she had a date with.)
That's too much.
I forgot about it.
(The name tag discourages
other male members.)
Hold on.
- In the beginning...
- We will go home.
- This is ridiculous.
- She is out of her mind.
Gosh. It happened in the beginning.
It happened in the beginning.
What are we supposed to do
if she makes her choice so obvious?
In Ah, you are too much.
What is up with the two of you?
(She takes out Man 3's name tag
she had in her pocket.)
It's a diversion tactic.
- I feel bad for Man Three.
- Seriously.
- Man Three is being used.
- Is it me again?
I am being used.
So Min, were you meeting up...
- with your uncle? Who was it?
- Yes.
I had lunch with my father.
- So Min.
- Yes?
Everyone was impressed...
by your filial piety.
You are such a filial woman.
The word has spread.
To be honest,
she called me with desperation.
You know that I am soft-hearted.
Don't lie. It was for points.
- Be quiet.
- It was for points.
Did she give him points?
- I will announce the points.
- Okay.
Among women,
only Cho Hee received two points.
The rest received one point each.
(The rest received 1 point each.)
The men's points...
will be revealed after the mission.
It's a game that tests your tenacity
for a partner,
Roll Around in Rhythm.
(Roll Around in Rhythm)
- Roll around?
- What is this game?
It will be a 1-on-1 match
between the members of the same sex.
Two members...
will lie down
at the end of the blanket and start.
They will wrap themselves up
and roll around.
- While hugging each other?
- As you can see,
there are yellow sirens...
- and blue sirens.
- That's right.
You will pick a color in advance.
The longer your siren goes off,
the more points you will win.
If the section has your siren,
you have to try staying there.
(If you make your siren
go off longer, you win.)
If the section has
the opponent's siren,
- you have to try moving along.
- Isn't the result too obvious?
- Okay, okay.
You know,
if we play this game
against Jong Kook,
- we won't win any points.
- This is insane.
This is ridiculous.
The last sirens...
are worth twice the time.
(The last sirens
are worth twice the time.)
Each round will go on
for two minutes.
The women will have a draw.
As for the men, we came up
with the list of matches.
- Good job.
- Did you come up with it?
A match against Kwang Soo
is bound to turn dirty.
It's unbelievable
from the first round.
(Roud 1, Man 5 versus Man 6)
This is embarrassing.
Seriously.
Even though he is a man...
Isn't it strange
to find it embarrassing?
This is embarrassing.
Come on!
- Come on!
- What?
Why is he overreacting?
- He is overreacting.
- It's just a game.
Hey.
All right.
- Suk Jin, your color is yellow.
- Okay.
Let's begin.
- Get ready.
- Okay.
- If you start from the top...
(Suk Jin needs to make
the yellow sirens go off...)
(and Haha needs to make
the blue sirens go off.)
Set, go.
You need to try staying there.
- Hold on.
- You need to roll over first.
- First...
- Yellow is Suk Jin's color.
- Suk Jin should stay there.
- He should stay there.
What's my color?
Yellow is Suk Jin's color.
(I see a blue siren!)
(Haha attempts
to make his siren go off.)
Stay there.
(Suk Jin 1, Haha 0)
(He pressed it!)
Suk Jin, you need to go past
that section.
- You need to go past it.
- Hurry up.
- It's game over.
Suk Jin's head
went inside the blanket.
It's game over.
Hurry up.
Suk Jin, try to stay
in the next section.
Hey!
(Haha earns over 10 points.)
Suk Jin, you need to roll over.
You need to roll over.
(Everyone roots for Old Man 5.)
(Their messages reach him.)
Time passes fast.
(Old Man 5 begins to use
his energy.)
They stayed in that section
for a long time.
Hold on.
They stayed in that section
for too long.
(It's hard for him
to move past the blue siren.)
(Shouting)
- Stop.
- Suk Jin is getting up.
Wake up, Suk Jin!
Suk Jin!
(After drawing ragged breaths,
the old man stops moving.)
Wake up, Suk Jin!
Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin!
- Wake up!
- Breathe!
Don't fall asleep!
Bring a stretcher!
Please save Suk Jin!
Ambulance!
Open your eyes!
Suk Jin, open your eyes!
Please save Suk Jin!
This match is over.
(The production crew
hurriedly ends the match!)
- You never know.
- He fought well.
- All right.
Suk Jin still has it.
Suk Jin.
- All right.
- Suk Jin still has it.
Here is the result of the match.
- Haha won.
- Okay.
Still...
It was too bad...
that I couldn't move my hands
in the blanket.
Kwang Soo's color is yellow...
and Jae Suk's color is blue.
All right. Set, go.
(The match begins.)
- Hold on.
- Kwang Soo's color is yellow.
(He attacks Kwang Soo's temple
with his front teeth.)
(He plays dirty right away
and makes the yellow siren go off.)
(By the way,)
(yellow is Kwang Soo's color.)
That's Kwang Soo's.
Is that Kwang Soo's?
(Kwang Soo gets over 10 points.)
That's Kwang Soo's.
(Jae Suk was so nervous
that he forgot his color.)
Jae Suk, roll over.
(He realizes it belatedly,
but he is caught.)
Kwang Soo.
Don't kiss!
Kwang Soo's eyes went crazy.
Those are Kwang Soo's eyes.
Kwang Soo's eyes.
The variety show eyes.
- The variety show eyes.
- Hey.
Hey.
(Those eyes come out
when Kwang Soo loves the mission!)
He looks scary.
(At that moment)
(My goodness.)
(He makes the siren go off
with his head.)
Jae Suk can't beat that.
Your tactic isn't working.
(Jae Suk continues to attack
with his protruding front teeth!)
(They thought
the match would end that way.)
(In that case)
(He loses his charms.)
How are the next players
supposed to use it?
The match is over.
My goodness.
That was unbelievable.
I don't want to play this game.
- That was hilarious.
- I am dying.
(It will be hard for Man 2
to get chosen by women.)
My goodness.
(They are in tatters
when Round 2 ends.)
Se Chan, just lie down comfortably.
Se Chan, are you okay?
Already...
Jong Kook's color is yellow
and Se Chan's color is blue.
You never know
what will happen, Se Chan.
Set, go.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- They are rolling over slowly.
- Make it go off.
- This is...
- They are rolling over slowly.
- Whose siren is it?
- Jong Kook's color is yellow.
- Yellow.
- That's Jong Kook's siren.
That's his siren.
Isn't it game over?
Hold on.
(What?)
He can't move.
Jong Kook, go to the siren
that is worth twice the time.
Isn't it game over?
- I can't move.
- Come on.
Try to roll over.
1, 2, 3.
(No matter how hard he tries,
Jong Kook is like a boulder.)
1, 2, 3.
(The invincible latissimus dorsi)
My goodness.
Just stay on your back!
(Just stay on your back!)
That's nice of him.
(His pink gums continue to dry up.)
1, 2, 3.
Just end the match.
The match is over.
- Okay.
- That was too pitiful to watch.
As for women,
you will have a draw.
If you pick number five,
you can pick a member
from number 1 through 4.
Cho Hee, pick a member.
I will pick at the end.
It does feel strange.
You would think...
that they would play quietly,
but that simply isn't true.
Let's begin.
They have the fighting spirit.
- They have the fighting spirit.
- You got a glimpse of it earlier.
In Ah's color is yellow.
- Really?
- In Ah's color is yellow.
Get ready.
Set, go.
In Ah's color is yellow.
(In Ah's color is yellow.)
She is holding out.
(In Ah grits her teeth
and stays in the section.)
That's good.
(He In rolls over.)
She is holding out.
(In Ah can't beat
the horseback riding enthusiast.)
- She is good.
- In Ah can't roll over.
In Ah, spread your legs a bit
before you roll over.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
When Cho Hee picks a member later...
- I won't pick either one of them.
- Seriously.
- Don't do that.
Ten seconds.
(Woman 3 and Woman 4 are serious
about Variety Village.)
The match is over.
I have no idea who won.
- It was neck-and-neck.
- You need to roll back.
Are you okay?
He In got 33 seconds.
In Ah got 64 seconds.
She is good.
(In Ah wins and receives 3 points.)
Ji Hyo versus So Min?
- So Min is like a paper doll.
- A paper doll.
So Min will need...
to play another game.
- I am sorry.
- She is most likely to get chosen.
- Seriously.
I know that So Min is a paper doll.
I need to preserve my energy...
since I have two games to play.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo)
Ji Hyo is relaxed.
I will lie down here.
Do you know what she said?
She is sleepy.
Ji Hyo is relaxed.
(Hugging)
Hey, why are you hugging me
so tightly?
Hey!
Ji Hyo hates being tickled.
So Min's color is yellow...
and Ji Hyo's color is blue.
Let's begin.
Roll over.
So Min.
Stop it.
So Min's color is yellow.
- Hey.
- So Min.
(So Min is holding out.)
She is holding out.
What?
Ji Hyo, you need to reach
the blue siren.
(Kissing)
She keeps kissing me!
Of course,
So Min plays dirty.
(Kissing)
(It's a big mess.)
Hey!
(Ji Hyo falters
because of So Min's kissing attack.)
Will she win with that tactic?
(The habitual kisser
rules the game.)
(But Ji Hyo is known to be
a delinquent.)
(She rolls over.)
- It's done.
- It's over.
- Look at me.
(You aren't the only one
who can kiss, okay?)
So Min, I need to play another game.
(The habitual kisser used up
her strength.)
It's over.
The match is over.
(Ji Hyo won.)
I wonder if So Min will play dirty
this time as well.
Will I need to kiss Cho Hee as well?
(She feels awkward about
kissing someone she just met.)
- We just met.
- Go ahead.
- This is a variety show.
- I am embarrassed...
about hugging her.
Should I lie down like this?
How should we do this?
(What is So Min doing?)
This is a bit awkward.
- I don't know what to do.
- So Min.
Hey.
- This is a variety show.
- Do it for a partner.
We aren't that close yet.
Get ready. Set, go.
(The first yellow siren
belongs to So Min.)
Heave-ho.
So Min.
What is this?
- Where are you? Where are you?
- She preserved her energy.
Stay still.
- Stay still.
- She looks really strong right now.
What?
- So Min.
- What is going on?
(So Min is like Jong Kook
against Cho Hee.)
So Min is like Jong Kook.
(The weakest member on the show
is pretending to be strong.)
- No!
- Stay still!
(It's payback time.)
Stay still.
- You did it.
- This is incredible.
That's funny.
(Kissing)
(Cho Hee suddenly attacks
with kisses.)
(Cho Hee benchmarked
So Min's tactic.)
No!
(Thrashing)
I knew that would happen.
(Kissing)
(The match is embarrassing
to watch.)
(Cho Hee holds So Min down.)
- Cho Hee.
- She is incredible.
(Woman 5's wits move
the male members.)
Cho Hee is dominating.
She is pressing hard.
(So Min kicks in happiness.)
The match is over.
(Cho Hee had
an overwhelming victory.)
Okay.
They became physically affectionate
on the day they met.
Before the last decision,
you will choose the dessert.
- The dessert.
I will first reveal the points
the male members received...
from the female members.
- Man One, Yoo Jae Suk has...
- Okay.
(Man 1 had lunch with Woman 1.)
(Man 1)
(Ji Hyo picked Jae Suk!)
(That means he has 1 point
at the very least.)
I should have one point.
A total of two points.
Really?
(2 points)
- Really?
- What?
- 2 points?
(At least one woman didn't give
a point to the man who visited her.)
- Did Cho Hee give him a point?
- Who did it?
Maybe they are from two women
other than Ji Hyo.
Who gave me a point?
- Why?
- I gave you a point.
Why give a point
to someone who didn't visit?
What charms does Man One have?
Why did someone give me a point?
The next one is Man Two, Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo has...
(As for Man 2,)
(he went to Cho Hee first
and showed off his charms.)
Kwang Soo has...
zero points.
(But he got 0 points.)
(Cho Hee doesn't like
sly-looking eyes.)
- How could you do that?
- She deserted him.
(The squid explodes!)
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Why did you go to her?
- I got it now.
Now, Jong Kook has...
One point.
A total of one point.
Of course.
- It's from In Ah.
- Is it from In Ah?
(The trainer's 1 point came from...)
(In Ah, as everyone expected.)
(Thankful for In Ah's choice,)
(he shows his snakelike eyes.)
They are exchanging looks.
- Now,
- I didn't expect that.
the remaining ones are
Se Chan, Suk Jin, and Haha.
- What is it?
- Do we have the same score?
- They got grouped together.
- Why?
Between the three of you,
2 got 0 points and 1 got 3 points.
- What?
- Three points?
- 3 points?
- Did someone get 3 points?
(3 points from the women
went to 1 man.)
- 3 points?
- Did someone get 3 points?
Three points?
Should I get excited about this?
Of course.
The charming man of Variety Village
who stole three women's hearts.
Among Se Chan, Suk Jin, and Haha,
the one who got three points is...
- Is it Haha?
- The one who got three points is...
(The surprising winner
will be revealed next week.)
(The women choose the person
they will have dessert with.)
(The men have to wait...)
(and the women have to choose.)
(The competition for survival turns
even more desperate.)
(As they change their minds,
emotions surge.)
(The Final Poll comes.)
I believe in you.
(What kind of twist
will the Final Poll reveal?)
(With the romance of the past,)
(8 free-spirited university students
with unique charms are coming!)
(The Entering Class of 1991
Is Back!)