Last week, in Variety Village...
(11 entertainers came
to Variety Village last week.)
I'm working in the IT industry.
(Man 1 runs a video arcade.)
Man six.
(Hi.)
(Man 6 made everyone have
convulsions from the beginning.)
(I like you.)
(The men were like
a pathetic rabble.)
(Women 1 and 2 bluffed
to get the men's attention.)
Why?
(In Ah is the owner
of a tanning ship.)
(She even hit
on the fitness trainer.)
(He In said she runs a flower shop
that she's always wanted.)
(Unusual for rookie entertainers,
they all are good at skits.)
(Cho Hee said she was a realtor
to look rich.)
(The guests of Variety Village go
more overboard than the members.)
(Only funny people can survive
in Variety Village.)
(Today's race
with the 11 entertainers)
At the end, you'll vote for the one
you want to pair up with.
The partners who chose each other
will not get any penalty.
Those who failed to pair up
with anyone...
will receive a penalty
regardless of the number of them.
If you get more than one vote,
you will receive gold as a prize...
regardless of whether you paired up
with someone or not.
(If they get more than one vote,
they will receive gold as a prize.)
(The points they get after missions
will be helpful at the voting.)
(That's how the romantic war
in Variety Village began.)
To be honest,
I'm quite fond of Man Three.
(Before lunch, Se Chan was
the most popular one.)
(But Se Chan wants to know
more about Woman 4, He In.)
Could you guys help me
just this once?
(The other men promised
that they would support him.)
Thanks.
(That's how he spent
some alone time with her.)
- I really like it.
- Thank you.
(He tries to continue
the conversation.)
(He In lives in Cheongdam-dong,
enjoys dancing, and rides horses.)
(I don't think we make
a good couple.)
(He gave up on her
only 10 minutes after the lunch.)
(And Woman 3 and Man 4 are
getting more intimate.)
(And a few men and women had
lunch together just for business.)
(Cho Hee was the only one
to be chosen by two men.)
(Now the women need to decide
whom they'll give their points to.)
(Cho Hee has
two votes in her hands.)
(And two men beg her for a vote.)
And that's Cho Hee.
(And the two men say
obvious lies to her.)
(What's her choice?)
(The result is announced.)
(The women got...)
(as many points
as the number of their partners.)
(Jae Suk got 2 points.)
Now, Jong Kook has...
(Jong Kook got 1 point.)
(See?)
(And Man 2 got...)
(They became intimate
during lunchtime.)
(But he got 0 points.)
- Zero points.
- Hey!
(Woman 5 voted
based on her own beliefs.)
(Man 2 finally revealed
her pathetic true colors.)
(He declared war
pointing his finger at her.)
Okay.
(After announcing the points
of Men 1, 2, and 4,)
(what remains is Se Chan,
Suk Jin, and Haha.)
(Why are we grouped together?)
(Among them, only 1 member
got 3 points.)
(One of them swept
all the remaining points.)
(Should I get excited about this?)
(He's feeling excited already.)
(The news about 3 points...)
(shock the women as well.)
The one who got three points is...
(Who got 3 points after
having lunch with the women?)
Yang Se Chan.
(Man 3, Yang Se Chan)
- I knew it.
- What's going on?
(Woman 5's points
were sent to someone else.)
What happened?
You're a liar.
(You should've given me the points.)
- Get out!
- Why?
He got all the points.
You said I didn't have
to give you points.
(Man 6 feels disappointed
and furious.)
I was a little surprised.
I guess Cho Hee tried
to play a joke on me.
That's what I think.
(Man 6 is flustered.)
I should've gone
to this innocent woman.
- At the last moment...
- How could you...
- Suk Jin.
- What makes me so attractive?
- What's so great about me?
- You said you'd give me your point.
Cho Hee had two points,
so it's from Cho Hee.
Cho Hee gave you two points.
My heart is pounding.
What should I do?
- Se Chan is popular.
- I'm serious.
It's beating hard.
I feel excited.
What makes me so attractive?
(Laughing)
It feels great.
My gosh. Why is this
happening to me?
They all have their own charms.
Se Chan is popular.
That means So Min gave
her points to Jae Suk.
She didn't give me her point.
Not you. I meant Jae Suk.
(Not you.)
(I meant she gave it to Jae Suk.)
My gosh. I wasn't talking about you.
I meant Jae Suk.
You got zero points.
- Gosh, you're...
- Pull yourself together.
I meant Jae Suk, not you.
So Min, how could you...
I got fooled again. I'm so upset.
I feel really betrayed.
This is frustrating.
- Cho Hee had two points.
- He In gave me her point.
Cho Hee gave you two points.
(A few minutes earlier,
during lunchtime...)
(While Man 2 and 6 were trying
hard to get 2 points...)
(Cho Hee.)
(You know you don't have to
pick one of them, right?)
(I should find my variety partner.)
(She gave 2 points to Man 3
with her sincere heart.)
(Woman 4 who had lunch
with Man 3...)
(gave him 1 point as well.)
(Meanwhile, Woman 2 who had
lunch with Man 5...)
All the women gave...
their points to only one man each.
- Good.
- All right.
Before the final voting,
you will choose the last dessert.
- Dessert?
- Gosh, dessert?
This time, the men will...
take their dessert and scatter.
I see.
Then the women will pick up
the drinks for their partners...
and go to the person they want
with the drinks.
The rules remain the same.
- Okay.
- Good.
All right.
(Now it's the women's turn
to make up their minds.)
Now it's the women's turn
to make up their minds.
Where are you going?
Wait. This is...
If my partner doesn't vote for me,
I can't win the race?
- Right. You'll get a penalty.
- I see.
If you get many votes,
you can get a prize though.
So I have to be a couple.
We should plan this together.
I'll go to Jong Kook then. Man Four.
You just told us
about it to say that, right?
(She beat around the bush
to get to her point.)
I want a partner who is athletic...
and passionate just like me.
So I think In Ah would be
my perfect partner.
What about you?
I'm still thinking.
- Pick Jae Suk.
- Gosh.
We already had lunch together.
I don't want to eat dessert too.
You need another partner
to eat dessert with?
(Woman 1 wants to pick
someone else for her dessert.)
I have only one goal today.
I'll stick to Ji Hyo.
I don't want anyone else.
Why did you give your points
to Se Chan, by the way?
Because I picked Se Chan
for the First Impression Poll.
- I see.
- So I just...
I think you might have to date him
for real after this show.
- He's serious about this.
- Really?
I see. That's not
what I want though.
Se Chan got the wrong idea.
That's not what I want at all.
I don't know why Cho Hee did that.
She also picked me
for the First Impression Poll.
Why did she pick me?
(She also picked me for the First
Impression Poll. Why is that?)
And Haha said silly things to me.
I wonder if she's interested in me.
I feel excited.
(Do you have any advice
for Man 2 who got 0 points?)
This is not advice though.
He tries so hard to give off
his charms when he doesn't have any.
That's the problem.
He should know what he's doing.
Right? I mean... Look.
You're being so condescending.
You're being ridiculous.
Why are you eavesdropping
on my interview?
You were saying stuff
like confidence and charms.
You should think...
about how you'll get drunk
alone at home later tonight.
(He will drink alone and go to sleep
as soon as he leaves the village.)
- This isn't a real situation.
- I guess you're right.
The annex?
(Woman 5 is about
to make her choice.)
(She heads to the building
where Man 2 and Man 3 are in.)
Cho Hee, hello.
(She heads to the building
where Man 2 and Man 3 are in.)
Cho Hee.
Just remember what I did earlier.
- Right. You came to me earlier.
- I know.
- I didn't even hesitate.
- We had a great time together.
Sure. Like I said earlier,
I'm fine that you didn't
give me your points.
- Really?
- Sure.
- Do you really not care about that?
- No.
- Okay. I got it.
- I'm relieved to hear that.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yes.
- I see.
- I want to take a walk around.
What? Are you on your way
to somewhere else?
It's not that you came here
to see me.
- But you said...
- Yes.
you don't mind
about the points at all.
It's not that
I don't mind it at all.
Gosh.
It's not like
I'm completely fine with it.
Woman Five takes off in a hurry.
(Woman 5 takes off.)
Woman Five chose Man Three.
Aren't you going
to come out and greet me?
Oh, dear. Sure.
- Come on out to greet me.
- Sure.
- Welcome.
- All right.
- I'm here.
- I see.
Have you made up your mind?
- Do you want me to leave?
- Gosh, no. I'm honored.
I hope he will eat his cake alone...
shivering with cold there.
- It's cold outside.
- It's cold.
Come on in.
I have a question.
Why did you give me
your two points? It was you, right?
How should I put it?
I'm a woman with a sincere heart.
It's my single-hearted devotion.
(Single-hearted devotion?)
- Are you serious?
- Yes. That's who I am.
You made a good first impression.
- My first impression?
- Yes.
You gave me a good first impression.
I'm extremely satisfied.
And now I know...
why Woman Five...
chose me.
So I'll give
my single-hearted devotion...
only to her.
(Who's your least favorite member?)
Woman Five.
She's the worst.
We had lunch together.
That's when I realized it.
Her face...
looks so greedy.
She looks so grumpy.
She has such eyes.
Are you saying that
because she didn't pick you?
No. Not at all.
Like I said, I don't mind
even if she doesn't pick me.
But she keeps...
getting on my nerves.
I don't know.
(Man 2 is pretty upset
after he got rejected.)
Gosh, it's not easy to choose.
(While Man 2 is throwing tantrums,
Woman 4 looks for her partner.)
It's hard.
And it's hard to get picked.
(Laughing)
Gosh, are you here to greet me?
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
(He pretends it is a coincidence
with his contrived pose.)
So have you made up your mind?
- I'm still thinking.
- I see.
It's not...
that I'm trying to convince you,
but during...
the private interview earlier,
I said I would choose Woman Four.
- I see.
- No pressure.
Okay. Let me...
go on my way then.
(Passing by)
(Laughing)
(The horseback riding lover
passes him by like a horse.)
Hang on. Where am I?
(The horseback riding lover
passes him by like a horse.)
He In.
What's your drink?
- I have Iced Americanos.
- Iced Americanos?
- I have something here.
- You do?
I have carrot cake.
Do you have carrot cake?
I used to...
- enjoy horseback riding too.
- You did?
(The sound of horse's hooves)
(Man 6 tries to win her over
with some cheap tricks.)
Just kidding.
(Just kidding.)
It's up to you.
(He speaks
all the English words he knows.)
(After watching
Haha's cheap tricks,)
(she approaches Man 2
who still pretends to be gentle.)
I'm not going to act pathetic.
Okay. Do you mind if I sit here?
(Shouting)
Thank you.
It's so cold out here.
Are you all right?
- I'm fine. Please have a seat.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Korean variety shows are strange.
(Korean variety shows are strange.)
I can't get used to them.
Se Chan told me...
- that you like horseback riding.
- I do.
I came here on horseback today.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's how much...
(He makes up some lies about horses
to have a chat with her.)
I like horseback riding.
- All the way here to Yangpyeong?
- Yes.
I love horseback riding.
But riding a horse on the streets...
is against the law in Korea.
No. I took routes... I mean,
- I crossed mountains.
- Mountains?
You did?
(Man 4 becomes an eccentric guy
who crosses mountains on a horse.)
Next up is Woman Three.
It's here.
Our eyes just met.
(Man 4 found Woman 3
from a distance.)
In Ah.
Artist, baby
Actually, In Ah picked me at first.
If Woman Three picks someone else,
I'll be done for.
I'll...
choose my partner
without hesitation.
I won't even show my face
to the other men.
Here I go.
Mr. Trainer!
- In Ah. Don't hesitate.
- My fitness teacher.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Good. I didn't even
look at the other women.
Thank you.
She runs toward him.
- She's not funny at all, right?
- Yes.
Woman Three's choice...
disappointed Men 5 and 6.
Can you call this a variety show?
- It's no fun.
- This is so boring.
Actually, I like...
your style and mindset.
(Me?)
Me?
- I like you too.
- I'm serious.
Shall we eat together?
If we end up alone,
shall we eat together?
- Deal.
- Okay.
All right. Let's eat together.
I had a lot of fun
in the blanket earlier.
(They felt warm camaraderie
in the blanket during the mission.)
Next up is Woman Two.
(Next up is Woman 2.)
- Is that So Min?
- The weird one is here.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
(Woman 2 with
unpredictable charm shows up.)
- Beautiful day.
- The sky is high.
It's a beautiful day.
So Min, I'll give you
my point no matter what.
Suk Jin.
- Hello.
- I mean...
(She tells him to trust her
with her eyes.)
If you leave now,
I won't believe you.
- Thank you.
- This is...
where I sat earlier.
Okay.
Are you sitting there?
- Are you going to sit there?
- Woman 2 chose Man 6.
- Thank you.
- Yes!
- Are you sitting down?
Hey!
Lastly, Woman One...
is meeting with Man One.
Ji Hyo.
- Hello.
- I was waiting for you.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Did you see me sitting here?
- I didn't even go out.
- Are you serious?
Man One says
he didn't even go out...
waiting for Woman One.
He In!
In Ah!
I'm right here. Where are you going?
Can I ask you for directions?
Why don't you come in
and have some tea?
I can't.
Just go.
After getting rejected four times,
Man One is feeling anxious.
Where are you going, Ji Hyo?
- I want to take a look around.
- What?
I just came to say hi.
- I wanted to thank you for lunch.
- Ji Hyo.
- You don't have to say hi.
- I'm here to say hi.
My gosh, Ji Hyo.
I really like it.
Oh, hi.
Hi, Miss...
Song.
This is my friend.
Hi.
- All right.
- I'm happy to be with my friend.
- Are you sitting there?
- Well...
Hey. Hey!
Gosh.
I can't believe you guys.
(Outraged)
The women are done
making their choices.
All they have left is
the final points and the poll.
Is Jae Suk alone?
(The men get as many points
as the number of their partners.)
The men can give points...
to the women they like.
Man Two.
You got chosen by one woman,
- so you get one point.
- Okay.
Man Four...
chose Woman Three who came to him.
Gosh, this is...
And the other men...
also chose the women
who came to them.
(Lee Cho Hee)
Then give me your points.
(Haha has 2 partners,
so he can give 2 points.)
- Haha.
- Yes?
I don't have many points.
I know that.
Man Six seems...
to have chosen one
between Women 1 and 2.
Are you announcing the results here?
- Yes. Here.
- Why would you do that?
It makes us uncomfortable.
Why would you do it here?
Woman One...
got two points.
(Woman 1 got 2 points.)
Meanwhile, Woman 2 got 0 points.
(And Woman 2
obviously got 0 points.)
(She finds out where the 2 points
went right on the spot.)
(Haha gave Ji Hyo 2 points
with very small letters.)
Gosh, don't act like a bully.
So Min, calm down.
I'm so upset.
- Relax.
- I'm so mad.
- Calm down.
Oh my goodness.
(The dessert time is over
with rage and betrayal.)
Why are you acting
like a little kid?
Now this is the final poll
for Perfect Partner Signal.
You can talk to other members
for 20 minutes.
And the final voting will begin
in 20 minutes.
Those who are matched
with their partners...
will be exempt from the penalty.
And you have collected your points.
You can buy an extra vote
with four points,
and give up your right to vote
with five points.
If you have an extra vote,
you can vote for different partners
to increase the chances of a match.
You won't get a penalty,
but you can't win a prize either.
(If they give up the vote,
they don't get a penalty or prize.)
That's not good.
But you will have to...
draw lots.
If you want to buy an extra vote,
you will have to choose
between a vote and a dud.
And it's the same for the right
to give up the vote.
So it's a 50-50 chance.
If you're matched with your partner,
you don't get a penalty.
All those who fail to find a match
will get a penalty.
If you get more than one vote,
you'll get gold.
All right then. You have...
- many points now.
- I have the most points.
So you should buy an extra vote...
and vote for a man
who's likely to get a penalty.
And you should tell him about that.
Suk Jin must be afraid...
that he would get a penalty.
So he'd want to make a deal.
You can go to him
and make a deal with him.
- Pick one.
- I should do that.
Then make a deal with Suk Jin.
Now they get to show off...
their charm for 20 minutes.
- I'm really disappointed today.
- With whom?
- In terms of variety.
- Why?
In terms of variety?
Because Jong Jook
chose you for lunch.
Then you should've gone
to someone else for dessert.
But you chose Jong Kook.
That's why I'm so disappointed.
That's what I said earlier.
- You don't have to come to me.
- I get it.
No one chose you.
It's not like that.
He's just jealous now.
- No one came to me.
- So he's upset.
Hey.
- Now...
- Yes?
He's upset because no one
went to him for dessert.
- He's throwing a tantrum.
- It's not like that.
- He says he's disappointed.
- He's just sulky.
I got really disappointed
in Variety Village.
- Why are you upset?
- In Ah.
I didn't know you'd be so boring.
You should focus on your drama.
What is he saying?
- I'm so disappointed in you.
- Stop it.
He can't spoil the mood like that...
just because no one chose him.
It wasn't appropriate.
I'm pretty sure that Suk Jin will
receive a penalty.
It's over.
- Really.
- Did you go to the drawing room?
- No. Can we go there now?
- Will you...
Of course, we can.
I can assure you one thing.
Kwang Soo won't choose you.
- He won't...
- Hang on a second.
- I didn't know you were here.
- Hey, mister.
- He won't...
- Hang on a second.
(I can't believe you.)
- I'm sorry.
- You know...
- I didn't see you there.
- I know you're impatient, but...
- Was he there all along?
- Suk Jin is right about that.
- I'm so disappointed.
- I can assure you...
- I won't pick anyone else.
- I'm telling you how to survive...
in this wild jungle.
- That's all I'm saying.
- I have no reason to do that.
- I understand.
- No one else will pick me either.
I didn't see you there. I'm sorry.
I'm going to approach He In again.
I think I should win her over...
so that I can
at least receive gold...
even if I fail to pair up
with anyone.
(Man 3 is planning to
reconnect with her.)
- This may sound stupid.
- Okay.
I'm going to learn horse riding
starting next week.
- Are you serious?
- Yes. I know it sounds silly,
- but I'll start next week.
- Really?
Yes. I didn't say it to impress you.
I really want to learn it.
Let's ride together some time.
- Sounds great.
- Man Three.
You seem to be wary
and jealous of me.
- This is so funny.
- What's the reason?
- What is this about?
- I mean...
- We were having a nice chat.
- Don't you own a lot of stocks?
Yes, I do. I think she and I have
a lot in common.
It seems to me that you have been...
caught up in an idea
since the beginning of the show.
That you're actually a rich man
who owns a lot of stocks,
that you can do anything you want
like horse riding and everything,
and that you're very popular
with women. You've been into it...
- That's not true.
- since you got three votes.
- The look on his face has changed.
- That's funny.
(The look on his face changed
after he got three votes.)
Listen, Kwang Soo.
I'll choose Woman Four,
and nothing can change my mind.
- But...
- I'll start learning horse riding.
- Will you do the same thing?
- Then... I am...
raising my own horse.
I'm raising one.
- You have a horse?
- Yes.
That's ridiculous.
Don't believe what he says.
I'm a little torn.
I'm afraid he might betray me
when I choose him.
Before I came on the show,
many people advised me...
not to trust him, if anyone else.
I need an extra vote,
so I can be relaxed.
(Meanwhile, Man 4 entered
the drawing room.)
I'll draw for an extra vote.
(He spent four points
to draw for an extra vote.)
(1 of the 2 balls in the box is
a vote and the other is a dud.)
I've made up my mind.
(He needs an extra vote to increase
the chance to pair up with someone.)
(Dud)
Dud.
(He wasted four points.)
Okay. There's a 50 percent chance,
but I'm getting even more nervous.
I have a 50-50 chance, right?
I'll take it out right away.
(Extra vote)
You got an extra vote.
(He got an extra vote.)
Oh, gosh. Seriously.
If I get to choose one more woman,
I would choose Ji Hyo...
(Meanwhile, Man 1 is leaving
after drawing for something.)
- Did you try that?
- Yes.
- Hey.
- But...
Based on his face, I think
he failed to get what he wanted.
His face turned red.
You picked a dud again?
Gosh. I'm sick of hearing that.
I can tell by his face.
(Jae Suk's lip is rolled up again.)
Man One.
(All he can do is laugh.)
- I know how you feel, Man One.
- My gosh.
- He seems very disappointed.
- I've been so unlucky today.
Ji Hyo...
might choose someone else.
I'll choose her
even though I know that.
You know what I mean, right? Yes.
- If we pair up with each other...
- Who will you choose?
- In Ah and who else?
- I'll pick no one else but you.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
You're the only one
that I'm thinking of choosing.
Ji Hyo, I'm a little disappointed.
Ji Hyo, I'm disappointed.
Don't be, Jae Suk.
I've already decided to pick you.
I said I will pick you
in the interview too.
- Really? Is that true?
- Yes. It's true.
I promise you...
- I'll pick you.
- It's a promise.
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo.
Man Six also needs Woman One's vote.
I hope you understand that.
If I don't succeed this time,
I'll be finished.
Please remember that I gave you
two points.
(He's trying to get her vote
using the points he gave her.)
- All right.
- You're my variety partner.
Should I choose Haha?
(Which 1 of them will be chosen
by Woman 1?)
Or should I choose Jae Suk
or Jong Kook?
I will choose you.
Whatever I do during the mission,
I always choose you in the end.
If we pair up with each other,
we won't get a penalty.
- That's right.
- Then should I...
- trust you for the last time?
- You should trust me.
In Ah, you have an extra vote now.
You should make a deal
with someone desperate.
Like Suk Jin.
But whenever I talk to him,
he says he doesn't want my vote,
- telling me to go shoot a drama.
- What's wrong with him?
- I'll talk to him.
- See?
- He looks so upset.
- I will...
convince him.
You go and get an extra vote.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Come over here. Gosh, seriously.
Will you get a penalty?
- I'll just get a penalty today.
- Why?
- I don't think anyone will pick me.
- You're wrong.
Why? Is there something
I don't know?
- Listen to me. In Ah...
- In Ah?
just went into the drawing room.
Listen.
- Really?
- If she gets an extra vote...
- Do I still have a chance?
- If she gets it,
she'll give me one vote...
- and give you the other one.
- I see.
- You won't get a penalty.
- That's true.
And she'll receive gold.
She'll win the race.
So she'll definitely pick you.
- Really?
- Didn't you know?
(That makes sense.)
Hello.
I'll buy two tickets
for drawing for an extra vote.
(In Ah with nine points will draw
for an extra vote twice.)
- Suk Jin.
- Why?
(Woman 2 noticed something's wrong.)
Are you really going to pick me
as you said?
Of course. I promised you earlier.
I'm just worried you might
change your mind.
Woman Two seemed so sincere
when she talked to me.
I don't know
if I should trust her or not.
You're contemplating
between So Min and In Ah, right?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Forget about her.
- I mean...
- If you give me assurance...
- Forget about So Min.
If you give me assurance,
I'll pick you.
Let's go with this plan.
I have two votes.
Of course, I'll pick you two.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's time for everyone
to cast their votes...
for their variety partners.
- Have you made up your mind?
- Yes, clearly.
I asked He In for her vote too.
If both of them choose me...
I don't know. What should I do?
(It's hard to decide
to the last moment.)
It's really hard to decide.
Should I pick Haha?
(So the 11 men and women have
cast their votes.)
Perfect Partner Signal. Finally,
the time for the announcement
of the result has come.
(It's time for the announcement
of the result.)
Is any one of you sure that you'll
pair up with the one you chose?
I should succeed no matter what.
I hope so. Please.
(Man 5 and Woman 2 exchanged
eye contact.)
So Min...
What kind of person is she?
- If Man Five trusted So Min...
- Yes.
- and risked everything...
- Come on.
- There's very little chance.
- You're wrong. You may be wrong.
- It won't happen.
- That's possible too, but...
- You may be wrong.
- I think that So Min...
- Yes.
might have given up
on her voting right.
- That's possible.
- Yes.
- Oh, right. We could do that too.
- She's crazy. She might've done it.
(She might've done it
to avoid a penalty.)
- She might've done it.
- No.
- Right?
- You'll get no penalty or prize.
(The ones who gave up on their votes
won't get a penalty or a prize.)
There's a chance that she gave up
on her vote.
That makes sense. She thought
she wouldn't get any votes.
- I saw Ji Hyo earlier...
- I trust you.
(The Exciting Love Matching Time)
- It wasn't me.
- Right.
- We decided the order.
- Yes.
We'll check
Woman Two's choice first.
- Me?
- But that's like the main event.
- It's the most interesting event.
- We'll see that first?
- Woman Two really?
- She's the 1st one?
We'll reveal the choice
that Woman Two made.
(Did Woman 2 give up on her vote...)
(or vote for Man 5?)
I'm sure she didn't vote.
- Show us.
- I'm so curious.
I'm sure she didn't vote.
Show us.
- Suk Jin, that hurts.
- What?
(Woman 2 chose Man 5.)
- What is this?
- What's going on?
(Her heart went to Man Five
whom she promised she'd pick.)
(Everyone is surprised
that So Min didn't betray him.)
- Suk Jin.
- It's hard to believe.
- He's finally smiling happily.
- I'm sorry for doubting you.
Gosh, Suk Jin.
Did you not pick me?
Let's find out.
- Let's move on.
- I can't believe he got a vote.
(Man 5 is smiling quietly.
Whom did he choose?)
I can't believe
that Suk Jin got a vote.
Next, we'll reveal the choice
that Woman One made.
- Woman One?
- I'm so curious.
- I wonder whom she voted for too.
- Ji Hyo.
- She probably picked Jae Suk.
- I'm sure she picked Jae Suk.
- I trust you.
- What do you mean you trust her?
- I guess she talked to Haha too.
We didn't just talk...
I've already decided to pick you.
(Did she pick Man 1
whom she ate lunch with?)
- It's a promise.
- Yes.
If I don't succeed this time,
I'll be finished.
(Or did she pick Man 6 who gave
her 2 points at the dessert time?)
(Or did she pick Man 4 who asked
for her vote at the last minute?)
(It's rare to see a love square
in Variety Village.)
(Whom did she choose?)
We didn't just talk...
- That's it!
- My gosh.
(It's Man Six Haha!)
- That's it!
- My gosh.
(She picked her dessert mate.)
Thank you. Wait here.
- I'm sorry. I had only one vote.
- Ji Hyo.
- I can't believe you.
- I had only one vote.
- It's shocking.
- Get ready to get wet.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
- Jae Suk, I'm really sorry.
- This is why I offered you a deal.
Next up is Man Six.
(Next, Man 6's choice
will be revealed.)
Please reveal Man Six's choice.
(If he picked Woman 1,
they'll pair up with each other.)
Please reveal Man Six's choice.
- Is it Ji Hyo?
- It's Ji Hyo.
(Woman 1 and Man 6 paired up
with each other.)
(They will not get a penalty.)
You guys won't get a penalty.
- You picked Ji Hyo, didn't you?
- Haha is safe too.
You picked Ji Hyo, didn't you?
He must have...
You should've convinced her
while eating with her.
He didn't even listen to others.
You should've impressed her...
- while eating with her.
- Sorry, Jae Suk.
I trusted you.
- What made you sure she'd pick you?
- I don't understand...
- Let's move on.
- I thought Ji Hyo was...
We'll reveal Man Five's choice.
- Me?
- He'll pair up with So Min.
(Man 5 already received
Woman Two's vote!)
- Please reveal his choice.
- I don't think he picked me.
I'm sure he picked her. Wait.
- What?
- He picked Woman Three?
(Woman 3!)
(Oh, my goodness.)
- Why?
- He picked Woman Three?
- So Min, I'm sorry.
- Suk Jin, why did you do that?
- That's unexpected.
- Why?
(The gullible Man 5 was convinced
by In Ah in the end.)
- Why?
- What happened?
So Min, I'm sorry.
- That's so unexpected.
- So Min.
- I...
- He changed his mind.
- I thought you wouldn't...
- Why did he pick Woman Three?
- Man Five, it's okay.
- Why did he pick In Ah?
- So Min, I'm really sorry.
- Exactly. He got mad at In Ah.
So Min and I promised
to pick each other.
You made a promise to her.
What do you think are the chances
she'll actually pick me?
I think there's
a zero percent chance.
- I should stay alert, right?
- Exactly.
(He said he would stay alert
because of what Jong Kook said.)
(But he was convinced
as he heard In Ah had two votes.)
I've been so loyal to you.
Everyone said that there was no way
you would pick me.
- That's what they thought.
- You made the right decision.
- Woman 1.
- Man 5.
- Come back here.
- I feel so bad.
- It wasn't like that.
- Then So Min will get a penalty.
- That was so mean.
- I mean...
- I can't believe this.
- That was so mean.
- You made the right decision.
- My gosh.
- I'm baffled right now.
- I chose the 100 percent chance.
- You did the right thing.
- Next up is Woman Three.
(In Ah's choice will be revealed!)
- Woman 3.
- Please reveal Woman 3's choice.
- I knew it.
- Exactly.
She had another vote.
(She picked Jong Kook as expected.)
(She had another vote.)
(She didn't have an extra vote.)
She didn't have an extra vote.
(What?)
In Ah, is that true?
- Really?
- Hey, how could you?
- Then why did he pick her?
- You didn't have an extra vote?
I could have gotten two more votes.
- You got bad ones?
- I got unlucky.
(Earlier on, at the drawing room,)
(she got a dud
at her first attempt.)
(She failed
at her second attempt too.)
(So she had only 1 vote.)
- I had no idea.
- What happened?
She stopped me...
when I was passing by
after promising So Min I'd pick her.
- She said she had an extra vote,
- Suk Jin.
and that I should pick someone
who would actually pick me.
Hey!
- So Min, I'm really sorry.
- Don't yell at her.
- I'm shocked.
- This is so unexpected.
- I asked you to trust me just once.
- What a twist.
I'm so sorry.
In Ah,
you're such a great entertainer.
- Right?
- I was...
- Suk Jin, I'm shocked too.
- Gosh, seriously.
- She fooled us both.
- I thought she was naive,
but she tricked me completely.
- I'm impressed.
- She's a good entertainer.
- You did well today.
- Next up is...
- Man Four.
- Me?
Please reveal Man Four's choice.
- What?
- My gosh.
- You had 2 votes?
- Yes, I had 1 extra vote.
I had an extra vote,
so I gave it to Ji Hyo.
Hey, you'll receive gold.
(Hey, you'll receive gold.)
- Oh, I'll receive gold.
- That's right.
(Ji Hyo and In Ah will receive gold
with two votes!)
- So will In Ah.
- That's right.
- In Ah will receive gold too.
- In Ah too.
Next up is Man One.
We don't even have to see that.
- Ji Hyo? I'm sure it's Ji Hyo.
- Please reveal his choice.
(Ji Hyo was his only partner
during the mission.)
Please reveal his choice.
(But Woman 1 chose someone else.)
- Okay!
- You didn't vote?
- He didn't vote?
- My gosh.
(Yoo Jae Suk gave up his vote.)
(He's the first person
to give up his vote.)
- My gosh. He didn't vote.
- Really?
(Man 1 barely saved himself!)
- My gosh. He's unbelievable.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
You got one?
Wasn't there a dud as well?
- Yes.
- But you got one?
- Yes, I did.
- Oh, wow.
- That's unbelievable.
- Okay!
(Man 1 made a decision
standing on the edge of a cliff.)
(I'll draw for abstention.)
(One is abstention right,
and the other is a dud.)
(He got the abstention right.)
- That was impressive.
- That's so cool.
- I just can't let others...
- I think he made the right choice.
- change my life.
- You're amazing.
- I feel bad for Suk Jin.
- He's having a meltdown.
- All right. Next up is...
- You did great.
(Next up is Man 2.)
Next up is Man Two.
- Man Two.
- Did he vote?
- That's right. I picked her.
- Oh, he voted.
(Unexpectedly, he chose Woman 4
as he promised!)
- He picked He In.
- He didn't give up?
I said I'd pick her
from the beginning.
Next up is Woman Four.
Please show us.
He didn't change his mind
as he usually does.
(Man 3 Yang Se Chan)
I'm sorry.
What?
(I'm sorry.)
My gosh. What's going on?
How did it happen?
- How did this happen?
- Why...
No one said I should trust you.
- Of course, she didn't pick him.
- But...
(It was a big decision
for a novice entertainer.)
(Everyone told her not to choose
Kwang Soo.)
(By the way, He In!)
(It's true about Kwang Soo.)
(He won't pick you.)
(She started to doubt him
because of his reputation.)
(She chose Se Chan who promised
he'll learn horseback riding.)
- This is ridiculous.
- You made the right decision.
She ate that darn dessert with me.
(She ate that darn dessert with me.)
- I thought we made a deal.
- Hey.
I'm sorry.
- She ate lunch with me. That's why.
- Okay.
- We ate lunch together.
- You made the right decision.
- That was so funny.
- Good.
- Just let it go.
- I feel so bad about it.
We'll reveal
Woman Five's choice first.
- What happens to me?
- Please show us.
I almost got into trouble.
(Did she pick Man 3
who showed an interest in her?)
- It's Se Chan.
- My goodness.
- That's impressive.
- He got two votes.
- I got two votes.
- Se Chan will receive gold.
Okay!
If Se Chan picked one of the women
who chose him,
she'll be exempt from the penalty.
So 1 of the 2 of them...
- will get a penalty.
- That's right.
Only one of them will get a penalty.
- Whomever Se Chan picked.
- I'm so curious.
Please reveal the choice
that Man Three made.
(Who did Man 3 Se Chan choose?)
(He had dessert with Woman 5,)
(and promised to ride a horse
with Woman 4.)
We made it.
(Woman 5 and Man 3 picked
each other.)
- I knew it.
- Why did you pick him?
- I knew they'd pick each other.
- Me too.
I knew it.
It was obvious.
(Both Kwang Soo and He In will
get a penalty.)
- He In, why did you pick him?
- What is this?
- Why did you let this happen?
- He In.
Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and In Ah will...
- receive 3.75g of gold.
- Okay!
Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, So Min,
and He In will get a penalty.
- Okay!
I mean, why...
- Thank you.
- Look at that.
Thank you.
We prepared the penalty to help
the ones who couldn't pair up...
with anyone wake up
and face the reality.
It's throwing water
and a towel with paint on it.
Oh, no. Paint?
- That's the worst penalty ever.
- That's the worst.
- This is the worst.
- How could you do that to me?
(The ones who used to be partners
will do it to each other.)
My gosh.
- That's the worst.
- Indeed.
- This is the worst part.
- Exactly.
- I'm sorry, So Min.
- Why would you rub it on her face?
Oh, no.
(The horse riding partners also
threw water on each other's faces.)
- That must hurt.
- Look at her.
- That's enough.
- That's enough. You can stop it.
- Okay!
- Thank you, everyone.
- Good job, everyone.
- Thank you.
With that,
Perfect Partner Signal ended.
(But what was waiting for them
outside of the Variety Village...)
(And...)
(The Entering Class of 1991
Is Back!)
(After major events...)
(such as the 1988 Seoul Olympics,)
(everyone was elated in 1991.)
(There had been a lot of changes
before the 21st century began.)
(The biggest change was...)
(the appearance of Generation X,
the symbol of the time.)
(We want to be free no matter what.)
They wear distressed jeans.
(Generation X refused to follow
the existing social customs,)
(and didn't worry about
what others thought about them.)
(Here come eight unique,
freewheeling college students!)
That's not all. They're not affected
by the fame of a few brands.
They don't
blindly pursue uniqueness either.
(The four leaders of Generation X
are on Running Man!)
("There's no textbook or examples
for their fashion sense.)
(They just wear whatever they want.)
(The Entering Class of 1991
Is Back!)
(This role play was inspired by
a video on "Psick University.")
(Fashion Kwang,
Entering Class of 1991)
(A young man who desires freedom)
(Cool H,
Entering Class of 1991)
(A young man
who's really into Michael Jackson)
What are you guys doing?
(What are you guys doing?)
Hey, you're here.
Hi.
Won't you say hi?
- Of course. Hello.
- Hi.
What were you two doing?
We were shopping.
(We were shopping.)
We were talking
about each other's fashion style.
Hey, come over here.
- Me?
- Yes.
Aren't you going to thank us?
For what?
You got to see something cool.
You should be thanking us.
Hey, aren't you going to thank us?
- Thank you both.
- Okay.
Give us some money.
(Give us some money.)
If you really are grateful,
give us some money.
(If you really are grateful,
give us some money.)
You look stylish today.
(You look stylish today.)
It makes me want to use
this umbrella.
Haha, you may be short, but you're
a giant when it comes to fashion.
Thank you.
You parted your hair nicely.
It's parted right in the middle.
It's disrespectful to fashion
if both of my eyes are visible.
Are you sure you're doing it right?
Honestly, I've never seen anyone
who's so tall but cute like you.
(Honestly, I've never seen anyone
who's so tall but cute like you.)
I'm so upset.
Why can't I find any white belt?
A belt? Oh, it was a belt.
I thought it was a mic.
(A belt? Oh, it was a belt.
I thought it was a mic.)
(The two young men lost track
of time talking about fashion.)
It was so hard to get this belt.
(The two young men lost track
of time talking about fashion.)
I got my hair permed.
Were you confused about the concept?
What? What do you mean by that?
All right. Shall we go now?
Let's go.
Let's draw some attention.
Wherever we walk becomes
a fashion runway.
Yes!
(The two fashion leaders left.)
This is nice.
- How nice.
- Indeed.
Where were you guys doing?
What? Oh, we...
You know, we have a dream.
- We will...
- Yes.
participate in
a college comedy contest.
- Right.
- Yesterday, I went home,
and I joked around with my mom,
and I got spanked again.
As I entered, I sang this.
- Excuse, excuse, excuse me
- Excuse me
- Are you the famous Fan Guru?
- Who can exactly tell the future?
I got a slap
in the back of my head again.
You should've danced
this diamond step dance.
- Exactly. That's essential.
- Like this.
- You can't miss it.
This is killing me, you know.
My mother just doesn't understand...
- the dream I have.
- Tell me about it.
- Unbelievable.
- Gosh.
Who are those guys over there?
Who are they?
- Hey, you.
- Who are those guys?
Check out that guy.
Is he trying to be Michael Jackson?
I'm impressed.
They both look great.
Only a nutjob
would dress like that for no reason.
- He looks great though.
- Only a true nutter...
would dress like that for no reason.
He took the theme too seriously.
I hear he mistook today's theme.
How have you been?
- Jong Kook, have you been well?
- Hold on.
I'm sorry to ask this,
but did you mistake
next week's theme for this week's?
- Are you sure that's not it?
- It's a bit too much.
Beat it!
His stylist got slapped
in the restroom just now.
You're dressed for
next week's theme, right?
Why aren't you dressed
for the occasion today?
Why? This is what people wore
in the 1990s.
- Isn't this from last week?
- Of course not.
You're mistaken.
This is like the clothes
you usually wear.
What I usually wear?
Don't be mistaken.
- We're the entering class of 1991.
- You, my friend.
I'm sorry to have to say this,
but you should go home.
- It's just weird.
- What's with you today?
You got it all wrong.
Are you coming back from a funeral?
Why are you dressed this way?
Anyway, where are our minions?
- I wasn't going to say this but...
- Unbelievable.
Whenever we talk about our style,
he immediately
changes the subject...
and suggests that we move along.
Kwang Soo, let him have
something you're wearing.
Why are you dressed this way?
- Let's enjoy our trip.
- What trip?
We're all travelers, aren't we?
Just dance, why don't you?
Did you hear the news?
We won't be changing out
of our outfits today.
(It's a day without
matching team shirts.)
It'll be awkward for me all day.
Hey, Long Legs. What's your dream?
A fashion designer.
Go ahead, sir.
(Coming through)
Bye.
That was my uncle.
He's not even acknowledging us
makes it more humiliating.
Why didn't you tell me
someone one coming?
- You should've told me.
- Not even the staff said anything.
My vision on this side is impaired.
- Here.
- A fashion designer?
- You must be studying fashion.
- I see.
What about you?
- Us?
- What's your dream?
- The Campus Comedy Contest.
- That's what we'll enter.
Why you though?
Me?
Meanwhile, a comedy contest
seems fitting for you.
Watch your mouth.
- Me?
- Aren't you already a comedian?
No, I'm not.
We came up with
quite the catchphrase, you know.
Anyway, let's get going.
- You...
- We'll jump on the count of three.
1, 2, 3.
(One, two, three, jump!)
Why haven't we transported?
(That's hilarious!)
- Unbelievable.
- I love...
that we'll be in these characters
for the rest of the day.
Is this
how it should be done though?
(While the 4 unique young men
make an introduction...)
I haven't been to a place like this
in a while.
(A coffeehouse in Euljiro)
It's a first for me.
- I smell ssanghwacha.
- Exactly.
- I can smell that too.
- The scent of ssanghwacha.
Ji Hyo, you look pretty today.
Are you making fun of me?
When did I ever tease you?
Please don't punch me again.
Again?
Did you say "Again?"
Why would you say that?
Will you punch me again?
How about a ssanghwacha
with an egg yolk?
Are you supposed to pop the yolk...
or just eat the whole thing?
The yolk.
I'm not that old, you know.
I wasn't born in the 1970s.
(Her purple eyelids say otherwise.)
- You seemed to know things.
- I...
Do you swallow the yolk as is...
or pop it and swirl?
You're supposed
to eat the yolk as is?
It's bland though, so why would you?
You're here on a blind date.
A blind date?
Am I here for a laugh then?
I'll be the one they avoid.
(I'll be the one they avoid.)
Who will our blind dates be?
(Who will our blind dates be?)
I should look like a lady today.
A well-behaved lady.
I hope they don't see me
as someone odd.
Order something on the menu...
if you like one of them.
(Lemonade, Plum Juice,
Iced Coffee, Ssanghwacha...)
In my case,
if I like someone,
I'll order an iced coffee.
And if I don't like anyone,
I'll order a ssanghwacha.
I'll order...
a ssanghwacha with an egg yolk...
if I absolutely loathe the guys.
- All right.
- Right.
I'll order iced kudzu juice.
Iced kudzu juice.
Always so feeble.
Where's your energy?
Is that so?
I hear their voices.
Their voices...
(Their voices sound familiar.)
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
(Could it be...)
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
(Jae Suk, an aspiring comedian)
Hello.
Goodness. May I ask
who you guys are?
Well...
(Likewise...)
Wait.
Are you the owner?
Is she the owner?
Please have a seat.
You seem overly dressed
for the occasion.
- I...
- I'm sorry to ask this,
but what happened to your eyes?
(Sighing)
- Are they bruised?
- Of course not.
It's as if someone punched you.
- That's absurd.
- Hello.
- It's a pleasure.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- My friend here was born in 1966.
- Really?
- In 1966?
That's right. I was born in 1966.
You see, from what I can tell...
- I took some time off.
- You see,
something came up for the friend
who was supposed to be here,
and he was the only one...
who I could reach
before coming here.
- I see.
- Well,
in my case...
- He's married.
- What? No, I'm not!
What are you talking about?
- Today...
- I'm not married.
I mean it. I'm a man...
- looking for a fairy tale love.
- I see.
Anyway, you see...
This is called
a denim jacket, right?
He has zero fashion sense.
We hate it when women whisper.
- You...
- Isn't that a bit rude?
- To be honest...
- He's wearing socks with dots.
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but what's with the handkerchief?
What's with the handkerchief?
(The handkerchief
makes her seem cheesy.)
I mean...
- She's trying to be ladylike.
- This is killing me.
Unbelievable.
Is it okay to leave?
- Sit back down, will you?
- Unbelievable.
I can't take this.
Sit back down.
This is exactly the type I hate.
There's no need to ruin the mood.
- So...
- Anyway...
Are you Song Ji Hyo?
Me? Yes, that's my name.
- Right?
- Yes.
He's Ji Seok Sam.
- Seok Sam?
- Seok Sam.
Seok Sam born in 1966.
Can I call you Seok Sam, then?
No, no.
- You should call him "mister."
- Mister?
How can you call him by his name...
- when there's a huge age gap?
- Hold on.
How old are you guys? Darn it.
(To Seok Sam who wanted
to be seen as young)
What was that for?
You should be more formal
considering the age gap.
Were you born in 1970?
In 1975, actually.
In 1975?
- Then...
- 1975?
Does that make sense?
It's 1991, so that means
you're in middle school.
(That means
you're in middle school.)
Something isn't right.
Sorry about that.
I was actually born in 1965.
1965? Then you're older than me.
Gosh, I'm sorry about that.
Say you were born in 1972 or 1973.
- 1973.
- 1972 seems about right.
- 1972?
- Yes, 1972.
What do you major in?
I study food and nutrition.
- Food and nutrition?
- Yes.
(Even her major sounds cheesy now.)
What about you, Ji Hyo?
I study fashion design.
Fashion design?
You never got into college.
- Why are you whispering?
- Sorry about that.
Why are you two whispering?
- You two...
- She told me...
that I don't go to college.
I didn't mean it like that.
- Wait.
- Hold on.
Are you lying to us?
- It's not like that.
- Only So Min's in college then?
Ji Hyo, why didn't you...
Not going to college
isn't a crime, but still.
You see, she...
I'm getting ready
for the Miss Korea contest.
The Miss Korea contest?
- Really?
- Yes.
Wait.
- The Miss Korea contest?
- Contestants these days...
all seem to have
these puffy hairstyles.
Like a lion's mane. What is it?
You're bad at these sketches.
I'm a master at them.
It's not like you're any better.
You should make it seem
more natural.
- It was natural enough.
- He was always bad at these.
He was terrible at these sketches.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but why don't we order some drinks?
- Of course.
- Something to drink?
What would you like?
(A few minutes ago)
(If I like someone,
I'll order an iced coffee.)
(And if I don't like anyone,
I'll order a ssanghwacha.)
Can I have an iced coffee?
(I'll have an iced coffee.)
- An iced coffee?
- Yes.
Me too. Could I have...
an iced coffee
that's not too strong?
Could I perhaps order a parfait?
(Which of the two does she like?)
- Black coffee?
- Yes, that'd be nice.
- Both of you?
- A mild iced coffee for me.
- Same here.
- Right.
I'll have iced kudzu juice, please.
That'd be nice.
He's one to worry about
his health, you see.
You should drink
something healthier too.
So three glasses of iced coffee?
- Yes, me too.
- Don't read too much into this,
but I own a car.
I own a car.
- Unbelievable.
- I'll have an iced coffee!
- An iced coffee.
- I own a car.
With sugar, please.
- You can't...
- Coffee with sugar?
Do you perhaps know
what this bell is?
- What is it?
- What is this?
Well,
it brings you luck.
Ringing this bell...
You know what they say, right?
Have you had your first kiss?
(Have you had your first kiss?)
(They're lost for words
at her abrupt question.)
Hold on a second.
- Unbelievable.
- I can't take this anymore.
- This...
- Can you believe it?
I mean...
- You're killing me.
- Ji Hyo's...
not that cheesy,
but So Min's a bit too much.
- Hold on.
- Unbelievable.
Which character
are you playing today?
Why do you keep
holding up your handkerchief?
You'll give your nose a rash.
- Here we go.
- Here are your drinks.
Thank you, ma'am.
This is the kudzu juice.
How did you know?
I could tell by the color.
I'd love to listen to some songs
by Sunflower.
You know Sunflower, right?
Why don't you sing one yourself?
(She immediately cuts him off.)
- You want me to sing?
- You said you wanted to...
listen to a song by Sunflower,
and she responded by
telling you to sing one.
Don't you offer music
to your customers?
Sunflower.
(Even the generous owner
knows how to clear a bomb.)
He only said he wanted
to listen to their song.
"Why don't you sing one instead?"
Hilarious, right?
(Just then)
- Hello.
- Goodness, who is it?
- My gosh.
- What's going on?
What on earth?
What are you wearing?
- What's going on?
- Who are these thugs?
- What is he, Gen X?
- Look at them.
What's going on?
Look at these delinquents.
Why is he dressed
like Michael Jackson?
- Hey.
- Are you Michael Jackson?
Did you go to a funeral
or something?
(We are the 4 fashion kings.)
- My goodness.
- What is this?
- What's happening?
- Who are they?
Look at his sunglasses. My gosh.
We're here for a blind date.
Hold on. You look like my aunt.
- What? Gosh, she scared me!
- She scared me.
- You're not...
- What do you mean by aunt?
- That's not the 1990s style.
- Hey!
Why are you insulting my girlfriend?
- She's your girlfriend?
- Yes.
Wait. How dare he yell at me?
- What does he mean by aunt?
- Why are you yelling at me?
Why are you yelling at me?
- Suk Jin.
- Why are you yelling at me?
- You need a beating.
- Get up.
I'm serious.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Suk Jin.
- He's the worst at doing skits.
- Hey!
- How dare you yell at me?
- He's picking a fight with me.
He deserves a beating.
- Why would you yell?
- I'm seeing him...
- for the first time.
- I didn't yell at you.
Please make him come to his senses.
I guess the one in the yellow cap
isn't popular.
- No, that's not true.
- Oh, you mean him?
- He's not popular at all.
- You must not be popular.
She keeps hitting on me,
but I'm pushing her away.
- Then she's...
- I clearly...
She's the one who is into you?
- She blatantly chose me,
- Really?
- so she...
- Maybe she will...
stay in character
until she gets home.
- Look how tacky her clothes are.
- You're the ugliest one here.
- That's not it.
- Wake up, will you?
- She keeps hitting on me.
I'm sorry, but don't you think...
he's too into his character
all of a sudden?
- But...
- Isn't that too sudden?
This is driving me crazy!
I think he picked
the wrong character.
- That's not it.
- All of a sudden...
You must be the chief mourner.
You're the chief mourner, right?
I hate how his stomach
is sticking out.
You should say something.
- Why don't you talk?
- Say something, Michael Jackson!
He's pretending he didn't hear us.
His head is too big
compared to his body.
I love that
he's playing Michael Jackson.
What? Is he going to dance?
He's dancing out of the blue.
He's dancing out of the blue!
Beat it!
(Michael Jackson is in Euljiro!)
- He's good.
- His belly is so plump.
His belly is so plump.
(The king of pop has a plump belly.)
What's that?
- Mister!
- His belly is...
Mr. Michael Jackson!
- What's with his belly?
He keeps doing that dance.
- What's with your belly?
- Say something!
- We're supposed to be in the 1990s.
- But why...
Why did you make me
dress like this alone?
Wasn't Michael Jackson
more active in the 1980s?
So why are you dressed like this?
- Why did you make me do this?
- Why did he dress like that?
- We didn't suggest the concept.
- By the way,
you were on "Master in the House."
Why are you bringing that up?
- Out of nowhere?
- Hey.
- We're doing a skit!
- I mean...
- We're in the 1990s!
- We're doing a skit!
- Don't bring that up!
- Aren't we in the 1990s?
- What is "Master in the House?"
- I was okay with everything,
but when he was asked
how he held out...
in the entertainment industry
for so long,
he said
his positive attitude helped.
(But on Running Man,
he's the most critical member.)
That's...
(I try to find even the smallest
aspect that might be positive.)
(Master Kim lectured on the belief
that's the opposite of his life.)
- I was like...
- Wait a minute.
I was okay with everything,
- but he went on about positivity.
- Wait a minute.
You can't talk about what we've
been up to all of a sudden.
- We're in the 1990s!
- Positive attitude?
Yes! Don't you know
how positive I am?
- Positive attitude?
- I am where I am...
thanks to my positive attitude.
That was just...
Are we not sticking to our concept?
I'll take off my hat otherwise.
- No, don't.
- Don't take it off.
- You should stick to it.
It's so difficult.
Back when I was in college,
areas such as
Euljiro and Myeong-dong...
were nearby.
I've been to this area a lot.
This area is really popular
these days.
Yes, it is because it's unique.
- Metro...
- Euljiro is...
Sorry, but it's not metro.
It's retro.
It's not "metro."
I was just kidding!
- You were kidding, right?
- Of course!
- Goodness.
- He's so funny!
He's funny.
It was really funny.
I didn't know he was this ignorant.
Just stay still
if you don't know anything.
I should've restrained myself,
but I just blurted it out.
I feel the same way.
But how could he confuse it
with "metro?"
We're supposed to be in 1991.
How old were you?
Weren't you in middle school?
What did you say?
- Since it's in the 1990s...
- How old were you?
- He was 5.
- I was 5.
- I was five years old.
- I was in middle school.
- You were in middle school?
- That's as good as being an adult.
- Right.
- My heyday was in middle school.
- He looked like this.
Suk Jin was 26.
- What?
- I was...
I was discharged
from the military in 1990.
- We are almost 20 years apart.
- I was 26.
You were 26?
He was 26 years old.
In 1991,
I released a song.
- Yes, you did.
- Right?
- Wasn't that in 1992?
- So you and I...
Oh, it was when I was
recording my songs...
to make my debut.
I met him before my debut
as a singer.
- At Yong Man's place,
- Since I'm friends with Yong Man.
he played an LP album
of his friend called Ji Suk Jin.
He told me Suk Jin is making
his debut as a singer.
Yong Min wanted me
to listen to his songs with him...
as he was coming with his album.
His album?
And he actually commented
on my songs.
I did.
So I told him,
"Your songs are too listless."
- You said that?
- Do you remember?
- For real?
- I actually...
- You weren't trying to be funny?
- No, I wasn't.
The chorus wasn't as upbeat
as I thought it'd be.
- I'm not good with the chorus part.
- It wasn't impressive.
But my strong aspects...
were my voice color
and singing techniques.
Back in my days, we'd go on
blind dates in Jongno 2-ga.
Have you heard of...
- Five Cent House on Jongno 2-ga?
- No, never.
I think I've heard of it.
- Of course.
- Everything cost five cents.
Oh, right. I forgot
that Michael Jackson was with us.
Join us in our conversation!
Michael! He's very resolute.
He can't join our conversation
because of his concept.
- Hey, you are...
- "Give me some chocolate!"
- Why did you dress like this?
I was told to dress like this.
- He's not talking much.
- Why did you dress like this?
He's not talking
because he's dispirited.
I thought everyone would dress up
like pop stars, such as MC Hammer.
- MC Hammer?
- Yes.
Why did they make Haha
dress like this alone?
1991 was the heyday...
- of Michael Jackson.
- He was the best.
- Was it his heyday?
Didn't you say you went to
his concert when he came to Korea?
- It was in 1999.
- I went to his concert too.
- Oh, it was in 1999?
- It was in the Olympic Stadium.
He was in a spacecraft.
He jumped onto the stage
out of nowhere.
- He jumped onto the stage, and...
- He stood like this for a minute.
- It was longer than a minute.
- That was in Korea?
It was longer than a minute.
- He stood like this.
- Just like Haha.
- That's it!
- Isn't he Michael Jackson?
He'd stare in that direction
for 10 to 15 seconds.
It was longer than a minute.
- Then he'd turn to the other side.
- Then he turned to the other side.
I remember it now.
The crowd went crazy.
He's so ugly.
- I remember it now.
- Right? I remember it too.
- I remember it.
- Look. What's wrong with him?
- It was crazy.
- Of course.
He'd go around the stadium
on a crane.
I saw how some people
passed out during his concert.
- Yes, they did.
- Please keep quiet.
Don't you remember that?
- Stop it! Stop!
- Actually, they didn't pass out.
- They were taken to the hospital.
- No, no.
- That's enough.
- That was New Kids on the Block.
It was another concert.
When New Kids on the Block
performed in Korea,
there were many comedy shows.
- We were called Sidewalk Blocks.
- With Yong Man...
- Seung Kyung, and me.
- It was your best days.
We came up with these skits...
You know how horrible
your dance was, right?
- I mean...
- You were even off the beat.
No, I often went
in the wrong direction.
When everyone went
to their right, I went to the left.
- He was...
- Why did you do that?
- It's because...
- I was too nervous.
- I mean...
- I was so nervous.
- My gosh.
I was so nervous.
(Jae Suk in 1991,
when he was 20 years old)
(Struggling)
(He's the only one who's excited.)
(He ruined the performance
because he was nervous.)
(He became pale
as he was too nervous.)
(He suddenly became timid.)
(Then he suddenly showed
his signature dance.)
(He was left with many regrets
in his 20s.)
- I was nervous in front of cameras.
- When does it get better though?
Because of stage fright,
I was really nervous.
And I completely
forgot all the moves.
We talked so long
about our old days.
- I'm sure there's a lot to share.
- We do.
But since we're taking a trip down
memory lane to 30 years ago,
you'll be a senior
who entered college in 1991.
You're to introduce the culture
of the 1990s...
that has become popular
to your juniors, the viewers.
All right.
As we're going back to 30 years ago,
we've prepared 20 popular items
from the 1990s.
- Really?
- That sounds like fun.
If you don't collect all the items
by the end of the race,
we'll determine
who'll get the penalty...
by the number of items you missed.
(If they can't find 3 items...)
(Pencil sharpener, vintage doll,
robot puppy, comic book set)
(The ones with the lowest number of
items will get the penalty.)
(Penalty)
All right. Before we begin
the main mission,
let's play a simple game
to determine who'll get the items.
The members of the winning team
will win the items.
That means, when you go
to a certain spot,
you'll play a mission to determine
who'll get the items.
You'll only find out
after playing the mission.
(Only 2 people will be
receiving 2 gifts.)
Here are the 20 hot items
that we prepared.
- What is it?
- Let me see.
Pencil sharpener?
- Oh, so that's a map.
- It's a map.
My gosh.
I know that this is still sold.
- I have that at home.
- Right?
- What?
- It looks like a train.
- I have it.
- They still sell these.
We used to hide money
in the pencil shavings.
They still sell this.
- There's a pager.
- Look, a pager.
There's a pager.
I remember that candy.
Of course. My grandma had them too.
That's right.
Taxi drivers used to...
- keep coins in them.
- That's right.
I can't see
those candies these days.
This is the bottle
for Del Monte orange juice.
- You're right.
- The ones we can recycle.
- Yes, the orange juice.
- We kept reusing them for tea.
That's right.
We used to put barley tea
in that glass bottle.
- I know.
- It was delicious.
So today, you'll be taking...
those few items with you.
It looks so cool.
- What's happening?
- What's going on?
The phone is ringing.
(Right then,
the phone starts to ring.)
The ugliest guest of...
the entering class of 1991
got a phone call.
- He's already standing up.
- Hey.
Don't be like that.
How did you know they'd call you?
- Wait.
- He's up.
- Gosh, I'm dumbfounded.
- If it wasn't for you,
then it would've been for Se Chan.
This is how we'd call people
back when we used pagers.
The owner would call for you.
- The owner did?
- So the owner...
connected me to the person
I wanted to talk to.
My mom used to tell me
the same thing.
Hello.
Here's the first mission
to win the items.
- Okay.
- Each of you will play a quiz,
and the winning members
will get the gifts.
The challenger will listen
to the question,
and say the answer
into the receiver.
- My gosh.
- Into the receiver?
Anyway, this is
a competition, right?
Will the quiz be about the 1990s?
We don't know the answer at all.
It's related to the 1990s.
(The first question
the ugliest guy is answering)
- Hello?
- Hi.
Listen to the song being played,
and tell us its singer and title.
- This is difficult.
- Is it for Jae Suk?
- It's for Jae Suk.
- It's his question.
- I think he knows every song.
- There will be a penalty.
I think he will know.
(Tell us the title and singer
of the song.)
- Hold on.
- I know this song,
- but I can't remember.
- My heart is already beating fast.
(The prelude that makes your heart
beat fast)
Oh, I know this song.
I need to listen to it first.
(Who sang this song
and what's the title?)
(They're familiar with the melody,
but they can't remember the title.)
I can't remember this song.
Can we not hear the lyrics?
I know this song.
All right, guess the answer.
I can't guess the answer
based on this.
- It's a song from 1991.
- How can you not know this?
I'm familiar with the melody,
but I have to listen to the lyrics.
- I don't think it's a famous song.
- Me neither.
- No, it's famous.
- How come you don't know this?
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo
already know the answer.)
(What's Jae Suk's answer?)
I have no idea.
All right. Let us play the answer.
- What is it?
- We don't know this song.
It's Lee Moon Sae's song.
- Right, it's Lee Moon Sae's song.
- Yes, it's Lee Moon Sae's song.
- No, it's not his song.
- It's in his seventh album.
- It's not "Gwanghwamun Love Song."
- It was right there.
It's not "When I Stand Under
the Shade of Roadside Tree."
I'm familiar with the melody, but...
I know all of Lee Moon Sae's songs.
What's this song called?
It's "Old People."
- Are you sure?
- Isn't it "Old Love?"
- It's "Old Love."
I see, it's "Old Love."
Michael Jackson!
Don't perform right now!
- Hey!
- It's Moon Sae!
- I look like him, right?
- You look like Moon Sae.
- They're very similar.
- They look alike.
It's like Moon Sae
dressed up as Michael Jackson.
- Moon Sae is...
- It was Moon Sae's song.
- That was really close.
- Jae Suk,
lift the phone again.
- That was really close.
- He's playing again?
- It's worth trying.
- Of course.
I can't guess the title
based on the prelude.
Jae Suk, you failed. Please pass it
to the next ugliest person.
My goodness.
- Here.
- You picked me?
It's Suk Jin.
- It's not me.
- No, no.
He passed the phone to Suk Jin.
- This doesn't make any sense.
- I mean...
- Hey, you should've picked him!
- You are...
- Do you think you're handsome?
- Very much so.
- What are you talking about?
- My gosh.
Okay. Let's do this.
It's disturbing that you think
you're handsome.
(Here we go.)
I'm sorry.
I need to use the bathroom.
He's such a nuisance.
- Why can't I go?
- He's playing!
It's not like I'm going to play.
- You need to do your job.
- That's true, but...
- My gosh.
- Then do you want me to...
relieve myself here?
- Sir!
- How can you say it like that?
- I'm sorry.
- Sir.
You need to be more positive.
(Positive attitude)
Please stay.
- That's how you last long.
- That's his secret to success.
- Got it?
- Okay, I got it.
- You need to be positive, okay?
- Yes, I got it.
- Positive, positive!
- Positive!
- Okay.
- I'll get this. Watch me.
Suk Jin, listen to the sound
we're about to play carefully...
and guess the name
of the product of the ad.
- This is...
- I think it'll be easy.
You should've given me
this question.
- Play the sound.
- I don't know ads from the 1990s.
Everyone!
(The background music
sounds like a carol.)
- Everyone!
- Of course I know this!
- I got it right away.
- I know this.
(Everyone, I hope
you become prosperous.)
- I hope you become prosperous.
- Of course I know this!
You should've...
- We know this too.
- You should've given this to me.
We know this too.
- I have to name the product?
- Yes, you need to name it.
You need to tell us the brand.
You want me to tell you
the brand of this ad?
It's an ad for
a credit card company.
- This is...
- Two...
Samsung Card.
- My goodness.
- Isn't it a credit card ad?
It's an ad for a bank.
Isn't his answer close?
- I hope you become prosperous.
- It's really famous.
"I really hope so!"
I really hope so!
The company that's considerate
of your finances, BC Card.
That's right!
- It was a BC Card ad.
- I remember it now.
You should've given me
this question.
- I could've gotten this right.
- Please pass the phone...
to the next ugliest person.
- Here you go, Se Chan!
- It can't be helped.
- Jong Kook, it's you.
(Jong Kook, it's you.)
- No, it can't be Jong Kook.
- Why not?
(They try to stop Suk Jin
who seems overly excited.)
- It's okay.
- No, that's not okay.
- You need to be positive.
- You're not supposed to go next.
- You're not the next one.
- Are you not in a good mood?
- I am, since I'm positive.
- You're next.
- It's you.
- Me? Okay.
You're uglier than Jae Suk
in some sense.
Oh, really? That's fine too.
- You're okay?
- Yes, I'm very positive.
Nobody can stop him
from being positive.
- I see.
- But his face turned red.
Sit down.
I'll play this with a positive mind.
There are three people
who are uglier than me.
You see?
1, 2, 3.
That's not true.
- Come on.
- He's being ridiculous.
- It's true.
- Okay.
He said I'm being ridiculous.
Listen to the song we'll play...
and guess the title and the singer.
- Okay.
- I'm good at this kind of question.
- It's difficult.
- This song is also from 1991.
It's difficult.
Music, cue.
It suits you, Ji Hyo.
(The song is being played.)
- Tell us.
- It suits you, Ji Hyo.
(The piano melody
is being played gently.)
(I got this!)
- You know this.
- You can't tell him.
(What's this song?)
Hey!
(Why don't you know this?)
- Hey!
- Guess the song!
- You know this song?
- I told you...
I know this song. Let me answer.
Let me answer.
Isn't it "Dancing Queen?"
- Wrong!
- Hey!
The yellow place in the far distance
- Let me answer.
- It's not my song?
It's Lee Sang Woo's song!
- What?
- It's "Met Her 100m Away."
- Oh, it's that song?
- He's right.
Seriously.
The yellow place in the far distance
(Listen to this.)
That's right.
(Even Michael Jackson
knows this song.)
The place where I met her
It's 100m away
(I thought it was an upbeat song,
but it's a slow one?)
- It's that song?
- It is.
(There has to be a beat
that goes like this.)
(Bom, bom, bom)
("Met Her 100m Away"
by Lee Sang Woo)
I haven't heard this song
for so long.
Let's dance!
Hello! Now turn!
You're good!
(They start showing off
their charms.)
That's the dance.
Can you move? What are you doing?
I used to like this song,
but I had no idea.
Jong Kook! How could you miss this?
- You should've guessed it right.
- My gosh.
Jong Kook, remember this dance?
- This dance.
- I thought it was "Dancing Queen."
(Shyly dancing
to the old dance moves)
- It's Sang Woo's song.
- My gosh.
- That's it!
- I used to love this song.
He's excited.
All right!
(Dancing)
Shall I do it?
It's not the climax yet.
(Some kids act cool alone.)
Let's go back to the 1990s!
- I think she's coming to me
(The Town Musicians of Bremen
are excited by the lyrics.)
- That was...
- That's it!
That was so nice.
It's so heart-fluttering.
- That was so nice.
- By the way...
That was so exciting.
So Min is good
at this kind of stuff.
That was fun.
It reminds me of the old days.
(Cute steps of the coy girl)
So Min is good at stuff like this.
I absolutely loved this song,
but I couldn't recognize it
from the prelude.
This song...
This song was ranked number 1
for the longest in 1991.
- This song?
- That's right.
- How did you not recognize it?
- I remember it now.
I had no idea from the prelude.
By the way,
I saw you dance...
with your uncle
for the first time in a while.
You danced with him
Seriously.
- The age gap isn't that big.
- You are like her uncle.
You are like her uncle.
Are you saying
I am older than her dad?
Yes.
That makes no sense.
- Her dad!
- I am not older than him, okay?
- It's just my impression.
- Her dad!
That makes no sense.
- It's just my impression.
- That's right.
- Suk Jin.
- I am younger than her dad!
Why are you angry?
- Why are you angry?
- I am upset.
- You should be more positive.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
- Be positive.
- Always.
Learn from Jong Kook.
- Wouldn't you be angry?
- Of course not.
Be positive.
- Wouldn't you be angry?
- Of course not.
It just means you have that image.
- That's right.
- Be positive.
- It's just my impression.
- He changed a lot...
since "Master in the House."
I didn't know...
- that he could be so positive.
- Be positive.
Of course.
I doubt it will go on
past this week.
- Next.
- You should have gotten it right.
Please pass the phone...
- to the next ugliest person.
- I knew it right away.
- Take it.
- Why is it me?
- I refuse.
Be positive and take it.
- So Min made a chicken.
- It's a chicken.
- I haven't seen it in a while.
- Seriously.
Look at this.
(They used to make chickens
out of handkerchiefs.)
I haven't seen it in a while.
Back in the days,
Dad used to bring fried chicken...
Be quiet!
It's a funny episode!
- It isn't funny.
- It's a story of my memory!
Stop it.
- I will tell my dad.
- There is no need to keep going.
Why would you share another story
about a chicken?
Listen to the sound
we're about to play carefully...
and guess the name
of the product of the ad.
I don't know much about commercials.
It's too bad.
Commercials are hard.
(Sound)
What is that?
After going an entire day
without sleep,
it's 2 a.m. again.
- I don't know.
- What is this? I have no idea.
I know this commercial!
You should know this commercial!
Gosh!
Let me answer.
- TRY.
- It's correct.
- What's the answer?
- TRY.
Incorrect.
- What is it?
- I will play the commercial.
- Isn't it TRY?
- Doesn't he have a bandage?
- TRY.
- It sounds unfamiliar.
(What could be the commercial
with ragged breathing?)
It's the sound of a basketball.
Shall we play another game?
- The energy drink.
- Youth knows no weakness.
(The symbol of youthful commercials,
energy drinks)
I should have answered
this question!
Look what you have done!
- Why did you make me go third?
- Be positive.
Be positive.
- Kim Positive!
I am sure good things will follow.
- That's right.
- You should think that.
Although I got the question wrong,
- good things will follow.
- That's right.
The next one.
Give it to the next ugliest member.
Gosh, why would you say that?
- Just...
- There are too many.
(Handing over)
- Ji Hyo?
- She would be annoyed.
It seems fake.
She would be annoyed.
I switched it up a bit.
My decision wasn't based
on your looks.
Ji Hyo.
Hip Ji Hyo.
The next ugliest member picked up
the phone.
Listen to the sound
we're about to play carefully...
and guess the name
of the product of the ad.
- The commercial jingle.
- You can get it right.
(Majestic background music)
- What is this?
- Isn't this a movie?
What is this?
Is there a commercial like this?
(Majestic background music)
There will be lines.
(Ji Hyo doesn't have a clue.)
(Jae Suk
doesn't have a clue either.)
What is this?
(The air is thick with tension
as if something will happen.)
What is it? Do you know?
- Do you know?
- All right.
- I totally know.
- Is that all she gets?
- Is that all I get?
- Yes. 5, 4...
- Guess.
- You should know this.
- Two,
- Do you know? You don't, right?
- one.
- He knows.
- I don't know.
- Incorrect.
- A telecommunications company?
- I will play the commercial.
"Do you know the taste of crabs?"
- Is it that one?
- Really?
"Calls go through if it's Gulliver."
- No, no.
- Gulliver.
- "Do you know the taste of crabs?"
- Shin Gu says,
- It's the pager generation.
- Is it correct? Really?
- Do you know the taste of crabs?
(Do you know the taste of crabs?)
That's right.
Is this from 1991?
- Is it from 1991?
- You were in their commercial once.
- I was a model for Lotteria.
- Seriously.
- She eats rice in it.
- That's right.
The rice burger.
- Here.
- I should have known.
- Haha.
- Then we are at the top...
- when it comes to the rankings.
- This choice is more natural.
- They suit each other.
- I would have felt good...
- if you hadn't moved up with me.
- They suit each other.
I will play the song
that was released in 1991.
- It's a song.
- 1991?
- I have confidence.
- Guess...
- Guess the song title and singer.
- It could be by Michael Jackson.
Then you should dance.
(Boom, boom)
Hey!
Then you should dance.
(As soon as the music comes on,)
(everyone gets up.)
This is too much.
Hey!
For goodness' sake.
Show your moves before you answer.
This is ridiculous.
(Euljiro's Ha Jackson
came to take over the coffeehouse.)
Answer. Answer.
- Do you want me to answer?
- He looks similar.
- Keep dancing.
You don't know the song title,
do you?
- I know.
- Do you know?
(He is the most excited
since the opening.)
Do you know?
- Here I go.
- All right.
Let me answer.
- Michael Jackson.
- What's the song title?
"Dangerous."
That's right. It's "Dangerous."
("Dangerous" by Michael Jackson
took the world by storm in 1991.)
It was the perfect question
for Haha.
(Euljiro's Ha Jackson
shows off his dance moves.)
Since you answered correctly,
give us a ceremony.
All right.
Do it properly.
(Ha Jackson takes the stage.)
What?
(He goes forward as he shows off
his dangerous belly.)
What?
(The entering class of 1991
is highly satisfied.)
That's it.
(Jackson is back.)
Jackson!
(He is out of breath.)
- Ha Jackson!
- His belly is so plump.
- This Michael Jackson...
- Why is it so plump today?
has the proportions of a snowman.
His belly is plump.
He danced right away.
My goodness.
- I miss Michael Jackson.
- Next.
- Kwang Soo.
- Me?
Then I'm number one
when it comes to looks.
Is Se Chan the most handsome?
(The sexy hermit crab)
Listen to the sound
we're about to play carefully...
and guess the name...
- of the product of the ad.
- Okay!
He knows a lot of commercials.
- I know.
- He knows a lot.
I got all the previous ones right.
(Twinkling sound effect)
Putting an elephant in the fridge?
(Elephant sound)
- Let me answer.
- I know the answer.
Did you figure it out already?
Think Big.
(Kwang Soo is correct.)
He is incredible.
How old are you?
- He is incredible.
I knew the answer.
- Se Chan.
- Give it to me.
- I am the most handsome man.
- Se Chan is the most handsome man.
Here comes the most handsome man!
I see that the rankings are
in reverse.
That's right.
- Give me the question.
- Listen to the sound and guess...
- the name of the product in the ad.
- An ad.
(Se Chan gets a question about
a commercial from the 1990s.)
(Background music)
(I love)
(Even the sadness in the world)
(I know this one!)
(The two of them make it clear
that they know the answer.)
Don't give him a hint.
(The woman raises his head.)
- You got all the information.
- Seriously.
- 1, 2, 3.
Cheonggwanjang.
- Hey!
You are incorrect.
- Why don't you know?
- Ghana Chocolate.
- She did that.
- Lee Mi Yeon.
It was this. She did this!
(Lee Mi Yeon's facial expression...)
(made people create many parodies.)
How could you not know?
I didn't know.
- He was too young.
- They are in the reed field.
- Her face is buried in the coat.
- The coat.
- That was the preliminary mission.
- One person got the answer.
Haha and Kwang Soo got the answer.
Haha, pick a product you want.
- That's too bad.
- Okay.
- Please don't take the LP.
- Seriously.
- Lee Moon Sae's seventh album LP.
- Oh, no.
Oh, no.
- I'll take the Walkman.
- Okay.
That's too bad.
I used to listen to my Walkman
so often.
We will now move
to the next location.
In the order of ugliness,
which is the same...
as the order
you picked up the phone,
- move to the counter.
- Really?
- The counter.
(Is there a secret mission?)
Ma'am.
Who will pay for the drinks?
(The tab will be deducted
from one member's paycheck.)
Should I say the name?
Okay.
Well, he has...
(Well, he has...)
- the most amount of money.
- Please write down the name.
(He doesn't even hesitate.)
All right. Thank you.
(He picked Old Man Suk Jin.)
(Old Man Ji Suk Jin)
Shall I give her a rose?
What should I say?
Who will pay for the drinks?
(He pretends to hesitate...)
(and picks Jae Suk.)
Make sure he pays.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin picked
each other.)
(Each member wrote down a name.)
For us, the song is...
Yoo Young Seok.
- I want to walk down the street
I want to get drunk
on a fragrant cocktail
- That was the heyday of reggae.
- That's right.
Was that reggae?
- You seemed to have forgotten me
- At first
It was popular.
- Did you put on your seatbelts?
- Yes.
You want to go back
to the 1990s, right?
Wouldn't you go?
- Where?
- Would you give everything up...
to go back to 1991?
I wouldn't go back
if I had to give everything up.
You have to lose your memory, right?
- That's right.
- You have to live...
- as you did before, right?
- Yes.
- Then I wouldn't go back.
- Really?
It wasn't fun anyway, right?
It really wasn't fun.
Things weren't easy in the 1990s.
- I struggled.
- You had no money.
If I could go back...
with the mindset I have now,
I would go back.
I would live each day diligently.
Why would you live
even more diligently?
- But I regret the past.
- You have lived diligently.
- You still have regrets.
- Yes.
I have an example.
I had so much time back then.
- Had I learned English...
- That's right.
Who could have imagined
the present day?
- That's right.
- Had I memorized one word a day...
That's right.
I had so much time back then.
- You played every day.
- I just lazed around.
There is another thing.
I didn't have much money then,
but if I had invested in stocks...
(If I had invested in stocks...)
If I had done that regularly...
- That's right.
- Everyone thinks that.
I should have invested in stocks.
- Even if I had 2,000 dollars...
- We are thinking that now, right?
"I should have invested in stocks
back then."
But 10 or 20 years from now,
we will think,
- "It wasn't too late to start."
- That's right.
"It wasn't too late to memorize
English words."
"It wasn't too late."
People always have the same regrets.
That's right.
"Why did I laze around at home?"
If Suk Jin starts
studying English now...
- Everyone.
- Yes?
Earlier, you chose a member
who will pay for the drinks.
- No way.
- The highest number of votes...
determines the number of presents
in the first mission.
So, if Suk Jin placed
1st with 3 votes,
three people will receive a present
after the next mission.
Your results are strangely varied
when you do something like this.
- Okay.
- It's really strange.
The member who received 2 votes
placed 1st.
Everyone else received one vote.
The results were varied.
Thus, the next mission
will involve...
- only two presents.
- No way.
The person who will have
38 dollars deducted...
- from his paycheck is...
- Let's see.
- Kwang Soo.
- Me?
- In the end...
- Why me?
In the end, Kwang Soo was chosen.
- All right. This is good.
- Why me?
Kwang Soo, you received two votes.
We will pay for the drinks
with money from your paycheck.
Kwang Soo, that's Bosingak.
At the end of the year,
the bell-ringing ceremony
takes place.
- Look.
- That came out of nowhere.
So that's Bosingak.
- I went there once with my parents.
- Take a photo.
It's like the golden bell.
(Kwang Soo's golden Bosingak)
Jongno is where I spent...
my adolescence.
I spent so much time in Jongno
in my 20s.
We will go around Jongno today.
- Suk Jin and Yong Man...
- I hung out in Jongno.
hung out here very often.
There was a restaurant called
Pine Hill.
- Was it run by Kim Du Han?
- Have you heard of it?
- It was a famous restaurant.
- Hey.
Kim Du Han isn't
from that time period.
Kim Du Han, the Jongno kid.
Didn't he mostly eat
at gukbap restaurants?
Kim Du Han had gukbap every morning.
For goodness' sake.
The first place is...
a pool hall.
- Okay!
- I can't play pool.
I love pool.
- If you can play pool...
- I could hit...
250 points.
Suk Jin lowers his average
on purpose.
Seriously.
- He can hit 300 points.
- He does it to earn money.
By lowering his average,
he takes all the money.
That's his trick.
- Du Han!
- Hey!
He avoids raising the average.
- That's his trick.
- He doesn't want to lose money.
He doesn't want to lose money.
It has been a while since I played.
(The pool hall from 1991)
(A retro pool hall that has
the same sentimentality)
I haven't been to a pool hall
in a while.
It has been a long while.
- Gosh, this place is...
- It has been a while.
Back in the day, these places
were filled with cigarette smoke.
- That's right.
- Was the ceiling this low?
The ceiling wasn't so low back then.
- No, it wasn't.
- In the 1990s...
This place has a low ceiling.
Don't make a fuss.
- Really?
- This place has a low ceiling.
Pool halls didn't have a low ceiling
in the 1990s, right?
It's just this place.
What is Michael Jackson doing
at a pool hall?
What is he doing at a pool hall?
Does Michael Jackson play pool?
I like it.
- Pool.
- Yes.
- Can you play pool?
- My goodness.
- That's so funny.
He is an amateur.
- Suk Jin is excited...
- Look at Suk Jin.
- to show his skills.
- Hit from this angle.
- He is excited.
- He lies about his points.
He lowers his average points
on purpose.
To those who can play well,
he says his average is 200 points.
To novices,
he says his average is 250 points.
- Really?
- The points fluctuate.
He is a total swindler.
He is the worst.
He should be punished.
(Master Kim begins to punish him.)
Look at his mouth.
(They play pool as they did
in the past...)
(and use seduction skills.)
(Even Michael Jackson loves
Korean-style pool!)
It's really retro.
(The entering class of 1991
begin their journey to the past.)
(The popular memories
are brought back!)
- 2, 3.
- Come on out!
(Girls and boys who loved
the alleys)
(They even go to the LP bar!)
(They forget about the shoot
and become excited for real.)
(And...)
(The songs of the past
conclude the journey.)
(They write down stories
of the past.)
I took a trip down memory lane.
Why are you crying?
What's wrong?
Standing before the passing time
(Revisiting memories
makes them think about their past.)
(The Entering Class of 1991
Is Back!)