Is it volleyball? That's high.
Why is it so high?
My goodness. It's so high.
- It's too high.
- Are we doing this on water?
On the water?
Is it possible?
What is all this?
Can we even spike?
- What's all this?
- The net is too high.
The net is too high.
How would we do this?
That's the ball.
We can't even jump.
We're playing with that ball.
We just need
to send it over the net.
- It's a gym ball.
- With a gym ball?
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
Yeon Koung is known...
to be very spiteful
during the volleyball game.
So we prepared this game
to see her spitefulness today.
It's called Baking Bread on Water.
(The last game of Fierce Transfer Race,
Baking Bread on Water)
We have two huge mats
floating on the water.
You will play volleyball on them
with a big ball.
Just like the volleyball rules, you
can use your hands, feet, and head.
Drop the ball on your opponent's
side with a maximum of three hits.
Okay.
You may go into the water
to receive the ball.
- I see.
- We can go into the water.
But you can't wait in the water.
I get it.
- We can only receive it in there.
- Right.
Then we should send the ball
to the water.
The team that scores 11 points first
wins the game.
And there will be only two rounds.
In Round One,
the first-string players
and the trainers will play.
Okay.
In Round Two, the second-string
players and plus one will play.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's do this.
- All the first-string players.
- Yeon Koung can't play.
We have to win this round.
We might lose.
- We must win.
- Yeon Koung is the second-string.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Yeon Koung will be in Round Two.
- We must win this round.
First-string players,
please get ready.
Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Let's do this.
- This is harder than I thought.
- This is hard.
It's hard.
My goodness.
Like this.
- Gosh.
- When the ball comes...
- We have to move.
- Don't fall into the water.
You have to dive into the water
to receive the ball, okay?
We have to win this round.
- We get 1.5 times more.
- We have to win.
We must win this round.
Okay.
- Throw it?
- Let's practice.
- This is a practice.
- Practice.
This is not easy.
(With their powerful
passion and energy...)
(shown in Tokyo this summer,)
(the volleyball players
advanced to the semi-finals.)
they are showing
the perfect defense.
(With their amazing performance
recognized by the world,)
(they advanced to the semi-finals.)
(The national volleyball team
touched the people's hearts.)
(How will they play
the variety volleyball then?)
- It's not easy.
- My gosh.
- It's flying.
- No.
What?
- My gosh.
- No.
(She falls into the water.)
- It's done.
- Hye Seon, are you all right?
(Humiliated)
(The slapstick comedy starts
with the national setter.)
That's it. That's what we should do.
- Okay.
- This is difficult.
Toss the ball.
- Send it over.
- Good.
Receive the ball.
(What?)
- What was that?
- Gosh.
This is a mess.
- What was that?
- Isn't it that you're faking it?
This isn't easy.
What happened?
- What's wrong?
- My goodness.
Hye Seon, what happened?
Why did you fall down?
The first-string players
are different.
- They don't spare themselves.
- We just need to send it over.
Let's begin then.
Let's go.
Let's give it a try.
This is the beginning.
- But this is...
- Stay focused.
- This isn't easy.
- Let's do this.
- Go.
- I'll receive the ball.
(The game starts.)
- I will.
- Slow down.
- It's behind you.
- Done.
- Slow down.
- Good.
- Send it over.
My goodness.
(Eun Jin falls into the water
trying to touch the ball.)
- Use one hand.
- Hey.
- Keep it low.
- It should be low.
- Just send it over.
- We should do that.
- This is slippery.
- Right.
Make sure to keep it low.
Make sure to use both hands.
- I just can't do this.
- Use both hands.
What's wrong with you guys?
- Yes.
- It's done.
- We did it.
- Well done.
Hey, we must win this match.
Here it goes.
(Air So Young's service)
- Well done.
- Nice.
Send it up high.
- Don't push it hard.
- Good.
- Mine.
- That was good.
- Good.
- One at a time.
- Spike.
(The ball is coming to Ji Young.)
(Libero Oh Ji Young is number one
in the dig ranking.)
(She doesn't spare herself
when the ball comes toward her.)
- Spike. Oh no.
- Nice.
(She throws herself
to save the ball.)
Well done. You did a great job.
- Send it over.
- Well done.
Save the ball.
You have to send it over.
No. Send it over.
- Gosh.
- You lost.
- We won.
- Yes!
We lost?
We did it again.
It's not going over.
- They did a good job.
- It's okay.
What's wrong with you?
Min A, what are you doing?
- Hye Jin.
- Hey.
We should stay focused.
- Focus.
- Did I save the ball?
You did.
You even send it over the net.
- It's 2 to 0.
- They're good.
- Good.
- That's great.
- Mine.
- It's coming.
Good. Send it over.
- Ji Young.
- Okay.
(Ji Young!)
(Ji Young falls into the water
without touching the ball.)
(Locust Gym finally
scores the first point.)
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Done.
- You guys are so bad.
- Well done.
- It's okay.
- Ji Young.
- It was so...
- It's okay.
- Switch places with me.
- Okay.
- Just send it over.
- You do it.
- Okay.
- We can do this.
- I keep falling into the water.
- Sorry.
- I'll begin.
- Focus.
Make it high.
Don't try too hard. My gosh.
All right. Send it over.
- Here it goes.
- Nice.
- It's short.
- Mine.
- It's over the net.
- It's done.
(Groaning)
- She fell.
- Hye Jin.
(Staggering)
(That's to Hye Jin's mistake,
they scored 1 point.)
We have to focus.
You should send it up high.
This is frustrating.
- I'll serve.
- All right.
- Okay.
- There it goes.
- Here.
- Send it over.
- Good.
- You can also pass the ball.
(They groan as they touch
the heavy ball.)
Pass.
- My gosh.
- Send it over.
- Receive the ball.
- Ji Young.
How would I do that?
(Splashing)
Ji Young.
How would I do that?
How would I receive it?
How...
Why do you keep
letting me do things like this?
I thought she'd do it.
(Teddy Bear keeps calling
Ji Young's name without moving.)
She doesn't want
to go into the water.
- Why do I have to do this?
- I'll stand at the back.
I'll be at the back.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
Good.
- Good luck.
- All right.
You keep letting me
go into the water.
You're the star of the day.
- Here I go.
- Send it to Trainer Kook.
(Jae Suk serves as he hopes
to score one more point.)
- It's flying over.
- Good.
Get the ball.
Okay.
(Groaning)
(While Hee Jin hesitates,)
(our libero throws herself again.)
- Nice.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Ji Young's slapstick comedy.
Hang on.
Why aren't you
getting into the water?
(Teddy Bear survived alone
on the mat again.)
- Why aren't you going into the water?
- Ji Young.
Look.
- She's all dry.
- She's not throwing herself.
- Is she dry?
- She's still dry.
- Dry
- I'll go home dry today
Why aren't you following the ball?
Let's do this.
I'll follow the ball this time.
Here it goes.
Good. Here comes Min A.
Min A, let's do this.
Get the ball.
- It's out.
- Out.
(Is the ball out?)
- It's out.
- Out.
- The ball is out.
- They touched the ball.
They touched the ball.
- Touch.
- They didn't touch it.
- The ball wasn't touched.
It was. Didn't you touch the ball?
- We didn't.
No one says they touched the ball.
- They always say no.
- They all are liars.
They lie every time.
Here it goes.
All right. Let's do this.
We must win.
Ji Young, jump.
- Ji Young.
- You should wait.
Now.
It's coming back.
I'll do it.
Mine.
Is it out?
(What?)
Mine.
(She sends the ball
to the water proudly.)
You should send it over the net.
You're doing this to me
on purpose, aren't you?
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- Good.
- It's a foul.
- Welcome
- to the locust world
- To the locust world
Welcome
- to the locust world
- To the locust world
(The ace player, Eun Jin's serve)
Good.
That was nice.
Send it over.
- Okay.
- You should wait.
- One and two.
- Gosh.
- Okay. It's done.
- Done.
Good.
It's out.
- No.
- Hurry.
Send it over.
No.
(What?)
She did it on purpose.
- Nice.
- It's our ball.
(Yeum Cheater's jump
stopped their upturn.)
- Ji Young is really good.
- Give us the ball.
She's amazing.
It's short.
- Good.
- Well done.
Wait a little more.
- One.
- My gosh.
(So Young received the ball.)
- Toss it over the net.
- Send it over.
- You have to toss it over.
- My goodness.
- Gosh, Hye Seon.
You have to toss it over.
- My goodness.
- Gosh, Hye Seon.
- Gosh. Hye Seon.
- Hye Seon.
Yeum Cheater.
- We did it.
- We scored.
Yeum Cheater is strange.
She doesn't know the timing.
Hye Seon, stand at the back.
- Should I stand in the front?
- Yes, you should.
(They stand in a new formation.)
Hye Seon.
You shouldn't think of it
as a real volleyball game.
- You should wait.
- You give it a try.
(You give it a try.)
I'll play soon.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
Mine.
- Good.
- That was nice.
- Turn around.
- You do it.
Touch it gently. Done.
- Send it to the back.
- Toss it over.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
(The ball is over the net.)
Hurry.
- Hye Seon.
- Get the ball.
One and two.
(Determined)
(Gurgling)
Hye Seon.
Gosh, Hye Seon.
How many times was that?
- Gosh, Hye Seon is...
- Yeum Cheater.
Gosh, Yeum Cheater.
- Hye Seon.
You're the highest-paid player here.
(She's ruining the game
after getting the highest salary.)
- The highest-paid player?
- We have to win no matter what.
We should never lose.
We must win.
Let's give it a try. Let's do this.
- I'll serve.
- All right.
Send it to Yeum Cheater.
- Focus.
- Score at once.
- You have two points left.
- You're doing a good job.
The ball is coming.
- Good
- Gosh.
(Trainer Yoo almost ruined it,
but Eun Jin saved the ball.)
Trainer Yoo, go to the back.
Trainer Yoo.
Mine.
- One more.
- Send it over.
Jump.
- You should wait.
- My gosh.
- Here it goes.
- You do it.
It's over the net.
- Mine.
- Jump.
Yes.
Jump.
(So Young falls into the water
without touching the ball.)
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
Good.
- Okay.
- So Young.
- Nice.
- Okay.
(Is she going to Locust Gym?)
This isn't your team.
(This isn't your team.)
(She goes to the wrong team
and gets kicked out.)
- This isn't your team.
- Come here, So Young.
- Come here.
- That's not your team.
Pull yourself together. It's here.
Come here.
- Well done.
- We have one point left.
Locust world!
Set point.
- I'll serve.
- Only one point.
- Let's do this.
- Score one more point.
Hey, we have to win.
- We need only one point.
- One point.
- Good luck.
- I'll serve.
It's one point.
(Eun Jin's stable serve)
Mine.
- Hey, you have to jump.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Get the ball.
- Eun Jin, come on up.
- Send it over.
- Hey.
- Mine.
- That was amazing.
- Good timing.
- Go to your place.
- Okay.
From the back.
- Okay. Good.
- Mine.
- One more time.
- Jump.
- Okay!
- Yes!
(Again...)
(Hee Jin tosses the ball.)
(She finishes the game
jumping into the water.)
- Okay!
- We won!
That was great.
- Yes!
- Well done.
Nice.
- Yes.
- Well done.
(In Round 2...)
- Get the ball.
- Mine.
Toss the ball, Suk Jin.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
You should've jumped
toward the ball.
(They get excited
as the game goes well.)
This is so nice. I'm excited.
- Mine.
- Yeon Koung.
Good.
- Ji Hyo. Push the ball.
- Push it.
(Yeon Koung's receive
and Ji Hyo's mistake)
(They celebrate it
with silly dance moves.)
You have to go into the water.
Good.
Hey.
(Thanks to Jong Kook's mistake,
Team Locust wins Round 2.)
Trainer Yoo gets 700 dollars.
(700 dollars for Trainer Yoo)
And Trainer Kook gets 400 dollars.
The trainers can...
distribute the last salary...
- as they please.
- Okay.
Please write it down.
- Oh, dear.
- Gosh, this is...
This is difficult.
Don't worry. I know...
you guys tried hard.
- Okay. Don't worry.
- I'll make it fair.
Don't worry.
(How would the fierce
three-week-long race end?)
Okay.
So this will be aired
for four weeks?
(The volleyball players
made 3 episodes with 1 shoot.)
It feels like I've spent
three days with them.
- We've become close.
- I feel comfortable around them.
I'll announce the prize
and penalty for today.
- Okay.
The prize is...
for the health
of our precious players.
It's a Korean beef set.
(The prize is a Korean beef set.)
- What about the penalty?
- The penalty is...
- Five of you will get the penalty.
- Yes.
The trainer with less money,
two players
with the least amount of money,
and another two players
picked by them.
(1 trainer, 2 players with the least
money, and another 2 picked by them)
- And two of them will survive.
- Okay.
The three people will be...
bombarded with whipped cream.
We haven't done it for a long time.
(They will have to shower
before going home.)
- Your face...
- It's been a long time.
will smell like cake all day.
- All day.
- It'd feel like your birthday.
That's too bad.
I'll announce the result
of the trainers first.
- Trainer Yoo has...
- He's our trainer.
Trainer Yoo has...
(How much money
does Trainer Yoo have?)
- 780 dollars.
- Gosh, that's a lot.
- It's unbelievable.
- I can't believe this.
- Is it 780 dollars?
- Hang on.
- He has 780 dollars?
- Is it that much?
- How could it be 780 dollars?
- That's a lot.
- What?
- He has 780 dollars?
- He has 780 dollars.
- Is it that much?
- He has 780 dollars?
Trainer Kook has 110 dollars.
- What?
- So he will get the penalty.
(Trainer Kook will get the penalty.)
- What?
- He has 780 dollars?
- How much does he have?
- He has only 110 dollars.
He'll get the penalty.
- Is it 780 dollars?
- That's unfair.
I didn't know I had that much money.
Why do I have so much money?
- The difference is 600 dollars.
- I guess he won first place.
He has 780 dollars.
That means you all can win.
One of you might win first place.
It's fine as long
as our team wins first place.
- Yeum Cheater.
- It's a shame.
This is real cheating.
- Stabbing someone in the back.
- I see.
The result came out.
Let's find out.
- Starting with the bottom place?
- Our team has a better chance.
Was it neck and neck?
Yes, it was neck and neck.
- I hope the winner is on our team.
- The winner?
- I'm sure it's our team member.
- Please.
- We'll start with 1st place.
- The 2nd place...
The person in first place...
(The winner will be revealed first.)
who will be exempt from the penalty
and receive the prize...
got 683 dollars.
- The winner is Yeum Hye Seon.
- Okay.
(The winner is Yeum Hye Seon.
who got 683 dollars.)
- Okay. That's great.
- Everyone, gather around.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- See? I told you so.
- Nice.
The person in second place...
who got 570 dollars is Kim Hee Jin.
(Kim Hee Jin with 570 dollars)
- I thought it'd be Yeon Koung.
- This is good.
- It's great.
- The second place is on our team.
- Good. We won the silver medal.
- Good job.
- Gosh, you.
- It's okay.
- Gosh. I'm sorry.
- I can't believe you took it all.
He took all the money.
- And there's...
- I'm sorry.
only a 20-dollar difference
between the 3rd and 4th places.
- Oh, my gosh.
- No way.
- It's you, Yeon Koung.
- If not, we'd be disappointed.
- I'm sure it's Yeon Koung.
- I really hope it's on our team.
- Please.
- I hope it's on our team.
- She has a chance too.
- Who is in third place?
- Let it be on our team.
- I hope so.
I wonder who is in third place.
The person in 3rd place
with 540 dollars...
- It must be Yeon Koung.
- who will get the prize...
It must be Yeon Koung.
and will be exempt
from the penalty...
is Lee So Young.
(Lee So Young with 540 dollars is
in 3rd place.)
- Good job.
- Lee So Young.
Don't be angry.
- You did great.
- I told you...
- You should've given her more.
- Great.
- I didn't know I had so much left.
- What's with your trainer?
- Trust me. I didn't know...
- You should complain to him.
- I didn't know I had so much left.
- This is the worst situation.
- You said you'd pay us well.
- I'm not lying...
- Come on, Yeon Koung.
- He's so greedy.
- Yeon Koung, trust me.
- I was wrong about you.
The person in 4th place
with 520 dollars is Kim Yeon Koung.
- That was close.
- Oh, boy.
Listen, Yeon Koung.
I gave you 200 dollars...
I came in fourth place again?
I'm in fourth place again?
Not again.
(Trainer Yoo reminded her of
the disappointment of the Olympics.)
- Everyone...
- The 2 people tied for 5th place...
are Oh Ji Young and Ahn Hye Jin.
They both got 490 dollars.
The person in 7th place
with 310 dollars is Park Eun Jin.
And Ji Hyo came in eighth place.
Suk Jin came in 9th place
with 230 dollars and 1 cent.
(The people in 11th and 12th places
will get the penalty.)
- See? I knew it.
- My gosh.
- I can't believe this.
- I guess it's me.
- No, I think it'll be me.
- Wait.
- I'm sure it's me.
- No, it's me.
- Those two will get the penalty.
- You crook!
- Never trust this crook.
- I told you...
- that 100 dollars wouldn't cut it.
- Exactly.
- I paid you equally as I promised.
- How much?
I gave you 200 dollars each
at the end.
- That's awesome.
- Oh, my.
- That was it for us.
- I said he'd pay more money.
The remaining players are
So Min, Haha, and Se Chan.
(The 3 remaining players are
So Min, Haha, and Se Chan.)
The one who came in 10th place
with only a 10-dollar difference...
- Who is it?
- Please.
- I think it's So Min.
- We're in trouble.
- I bowed to him.
(Which of these 3 will survive?)
It's So Min who got
146 dollars and 99 cents.
(It's So Min!)
(The team members are happy
for So Min.)
- You're not in the bottom two.
- I'm so happy for you.
- I'm so excited.
- We won.
- We made it.
- Oh, yes.
It's So Min.
(Se Chan and Haha
will get the penalty.)
If I hadn't given them
five dollars...
- I mean...
- You thief!
- How could you?
- Come with me.
- Go ahead.
- Gosh, you.
- I'm disappointed.
- I'm sorry, guys.
- Throw him in the water.
- I apologize.
I'm sorry.
(He apologized too late.)
(Punished on the spot)
That darn...
Hey.
- That darn locust.
- I'm sorry.
I can't believe
I let that locust fool me.
(In 11th place, Haha, 135 dollars,
In 12th place, Se Chan, 127 dollars)
- What if I kept five dollars?
- He got 780 dollars.
That's the thing
about the world of professionals.
It's tough to survive
in the world of professionals.
(So Min avoided the penalty
thanks to the stingy Trainer Yoo.)
- Congratulations.
- She's safe now.
- We did a great job.
- Now...
The 2 of you can choose 2 players
to get the penalty...
except for the top three players
and Jae Suk.
- We can discuss and choose them?
- Yes.
You guys acted up when our rankings
were revealed, but you're quiet now.
(Everyone is standing politely
with their hands together.)
Choose two players
on the other team.
- We'll do that.
- By the way...
Didn't you promise
you'd give me 20 dollars?
You mean our team?
- You mean our team?
- But you left our team.
- True.
- It's not like I had a choice.
- You moved to that team gladly.
- You did your best to win.
- Really? Fine. Watch your tone.
- I mean you were so excited...
- It's okay. You can't choose them.
- We're safe.
- We don't care.
- They're okay.
- Try all you want.
- They're in 2nd and 3rd place.
- Go ahead.
- We're in 2nd and 3rd place.
- Oh, I see.
- Oh, that's right.
- They're safe.
We can't choose them.
- You see, I...
- Go ahead.
I wish the 2nd and 3rd place were
on our team.
- I know.
- It's okay.
- Okay. We'll choose one first.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- We agreed to choose this person.
- Yes, we did.
- The first one is... One, two...
- Two, three.
- Kim Yeon Koung.
Gosh, seriously.
- Here's why. The one to get...
- The one to get...
- a penalty is always Lee Kwang Soo.
(The one to get a penalty is
always Lee Kwang Soo.)
- Feeling! Cross!
- Intuition! Cross!
- Oh, gosh. Not Yeon Koung.
- We chose Yeon Koung.
Why would you...
What's wrong with our team?
- I said I would move to that team.
- She's a second-string player.
- Exactly.
Kwang Soo, you're lucky...
- when it comes to a penalty.
- Why would you call me that?
- You're Kwang Soo.
- Oh, no. I feel bad for her.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
I think she did a good job.
- I'm on the same team as you.
- You should choose from that team.
- Right. I don't see Ji Young.
- Actually...
- Hide behind us.
- Where did Ji Young go?
- Ji Young, can you step forward?
- I don't see her.
- Ji Young.
- The amazing Ji Young.
- The amazing, awesome Ji Young.
- She left.
- She left early.
- Come out.
- She didn't feel well.
- She went home.
- Ji Young went home.
- Really? Shall we call her...
- to see if she comes out or not?
- Okay.
Let's try calling her.
If she left, she wouldn't come out.
- But if she's still here...
- You promised you'd help me out.
- She's here.
- Really?
- That's good.
- All right.
One, two, three.
- The amazing and awesome...
- Oh Ji Young!
- Okay.
(Ji Young will get the penalty too.)
We're safe.
- I'm the only one on our team.
- There will be a draw.
But we'll draw lots
to choose who will be exempt.
- We'll give the winners the prizes.
- Why did you choose me?
You can pick the good one.
- If I don't get lucky...
- You can avoid it.
Let's all step forward now.
We'll give you 5 files.
Choose 1 without looking.
- Will you put them on the table?
- Yes.
- We'll put them on the table.
- That's unnecessary. Just pick one.
- Which one should I pick?
- Should we pick ourselves? Gosh.
- You should get a blank one.
- Just pick one.
It's going to be... I mean...
You shouldn't look inside.
Which one should I choose?
Don't look inside.
(Taking one)
- Each of you can take one.
- Pick something else.
- I pick number three.
- What should be in there?
What's wrong with you?
- Pick something else.
- I pick number three.
What's wrong with you?
- Let me have number three.
- What should I check?
- All right.
- It must've been written inside.
- Don't look just yet.
- Don't look.
- No, what's written inside?
- Does anyone want to trade with me?
- No, I won't trade with you.
- I don't know.
- "Penalty" is written in three.
- I won't trade with you.
- Let's start with Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook will go first.
One, two, three.
(What could be Trainer Kook's fate?)
- "Penalty".
- You'll get a penalty.
- Nice.
- Okay.
Variety show deity.
(Jong Kook ended up going broke
and getting the penalty.)
- Please help me.
- Please.
- You have a chance.
- Yes, we do.
- Please help me just this once.
- I'm worried.
- Just this once.
- I hope I get lucky this time.
- You'll get a penalty.
- Okay.
(Ji Young will get a penalty.)
My gosh. Unbelievable.
(Variety show deity,
please help me!)
- The amazing and awesome Ji Young.
- Ji Young.
Our team made it.
- Our team won.
- Let's check them at the same time.
- Please.
- Only one of you will be chosen.
- Just one.
- This is hard to believe.
- Only one of them.
- Don't look.
- Please.
- Two of you will avoid it.
- Please help me just this once.
It'd be the worst
if the two of you avoided it.
That would be the funniest.
- Please help me.
- One.
(Will the 2 guys avoid the penalty
when they're the bottom 2?)
Two.
(Will the 2 guys avoid the penalty
when they're the bottom 2?)
(Or will Long Legs get lucky
and avoid the penalty?)
- Three.
- Here.
(Yeon Koung will get the penalty.)
Oh, no.
(The variety show deity has spoken.)
- I really didn't know. I swear.
- Darn it.
I hate you.
- You took it from me.
- Shut it.
Leave me alone.
- What is this?
- I was so surprised.
- I really didn't know. I swear.
- You took it from me.
- I swear. I didn't know.
- This is ridiculous.
Hey, Yeon Koung sure is
just like Kwang Soo.
(She's even unlucky
just like Kwang Soo.)
- This is crazy.
- Hey, Yeon Koung.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- Yes!
- This is hilarious.
- One, two, three. Yes!
- See?
- This is unbelievable.
- I said our team would be safe.
- Oh, my. I'm so surprised.
- The volleyball players...
- Please stand in the middle.
- joined us on the show today.
- Yes.
We had a blast.
Let's give them a hand.
- Thank you.
(Thank you for your appearance,
national volleyball team players.)
- I hope to see you all again...
- No matter what.
- after the season is over.
- Yes.
- All of you should come back.
It's time for the penalty now.
- Trainer Kook and...
- Gosh, I really don't like this.
Yeon Koung is glaring at us.
- Does it shoot the cream like this?
- Yes.
Is the blast strong?
- No, it's not that strong.
- I'm scared.
- It won't hurt. Trust me.
- Don't worry.
- It won't hurt at all.
- It's just cream.
Ready. One.
Two.
(The two oldest players wait
to get the penalty.)
Three.
She got hit properly.
(The other two didn't get hit
straight on their faces.)
- Ji Young got hit properly.
- That's how you all should look.
- That's perfect.
- My gosh.
Don't touch your face.
- Don't touch it.
- You'll get a close-up shot.
Who wants to take a picture
with her?
- Me.
- Ji Young.
- You look perfect. It's great.
- Take a picture with her.
Yeon Koung looks so cute.
- Yeon Koung looks so cute.
- One, two, three.
Nice.
(We thank the volleyball players
for giving us all a good laugh.)
- Good job, everyone.
- Thank you.
You look so cute.
(So the 3-week journey ended.)
(Firenze, Italy)
(The area still has the beautiful
atmosphere of the Renaissance.)
(Firenze, S restaurant
in Jamwon-dong near the Han River)
(An important business meeting
will be held here today.)
- Oh, my.
- It's European style.
- It's nice.
- Are we having a party today?
- I see Mount Nam and the Han River.
- It's pretty.
- You eat here all the time, right?
- This is really nice.
- Suk Jin is not wearing pants.
- By the way...
Why are you wearing your shorts
like that?
- Suk Jin, what are you wearing?
- What do you mean by that?
- Attack!
- Na Eun...
Na Eun looks like this
with her diapers under her shorts.
- She looks chubby like you do.
- It's the diaper look.
- Gosh. I don't know.
- The front part is bulging.
- What?
- Why is it bulging so much?
- It's bulging.
- Like I said,
that's how Na Eun looks
when she wears shorts...
- over her diaper.
- Did you put something in there?
- It's designed this way.
- Why did you add padding there?
- It's for next year's...
spring-summer season fashion week.
Then why do you seem so eager
to sit down?
Because this is my boat.
This is my boat.
He says it's his boat.
(Grabbing the air)
- Why didn't you fall for it?
- That's an old trick.
- It's such an old trick.
- What a shame.
- Here you go.
- By the way,
I have to tell you about So Min
before we begin.
- Exactly.
- What happened?
- I heard that she couldn't come.
- Actually,
She won't come today?
someone on the set
of her drama was diagnosed...
- with COVID-19 last week.
- Oh, no.
The epidemiological investigation
is being carried out.
- I see.
- She doesn't know...
if she has to go into quarantine...
- Or if she can come out?
- or if she's fine.
- At the moment, So Min is...
- She's on standby.
waiting for the result at home
while sighing.
- In fact, we all came here.
- By the way...
- But we're not in great condition.
- True.
Everyone besides me
is not feeling so well.
- We're enduring it.
- He...
- He got a shot.
- Se Chan...
- Grape juice.
- isn't feeling well...
Oh, right.
- He got his vaccine shot.
- That's right.
- I'm feeling hazy.
- Gosh, you're so weak.
Hey, Se Chan already chose
this seat.
- I called dibs on this seat.
- What is wrong with you?
That's ridiculous.
What's with your pronunciation?
I don't know.
It happens in the morning.
- I mean...
- It happens in the morning?
- You sit there, you punk.
- He says it happens in the morning.
- Sit here, Se Chan.
- Okay.
I'll let you sit there
in the morning.
I'm sorry,
but what do you do for a living?
- Pardon me?
- What is your profession?
I import fashion products...
- from Italy.
- I see.
I also export Korean products
to Italy.
So you're a peddler, aren't you?
Aren't you the one who got caught
selling fake designer goods?
- You earned a lot as a peddler.
- A peddler?
- Don't call me a peddler.
- He made money as a peddler.
- I sell a ton per month.
- Mr. Fake Goods.
- Haven't you been on the news?
- No.
I think I've seen you on the news.
- It wasn't like that.
- He was wearing the same clothes.
I was on the news
as a model taxpayer.
- A model taxpayer?
- Yes.
- But you don't earn that much.
- How much tax do you pay per year?
- Pardon me?
Must I tell you that?
I mean...
- Must I tell you that?
- Seeing that you were on the news,
- you must pay a fortune for taxes.
- Absolutely.
- He must pay a lot.
- How much tax do you pay per year?
No comment.
- Pardon?
- No comment.
Don't you run your own business?
- We all do.
- Hey, is your business going well?
Yes, it's going well.
I'm sorry, but Ji Hyo isn't feeling
well either, so don't talk to her.
She has mild enteritis.
I can't talk to her
because she has enteritis...
or to him because he got vaccinated.
Then whom can I talk to?
You can talk to me.
(- Then whom can I talk to?
- You can talk to me.)
- I'm in good condition today.
- Should I talk to this glass?
- I feel like I can even fly.
- Hey, how are you feeling?
- I feel so energetic.
- My gosh.
Whom should I talk to?
- You can talk to me.
- Seriously.
- You have enteritis?
- Yes.
I'm suffering from
severe seasonal allergies.
Haha is suffering from
allergic reactions.
- And he...
- I can't take off my sunglasses.
Do you have a runny nose?
It'd be crazy.
By the way, when Haha is shooting
this show with us,
he often says he's not feeling well,
but he seemed so enthusiastic
on "How Do You Play?".
- I know, right?
- Hey.
- Right? You saw that too, right?
- Yes, I did.
- That's not true.
- Since he joined that show,
- I mean...
- he gives his all over there,
and then he's bedridden
for six days.
- Right? He seemed so enthusiastic.
- No, that's not true.
- Bo Pil must be upset.
- Don't think that way.
- It's all a misunderstanding.
- He really is enthusiastic.
He is, right?
- I'm not joking. He works so hard.
- He took me by surprise.
Jae Suk is complimenting him.
You know...
- that I rarely compliment him.
- He was so passionate.
- He works really hard on that show.
- Right?
- I'm so disappointed.
- I'm grateful to him.
Bo Pil, it's not true.
I work just as hard here.
- That's not true.
- He just acts arrogant here...
and tries to go home early
saying he's not feeling well.
- Seven to three?
- I think so.
He's been working hard
to become a regular on that show.
- That's not true. Believe me.
- I can see that.
We prepared
some special food for you.
Really? But why are you feeding us?
- I see. Sounds great.
- Oh, my.
Thank you, Nam Joong.
(Plenty of food is served
on a 3-tier tray.)
- Why are you giving us food?
- What's that?
- It's eggs benedict.
- Thanks.
- It looks good.
- What's this?
(From truffle cream sauce pasta...)
(to homemade hamburger
with a rich cheesy flavor)
- Oh, it's a souffle.
- This is injeolmi. What's that?
What is a souffle?
Don't you know what a souffle is?
- I should exercise hard after this.
- I think it's a souffle.
- I don't like it when they feed us.
- Nam Joong.
I'm not sure if we should
just enjoy the food.
- I love souffle pancakes.
- It looks so good.
- I think we should do this.
- It looks delicious.
- What are you doing?
- Everyone.
Are you the president of this group?
Why do you keep acting up?
- Haven't you watched any movies?
- I guess...
- I guess he watches TV a lot.
- Exactly.
- They tap a glass to give a toast.
- That's right.
- We have enough time.
- They tap a glass like that.
Let me make a toast.
- Did you just ring a bell?
- It's his treat.
No, that's not it.
By the way, this is so delicious.
- Oh, my.
- Is it? It looks good.
It tastes even better
as we're eating outside.
- It'd still be tasty indoors.
- I agree.
What's that? Is it pork rind?
What did you say? What's that?
What's that?
- What?
- What's going on?
Why are you giving us so much food?
What's going on?
Aren't we getting lunch today?
Hey, give me the lamb steak.
He's just unbelievable.
He never eats lamb
with his own money.
- He's ridiculous.
- He likes free food too much.
By the way, why are you giving us
so much food?
It's not lamb. It's Iberico pork.
- Is it not lamb?
- Oh, Iberico pork?
Pork is good for our health.
- Oh, my.
- Why are we getting so much food?
It's a good source of protein.
(They're gulping down the food,
putting their doubts aside.)
- Did we win an award or something?
- It's so good.
(They're gulping down the food,
putting their doubts aside.)
Or is one of us leaving the show?
Since Haha and some others
haven't been feeling well,
we prepared some healthy food.
- This one is really tasty.
- Indeed.
When Haha doesn't feel well,
you just have to bring a camera
from the "How Do You Play?" team.
(Just bring a camera
from the "How Do You Play?" team.)
- Haha is taken aback.
- He'd put on funny makeup...
- and everything.
- Hey.
You know what they do.
They will fully take advantage
of you.
You all know that it's true.
- He...
- He doesn't have to work so hard.
- I'm different because...
- It's pointless.
- He appears on the show regularly.
- I'm a cast member, not a guest.
- What?
- He's a cast member now.
You must be happy.
(You must be happy.)
Se Chan, what did you do
to make money in Italy?
I'm sure you don't speak Italian.
- Italian...
- I bet he hasn't been there.
Isn't "bonjour" Italian?
- "Bonjour" is French.
- That's French.
- They all make this gesture.
- It's "ciao" in Italian.
- "Buongiorno."
- Right. "Buongiorno."
I said, "Ciao."
"Ciao" means "hello".
I'm sorry,
but have you been to Italy before?
(I'm sorry,
but have you been to Italy before?)
You don't have to go to Italy
to do business.
What I meant was...
- Haven't you been there before?
- Haven't you?
Look here.
All my employees are over there.
- I just give them orders.
- What kind...
What kind of business is it, mister?
- I import fashion items.
- Exactly what items?
- What fashion items?
- What did you import recently?
- Pardon?
I imported some suits recently.
- Did you just say "sperm"?
- Yes.
- "Sperm"?
- You imported sperm?
- Mister.
- "Sperm"?
- Gosh. That's too much.
- Why would he say such a thing?
- Where do you get it, mister?
- Mister.
- Gosh, what's wrong with you?
Where do you get that?
There's something wrong
with his pronunciation.
- Where do you get it?
- Is it so hard to pronounce "suit"?
- It was unexpected. I'm baffled.
- So you sell "sperm"...
Hey, kid, what do you do?
- What do you do?
- Are you talking to me?
- Yes, you. What do you do?
- What?
Haha, you should at least talk
with more enthusiasm.
(You should at least talk
with more enthusiasm.)
I just improvised a joke.
- Why can't you be more passionate?
- He should've played along with me.
- He's unlucky to sit there.
- That was a bad one.
Gosh. He's driving me crazy.
- Seriously. I mean...
- Come up with one good joke...
- at least.
- I can't believe you.
- Make people laugh at least once.
- Keep going.
- Haha, what are you doing?
- Make our viewers laugh.
- You could do some funny acts.
Gosh. You guys are making me
feel so uncomfortable.
Haha, what are you doing?
- You should admit it.
- Why did you choose that seat?
- You should've come here.
- Go, Haha!
- Haha, cheer up.
- Why didn't you come here?
- You've got this.
- I'll keep an eye on you.
Hey, what line of business
are you in?
You're eating the food that I made.
- I work in the restaurant industry.
- Oh, you're in the food industry.
- Are you a chef?
- Yes.
You see, you shouldn't run
a business with your boyfriend.
(You see, you shouldn't run
a business with your boyfriend.)
- What's with that comment?
- Hey.
Gosh. You won't play along
with any of my jokes.
- You should've said something!
- Go, Haha!
- Haha, what are you doing?
- Haha, go for it.
- What was that?
- You know...
Pour all you have into the shoot
on Thursday.
Today is Monday.
You have three days left.
- Pour it all into Thursday's shoot.
- I mean...
- Save it for Thursday's shoot.
- That kind of joke...
He wouldn't make that kind of joke
on "How Do You Play?".
- Save it for Thursday.
- Am I right?
- We have class too.
- He's doing great.
I'm surprised that Jong Kook saw him
on that show.
You watched that show.
It's not like that.
I was so surprised. I found out
about it from a news article.
Haha on "How Do You Play?".
I think I should visit the set
to see Haha shooting the show.
(He's planning to visit him
at his other workplace.)
- Go to see him.
- He must feel suffocated.
- That must be so scary.
- You'd make him feel threatened.
The weather is so nice.
- Cheer up.
- Thanks. The weather is so nice.
(Exclaiming)
- It must be too greasy for you.
- It's good.
This boosts my appetite
so early in the morning.
- This Iberico pork steak is tasty.
- It's so good.
Are you all full?
- Yes.
- I really enjoyed it.
- You can listen to me while eating.
Today,
to celebrate the beginning of fall,
the season of feeding our minds
and bodies,
we prepared Elegant Western Road
to do just that.
What is that?
Are we going somewhere else
to eat more food?
Obviously, we prepared food
for you for a reason.
Today,
you will be a lady and gentlemen
with dignity and manners...
and visit famous Western food
restaurants all day long.
I like Western food,
but I can't eat it all day long.
- I'm already tired of it.
- It's too greasy already.
- Listen.
- It's too much.
I craved young radish kimchi
when I had my last bite.
Since it's Elegant Western Road,
you'll eat creamy, greasy,
- soft, and sticky food...
- That'd be so oily.
with lots of butter, cream,
and cheese in it.
- Oh, gosh.
- "Soft and sticky"?
When the tour ends,
the one with the most prize badges
will win and get a prize.
And one person chosen
by picking a penalty ball...
- will get the penalty.
- Oh, gosh.
I'll explain how you get
prize badges and penalty balls.
At every restaurant you visit,
a certain amount of food
will be prepared for you to taste.
If you fail to finish the food,
you receive a penalty ball.
- I see.
- How do we finish all the food?
How do we eat Western food
for three meals straight?
- Besides...
- Food made with flour.
I just ate three pieces
of Iberico pork steak.
I also ate some pasta and...
- Iberico pork.
- Gosh. I ate three pieces.
- But you have a chance.
- What chance?
You will play a game
before eating food,
and it will decide the number
of the badges you can get.
Who wins the badges
will also be decided.
Those who win the badges
may skip the meals...
and enjoy any kind of dish...
- that they requested beforehand.
- Any dish?
It has to be ramyeon.
And that's all you'll have to eat.
- I wouldn't mind a spicy dish.
- Or something refreshing.
What I'm craving the most
is kimchi stew.
- Same here.
- I want naengmyeon.
The winner of the games...
will be able to save others
from eating heavy dishes.
- Just one more person.
- That's right.
At the next restaurant,
you'll be enjoying
creamy and cheesy...
doughnuts.
- No way.
- Doughnuts?
- Doughnuts with sugar?
- I hardly eat them.
But right now, name the dish...
you'd like to eat
should you win the game.
It could be something spicy...
- or something refreshing.
- What should I choose?
Can cold kimchi noodles be served?
- Cold kimchi noodles?
- Or something like that.
- I'd like that too.
- What do you think?
Cold kimchi noodles sound good.
- Then that will be served.
- Nice.
- Shall we get moving?
- Yes, let's go.
My gosh.
Hold on a second.
- Aren't we wearing team shirts?
- You'll be wearing that all day.
(You'll be wearing that all day.)
- Wait. Are you kidding me?
- No, I'm not.
You should wear this at the waist.
Would you like to tuck this in?
Hold on.
I'm supposed to fasten my belt.
- Yes, you have to.
- You don't have it fastened?
But we're still parked.
It doesn't matter.
We need to stay focused today...
since we're down a member.
- How can I...
- And you should talk more.
Ji Hyo looks lonely,
so go and sit next to her.
Be chattier.
I'm chatting right now.
Why is the seat
next to Ji Hyo empty?
- She looks lonely.
- She'd appreciate the space.
Hold on.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Could I sit next to you?
- Right. Sure thing.
- The seat's empty.
- But Jae Suk never sits there.
- Why though?
You're making her uncomfortable.
- In what way?
- She was enjoying the space.
She panicked just now.
- But I...
- You made her uncomfortable.
- But I've been her colleague...
- You took her by surprise.
for ten years.
- She was startled.
- We're close friends.
He's not the Grim Reaper.
- He's not the Grim Reaper.
- I like it here.
- No.
- Get back here.
Have us look balanced on camera.
- Bo Pil.
- Do we have a blanket?
Cover his legs
with a blanket, will you?
They're too skinny.
They're slender, not skinny.
- Gosh.
- Is this for your bagpipes?
Do you play the bagpipes?
You actually gave me one.
That's what I call good manners.
- It wasn't easy on the eyes.
- Must I use this all day?
Doesn't it look like
what they use in nursing homes?
This is much better.
He looks like an old Scottish man.
- It wasn't nice.
- Yes, an old Scottish man.
- So today...
- Since you're here, Jae Suk,
I'll head to the back.
Where are you off to?
Ji Hyo, where are you going?
- Are you battling over seats?
- Are we swapping seats?
Haha, you should sit here.
- No, don't.
- "How Do You Play?"...
Hold on a second.
There's no romance
on "How Do You Play?".
Yes, keep that seat vacant
and we'll see.
- I'll sit here.
- Seriously?
Should this seat stay empty?
- Yes, keep it empty.
- Why though?
Ji Hyo, then I'll...
- Stay in your seat!
- Let me head back there.
Just don't. What on earth is this?
There we go.
- Good.
- This wasn't my intention,
- but it ended up this way.
- This is much better.
Is this it though?
Don't we have a guest today?
Yes, we'll get going.
Call anyone nearby who's free today.
- At least one will be free.
- Why not?
But what for?
Nam Chang Hee will come over
in a heartbeat.
Chang Hee sounds like a good idea.
- He's only free until 4 p.m.
- I quite like him.
- Only until 4 p.m.
- Really?
- Why?
- He has a live radio show to host.
Mr. Radio
- What don't you tune into?
- Do you listen to that too?
- Even radio shows?
- Mr. Radio
He's unbelievable.
I'm just as amazed.
- That's not it.
- He knows about everything.
Why on earth do you watch
home-shopping channels?
- What about them?
- You have no idea.
- Why?
- It's hard...
- to associate him with them.
- They aren't for him.
- You don't like to shop.
- But you're on the channel.
He tunes in
when he stumbles onto one.
I watch the shows that Haha is on.
I didn't know you were selling
your budaejjigae...
- on home-shopping channels.
- I do.
Budaejjigae and pork cutlets.
You should tune in as well...
since he works hard
to make a living.
My wife loves
the pork cutlet he launched,
so she buys some every month.
What's the brand?
- It's his brand.
- What's its name?
The name is in three syllables.
Is it "Merry"?
(Did he say "Merry"?)
(Is it "Merry"?)
Merry Pork Cutlet.
How festive, right?
Merry Pork Cutlet!
Be merry!
Eating it will bring you joy.
Merry Pork Cutlet! It's not bad.
- Merry Pork Cutlet.
- It's hilarious.
Wait. What is this place?
- It's beautiful.
- Go on in.
I love the color scheme.
I see doughnuts!
(Colorful doughnuts
with cream fillings)
You're at a doughnut shop.
- Right.
- Hold on a second.
- I feel sick already.
- I know.
- I feel kind of sick.
- This place...
Their doughnuts are delicious.
- I've had a few before.
- Really?
We should at least
get beverages with them.
- We'll be giving out prize badges.
- Right.
But first, you'll play a team game
to decide the number of them.
- It's called Delivery.
- Delivery!
- I think we've done it before.
- Do you see those boxes?
- Yes.
Choose a box out of those...
that are worth different points
depending on its size.
You'll then have 30 seconds
to tear off the tape.
- But that's easy.
- Do we get a box cutter?
No. Just use your bare hands.
- You'll have 30 seconds.
- It's not easy.
- I can get it done.
- It's difficult.
- I bite my nails!
- We can do it.
We'll allow slight tearing
of the outer layer.
- The outer layer?
- But tear the box in any way...
and you'll have failed.
- Get 18 points to win 6 badges.
- A total of 18 points?
Getting 15 points
will give you 5 badges...
while getting 12 points
will give you 4 badges.
We'll have to go
with the bigger boxes.
- We need 18 points.
- Go for 5 points each.
Ripping off box tape...
- frustrates me.
- I'm terrible at this.
I normally use box cutters.
Using box cutters
is how you keep it neat.
I rip the box instead.
- The box itself?
- Right?
Jong Kook probably rips it apart.
But that's scary.
- This isn't what I do.
- It's frustrating.
How well is it taped?
- Let's see.
- It's completely doable.
No, it won't be easy.
Just so you know,
the level of taping...
- is on the slightly annoying side.
- See what I mean?
- Unbelievable.
- There are two layers.
- So what will it be?
- Seok Sam, take your pick.
- This.
- Old Scottish man will go first.
- Take a look at it first.
- That's not it.
- Start from the side.
Let me take a look. Oh, right here.
- Exactly.
- Follow that line.
- Ready...
- Hold on. Okay, now I'm ready.
Get set, go!
Hold on.
(The diaper smuggler
is familiar with delivery boxes.)
(Can his many years of experience
get him through the challenge?)
- Hold on.
- It's already over.
He's done for.
You can't rip the box.
This much is allowed.
(A big hole)
- Seriously?
- What are you doing?
That's not how you do it.
Why? I'm getting it done.
Sure, keep going.
- You're doing great.
- Hold on.
- This isn't what the game is.
- This much is allowed.
- Suk Jin...
- Come on.
This much is allowed.
- This is fine.
- Seriously?
- That's it. You got one side.
- Right.
But your time is up.
- This much is allowed.
- How can you be so weak?
- Unbelievable.
- What's the time?
- So...
- This isn't how it should be done.
- But I got it done.
- You didn't get all of it.
- He did it.
- You removed the tape,
but you put a hole in the box.
You ripped it.
- This isn't allowed.
- That's what I said.
You failed anyway
because of the remaining tape.
- Was I supposed to remove this?
- Of course.
- But I got it open.
- Isn't it obvious?
Let me have a go at it.
Unbelievable.
Jae Suk, go for four points.
No, three points.
The one with four points
will definitely be easier.
- Really?
- Yes.
How is this easier?
I'll get us some points first.
- Go ahead.
- Look.
- Look at me juggling the box.
- Nicely done.
- Are you seeing this?
- Nice.
You'll hit yourself in the mouth.
That's what he'll do again.
- Look at this.
- Are you kidding me?
Look at how he's enthusiastic...
- both on Saturday and Sunday.
- Take a look.
- Unbelievable.
- Are you seeing this?
That's what you call a professional.
All right.
- Let me take a look first.
- Ready...
- Wait.
- This isn't easy.
Get set...
You have enough time,
so don't rush it.
There's no need
to use a lot of force.
- No, use all the force you have.
- Put muscle into it.
- He's ripping it.
- Pull with all your might.
You annoying little box!
You're already done for.
Use your teeth.
You're doomed.
(The nation's top MC
shows his true nature.)
He won't be able to do it.
(Being desperate,
he uses his teeth.)
You're done for.
You need to do some shopping
to know how to remove packing tape.
- Darn it.
- This is what you get...
for showing off earlier.
- It's over for you.
- He's frustrated.
- What are you doing?
- What is this?
- It's over, Jae Suk.
It's still not coming off.
- Darn it!
- Are you kidding me?
Seriously?
- Jae Suk.
- What...
Let me try that once more.
Give me another chance.
You exhausted yourself
before the actual game.
- Let me try that once more.
- This is insane.
- It won't come off.
- Let me try it.
Hold on. Se Chan,
aren't you good at this?
I have longer nails,
so I'll go for five points.
- I have faith in him.
- This is the one.
I'm sorry.
- Se Chan...
- It's super frustrating.
Se Chan will try to win five points.
- We need the five points.
- I'm mapping it out.
Let me see
how I should go about this.
How many seconds do I have?
- Thirty seconds.
- Thirty?
No head starts are allowed.
- I was only checking.
- Don't be too uptight.
(The Italian petty offender
uses his petty skills.)
- Please get ready.
- Just a second.
- Get set...
- Hold on.
Okay, good. Nicely done.
He used his teeth.
(He used his teeth.)
There you go. Use your teeth.
What does he remind me of?
Oh, yes. A vole.
- He's a vole.
- Nice.
- Is this animal kingdom?
- Use your teeth!
There you go. Keep at it.
- We're watching a vole.
Nice!
Nice going with your teeth.
Yes, keep using your teeth.
- Yes, your teeth.
- No way.
Open! I got it.
It's open.
- Look to the side.
- The side.
- You're good.
- Unbelievable.
- You did it.
- Nice!
(The vole succeeded.)
- Nicely done.
- That was great.
Should my teeth be hurting?
You can't get it done
unless you use your teeth.
Try opening it
with just your strength.
It can't be done.
- No, it could be.
- You can open this...
- and I'll open this.
- So Se Chan...
- received five points.
- Five points?
Yes, five points.
- Jong Kook is next.
- Let me see.
Is it my turn?
- Cut it and then rip it off.
- Let me try again.
They've been taped differently.
This doesn't start on the side.
- Here you go.
- The top layer...
Hold on a second.
I was only giving him pointers.
Jong Kook,
that's where you should start.
- I should rip the side first?
- Right.
- How am I supposed to open this?
- You look like...
a boy who picks someone's pocket
at a dockside from some movie.
Watch your pockets.
From movies like "Titanic".
- Ready.
- Hold on.
Use your strength. I might get hurt
if I stay next to him.
I might get hurt
if I stay next to you.
You should use your strength.
- That's good. Use your teeth!
- That's good.
It seems too easy for him.
- It looks so easy for him.
- Use your hands. There you go.
- Goodness.
He's just ripping it.
(Halting)
Hey, where is it? Darn it!
Come out!
- It's annoying, right?
- Hey, you punk!
- Come out!
- Hit it with your fist.
- You punk!
- You can't break it!
(Smashed)
That's good.
(Trembling with fear)
- He smashed it!
- That's good!
That's good! Keep going!
- Keep going!
- You got it!
- The box is still in its shape.
- Punch it!
You punk!
- It's smashed.
- You punk!
- That's good.
- You brat.
- You're incredible.
- You're almost done.
You punk!
- That was close.
- You were almost done though.
- This...
- You were almost done.
- This comes out easily.
- You should've punched it...
- from the beginning.
- It's funny.
What do you mean it was close
when you crushed the box?
It's totally crushed.
I punched it too hard.
How long has it been
since you last punched something?
Wait a minute. This is...
- Let's go, Haha!
- The man of Sunday.
- What are you doing, Haha?
- Let's see how good you are!
Show some good performance
on Running Man, Haha!
I'm the man of Sunday!
Let's go!
From the "X-Man" days...
to Running Man!
Let's go!
That's good!
(He starts with determination.)
- He's fast. Use your teeth.
- That's good.
(Four points)
He got it.
- He got it.
- That's good.
(Nimble moves of the man of Sunday)
- He got it. He's almost done.
- He's good.
- Just a little more!
- It's the last piece.
- Just a bit more! The other side.
- The last piece.
I think he's done.
- I'm done.
- You forgot this part.
- I'm done!
- All right.
- Haha succeeded.
- All right!
The man of Sunday!
- He's the man of Sunday.
- I'm the man of Sunday.
You know me, right?
Hey, save your energy.
There's another shoot in three days.
Jae Suk told him
to save his energy.
- Yes.
- Didn't I do well?
You can do so well,
so why didn't you?
Next is Ji Hyo.
- You earned nine points so far.
- You punk.
Ji Hyo, are you okay?
Is your stomach okay?
I'm okay. I'll be okay...
- if I don't tighten my stomach.
- Don't hold your stomach.
Okay. I'll be okay as long as
I don't tighten my stomach.
Ready.
(How well will Ji Hyo
with enteritis open the box?)
Hey, start from there.
You're opening it so calmly.
- Hey.
- You're opening it so calmly.
You're pretty good.
(Her delicate movements
are accurate.)
(She's opening the box
with a kind smile.)
She's too calm.
Ji Hyo, it looks like you're opening
a parcel your boyfriend sent you.
You're cherishing it so much.
She's not going to make it.
- She's actually unboxing it.
- What are you doing?
She's actually unboxing a parcel.
- No, I'm not.
- You're not playing a game!
- You're just unboxing it.
- You're opening it too slowly.
"What could be inside the box?"
You don't have to rush.
- What's going on?
- She's almost done though.
Do you even know
how to play this game?
Are you opening
a Christmas gift or something?
You're not supposed to unbox it.
- She won't make it.
- There you go.
It was too...
- You were almost playing with it.
- Well done. She's done anyway.
Ji Hyo failed.
Why are you so generous with Ji Hyo?
You can't be okay with this.
Why are you strict to me
but not to her?
He finds you so adorable.
Hey, she's different from you.
You are...
Oh, right. She's different.
I agree with you.
Thank you, Jong Kook.
- She plays along with it.
- Thank you.
You have nine points so far,
but someone can play
in place of So Min.
- Then...
- I'll do it.
- No.
- You shouldn't play!
Just stay still!
- But...
- I'll be okay.
- Se Chan, you should do it.
- We don't have that many points.
Rat, I'll do it.
Jae Suk, use your teeth too.
Then we'll let you play
in place of So Min and Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo too?
- In place of Kwang Soo too?
Why would you do that?
- Hey.
- I have a lot to say to him.
- Why?
- What is it?
I watched the movie
he was recently in, "Sinkhole",
and it looked like he could've
made it out.
He could've made it out of the cab.
- That's right!
- But it's just a movie.
- It was more important for him...
- I mean...
"He could've made it out."
I was really upset with him
when I saw it.
It must've been upsetting.
He just wanted more screen time.
I haven't watched it though.
He just stalled for time.
Then...
You can play two more times.
Rat, you should play it.
Big Rat is going to do it instead.
- He's just a mouse.
- Is he?
- Are you going to use your teeth?
- I'm just a mouse.
If you're going to use them,
I'll let you play.
- I'll use my teeth then.
- Okay. Use your teeth.
- Okay.
- Let him play.
Let's see how well he does.
He's being playful again.
- Keep tossing it.
- Seriously.
Why would you waste your energy
before even starting?
He looks like a magician.
You'll be able to succeed
as long as you don't play with it.
He's a magician.
(He adds another character.)
(Making a fuss)
(He's number one when it comes to
wasting energy on useless things.)
He reminds me of the old comedian.
- Ready.
- Hold on.
If you succeed,
you'll earn another badge.
- Where is it?
- You need to check it first.
- Take a look at it first.
- Start from here.
(Mouse's second try)
- That's good.
- Darn it.
(What?)
(He made a mistake again
as soon as he began.)
Hold on.
I think he needs to start again.
- Gosh, that mouse.
- This is...
- No, this is... Hold on.
- Gosh, that mouse.
- I told you to check it first.
- No, I was just flustered.
Use your teeth!
(He attacks it with his buck teeth,
his secret weapon.)
That mouse. Wait, he opened it.
That mouse.
(He opened it at once?)
- He opened it.
- I'm almost done opening it.
You're not done.
Check the sides as well.
- There's nothing more.
- Check it thoroughly.
- He's done?
- Good job, Mouse.
- Nice!
- There's nothing more?
- Did he succeed?
- Show it to us.
Show us the other side.
- Where?
Where is it?
(Where?)
- No.
- There's nothing on it.
- There's nothing more.
- What's there?
- Where?
- There's nothing more.
- Where is he talking about?
There's nothing more.
- There's nothing more.
- You saw it wrong.
(The box vanished in the air
in no time.)
- The box...
- There's nothing on it, seriously.
- There's really nothing on it.
- He ripped it all.
- Go for it.
- He's amazing.
- I got it. I'm done.
- I'm done.
- Good job.
All right.
(Rat gave it a try next,
and succeeded in earning 2 points.)
- That was incredible.
- He finished it in 18 seconds.
- In 18 seconds?
- Wow, Rat.
- My mouth tastes like blood.
You've earned a total of 14 points,
and you've earned four badges.
- All right.
- That's good.
Well done, everyone.
(The winner of the next mission
will take all 4 badges.)
- Everyone.
- Yes?
Last week,
on Running Man's official Instagram,
we asked our followers to
write us questions...
that the members of Running Man...
will have a difficult time
answering.
We got a lot of comments.
We had about 7,000 comments.
- We got 7,000 comments?
- We selected a few from them...
and picked out the questions
you'll find difficult to admit.
- Really?
- This is...
We can just admit to them.
So those who admit
to the questions...
will need to give
a short explanation.
Oh, after admitting to the question?
You need to tell us why
you're admitting to it.
You can even make up
a reason to answer it.
- I can just admit to them.
- We're really cool with anything.
- Of course.
- But they must be on another level.
This will be a team match.
The team that admits
to more questions wins.
- Is it better to admit to them?
It's good for the team
if you admit to them.
Shall we divide into two teams
according to how we're seated?
Okay. Let's divide into teams
like this.
- For those questions...
- Just admit to them.
You should also tell us
why you admit to them.
It'll be fine as long as
the reasons are reasonable, right?
Is this supposed to be difficult?
I'll admit to most of them.
Okay.
Let's start with Suk Jin.
Me? Okay. I'll just admit to it.
Our viewers gave us these questions.
"I admit that I'm quite bad
with ad-libs as a comedian."
- Could you repeat it?
- Just admit it.
"I admit that I'm quite bad
with ad-libs as a comedian."
- I can't admit this.
- How many years has it been?
- I can't admit to this.
- He's been a comedian for 30 years.
- And he got a question like that?
You should admit to it.
- I can't admit to this.
- Gosh, this is difficult.
- You must admit to it.
- You should...
- Suk Jin!
- We're questions like this?
The questions are
from our viewers, right?
He's too proud to admit to it.
- I can't do it.
- But this is...
I'm really good with ad-libs.
- He's bad at them.
- No, I'm not.
He can just admit to it.
- Of course.
- I can't admit to it.
- Why wouldn't you admit to it?
- This is how the public thinks.
- You must admit to it.
- It's a bit strange...
that you can't admit to it.
How come? I can't admit to it.
I've been leading my career
with ad-libs.
It's clear that he's bad
with ad-libs...
because whenever
we criticize his outfit,
he goes,
"You don't know fashion at all."
- What else can I say to that?
- He's been saying it for two years.
- It's nothing new.
- He has no wit at all.
(Whenever he was criticized
for wearing something weird...)
It's all about challenging yourself.
Don't be afraid to try new outfits.
(Big Nose didn't come up
with any witty ad-libs.)
(He only told them that they
don't know what's fashionable.)
(He's been using the same comment
for 2 years.)
- Celebrities must dress like this.
- They're fluffy.
- Suk Jin.
- Your shorts are fluffy.
- His main strength is a monologue,
- Of course.
so he's bad with ad-libs.
Who doesn't use ad-libs
during a monologue?
You can understand it as
ad-libs for variety shows.
How can I do a monologue
without ad-libs?
- Let me tell you what it is.
- What?
- Ad-libs are all about being witty.
- Exactly.
- It's all about wit.
- You're a good talker.
- But you're not witty.
- No.
Being a good talker
and being witty are different.
- That's true.
- You punk.
You see? He should've come up
with an ad-lib to refute.
- Exactly.
- There's nothing...
- There's nothing to refute.
- Of course, there is.
When it comes to ad-libs...
Those who think I'm bad
with ad-libs, raise your hands.
- Raise your hands.
- He must admit to it.
All his life...
- I can't admit to it.
- Just admit to it!
- No, I won't.
- You're a good talker.
- I won't admit to it.
He didn't admit to it.
Being a good talker
means I'm good with ad-libs.
You won't earn any points
since he didn't admit to it.
- All right.
- Okay.
Next is Jong Kook.
- I have a few in my head.
- Jong Kook.
He'll get this question for sure.
I'm 100 percent sure
that we'll hear that word.
- It's guaranteed.
- I'm certain.
I'll admit to it if I can.
It's good for the team
if I admit to it.
- Here's the first one.
- I'll admit to it if I can.
- You'll get this question for sure.
- There's nothing hard about it.
"I actually find..."
"Ji Hyo really adorable."
("I actually find
Ji Hyo really adorable.")
- He finds her adorable even now.
- Gosh, you.
- She's adorable.
- You need to give a reason too.
She's adorable. Everyone is. Do you
find Suk Jin adorable or not?
- He's adorable.
- You can admit to this.
Jae Suk is adorable too.
- Ji Hyo and Se Chan are adorable.
- Yes.
I'm too. We're all adorable.
He finds her especially adorable
these days.
What's the question again?
"I actually find
Ji Hyo really adorable."
You find her really adorable.
You even want to bite her
because she's so adorable.
- She's just adorable.
- You want to hug her too.
- Everyone is adorable.
- You even want to bite her.
If you admit to it,
you need to state your reason too.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- She is adorable.
- Of course.
- Are you admitting to it? Lift it.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- She's adorable.
- All right!
Why do you find her adorable?
She has plump cheeks,
so she's adorable.
What about her behavior?
Of course, she's cute.
When she did the "Rollin'" dance,
I was really surprised.
- You find her so adorable?
- Yes. She's really adorable.
- Of course.
- She's become really cute.
You're totally into me.
He's deep in love with you.
- She's really adorable.
- Honey.
- "Honey"?
- There are times I find her cute.
- "Honey".
- Honey.
- You admitted the first question.
- Yes.
All right.
"I've dated a guest I met
on a show."
Darn it. Hey!
("I've dated a guest I met
on a show.")
- I'm really curious though.
- You need to be honest.
This isn't about my opinion.
It's saying a fact.
- Jong Kook is incredible.
- You can tell us if it's true.
If you don't admit to it...
If it's not true,
then you don't have to admit to it.
- You can just not admit to it.
- Stay still.
- But this is...
- You should reduce the standard...
- They should ask me a question...
- that needs my opinion.
- of dating.
You've been on variety shows
for a long time.
I have, but...
- You can just not admit to it.
- But this is...
It could've been just flirting.
- Between Ji Hyo and you...
- No, it's dating.
They practically dated each other.
Are you talking about Eun Hye?
- Stop it!
- I mean...
- There will be other questions.
- There will be?
- I'm just curious.
- Let's wait a bit.
- Jong Kook.
I only made it clearer.
That's not it. This way,
I can't admit to it.
Let's wait a bit.
Goodness, this is frustrating.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Here.
He didn't admit to it. It's okay.
Your face is really red.
What? It's hot in here.
Why is it so hot in here?
This time, we'll ask Jae Suk
a question.
- Me? All right.
- Great.
- You can admit to all of them.
- Come on.
Just admit to all of them.
I can admit to all of them.
You have everything. What's so hard
about admitting to them?
- I'll admit to all five questions.
- You have everything.
- Okay. Let's start.
- What's there not to admit?
"I..."
"admit to all secrets of my body..."
"that were mentioned on shows."
("I admit to all secrets of my body
that were mentioned on shows.")
You should admit to them.
- They're really adorable.
- Of course, he should admit to it.
They're cute.
It's true.
- They're really cute.
- It's true.
- Just admit to it.
- It's the mystery of the human body.
- Just admit to them.
- His body is really mysterious.
- Hey.
- I thought he was Dream.
- He thought you were Dream.
- Ji Hyo.
He thought you were Dream.
Ha Dream. Dream?
- Sit down.
- Hey!
- You want me to admit to it?
- Just admit to it.
- I can't admit to it.
- You have everything!
- Hey!
- What's wrong with it?
- You want me to admit to it?
- Just admit to it.
- Ji Hyo.
Don't try so hard to deny it.
- I'm not trying to deny it.
- Don't try so hard to deny it.
It's what So Min made up.
That's right.
She called it a sweet potato.
How can it be so exaggerated when
it's just a rumor that she started?
Many of his body secrets
were revealed on shows.
That's not all.
- That's right.
- You're low-chested too.
They're talking
about your low chest.
I can admit to my low chest,
but it's just not true!
- No, that's...
- I won't admit to it.
- Why not?
- Just admit to it.
I won't admit to it.
It's just not true.
- Just admit to it.
- It's just not true.
- You said you'd admit to it all.
He didn't admit to it.
It's good for us.
- My gosh.
- Oh, right. It's good for us.
- It's good for us.
- It is.
"Running Man lasted
for 11 long years,"
"and it's all thanks to me."
- The thing is... Listen.
- But this isn't right.
But you understand
what this game is about, right?
Don't get confused.
You can just admit to it.
- Actually...
- He's going to admit to it.
- I think he'll admit to it.
- You're going to admit to this?
- What about us?
- He did everything.
If he admits to this,
just change the title
to Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man.
You know how hard he worked
in the beginning.
But I need to admit to this
for our team.
- That's right.
- I must admit to it.
- Of course.
- Even if you admit to it,
- If I don't admit to it...
- many people will agree.
- You deserve to admit to it.
- I admit to it!
- There you go.
Yoo Jae Suk's...
- Running Man!
(Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man)
It sounds so smooth.
Don't walk but run!
Please tell us why
you think that way.
- Right. You need to tell us why.
- Just tell them a reason.
- We contributed nothing?
- It needs to be convincing.
I guess we meant nothing to you.
- We were just...
- I guess we were nothing.
- Look at all these scars.
- We didn't contribute at all?
I'm not saying that I did everything
on my own.
That means
you're not admitting to it.
- Then change your answer.
- You're not admitting to it.
It's all thanks to you.
How should I say it?
You need to be brazen.
It can't be helped.
- That's right.
- You can say that I did everything.
(You can say that I did everything.)
- Okay?
- Give us an example.
- Like what?
- There are just too many.
You can say that I did everything.
- There you go!
- He's right.
- That's all.
- Let's move on.
All right, then.
(Team Jae Suk earns a point
by admitting Jae Suk's hard work.)
"I..."
"admit from
the bottom of my heart..."
"that I'm the ugliest member
of Running Man."
You must admit to this.
This is the easiest.
- What's there to think?
- This isn't hard at all.
- It's a simple question.
It's disadvantageous to us.
But do you think you're uglier
than Se Chan?
But that's a given. Haha.
- You can't admit to that.
- Just admit to it.
As long as you're okay with it,
it's fine.
Jae Suk, take off your glasses
and see for yourself.
I'm not so sure.
Jae Suk, look who's sitting
next to you.
Don't forget
that you have buck teeth.
Look at him.
At least my teeth are straight.
Take off your hat.
I know that we both have
protruding mouths.
(The man who straightened his teeth
is bragging to buck teeth.)
(What a sight.)
- Jae Suk.
- You're going to admit to that?
Your teeth are really straight.
- Yes, they are.
- I think...
- That's why I look better.
- Besides Se Chan,
I think you're worse than me.
It's baffling to see
how brazen you are.
- What do you mean?
- It's baffling.
Look at him.
I find you baffling too.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
- He has guts.
- You're not that good-looking too.
- Still, this is...
- He thinks he's good-looking.
I can't admit to this.
If I take it too seriously,
if I don't admit to them,
we can't win.
- Of course.
- That's that, but...
You can just admit
that you're the ugliest.
- Then he shouldn't admit to it.
- Admit that you're the ugliest.
- I admit to it.
- He admitted to it.
- Tell us why you think you're...
- If you admit to this,
this will be on the record.
- Of course.
- Tell us a reason.
- He admitted to it.
- Tell us why you think...
you're uglier than me.
- Which part and why?
- He admitted to it.
He admitted to it already.
From today on, the ugliest member
of Running Man...
- is Jae Suk.
- Yes. It became a fact.
You're actually more handsome
than him, right?
- Of course.
- You need to tell us...
which parts of Suk Jin and Se Chan
are better looking than yours.
- Tell us.
- That's right.
- Darn it!
- Honestly,
- I'm pretty decent looking.
- That's true.
But this is... Do I have to
say it specifically?
- Of course.
- You need to tell us a reason.
Of course, since you admitted to it.
(Tell us one good-looking part
of Se Chan.)
Tell us one good-looking part
of Se Chan.
Here.
(Here.)
Go ahead. Which part of me
do you find handsome?
He just shut his eyes.
Which part of me
do you find handsome?
He needs to compliment
Suk Jin as well.
He's not telling us the reason.
That means he didn't admit to it.
This is the worst.
Come on. Tell us.
- Tell us.
- Your gums are really pink.
Are they? Okay. Tell us.
- Well...
- Parts that are better than yours.
Well, you are...
- Am I much better?
- Which part?
You find me much better?
- Which part do you find handsome?
- Are you jealous of me?
(Catfish induces Jae Suk
to compliment him.)
- Which part of him?
- I have something...
that you don't have, right?
I can't admit to this!
- No!
- I can't admit to this!
I can't do this! I can't find it!
It looks like he really can't
admit to it.
- I really can't do this!
- He couldn't say anything.
No matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't find a part
that's better than mine.
- That's good.
- I can't admit to this!
- This is good.
- Well done.
I ended up provoking him.
He didn't admit to it. Great.
He didn't admit to it.
- Let's move on to Ji Hyo.
- Me?
- You can admit to all five of them.
- It was really hard.
- Admit to all of them.
- You need to admit to all of them.
- Okay.
- You need to admit...
to at least three of them.
All right.
"I..."
"can name the 12 months
of the year in English..."
"since I set it as my wallpaper
on my phone."
If you admit to it,
you have to name them all.
She must name them.
You must name them all
if you admit to it.
- She knows. January, February...
- I won't ask you to spell them.
You can just name them.
January, Febury...
Just name them all.
- "Febury"?
- I'm just saying it as an example.
- It's just an example.
- What do you mean by "Febury"?
- Just admit to it first.
Just laugh about it.
- You...
- No. We will check if it's true.
I admit it.
- She admits it.
- Go ahead.
- It won't count if she fails.
- Try it.
(They will check
the veracity of her words.)
- The 1st month.
- Start with the 1st month.
Don't do it.
Don't tell her.
Go ahead.
Go ahead. January.
(Will Ji Hyo be able
to say the 12 months in English?)
- Ja.
- There you go.
- You studied.
- Ja.
- What comes next?
- January.
- There you go.
- Okay.
February.
- February.
- She knows.
- Ji Hyo studied.
- You memorized them.
I deny it.
(She suddenly denies it!)
You memorized them.
I deny it.
(The English calendar stops
at February.)
- She couldn't get past February.
- There we go.
You memorized them.
I just memorized the latter months.
She is so cute.
(This man finds her cute as well.)
That was so funny.
Next.
"My ideal type of man
is Kim Jong Kook,"
"and he makes my heart flutter."
(My ideal type of man is Kim Jong Kook,
and he makes my heart flutter.)
- Hey.
- Answer with seriousness.
- This one is...
- Ji Hyo.
- She isn't averse to it these days.
- It's okay.
There hasn't been
an official question like this one.
Just admit it. He is charming...
- Admitting it...
- He said that you were charming.
will put Jong Kook in a pickle.
- It's Ji Hyo's one-sided love.
- Isn't that right?
It's just how you feel.
It's not like you will confess,
so it doesn't matter.
Your heart should flutter even now.
The statement says,
"He makes my heart flutter."
- No.
- Suk Jin is right.
- It's "He makes my heart flutter."
- Really?
Then it can stop fluttering
tomorrow.
- That's right.
- It will flutter just for today.
That's impossible.
Why is that possible?
- It can stop fluttering tomorrow.
- Come on.
- I don't know.
- That's ridiculous.
It can stop fluttering tomorrow.
This is...
- a matter of Ji Hyo's pride.
- That's right.
- I foresee many articles.
- This isn't about the character.
- I foresee many articles this week.
- That's right.
- You need to reveal why...
he makes your heart flutter.
You need to reveal why
I am your ideal type.
The moment will pass.
Just say your heart flutters...
when he smiles at you.
- You need to reveal the details.
- Just say something like that.
- Don't control her.
- What?
- My goodness.
- "Don't control her."
I didn't control her.
I just gave her advice.
Hold up the "I admit it" sign.
- I admit it.
- Okay.
(She admits it.)
Okay. Reveal the details.
(Okay. Reveal the details.)
Reveal why I am your ideal type.
- What do you like about him?
- Reveal it.
Hold on.
Why are you telling her to do that?
- She needs to give her reasons.
- Does he make your heart flutter?
What is up with you?
- Are you excited?
- She needs to give her reasons.
- Why are you excited?
- She admitted it.
- She admitted it,
- so she needs to give her reasons.
- Well...
- Go on.
- Everything she says will be real.
Reporters, take notes.
He urged the reporters
to take notes.
(The reasons why Jong Kook makes
Ji Hyo's heart flutter)
- Just say it.
- He is dependable.
- She likes dependable men.
- He looks after me.
- He looks after you.
He eats well.
He drives a Mercedes-Benz G-class.
He lives in Apgujeong-dong.
Really?
"He lives in Apgujeong-dong."
- He has so many charms.
- Seriously.
- That counts.
Why do I make your heart flutter?
- What?
- Tell him the reasons.
(Why do I make your heart flutter?)
- What is up with him?
- Tell him the reasons.
- Listen.
- She needs to answer that too.
- Talk among yourselves.
- Do you want to hear more?
- I mean...
she should reveal
why I make her heart flutter.
Call her if you want to hear more.
- I will call you later.
- That's right.
That counts. Haha is up next.
I will admit it
no matter what the statement is.
- Let's do that.
- This is getting boring.
"I am 168cm tall."
Hey, I am 171.5cm tall.
Hey!
(He denies it
in the speed of light.)
- Hey!
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Hey.
- I am 171.5cm tall.
- Think about it.
If I am in a good condition,
I am 172cm tall.
Think about it.
That's my actual height.
There is no way you are 172cm tall.
- Seriously.
- I am 172cm tall.
- Yoon Jong Shin...
and Jang Hang Jun admitted it.
- I give hope to Shorry.
- Don't say anything.
- Why won't he admit it?
- He denied it.
I give hope to Shorry.
I am the tallest
among the short ones.
You should admit this one.
Jong Kook, I can't do that.
- There isn't much of a difference.
- Jong Kook.
I am the only celebrity...
whose height is in the tenth digit
on the search engine profile.
- It means a lot to me.
- Hey.
What's your exact height?
I am 171.5cm tall.
- Haha, I am 172cm tall.
- If I am in a good condition...
You are 177cm tall, you punk.
No, I am not.
I am 172cm tall.
Let's measure his height.
If I am in a good condition...
- I am serious.
- So you deny it.
I am serious.
- The next team.
- You should think about the team.
I would admit to anything
but this one.
He doesn't think about the team.
Anything but this one.
(Haha is past
the statement about his height.)
"My YouTube channel..."
"isn't worth watching."
- I deny it.
- Hey.
Hey!
I can't admit it.
If I were to rank...
the importance,
this is the most important.
- Haha PD is the most important.
- Hey.
After that comes Running Man...
and How Do You Play?.
I put my life on my YouTube channel.
Are you out of your mind?
(He puts his life on anything.)
I can't admit it.
- Just admit it.
- I can't.
- This is the most important.
- Hey.
- Se Chan is the last one.
- Se Chan.
- Jae Suk.
This is meaningless to me.
I will admit five statements.
They can't be that bad.
- Go ahead.
- This is meaningless to me.
All right.
"After watching closely
for four years,"
"I don't know why
Yoo Jae Suk is the national host."
For goodness' sake.
I don't know who came up
with that statement.
- Admit it.
- I can't admit it.
My colleagues and junior comedians
will watch this.
- You are a great host.
- Admit it.
That isn't important.
If I admit it,
I won't have anything to say.
Who raised you?
You did well on your own,
but someone helped you.
Just admit it.
Is that what you really think?
- That statement...
- I guess...
comedians say that when they meet up
for "Comedy Big League".
- Hey.
- You thought he was legendary.
But after a few years,
you realized that he isn't so great.
For attacking Jae Suk once,
- Yes, I remember.
- I struggled for three years.
- That's right.
- Three years.
Just deny it.
I deny it. I can't admit it.
- Come on.
- I can't. I deny it.
- I deny it.
- You deny it.
- Okay.
- That's good.
"I want..."
"to quit Jong Kook's soccer club
because paying the fee is..."
"a waste of money."
(I want to quit
Jong Kook's soccer club...)
(because paying the fee is
a waste of money.)
(I am sure he will deny it.)
I bet you think
it's a waste of money.
- Hold on.
- I bet you do.
You were a struggling comedian.
I bet you think
it's a waste of money.
- Se Chan.
- Is it 50 dollars...
Is it 50 dollars
for people in their 30s?
- Se Chan.
- It's 40 dollars.
You pay 40 dollars
even though you don't go there.
You play golf all the time
even though it's expensive.
- You have to make up your mind.
- That's right.
- Just admit it.
- Explain yourself then.
- Say why you think it's a waste.
You know how serious Jong Kook is
about soccer.
I will make an announcement
in the group chat room.
I will say
that Se Chan wants to quit.
- You won't quit anyway.
- You pay the fee every month.
- Jong Kook is joking around.
I don't know what to do.
"Se Chan..."
- "Se Chan wants to quit."
- He thinks it's a waste of money.
I will do it.
- You think it's a waste of money.
- Admit it.
I don't think...
I admit it.
Okay.
I don't think it's a waste of money.
- Okay.
- Please take his phone.
We are filming.
- We are filming.
- Hold on.
- Listen.
- I will make an announcement.
- I mean...
- "Se Chan..."
Hold on. Don't go that far.
Let go of me.
- "Se Chan..."
- Jong Kook.
- "will quit."
- Don't do that.
Come on.
- I did it to win a point.
- "He will quit."
It's a good opportunity.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- "Se Chan will quit."
I sent the message
to the group chat room.
"Se Chan will quit."
- I sent the message.
- I did it to win a point.
- To be honest...
- Give your reasons.
- He doesn't want to quit.
That's right.
(Chuckling)
- Does the club embarrass you?
- Is it bothersome?
- You like golf, but not soccer.
You like golf, but...
The thing is,
I pay 40 dollars.
I gave it some thought.
Even when we didn't meet up
due to COVID-19,
- we paid the fees.
- Of course.
- Hey.
- Fees are like that.
You pay 250 dollars at a time
to play golf.
- Is 40 dollars too much?
- Hold on.
Hold on.
- Is 40 dollars a month too much?
- Hold on.
- No. That's not what he is saying.
- How can you say that?
Are you saying
Jong Kook stole the money?
(Are you saying
Jong Kook stole the money?)
Is that what you are saying?
I can't believe it.
That's what you are saying.
How could you say that?
Why did you kick the hornet's nest?
That's what you are saying.
- Me?
- That's what you are saying.
- I didn't steal anything.
- You are saying...
he stole 40 dollars from everyone...
- and put it in his pocket.
- I pay 100 dollars.
Hold on. I know that you pay
a lot of money.
I will explain.
To be honest,
I do like golf better these days.
That's why...
- Jong Kook.
- He is serious.
- That's how he really feels.
- Hey.
Sit down.
This is annoying.
(Laughing)
- Please cover for me.
- Don't worry.
You should cover for me,
not laugh about this.
- I will cover for you. Don't worry.
- Please do that.
- Jong Kook.
- How will you cover for him?
What do you know about soccer?
How will you cover for him?
- How will you do that?
- Hurry up and cover for me.
How will you do that?
I will play soccer
in Se Chan's stead.
(I will play soccer
in Se Chan's stead.)
(He will be a substitute.)
Will you play soccer in his stead?
- That works.
- I will do that.
- Really?
- I will play soccer.
- That works.
- Okay.
The fee is 70 dollars
for people in their 50s.
- But...
- He should pay 100 dollars.
- You should pay 100 dollars.
- I will pay 100 dollars.
- Okay.
- Pay 100 dollars a day.
- That's so funny.
The money will be used
to pay for beverages...
and snacks.
I admitted it for a point.
I will bring a member.
Here comes the next statement.
The statements are intense.
"To me, Suk Jin is
a great man and a role model."
- Deny it.
- I totally deny it.
(He doesn't hesitate.)
A great man, my foot!
There is nothing to learn.
(He can't admit
that Suk Jin is a great man.)
There is nothing to learn.
I deny it.
I don't need to say anything else.
It's a waste of time.
This is a statement we should skip.
- A great man?
- He said, "A great man, my foot!"
- "A great man, my foot!"
- "My foot"?
He is just an old man.
- He is just an old man.
- An old man.
(They received
all of the statements.)
As a result,
- the score is 7 to 7.
- Is it a tie?
- Really?
- Within the teams...
- The winners are the ones...
- Three.
who admitted three statements,
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- Thank goodness.
All right.
Here comes the food.
- We are okay so far.
- We are okay.
This place has tasty doughnuts.
(Here come the doughnuts.)
The basic one is tasty.
This one is tasty too.
(There is sweetness
both inside and outside.)
These are the doughnuts...
you would see in a cartoon.
(You can feel the sweetness
by looking at the doughnut set.)
My goodness.
I don't think I can eat them.
Here come the cold kimchi noodles.
(The cold kimchi noodles are served
for Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
- All right.
- Give me some.
I will eat a lot.
(Penalty balls will be added
if they leave food behind!)
Do we need to finish
the drinks as well?
Yes.
Why?
(They eat diligently
to avoid the penalty badges.)
- It's so sweet.
- It's really tasty.
Eat this.
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook have
cold kimchi noodles.)
This is really hard.
I haven't had
something so sweet recently.
Let's receive the penalty badge.
We can't finish them.
These are too sweet for me.
You can choose the next menu
in advance.
Cold buckwheat noodles.
That would be a good dish.
I want it.
It reached his mouth right away.
- Thank you for the food.
- Let's eat it.
It's okay.
(They clear the bowl easily.)
Keep eating.
It looks tasty.
It's too rich for me.
I am practically dying over here.
It is quite rich.
- You couldn't finish the food.
- No.
The three of you will receive
an additional penalty ball.
I like such dishes.
(It's the last mission place,
C pizza place in Shinsa-dong.)
It's the last step to become
ladies and gentlemen.
It's the Empty Head
English Speed Game.
(The Empty Head English Speed Game)
- There is no hope.
- We need So Min for this.
- So Min.
- She would have made me look good.
- We need So Min for this.
- So Min.
One member will give the question...
and five members will answer.
The member
who gets the correct answer...
will pick the next person
to ask the question.
Then that member
will ask the next question.
Can you pick the same person?
- It doesn't matter.
- I see.
But we distributed the points
to match the English skills.
If you answer Jong Kook's question,
you will only receive one point.
(Jong Kook's question
is worth 1 point.)
Jae Suk and Suk Jin's questions
are worth two points.
If you answer their questions...
- I should be in that group.
- They are good.
(He is brazen.)
- Haha.
- I am not in Se Chan's group.
Haha, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan's
questions are worth three points.
No way.
(Haha is upset
that he is on Se Chan's level.)
They divided up the members.
I am not in his group.
- Haha is slightly better.
- He is an ace player.
Haha and Ji Hyo's questions
should be worth three points...
and Se Chan's questions
should be worth five points.
Seriously. My questions
Okay. Let's do this.
You will play the game
for five minutes.
The number of badges
you receive will match...
the number of questions
you answer correctly.
So you can win up to five badges.
After five minutes,
the winner will be decided.
- Okay.
- Okay. We understand.
Let's try to get
the three-point question right.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo's question.
Ji Hyo's question.
- Will Ji Hyo go first?
- I am on Ji Hyo's level,
- so I can understand her better.
- Ji Hyo.
- You can't use gestures.
- Make it easy.
- Okay.
- Ready.
- Tell us about the subject first.
Set.
Go.
- What?
- Go.
(Sighing)
- What?
- Is it difficult?
Is it difficult?
Son.
- Sun.
- Son.
Sun. A four-character idiom?
- Land.
- You can't...
- speak Korean.
- Rice cake.
Rice cake?
Patbingsu. Dessert.
- Tteokguk?
- No.
I guess it's tteokguk.
- Food?
- Listen.
(The answer is revealed.)
- Food.
- Sun?
Songpyeon.
- Son.
- It's the sun.
- Sun and rice?
- Rice cake.
One more.
- One more?
- I see.
Sun and rice?
- New year.
- Gosh, son!
- What?
- "Gosh, sun?"
You should give an answer.
Are you saying S-O-N or S-U-N?
- You mean a son?
- S-U-N.
- Sun?
- Oh, it's S-O-N.
- I see. It's a son.
- I see.
Son.
Boy.
- Boy.
- Boy bread?
- Boy rice cake.
- Son rice cake.
Son and daughter.
It's no use raising
sons and daughters.
(It's no use raising
sons and daughters.)
Live happily
with sons and daughters.
- Gosh.
- What about a son?
- What?
- Say something.
Is it a proverb?
- It's a proverb.
- I get it.
- Son and daughter.
- Birthday cake.
You give an extra rice cake
to someone you hate.
That's right.
- Is that it?
- How could it be...
- I don't get it.
- Hey, you should've said "hate".
- You should say "hate".
- Let's move on.
- Tell us who will go next.
- Move on.
Hurry. We don't have time.
- The one with the highest scores.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Rice cake? My gosh.
- Here we go!
- What?
(Here we go!)
What?
- Celebrity?
- Yes. Celebrity.
- Celeb.
- An American celeb.
Do you know... Coin?
(Coin and an American celeb)
- Yes.
- Bit Coin.
- It is...
- Coin.
- Bit Coin.
- Elon Musk.
- Yes! Haha.
- It's Elon Musk.
I knew you'd pick me.
- I didn't recall his name.
- Elon Musk.
- Let me start.
- A celebrity?
(Haha who claims to be different
from Se Chan goes next.)
Another celeb?
(Corrupt official)
(It's not easy to explain.)
Difficult?
- Difficult?
- It's a job.
- Job?
- A job name.
- Joseon.
- Yes.
- Undercover emissary.
- No.
- A policeman?
- A four-syllable word.
- Yes.
- Duck.
- What?
- Duck?
- Let me answer.
(Corrupt official!)
- Corrupt official!
- Jae Suk was fast.
- I got it, right?
- I said I'd answer.
- I was faster.
That doesn't make sense.
You should give me
a chance to answer.
- You're like a corrupt official.
- No.
This is ridiculous.
Stop it, Mr. Underpants.
- Why are you being like this?
- I said I'd answer.
I'll give both of you the point.
Okay.
All right. It's a celeb.
- A celeb?
- Yes.
(The celebrity of the century,
Einstein)
- Yes.
- No gestures.
- Okay.
- No moves.
Helicobacter pylori?
- What?
- Let me answer.
- Pasteur.
(Pasteur, Metchnikoff)
- It's almost the same.
- Same?
- Something like that.
- Five syllables.
- A five-syllable word.
- The name is almost the same.
- Yes.
- A Korean celeb.
- Okay.
A member of MSG Wannabe.
- KCM?
- No.
No? Gosh.
Let me answer. Einstein.
- Yes.
- What?
- What? Einstein?
- I was going to say that.
How is it Einstein?
What does Einstein have to do
with Helicobacter pylori?
- It's math.
- It sounds similar.
- Einstein.
- Okay. Well done. Thank you.
- Who's next?
- Haha.
- Okay.
- I hope it's a celebrity.
I should've said Einstein.
- A celeb.
- A celeb?
No celeb? A celeb?
(It's like a default question.)
- A four-syllable word.
- Okay.
I guess it's a four-character idiom.
- The first word.
- Yes.
Gold.
- Gold.
- Adding flowers to embroidery.
Gold.
(- Gold.
- Adding flowers to embroidery.)
Returning home in glory.
(Returning home in glory)
(The empty heads
understand each other.)
Empty.
- Empty.
- That's the only word I know.
How did he know that?
(Next up is Jae Suk who is
tired of the silly explanations.)
- Yes.
- Yes. A four-syllable word?
A celeb?
- This is fun.
- It's a proverb.
- Okay. Yes.
- A proverb.
- Right.
Eat eggs.
Hitting a rock with an egg.
Eat birds.
- Birds.
- Eat birds, eat eggs.
- Eat eggs.
- Birds that get up early...
- Eat eggs, eat rocks.
- Let me answer.
- Eating a pheasant and its eggs.
- That's right.
(They can answer no matter
how lame the explanation is.)
- Who?
- My gosh.
All right. Se Chan.
- Eating a pheasant and its eggs?
- How did you know that?
- That was unbelievable.
- Let's go.
(What about this time?)
We're pretty good.
- Bird.
- Bird's foot.
Bird.
(Bird!)
- Bird's foot?
- Blood in a bird's foot.
Correct.
(They got it right
only with two words.)
(He's even more surprised
by the answer.)
(It is a good thing
that they don't know many words.)
(This is so easy for them.)
- Bird's foot?
- Bird's foot.
- A bird's foot.
- Haha is next.
- Okay.
- Blood in a bird's foot.
- Bird's foot.
- Haha, please begin.
Oh my gosh.
- Long?
- A celeb.
- Yes.
- My sister, Ji Hyo.
Favorite...
- American.
- An American celeb?
- Superstar.
- Superstar?
- Michael Jackson?
- Yes.
(An American superstar?)
(Madame Curie is
a French scientist.)
- Why you...
- Married.
- Married?
(The reason why Madame Curie
is Ji Hyo's favorite superstar...)
(Episode 460,
what's your favorite book?)
(Ji Hyo said "Madame Oat".)
(Ji Hyo's favorite biography,
"Madame Oat")
(Ji Hyo's favorite superstar)
(Mrs. Curie)
- Well...
- Beyonce.
- No.
- Married?
Very smart.
Ji Hyo should know that.
I get it. Madame Curie!
Yes!
(The empty heads' telepathy again)
- Yes!
- How did he know that?
It was a lucky guess.
- Madame Curie.
- Madame Curie?
Okay. Madame Curie.
- Ji Hyo...
- Madame Curie?
- She said Madame Oat.
- Right. Ji Hyo likes her.
It's Madame Oat.
- My gosh. It's long.
- This is fun.
- Long.
- It's a long word.
- Four.
- A four-syllable word?
- No, it's long.
- Long.
- Four?
- Four.
Ball.
- Marbles.
Let me answer.
Too many cooks spoil the broth.
- Nice.
- My gosh.
This is working.
How did he figure that out?
- Four balls?
- Okay.
He's good at this.
Good.
- My goodness.
- Why?
- A very famous movie.
- Celeb?
- Movie.
- It's a movie.
A three-syllable word.
- Three syllables.
- Yes.
- Vegetarian.
- Let me answer.
"Parasite".
- No.
- Vegetarian?
Yes. Vegetarian.
"Minari".
(Minari!)
(How did he know that?)
Yes! "Minari".
I just can't do this.
I know.
(The game is over after
a series of surprising answers.)
- Vegetarian?
- Vegetarian.
- "Minari".
- I'll announce the results.
- I bet Jae Suk wins.
No.
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- Right.
The winner is Jae Suk.
(1st place Yoo Jae Suk)
Jae Suk answered most
of the three-point questions.
He answered all my questions.
- Right. He did.
- I also answered many questions.
- We will bring in the last dish.
- Okay.
(The last dish has
a lot of cheese on it.)
- It looks delicious.
- Look at the cheese.
- It has a lot of cheese.
- This is amazing.
This is great for the first meal.
It would be nice to bring it home
and eat it with my family.
That's a lot of cheese.
Is that one piece?
- It's big.
- It's like a whole pizza.
- It's as big as a whole pizza.
- This can't be a piece.
This is Italian pizza.
The dough is focaccia.
- Fucaccia?
- Focaccia.
- Fuca what?
- It's Italian bread.
- Focaccia.
- Celeb?
- Focaccia?
(Jae Suk enjoys ramyeon and coffee
with Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
This is good.
- It's good.
- It's spicy though.
(He finished ramyeon immediately
enjoying the taste of Korea.)
It's spicy
because of Cheongyang chili.
(He finished ramyeon immediately
enjoying the taste of Korea.)
Do you have a hot sauce?
(Se Chan, Suk Jin, and Haha
enjoy the huge pizza.)
Gosh, Italy?
Italy?
This is so greasy.
It's good though.
It would've been nice
if this was my first meal.
It is good, but I can't eat it.
It is delicious,
but I can't eat it now.
Let me answer the results
of today's race then.
Gosh, I'm so full.
The two members with the most badges
won't get the penalty.
What matters is
who will get the penalty.
The member with the most badges
is Yoo Jae Suk.
(Yoo Jae Suk wins 1st place.)
And the second place will
receive the same benefit.
- Is it Ji Hyo?
- It's Song Ji Hyo.
(The 2nd place is Song Ji Hyo.)
Right. He won first place earlier.
The prize is the Italian
food ingredient set for you...
to enjoy the Italian dishes you
didn't get to eat during the race.
That sounds great.
That's a lot.
My children like to make
dishes like this these days.
- It will be fun to cook with them.
- Right.
The penalty is...
a water slap that will
help you digest.
You will pick a penalty ball.
The first person to be picked
will get water slaps.
The next two people
will give water slaps.
Jong Kook has two penalty balls.
Suk Jin has four.
Haha has 3, and Se Chan has 3.
Even if I have only one ball,
I can still get picked.
- I hope it's not me.
- Please.
I picked one.
- I have a hunch that it's me.
- You do it then.
- It's probably me.
It's me, right?
- All right.
- I bet it's me.
- The person to get a penalty...
- It feels strange.
- I guess it's me.
- No way.
Is it Seok Sam?
- It must be me.
- Or me?
The person to get a penalty...
It's me, right?
is Haha.
(Haha will be given the water slap.)
Weren't you confident earlier?
Are you receiving the penalty?
- The celebrity.
- You're a celebrity.
And you'll be receiving the penalty.
Are you receiving the penalty?
Is Haha receiving the penalty?
- Who will be splashing the water?
- Here we go.
- Okay.
- It's Suk Jin.
(Se Chan and Suk Jin
will spray the water.)
Would you like
to check the temperature?
Check the temperature.
- All right. That's good.
- Good?
- Okay.
- Yes, all right.
- You made a good duo today.
- Look at Suk Jin.
You and I...
look like we're here
for this purpose only.
- As professionals in the field.
- Right.
(Body scrubbers from Italy)
It can be Gangnam or anywhere else.
We'll be there.
We serve you for just five dollars.
Do you need
to relieve yourself of stress?
Stress?
Do you need to blow off some steam?
Our water slap...
will blast away your stress!
Call us at any time!
- For just five dollars.
- Call us.
- Go.
- Let's go.
There you go.
- That was right on his face.
- Let's go.
(The cold water slap
pushes down all the heavy cheese.)
- Okay!
- That was right on his face.
Good job, everyone.
What now?
My gosh!
"It's your last chance..."
"to turn your life around
by winning a big cash prize."
"Will you participate
in the Webfoot Octopus Game?"
Webfoot Octopus Game?
(Webfoot Octopus Game)
What's going on?
- That startled me.
- Welcome to the Webfoot Octopus Game.
It's the Webfoot Octopus Game.
- What on earth?
- What is this?
Why? I'm Han Mi Nyeo.
- There.
- Are you the captain?
- He's Il Nam.
- Hey.
- Hey!
- What do you mean?
- Let go of me!
- Wait.
- You can't take everything.
- Let go of me!
I was robbed.
- What's going on?
- Why do I need to die?
- Wait.
- I'll get rid of it if I can.
(Playing for chump change)
- Move.
- Just do it.
Haha, you've been eliminated.
- How much is this?
- Three million dollars.
Did you say 3,000 dollars?
- Look how it has no limbs.
- No way.
Yang Se Chan,
you've been eliminated.
(A hunt for laughter)
It must indicate...
- each of our lives.
- So Min, you've been eliminated.
(A hunt for laughter begins.)
I'm taking your life today.
We'll all end up dead at this rate.
(Webfoot Octopus Game)