- What is this place?
- It's so pretty.
It's beautiful.
(Maehyang Ecological Park
with beautiful scenery)
I didn't know Hwaseong had
a place like this.
- Okay!
- This place is so refreshing.
(The park has green fields that look
like ones from fairy tales.)
I'll definitely come back
to this place with my family.
- This is amazing.
- This is a good place for families.
This place is really beautiful.
This is perfect.
- Everyone.
- This place is unbelievable.
Guys. This is not how you're
supposed to advertise a product.
- You think?
- Is this an advertisement?
We shouldn't be doing this.
Gosh, I want to do chin-ups here.
This isn't an advertisement.
We're supposed to pay to be here.
- That's right.
- We are very grateful...
for the financial support
for our show.
- Thank you.
- Thanks to you...
- This is so relaxing.
- Because...
- Hwaseong is so beautiful.
Does this place offer good money?
If it does, I'd like to make
a workout video here...
- for my YouTube channel.
- Really?
Stop talking about
your YouTube channel!
You have a million subscribers!
- I'll do chin-ups here.
- But...
the thing is...
- This is ridiculous.
- I feel a little dejected.
Suk Jin and Haha...
have worked really hard...
to have more subscribers.
But they're not even close
to having one million subscribers.
It turns out there were a lot
of people who like to work out.
I felt happy for him
until he got 500,000 subscribers.
- Right. He did.
- Until then, I thought he was good.
The number of subscribers
increased rapidly.
I was happy for him
when it went just well.
But it's going too well now.
I even thought he probably
hired some people for his channel.
- Suk Jin.
- People who write comments.
To be honest, I have
no appetite these days.
I don't want to eat anything.
I've lost some weight.
- You shouldn't try too hard.
- You're right.
- I agree.
- Don't try too hard.
- That's not true.
- You even got the thumbnail...
where you were shirtless.
And you tell us not to try too hard?
Anyway, I'd like to thank
all my subscribers.
- The workout lovers.
- I'm happy for you.
Your channel is fun though.
This is so fun.
By the way,
this ecological park is really nice.
Look. There are butterflies.
This is so refreshing.
This is amazing.
I haven't seen butterflies
for 30 years.
- It's been so long.
- And, So Min,
you should stand in the middle.
- Good. Let's do that.
- Come here.
We should have the girls
in the middle.
They wanted to stay in a corner.
Why are you being like this?
- Just stand there.
- Did I push you away?
Let them stay in the middle.
What are you talking about?
How many crew members
did you bring today?
- How many people do you have?
- He brought a lot.
- He's a celebrity.
- I wanted...
All the crew members are lying down.
They are his subscribers.
- Ji Subscribers.
- His subscribers.
- They are tenacious.
- How tenacious.
- Tenacious subscribers.
What? Hang on.
- What?
- Yun Sang is still here.
I bet Kwang Soo is coming.
- What is Yun Sang doing here?
- Is Kwang Soo today's guest?
- Is Kwang Soo coming?
- Yun Sang is here.
- I know.
- Who are you in charge of?
I just shoot the scenery.
- He sounds so sad.
- The insert shot.
- He's shooting the insert shots.
- Oh, no.
That's nice.
So what are we doing today?
- It's fun to talk here, right?
- Yes.
A lot of comments online...
of fans of Running Man say...
that the opening is fun because
the members have good chemistry.
They say they'd watch our show
even if you just talk all day.
- Seriously?
- So we are going...
to see it through to the end.
Really? Are we
going to talk all day?
In order to reflect
the opinions of our viewers...
and let you chatter
as much as you want,
- I'd love that.
- we planned The Day for Chattering.
That sounds great.
- We're supposed to talk.
- That's what we're doing.
We often liken chattering
to dried young pollack.
- That's right.
- Right.
Actually, we're not supposed...
- to catch too many young pollacks.
- I see.
So we prepared dried pollack
instead of young pollack.
- I love dried pollack.
- It tastes good.
- It's good with mayonnaise.
- We often call it young pollack,
but it's actually dried pollack.
And you will be receiving...
- 100 dried pollacks today.
- I see.
You are to go around good places
to have a talk with no break,
and we will deduct
two dried pollacks every 10 minutes.
(2 dried pollacks will be deducted
every 10 minutes.)
All we need is So Min and Suk Jin.
- And we have Jae Suk.
- If you manage to deduct...
all the dried pollacks by 3 p.m.,
you can go home
without getting a penalty.
But if you fail,
two of you will get a penalty.
The number of members to get
a penalty increases every hour.
So what you mean by chattering...
There are various topics.
Will you give us a specific subject?
You can talk about what you like,
and we will also give you a topic.
- Really?
- Yes.
I realized something last week.
The selfie stick makes me
keep talking. Seriously.
He was excited because
he was getting a lot of subscribers.
- It's not like that.
- Good for you.
- I'm serious.
- He's good.
So I'd like you to talk
as much as you can until 3 p.m...
- to get rid of them all.
- Okay.
If you are silent
for over 10 seconds,
you will gain
two additional dried pollacks.
- For 10 seconds?
- We shouldn't stop talking.
- We shouldn't keep silent.
- I don't like it...
when I'm forced to talk though.
- We have no choice.
- Against my will.
You can also get rid of
more dried pollacks...
by completing additional missions
every 30 minutes.
You can also get rid of
dried pollacks by eating them.
- Let's eat.
- We should eat them.
- We can eat them.
- Grill the pollacks for us.
Hyung Gu, are you done
working as a producer?
He's just...
- He's good though.
- Hyung Gu, do you like it better?
Aren't you here
to learn about editing videos?
My dad is a big fan of you.
(Thank you.)
That's what he got from So Min.
- He's wearing it.
- He got the mask from So Min.
It has So Min's autograph on it.
- He got it from fans.
- I see.
All right.
Time is ticking.
- You can have a seat now.
- Okay.
- Can we sit?
- Who wants a dried pollack?
So this is dried pollack.
- Who wants a multigrain shake?
- They are dried pollacks.
I want a multigrain shake.
Do we have some sauce
like mayonnaise...
- We will bring them to you.
- soy sauce, and peppers?
It tastes better
with some sesami oil, right?
Does this count too?
You should go talk over there.
Okay.
- This is nice.
- My gosh.
There's a multigrain shake.
Can we eat this, sir?
Yes. It's all for you.
Who wants a multigrain shake?
- Me. I want it.
- I like multigrain shakes.
This is a multigrain shake.
It's thick, right? Is it good?
Jae Suk, have some.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- I want a multigrain shake too.
- The multigrain shake you serve...
- looks like a protein shake.
- Get me some multigrain shakes.
- Do you like the multigrain shake?
- I want a multigrain shake.
It's like a protein shake.
This is really...
This is place is good to run around.
By the way, this place is...
- Kids will love this place.
- This is so relaxing.
There are butterflies flying around.
- We need to see something green.
- I've...
never seen
so many butterflies before.
- It's beautiful.
- Isn't this interesting?
When I was young, I didn't
like places like this.
- Me neither.
- I know, right?
- I hated it.
- I was...
- I really hated it.
- My dad was...
See? I can't stop talking.
This is what
those who like to talk look like.
- After seeing some butterflies...
- I know.
Once I see something,
I can keep talking about it.
So...
- I don't say anything useless.
- What?
I just say fun things
only when they are needed.
Suk Jin is the best...
- when it comes to sedentary work.
- He's the best.
- That's not true.
- He's the Catch-Rats guy.
- When the cameras are on,
- The Catch-Rats guy.
Suk Jin doesn't have many things...
to talk about.
- I can talk about everyday life.
- He's only interested...
in real estate, stocks,
and investments.
We can also talk about
real estate here.
Or he just gossips...
about celebrities
who are going through hard times.
- That's all he can talk about.
- That's not true.
- And he talks about his past.
- I know.
- He can talk about the past.
- Right.
- Tell us about your past.
- Let's do that.
Tell us what it was like
when you were younger.
- When you were popular.
- Hey.
- Your prime time.
- Honestly...
I cried when Suk Jin told me
about his past love.
- Hey.
- Really?
Did you believe what he said?
Isn't that true?
- I'll tell you if it's true or not.
- I'm...
- Let's see.
- Actually, when I was younger,
women chased me around.
- I'm serious.
- That's a lie.
- Tell us more about it.
- I was on a bus.
Someone touched me.
We didn't have
cell phones back then.
She said, "Excuse me."
This is a true story.
By the way,
while he's talking...
- How could you...
- What's wrong?
Do you own this hut?
We can be free these days.
- This isn't about being free.
- You don't have to worry.
- You can't show off your feet.
- This is free.
- We don't want to see your feet.
- Can he show the sole of his feet?
- Why would you zoom in?
- We should be free.
Why would you zoom in on his feet?
We can be free.
It never happened to you, right?
A woman asking for your number.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- It never happened, did it?
- Gosh.
- There's no need to say.
- When you were unknown.
Haha can't say a word.
It did happen to Haha.
- I bet it happened a lot.
- It was a long time ago.
When he touted for business
on the street in Itaewon.
- On the street?
- Is he from the street?
- He's from the street.
- The street!
- I just did it twice.
- Hey, Haha.
- If it was twice...
- I did it for Geun Sik.
Hey, that's enough. Stop that.
You shouldn't be ashamed of that.
- It's okay.
- It's something cool.
- You just shamed him.
- Se Chan is...
Surprisingly, Se Chan is...
quite popular with comediennes.
- He's popular.
- Right.
That's not true.
There aren't many comediennes.
Is it true that there was something
going on between Do Yeon and you?
No, it wasn't like that. Actually,
Yong Jin and Do Yeon had
something going on.
- Right. It was Yong Jin.
- There was something.
Nothing happened between me and her.
- With Do Yeon?
- Nothing.
Yong Jin is your close friend.
So you can't do
anything about Do Yeon.
And it's not just that.
Before that, Na Rae said...
she had feelings for me.
- She told everyone.
- Right. She announced it.
She'd attack anyone
who approaches me.
So no one could ask me out.
- I see.
- He's really popular.
Se Chan is popular with girls.
This is from a long time ago,
but did you have feelings
for Eun Hye when we did "X-Man"?
My goodness.
(They can't talk about the past
without mentioning her name.)
Stop talking about her!
That's enough!
Don't say that.
- I told you not to talk about her.
- I want to know.
That's enough. Stop it now.
- You're finally sitting up.
- Don't say that.
- I'm curious as a viewer.
- That's enough.
Stop it. Don't say that.
- I saw it only on TV.
- Just don't say that.
- Aren't you curious?
- Enough.
By the way,
you were really popular
when you were doing "X-Man".
- I was very popular.
- Right?
(I was very popular.)
I heard that
he was popular back then.
(This is when he says
he was very popular.)
(It's hard to believe
that he was popular back then.)
- I was very popular.
- Right?
I heard that
he was popular back then.
There was a girl...
- who had a crush on her.
- That can't be true.
It's true.
- Jae Suk.
- She really liked him.
- It's not like that.
- So...
you went out with her.
There was a show...
- called "Fort Boyard".
- Exactly.
She told me that
when I was doing the show.
She always said
that you were her ideal type.
We expect...
this to be cut off, right?
- But they don't cut it off.
- They don't.
It's okay.
- Don't cut it off.
- This is true.
- Can I tell you something shocking?
- What?
(Something shocking?)
- What is it?
- A girl group member liked you.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
She was a close friend of mine.
She was serious.
She's married now,
so I can't tell you.
I heard that a lot,
but no one ever asked me out.
- She had a huge crush on you.
- Really? That's hard to believe.
He looks...
- like a decent guy now.
- Right.
But when he did "Kungkungtta",
he was a little like a delinquent.
Just a little.
- That's true.
- He was...
- Hey.
- I mean...
Just this much.
- Be honest. It's true, isn't it?
- Back then,
he used to smoke back then.
Really?
- Back then...
- Did Jae Suk smoke?
He used to smoke
with his colleagues after work.
Actually, Jae Suk made...
good smoke rings back then.
(He even had some skills.)
I could even...
make small smoke rings.
- It's hard to believe.
- But...
we have many young viewers...
who are watching this.
- Smoking is a bad habit.
- It's bad.
- That's why he quit smoking.
- He quit a long time ago.
I quit smoking...
- after I started this show.
- That's right.
And do you know
"X-Man" is on air now?
- Really?
- Seriously?
- "X-Man" is on air now.
- I watch it.
- Is it on air?
- Yes.
This is what
Jong Kook did back then.
He just smiled.
He acted like a prince.
Is he G-DRAGON or what?
(He just put on a serious look.)
(What else can I do?)
(He was a tough man
who didn't say more than a word.)
I didn't know Jong Kook
was so talkative back then.
Why have you become so talkative?
- He is so talkative now.
- I didn't like to talk.
- He was always like that.
- Jong Kook is...
- talkative. He likes to talk.
- He's really talkative.
I like to talk
when the cameras are off.
He's shy of strangers.
But I couldn't do it
when the cameras were on.
Is that when Haha became famous?
- That's when he became famous.
- Right.
- By copying him?
- He tried to copy me.
(They even stand in the same pose.)
(This is when
their relationship began.)
(Haha and his friends
tried to copy Jong Kook.)
(He practiced the dance moves
of Turbo's songs instead of his.)
- He was a copycat.
- I copied him.
- I wasn't a copycat though.
- Weren't you a copycat?
- Just don't call me a copycat.
- It's different.
- You were a copycat.
- I just tried to copy him.
You were a copycat from the street.
It's true that you were a copycat
from the street.
- From the street?
- Don't call him like that.
A copycat from the street?
Hey, Ji Hyo.
What were you doing back then?
Was it when you shoot
"Whispering Corridors"?
It was 2002 or 2003.
I'm finally telling you
about Ji Hyo now.
Before Ji Hyo joined Running Man,
she was a guest...
- That's right.
- on "Family Outing".
(Ji Hyo was a guest
on "Family Outing".)
I brought some dried pollacks.
(It's interesting that she brought
dried pollacks when they first met.)
- Dried pollacks, not flowers?
- Right.
(That's how
the dried pollack universe began.)
We went out of town
early in the morning,
so we were very tired.
- And the guests felt very nervous.
- Right.
So I told Ji Hyo
to go get some rest.
- And she said yes.
- Did she lie down?
But she didn't come back
when we started the shoot.
I said, "Where's Ji Hyo?"
No one knew where she was.
Were you asleep?
And I found her...
- snoring in the next room.
- You're unbelievable.
- She even slept dressed as a ghost.
- I know.
She even slept in a ghost costume.
Did the producer of "Family Outing"
direct Running Man?
- Yes.
- It was Hyo Jin.
- We had several candidates,
- Right.
but our crew members
found Ji Hyo very impressive.
That's how Ji Hyo joined our show.
It was because of "Family Outing".
Was Suk Jin one of the candidates?
- Suk Jin was...
- How did he join our show?
- Was he a candidate?
- Can I tell you about him?
Yes, please.
- Can I?
- Go ahead and tell us.
- What's the behind story?
- Among all the candidates...
Tell us. Let's see how it's
different from what I know.
It's been 11 years.
Let me tell you then.
I'll just tell you the situation.
The crew members cast the members.
- Right.
- But...
- sometimes they ask my opinion.
- I see.
Back then, Hyo Jin asked me.
"Jae Suk, what do you
think of Suk Jin?"
- He brought it up first.
- Right.
The director mentioned
his name first.
He pulled out the sword.
I was surprised that Suk Jin was...
- one of the candidates.
- Surprised?
You didn't mention his name?
It's not that you mentioned
his name first.
- You didn't say Suk Jin's name?
- Because...
he was my close friend, so...
- You punk.
- I'm just curious.
Back then, I hesitated...
to join this show.
- That's true.
- I'm serious.
- Back then...
- Were you doing "Star Golden Bell"?
I was doing
"Star Golden Bell" back then.
- I was doing a lot of TV shows.
- So...
One of the names
Hyo Jin mentioned was...
- Kwang Soo.
- I met Kwang Soo on "Come to Play".
- Right.
That's where I met him.
When I met Kwang Soo
on "Come to Play",
- he was really good.
- Really?
When Hyo Jin mentioned his name,
I said, "I've worked
with him before."
"I think he's really good."
- "I'm not sure though."
- I see.
"Then what about Suk Jin?"
Suk Jin is...
- my close friend.
- Right.
- So I was...
- I was rather...
- He must've been uncomfortable.
- It could be uncomfortable.
To be honest,
I hesitated because of him.
I don't want you to butt in
when I talk.
- Why do you keep cutting in?
- You can't talk alone.
Are you the only one to talk?
- My gosh. He just...
- I was into it.
- Hang on.
- I was into his story.
- I can't go on if he keeps this up.
- But suddenly...
- Come on. Tell us.
- Come back, Jae Suk.
- Please tell us the story.
- Jae Suk, I'm sorry.
- Please.
- Don't be mad.
- I mean...
- What's the matter?
- Was it supposed to continue?
- It's not like that.
- Of course...
- I was falling...
- Exactly.
- into his story and you ruined it.
- It was so interesting.
- Gosh, seriously.
Jae Suk, don't be mad.
- All right.
- You all know the truth, don't you?
It feels as if I woke up
in the middle of a good dream.
If this were a YouTube video,
it would've been a commercial break.
- The second part begins.
- Gosh.
- What's wrong with you, Suk Jin?
- So what happened, Jae Suk?
You see, some viewers might think...
that I recommended Suk Jin...
- Right. Some might think that way.
- because we're close friends.
- No, I didn't need his help then.
- Come on.
Gosh, seriously!
I was enjoying his story.
That's not true. I don't want anyone
to get the wrong idea.
- My position was...
- Hey, there's a four-leaf clover.
- Suk Jin, can you pick it for me?
- Hurry. Go on now.
(A lucky 4-leaf clover?)
- Where? Here?
- Over here.
(Seok Sam plays along
with any joke.)
- So what happened?
- He's looking for it.
Continue.
- Tell us.
- So...
- But still...
- Yes?
(He continues telling the story
while Suk Jin is gone.)
- I couldn't disapprove of him.
- Right.
That would've been weird as well.
- Of course.
- Listen. I was...
I wasn't sure
about joining the show either.
Mister, the four-leaf clover...
- is right behind you.
- We'll hear your side later.
- I contemplated...
- We'll hear his side first.
- because of him.
- There's a butterfly over there.
- Over there.
- So I told them what I thought...
(Chasing a butterfly at the age
where one grows fond of nature)
trying to be as objective
and cool-headed as I could.
- From an objective perspective.
- I told them my honest opinion...
saying that I wasn't sure
if it would work out well.
- I told them about his strengths...
- Yes.
- as well as weaknesses.
- That's great.
- I told them both.
- No one must know this story.
- Come on. Tell us.
- Please tell us.
- I'm so curious.
- His strengths and weaknesses.
First, Suk Jin is good with words.
- True.
- And he's funny.
- He's funny.
- And...
- he's generally a friendly person,
- Yes.
so when he works as a team,
- He gets along well with others.
- he gets along with no problems.
- He blends in well. That's it.
- Yes.
However, his weakness is...
(However, his weakness is...)
- He was a solo host on many shows.
- True.
Although he's a friendly person,
he might get stressed out
because he wouldn't get...
the spotlight all to himself.
That's absolutely true.
- Absolutely true.
- He hates sharing the spotlight.
He used to be
a little authoritative.
He didn't like being friendly
with his junior entertainers.
- Did you want all the attention?
- I mean...
- I can't deny that.
- He couldn't work on a team.
- I was bossy back then.
- Right?
- I was bossy.
- Yes, he was.
Now I hang out
with my junior entertainers...
after a shoot,
but back then, I didn't like it.
- True. He didn't even look at us.
- Yes, but... What?
So what's your side of the story?
How did you get the offer?
Of course,
they gave me an official offer.
- How else would they have done it?
- I mean...
- My gosh.
- How else?
- Why would you get upset?
- Why would you get angry at him?
- Gosh. I heard you were friendly.
- I was just asking...
- Why would you get upset?
- His intention is annoying.
I had no intention.
I was just curious.
Your intention is annoying.
Since Suk Jin was more of an MC
rather than an entertainer,
I asked if he was cost-hosting
with Jae Suk.
Then the director said, "Gosh, no."
(The main director said,
"Gosh, no.")
- Did he really say that?
- "That won't work."
- Did he, really?
- You know that, right?
"Gosh, no."
"That won't work."
I clearly remember it.
- You see, I...
- Why doesn't Suk Jin jump in...
at the right time
as he said he would?
- Well... Yes.
- I was... What?
You told me not to interrupt,
you punk!
Why would you yell at me?
- I can't go on like this.
- That's not cool.
- He's too much. I'm scared.
- What was that?
Let me explain.
I hadn't been on a variety show
like this before.
- Stop frowning, will you?
- It's not like that.
- The sunlight hurts my eyes.
- Is that so?
- It's because of the sun. Okay?
- Okay.
(He made a fake smile
as Jong Kook complained.)
- It's because of the sun.
- The sun...
- Don't do that.
- No, no.
- This won't work because of him.
- Why would it hurt your eyes?
- It's because of the sun.
- You're sitting...
- in the shade.
- He keeps yelling. What's this?
- He's upset.
- Come on.
- That's not true.
- You keep yelling at us.
- Exactly. This is...
- By the way...
I didn't realize how important
teamwork was...
because I hadn't been
on a show like this before that.
I used to go straight home
after a shoot.
Do you know what I regret the most?
- This is what really happened.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook and Haha,
- Yes.
you guys called me at 5 a.m.
- Me too?
- I lived in Cheongdam-dong then.
- I was almost home.
- Yes.
You guys asked me to eat breakfast
with you.
- At 5 a.m.
- Right.
But I said I was too tired
and just went home.
- And I regret it greatly now.
- Suk Jin, I remember that.
- I remember it as well.
- It was...
- When we called you at 5 a.m...
- Yes.
You remember it, don't you?
I knew that you hated me...
- It's all in the past now.
- Yes, it's all in the past.
Suk Jin was hurt a little
at the time.
- That's right.
- So...
- he complained about many of us.
- It was quite intense.
- But I realized that I was wrong.
- And...
- He talked about Haha too.
- That's right.
- This is what he said about Haha.
- Yes.
"That little punk
won't stop acting up."
(They finally tell each other
how they really felt 11 years ago.)
- Also, back then...
- That's so cute.
I was playing the role of someone...
- who teased another member...
- That's true.
and made the others tease him
with me.
- When someone teased him,
- But it wasn't so bad.
if I giggled,
he would glare at me like this.
(Glaring)
- He looked so scary.
- You see,
I'd like to apologize to Haha...
because it was all my fault.
I know that now.
- I was too bossy.
- That's so funny.
- You couldn't open up your heart.
- Exactly.
- I didn't realize...
- People usually don't change.
I had a similar experience to that.
- Really?
- In the early years...
when you guys got together
quite often,
I never...
- joined you guys.
- You never joined us.
Kwang Soo called me several times...
to ask me to come out
to meet you all.
But I got the wrong idea.
I thought that Kwang Soo...
was hitting on me.
(She thought he was hitting on her.)
He called me to ask me
to come out so often.
- I see why she thought that way.
- That's understandable.
- Right.
I get it.
- I see.
- That's understandable.
- That's so funny.
- That's hilarious.
- That's understandable.
- I was so annoyed.
- I told him to stop calling me.
- That's so funny.
And I hung up.
- He really stopped calling me.
- Oh, I see.
Anyway, what's important is,
Ji Hyo...
that they didn't get together
so often.
And I didn't meet with them
often either.
- That's true.
- Yes.
- You were too busy then.
- Jong Kook likes to meet friends.
Yes, I do like that.
- Here we go, here we go
- Here we go
- Also, Jae Suk...
- He likes to gather with friends.
Whenever we walked down Garosu-gil,
we walked in single file.
Why?
- "We are one."
- Exactly. "We are one."
- I see.
- We always walked in a single file.
Jong Kook likes
doing things like that.
- I was even worse back then.
- Are you serious?
- I was...
- "Today's dress code is black."
- We had to wear black clothes.
- You had a dress code too?
I liked hanging out with them
as a leader.
- Jong Kook would hold...
- Right.
- an Americano in one hand,
- Exactly.
- and chicken breast in the other.
- That's right.
(Americano in 1 hand
and chicken breast in the other)
(Walking around cheerfully)
- Exactly.
- That's how exactly he looked.
- Yes, that's right. Exactly.
- Right?
- Behind him...
- Ladies and gentlemen,
- please don't get me wrong.
- Behind him...
It's not that I went to Garosu-gil
carrying coffee and food like that.
- Right.
- The gym I went to was there.
- It was right across the street.
- It was fun.
We came this far
starting with Suk Jin's story.
- I didn't think of teamwork.
- That's why...
- Suk Jin was...
- By the way, the exact time...
when Suk Jin became
more enthusiastic was...
- after our overseas fan event.
- Exactly.
- To be honest...
- That's true.
- Only we knew about this.
- Absolutely true.
- He changed his attitude...
- That's right.
- after our overseas fan event.
- Yes.
- Why do I feel embarrassed?
- Our first overseas fan event...
- In fact, in Running Man's history,
- True.
- there were a few turning points.
- That's right.
That's true.
- We were...
- The shoot in Thailand.
- I'll be honest.
"Infinite Challenge" had
turning points as well.
- True.
- The show could've ended.
- What I'm saying is...
- We tried not to get our hopes up.
- It costs a lot for one episode.
- That's true.
- From the network's perspective,
they invest a large sum of money
to shoot the show...
- expecting to make a profit...
- Yes.
so they can continue to shoot
the show.
- Exactly.
- Or else, it's not possible.
- It must be profitable.
- When we went to Thailand...
- Yes.
- We were surprised.
- We were really surprised.
- We were all discouraged.
- It's because...
the week before that shoot,
- Our show was going to end soon.
- we heard that our show would end.
- We didn't have any expectations.
- So I said,
"We're going to pour out
everything we have..."
"since this will be our last shoot."
The director said,
"Yes. You did your best."
"It's okay even
if it doesn't work out."
But when we arrived...
At first, I thought it was
a hidden camera prank.
- At the airport?
- Yes.
- We were so surprised.
- I thought it was a prank.
(July 3, 2011,
Running Man, Episode 50)
(The cast and staff members
didn't have any expectations.)
(But as the cast members arrived,
they saw...)
(the Thai fans
who filled the airport.)
Hey, this is...
(The Thai fans' unexpected
and passionate welcome...)
(surprised the cast
and staff members.)
So many people are... Oh, hello.
(A great number of fans gathered
to greet the cast members.)
(Could this be
a hidden camera prank?)
(This is how popular
Running Man is.)
Isn't this a prank?
I'm puzzled right now.
(They were discouraged
thinking the show would end.)
(But the foreign fans encouraged
and cheered them up greatly.)
(Oh, this is... My goodness.)
(Who made this happen?)
(Oh, wow. This is incredible.
It's hard to believe.)
(The foreign fans' passionate love
still touches their hearts.)
We were all so surprised.
- I thought it was a prank.
- I don't know how this might sound.
Obviously, we're very grateful
for our Korean fans.
But we're even more grateful
for our foreign fans.
We're incredibly grateful for them.
- We were able to continue...
- Absolutely.
- the show because of them.
- Yes.
I thought that an idol singer was
behind us.
I thought the same thing.
- But we saw our names on the signs.
- We didn't think they came...
- to see us.
- It made me start crying.
We didn't think they came
to see us...
because there were
more than 1,000 people there.
- After the shoot in Thailand,
- It was so touching.
we all got Botox shots
and skin treatment.
(He became more emotional
than the others.)
- We all started losing weight.
- We started changing greatly.
We all started
social media accounts.
I don't know if I'm right,
but Suk Jin changed a lot
after that.
- Really?
- He changed a lot.
Since I realized
that we had so many fans overseas...
who were watching our show,
I felt a sense of responsibility
on my shoulders. That's why.
I thought I should work harder.
- Did someone hop on your shoulders?
- Yes.
I felt all that attention
on my shoulders.
Are you carrying all your fans
on your shoulders?
I felt a sense of responsibility
and thought I should work harder.
I actually thought
that I could burden everyone.
You hated being called Big Nose,
didn't you?
But at every concert,
he would scream, "Big",
and his fans would scream "Nose".
- That was so funny.
- That was the worst.
That was the funniest thing.
- "I say 'Big',"
- "you say, 'Nose'!"
- "You say, 'Nose'!"
- "Big! Nose!"
- "Nose!"
- He's the worst.
- Right.
- That was so hilarious.
I laughed so hard.
- They said "nose" in Thai.
- Right.
- Now...
- By the way,
- you can say...
- Now...
(Now...)
(They won't stop chattering,
ignoring what the director says.)
Shut it.
We're having a conversation here.
- You told us to chat.
- Right. Shut it.
- We're doing this for the show.
- Why would you interrupt us?
- Just shut it so we can chat!
- Be quiet.
- You told us to have a chat.
- So we can eat while chatting.
- Stop it.
- Are we doing it right?
- All right.
- Please give us some.
You know... Well...
- I forgot what I was saying...
- Right.
- because of you.
- Why did you make him forget?
We were having so much fun.
What were we talking about?
- Big Nose.
- That's right. Big Nose.
He didn't like the nickname
but he changed his attitude.
- We were saying it was funny.
- Right. I remember now.
- Are we doing it right?
- Hey.
(Big Nose, once dreamed of becoming
a world star)
Can you give us some pollacks
so we can eat while chatting?
- We'll give you some if you want.
- Please give us some.
- So the adequate amount...
- It happened a lot back then.
Guys, the staff members are starting
to look bored.
What's wrong?
- Why? We're chatting.
- Just don't say anything!
- Let us have a chat comfortably.
- This is a realistic chat.
- Of course.
- It's so interesting.
A real chat!
- All right?
- Exactly.
- A real chat!
- This is a real chat.
- That's right.
- Our food is here.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you. Oh, my.
- We should eat some.
- Oh, wow.
- Thank you.
- They added spicy chili.
- Actually...
Actually, this is
a very good place...
to have a nice, long chat.
- And it's so cool here.
- It's really sunny today,
- Exactly.
- but we're under the shade.
We get to enjoy
a picturesque view as well.
(The chatting paradise)
By the way, I like the way
things are these days...
Back in the days...
I mean there are...
many young directors these days.
You know, these days, so-called...
- He's excited.
- Well...
Jae Suk is so excited right now.
- Like "Three Meals for Jae Suk"...
- All right. Then...
This is just like
"Three Meals for Jae Suk". Come on.
- I...
- Take it easy.
I talked about product placement
with Bo Pil this morning.
(Korea's best MC's opinion
on product placement)
That's right.
I mean it's just our job.
We're human just like everyone else.
Although I have never met
So Min's father...
The air quality was
a little bad in the morning.
I feel so relaxed.
- Jae Suk, wait. Listen to me.
- But I think...
- He won't stop talking.
- Jae Suk, come here.
How many more places will we visit?
I'm sorry, but at least three of us
are already tired.
Later, we can...
(Their ears hurt now.)
Not me.
- I'm not tired either.
- Me neither.
- I'm full of energy.
- I haven't even started yet.
Then let's stop talking
about showbiz.
Shall we?
- Is the next topic love?
- Let's talk...
- about So Min's favorite topic...
- Love?
- this time, which is love.
- Let's talk about love.
Where do you want me to begin?
- Sorry?
- Where should I begin?
Hey, have you ever fallen in love
at first sight?
Love at first sight?
Actually, I'm not the type
that falls in love at first sight.
Why are you sitting on the edge
like that?
(She's elated
as she's an expert in this topic.)
She's excited because it's her turn.
- It's her turn now.
- I rather get attracted...
- to a man I didn't like at first...
- Right.
- more easily.
- Me too.
- An unexpected charm...
What are you doing?
Gosh, seriously.
- Actually, lately,
- Yes.
- I feel...
- Are you interested in someone?
Well... He's a friend...
- who lives in my neighborhood.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He'll know when he watches this.
- He'll know.
- Anyway,
I get a text message
at late night sometimes.
- From him?
- Yes.
- I bet he likes her.
- Did you meet him before that?
I met him with some other people
only once or twice.
We don't know each other well.
- Do we know him too?
- No.
Is it okay for you...
- to talk about him on a TV show?
- Someone we don't know.
- Go on and tell us about him.
- Nothing's going on between us.
- Right.
- It's not like that.
- Okay. Go on.
- We're just friends.
But I have this feeling...
- I feel...
- Oh, I see.
Right. I think I know what you mean.
One day, we ran into each other...
and walked home together.
Why would you walk home together
if you ran into each other?
Don't people part ways
when they run into each other?
I'll be honest with you.
- Don't you think it's weird?
- They should go home together.
- They were in the mood.
- Oh, I see. Okay.
Hey, why are you getting upset?
- I'm not getting upset.
- Why would you get upset?
(Why are you getting upset?)
- I mean it's unnatural...
- Why would you get upset?
- Goodness, you. You're jealous.
- I'm not jealous.
- Why would you get upset suddenly?
- It's not like that.
Okay. I'll just listen.
I really ran into him on the street.
I asked him,
"Hey, what are you doing here?"
He said he was on his way home
after working out at the gym.
I'm an extrovert, you know.
I wasn't trying
to show my interest in him.
- I said, "I'll walk home."
- "Would you walk with me?"
"Do you want to walk with me?
How about you exercise more?"
- That's how it happened.
- My gosh. Clearly, you...
- That's a fake coincidence.
- It's strange.
Clearly, you talked him into it.
- I think you made a move on him.
- That's a fake coincidence.
That wasn't a coincidence.
It's definitely not a coincidence.
He said, "I'm sorry,
but I'm too tired."
- He refused indirectly.
- Yes, he did.
So I said okay
and started walking home.
It felt strange while walking.
- Why?
- He was walking with me...
- unlike what he said.
- I see.
So I said,
"Hey, you said you were going home."
He said, "Well, I'll walk you
over there and leave."
- But he wouldn't leave.
- Oh, my.
I bet he refused
but felt bad about it.
Suk Jin is right.
He must be a thoughtful guy.
He's a thoughtful guy.
And then we continued walking.
But I had this feeling
that he was...
So I said...
"We're almost there.
How will you go home from here?"
He said he would take a bus.
So I said I would walk him
to the bus stop.
He said, "That's okay.
You can go home."
But I insisted on walking him
to the bus stop.
It sounds like you have
a one-sided crush on him.
- This is...
- He doesn't seem to like you.
- I think...
- She's practically writing a novel.
- A novel about unrequited love.
- You're the only one in love.
- But it's not that he doesn't...
- So Min, listen.
But I felt so good...
when we arrived at the bus stop,
and he said, "Bye, sis."
Oh, gosh.
(He called her "sis"?)
He called you "sis"?
(She made a mistake.)
- "Bye, sis."
- He called her "sis".
- He must be younger than her.
The man who is younger than So Min
and lives in Yongsan,
you'd better behave yourself.
Got it?
Are you going to keep
holding things back from us?
- If you're younger than So Min...
- You could've told us...
- that he's younger than you.
- Be good to her, you brat.
- So Min likes you, you brat.
- Why didn't you tell us?
Hey, kid!
(I will call you by your first name)
(Whatever you say)
- The man living in Yongsan,
- Stop it.
- call So Min by her first name.
- Hey, stop it.
- Say that she's your girl!
- Gosh, seriously.
Call her by her first name.
(They all became more energetic
because of her love story.)
- The pollacks...
- I want to know...
- Ask any question.
- Bo Pil wants to say something.
- What?
- He picked up a mic.
You have the whole day, so...
- Are we more chatty than expected?
- Yes.
- I haven't even started yet.
- We can go...
We can go on all day.
You've been chatting...
for 70 minutes
since we started shooting.
Really?
(They've been chattering
for 70 minutes since the beginning.)
- Really?
- Is that true?
Since the beginning, yes.
We deducted 2 pollacks
for every 10 minutes.
14 pollacks have been deducted.
We've been chattering
for 70 minutes without a break?
We didn't pause at all?
And you ate 2 pollacks. 16 pollacks
have been deducted in total.
By the way, this is so tasty.
Keep it coming.
The first mission
where you can deduct pollacks...
requires a joint effort
from all seven of you.
- It's Doppelganger Tug of War.
- What?
(The 1st mission,
Doppelganger Tug of War)
"Doppelganger"?
You'll have a tug of war match
against seven staff members.
If you win at least once,
we'll deduct pollacks.
10 pollacks will be deducted
on your 1st win...
and 9 pollacks on your 2nd win.
The number goes down like his.
And from the 3rd round,
1 random member from each team
will be taken out in every round.
(From the 3rd round,
1 member will be taken out.)
We selected staff members
who have similar physiques...
to each one of you.
Let me introduce them.
The first member,
against the veteran Suk Jin,
is the veteran staff member,
the legend of variety shows,
Kang Chan Hee.
- We have a chance of winning.
- We can win.
- Chan Hee doesn't seem so strong.
- Chan Hee...
He does have a similar physique
to Suk Jin's.
- Next up is...
- Chan Hee has a nice body.
Yoon Hong Min whose body is
as muscular as Jong Kook.
- Gosh, we're in trouble.
- Oh, no.
- We might...
- He has such a muscular body.
- We might lose.
- Look at his shoulders.
How do we beat him?
Look at his back muscles.
Next up is the Yoo Jae Suk
of the staff members...
who is skinny but strong
and has similar facial features.
- Lee Ju Yong.
- Oh, it's Ju Yong.
(Jae Suk's look-alike,
Producer Lee Ju Yong)
Next up is Na Dong Geun
from the directing team...
against the swift Haha.
- Oh, gosh.
- Dong Geun is strong.
Cameraman Choi Yun Sang
will defeat Se Chan.
- Oh, Yun Sang?
- Yun Sang?
And Assistant Writer Yeo Si Yeon
who is as competitive as Ji Hyo,
the determined fighter
of Running Man.
Last but not least, Choi Hyung In
who's as passionate as So Min.
- Hyung In?
- Oh, Hyung In?
But Hyung In is stronger than me.
- So they represent the staff.
- Let's give it a try.
Please come out and get ready.
- Let's go.
- It's important to pull the rope...
- at the same time.
- No. That's not important.
- I learned this from experience.
- Let's do this.
We can win if we can just hold
our position at the beginning.
How about we say "1, 2"
to pull at the same time?
- We should do that.
- Just lie down on the ground.
I know we should lie down, but...
- It won't be easy.
- Shouldn't we pull it toward us?
Like this. "1, 2. 1, 2."
Shouldn't we wear those shoes too?
Hey, are you guys wearing spikes,
Hyung In?
Those are spikes.
- What?
- That's not fair.
What are you doing?
- They're wearing spikes.
- That's not fair.
Don't you think that's unfair?
- They can't beat us anyway.
- My gosh.
Give us spikes too.
We didn't have enough money,
so we only got seven pairs.
Excuse me.
What are those gloves?
- What are those gloves?
- Come on. Take them off.
(The staff members are
fully equipped.)
- That's what Kim Byung Man uses.
- What are those gloves?
That's not fair.
They're non-slip gloves.
- They're just like yours.
- They have better gear.
Guys, it's almost like sandpaper!
- But...
- They're not slippery at all.
Fortunately,
the ground has dried up.
It's not slippery. We can do this.
- Okay. Let's trust Jong Kook!
- We can beat them.
Jong Kook,
what order should we stand in?
- I'll show you.
- Let's do this.
- Grab the rope.
- Cross your arms.
Grab it and put it under your arm.
Keep the rope close to your body.
And we should stand
close to each other.
- Stay close to each other.
- Let's chant.
1, 2, 3.
- Let's go!
- What? Let's chant as they did.
- Just lie down.
- Let's chant.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3.
- We can do this!
Lean back once it begins.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Jong Kook, we should hold the rope
with our arms crossed, right?
Hold it first and then pull.
Put it under your arm.
Stand closer to him.
- Suk Jin, step back a little.
- Okay.
- Wait. Hold on.
There's no space for me.
- Okay. Stand close to each other.
- Come.
- Put it under your arm.
- Okay. I did it.
- Hold it.
- Okay.
Lean back as soon as it begins.
Wait. Hey.
- Don't lean back yet.
- Come here.
Are you ready? Are you good?
- All right.
- Goodness.
(They've built teamwork
for 11 years.)
(They only need to win once.)
Please get ready.
(The elite staff members
aren't easy to beat.)
(The grit gloves and spikes
add confidence.)
(They're ready to fight
for the honor of the staff.)
Please get ready.
And...
(All 14 players
are determined to win.)
And go!
(The game begins.)
(What?)
And go!
(They get dragged
as soon as the game begins.)
What the...
(They were easy to beat
which made the staff fall down too.)
What on earth was that?
I had no idea they'd be this strong.
- Hold on a second.
- No way.
- That was a mess.
- How can we possibly beat them?
- That was insane.
- What was that?
This is insane!
- The gloves.
- I mean...
The gloves and the spikes.
- Seriously?
- We should lodge a complaint.
The gloves and the spikes!
- Let us have those too.
- You lost the first round.
Let's get ready
for the second round.
Unbelievable.
- It's as if they're beatable.
- How can we win?
- Pull right away.
- Got it.
Guys, don't leave
too much space between us.
Don't pull just yet.
Don't pull. Don't pull just yet.
Guys, don't pull just yet.
Lift up the rope.
- Stay safe, guys.
- Lift up the rope.
- He wrapped the rope around him.
- Lie down instantly.
- Get ready.
- Just a second.
- Lie down instantly.
- We're ready.
And go!
(Round 2 begins.)
(They get dragged once again.)
Darn it!
- Darn.
- This is no fun!
- We can't win.
- Why won't they budge?
Also, the rope's too slippery.
One from each team
will be taken out.
- From this team...
- But our shoes!
You gave them spikes.
Please choose a member of the staff
to sit this next round out.
- The jimmy jib cameraman.
- Jae Suk,
- the jimmy jib cameraman.
- That's right.
He needs to go.
Let's take one out from that team.
- That person will be out.
- Na Dong Geun.
Dong Geun,
you'll sit this round out.
Dong Geun?
- So Min.
- So Min will be left out.
Nice!
(Round 3 will commence
without So Min and Dong Geun.)
- This is great news for us.
- So Min's out.
This is great news!
- This is great for us.
- Okay!
So Min, you can be the referee.
Nice. This is the best news for us.
Being the referee is the best.
It is.
Why don't you like
being the referee?
Pass her the whistle.
How did you draw my name out?
- Was it really random?
- Can't I be the referee?
- Was it random?
- I'll do it.
I'd rather be the referee.
You get to blow the whistle.
- How was my name drawn?
- You get the best role.
It'll be fine.
Guys, please pick up the rope.
- Pick up the rope.
- Jae Suk, get over here.
Make sure that the rope
is in the center.
- Bring it to the center.
- Step back a little.
Make sure it's in the center.
- Don't pull just yet.
- Bring it to the center.
- Here we go.
- Don't pull.
- Bring it to the center.
Don't pull!
- Hold on tight.
- Don't pull.
I'll give you the signal.
Get ready.
Get ready!
And...
(The grasshopper on the staff team
gets ready.)
Get ready! And...
(We can't lose this round too.)
Hold your ground.
(The Grasshopper Producer...)
(and the human forklift)
Hold your ground.
You can't win even with my help.
Even my help wasn't enough.
Seriously?
- It's the shoes.
- The shoes are the problem.
Let's compete barefooted.
Let's take off our shoes.
The shoes.
It's too slippery.
- It's too slippery.
- Just lie down.
- The ground is too slippery.
- Choose another name.
Choose Ji Hyo's name.
(Who will sit out the 4th round?)
The jimmy jib cameraman, please.
- Yun Sang.
- Choi Yun Sang.
And Haha.
Bring on the great news!
This is great news!
We could win
now that Yun Sang is out.
Yes, we could.
- We might be able to.
- It looks promising.
- Stick closer together.
- There's no way we'll lose this.
We need to lie down,
so give me some space.
Move a little to the right.
Lie down, okay?
Just a second.
Are you ready?
- They came prepared, didn't they?
- Okay, let's do this.
(Will they be able to end the game?)
(Round 4 begins.)
(They help them a little.)
(Team Running Man
hangs in there longer this time.)
(Neck and neck)
(The Grasshopper Producer
hops to add more weight.)
(Heave-ho)
(They get dragged
by Mr. Muscle once again.)
Am I the issue here?
It just can't be done.
- Am I the issue here?
- It's the shoes.
- Yes, the shoes.
- It's too slippery.
It seemed doable this time.
- It seemed doable.
- As if.
- It was doable.
- Draw the next names.
Is something on the line
for the staff too?
Why are they fighting
with all their might?
- The jimmy jib cameraman.
- It seemed doable.
We could've won.
(Which staff member
will sit out the next round?)
Yoon Hong Min!
Finally. All right!
- Okay, we've got this.
- Nice!
Please let it be Suk Jin.
Nice. All right!
(Who will also sit this round out?)
- Oh, no.
- Nice. Suk Jin's out!
- Let's party!
- That's great news.
Talk about great news.
- We've got this.
- We'll win this time.
We can't possibly lose this round.
We'll win this round.
Losing this round means
there's a spy among us.
There has to be a spy.
It won't make any sense.
- We have to win this.
- Losing won't make sense.
He's really invested
in the show, isn't he?
Also, check out his stance.
He's experienced
when it comes to tug-of-war.
- "2 Days and 1 Night"?
- He did it a lot on that show.
Check out his biceps.
He was coaching the entire team.
Exactly. The stance he carries...
You need to lie down
and hold your ground.
Is this better?
This time around...
- We'll win.
- Pull at a certain rhythm.
No, we'll win for sure.
Adjust as you go along.
Move a little forward, please.
- This...
- A little to the left.
Move a little to the left.
- Okay, good.
- Good.
- Here we go.
- Are you ready?
- We'll win for sure.
- We're good.
- Get ready.
And...
(The immortal Chan Hee
isn't an easy competition.)
(Who will win this round?)
Heave-ho!
- Hey!
- Lie down!
Lie down!
(They pull with all their might.)
(The passionate grasshopper
holds his ground.)
You fools.
- Hey!
- You fools.
- Just lie down.
- How does this make sense?
(Screaming with agony)
- It's over, guys.
- How come he's this strong?
How does this make sense?
(The staff team wins after fighting
with all their might.)
- It's too slippery.
- Yes, that's the reason.
- Give us those shoes too.
- Seriously?
- And the gloves.
- How is this possible?
Si Yeon's really strong.
- Si Yeon's super strong.
- Si Yeon plays a huge role.
- I know.
- She's probably stronger than me.
This doesn't make any sense.
You'll pick the next names.
- Chan Hee needs to go.
- Or Ju Yong.
Ju Yong or...
- Kang Chan Hee!
- All right!
Song Ji Hyo.
Nice, Ji Hyo's out.
If you lose this...
- If we lose this...
- We can't lose this round.
Si Yeon, Ju Yong, and...
This we must win for sure.
- Of course.
- This we must win.
- We should win this.
- We can win this round.
- Let's win this.
- Why don't I wrap this around me...
and pull?
No, just grab the rope.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's do this!
Losing this won't make sense.
- We'll win this one easily.
- And we should.
- Unbelievable.
- Are you thinking you can win?
Look at them sweating.
Okay, we're good. We've got this.
Are you standing in the center?
What's going on?
Si Yeon,
are you taking on Jong Kook?
Bring it on!
- All right. Bring it on.
- Just a little more.
- Get ready.
- It's not in the center yet.
- All right.
- Get ready.
- Here we go.
- There's no way we'd lose this.
(They have a chance to win
after losing 5 rounds.)
(We will win this time.)
(The passionate grasshopper
is ready.)
(Go!)
- Heave-ho.
- You've got this.
(He pulls with all his might.)
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
You've got this. Yes, you'll win.
(They tug with all their might.)
- Heave-ho!
- You're winning.
(The rope finally goes over
to Team Running Man's side.)
Finally.
(They finally win.)
Good job.
(He falls on his behind
after trying to beat two women.)
- Ji Hyo...
- Okay!
- Come on!
- You're good.
You're good.
(The staff gets knocked
off their feet.)
Okay!
Just to win against them...
- Si Yeon.
- You pulled with all your might.
- I'm sorry.
- How dare you come at us!
- It's not a good feeling.
- Did you think you can take us on?
I'm sorry about this.
- I'm sorry for doing our best.
- It was embarrassing.
I'm sorry for doing our best,
but we had no choice.
I didn't know we'd win
until the last moment.
- I'm so sorry.
- That was pathetic of you guys.
I'm sorry, Si Yeon.
- Think twice before challenging us.
- That surprised me.
We had to win though.
You won the game...
in the sixth round,
so you get to deduct
five young pollacks.
That was tough.
Let's deduct them just by talking.
- Yes, with our words.
- We have no other choice.
- If you think about it...
- I know.
You'll then relocate
to another place to chatter.
- Yes.
- Got it.
(They get on a bus
to head to another location.)
- We'll leave this seat vacant.
- No one's there.
This used to be Kwang Soo's seat.
- That's right.
- Haha usually...
- sits here or here.
- Right.
Usually,
when it was the eight of us,
there were no vacant seats...
Okay, so let's go ahead and...
- There were no vacant seats...
- Okay, so let's go ahead and...
chat some more.
- Okay!
- All right.
If only you were close enough
for me to punch.
- What do you mean?
- Will you hit his mouth?
- Let's...
Let's get started.
- Let's go!
- Let's do this!
- How meaningful was that?
It breaks my heart
that there's an empty seat.
It's so great
that we have more space here!
- Of course! It's more comfortable!
- This seat is...
- I can stretch out my legs.
- It's really nice.
- I can even flutter my feet.
- All right!
Okay, let's do this!
You can deduct dried pollacks
while traveling to other spots.
- All right!
- That's so nice!
Let's deduct dried pollacks!
- That's right!
- No more dried pollacks!
All right!
My gosh, it's so pretty!
Does anyone know
what those flowers are called?
- Freesia?
- Aren't they wildflowers?
- Freesia.
- No, they're not.
- It's freesia.
- They're small cosmoses.
- It's indeed pretty.
- It's so pretty!
- Is it that pretty?
Yes! It's so pretty!
- It's hard to see...
- It's really pretty.
It's really pretty.
Let's talk to Kwang Soo
since it's been long.
- Kwang Soo.
- Hi, Jae Suk.
What are you doing?
I'm at my parents' place.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
It seems like you're free
on Mondays.
(Laughing)
If you're going to rest,
then just come join us.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I'm just going to
loaf around the house.
We have a shoot tomorrow,
so just loaf around here.
- You don't have to be on the show.
- Exactly.
- Just loaf around here.
- Watch us from afar, okay?
Why would I watch you from afar
when I'm not even on the show?
- It's been so long.
- Hey, hey!
- Just do it!
- Hey, listen!
- You're quite stubborn.
- Just do it.
- Learn how to fly a drone.
- Why would I...
Ever since you quit,
Yun Sang has nothing to do here.
- He films butterflies.
- He films the scenery...
and plays tug of war with us.
He even films ants.
(They share what Cameraman Choi
is up to these days.)
Seriously.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
I heard you talked with Suk Jin
on the phone.
- It was yesterday.
- It was a joke.
I gave a gift to him,
and I saw how he exchanged it
with something else the next day.
Is that true?
- Oh, my gosh.
- He's the worst.
- Seriously.
I exchanged it with shoes.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
I'll call you again.
- Bye.
- Okay, bye.
- Pick up the call next week too.
- Okay.
You should learn how to fly a drone!
I'm sure he doesn't feel like
he quit the show.
(Kwang Soo gets teased every week.)
There's an ant
on your face, Suk Jin!
Darn it!
There's an ant
on your face, Suk Jin!
(There really is
an ant on his face.)
(Darn it!)
(He hates it.)
- Hey!
- This is hilarious.
- So Min, that was funny.
- You should've hit it away.
How did you get an ant on your face?
- Do you have it as a pet?
- This is incredible.
Why was an ant there?
- It was so funny.
- There really was one.
Maybe your ear is an ant tunnel.
- I'm getting goosebumps.
- Maybe his nose is.
- It must've taken it as a tunnel.
- Maybe it took your face as ground.
Gosh, I slapped my eye too hard.
Suk Jin, that was funny though.
You're the pride of comedians.
- That was funny.
- That was a good one.
- I slapped it too hard.
- "Darn it!"
(He hit his face really hard
as he hated it.)
- I was wondering what it was.
- You hit your face so hard.
It was so funny.
I felt something weird.
This could go viral. "Darn it!"
(It could become
the buzzword of the year.)
The next place we're heading to
is a village hall.
A village hall?
It's a good place to hang out.
It's a good place to talk.
(A village hall is a good place
to sit around and talk.)
- There's watermelon.
- It's a must in summer.
My gosh.
They're giving us a chance to talk.
You're having fun.
Yes, come sit down.
So Min likes
a certain type of humor.
Something out of nowhere,
but something funny. Am I right?
- I love those.
- It's sweet.
She was getting off the car,
so I went...
(The door is opening)
Then So Min went like this.
I thought it was a skit.
She likes a certain type of humor.
- Kwon Ryeol is there too, right?
- Yes.
Kwon Ryeol
is the main director there.
- He is.
- Oh, really?
- Really?
- He's the main director.
He's a director now.
He's a big shot now.
No, he's still as short.
(Sullen)
You laugh at everything
Jae Suk says.
- That was witty.
- It was.
"He's a big shot now."
- That's...
- "No, he's still as short."
An adult can't grow any bigger.
(That's why he burst into laughter.)
- That was a good one, Jae Suk.
- Thanks.
I should use this joke.
My gosh.
- That was...
- That was a good one.
He's biased to Jae Suk.
You must be really happy
since you have so many fans.
Yes, it's nice.
No, I really liked his joke.
- It's incredible.
- I'll use it elsewhere.
This is good, right?
Do we get to have lunch today?
Our culinary team who is known
to be good...
is making bibim guksu right now.
(They're making bibim guksu.)
It's perfect for a hot day
like today.
- It's perfect.
- And they're making assorted jeon.
- I really love...
- I ate so much.
- bibim guksu.
- I know. You must have it.
- Here it comes.
- We have to keep talking...
even when we eat, right?
- Even while we're eating?
But they say we have good reactions.
(They need to keep talking
to deduct dried pollacks.)
(Here come bibim guksu
and assorted jeon.)
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- What's all this?
They're giving us nice food
so we won't be able to talk.
They'll keep us from talking
with these.
We can take turns to eat them.
We can talk
about the food too, right?
- Of course.
- Can I give this to you?
- Sure, that'd be nice.
Give me just a little.
- Just a little?
- Yes.
My mom's really good at this.
- Really?
- Really? My mom's horrible at it.
(A sudden diss)
(A bad son who disses his mom)
- Lucky you.
- You should...
- You are...
- You should stop dissing her.
- How could you...
- How could you diss your mother?
- Doesn't that make you feel bad?
- She's really bad at it.
- This looks so good.
- It really does.
Let's try it.
We still need to keep talking.
- We need to keep talking.
- Okay?
Why? How is it?
(He's gone speechless.)
This is so good.
- It's so good.
- It really does look good.
It's really good.
(It's so good that they can't
continue talking.)
It's really good.
(Impressed)
(The newbie in describing the taste
reacts to it without even chewing.)
It's sweet and sour.
- It tastes like the one that...
- It's so good!
grandmas used to make for us.
It'll be even better with jeon.
- It's so good.
- If you have it with hamburger...
I'll have it again.
- Then I will...
- Yes.
- wrap it with jeon.
- Go ahead!
- I'll give it a go.
- You'll describe the taste, right?
- How is it?
How is it?
(Exclaiming)
- He's not really good at it either.
- He doesn't do it often.
He's not really good at it.
I bet he has nothing much to say.
If it's good, just say it is.
- Hey.
- Yes?
(Then suddenly came silence.)
Look, they started the countdown.
- Start talking. Why won't you talk?
- Goodness.
How is it, Suk Jin?
Try describing how it tastes.
So this is
what savoriness tastes like.
(Reacting like a robot)
It fools my tongue
with its savoriness.
- What? What did you say?
- The noodles, I mean.
- Who fools what?
- You see? You punk.
(He's only picking on Se Chan
who's an easy target.)
It's your attitude.
How was I supposed to react
when you talked about your tongue?
It's your attitude.
You weren't going to react
to whatever I say anyway.
I think today's the day
Suk Jin is going to cry.
He's going to cry?
But I think...
Hey, you punk. Hey!
I told you not to do it.
Hey!
(He killed it at once.)
He caught it.
- He caught it.
How did you catch it?
I shouldn't use this spoon.
Please give us one more spoon.
Give that to Suk Jin.
No.
(Shocked)
Give that to Suk Jin.
Why did you say that?
We're spewing out nonsense.
Why did you tell him
to give the spoon to me?
(Even he thinks it's absurd.)
What was that?
Now we're just saying
whatever we want.
(Even Suk Jin can't take
the nonsense Jong Kook said.)
- There's nothing to say.
- Let's keep talking!
- This is so good!
- Let's eat a lot and work out!
- Thank you.
Thank you, Min Hee.
Ji Hyo, tell us how it tastes.
- Is she upset?
- What was that?
Isn't that what teenagers do
when they're mad at their parents?
- She was...
- "I hate you, Dad!"
"I hate you, Dad!"
Then they slam the door.
- Maybe she was upset.
- "How dare..."
I didn't even ask her to bring it.
She did it on her own.
Also, everyone else is using
wooden ones. She brought me this.
She brought me a metal one.
What am I supposed to do?
Give it to Suk Jin.
(He spews nonsense again
when Suk Jin dropped his guard.)
Why does he keep saying that?
- Stop it.
- Hey.
It's the funniest buzzword.
"Give it to Suk Jin."
Don't you have rules when it
comes to having conversations?
- He wants me to give it to you.
- Why would he say that?
- It suits you, that's why.
- He's taking care of you.
You're not crying while eating,
are you?
I don't cry.
- Stop lying.
- Come on.
Stop lying.
He's such a hypocrite.
- Stop being like that.
- He's a total hypocrite.
- Did you call me a hippo?
- No, I said you're a hypocrite.
You're offended by everything I say!
You're just upset at me.
- Stop it.
- He misheard what I said.
He called me a hippo,
and I should let that go?
- He said you're a hypocrite.
- They're two different things.
I meant that you're fake.
A hypocrite.
Oh, a hypocrite?
He grabs every chance
to get back at me.
- "What did you say? A hippo?"
- He thinks you're a pushover.
(His eyes went really wide.)
- He's annoyed by you.
- Is he going to attack me only?
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
You're not having a beer
all by yourself, are you?
The way you're sitting...
(He's suspicious of Ji Hyo.)
You look like...
- You drank it refreshingly.
- It's a plum tea.
(Ji Hyo was excessively having
the plum tea.)
(Suk Jin's glass is empty.)
Suk Jin, do you want more plum tea?
- Why would I want it?
- I'm just giving it to you.
- Why would you doubt him?
- Gosh, I'm leaving!
- Suk Jin.
- I just wanted to give him more.
His glass was empty,
- so I wanted to give him more.
- I know.
- Suk Jin, stop it already.
- Do you think I added...
something bad in it?
He obviously did it out of goodwill.
- I'm so sorry.
- Suk Jin.
- All right.
- It's really plum tea.
Stop it already.
Goodness, it's from Se Chan.
- It's plum tea.
- Okay.
It really is.
It's been 30 minutes already,
so we deducted
the dried pollacks for you.
Here's the second mission.
Patience is the virtue for this one.
It's called Hold That Scream.
Is it where we have to
endure the pain?
- It must be something painful.
- We have to endure it.
Since we're at a village hall,
we prepared a mission that suits it.
We'll show you acupuncture points.
An expert will press
the acupuncture point...
- that you pick.
- We're in trouble.
Since it's acupressure,
I should pick a point...
- that hurts.
- My shoulders hurt a lot.
If you endure the pain
for 10 seconds,
five dried pollacks
will be deducted for each person.
An expert will help us.
How have you been?
You look...
You lost some weight, right?
Yes, a little.
I knew it. He looks much younger.
- His bone might break.
- Ready, go.
(With his expert touch, he helped
the members become healthier.)
(A master of sports massage
who gives back your vitality)
- It's been so long.
- How have you been?
The order is important.
How will you decide on the order?
Well, we will...
Jae Suk,
let's have Suk Jin go first.
Right. Since he's older,
- Me?
- let's have him go first.
We should hold out
as much as we can.
- Can I just stay seated?
- All of us.
I'll sit here. Is this it?
Oh, it's right here.
- Hold out, Suk Jin.
- It's 10 seconds.
Ready.
Set, go.
He's enduring it.
It must be relieving.
- I'm used to it.
- Is it usually this hard?
- My gosh.
- Success.
It was really relieving.
- I mean it. It was relieving.
- You should've picked elsewhere.
Then I'll choose this area.
- The back will be okay.
- Then you should lie face down.
Oh, I must?
- Could you...
- Then I think it'll hurt.
It didn't hurt at all.
Ready.
It must be painful for Jae Suk.
He's going to flap. Let's hold him.
- Set.
- It's only 10 seconds.
- Hold on.
- Just hang in there for 10 seconds.
- Set, go!
- Darn it.
(Darn it.)
(He failed in 3 seconds.)
Why couldn't you endure it?
- What's wrong, Jae Suk?
- It must be painful.
- Does it hurt?
- My gosh.
He's dying here.
- He's dying here!
- Hold on. Sir!
How could you...
I just wanted to relax your muscles.
Why would you mangle me?
- You failed.
- I knew you'd fail.
- Can I get a massage on my neck?
- Sure, go ahead.
You should get this part massaged.
Which part are you talking about?
- Right here.
- Darn you.
Why not?
You can hold out.
- You should get massaged there.
- Just do it already.
- This part.
- Wouldn't he urinate blood then?
I'll get massaged
on numbers 4 and 5.
(He picks
the back of his neck instead.)
Hold on. It hurts already.
You need to relax the muscle here
to be relaxed.
- Let's do it.
- Sir, it hurts there.
You already started.
- No, I haven't.
- Ready, set, go.
- Darn it!
(Darn it!)
- Don't curse!
- Don't curse.
- Darn it!
- Come on.
- Don't curse.
- You're done.
- It hurts so much!
You need to relax the muscles.
- It was really painful.
- By the way,
Suk Jin is checking out
the acupuncture points...
after seeing us getting massaged.
(Suddenly checking out
the acupuncture points)
Ready, set, go.
(Unlike Suk Jin
whose turn ended quickly,)
(the other members
are making it funny.)
(Suddenly got concerned
that his part won't get aired)
Let me take a look.
(He quickly looked for a point
that'd give a big laugh.)
Which point will get me
a good reaction?
(Looking for an acupuncture point
to get good reactions)
Which part will be most painful?
Ji Hyo picked her part too.
- Which part did she pick?
- The head.
- She picked the top of the head.
- Let's have Ji Hyo do it.
It's an acupuncture point
called baekhoe.
Right. I'll give it a try.
- Does it work?
- Ready.
Set, go.
She's enduring it.
(Pressing hard)
Look at her.
- It must hurt a lot.
- Stop.
- Endure it!
Let's have
our dried pollacks deducted!
You can do it!
Goodness!
(Success)
- It must hurt a lot.
- That was amazing.
I can't believe she endured it.
You didn't press the button
of the cap, did you?
He pressed the button on her cap!
He pressed this!
- Are you okay?
- I can't believe she endured it.
(But her complexion got better.)
- She cried toward the end.
- I'll pick gokgol.
One must try that part.
- Come here.
- Se Chan is going for gokgol.
- He's going for gokgol.
- Are you sure you'll be okay?
- This part.
- But it's a little above.
- Really?
- Right here.
But it'll be really painful.
- It's right below the belly button.
- Isn't it below the belly button?
- It's lower than that.
- What if he presses wrong?
- This part is...
- Hold on.
(Surprised)
- This part is...
- Hold on.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'll switch.
- Why?
You already picked it.
You can't switch.
- You can't switch.
- It's too late.
It'd be really funny
if your hand comes down like this.
Ready.
Set.
- Oh, no!
- Go!
(Screaming)
- I told you that you can't take it.
- I'll never be able to.
- Why not?
- I'll never be able to endure it.
Did it hurt?
I bet Suk Jin
will be able to take it.
(I bet Suk Jin
will be able to take it.)
Let's get your gokgol massaged!
- Me?
- I bet Suk Jin will be able to.
- Let's get your gokgol massaged.
- Give it a try.
I bet Suk Jin
will be able to take it.
Your fans are watching!
All 400,000 fans of Suk Jin,
cheer for him!
Let's go!
Actually,
it doesn't really matter to me.
I'm good with it.
I don't really feel pain much.
Yes, it's right there.
(How will he
endure the pain this time?)
Ready, set, go.
(Grunting)
(He begins with a pitiful grunt.)
(He moves like a grasshopper
to forget the pain.)
You're doing well!
- Doesn't it hurt?
- Success!
- All right. He did it!
- My goodness.
(The old man stopped his fans
from unsubscribing his channel.)
- He endures it so well.
- It does hurt.
- Does it hurt?
- Yes, it hurts a lot.
- Which part should I get massaged?
- Here's the chart.
I should relieve the muscles
on my buttocks for my back.
- I'll massage hwando then.
- He'll have his hwando massaged.
That's the part that hurts the most.
- Hwando.
- That'd kill me.
- Ready.
- That will be really painful.
- Set.
- That part hurts a lot.
Set, go.
That part hurts a lot.
He's enduring it.
(He's enduring it.)
It's not that painful.
My gosh, Mom!
Let's have
five of our dried pollacks deducted!
- It's for the dried pollacks.
- He's...
Success.
- That was...
- My goodness.
It's relieving, right?
Do you want to try it, So Min?
Right below your pelvis.
- Your pelvis is here.
- Lie down on your side.
- On your side. That's it.
- Pull your leg up.
I'll just press it gently.
(Screaming)
- Just give it a try.
- Don't do it.
- No, I'm not doing anything.
- Just give it a try.
Try it. Let's start.
- He's started, right?
- No, not yet.
Ready, set, go.
(Screaming)
(The frog screams.)
That hurt so much!
That hurt so much.
- That hurt so much.
- It does.
- Yes, it really hurts.
- Right.
Why don't you try it one more time?
(Suk Jin, you're the last to go.)
Suk Jin, you're the last to go.
- All right!
- Why didn't Suk Jin do it?
Suk Jin,
why don't you try this part?
- Suk Jin!
- It's called yosu.
What's wrong?
- You haven't done it yet!
- Stop it already.
- What's wrong?
- He wanted to go last.
- You're the last to go.
- Let's do a skit.
- I haven't done it yet?
- It's been long. Let's do it.
- Yes, give it a go.
- Yes, do that.
- "Give it a go?"
- Ji Seok Sam!
I can endure it
if I try really hard.
- How about deducting 10?
- Give it a try.
Then we'll deduct five each.
- 5 each? Okay.
- 5 each.
Let's give it a go.
Go for it, Ji Hyo.
- I can endure it.
- Ji Hyo, it's...
- I couldn't endure it.
- It's really painful.
- You think you can do it?
- Which part is it?
- I'll do it then.
- Ready.
Set.
- It hurts already, right?
- Set, go.
(Moaning)
(Wait, this is...)
What was that?
- Hey!
- Hey! That's embarrassing!
- What was that sound?
- What was that?
Delete that sound! Delete it!
What was that?
What on earth are you doing
at a village hall?
- Our show is for...
- I know we're having fun, but...
(Her moaning made the elders
of the village displeased.)
- What was that?
- That was embarrassing.
Get out of here! Move!
- Hey!
- Go away!
- Get out.
- It... It really hurt.
Why did you do that
with a smiley cap?
- It hurt so much.
- This time...
- We can have five more deducted.
- You're tearing up.
Se Chan is the last one to go.
- I did it already.
- No, you haven't tried this part.
- I got gokgol massaged.
- No, I mean this part.
- You said you'd get yosu massaged.
- You haven't tried hwando.
- You should give it a try.
- You should try everything.
- That part.
- It doesn't hurt much, right?
You endured the pain earlier.
Yes, bring it on.
Stretch out your legs.
- Stretch them out.
- I want to stay like this though.
You need to stretch out your legs.
- It'll be more painful though.
- Really?
- I'll stretch them out then.
- Okay.
I'm telling you the posture
that'll give you less pain.
He might be able to endure it.
All right.
It hurts as soon as he presses it.
Shall we? Ready, set, go.
(As soon as he starts...)
He's enduring it.
You really look like Han Moo
right now.
(His eyes pop out
along with his protruding mouth.)
- He's enduring it.
- You can do it.
Could you massage his calf too?
- Success.
- He did it.
- Massage his calf.
- I did it. Why would you?
Why would you massage my calf?
(No, no. I don't need you
to massage this part.)
No, no. I don't need you
to massage this part.
No, that'll kill me! No!
(Screaming)
I'm dying! I got cramps!
I got cramps! I got cramps!
(Putting on a straight face)
Sir!
- "Sir".
- Sir!
Sir, that hurt a lot!
- Thank you.
- "That hurt a lot."
Does massaging the calf
hurt that much?
It really hurt.
Jae Suk! Give it a try.
- No, I did it already.
- Give it a try!
- I already...
- It's different. Your calf...
- No, I did it already.
- It's on another level.
Please lie down properly.
Darn it!
I didn't even start.
- He didn't start!
- Don't lie!
- He didn't even start.
- But it hurt so much!
- Just do it!
- I said it hurts!
You should give it a try.
- He said he didn't even start.
- Try it.
- It hurts!
- Give it a try.
Try pressing yosu.
(He got his vitality back.)
- Darn it!
- Sir!
(Jae Suk misses him.)
He ran away.
That hurt!
- It must hurt a lot.
- Calves must hurt a lot.
- It's like I was shot in the leg.
- It really hurt.
It feels like I was shot in the leg.
Could you massage Jong Kook's calf?
- I can't...
- Try it.
I don't think I can endure it.
Let's hear Jong Kook scream
since it's been a while.
- Right leg or left leg?
- Let's hear him scream.
My left knee is bad,
so I'll have my right leg massaged.
Let's hear Jong Kook scream.
(Screaming)
(He hits high notes with his shout.)
(It was the highest note he hit
since his debut.)
He does feel pain!
This is a rare clip.
This is a very rare clip.
- This is a rare clip.
- The calf.
I can't stand the calf pain.
(Let's check out
the rare clip again.)
We learned something new.
He does feel pain.
- I can't stand the calf pain.
- They are his weaknesses.
- The calves.
- I can't stand the calf pain.
His calves are his weaknesses.
- We figured it out.
- The calves.
- His calves are his weaknesses.
- We figured it out.
I can't even get my calves massaged.
My goodness.
Thanks
to Mr. Kim Hyung Joon's massage,
- you became healthy.
- We became very energetic.
That really woke you up, right?
- Yes.
- My eyes became alert.
- My eyes went wide.
- That was incredible.
- I was feeling tired.
25 dried pollacks
have been deducted.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
We will now move
to the next location.
Let's go.
- The sky looks nice today.
- It's pretty.
The sky hasn't been that blue
in a while.
The current time...
is 2:48 p.m.
You deducted
48 dried pollacks with time,
30 dried pollacks with missions,
- and four dried pollacks by eating.
- How many do we have left?
You have 18 dried pollacks left.
- We are almost done.
- We still have many dried pollacks.
If you succeed by 3 p.m.,
the shoot will end.
If you go over that time,
two people will receive the penalty.
You made a mistake
with the rules today.
- When it comes to talking,
- That's right.
- we don't get tired.
- Seriously.
- We don't get tired.
- No.
We never get tired of talking.
Suk Jin and Yong Man...
used to stay up all night talking.
We surprised people at the funeral.
- I remember that.
- I got goosebumps...
- because of ourselves.
- Me too.
- Why?
- We went to a funeral...
to offer our condolences.
(They chatter about
how they chattered at a funeral.)
We had things left to talk about,
but we said, "We should leave."
- "This looks a bit bad."
- I can't believe it.
One time, Haha and I went to LA.
Ji Hyo becomes talkative
after a few drinks.
I become talkative when I drink.
Did you know this?
- Dolphins from different regions...
- That's right.
- can't communicate.
- Do they have languages?
You are really good at chattering.
Let us keep chattering.
- I want to hear more stories.
- Rules are rules.
While you were chattering,
it turned 3 p.m.
So two people will receive
the penalty.
(2 people will receive the penalty.)
If you fail the mission,
two more people will be picked.
Hold on. What's the penalty?
What's the penalty?
I will tell you
that you will need to stay behind.
- It must be something tedious.
- Seriously.
You will get stuck in the traffic
on your way home.
- Staying behind is the worst.
- Staying behind.
Being on the bus with Jong Kook
reminds me...
of "Family Outing".
That's right.
- The bus.
- There are rice fields outside too.
- Rice fields.
- My goodness.
"Family Outing" was exhausting.
- Seriously.
- I watched it on TV.
Now, I can say...
that being on "Family Outing"
with Jong Kook was...
- The way there was exhausting.
- That's right.
- Then we worked in the morning.
- I remember that.
Watching that made me anxious.
If you were late,
everyone shunned you.
We must have gotten
about two hours of sleep.
We worked late at night
and early in the morning.
- Ramyeon we had late at night...
- That's right.
The production crew fed us ramyeon
on purpose...
because it was funny
to make our faces puffy.
The production crew fed us...
- ramyeon and snacks on purpose.
- We ate late at night.
- It was to make your faces puffy.
- That's mean.
It was their technique.
- That was a long time ago.
- I know.
Don't you feel like
you have become an adult?
"I feel like an adult
when I do this."
Well, that's...
The third location is...
the old-fashioned pub
in the countryside.
(They arrive
at the old-fashioned pub.)
- Puffed corn.
- How about beer?
We should have some fried chicken.
We should have a glass of beer.
1, 2, 3.
(He pretends to end the shoot
with a clapperboard.)
- It looks the same.
- It's fascinating.
It really looks the same.
(They begin to chatter.)
(They chatter
until the production crew comes.)
It's an old-fashioned chicken place.
(They enter the old-fashioned pub.)
This is an old-fashioned pub.
The production crew is fed up
with us.
They realized that
they made a mistake with the rules.
What do you mean?
They didn't know
we would chatter so much.
I feel dizzy because of you guys.
Guys.
- They are fed up with us.
- Sit here.
Come here. I will sit with Haha.
You know,
I am impressed with ourselves.
We keep eating dried pollacks.
- It's tasty.
It's tasty.
(They keep eating pollacks.)
- You know,
- Dip it in the sauce.
we talk a lot,
- but there is one problem.
- What?
We talk about the past too much.
We couldn't contribute
to some topics.
Then you guys should talk about
the present.
- Go ahead.
- If we do that,
- we will sound like you guys.
- Talk about the present.
What's your interest these days?
- What's your interest?
- Golf.
- It's golf.
He really likes to play golf.
- Really?
- Yes.
I get that you like to play golf,
but you shouldn't keep missing
soccer games.
I will end you
if you play golf on Saturday.
I was just talking about
my interest.
"I will end you
if you play golf on Saturday."
Why would you schedule to play golf
on Saturday?
There are other days.
(The scary soccer enthusiast
makes Se Chan choke.)
I can't believe him.
(The scary soccer enthusiast
makes Se Chan choke.)
Sprite and Coke.
You are so strong.
It's no wonder we lost.
- I can't believe her.
- I am impressed.
(Si Yeon still has strength
after the tug-of-war.)
- Si Yeon.
- It must have been exhausting.
I didn't know she was like that.
- She didn't even tremble.
- She surprised me.
(The production crew is full
of human weapons.)
- What do you want? Coke?
- Yes.
- Do you want Coke?
(Suk Jin likes Coke.)
It's okay.
I don't drink Sprite.
Hey.
What?
I am looking after you.
It would be rude of me
to keep your glass empty.
- He is clearly looking after you.
- Right?
- That's what I do.
- All right.
- I will make a toast.
- Okay.
O.Y.S.N.!
- Our youths start now!
(Our youths start now!)
That's so old-fashioned.
- So what's the game?
- If you go to Euljiro...
It isn't time yet.
I see.
- Really?
- Yes.
If you go to Euljiro,
there is the Dried Pollack Street.
Shall we go to Euljiro?
- Right now?
- Yes.
(Chewing)
- So suddenly?
- What?
The shoot will end soon.
Jae Suk sounded so carefree.
- The shoot will end soon.
- "Right now?"
- I want to go home and rest.
- Suk Jin is anxious.
- Can't we go there?
I might not have the energy
after the shoot.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Isn't that beer?
- That's beer!
(What? That's beer!)
No, no. It's the shaken barley tea.
- Is it a prize?
- Is it barley tea?
- What? For goodness' sake.
- For goodness' sake.
- What?
- It's barley tea.
It's barley tea.
- Is it beer or barley tea?
- Is it really barley tea?
(The beer lover
becomes disappointed.)
Is it really barley tea?
Isn't it beer?
It's really barley tea.
- It smells like barley tea.
- I won't lie.
- It's barley tea.
- It's really barley tea.
It's barley tea.
How does it look so much like beer?
You will now have...
- the Joint Responsibility Quiz.
- Oh, yes.
- It's simple.
- And I am sitting with you guys.
Before we begin,
who would be the top 4
and who would be the bottom 3?
It's obvious.
Who would be the top four?
- The top 4?
- Yes. Choose 4 people.
- I would be included.
- No way.
- Jae Suk,
- Suk Jin, Jong Kook...
- Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and me.
- But Haha...
- I should be included.
Haha and So Min are
on the same level.
- We are about the same.
- Hey.
Didn't you see me guess "Mile"...
- last week?
- What?
Can you spell "Kitchen"?
- Hey!
- Can you?
- I didn't forget, okay?
- Do you want to spell it now?
- My goodness.
- Do you want me to do that?
I am staying quiet.
I can spell it.
- Ji Hyo.
- Shall I spell "Kitchen"?
I will let you off
since you stayed quiet.
(I will let you off
since you stayed quiet.)
- You know that I am better.
- Haha and us 3 are the bottom 4.
- Pick the bottom three.
- That's right.
It's the three of you.
The production crew is so wicked.
It would have been easy
to pick the bottom four.
- Why...
- The bottom four.
- Let us pick four members.
- "Wicked".
They are so wicked.
Just three?
- Just three.
- Shall we form a group?
- Sure.
- Okay. We are in the bottom three.
These four members are
in the upper rank.
- The rest are in the lower rank.
- Let's do this.
For this mission,
the four members
of the upper rank...
and the three members
of the lower rank will alternate.
It's the Upgraded
Joint Responsibility Quiz.
- We need to alternate.
Listen to the question.
If you know the answer,
pick up the beer glass
that is filled with barley tea...
and shout, "Let me answer."
Say the first letter or syllable
of the answer...
and toss it to someone
who is sitting next to you.
That person needs to say
the next part of the answer...
and toss it again.
I get it.
Let's say the answer is Running Man.
(What's a variety show that airs
every Sunday at 5 p.m.?)
Run.
- Ning.
- Man.
Every time you get the answer,
we will take out two pollacks.
- It's like the 007 Bang Game.
- The last member...
No, it isn't.
It's different.
For goodness' sake.
He should be in the bottom rank.
- He doesn't understand the rules.
It's totally different
from the 007 Bang Game.
Do you think the members
will get eliminated?
Seriously.
He got attacked.
If you say something wrong here,
- you get torn apart.
- You pay for it.
I am getting attacked
since Kwang Soo isn't here.
Now,
the bottom three will sit...
- between the top four.
- Okay.
- I will sit here.
- Shall I sit at the end?
- Can we sit like this?
- Yes.
Two bombs are sitting...
next to Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
(The worst members are sitting
next to the first place.)
She is the only one
I can toss the answer to.
I am the only one
you can toss the answer to.
I will take out two dried pollacks
every time you get a question right.
You could end the mission...
- or go over 4 p.m.
- Okay.
Here comes the first question.
What's the term for media...
in which a person's face is attached
to another video using AI?
What?
- A person's face...
- Me!
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
(He needs to say a syllable
and toss it to Ji Hyo or Se Chan.)
Deep!
(Deep!)
(Dazed)
(Neither of them
can move things along.)
What is it called?
Deep.
(Deep)
Fl.
Is it incorrect?
- Deepfake.
- Deepfake?
- Incorrect.
- I thought it was "Deep flow".
(I thought it was "Deep flow".)
I thought it was "Deep house".
(They fail to answer
the first question.)
I didn't know what "Deepfake" was.
Deepfake.
The next question.
In one SBS variety show,
a woman confidently claimed...
that "Umbrella" starts with A...
and made everyone laugh.
(Episode 551 of Running Man,
Speed Quiz)
(Jae Suk, there are thousands of
words starting with an A.)
(Umbrella!)
(So Min's shocking comment
got filmed.)
What's the correct spelling
for "Umbrella"?
- Me! Let me go first!
- Spelling?
- Yes.
- Me! Let me go first!
(Haha confidently takes the glass.)
- U.
- What?
- Hey.
- M.
There you go.
(What's the correct spelling
for "Umbrella"?)
B.
R.
E.
What?
- Go ahead.
(What will So Min say?)
5, 4...
R, E...
- A.
- Oh, my goodness.
(She says A again.)
Hey!
- You like the letter A, don't you?
- No.
- Come on.
How could you trap a member
with a question?
So Min got it wrong again.
You were out to get me, right?
Isn't it A? A?
- Umbrella.
After R and E,
- what should come?
- E, A.
You spelled "Umbrea".
Umbrea. Umbrea.
Umbrea.
The questions aren't difficult.
All right.
Here comes the next question.
The literal meaning is
"Returning home in silk clothes",
What's the idiom which means
"Returning to home successfully"?
- You know it, right?
- I know this one.
- Go.
- Then I will go.
- I know this one.
Geum.
Yi.
- Hey!
- It's "Ui"!
The character for "Clothing"!
(She got the second syllable wrong.)
- "Ui"!
- The character for "Clothing"!
- Clothing!
(So Min turned the pub upside down.)
So Min, don't open your mouth today.
"Sik" means "Food",
"Ju" means "House",
"Ui" means "Clothing".
I don't think
you are in a good condition.
- Se Chan, don't laugh.
- This will chase men away from her.
- Food, house, and clothing.
- Don't laugh.
- So Min.
- The man she is interested in...
won't call her again.
- If he watches this episode,
- Don't watch this.
- he won't call again.
I think So Min saved Ji Hyo.
- I know that for sure.
- What would you have said?
When So Min answered,
Ji Hyo didn't laugh.
(When So Min said the wrong answer,)
(she just bit her lips.)
(So Min and Ji Hyo save each other.)
- Here comes the next question.
- Okay.
It's Swahili for "Don't worry.
Everything will be fine."
What's the phrase
that became famous everywhere...
after its appearance in "Lion King"?
- Six syllables.
- What?
I know this one.
The phrase from "Lion King".
(The answer is "Hakuna matata".)
- Let me answer.
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- Ha.
- I know this one.
- Ha?
- Ha.
(Haha?)
No, no. We will start over.
I will go first.
- I will go first.
- Go ahead.
- I don't know.
- Then toss it to me.
Toss it to me.
- Ha.
- Ku.
Go ahead.
(Haku)
Na.
Ma.
Ta.
Na.
- It's my turn.
- Hey!
- Ta.
- Na.
(She suddenly intercepts.)
It's my turn.
- It's my turn.
- Hey!
It's "Hakuna matata"!
Her answer doesn't count.
- So Min.
- Don't give it to me.
So Min, keep your mouth shut today.
What was that?
Here I go. Ta.
- Hakuna matata.
Hakuna matata.
Hakuna matana.
- All right.
- Thank goodness.
Don't toss it to me.
- Don't toss it to me.
- So Min is in trouble.
Haha, you totally belong
in the upper rank.
Do you see it now?
I see it now.
Haha belongs in the upper rank.
(You can be in the upper rank
by knowing "Hakuna matata".)
He says I belong in the upper rank.
He belongs in the upper rank.
He is knowledgeable.
(10 dried pollacks remain.)
- Here comes the next question.
- The king of common knowledge.
- Cro.
- Co.
- Dile.
- Te.
- Ar.
- Yes!
(They succeeded in getting
"Crocodile tear".)
- S.
- Pin.
(What is the term for a new story
that is based on an existing one?)
- O.
- Ff.
(They succeeded in getting
"Spin-off".)
Everyone knows that.
- Se Chan,
- Nice.
you are doing pretty well.
- I know that.
- Four dried pollacks remain.
This is hard.
The next question.
What's the idiom that means
"Original and eccentric thoughts..."
"that are beyond
ordinary people's comprehension"?
Eccentric?
You use this idiom a lot.
Really?
- Hold on.
- I think I know.
- "Beyond ordinary people's..."
- You say something is...
- Shall I give it a try?
- Yes.
- Do you know the answer?
- Se Chan wouldn't know.
"Lit".
Gi.
- Go on.
- Sang.
(Gisang)
- "Gisang".
- I know what it is.
- Five,
- four,
- It isn't that one.
- three,
- No, no.
- two,
- What's "Gisang"?
- one.
- What?
- Were we right?
(Were we right?)
- You were right.
- Gisangcheonoe!
(The answer was "Gisangcheonoe".)
- How could you not know that?
- Gisangcheonoe!
- Come on!
- Even I knew the answer.
- How could you not know that?
- Jae Suk.
- Original thoughts.
- Gisangcheonoe.
- Jae Suk, even I knew the answer.
- Really?
- Gisangcheonoe.
- I said it's "Gisangcheonoe".
- I had no idea.
- You didn't know?
- No.
- Gisangcheonoe.
- Jae Suk, even So Min knew.
It only occurred to me
when you brought it up.
I thought "Sang" was incorrect.
- I am sorry.
- It's okay, Jae Suk.
(Overjoyed)
What's the idiom that means
"Someone who ignores people..."
"and does everything on his own"?
- A greedy person.
- Could it be...
We had it earlier.
- What could it be?
- "Someone who ignores people..."
It has the nuance of someone
who is alone.
That's right! It's that one!
- We use it very often.
- I know it.
- Go ahead.
- Isn't that it?
- That's it. I think it's correct.
- Is it correct?
- Dok.
- Bul.
Jang.
(Dokbuljang)
(Time has passed
and only two dried pollacks remain.)
(If Ji Hyo answers it correctly,
they can get off work.)
Gun.
("Dokbuljanggun" is correct.)
(They successfully got rid of
100 dried pollacks.)
- Dokbuljanggun.
- All right!
- We are done.
- Are we done?
Let's take out
the last two dried pollacks.
Okay.
- Okay.
- We are smart.
We got rid of
all the dried pollacks.
Ji Hyo told me...
that when Jong Kook said "Dok",
she thought it was "Dokgodie".
(Thankfully,
she figured out the correct answer.)
My goodness. That's hilarious.
- The current time is 3:42 p.m.
- Okay.
Two people will receive the penalty.
- Oh, no.
- We will pick...
1 member from the upper rank
and 1 member from the bottom rank.
It's the Random Porcupine Game.
- How cute!
- Push its nose...
three or fewer times...
and toss it to the next person.
You lose if the needles pop out.
It's so cute.
- How do I do it?
- Push its nose.
- Do we touch the nose?
- Push it down.
Push it down.
- You can do it once more.
- Up to three times.
- It's up to you.
- As much as we want?
She pushed it three times!
Three or fewer times.
- Pop out!
- It's scary.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
I will get picked.
You don't know that.
You can push it two more times.
- Done. I won't push more.
- You never know.
The needles will pop out now.
I won't push more.
- Gosh.
- What was that?
You will break it!
No.
(Who will get the tedious penalty?)
I have a bad feeling about this.
The needles won't pop out this time.
I doubt the needles will pop out.
(The needles pop out!)
Why did you say that?
You are good at making
the wrong predictions.
(He is good at making
the wrong predictions.)
Se Chan will receive the penalty.
Okay.
(The order will be Jong Kook,
Jae Suk, Haha, and Suk Jin.)
- There are four of us.
- Kwang Soo isn't here.
- Staying behind is the worst.
- We have some reckless ones.
- Today's penalty...
- Kwang Soo isn't here.
involves staying behind.
Who will go second?
It's my turn.
He pushed it two times.
I hope they pop out.
(The needles bounce.)
I thought about pushing it again.
That's right. You don't belong
in the upper rank!
You shouldn't play with people
(A brave man who dreamed
of the upper rank)
- Okay.
- I thought about pushing it twice.
- That serves him right.
- The upper rank doesn't suit you.
I knew he would get chosen.
You should do what suits you.
That's so upsetting.
Thus, Se Chan and Haha...
- will get a penalty today.
- Okay.
There's a new baseball park
in Hwaseong here.
- I saw it on my way here.
- Right.
It's a baseball park for children.
You'll get a penalty there.
At a baseball park?
We should go there.
What are we doing
at a baseball park?
- It's the worst penalty ever.
- It's the worst.
You have to go somewhere else.
- That's the worst penalty.
- I know.
I'd rather get slapped in the face.
It's better to do it here.
- Sure. That's a lot better.
- Is it far from here?
Thank you for your hard work today.
- Thank you.
(Haha and Se Chan go to
the penalty place...)
(while the others go home.)
This baseball park is really nice.
- This is amazing.
- I know.
I didn't know Hwaseong had
a place like this.
Gosh. I'll definitely come here
with my family.
- It's good to play baseball.
- Of course.
So are we supposed
to play baseball here?
- You will get a special penalty.
- Okay.
You will play rock-paper-scissors
to decide orders.
And the one who loses...
Do you know the tee batting?
- You put a ball on there.
- Right.
You will hit 10 balls.
And the other person
should pick up the balls.
- You will do it in turn.
- In turn?
So it matters who goes first.
The one who goes first
is at a disadvantage.
- So it's 10 balls per person?
- Yes.
The farther the ball goes...
So you should talk to each other.
What are you up to?
We should just touch it gently.
Let's do this.
- But if you...
- What?
- I'm really stressed out.
- Don't be.
He's even worse than Kwang Soo.
Okay. I'll be a new man.
Just drop the ball here.
- I'll hit it gently like this.
- Sure.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Will you go first?
- Yes. He goes first.
- Me?
I'll go next.
If you hit it hard,
I'll send my ball really far.
You should remember that.
If you ever...
send the ball over the line,
I'll hit the balls as hard as I can.
You should remember that.
If the ball goes over the wall,
you should go out to pick it up.
(Se Chan goes next,
so he has control of the game.)
- Haha.
- I have a lot on my mind.
It's okay to hit it hard.
I've never done this before.
Haha, you should
hold your bat short.
(Haha, you should
hold your bat short.)
Okay? Hit it gently.
Just do what you want
and see what I do to you.
(What's Haha's choice?)
Hit it gently. Then I'll be gentle.
(A long hit to the left)
I'm 100 percent sure
he won't keep his promise.
I know him.
(Haha had no intention to trust
Se Chan in the first place.)
(Gasping)
Where is it?
(The little clean-up hitter
is quite strong.)
I know him.
Go ahead and do it.
(He lures Se Chan
with an infield hit.)
(Then he makes a long hit
to the right.)
I went that way earlier.
It's over.
Gosh, it's so bothersome.
It's so annoying.
Haha, you'll see.
(You'll see, Haha.)
You sent the ball there.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
(They've become serious
after the 10 long hits.)
(Is the ball flying toward Haha?)
(He fails to catch the ball
because of his short legs.)
He almost caught it.
I should hit it this way.
(A long hit to the right)
(When Haha is on the right,)
(he sends the ball to the left.)
(Now he hits it gently.)
Pick it up.
(The clean-up hitter
from Dongducheon is clever.)
- That punk.
- It's over.
- Pick them up.
- It's so bothersome.
Haha and Se Chan,
your penalty is over.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
(One shiny day)
(In front of the photo wall,)
(the members pose for a picture.)
(What are we taking pictures for?)
(The Strange Family Photo Race)
(They stand on their spots
according to their roles.)
(Keep a straight face.)
(The photographer asks
for a straight face for no reason.)
(Are they switching roles?)
(The race to defend
their roles begin.)
(Quadratic formula)
Geun Sik formula?
(They struggle to be remembered...)
(as a person.)
(How would
the new family picture end?)
(The Strange Family Photo Race)