(A dark and rainy morning)
(A mysterious place...)
(with dim lighting)
(The 8 members have been invited
to this place.)
What?
What is this place?
(The 8 members have been invited
to this place.)
What is this place?
(The light is coming down
in dead silence.)
- Jae Suk.
- What?
Below the average common knowledge.
(Below the average common knowledge)
- What is this?
- The empty heads of Korea.
Welcome, members of Running Man.
- What did it say?
- What?
Hello.
(With a mysterious voice,)
(all the lights are turned on.)
- What?
- I heard the word "empty heads".
- Did he say empty heads?
- "Empty Head Land"?
(The empty space appears.)
- Se Chan is Empty Head.
- What?
Hello.
- What are we doing here?
- I heard the word "empty heads".
- What?
- Empty heads?
- "Empty Head Land"?
- Did it say "Empty Head Land"?
- Why is it Empty Head?
- Empty Head Land?
We know what Empty Head is.
- Se Chan is Empty Head.
- Empty!
- This is strange.
- It is.
Are we taking tests today?
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
Only when we're smart?
The test will begin soon.
You can choose a room you want
from numbers 1 to 8.
Are the rooms different?
Is there any difference?
- What is this?
- What? Are we taking tests?
This is... Gosh.
- I'll pick number 6.
- I want number 8.
This is crazy.
What is this?
(Jong Kook picks Room 8,
and Jae Suk picks Room 1.)
What is this?
- I want number 2.
- Number 2?
- I pick number 4.
- I want number 8.
Number four.
I hate the rooms to begin with.
Gosh, it's stuffy in here.
I bet this can be difficult.
This is so annoying.
Gosh, I really hate this.
What do I do?
What's all this?
I might not be able to go home.
(Right at that moment...)
Who is it?
- Quiz...
- What?
- Are they locking it?
Why are you locking the door?
What are you doing?
Hey, quiet down!
- Why are you locking the door?
- Are they locking it?
Are they locking it?
- Don't lock the door.
- Why are you locking the door?
(The members are locked
in the rooms they picked.)
- What are you doing?
- Did they lock the doors?
Why are you locking the door?
- It's so stuffy in here.
- What is happening?
What is this? Number four...
(All 8 members are locked
in Empty Head Land at 10 a.m.)
Gosh, this is...
What is this? Invite a friend?
(Each room has a computer...)
(and a whiteboard.)
"This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from..."
"only when you're smart.
This room is for the pretest..."
"where we will test your potential."
"Answer the questions of the pretest
to get 100 points in total."
"You can choose
the question's level of difficulty."
"And points vary according to
the difficulty of each question."
"Check the table below for
the difficulty level and points."
"If you answer wrong,
you lose ten points each."
Ten points for Kindergarten.
15 points for Elementary School,
25 points for Middle School.
And 70 points for Bar Exam.
(The questions are based
on the actual curricula.)
My gosh.
If I answer wrong
to the question for Kindergarten,
it will be humiliating.
Darn it.
To get 100 points,
I just have to answer ten questions
for Kindergarten.
It can be humiliating,
but I have to get out of here.
(They can get out by answering
10 questions for Kindergarten.)
I guess we should send a message.
(Each laptop has a chat room on it.)
Hello?
(Welcome to Room 1.)
(Can I chat now? Hello?)
(We will begin the pretest now.
Choose the level of difficulty.)
"We will begin the pretest
of Empty Head Land now."
"Choose the level of difficulty
that you want and type it."
"Then you will get
your questions accordingly."
"Write down your answer
on the whiteboard..."
"and show it to the camera."
I bet this is difficult.
(The members can only communicate
through the chat room and camera.)
(10 points, 15 points, 25 points,
and 70 points)
Come on.
I'll go with the question
for Kindergarten.
It's because...
I love children.
Are the questions
for Kindergarten difficult?
(Haha chose a question for
Kindergarten from the beginning.)
(Shouting)
Hey!
How is this...
How is this question
for kindergarteners?
What?
Hey, how is this question
for kindergarteners?
- Gosh, this is...
- Is it difficult?
This is so humiliating.
- I'm so ashamed.
- Is it hard?
Dream, don't watch this episode.
(Dream, don't watch this episode.)
I'm sorry, Dream.
Watch the show again next week.
I don't even remember
how many times I said this.
All right then.
(He starts thinking carefully.)
I need to read
the Chinese character.
Hang on. So this is...
This is for kindergarteners.
So this might be "yu".
I'll go with "yu".
I'll just take a guess.
(Yu)
(Incorrect. The answer is "jwa".
You lost 10 points.)
(Haha's current score is
minus 10 points.)
(He's a shameful father
who insists that "jwa" is "yu".)
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed!
(He lost 10 points right away.)
I'll go with Middle School.
Gosh, this is...
Is this for kindergarteners?
I don't think so.
Isn't this
for elementary school students?
How is this for kindergarteners?
That's ridiculous.
I'll go with Elementary School then.
(Jae Suk's current score
is 10 points.)
My fellow comedians
are watching this.
(The original Empty Head,
Se Chan is very anxious.)
I'm doomed.
I'll answer 10 questions
for Kindergarten and get out.
A question for Kindergarten.
"What's the Chinese idiom that means
you sing and shout while drunk..."
This is...
Hey!
Hey! This is ridiculous.
I know this one.
I know the answer,
but this is...
hard enough to be for Bar Exam.
"Goseong..."
(Goseongbang)
(Hesitant)
Is it "goseongbanggwa"?
(Goseongbanggwa?)
Goseongbangga...
Goseongbangga?
(He hesitates to write
his answer after bragging.)
Goseongbanggwa?
This should be right.
It's "goseongbangga".
No?
It's correct. Okay!
(Correct. You get 10 points.
Choose the next question.)
This question isn't
for kindergarteners.
Bar Exam.
"Bar Exam."
Do you think we'd never get
questions for Bar Exam right?
(The empty heads pick questions
for Bar Exam to avoid disgrace.)
I'll go with Bar Exam. Bring it on.
I just need to pick a number.
I should go with Bar Exam.
(Suk Jin tries to answer
the question for Bar Exam.)
I should give it a try.
It's here.
(The long question for
Bar Exam appears on the screen.)
Gosh, I'm doomed.
The Bar Exam question is too hard.
"Which of the following
is not true about the case?"
(The small letters
fill a whole page.)
What is this?
I want to go home already.
What is this thing?
What's the thing that looks
like a fly swatter?
(This is the fly swatter.)
There are Chinese characters.
I'm so doomed.
Constitutional Court?
I feel like throwing up.
(Retching)
I'm so stressed out.
(I'm so stressed out.)
I don't know. I took a guess.
(She just took a guess
after writing some letters.)
Oh no.
"Due to an infringement accident..."
Gosh, it's wrongfully used.
(The middle-aged test taker
still hasn't given up hope.)
(He carefully reads the question
in the tiny cell.)
"However, it was denied
for lack of legal grounds."
It was leaked.
All right then.
(He finally made up his mind.)
This is the answer
to the question for Bar Exam.
(Correct. You got 70 points.
Choose the next question.)
(Suk Jin's current score
is 70 points.)
I got it right! It's correct.
This is amazing.
(Big Nose picked the correct answer
to the question for Bar Exam.)
Guys.
My current score is 70 points.
- That's amazing.
- Are you bragging?
Yes, I'm bragging.
(Convert the following fraction
into a percentage.)
Percentage?
I don't know percentage.
(So Min is stuck on a math problem
for elementary school students.)
I'm not good at mathematics.
I can't do math.
This is my answer.
Isn't this it?
(She just multiplied 4 by 100.)
I lost 10 points. I'm in trouble.
25 percent?
Oh, it's about percent.
What do I do? It was percent.
I know that a fourth is 25 percent.
Please edit this part cut.
(So Min's current score
is minus 10 points.)
Okay. Let's go.
What?
Which one is not true?
(This is an invitation
to a birthday party.)
(Which of the following
is not true?)
Gosh, this is funny.
(Correct. You got 25 points.
Choose the next question.)
(What should Kwang Soo say
in the following dialogue?)
"Good morning, Kwang Soo."
"Hello, Dad."
(Good morning, Kwang Soo.)
(I slept like a rock.)
"Hello, Dad. I slept like a rock."
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is "Good morning.")
(Se Chan's current score
is minus 20 points.)
(The more he tries to solve,
the lower his score gets.)
I want to get out of here.
My fellow comedians
from "Comedy Big League".
Change the channel.
(It's 3:20 now.
What time was it 43 minutes ago?)
43 minutes ago?
(She does the math carefully.)
All right.
(It's 3:20 now.
What time was it 43 minutes ago?)
I got it.
(2:57)
The answer is...
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is 2:37.)
Gosh, I calculated it in tens.
I can't believe this.
I calculated it in tens.
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo's current score
is minus 20 points.)
(What's the name
of the following formula?)
(He's facing the 2nd crisis.)
(It makes him repent
of his ignorance.)
Dream.
I studied liberal arts.
I mean, liberal arts are...
about something grammatical...
and something artistic.
That's what I studied.
I just try to be wise.
(What's the name
of the following formula?)
(Groaning)
When I took
the college entrance exam...
This is the trick I did.
Usually...
The answers are one of these.
One of them might be
the correct answer.
(It's the legendary principle
of -1, 0, and 1.)
All right then.
(He thinks he's supposed
to solve the equation.)
Minus b... Plus and minus?
Why does it have
plus and minus together?
It looks like a Chinese character.
Is this "to"?
(He says "to" after getting
the problem about "jwa" wrong.)
There are only a, b, and c.
It should have some numbers.
(Oh, right.)
"What's the name
of the following formula?"
Hang on.
Hold on.
What kind of formula do I know?
I think I can get this right.
The name of the formula?
It can't be the separation formula.
The only formula I know is...
(Quadratic formula!)
Here I go.
(He writes down
the only formula he knows.)
Quadratic formula?
(Quadratic formula)
(Correct. You got 25 points.
Choose the next question.)
(He finally stops losing points
and recovers from the minus.)
Hey.
This is going well.
(Haha's current score is 5 points.)
Make sure to show
that I said quadratic formula.
(He's surprised by himself.)
Is quadratic formula the base
times the height divided by two?
It's the radius times
the radius times 3.14.
3.14 is pi.
I'll go with Elementary School.
How many questions should I answer?
Continent?
Hang on. Which continent is this?
I don't think this is a question
for elementary school students.
(Oceania)
(Correct. You got 15 points.
Your current score is 55 points.)
Hey, this is too difficult.
(Correct. You got 15 points.
Your current score is 55 points.)
(He chose a middle school question
continuing his sweeping upturn.)
Oh, that? Gosh.
(What is the layer between the crust
and the outer core?)
I'm not sure if this is right.
(Mantle)
(Correct. You got 25 points.
Your current score is 80 points.)
Is it the correct answer?
(Correct. You got 25 points.
Your current score is 80 points.)
This is great.
Really? Is it the correct answer?
(Elementary school, 15 points,
Find the angle for the blank.)
What's this?
(Elementary school, 15 points,
Find the angle for the blank.)
So this is 80 degrees.
How would I know this?
This one here looks...
similar to that one.
I feel so lonely.
This is a lonely fight.
It's slightly wider than that.
(This is how he solved questions
his entire life.)
That means it's slightly bigger
than 45 degrees.
And the other one is 80 degrees.
It looks around 50 degrees.
Or 55 degrees.
It must be around 55 degrees.
55 degrees.
Darn. I'm so upset.
What? Is it the correct answer?
(Correct. You got 15 points.
Choose the difficulty level.)
Great. I just guessed
and got it right.
(Happy)
(He's excited that he solved
a math question after decades.)
That's funny.
(Write Lee Kwang Soo's nickname
"Giraffe" in English.)
They underestimated me.
Oh, I got it right. Okay!
- It can't be for a kindergartener.
- "Giraffe".
Gosh. I'm getting confused suddenly.
This is driving me nuts.
How to spell "giraffe"...
I think I'm not getting enough air
in this booth.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
What is "giraffe" in English?
- It's "40 signal".
- "40 signal"?
Yes.
- Girin.
- This is ridiculous!
Is it "girin"?
(Is it "girin"?)
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is "giraffe".)
"Gir..."? "Giraffe"?
What... What's "giraffe"?
- Oh, man. Please.
- Please.
(Kwang Soo wrote "girafe".)
(It's missing an "F".)
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is "giraffe".)
(Room 7, Lee Kwang Soo,
current score, minus 20 points)
I swear. I really knew the answer.
I saw this word so many times.
(He got it wrong when it was one
of a few English words he knows.)
I choose the kindergarten level.
(The point hunter Jong Kook chose
the kindergarten level.)
What's this?
(Kindergarten, 10 points)
(Write the names of the dances
of each country.)
(Korea, Fan dance)
I don't know the answer
to the last one. Hold on.
(Egypt)
What country is this?
(The last question is
unexpectedly difficult.)
Why is the kindergarten level
so difficult?
What is
the traditional Egyptian dance?
Jong Kook, it's Macarena.
- No, it isn't. What?
- The sphinx!
The sphinx dance
that Ji Sang Yeol does!
Jong Kook, it's the cobra dance!
I'll pass.
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is "Tanoura".)
You know, I feel so betrayed
by kindergartens.
I told you so. It's not easy at all.
Then I should solve
another middle school question.
Come on. I've done well enough
to get out of here.
Here. If I get this one right,
please let me out.
You should let me out now.
(Congratulations! You passed
the test with 105 points.)
105 points! I passed!
I want to get out of here.
Let me out now!
How do I get out?
(Jae Suk is the 1st
to get 100 points.)
(The door to the secret room is
opening.)
(Jae Suk who passed the test...)
(entered the main room
of the Empty Head Land.)
What?
Hurry up and come out, guys.
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, did you get out?
- Of course.
- Really?
Of course, I came out.
(Jae Suk is waiting alone
in the main room.)
Jae Suk, I can't even understand
the questions.
What does it say?
I got another one wrong.
(Many are screaming
as they get questions wrong.)
I think I might have to wait
for too long.
(He might have to wait for long
in the empty main room.)
Gosh. My score is 90 points.
The kindergarten questions are
so darn difficult.
(Kindergarten)
Let's go. Let's go.
Give me an easy question this time!
(He chose the kindergarten again
typing with only his index fingers.)
Give me a question about something
I learned in kindergarten!
I didn't learn things like this
in my kindergarten!
(Write the numbers in the blanks
in order.)
Oh, good.
(Write the numbers in the blanks
in order.)
But... It hurts my pride somehow.
(Write the numbers in the blanks
in order.)
21, 22, 23, 24...
(He's mumbling
after writing down the answer.)
I can't believe I had to
double-check my answer.
(Congratulations! You passed
the test with 100 points.)
Okay! Where do I get out?
(Jong Kook is the 2nd to pass.)
Jong Kook is done.
- Where do I get out?
- Jong Kook, did you pass the test?
(Jong Kook tenaciously stuck to
the kindergarten questions.)
- What's this? Hi.
- Welcome.
(He's overwhelmed to meet
the winner of the test.)
Why would the kindergarten questions
be so difficult?
- Gosh, seriously.
- They're from the actual exams.
Really?
- My gosh.
- They were so difficult.
Two of us got out.
It's my turn. I'll get out.
"1 carbon atom
and 2 oxygen atoms..."
(What is the molecule made up of
1 carbon atom and 2 oxygen atoms?)
(1 carbon atom
and 2 oxygen atoms...)
The square roots are inside and out
of the parentheses. I have no idea.
(Sparkling water)
Incorrect?
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is "carbon dioxide".)
Carbon dioxide? Oh, right.
But doesn't sparkling water have
something to do with carbon dioxide?
(Solve the equation below.)
(Darn it.)
Hey, you mean punks!
(Middle School, 25 points,
Solve the equation below.)
The square roots are inside and out
of the parentheses. I have no idea.
I'll try to solve it my way.
3 plus 2 equals 5.
And that's 4. The answer is 1.
3 times 2 equals...
(He even tries to multiply
all the numbers he can see.)
It's 6. So it's 6.
All right. The answer is...
Two.
Is it five?
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is 5.)
(While the original empty head is
struggling with square roots...)
She's coming out?
- Gosh. I'm upset.
- Ji Hyo passed it.
- What?
- How?
- Ji Hyo passed it?
- What?
No way!
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook were
watching the others.)
She's coming out?
- Ji Hyo passed it.
- What?
- Ji Hyo passed it?
- Ji Hyo got out?
- No way!
Ji Hyo passed it?
(Hi.)
- What did you say?
- Don't lie to me!
- Hey, you...
- Gosh, you empty heads.
Hey.
- Hey, how did you...
- You empty heads.
How did you get out so fast?
No way. Ji Hyo can't be out already.
No way!
There were very easy ones too.
I got one bar exam question right.
- Really?
- You got it right?
- She got a bar exam question right?
- Really?
- That can't be true.
- Are you serious?
- I got it right.
- You should start studying.
I choose the Bar Exam.
(5 minutes earlier)
(She got a question wrong
but tried again.)
I don't know.
I'll just take a guess.
(Number 4)
(And number 4 was
the correct answer.)
- That's impressive. Ji Hyo.
- You should take the bar exam.
- You're incredible.
- Prepare for the exam.
You should start studying.
Suk Jin is still in there.
(Suk Jin even solved
a bar exam question.)
- Even Ji Hyo got out too.
- The square root of three...
Hey, do you know
how to calculate a square root?
Gosh. This is so difficult.
Wait. It's not.
9 times 4 equals 36.
9 times 4 equals...
9 times 2 equals 18.
9 times 4... That's 37.
Then add 3...
9 times 9 equals 81. So it's 84.
That's right.
(After a weird calculation...)
Let's go. Let me answer.
This is it.
(He submitted a weird answer.)
5? The answer is 5?
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is 5.)
Gosh.
The staff members seem
quite baffled too.
That should be considered
as a correct answer.
You guys are so mean.
30 minutes have passed
since the test began.
From now on,
the points for every question...
- will be doubled.
- Okay.
- I'll be out if I get this right.
(If x is minus 3, what's the value
of 2 minus the square of x?)
No more math problems, please.
I was always bad at math.
It's taking you too long.
I got only 1 or 2 questions right
in the CSAT.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- That's pi. Pi equals 3.14.
- Please give me an easy question.
Darn it. I don't know.
(He wrote down an answer
while mumbling about pi.)
This one is actually quite easy.
- Isn't this correct?
- I want to get out of here.
(Correct. You got 50 points.
Your current score is 110 points.)
- What is it? Did you get it right?
- I got it right.
- What?
Why are you so surprised?
Okay!
(Kwang Soo came in 4th
in the preliminary test.)
- Kwang Soo is coming out too.
- Kwang Soo passed it too?
It took me a long time.
(He came in 4th unexpectedly
just like Ji Hyo.)
- It's unexpected.
- Oh, this is what it's like.
- I'm getting out.
- Hey, you're out.
(Following Kwang Soo,
So Min escaped.)
So Min came out.
I knew it. You should've
studied hard in school.
"Complete the sentence
using the right interjection..."
Suk Jin hasn't come out yet?
Suk Jin, what's your score?
It's 55 points.
(He has a long way
to get 100 points.)
He didn't ask about your age.
- Not your age.
- My score is 55 points.
"Complete the sentence
using the right interjection..."
- "for the situation."
- Poor Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is still in there?
- Why...
Why does he always act
like a know-it-all?
I think he's in there intentionally
to be funny.
- He always acts like that.
- I believe that's the case.
- He just wants to be funny.
- But do you think it's funny?
Is this funny?
It's not funny. It's sad.
"The right interjection..."
She slipped and fell?
It says "It hurts."
"Thump! It hurts." An interjection?
An interjection?
I have to write an interjection?
Hey, what is an interjection?
An interjection, you know.
- "Wow."
- "Oh, gosh."
- "Oh, dear."
- "Darn."
"Geez."
- "Shoot."
- "It hurts."
- Right.
- That's it, Suk Jin.
- This is the answer.
(He decided to go with
"Goodness! It hurts.")
Gosh. The answer is "oops".
"Oops"?
(Incorrect. You lost 10 points.
The answer is "Oops!")
This is driving me nuts.
- Come on out now.
- "Oops!"
This is so...
- Suk Jin won't get out soon.
- Wait.
My score is 45 points.
- Okay!
- Is someone coming out?
Is it Se Chan?
Okay!
(Se Chan came in 6th
in the preliminary test.)
That made me feel so good.
(He barely managed to get 100 points
as the points were doubled.)
- Really?
- Se Chan passed the test.
Hey.
I'm totally humiliated.
(He's walking out
with an upset look on his face.)
- Are you serious?
- "Oops!"
(Right then,)
(Kwang Soo gave him a hand signal.)
(At the place Kwang Soo pointed at,)
My gosh.
(Se Chan received an envelope.)
Suk Jin won't get out soon.
Jong Kook, trust me.
He won't get out soon.
- Hey, you came out.
- He won't get out soon.
(Check that out first!)
(Those who passed the test
have their eyes on Se Chan.)
Okay.
(What secret could be written
in the envelope?)
(You are 1 of the geniuses
of Running Man...)
You are one of the geniuses
of Running Man...
who passed the preliminary test
before the others.
This is a hidden rule that's given
only to the six geniuses.
(You are 1 of the geniuses
of Running Man.)
Hey.
(This is a hidden rule that's given
only to the geniuses.)
- The remaining two members...
- Focus!
will participate in the race
without knowing this rule.
So please act naturally
to the end of the race.
You should be smart
to escape from this Empty Head Land.
The 6 geniuses should use
the 2 dunces to escape.
You have six hours to escape.
If you figure out the passcode
for the exit door...
and escape from this room
in six hours,
the six geniuses win the race.
The geniuses will receive
3,000 dollars as a prize,
and the dunces will receive
a penalty.
However, if you fail to escape
in time,
the six geniuses will receive
a penalty,
and the dunces will receive
the prize money.
(The dunces will receive the prize
if the geniuses fail.)
(A few minutes earlier)
(Jae Suk who came out first
received the hidden rule.)
What is this?
(Jae Suk who came in 1st
received the hidden rule.)
Why would the kindergarten questions
be so difficult?
(Jong Kook who came in 2nd
also received it.)
Oh, my goodness.
I understand.
(Smiling)
When 1 of them comes out,
the remaining 2 will team up, right?
That's right.
- But we shouldn't tell them.
- Of course.
We shouldn't tell them.
(The geniuses were secretly informed
about the hidden rule for them.)
(So the team of 6 geniuses
was formed.)
When all eight of you gather again,
we will announce that today's race
is a group mission for all members,
so either all of you win
or all of you get a penalty,
which is a fake rule.
(When everyone gathers again,
a fake rule will be announced.)
Every time the geniuses succeed...
in completing a mission
while lying to the dunces,
the geniuses are allowed to enter
the escape room.
You can get all the information
regarding the escape in the room.
So you should act as if you are all
on the same team...
so that the dunces cooperate
to the end.
(You can find the passcode there,
so make sure the dunces cooperate.)
(The geniuses have to lie
to the 2 dunces...)
(and use them to escape
and win the race.)
- It's real money.
- We're on the same team, right?
Yes.
Here you go.
(While the geniuses exchange
silent signals with one another...)
Why are the kindergarten questions
so difficult?
(Why are the kindergarten questions
so difficult?)
Was it Dangun Wanggeom? Gosh.
Kids learn this in kindergarten?
- They're trying to make fun of me.
- Hey.
Suk Jin is still in there too.
So don't worry.
It's not too late.
Suk Jin is in there too.
Just focus!
This is the answer.
(Dunce 2 who used to be a genius...)
I got this one wrong too?
This is driving me nuts.
Hey, my score will
go below zero again.
Gosh.
Suk Jin...
(Laughing)
- Suk Jin looks so serious.
- If you just look at the screen,
he looks like a businessman
working in the IT industry.
Suk Jin...
What? Everyone else got out?
Time's up.
The preliminary test is over.
Suk Jin and Haha
who failed to pass the test...
will come out
regardless of the result.
- Is it over?
- Who else is left?
Gosh, those empty heads.
This is embarrassing.
- Forget it. Just come on out.
- You can just come out.
You majored in
business administration in college.
Gosh. I'm so upset.
- I mean, Those questions...
- You know, right?
- They can't be for kindergartners.
- It was so difficult.
- Exactly.
- I'm pretty sure...
- Suk Jin.
- There's something fishy about it.
- I think...
- They tried to make fun of us.
- I got more difficult questions.
- But...
It's because... Listen to me.
Those can't be questions
for kindergarteners.
I understand why Haha failed.
- But you...
- Hey.
- What?
- I...
- That's even more upsetting.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
- At first...
- I chose middle school questions.
All eight contestants,
please gather around.
As a result of the preliminary test,
only the six members who passed it
are acknowledged as geniuses.
Suk Jin and Haha who failed it...
will participate in the race...
- as dunces.
- Mr. Dunce.
As I told you in the beginning,
today's race is Smart Escape Race,
Empty Head Land.
You have to complete given missions
and solve quizzes...
and escape from this room
to win the race.
All we have to do is
to escape from this room?
You have six hours to escape.
- We'll start counting down now.
- How can you be one of them?
Today, all of you are
on the same team.
(Today, all of you are
on the same team.)
(The fake rule about all the members
playing as a team is announced.)
(When all eight of you
gather again,)
(we will announce that today's race
is a group mission for all members,)
(so either all of you win
or all of you get a penalty,)
(which is a fake rule.)
(Only the 6 geniuses were informed
about the fake rule.)
(The fake rule is announced again
for the 2 dunces.)
If you escape in time, you will all
share the price of 3,000 dollars.
(The geniuses are acting
as if they never heard about it.)
- Really?
- Oh, my. 3,000 dollars?
If you fail, all of you will receive
a penalty together.
- Can you see the escape room?
- Yes. What is it?
If you complete a mission
where all of you should succeed,
- we'll open it for five minutes.
- Is that so?
But only the geniuses are allowed
in that room for five minutes.
And if you solve a quiz in the room,
you'll get the passcode
for your choice of lock.
While the six geniuses are solving
quizzes representing the team,
the two dunces will carry out
another mission in the main room.
The result will determine
the difficulty level of the quizzes.
Got it.
We're good at things like that,
right?
The result of their missions will
determine the difficulty level...
- of the quizzes we'll solve, right?
- Correct.
- You should do well.
- But we're all on the same team.
- We're geniuses.
- We're geniuses, and you're dunces.
We'll solve the quizzes
while you two...
- Hey, stop saying that.
- Suk Jin, listen.
You and Haha should do well
in the main room.
- We need you guys to succeed here.
- Shut your mouth.
- You managed to get out somehow.
- We'll ask you.
(Time left: 05:51:42)
We'll begin the first team mission.
- What is it?
- The first test is...
the Brain Health Test.
- "Brain health"?
This is a scientifically proven test
through which you can check...
your brain health by yourself.
- Really?
- It's scientifically proven?
Look at these 35 words
written in different colors,
and say the color of the words.
- For example...
- I should say "red"...
- Yes.
- although it says "blue".
That's right. You should say "red"
for this one.
- Okay. I get it.
- Black, green, blue, yellow...
In this case, you should say
"black, green, blue, yellow, red".
I can actually check
my brain health.
That looks difficult.
You'll take turns
until three of you succeed.
You will have 20 seconds
in the beginning.
You'll get 1 extra second
whenever 2 members fail.
Oh, boy.
But you will have to spend
more time escaping.
- Oh, right.
- I get it.
Okay. I understand.
- Let's give it a try.
- Black,
- blue, yellow, red...
- I see.
I'm mildly colorblind.
Me too. Actually, I'm...
I'm mildly colorblind too.
(I'm mildly colorblind too.)
You are?
The dunces will go last, right?
Let's put them in between
since they're bad at it.
- Gosh, those punks.
- Gosh.
Hey, how about a 2-on-2 match?
- Against whom?
- No way.
- How about a quiz match?
- Let's do it later.
Come on. Both of you, calm down.
- You know why we're upset.
- Just laugh it off.
- But what are you going to do?
- I'm so upset.
Who wants to go first?
(Raising her hand)
So Min will go first.
- Ready. Set. Go.
- Get set.
- You can start now.
- Green, red, black,
black, red, black, yellow,
black, red, black.
- That's black.
- Keep going.
- Continue.
- Should I keep going to the end?
Red, yellow, black, green, black,
- green, re... Bla... No, blue.
- I don't think I can do this.
Green. No, bla...
(Bla... No, blue. Green. No, bla...)
Red, yellow...
- Gosh, seriously.
- It's difficult.
- Hey, hey!
- That's a lot.
- I couldn't...
- So Min, focus, will you?
Your brain has rotten!
Don't read the words.
You shouldn't see the letters.
You should focus on the color.
You shouldn't read them
but see the whole thing.
You can't see the forest
for the trees.
It's so difficult.
There are too many of them.
- So Min.
- I'll go next.
- You should focus, okay?
- I'll do it.
- You should...
You should never let the letters
confuse you.
- Hey, Rambo.
- Can you do that?
(Jong Kook tries it.)
Blue, black, red, yellow, black,
red, blue, black, green, black,
- red, blue.
- Oh, wow.
- black, green,
- Faster.
black, black, green,
yellow, red, red,
green, green, black, blue, red,
- blue, green, blue, red, black,
- Oh, my.
- green, black...
- He sounds angry.
- What a shame. You did well.
- That wasn't fast enough?
- Hey, you should've done it faster.
- You should be faster than that.
What?
(What?)
Hey, Rambo.
Can't you do it?
- I mean...
- Look at me.
You see,
I watched one of the "Rambo" movies
starring Sylvester Stallone...
once again not long ago.
I think he looks just like Rambo.
- He looks just like Rambo.
- I agree.
- Hey, Rambo.
- Jong Kook, wear a red headband.
- Hey, listen. Keep your mind...
- Hey, Rambo.
- He looks just like Rambo.
- You see...
Watch me. I'll try this time.
(No one is listening to him.)
- Hey...
- I think he looks just like Rambo.
- No one is listening to you.
- He looks just like Rambo.
- I'm listening.
- Hey, Rambo.
- As if I was talking to myself.
- Since we're the dunces,
- Listen.
- we can't seem to blend in.
- I'll go next.
- Will you?
- No.
- I'll try. And I'll tell you...
- Step back, guys.
- what you guys did wrong.
- Gosh. I'm so upset.
- What did I do wrong?
- I'll tell you.
- You got carried away.
- Suk Jin.
- You should stay calm...
- Okay. Stop talking and show me.
- And speak in a low voice.
- Show me how to do it.
You should see it from a distance.
- You should speak in a low voice.
- We can't see the screen.
- We can't see it.
- Ready, go.
Yellow, blue, blue, green...
- It's over.
- Blue, green...
- What is he doing?
- He's hopeless.
- This is so funny.
- Yellow, yellow, green,
- I think...
- Could he develop dementia soon?
- green,
- red,
- What's wrong with him?
- black, yellow, yellow,
- How bad is his brain health?
- green,
- Could he develop dementia soon?
- Why is he doing this?
- green,
- red, green,
- Am I right?
- He's moving his hands like this.
- black,
- blue...
- I think...
- Suk Jin, please cheer up!
- You can do this!
- Black, blue...
Good health, blessing,
- and luck.
- Black...
- Green.
- You're bad at this.
What on earth was that?
- Suk Jin...
- You guys made me laugh.
- He was terrible at it.
- Do this...
Do this in your free time.
- Or this.
- Do this in your free time.
Things like this.
- Or play cards.
- In the opposite direction.
- You guys made me laugh.
How could you be that terrible?
You should've at least
made it to the last line.
- Darn it.
- It wasn't bad though.
Sure.
You...
- It's important to stay focused.
- Did you see that just now?
- Did you see that?
- See what?
Suk Jin answered Haha's response...
with a fist bump, but he...
Show them.
(High five, fist bump)
- We don't click.
- You guys don't click at all.
(Suk Jin went for a fist bump
while Haha went for a high five.)
(They tried to match
the other person, but failed.)
- We don't click.
- You guys don't click at all.
You can say that again.
Don't be so considerate, okay?
(This is how it's like to click.)
They're both too sweet.
- I'll give it a go.
- Sure.
- Just look at the colors.
- Rambo,
- focus on the colors.
- But near the end...
Okay, I'll speed through them.
- You have 22 seconds left.
- See me fly through this.
- Let's do this!
- All right!
Red, black, green, yellow,
green, red, red,
yellow, blue, black,
yellow, black, yellow, black, blue.
- Then...
- His legs.
- Yellow, blue, green, green.
- What's with your legs?
- Black, red...
- Why are you all worked up?
- Blue, black, yellow.
- Hurry.
Red, yellow, blue,
green, no black.
Red, red, yellow.
- Wrong.
- Darn!
- You were almost there.
- It's difficult, you know.
- Focus only on the colors.
- It's not easy.
Only look at the colors.
- Jae Suk.
Why were you stomping your feet?
Where were you off to?
- Hey. Be quiet.
- Why were you...
- Stay put, will you?
- Stop being so nervous?
- Who next?
- Kwang Soo.
- I'll give it a shot.
- You'll get 22 seconds.
I've tried it on the sidelines,
- and I got it right every time.
- Look at it from a distance.
Wish yourself good luck first.
- Go for it.
- Wish me luck!
Good luck.
- Let's go.
- Go!
Red, yellow, black, blue, yellow,
green, green, black, green, black.
- Yellow, blue, blue, yellow.
- He's good.
Red, red,
green, red, blue, black,
green, blue, black, green, yellow.
- You're almost there.
- Black, red, blue,
black, yellow,
black, red, blue,
black, red, green,
black, red, green, blue.
Red, green, blue!
- Okay!
- Nice!
- Good job.
- Nice.
Okay, let's move on.
Rambo, wait.
Wait.
- You were amazing.
- That was great.
- But why...
- Rambo.
- Didn't I do well?
- Step aside now.
- We have a game to play.
- Move.
Okay!
- Haha's next.
- Haha.
- Hey.
- You've got this.
- Let's go.
- You can do this.
You can do this.
Blue, yellow, red,
blue, black, blue,
red, yellow, red,
- yellow, green, green.
- Everyone has a routine.
- Blue...
- Are you a rapper?
- Blue, black,
- blue, blue.
- Are you in a rap contest?
- Black, blue...
- You look younger than your age.
Red, blue,
yellow, green, green,
red...
- Wrong!
- Darn it.
It reminded me of Z-KIRI.
- Hey, Z-KIRI.
- You shed years off your age.
You were Z-KIRI again.
Why were you back as Z-KIRI?
- His method though...
- Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- Could you do this?
- You were in third place.
- Go, Ji Hyo.
- Her brain could be healthier...
since it hasn't been used much.
- Like the brain of a newborn.
- Go ahead.
Green, green, red, black, yellow,
red, blue, yellow, red, blue.
- You're out.
- That was black.
- Which one?
- Ji Hyo, go ahead and take a break.
Ji Hyo, go ahead and take a break.
- Time out.
- Take a short break.
- Wait.
- She's not done yet.
- Take a short break.
- A brief one.
- Ji Hyo wasn't ready.
- Steady your pace.
- Calm down a little.
- She wasn't ready.
- Well...
- Did she say "black"?
- Ji Hyo wasn't ready.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo.
I'll go.
- Here I go.
- And go!
- Good luck.
- Red, yellow, black,
blue, yellow, green, green,
black, green, black,
yellow, blue, blue, yellow.
- Stay focused!
- Blue, black, red.
- You're almost there.
- You've got this.
- Green.
- Go, Rambo!
- Green, black, red, green.
- Go, Jong Kook.
- Blue.
- Blue!
(He did it this time.)
Rambo.
- You were swaying as well.
- Rambo.
You were also moving side to side.
I, Rambo...
My heart started pounding
near the end.
I, Rambo, was a nervous wreck.
- Rambo...
- That was hilarious.
Good job.
- She's got this.
- Green, blue, red,
- black, green, black.
- She'll make it.
Red, blue, black!
Nicely done.
We should be happy too, right?
Stepping to the rhythm is vital.
- Right.
- It's necessary.
I can see that this is needed.
It helps the brain function.
I'm amazed.
Although it took you some time,
you will now get to enter
the escape room.
While the others head inside,
the two of you
will be given a mission.
There are different levels
of quizzes inside.
What they'll be solving
depends on you two.
- Then...
- Let's do this.
Of course. Do well outside, okay?
- We'll get going.
- See you.
- What about us?
- Good luck.
You need to make it easier
for us in there.
Don't worry.
We'll have a mission to solve too.
Ask if you need any help.
- You're playing a big role too.
- Okay.
Isn't it weird
how I'm going in there?
Just because of some random test...
- Get going.
- This makes no sense.
Good luck.
(The geniuses
enter the escape room.)
That...
(Time left: 05:09:55)
(This is the escape room.)
It's quite spacious.
- What's this?
- Spacious, isn't it?
(The escape room
that the geniuses just entered)
What is this place?
- What's this?
- Are these the levels?
(3 quiz tables)
(Firmly locked 3 locks)
Choose One or the Other.
The next one is Arrange in Order.
(Celebrity Keyword)
- They unlock the locks.
- Right.
- There's a lot.
- This is for the third lock.
Welcome to the escape room...
that can only be accessed...
- by geniuses.
- Good.
The three locks behind you...
only open to
the correct four-digit combination.
It is one number per question.
That's a total of 12 questions.
That's what I said.
There are 12 questions.
Each lock has questions
of a different category...
that have different levels
of difficulty.
If the dunces
complete their mission,
the level of difficulty
will be lowered.
Choose the lock
and the place of the number.
We can always guess...
- the last digit, right?
- Right.
- There's no need to know them all.
- Just the first three.
- We can always guess.
- Let's figure three out first.
(They agree to guess
the last digit.)
The amount of time
you'll be given...
will always be five minutes.
The siren will go off
when you have 30 seconds left.
- I...
- One is the Celebrity Keyword.
- Arrange in Order.
- How about Arrange in Order?
There's also
Choose One or the Other.
Choose One or the Other
sounds difficult.
(They will only get 5 minutes
in the escape room each time.)
- Which should we try first?
- Arrange in Order?
- Arrange in Order.
- For the first one.
- We have to do it anyway.
- Let's do this.
Arrange them in chronological order.
- This is easy.
- It's an easy one.
- Here.
- It's like this.
All right.
Wait, it's not easy at all.
- It's not easy.
- I only know Suk Jin's birthdate.
Let's see.
That goes here.
- 1966.
- Right, 1966.
- Saemaeul Movement?
- Well...
This is a tough one.
Was it in the late 60s?
When did Patti Kim make her debut?
- Didn't she debut at a young age?
- Right.
Wouldn't it have been
after Suk Jin's birth?
This probably goes here.
We're all in the back...
We're all in the back
and not contributing.
- Then...
- What's this?
What does this even mean?
The five-year
economic development plan?
A five-year...
economic development plan
was announced.
Wouldn't it have been after...
Suk Jin's birth?
Just go out there
and find us some clues.
Like this.
Don't you think this happened first?
- What?
- But...
No way. That makes no sense.
Let's just give it a try.
What about this then?
Like this.
Was the Saemaeul Movement
in the 60s?
- Like this.
- I think that goes second too.
- Wait.
- This goes second?
Wouldn't this...
Don't just copy what they're saying.
(I'm warning you.)
- Try this.
- Is Suk Jin...
- that old?
- Have you reached a decision?
Was Suk Jin born
before the Saemaeul Movement?
This is it. I'm sure of it.
This order...
(This order...)
is incorrect.
- Really?
- The correct order is like so.
Patti Kim's debut.
- What?
- The Chang Myon administration.
Suk Jin's birth and
Saemaeul Movement.
What we had...
Was that the correct order?
- Patti Kim.
- When did she make her debut?
- In 1958.
- Really?
Suk Jin was really born
before the Saemaeul Movement.
- Patti Kim...
- When did she make her debut?
Your mission...
is to bounce the ping-pong ball...
on the boxes
all the way down to the cup.
It's too difficult though.
It's not easy.
Can we begin the game?
I'll give it a try.
Haha, go for it.
(Them succeeding will lead to
easier questions.)
How is this even possible?
- Are you out to get us?
- This is super hard.
Why are you torturing us?
- How about the same category?
- Sounds good.
Heo Jun, Jeong Yak Yong,
Jang Yeong Sil, Yi Hwang.
Place their portraits in that order.
Yi Hwang. Okay, got it.
(Heo Jun, Jeong Yak Yong,
Jang Yeong Sil, Yi Hwang)
(Place their portraits
in that order.)
- I'm clueless.
- He's Yi Hwang.
- That's right.
Next...
- We're all standing in the back.
- Is he Heo Jun?
None of us are willing
to contribute.
Where's actor Jeon Gwang Ryeol?
I'm confused between
Jang Yeong Sil and...
I wonder who this is.
Isn't he Jang Yeong Sil?
He's Jeong Yak Yong for sure.
His portrait is on display
at Namyangju.
- What?
- Really?
Yes, because he rests there.
- Like this.
Good. I think it's right.
This order...
(This order...)
- It's correct.
- Nice!
I told you it was right.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Why weren't you contributing?
- I knew the answer.
- Good job.
- They didn't need my help.
Here's the first digit...
to the second lock.
Please choose the next question.
The second digit
in Arrange in Order.
Countries.
- We've got this.
- Oh, no.
- This...
- Of course.
- Germany.
- That's Germany.
I only know
since I enjoy soccer games.
- The Netherlands.
- That's Germany.
I only know
since I enjoy soccer games.
- This is the Netherlands.
- Isn't it Argentina?
This is the Netherlands.
- This is the Russian flag.
- And this is the Hungarian flag.
- This is it.
- Right. This is it.
- This order...
- This is it.
- is correct.
- Okay.
I'll give you the second digit...
of the second lock.
(They earned the 2nd digit
of the 2nd lock.)
- Please select your next quiz.
- Okay.
- Let's choose the 3rd digit.
- We should pick the 3rd digit.
- We should choose that.
- Let's pick the third digit.
(Right then!)
You have only 30 seconds
to use the escape room.
We have only 30 seconds?
This one's the leopard. Wait, no.
That's not it.
- Oh, gosh.
- I have no idea.
They all look the same.
(List them in this order.
Leopard, cheetah, jaguar, puma)
- Gosh, this is...
- This is a cheetah.
This is a cheetah?
- This is a jaguar.
- Isn't this a puma?
- Jae Suk, this is...
- This is a puma.
Wait, this is a puma.
- This is...
- This is a cheetah.
Yes, it's a cheetah. Hang on.
- This is a leopard.
- This is a jaguar.
- This is a jaguar. We got it.
- Let's try it then.
- I think this is correct.
- Jaguars are rather cute.
- Their heads are big.
- This is a cheetah for sure.
- No, it's not.
- Isn't this a leopard?
- No, no.
- Jaguars' heads are big.
This order...
(Leopard, cheetah, jaguar, puma)
- is not correct.
- It's not?
- This is wrong?
- This is the answer.
- This is a jaguar?
But jaguars are supposed to be cute.
So this is how jaguars look?
This was too hard.
(They failed to find the third digit
and finished their time...)
(in the escape room.)
Let's go now.
- That was too hard. What was that?
- That was too hard.
That was too hard.
- We didn't get to say a word there.
- Hey.
So Min and I couldn't do anything
in there.
Try it. It doesn't bounce.
They should give us a game
we could play.
It doesn't bounce.
- You couldn't do this?
- It doesn't work.
I want to play something like this.
It's time for the second mission.
- The second mission...
- Yes.
is a general knowledge test.
The person trying for the answer
should put paint on their fingers.
That thing will spin.
You need to spin seven times
behind the starting line.
Then you'll need to pick a country
and guess its capital city.
Oh, the capital city?
- It'd be hard to pick a country.
- I'm not good with capital cities.
It's already hard to pick a country,
but we have to guess its capital?
Choose a color for yourself,
- and put them on your fingers.
- Okay.
- Then you can go for it.
- Let's do this.
Where is Russia's capital city?
- What?
- What's the capital city of Russia?
- Russia?
- Yes.
Don't stall for time.
It's Luxembourg.
- The capital city of Australia...
- Russia...
is Sydney, right?
- No, it's Melbourne.
- Melbourne?
- What about Russia?
- Gosh, these guys...
- No, no. We need to let them pick.
- Pick the biggest country.
- You need to pick China.
- Do you want to go first, Ji Hyo?
- Let's go, Ji Hyo!
- You can do it!
Spin seven times,
and we'll count to three.
- Ready, go.
- Spin.
- 1.
- 2.
She's spinning slowly.
- Three.
- It's okay to spin slowly.
- 4.
I think I'm spinning the wrong way.
- Five.
- Is there a time limit?
- Six.
- I don't think she can walk.
- You need to spin faster than that.
- Seven.
- That's seven. Go.
- Go.
(She needs to pick a country
on the map within 3 seconds.)
- Go.
- Hurry, Ji Hyo.
2, 1.
(She needs to pick a country
on the map within 3 seconds.)
2, 1.
Which country is it?
She did pick one.
- Which country is it?
- Which country? She did pick one.
It's in Asia. It's near Korea.
- She did pick one.
- You need to stop it.
It's the Philippines.
- She picked the Philippines.
- It's not bad.
- You can do it.
- Okay!
- Three...
- You can do it.
- Okay!
- Three...
- Manila!
- That's correct.
(Manila is correct.)
- Great job.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
- She picked the Philippines.
- That was great, Ji Hyo.
- Of course she knows.
- How did she know?
You're studying these days,
aren't you?
You're dizzy, right?
They say it's never too late
to learn things.
Ji Hyo is on fire these days.
I think Ji Hyo is getting tutored
these days.
- Ji Hyo became...
- Are you getting tutored?
- really smart.
- It was a difficult one.
- Suk Jin, you're up next.
- It's your turn, Suk Jin.
He can't stand being dizzy though.
- I should endure it.
- Okay.
Here he goes.
- One.
- Faster, faster!
- Two.
- My gosh, Suk Jin.
- Three.
- Stoop down more!
- Four.
- Oh, no. I'm in trouble.
- Five.
- Six.
- I'm in trouble.
- Let's go.
- Seven.
- 3, 2...
- Oh, gosh!
- One.
- Pick a country!
- It's over.
- My gosh.
(His steps seem unstable already.)
(He couldn't even pick a country.)
- Come on.
- Seriously?
You should've picked
an ocean at least.
- An ocean!
- Suk Jin.
- Anyone could tell...
- Seriously.
he was trying to get more airtime.
Aren't I right?
- You're so greedy.
- We've been too generous.
- Suk Jin!
- No.
- We've been too generous.
You should know when to stop.
I was really dizzy.
- Suk Jin.
- I was...
- That was lousy.
- That was a little too much.
I can guarantee you'll be dizzy too.
You try it.
- Suk Jin.
- You won't be able to pick one.
- You were too greedy.
- You can't pick one either!
You can't take up airtime like this.
That's not what I was after.
Go ahead and try it yourself.
- His steps were too fake.
- Seriously.
- He looked awkward.
- He did it like this.
He was walking toward
the map like this.
- The way he walked...
- I swear...
- that I didn't fake any of it.
- The way he walked...
- It's because...
- You should try it.
You know walking like this
on a variety show...
That's considered cheating.
- You try it.
- I understand how you must've felt.
You know what? I'll give it a try.
He tried to make us laugh
with fake moves.
He was greedy to get more airtime.
This isn't right, Suk Jin.
- But the thing is...
- What is it?
You can't fake things
to get more airtime.
- Don't do that.
- That's not right.
- It's because I'm cold.
Okay, fine.
This isn't fake, is it?
Let's not make it unnatural.
People hate fake things these days.
Ready, go.
- He doesn't get dizzy.
- One.
Two.
- 3, 4.
- People don't like fake things.
- Five.
- Six.
- Make us laugh genuinely.
- Seven.
- Let's go.
- That's good.
- Two...
(He takes genuine steps
to make them laugh genuinely.)
2, 1.
- That's good!
- Nice!
- Which country is it?
- China!
Let's stop it.
- It might not be China.
- I don't think it is.
I think it's Mongolia.
No, the red color covers China.
- Isn't it Kazakhstan?
- No, it's not.
- It is China!
The land that got the pain the most.
- It's China.
1, 2, 3.
- Beijing!
- Okay!
- Good job.
- Isn't this too fake?
- No, it's not? Why?
- Isn't this fake?
- That doesn't look like snot.
- What's wrong with you?
You must've spun so fast
to get snot like that.
Could you turn down
the air conditioner?
It's so cold.
- Turn down the air conditioner?
- Yes.
- We're going again?
- For extra time,
those who haven't tried it
could give it a go.
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Extra time?
- Yes.
- What are we doing again?
- For extra time...
(Approaching)
(Laughing)
Why are we making things unnatural?
(He prefers to
make people laugh genuinely.)
- You said you won't do it.
- This is crazy.
Guys, work harder!
- Let's do this!
- Just like me!
Work hard until your nose bleeds.
- Let's do this!
- Hey.
- How are we supposed to...
You should take care
of your health, So Min.
We're all doing this
because of Suk Jin.
I'm so tired.
- Let me see, Haha.
- Oh, my.
- Aren't you tired?
- I am.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Let's do this!
Next is Kwang Soo.
If you succeed,
you'll get extra time.
(If he succeeds, they'll get
more time to use the escape room.)
- Ready.
- Let's see how he does it.
Set, go.
- One.
- Come on.
- 2, 3.
- 4.
- 5, 6.
Seven. You can go now.
I'm so dizzy!
- I'm so dizzy!
- You should still go for it.
- 5, 6.
- Come on.
(Rubbing)
- Seven. You can go now.
- I'm so dizzy!
(He has paint all over his face.)
His face turned yellow.
- He couldn't even pick a country.
- No, no.
- His face turned yellow.
- I did pick a country!
- He did pick one.
- I'm so dizzy!
- You ran out of time.
- Hey.
Your face turned yellow.
My face is yellow?
Everyone is going overboard
because of Suk Jin.
- What's this?
- You should all act natural.
- It's so awkward.
- What's wrong with you?
You should've acted naturally.
Why did you put paint on your face?
Wipe your nosebleed
before saying anything.
You succeeded to enter
the escape room.
- We'll give you a chance to enter.
- Okay!
Please try a little harder.
- You should do better here.
- I'm doing my best!
The mission is difficult
inside the escape room too.
You should succeed here
so it'd get easier for us.
Can you bounce the ball
three times and make it go in?
- Just do it, you punk!
- It's difficult.
If you're not smart,
then use your body!
(He can't refute that.)
Let's go inside the escape room.
We can do this, Suk Jin.
- Let's do this!
- Let's do our best.
Let's go, dunces!
Are you solving questions in there?
My gosh.
- We should pick that one.
- So, the rules...
- This is driving me crazy.
- Gosh, this isn't fun.
- Let's try the third digit.
- Let's try this then.
- Okay, but it's too hard.
- It's my turn again?
- It's my turn.
- Let's give it a try.
We should list them in the order
of the event that occurred first.
- The launching of the Euro.
- They're economic events.
- It's difficult.
- The September 11 attacks.
- This isn't it.
- That happened in 2001.
- September 11 attacks came later.
- The IMF crisis.
- That happened in 1998.
- Gaeseong Industrial Complex?
- The groundbreaking ceremony...
of Gaeseong Industrial Complex?
- I have no idea about this.
- This...
Gaeseong Industrial Complex?
What's the launching of "payment"?
- The Euro.
- The currency of the EU.
He thought it meant "payment".
- It's the Euro, not "payment".
- It's the Euro.
- I read it wrong.
- I'm so sorry.
I read it wrong
because it was too far.
We thought the Euro was...
- The launching of the Euro?
- Hold on.
I went to Europe to shoot a show
in 2002.
I remember using the Euro.
Isn't the construction of Gaeseong
Industrial Complex before that?
Maybe it's earlier than we thought.
Let's put them in this order then.
Se Chan has been saying something,
but you're all ignoring him?
Let's put them in this order.
The launching of the Euro,
The September 11 attacks...
I think Gaeseong Industrial Complex
was built before that.
The IMF crisis,
the launching of the Euro,
- The September 11 attacks...
- Hold on. I have no idea.
This order...
- is correct.
- It's correct!
- What did I tell you?
- I was right. Go away.
- He's so smart.
(IMF crisis, launching of the Euro,
September 11, Gaeseong Complex)
I'll give you the 3rd digit
of the 2nd lock.
It's zero.
It's done.
You should try the last digit.
Try it.
We need to know the rest of them.
She got it. It's open.
(They unlocked the second lock.)
It's 5202.
For the third lock,
you'll play
a celebrity keyword quiz.
Listen to the keyword,
and all of you need to say...
different answers.
All six of us?
I don't think we can do it.
- We'll take turns in this order?
- Let's do it.
It must be something like guessing
the works Kwang Soo was in.
I think that'd be
the most difficult one.
- It's the most difficult one.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- I'm not that bad.
Excuse me, Payment. Please get out.
This isn't a free show.
And why did you put paint
on your face?
Did you think it'd be funny?
Wait. Didn't you draw a nosebleed?
You drew a nosebleed
with the red paint.
- Hurry.
- This is upsetting, you know!
- Let's give it a try.
- We need to focus here!
Let's give it a try.
Is it difficult?
Maybe they got something
on the outside.
I think so.
I mean...
- Isn't there something else?
- We should keep trying.
Let's do this.
Jae Suk did it earlier.
- I think this is easier.
- It's difficult, Suk Jin.
So we have to succeed five times
in a row, right?
- Let's keep going. What's next?
- Let's play the next one.
- Let's do it again.
- Oh, this is how it's played?
- I think we can do it.
- Okay, let's do it.
Name a celebrity
whose surname is Song.
- 1, 2...
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Il Kook.
- Song Hae.
- Song Hye Kyo.
- Song Eun I.
- Song Seung Heon.
- Okay!
That was great.
- We got it.
- Good job.
We know everything about showbiz.
Yes, we do.
I'll give you the 1st digit
of the 3rd lock.
- We don't have much time left.
- Let's hurry.
- We can play one more time.
- Hurry up and give it to us.
- Hurry!
Name a song that has "summer"
in its title.
- "Summer Please".
- I was going to say that!
- "Summer Story".
- Oh, no!
(Summer, ice)
(We should have
iced coffee in summer)
iced coffee in summer?)
- That's a song in a commercial.
- Come on!
- Why not?
- It's a song for Maxim.
- It's Maxim's song.
- Why would you sing that song?
- It has "summer" in it!
- The title has to have "summer".
- That was so unnatural.
- Why not?
- It has "summer" in it!
- That was funny, Ji Hyo.
We were supposed to sing a song
with "summer" in its title.
(An exciting...)
(summer song)
This doesn't work.
- Maxim iced coffee.
- You still haven't succeeded it?
- We did up to 1, but doing 3 is...
- What were you doing?
You have a separate mission,
don't you?
- You do, don't you?
- What do you mean?
- You have another mission, no?
- No, we don't.
- You did one?
- Haha.
You have another mission, don't you?
- It's written there.
- You're doing another mission, no?
- What do you mean?
- Don't you have another mission?
- We're only doing this.
- Oh, really?
We've been playing this only.
(We've been playing this only.)
- Everyone.
- This doesn't work.
(Se Chan finds
the dunces suspicious.)
Now, you'll play the third mission.
This time, it's One Heart, One Body.
You'll hear a proverb...
and make a gesture
you're reminded of.
Everyone needs to
make the same gesture.
I think this is doable.
It's a proverb, not a word,
so making the same gesture
is extremely hard.
Therefore, you'll roll dice
before the game begins...
and only the given number of people
need to make the gesture.
Okay, it sounds doable.
There are 3 to 8 dots on the dice.
The number on the dice
determines the number of people...
- that need to make the gesture.
- It's doable.
Who'll roll the dice?
Ji Hyo, you should do it.
- You're the lucky one.
- She's lucky.
- Lucky girl!
- Let's do this!
The lower the number, the better.
It'd be best to get three.
1, 2...
- Three!
- Throw it in a funny way.
What was that?
- It went over the wall.
- Hey!
(The prankster couldn't help
but pull a prank.)
(An out-of-the-set homerun)
(The staff members were
on standby in the escape room.)
(They were attacked
by the dice out of nowhere.)
(Who did this?)
(They're running out of time,
but the prankster had to kick it.)
- Come here.
- What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
Why don't you listen to me?
- What's wrong with you?
- I mean...
- It fell right here.
- Why does he keep being playful?
It fell right in front of me.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why is he in such good condition?
I thought it'd fall inside.
He wanted to make it fun.
Don't touch it! You're unlucky!
- Don't touch it!
- Okay, okay.
He's really excited.
- He's excited every day.
- I'll throw it.
Throw it gently.
- There you go.
- Don't kick it.
- Hey!
- Come on.
(It went out to the other side
of the set this time.)
- Gosh, they're not in a good mood.
- Suk Jin.
- This isn't fun at all.
- Suk Jin...
- You're ruining the mood.
- Jae Suk did it already.
I'm quitting.
- I quit. I'm quitting.
- Jong Kook.
- Suk Jin, you ruined the mood.
- That's not it.
- Apologize to Bo Pil.
- I will, but...
- Apologize now.
- I'm sorry, but...
- What's this?
- Apologize to Chan Hee too.
You can just edit it out
if it's not fun.
But if you edit it nicely,
it could be fun.
Chan Hee would've dropped
his camera in the old days.
Chan Hee likes me a lot.
And I like him too.
- It's gone.
- See? He dropped his camera.
(He decided that it's not fun enough
to air.)
- Chan Hee!
- He dropped his camera.
- You see?
- Of course.
- Ji Hyo.
- In the old days...
- I'll throw it now.
- Let's go!
You must get three.
- The lower the number, the better.
- That's right!
- Ji Hyo.
- Suk Jin,
if you stick your foot out,
I'm going to kick it.
Okay, okay.
But when that thing is in the air,
you can't help but kick it.
I get why he kicked it.
- Honestly, I want to kick it too.
- You should kick it now.
But when that thing is in the air,
- you can't help but kick it.
- Let's make a promise.
- Hold back yourself.
- I get why he kicked it.
- I want to kick it too.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Right? I want to kick it too.
- You should stand here.
- I want to kick it too.
Stay here. This is the perfect spot.
- I won't kick it.
- I want try kicking it.
- You should hold yourself.
- I'm going to kill you if you do.
I didn't want to kick it at all.
But when it comes
right in front of you...
(Boiling with anger)
He's upset.
Ji Hyo, can you throw it over here?
- Don't do it.
- We never know.
- All right, let's go.
- Rambo is really upset.
- Hold it back.
- We never know.
- Let's see.
- Hold it back, Kwang Soo.
Hold it back. Hold it back.
- All right.
- Hold it back, Kwang Soo.
- Oh, no.
- You'll want to kick it.
- Everyone is...
- Hold it back even if you want to.
Throw it high.
(The die is cast.)
- He missed it.
What's the number?
(The counterattack
of the short legs)
(What's the number
on the dice that Haha kicked?)
We're going to use the number
you got.
It's 8! Gosh, it's 8!
(Oh, no. I'm dead.)
- Kwang Soo, why...
- Why did you get eight?
You punk.
How dare you kick the dice
when you're unlucky?
- How did we get eight?
- It's okay. We can make it.
- What are we getting?
- It's okay.
It's okay as long as
we make the same gesture.
- It'll be hard.
- We'll make the same gesture.
When I count to three
after saying a proverb,
make a gesture...
- that describes this proverb.
- Okay.
Let's focus on using our upper body.
And let's base it on the last word.
All right.
Please hold after making a gesture.
Eight of you need to make
the same gesture...
for the first proverb.
A mad dog sees everything as a club.
- Focus on using our upper body.
- 1, 2, 3.
(They all made the same gesture
for "club" using their upper body.)
- Let's base it on the last word.
- 1, 2, 3.
(They made a gesture
for the last word, "club".)
(A mad dog
sees everything as a club.)
(Four of them made the same gesture.
Will they succeed?)
(Here are two mad dogs.)
(We have two more here.)
- Darn it. Who's holding a club?
- A club.
- You should've done the mad dog.
- It's better to use "dog".
- She said focus on the last word.
- Yes, we decided to do that.
- You should've done the mad dog.
- The last word is "club".
- It's "club". It's the last word.
- We decided on using the last word.
- The last word.
- The last word?
The last word!
Jae Suk, how come a mad dog
looks so gentle?
That's why it's mad.
- Right.
- Did you see his gesture?
Make sure to do the gesture
for the last word.
- The last word?
- Do the gesture for the last word.
You should throw it.
- Okay.
- Don't you kick it.
I shouldn't be looking.
(I shouldn't be looking.)
- I really want to kick it though.
- Me too.
Don't kick it.
(Will they be adults
and hold themselves back?)
(The die is cast.)
(He couldn't hold it back
and kicks it hard.)
All right. Let's just use that.
It didn't go out!
No, no. Wait.
What's the number?
- It's 4!
Only four of us
need to make the same gesture.
Okay. We got this.
(If they succeed this time,
they can enter the escape room.)
- Just 4 of us need to get it.
- Just 4?
Once startled by a turtle,
you'll also be startled...
- by a cauldron lid.
- 1, 2, 3.
Wrong!
- We need to do the cauldron lid.
- The cauldron lid.
You're supposed
to lift the cauldron lid.
(2 of them did the "startled" part.)
(4 of them did
whatever they wanted.)
(Doing different gestures)
(They've been together for 11 years,
but they have zero teamwork.)
- The cauldron lid.
- I mean...
- I did the "startled" part.
- The cauldron lid.
- I made a gesture for the lid.
- This is a cauldron lid.
- What's that?
- That's just a cauldron, you punk.
That's just a cauldron!
Don't you grill pork belly
on the cauldron lid?
Hang on. Jae Suk,
what are you describing?
- What's that?
- The "startled" part.
- That's too cute though.
- Why does he keep acting cute?
You made this gesture
for dog earlier.
What did you do, Ji Hyo?
The turtle.
- Hey, that's...
- That's not a turtle.
- How is that a turtle?
- You call that a turtle?
Let's just not decide which word
to use beforehand.
- Let's not decide anything.
- We need to do it spontaneously.
- Just do it spontaneously!
- Okay?
- Let's not decide anything.
- Just do what comes to your mind.
- So Min, you should throw it.
- Okay.
Don't kick it.
- But I want to kick it.
- If you kick it...
- Just head it.
- I want to kick it so bad.
- Of course you want to kick it.
We got it.
Let's see. Let it be three.
It's still rolling?
Seven.
You see? That's how she is.
He said, "That's how she is."
- But this time...
- She's never lucky.
- It could be easy this time.
- Really?
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- Guys, do it spontaneously.
- Let's do whatever comes to mind.
There are those who run
and those who fly above them.
(There are those who run
and those who fly above them.)
(More than 7 people
need to make the same gesture.)
1, 2, 3.
- We got it!
- We got it.
We got it.
(They all seem to be doing
the same gesture.)
(Will they succeed this time?)
All of us are flying.
You succeeded.
We did it.
We succeeded
when we didn't plan ahead.
- Yes!
- We did it.
- Let's go.
- Okay, okay.
We did it.
Since the show is Running Man,
I thought of doing a running motion.
- He said it might be easy.
- That's right.
We could have done a running motion.
Now, you will enter
the third escape room.
- We will be back.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Give us the question.
- This is hard.
- Give us the question.
Let's begin.
Name a zombie movie each.
- This is hard.
- "Dawn Of The Dead".
"Train to Busan".
"Haeundae".
- "Haeundae"?
- You fixated on Busan.
Wasn't "Haeundae"...
- a zombie movie?
- It's a movie about a tsunami.
Wasn't there a single zombie?
There is "The King".
- There is "Kingdom".
- "Kingdom".
It's "Kingdom".
- Oh, you are right.
- It's "Kingdom".
- We should hurry up.
- I think...
we should choose the order wisely.
Hey, this is...
This is impossible.
It's so hard.
This is ridiculous.
Try it. Keep trying.
(He bounces the ball halfheartedly.)
How are we supposed to get three?
(His loud voice sounds unnatural.)
They must have
a secret mission, right?
- I bet they do.
- Right?
Jae Suk, I asked Suk Jin...
if he was up to something.
- He trembled.
- Seriously.
In my opinion, the setup was...
- too fake.
- That's right.
- Do you know why?
- It was so messy.
Two people wouldn't have used
that many ping pong balls.
They were all over the floor.
I asked Haha too.
He behaved suspiciously.
Things are going
too smoothly, right?
- That's right.
- For us anyway.
1, 2...
This is impossible.
(They have never succeeded
the mission.)
We have to make sure
we don't succeed.
Let's do another mission.
I am worried.
You should give us
a mission we can do.
(Why do they need to make sure
they don't succeed?)
(Why are they pointing?)
Can't you throw better, Suk Jin?
- Come on.
- Number two.
(He checks the room number
and goes straight to the laptop.)
I need to solve this.
(He suddenly solves a question.)
(The secret behind Empty Head Land)
(The members were locked in a room.)
(The 6 geniuses succeed in escaping
1 at a time.)
How many people remain?
(The 2 of them became dunces.)
(The 6 geniuses were happy
to hear about the hidden rule.)
(The dunces got a hidden rule
as well.)
(Now, the two of you will receive
a hidden rule.)
(Since the other 6 members
are watching through a monitor,)
(continue to act like
you are solving questions.)
(Since the geniuses were watching,)
(they had to receive
the rule in secret.)
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
It's a match
between 6 geniuses and 2 dunces.
The team that succeeds
to escape first will win...
and the team that fails
to escape will receive a penalty.
The 6 geniuses already know
that it's a 2-on-6 match,
but they will try to fool
the 2 dunces with fake rules.
Thus, you need to pretend...
to believe the fake rules.
Today, all of you are a team.
(The received the fake rule
about all members being a team.)
(The 2 dunces pretended
to believe it.)
(The dunces were doing the tricking,
not the geniuses.)
You can escape Empty Head Land
only through the real exit.
The real exit is hidden
behind the dresser in the main room.
(The real exit is here!)
(The real exit)
However, the six geniuses believe
the exit is in the escape room.
They mistakenly think
they will win...
if they open the fake exit
in the escape room.
(The 6 geniuses are trying to open
the fake exit!)
Thus,
while the six geniuses are
in the escape room,
you must open the real exit
and escape first.
Got it?
- It's here.
(The 2 dunces checked
the location of the real exit.)
The password has
eight digits, right?
- Eight digits.
- What do we have now?
(The password has 8 digits.)
The password of the real exit
has eight digits.
You can get the digits
by entering the eight rooms...
and solving questions.
(Enter the 8 rooms and type in
"Empty Head" for the quiz.)
For goodness' sake.
(That's why Suk Jin tried
to solve the question!)
(Each room gives a digit
from the 8-digit password.)
Keep throwing the balls.
I will solve the questions.
(Only Suk Jin gets to the quizzes
to avoid suspicions.)
(Suk Jin went into Room 4.)
(He plans to get the 4th digit.)
This is the answer, right?
(Mottled)
(It's correct!)
(The 4th digit of the password
is 2.)
(They gained the 4th digit, 2.)
(During the second escape room...)
Is this the answer? I think it is.
(He entered Room 3...)
(and gained the 3rd digit.)
It's correct.
Did you hear me? The 4th digit is 2.
The 4th digit, 2.
Okay.
But once the six geniuses open
the fake exit,
they will learn about
the real exit...
and the hidden rule.
Hurry up and escape before that.
(This is the fake exit.)
This is hard.
(To keep the difficulty level up,
they failed the mission on purpose.)
I don't know what,
but they have a secret.
- They have a secret.
- We should get out soon.
- This is hard.
- Hurry up.
Here is the password.
- Hey.
- The third one.
It was nine, right?
The third one.
- Hey, hey.
- What?
I got another one right.
(They already have
3 out of 8 digits.)
- How many seconds?
- Do we have more time?
We don't have more time, right?
(The escape room will end
in 30 seconds.)
How many digits do you know?
I know three. They are coming out.
- Keep going.
- They are coming out.
- What are you doing?
- One.
(The dunces pretend to do
the mission.)
How are we supposed to do this?
(Something is strange.)
- They are suspicious, right?
- Yes, they are.
This is impossible.
How are we supposed to get three?
They are really suspicious.
I didn't hear the ball bounce.
- The mission is too shabby.
- I know. It's strange.
It's too shabby.
That's what I am saying.
- You and Haha are suspicious.
- What's up with you guys?
I am serious.
- This is the mission.
- What does it involve.?
What are you guys doing in there?
We are trying...
- to open the exit.
- Why are there so many?
We played around earlier.
- Is that so?
- That's right.
They are really suspicious.
- Something is strange.
- Why is there water?
You are really strange.
Why are you acting?
(He laughs
because he is taken aback.)
- Seriously.
- No, no.
- Something is strange.
- Do you know what he did?
"Something is strange."
(Serious)
- But...
- It sounded like...
he was saying that for no reason.
But something really is strange.
- What's strange?
What are you doing in there?
- We are playing a game.
- You know that.
Couldn't you hear us?
- Couldn't you hear us?
- I could hear you.
- I am sure you heard everything.
- This is a group mission.
- You have a secret mission, right?
- Can't we switch once?
- You have our own mission.
What mission is it?
It's to help you.
Then why aren't you doing it?
- Try it.
- We had to choose.
- Try it. Try it.
- Try it then.
Try it.
How are we supposed to get three?
Keep trying. All right. Okay.
- Why are you getting angry?
- It's not like that.
- We are trying.
- We are in this together.
- You should know our pain.
- We are a team.
Unless you lower
the difficulty level,
we won't be able to succeed.
- The difficulty level goes up.
- Jong Kook.
- We are getting better.
- He is acting.
- We got two the last time.
- I can tell...
- It's hard.
- if you are lying or not.
- How?
(He uses a new type
of lie detector.)
What are you doing?
Aren't you just making fun of him?
You are just making fun of him.
Is he lying or not?
- I am so annoyed.
- You are just making fun of him.
Suk Jin was waiting patiently too.
Let's go.
Suk Jin,
your palms are really sweaty.
- He is hiding something.
- We need to hurry up.
Let's hurry up.
It's because I am nervous.
Why are you so nervous?
I am usually good at this.
Let's go.
Now comes the seventh test.
It's the strength test.
With one knee bent,
hold the other ankle...
and stand up without using the hands
to succeed.
- Anyone can do it.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Stand up.
- I can't stand up.
- Can't you do it?
- How did he do it?
- It's impossible.
- You can do it.
(I bet I can do it.)
How did he do it?
What am I going to do?
Hold on. I got a cramp in my foot.
- What's wrong?
- I got a cramp in my foot.
- Why does that happen so often?
- What's wrong with you?
Why don't you become a cheerleader?
Why is your foot so hot?
(He suggests that she changes
her position.)
I am sorry.
Thank you.
I was so surprised
that I got a cramp in my foot.
- Like this?
- Like that?
- You succeeded right away.
How many people need to do it?
You succeed if four people do it.
- Ji Hyo, try it.
- She would be good at it.
All of us would be good at it.
- Two,
- Ji Hyo always succeeds calmly.
three. For goodness' sake.
(She complains calmly.)
It's a game.
It's okay even if you fail.
You don't need to be
so disappointed.
Like this?
- Don't put your hand on the knee.
- Where?
- Hold on.
- Don't do it halfheartedly.
- All right.
- Don't put your hand on the knee.
- So I can't hold anything.
- No.
- I did it.
- Of course.
- I can't do it.
- Let's see who else can do it.
- I did it.
- I knew you could do it.
You passed the seventh test.
- Okay.
- Let's go, let's go.
You can enter the escape room.
(With 22 minutes remaining,
it may be the last escape room.)
They are hiding something, right?
They are hiding something.
- Quiz, quiz.
- Let's choose the quiz.
We will have the quiz from earlier.
(The geniuses continue
to suspect them.)
We don't even need to hide
at this point, right?
They suspect us anyway.
Let's do what we need to do.
I think they are hiding something.
- They definitely are.
- Really?
I think they are up to something.
That's the vibe.
They are too awkward.
And the fact
that they are suspicious of us...
All right. Quiet down.
Once all the clues come out,
you will see
that we lost because you cut me off.
- That's absurd.
- This is why we will lose.
For goodness' sake.
That's absurd.
The mission is too simple.
They have been bouncing
those table tennis balls for hours.
- They are up to something.
- It makes no sense.
- We need to work fast and escape.
- We are missing something,
- so we need to work fast.
- Let's go.
- 5th, 6th, 7th, 8th digits.
We need the 1st, 5th, 6th, 7th,
and 8th digits.
- Let's get the quizzes.
- The quizzes.
(The dunces work on the quizzes
without pretense.)
Each name a movie
Yoo Hai Jin starred in.
Let's begin. 1, 2, 3.
"The Battle: Roar to Victory".
- One...
- "Tazza".
- "Space Sweepers".
- 1, 2...
- "Moss".
- "Luck-Key".
- "The Pirates".
(Each name a movie
Yoo Hai Jin starred in.)
(They acquire the 3rd number
of the 3rd lock.)
- We are done.
- It's here.
Try the numbers.
Choose One or the Other.
(The unlock it.)
It's the last lock.
We need to work fast.
Three members will play
Choose One or the Other.
- Me.
- Jong Kook.
Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, and Jae Suk.
Which is grammatically correct?
(On Monday versus At Monday)
- The first one.
- There you go.
- Good job.
- Jong Kook.
Who was the first person
to invent gunpowder in Korea?
The second one. Okay.
What's the unit for 20 squids?
- The first one.
- Chuk.
- Okay.
- We did it.
- The next one.
The second number.
Give us the question.
- You need 3 members.
- 6.
We need two more numbers.
Hold on.
You know,
I am so happy that I am included
in this trio.
- Let's begin.
- We don't have a choice.
- It means I am one of the smartest.
Let's begin.
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
18 minutes remain.
- This is driving me crazy.
- We are running out of time.
We don't have much time.
We need to escape this time.
(They need at least 3 more numbers.)
We need to escape.
- We need to hurry.
- Number one, Opportunity cost.
- Correct.
- Okay.
- Get the number on the lock.
- What is it? Two?
- 2?
- 6, 2.
Let's keep going.
- We need one more number.
- Choose One or the Other.
We need one more number.
At which country
does the sun rise first?
I know. Number one,
the Republic of Kiribati.
Correct.
It's correct.
Why are you surprised?
Which country had
the first female president?
Number two, Argentina.
- Okay. That's good.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- This is the last one.
(The big chance
falls on Jae Suk's shoulders.)
(Only one question remains
until the last lock.)
(What will be the fate
of the geniuses and dunces?)
From the two...
What's a marketing concept
that draws people's attention...
and secures customers
in the beginning?
(Purple ocean versus Purple cow)
Purple cow.
The answer is...
(If it's correct,
they'll get to open the last lock.)
number two, Purple cow.
- Okay!
- We did it.
You will receive the third number.
It's over.
It's over. It's over.
Let's go.
It's over.
Let's hurry up and escape.
- Done.
- Hurry up.
- Let's go.
- What?
(When they open the door...)
(This is the fake exit.)
(A sign shows them
that it's the fake exit.)
The fake exit.
(The real exit is behind the dresser
in the main room.)
It's behind the dresser
in the main room.
"The real exit is behind the dresser
in the main room."
- The dunces knew this.
- I see.
That's why they were in the rooms.
They are trying to figure out
the password now.
(You can get the digits
by entering the eight rooms...)
(and solving questions.)
This explains
their suspicious behaviors.
That's why they were in the rooms.
"Type in "Empty Head" on the laptop
and solve the questions."
(Type in "Empty Head" on the laptop
and solve the questions.)
- Let's go.
- Do we need to go now?
Hurry up. We need to escape.
We don't have much time.
- I have the answer.
- The quizzes are hard.
Okay.
(It's correct. The 6th digit is 0.)
Hurry up.
(They have four digits.)
The first digit.
(They are leading.)
(The geniuses enter.)
- What are you up to?
- What were you doing?
Okay.
(The dunces got caught
while solving quizzes.)
- It's a quiz.
- Why are you solving a quiz?
What is that?
Are you done?
It's a number game.
(The air turns frigid.)
Gosh, this is... What is this?
What is this?
(Wary)
- What is this?
- You used the chat room!
What is this?
(They finally see
the effort the dunces made.)
You used the chat room.
They were doing this
while we solved the questions.
(They find the real exit
as it said on the sign.)
Jae Suk!
There is a door.
(The geniuses found everything.)
(The dunces become
more pressed for time.)
- Is there a lock?
- There is a lock.
Here.
(They find the real exit
with the 8-digit password.)
There is a lock.
(The geniuses need to figure out
all 8 digits.)
Where should we begin?
They figured it out.
This is what they were doing.
(The numbers the geniuses acquired)
(The numbers the dunces acquired)
(What's a word that was coined
by Thomas More...)
(which means an ideal country
that doesn't exist in real life?)
(Utopia)
Okay.
Is this the answer?
Hurry up, Suk Jin. Hurry up.
This is driving me crazy.
I got it!
Here is the answer.
The fourth number.
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
- 7 minutes remain.
- 7 minutes?
Hurry up, Suk Jin. Hurry up.
- Hold on.
- Hurry up.
(Team Geniuses acquired 4 numbers.)
(Team Dunces have 5 numbers.)
We don't have much time.
Get the question right.
This is driving me crazy.
Other rooms...
Hurry up.
- The board.
- It's a new question.
Is this right, So Min?
Did you get it right?
This is hard.
(After wandering for a short while,
he enters a room.)
(Then he stares at the sign.)
(Then he checks the sign
at the fake exit.)
(This is the fake exit.)
(The real exit is behind the dresser
in the main room.)
"Behind the dresser
in the main room"?
(He walks back out
with a surprised look on his face.)
1, 5, 7, 8.
- 7 minutes remain.
- 1, 5, 7, 8.
- Hey.
- We don't have much time. Hurry up.
What is going on?
It's five, right?
(He checks all the signs
that are scattered in the place.)
Jae Suk, we are going to lose.
(He studies the exit
from different angles.)
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
Three minutes remain.
(Knocking)
Why are you knocking?
What?
You knocked.
(When he knocked,)
(the entire wall opened.)
What?
You knocked.
- What?
(What is going on?)
Did it open when you knocked?
(Everyone is flustered for real.)
- What?
What happened?
You knocked.
(Jae Suk can't even react
because he is flustered.)
(Only Jae Suk figured out
the secret of the race.)
We need to go into the room
and solve some questions.
(There were too many signs
around the place.)
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
Seven minutes remain.
(Jae Suk studied the sign again.)
(This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...)
(only when you're smart.)
(Then he noticed
the underlined part.)
It's underlined.
("Smart" is a homophone
for "Knock" in Korean.)
(A place you can escape from
only when you knock)
(The sentence was repeated
too many times from the opening.)
(A place you can escape from
only when you're smart)
(Jae Suk became suspicious
during the countdown.)
(He knocked on the wall
with uncertainty.)
(There were two ways to escape.)
(You can escape by opening the lock
with the password.)
(But you can also escape
by knocking.)
- Hey!
- What happened?
- I got goosebumps.
- Was it about knocking?
I got goosebumps.
What just happened?
Was it about knocking?
I got goosebumps.
So you could escape
by knocking on the door?
- I got goosebumps.
- Is it over?
But the questions...
Is it over?
- I got goosebumps.
- This is ridiculous.
Did it open because he knocked?
This is ridiculous.
(The dunces were slow-witted too.)
This is Empty Head Land,
a place you can escape from...
only when you're smart.
("Smart" is a homophone
for "Knock" in Korean.)
- We just needed to knock?
- It was "Knock", not "Smart".
It was "Knock", not "Smart"?
I just knocked without any thoughts.
It was pointless to solve
the questions.
It was pointless.
My face suddenly turned red.
I just got ridiculed.
- What is this?
- Team Geniuses with Jae Suk won.
It was about knocking.
(They have a ceremony
at the real exit.)
Is that 3,000 dollars?
- No way.
- Will we really get it?
(The 6 geniuses will get
the prize money and medals.)
Since this morning,
I said at least 20 times...
that you can escape only
if you're smart or if you knock.
I thought it meant "Smart".
(Thanks to Jae Suk,
it didn't end as a quiz match.)
I didn't think it meant "Knock".
So the password
wouldn't have worked?
It would have worked.
That was one way to open the door.
- You could open it by knocking.
- That's right.
Would it have opened
if we knocked during the opening?
- It would have opened.
- He repeated the line many times.
Then the part was underlined
on the signs.
- Really?
- So I thought, "No way."
Since he repeated the line
many times,
I knocked to check.
He is the best
when it comes to tricks.
When I walked over,
he was doing something to the door.
He knocked on the door...
and I thought,
"He is being an idiot."
- Seriously.
- Then the door opened.
"Look at him knocking.
What an idiot!"
But the wall opened up.
I didn't do it with certainty.
You got many questions right.
That's right.
- That's right.
- Good job.
You will receive cash
and a gold medal.
Haha and Suk Jin will receive
the penalty.
Here is the penalty.
Recently, on the web,
Se Chan's Empty Head meme
has become popular.
Make a new Empty Head meme
that will become just as popular.
Empty Head!
Use wigs and makeup
to dress up as fools...
and try the gesture
in many different versions.
Did I become a popular meme?
Gosh, I had no idea.
Gosh, I hope this episode
won't be aired.
This is really upsetting.
(The two fathers are dressing up
like fools.)
I don't want my kids
to watch this episode.
Gosh, I can't make a foolish face.
Stand here and look at the camera.
This is what Se Chan did.
But you can try
many different gestures.
Let's do this separately.
(New Empty Head Candidate 1)
Empty Head.
Go ahead.
You don't know how to play a fool.
I'm not good at this.
You should smile to play a fool.
(New Empty Head Candidate 2)
Empty Head.
Come here.
(The middle-aged empty heads
are trying it together.)
Empty Head.
(They try hard to make a new meme
even though it seems useless.)
Empty Head.
(They try hard to make a new meme
even though it seems useless.)
- It's done.
- My gosh.
(Laughing)
(He bears the shame
and runs the meme factory.)
Empty Head.
(Ha Dong Hoon, a dad of three kids
finally came to terms with himself.)
Empty Head.
(Ha Dong Hoon, a dad of three kids
finally came to terms with himself.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
This is so upsetting. Darn it.
I've worked so hard
to build a smart image.
Hyun Woo’s Dad and Dream's Dad,
thank you so much.
Turn off the TV.
Otherwise, you'll become like me.
(Sleep is...)
(a time just for myself
and for recharging my batteries.)
(I want to meet a man
who respects me.)
(The sleepyhead client, Song Ji Hyo)
(I like to read.)
(And I listen to music a lot.)
(Is there anyone who will enjoy...)
(those things with me?)
(The client with many hobbies,
Jeon So Min)
The two clients are
not easy to deal with.
(The CEOs are here
to deal with the picky clients.)
(CEO of Married Corporation,
Lee Yong Jin)
(CEO of Single Dot-com,
Sung Si Kyung)
(They start exploring the clients.)
(A man who feels sorry.)
(I'm sorry)
(The CEOs seem somewhat peculiar.)
(He's my type.)
(Won Bin who belches out moths)
(Won Bin is always good,
no matter what.)
(Lee Kwang Soo
who is potty trained well)
(They don't want to get married.)
My goodness.
(They have comprehensive
ideal types for the clients.)
(Will the clients be able to find
their ideal types?)
All men are the same.
(We Will Find Spring For You)